Can't wait. You got chat open? I don't, I don't have chat. I don't have chat open.
Yeah, cut em! Cut em out! Well, I think, uh, honestly, what, uh, if you want my opinion
on that, uh, I think that 2077, no, I don't think so. Uh, well, I don't have a, I don't
have one of those things under here. No, they can't. Yeah, definitely. Am I still here?
Hello? Can you guys hear me? Oh, there you are. Yeah, just milk. It was nice. Yeah,
yeah. I think, I mean, the whole thing with the game is, uh, it takes place in the future, so
I just want to know what kind of food they eat in the future. You know what I mean? What's
happening to my fucking feed? Hey guys, how you doing? Enable what? I mean, there's no sound.
It was muted the whole fucking time! I gotta do the whole thing again. Just relax. I'm,
I'm definitely hyped about it, of course, but I'm not at, like, co-levels or, or levels of,
of fanboys that I could be, that I am for, say, Bloodlines 2. Like, I'm really excited to
see more Bloodlines 2 stuff. I can't wait. That's great stuff. Devolver Conference,
I'm super hyped about that, but, like, as far as the cyberpunch it, I'm, I'm,
I'm on an even keel for that stuff. Can we swear here? Yeah, yeah. Let's talk about
some of the other stuff that we'll see outside of, uh, third party. Let's talk first party
for a second. Halo Infinite. I don't think, are, Rami, are you a big Halo fan? Where are
you at with the Halo? I'm a big, I'm a Halo fan. I can tell you about it. I, I'm not,
you know, I want to be excited about Halo again. I, I haven't, I haven't been in a
while. Like, ODST and Reach were sort of like where it ended for me. And even though I really
respect Halo 4, um, and, you know, like in, the Halos that have come after have just not,
they haven't mentioned, they haven't managed to capture that, that feeling that I had with
the early Halo 4. Yeah, like a, like a, like a Pokemon. I don't know, because, like,
obviously I've been playing Destiny a lot, and a lot of my love for Halo is in, in Destiny.
But I really hope that Halo finds a new identity, right? A new, like, this is Halo,
instead of trying to kind of be old Halo and kind of be not old Halo. And I just, I'm just,
I want to be excited about Halo. Please give me something to be excited about.
That's really what I want. All right. Does this excite you? Does a,
FPS's 2019 BR, is a Halo BR? No, no, no BR. BR doesn't excite me at all. I'm sorry,
I'm in a hurry to open your butt. Is BR out the window now? Yes, I think so. Do they just
go back to what Halo was? I think BR is just the thing that was like League of Legends.
I don't, I don't, I really don't care too much. I do. I know this. I know this. Let me answer.
I know this. I, I can see it, but I also don't really need it.
Chat's definitely not in the VR world as well. So I think that, uh. It's honestly,
for me, it's, Halo was always about, like, diagonal shootouts, corridors, throwing grenades,
weird physics bugs, like throwing, throwing a warthog over somebody's head with a grenade.
Like, that's Halo for me. Right. I don't really need that 100 people.
Yeah, yeah. What were you going to say before I interrupted you?
You interrupted me! I was going to say something about BR!
Yeah, now I remember. Thank you. So basically, it's an interesting situation because with Halo,
it's kind of like a Borderlands thing, where it's such an established franchise. You're going
to have a fan base, a broad fan base in Halo's situation, where they're going to be
expecting kind of the same thing. They want more of what they already love. So it's a
very fine line to walk when making a subsequent... I'm always blocking the name, though.
Oh, sorry. Where it's kind of like, how much new stuff can you really put in without alienating
that already established, very established Halo's case? Just like the end of the presidential
debate. Just because I'm like 2% of the poll doesn't mean I get to say anything!
We talked about Fable on our pre-show. Are we, do we think that's, I mean,
it was listed in the Mixer game directory, also the Twitch game directory. That's what
everyone's thinking it's going to be here. Is it time for a new Fable? Is it time to put
that game back out there? Fable 3, I think. I mean, is it time for a good new RPG?
Is the bigger question. If you frame it that way, I think so. Yeah. Yeah. Come on, it's
about time. What has been the big RPG? It's been what? The Witcher 3 was the last really
big one that kind of made me feel like, oh, wow, here's a big old fantasy RPG.
No, no, what do you think? I've heard from CRPGs, yeah. It's been kind of...
Well, that type of RPG, right? Yeah. Yeah. All right, I'm done with this.
Stop the stream for a second. Welcome. That was a long... how long have I been streaming?
Like six minutes? I feel like I was streaming for like four hours already. Is that weird?
Oh, you missed the beginning, too. I feel so fucking bad about that. Everyone got silent
and I said like, hey, why do I not have one of those things? And they were like,
somebody coughed. I can't believe I'm so pissed that it was muted. Anyways, hello.
Uh, we're gonna watch the Microsoft E3 conference today. I've made sure to get nice villain hair
for you guys. I know you like the villain hair. I did it specifically. You just finished
what? How tall am I? Why is my hair receding? Let me get back to the fucking cast. This
actually looks kind of... hold on. This is my show now. Right. By the time it gets to E3,
obviously you have a good idea of what it is, but some of the games you're gonna see
today have absurd history stories, like just ridiculous stories of deals, development problems.
It excites me, too. They work so damn hard, you know? They really do. Sorry,
I'm like a huge person. I just want to make sure everyone's aware of this. That's why I need
so much screen real estate. I'm eight and a half feet tall. There's no webcam. These
are four webcams attached in squares. I've edited out the middle. Because Cyberpunk's
already there. So that's kind of... Is it? It is already there. You're right. Yeah. Showing
Halo off or the new console off? Like what's the big thing that everyone's going to be talking
about? If they have the console, it's going to be the console. You think? Like Sony seems
convinced that it's the console because they've been talking about there if they clearly want
to be ahead. So yeah, I guess we'll see. Zeke, what about you? Are you all in on the
indie stuff? Is there any one particular thing here that you're super excited about with the
potential to see as we're about five minutes away, six minutes away? What do you think? Well,
like last time you cut my legs out before I even had a chance, you're like... And you
can't say new IPs because that's always what I'm looking for. That's bullshit. I can't wait
for the new console, by the way. To be shown there, whether they're indie or otherwise. But
I mean, if you're going for like a long shot outside chance, like, man, Skate 4 would be
fucking cool. Oh, well, I would love to not have that released because I hated the third one so
much. That would be pretty sweet. Did you happen to see, I think it was, I didn't, maybe
Rami read this fully, but Adam Sessler works for like a data company when it comes to what
people are excited about. I think Skate 4 was the number one mentioned thing yesterday during
all of like social media and chat across all their different platforms. During the EA,
not conference, the EA play, sorry, I'll stay on brand. Skate 4 was mentioned more than anything
they showed, which is kind of funny. Drinking fermented milk. I look like a dream person.
Do I like waking fucked up right now? Look at this. What's wrong with my face?
I'm having a mental breakdown. That was pretty hard, man, because like basically Anthem...
Look at me. I look like a fucking snake person. Do I look fucking strange or am I Adam? What's
wrong with me? And most of it was we need more content as fast as possible. And then months go
by. And then at the EA play show, they announced that they have been spending the resources
to make a public server to get feedback on the game. And they were like, wow,
are we awesome listening to our people? It's kind of like, yeah. Anyways, that's Anthem. We'll be
talking about that on our recap. And anyway, I think that it's time for me to talk. Do you
think they give any love to the PC side of Xbox here? Do you think they devote any time to...
No, they never do. Joe, they never do, Joe. I had a game list earlier today. I think it's
10 bucks. One of them including, or one of them being Metro Exodus. They're going to come
up with a companion app for Dead Rising 4 that lets you check the map where treasure could be.
I didn't even tweet this.
Well, like, yeah, they're obviously trying to make this one thing. So I don't think we'll see
anything specifically for PC. But oh, yeah, they're going to mention PC like all night.
If we don't have PC on the bingo card, there needs to be PC on the bingo card.
I don't think they're going to.
I mean, to put it in a little bit, you can go right now to the Epic Games store
and you can buy Metro Exodus for $49.99. Or you could give Microsoft $5. And as long
as you beat it in a month. It's just Gamefly. Joe, it's Gamefly. Gamefly was way before its
time. They were the first company that ever thought that was a decent idea and they stole
it from them. What do you think is the opener? Do you open or close with the new console?
Do you open or close with Halo? Oh, you close with the new console. Last thing you do
is you say, and one more thing. And they walk off stage in the trailer please behind you.
It's going to be like in the first few minutes and they're going to start off with a game
that shows off what it can do. It's going to be one image too.
Joe, it's going to be one image. That's it.
Real quick, by the way, apparently it's one dollar during the beta phase to.
Am I allowed to do this?
They are trying to get some early adoption rate going over.
Why? What do you mean?
My seems kind of okay. Anyway, what was the question?
Am I not allowed to be doing this?
In a minute 40, a minute 30.
Probably be the standard montage.
I'm pretending to be on their podcast.
I'm not on their podcast right now. I'm just stricken.
I would guess Game Pass. I would probably guess Game Pass and then right into their
establishments, which would be like Halo and then maybe some other stuff. They may
open with teasers though, which could be really interesting.
That's true.
Like here's a quick snap of something that you'll see later in the show.
Look at how bad my head looks from this. I'm not even going to show you.
I look fucking all right here. I look like stretched out man.
Zeke, what are your predictions? What are we seeing first here?
Ignoring the bingo.
Something surprising.
Is it bingo?
Like a surprise like that no one that might not have gotten leaked.
The one thing-
I wanted to bingo, but it's too much to pay attention to.
Exactly. Exactly.
They're going to open with like, hey, Xbox dildo coming right at you.
It's like, whoa, what?
Can't say that on TV.
They've taken the timer off. For everyone that's over at slash
Twitch. I think we're going to get shut up over there.
Oh, I'm ready.
Join us. We're going to be talking over the conference here
at that twitch.tv slash at mejp and we'll be back after-
Go stay here.
Stay on my stream.
Here any second. I'm going to go ahead and kick it over.
Bingo, bingo, bingo. I don't have enough time to do a bingo.
What the fuck is this bingo card?
Hold on.
It's true. It's true.
Annoying.
Jerma hyped for From Software.
Minecraft.
Jerma's a sellout because he likes something.
Make sure you watch-
I don't even have things set up for this.
Oh my god.
My screen just went down.
Fuck it.
Mike, Windows 10.
Why did everything just fall down?
Okay, I don't have time.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
I got to be quiet.
Who's this?
Wait, why are we all here?
Hold on.
Am I missing something?
Why are we all in boxes down here?
Are they going to add everybody?
I don't-
Am I on the wrong channel?
Wait, is this a visual?
How do I get it-
How do I get on a different show?
I'm on the wrong stream.
No, I'm not.
They've left me.
They left me.
No, this is right.
This is like turned up all the way.
Am I going to be bigger than this?
Oh, this is my favorite part of a former Marvel movie.
When it shows everything, it like says Marvel.
I bet they show Forts of 12.
Xbox Game Studios.
Please welcome.
Marvel is the oldest and most efficient-
I didn't try to shut up.
...history has ever shown us.
Scheduled scarcity is a premium feature of colonial life.
A colony must never lose faith.
That is what the board provides.
Security in a senseless and chaotic world.
This is Halcyon, the furthest colony in the galaxy.
Proudly owned and operated by corporations.
Everything we have.
Everything we are.
We owe to them.
Who's here?
All right, this is the-
This is the outer-
They're always with us.
The outside.
Whatever it's called.
No one has ever gone against them.
A stranger has just arrived.
Someone who's challenging the corporate board.
Someone who's digging up their secrets.
Someone who could be a villain.
Or a hero.
Looks like the bleeding stopped.
I owe you one.
Here.
Hope this gun serves you better than it did me.
Or a psychopath.
Oh.
Classic German joke.
I suppose time will tell.
But no matter who this stranger chooses to be.
The Halcyon colony will never be the same.
Yeah, this is the outer-
What's it- whatever it's called.
Yeah, see? I told you.
You don't know what I'm talking about.
Outer Worlds.
All right.
I took pregnancy classes just for this moment.
Come on, Phil.
Please welcome from Ninja Theory,
Rami Tucker and Dom Matthews.
Let's see what they have to say.
God, I wish I was in that audience right now.
Screaming.
At E3 2018, we announced that Ninja Theory had joined Xbox Game Studios.
A move that has given us an incredible boost
in achieving the creative ambition of our teams.
We've started work on a number of new games at the studio.
And in the near future, we'll be sharing details on all of these projects.
I need a fucking coffee so bad.
When we joined Xbox Game Studios,
we already had a very exciting game several years in the making.
Oh.
And we're happy to return to E3 to share this with you.
As creative director, I'm stoked to be here
to share a new game with you guys.
It combines two of my gaming passions.
Third-person action combat and competitive team multiplayer.
Our technical alpha is kicking off in just a couple of weeks.
And card games.
And we'd love for you to sign up, get involved,
and tell us what you think.
Or if you're here at E3, come and join us for a game.
It's my two favorite things.
Card games and microtransactions.
This is Bleeding Edge.
It's my favorite thing.
All right, all right.
I'll shut up.
Oh, it's the Outer Worlds.
It's the Outer Worlds.
Oh, they're showing more Outer Worlds.
Nice.
Can we just turn into a motorcycle?
Technical Alpha starts on June 27th.
Technical Alpha.
I'm not sure you'd want to...
We're getting earlier and earlier
when you start to let people play your game.
Does that mean that there's like sounds?
There's no sounds in that game.
Did they show this last year?
I feel like they did.
Or like the Game Awards or something.
I can't wait.
A big three in a row.
Oh my god.
See you in a minute.
Minecraft version 2.12.
This chapter in the game now.
What is this?
This is a pretty big update for Minecraft.
This is Diablo Immortal.
This is Minecraft Diablo.
This is gonna sell like a trillion copies.
You know it.
Well, you know, it's really sad when
probably the best action RPG to come out
in probably two or three plus years
is Minecraft spinoff.
I'm excited for that.
That sucks.
I am.
I want to play that.
I like that.
I don't even like Minecraft,
but like I've all like...
Here he is.
I'm excited for that.
I actually am.
Like I think that'll be fun to play for like an hour.
There he is.
Come on.
Come on, Phil.
I've been drinking kefir all morning waiting for you.
Somebody just...
Live for this exact moment.
We get to share the best of our art form
here with you in LA.
And the moment you get to experience breathtaking new stories,
new worlds, and new heroes for the very first time.
Man, it's pretty sick that we're the only fucking people here.
So even if you have bad magic tricks,
you're the only magician in the room.
This decisive moment of discovery is etched
in your gaming history alongside your every achievement,
your every moment,
your every new friend.
This is why we on Team Xbox are always
and will be dedicated to unleashing the next
new games for you to discover and love.
Show us.
So whether you're one of the thousands with us
here in Microsoft Theater...
That like hurt my jaw.
...one of the billions around the world who play games...
There were billions of people watching this stream.
...welcome to E3 2019.
This is all, this is loud as I can go.
This right now is the single most creative
and energizing time in gaming history.
Games and games together...
That's my son?
Phil Spencer's dad is here.
...to be a significant unifying force for the world.
The expanding...
That guy's getting thrown out.
...has opened a new era of creative possibility.
With more games, more creators,
and more industry players than ever before.
And gamers were everywhere.
Somebody just walked up and was like...
Shh, can you stop doing that please?
...players in the world has more than tripled.
Over two billion of us now play games
in every region and on every continent.
And with new technological leaps,
we get to play whatever we want
with whomever we want and wherever we want.
Yeah, mom, you can't tell me when I can't.
I can't play my game now.
You can't tell me what to do, mom.
Every decision is guided by our belief
that gaming is for everyone.
My team and I are single-minded in our resolve
to bring everyone the games they want,
to connect everyone to play with the friends they want.
All right, I gotta get a copy.
And to empower everyone to play wherever they want.
Okay, I'm gonna get a copy.
So, just, I can't miss this.
Something big is gonna happen.
This is why we be innovating hardware and services.
It's why we're uniting communities through cross-play.
And it's why we're investing with new distinctive creators.
I'm gonna fucking sprint.
I'm gonna sprint as fast as I can.
This is why we scour the world for your next new games.
This today is the largest showcase of games
on any stage, anywhere this year.
Today, from the thousands of games in development
across Xbox One and Windows PC,
we're highlighting 60 games for you.
60 games?
Including 14 games from Xbox Game Studios.
That's too many.
How long is this broadcast?
An Xbox Game Pass.
It gets 60.
Yeah, we decided to not have anything to show you
for the last four years.
We thought 2019 was the time to do it.
What's next at Xbox Game Studios?
Expansive plans for streaming.
And of course, revealing more about our next new console.
So thank you for joining us today.
Let's jump in.
Ow, my knee.
Star Wars Episode VI?
I don't think this is weird.
Figuring it out.
Eh.
I saw that yesterday.
I feel like this is going to be like every other game I've ever played.
I might as well just sit back and drink my beer.
New horror game.
Outlast 3.
Actually, is it Outlast 3?
I knew you guys were going to say Peter.
Wait up, bullet.
Bullet!
Dog.
Into the trees.
Dude, when you play the game, it's you watching the videotape.
Tapes in the trees.
That's what's going to be called.
Tree tapes.
Tree tops.
Tree tape tops.
The player of which...
I was close.
Oh, here comes another one.
That's a neck warmer.
I love it.
I want it.
Neck toaster.
Dude, I can't wait for this 742-hour long campaign.
I can't wait.
Think about all the good **** that we're going to have, huh?
Oh, sorry.
Damn.
Oh, I got...
Take the ****, champ Dex.
He's got a jacks finger.
Did you see that?
Every corporal cop in this city is going to be blasting down these doors
after what you and your psycho friend did.
We didn't need all this **** tension, damn it.
Made for TV.
Edited for TV.
Cyberpunk 2077.
On USA Network.
Wake the **** up, samurai.
Wake the **** up.
We have a city to burn.
Hold on, is that John Wick?
Hey, Keanu Ree...
Keanu Ree...
Is this, like, John Wick 5?
Please welcome...
John Wick.
His name's not even Keanu anymore.
What is this, like...
What is this button on the screen?
Free order on Amazon.
What the ****?
See ya, thank you.
Legend.
It's like having Picasso on the stage.
I gotta talk to you about something.
CD Projekt...
Why is he acting like Christopher Walken?
Cyberpunk 2077.
I gotta tell you.
A while back...
He's being like Walken.
The guys from CD Projekt Red approached me
and asked me to be a part of their new project.
Cyberpunk 2077.
They were going on and on.
How they'd create this vast open world
with a branching storyline.
How you'd be able to customize your character
through in-game choices.
And it's not something I knew before,
but I was excited by it.
And I'm always drawn to fascinating stories.
I mean, this is cool.
Like, this is...
I gotta get on stage with John.
Is set in a metropolis of the future
where body modification has become an obsession.
Play as an outlaw.
An enhanced mercenary
working in the sleazy underbelly of the city.
Yeah.
Let me tell you.
The feeling of being there,
of walking the streets of the future
is really going to be breathtaking.
I'm trying.
All right, all right, all right.
So I gotta finish this.
So tell me.
Do you guys want to know
when there's the release date?
I think a lot of people do.
All right.
Be nice.
Then check this out.
You know, easy.
Mr. Hanson, am I right for the job, boy?
That's really cool, though.
If you have gone through to the other side,
let's do this.
This is going to be a pretty fun money management sim game.
They got you guys all fucking jacked up
of it being this crazy action game.
Now, it's going to be like a banking simulator.
World premiere.
That's a long way away,
but at least we have a day.
This fucking Keanu Reeves is just on the stage.
That's unbelievable.
Keanu Reeves is in this one, too.
Sell.
Hug.
Bail at Super Mario 2.
Radishes.
And how to say goodbye.
Look inside somebody's eye.
So you play like a germ.
And no, I'm not talking about you guys.
You know, I'm one of the germomites, one of the germs.
Once upon a shooting star.
I'm a spirit fairer.
Either one of them.
They really have like 100 games.
All right.
This better be fucking good
because I've been waiting a long time for this shit.
I'm not excited for it.
It looks good.
It looks all right.
It's just I don't like that kind of 2D.
Style for a game like that.
It's all right.
I'm not excited.
But it might be okay.
It looks pretty cool.
Look at how cool this looks.
This is the best game they've shown so far.
I can't remember what they showed.
I don't even know what that says.
Rip.
Pig.
I don't know what that said.
That's not a good marketing technique
because I don't know what the fucking name of the game is.
Egg time?
We're all right.
It is in full screen.
Oh, you're talking about them.
What was that one?
What was the one with the cameras?
Good luck with the one with the camera.
Supermarket Tree.
Springs Park game.
I mean these are all just going to get dumped on Xbox Live.
Wow, that was all one game.
Interesting.
What did I do with my camera?
Please welcome head of Xbox partnerships, Sarah Vaughn.
All right, here we go.
Let's get some like a big announcement here.
Very large announcement.
All the idea of Xbox games you just saw
will premiere on Xbox Game Pass day one.
Today?
Oh, there we go.
Where's the shot?
At Xbox, our passion is to help you find
and play the games that you love
through creation, curation, and discovery.
The ultimate expression of that passion is Xbox Game Pass.
My team travels the globe seeking out fan favorites
and hidden gems and craft partnerships with their creators
so that you can discover your next favorite game.
Mind-blowing experiences, epic adventures,
and iconic characters, all for you to explore.
It's all for me.
It has been awesome to see the record-breaking success
developers have had in Xbox Game Pass,
introducing their games to new players
and creating lifelong fans.
They got the computer set up.
Since launch, we have tripled the number of partners
in Game Pass, adding more games from more genres,
platformers, RPG, adventure, sports, puzzles,
and more every single month.
And of course, every Xbox Game Studio's title you see today
will premiere in Game Pass day one.
I mean, it's...
We are thrilled to announce new titles
coming to Xbox Game Pass on console today,
including Batman Arkham Knight,
Metro Exodus, and the Handsome Collection.
I mean, Microsoft has to do something.
They have to do something different
or something that Sony's not doing
because Sony's crushing them every single week.
Nintendo and Sony are crushing them.
Like they're being crushed.
It's for you to be able to play any game
with anyone, anywhere.
And we know for many of you that means PC.
That is why...
Okay, I'm listening.
Last month, we announced Xbox Game Pass for PC.
All right, I swear to God, I thought about it for a second.
I was going to dump the coffee on me.
Today, the Game Pass journey on PC begins.
That would be really dumb.
That would be a really stupid thing to do.
PC players can discover their next favorite game
with Xbox Game Pass.
We have curated over 100 games just for PC,
including favorites like Imperator Rome
and Football Manager 2019.
Did you already play these?
Like why do I need an Xbox Game Pass
if I already own like, everybody already owns these.
And for the first time on PC,
starting with Halo Reach,
the entire Master Chief collection.
Yeah, but we all knew that was coming.
It's Banjo-Kazooie 3 on PC only.
We are thrilled to share that Xbox Game Pass for PC
launches in open beta today.
Let's go get it.
Whenever you're ready.
Today.
Are you guys ready to play a bunch of games
that you've probably already played?
It's like a steam sale.
But like, those of you guys,
I can't speak, this is too loud in my ear.
If you haven't played these games,
you can spend like $2 to buy, you know,
the game that you like, Ark.
All right, if you haven't played Ark yet,
yeah, that was a game that you can get on steam sale
for like four dollars.
Wolfenstein 2, get that one for like six bucks
in like a month or two.
Pum Raider, yeah, these are all,
this is steam sale, this is Xbox steam sale.
But it's, but it is cool though, it is.
At least they're trying something different
because they're going to start to do this
and they're not,
the Xbox ain't going to fucking sell games anymore
like in five years.
Xbox Game Pass for PC is here.
It's going to be a subscription, like Netflix.
Now, try it out by downloading the all new Xbox app
on Windows.
And if you want it all,
we have created a membership just for you.
What is it?
Xbox Game Pass Ultimate.
What does that mean?
What's the difference?
Why do you have two?
Wait, why are there two?
You get everything.
Xbox Game Pass for console with over 100 great games.
Xbox Live Gold, an unrivaled gaming community.
And now, Xbox Game Pass for PC at no additional charge.
All right, that's for, it's 15 bucks.
If it was like 20 or 30,
I might've been a little skeptical on that one.
Because it's E3, everyone can jump in
and play today for $1.
That's just to get you to sign up
and then you have to put your credit card in.
Your next favorite game.
They're doing the gym.
Xbox is going to win the next console war.
They're doing the gym fucking pass.
You know you're going to buy that for a dollar
and you're going to forget about it
and it's going to charge you every month.
You're going to forget you have it.
What a perfect, what an unbelievable strategy.
The you don't go to the gym strategy.
It's only five dollars to sign up
and then it's 20 a month.
Flight Simulator.
Somebody said Google Earth 4.
When was the last Flight Simulator
that they actually came out with?
This is a big deal to a lot of people.
Now Flight Simulator has a really,
really dedicated, huge community.
I'm telling you, there are people
that are freaking out right now
that are so happy to see them.
I'm glad, hopefully it's good.
Yeah, you might think that's boring
but that's a big deal to a ton of people.
Do you remember a time when armies were built
and powerful cities collapsed
when the smallest of choices
through the pages of history?
I wasn't going to lie.
It was an age of empires.
Yeah, here's the most played strategy games
ever in 4K.
This is the one where the guy
was on the plane, right?
Remember I told the story,
this is the one where I was watching
the guy playing on the plane.
This is Age of Kings, right?
Which was Age of King.
That wasn't Clash of Clans.
I was like fucking 14.
Razors, I see you at a donkey's age.
Welcome to beautiful Colorado.
Hold to the purple mountain's mastege
of the Rockies.
Hike through colorful canyons.
Get up close and personal
with a wild and wooly wildlife.
Sample our own cooked delicacies.
Eat where the locals eat.
Visit Colorado Springs.
There's so much to see and do
in this post-apocalyptic winter wonderland.
Do you like XCOM?
Be new people, make new friends.
Colorado has colorful characters
and friendly faces everywhere you look.
See our beautiful airport
and don't forget to pick yourself up
a nifty souvenir.
So don't be shy,
Colorado's waiting for you.
First round's on me.
First round's on you.
Oh, Wasteland, okay.
Please welcome, kind of Xbox Game Studios,
Matt Booty.
What do you got for us?
Games are at the heart of our mission.
Games!
All last year, we added seven new
game development studios to Xbox.
That's a lot.
It's fantastic to see some of these
studios already sharing new games
on our E3 stage and there's more to come.
I have the privilege of working with
some of the best studios around the globe
and for me, great studios are about
people, teams, and ideas.
Our success comes down to one thing,
creating great games that players love
and great games come from great developers.
That's why I'm honored today
to announce that joining Xbox Studios
is Double Fine Productions.
Double Fine has been a beacon of
creativity and spirit in game
development for almost 20 years
with classic games like Psychonauts,
Brutal Legend, and Broken Age.
I'm looking forward to Double Fine
joining Xbox and seeing what we create together.
Broken Age was kind of a disappointment.
Please join me in welcoming the founder
and president of Double Fine
Productions, Tim Schafer.
Psychonauts might be fun, Psychonauts 2,
but like Broken Age was that big
comeback kind of game there.
Thank you.
Thank you so much and thank you, Matt.
We are so excited to be joining
Xbox Game Studios and I'm here to
personally reassure you, Matt.
I don't know what you've heard,
but I'm a team player.
Whatever you need from Double Fine
will make the Halo stuff.
Forza stuff, Excel stuff,
whatever you want, we are there.
Tim, we just want you to make great games.
Oh, that's such a relief,
because I was totally lying.
Why don't they just get closer?
In that case, why are you talking
this far away from each other?
They're having like a general conversation
like fucking 60 feet away.
Just like stand in the middle together.
That was so weird because it was like,
oh hey, so what do you think about this?
Guy fucking a football field away?
All right, I gotta shut up.
My name is Raz and today is my first
official day on the job.
We're on a mission.
Rasputin?
I'm on him.
Looking for me?
The mission is falling apart.
We've lost control of Roboto.
I put the whole leg in the box
and the basket in the basket.
No, no, I won't tell.
I won't tell anyone.
I promise.
Yes, no, please, no.
Psycho Nox 2, back into the domain.
No tagline, okay.
No, no, um.
World premiere.
No colon?
Every fucking star, I mean, this is like,
when you hear the music
and you hear the lightsaber sounds,
I feel like I hear this in my fucking sleep.
I gotta tell you about a dream I had.
It's crazy.
Nothing to do with Star Wars or E3.
I'll wait till the presentation's over to tell you.
What do you mean, shut up?
Shut up?
It's LEGO Star Wars.
Is it that big of a deal?
Should I be quiet?
Yes.
Is this Dragon Ball Z Full Fighter
First Extreme Four?
All right, if it's over 10 syllables, I win.
Dragon Ball Game Pro, hold on.
Dragon Ball Game Project Z.
What's underneath it?
There was something underneath it too.
World premiere.
I have a surprise for you.
Okay.
You want to guess what it is?
This is an outfit for a newborn.
You bought it this morning.
You wanted to surprise me.
I'm sorry.
You're pregnant.
You know?
I know because you already gave it to me.
This has happened before.
What are you talking about?
What's going on?
Someone is coming.
He's going to hurt us.
He says you killed your father.
I need to know what happened.
Why are you doing this?
My father died.
Tired of a heart attack?
No, I didn't have anything to do
with it.
Any second now, he's going to knock on that door.
Help me.
This isn't happening.
This can't be happening.
Police, open up.
That's him.
Did you call the police?
We have a warrant.
Please open the door.
I didn't do anything.
We're here to help.
Don't listen to him.
I'm your only chance.
Open the door right now.
What?
You know what I mean.
I love you.
You have to believe me.
Stop.
No.
You're under arrest.
Hey!
Is it 47?
You're home.
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
This is what it's like to be a hitman NPC.
Holy shit, they're really going meta with this.
He keeps reloading the same level.
And he keeps coming and killing us.
You gotta help me.
He thinks it's really funny to like throw shit at our heads.
Like rocks and shovels.
The lights will guide you.
Bambi.
Look at this.
What's in here?
Let's go.
Be careful, let's jump.
I want a treat.
Here, you can have a treat.
Here, take that.
They're losing him.
I'm already gone.
I don't know who that is.
I don't know who to cheer for.
I don't know what this is.
Is this Gears of War?
Are these the people she's like consumed?
Are these all the souls that she's consumed or something?
I don't know what this is.
I might have an unpopular opinion about Gears.
But Gears, to me, is one of those like TV shows
that had like the first or second amazing season.
And then they were like, we're just going to keep this going.
Studio head Rod Ferguson.
It's like you came out with, you came out with like Westworld.
And then, holy shit, this was awesome.
And then you like decided that Westworld 2 and 3 were going to come out.
And it's like, whoa, what are you doing?
Thanks, everyone.
We're excited to announce that Gears 5 is releasing on September 10th.
I didn't even know there was a Gears 4.
I swear to God, I didn't know that.
And if you want to play four days early, you can.
With our Ultimate Edition or membership
in the newly announced Xbox Game Pass Ultimate.
It's fun, right?
It's like third person multiplayer.
Like out of Gears 3, it was fun, right?
But they really are just seasons now.
In September, we return to the biggest Gears campaign ever,
where we'll explore more of Kate's harrowing journey
and celebrate our launch on September 10th.
But what are we talking about today?
Today, it's a brand new way to fight the swarm.
In Escape, you play as one of three Hive Busters.
Why do I need to be here?
You and your squad infiltrate the hive,
plant the bomb, and escape with your life.
Because we all know that best defense is a good offense.
It's everything you love about Gears.
Turned up to 11.
No, actually, the best offense is a good defense with thorns.
Get your RPG right.
Oh, Jesus Christ!
You did it too early!
Holy shit.
He was probably shitting his pants up there.
Like, please don't press the fucking button early.
Please don't press the button early.
Dude, somebody in the front row got like their eyebrows singed off.
That's like a...
What the...
Ah!
Wait, are we under the stage?
They attacked.
We lost everything.
Everything except the need for revenge.
This might look like a surrender, but it's not.
It's an invasion.
Gears 6.
That's right, we're doing both back to back.
Two months apart.
Escape 4.
Ozzy Osborne and then Gorillaz.
I don't know what else feels like we're...
It's hard to differentiate video games, huh?
Am I getting old or is it just like...
Are we just seeing like the same five video games made?
Like in the last three or four years?
I mean, I'm just getting old.
Escape.
Oh, it is Gears.
It just is Gears 5.
Okay, all right.
Okay.
An aggressive three-player co-op experience perfect for your living room couch.
Wait a second.
Oh, fuck.
It's not just about...
They're gonna press the fire button again.
Are we gonna get out of here?
And challenge your friends with the experiences you create.
And tonight, join me on Mixer as we challenge these three WWE superstars,
Xavier Woods, AJ Styles, and Tyler Breeze to find a gameplay deep dive from
right here in the hive.
For these at home, for the next two days,
you and your friends can play in select Microsoft stores.
So good luck out running the swarm and we'll see you on the leaderboards.
Oh, and for anyone who pre-orders or plays within the first week,
I got something special just for you.
What is it?
Oh, not the ice.
It's getting cold in here.
They all freeze up.
Special fucking pre-order armor set with extra fucking buttons on it.
It's the Terminator.
Oh, my God.
Games are so weird now.
What is this?
It's a new mouse.
New controller.
The Xbox T Leap Mouse.
Not about a controller.
It is.
It's a controller.
World's most advanced controller.
That's too many buttons.
That's too much.
I don't want to...
That's like freaking me out.
The thumb stick comes off and then turns the car and then engine in there.
All right.
That's actually really cool.
You change the thumb stick.
That's everything you like.
That's really cool.
This is awesome.
Is this like 500 bucks?
Can you get an Xbox Elite controller or a Vive?
Let's find out.
All right.
All really cool things.
All really awesome features.
Looks great.
Can I experience virtual reality or own a new controller?
Pre-order now at Xbox.
Let's find out how much it is.
How much is it?
You watch this, I'll forget something.
My father saved my life.
He told me never to forget who I am.
Where I come from.
In this place, nobody even wants to know my name.
Getting attached is deadly.
By the way, maybe we talked about...
Every game is like the same five games.
Every game also uses the same five voice actors.
I might be gone.
We'll get into like...
Just like shake us all up in a jar.
But I won't let it turn me into an animal.
Staying alive became the essence of our existence.
Yet life must be more than just survival.
It's $150, by the way, for that console.
Every day the disease tries to crush us
and make us forget who we are.
But I keep fighting.
Name is Aiden.
I'm infected.
Dying Light was fun.
Maybe it'll be fun again a second time.
World premiere.
I'll be on camera for like at least 10 seconds on this one.
Just in case I need to do like a fucking fake reaction.
He steps on the gas.
Starts peeling out of the stage.
No, that's the big thing.
They put a jump on the stage and he hits the gas.
And it goes zero to 60.
Goes over the fucking jump.
Over the audience like Evel Knievel style.
Like lands over them.
Everyone's like, holy fuck!
It's LEGO!
Why do they have to do this to every single franchise?
LEGO!
I just gave myself a headache.
Why does everyone have to have LEGO counterparts?
LEGO!
I gotta shut up.
I gotta be quiet.
I think they just figured out how to make double the money.
Just make a video game and make a LEGO counterpart.
Please welcome Ralph Bolton.
Just reskin it as a LEGO game and it'll sell twice as much every time.
Aaron's passion for design with about half a million of LEGO's legendary bricks.
Make Gears LEGO.
Incredible life-size LEGO Speed Champions McLaren Senna.
Now watch me destroy it with this baseball bat.
Took him 200 hours to make this fucking thing.
LEGO Speed Champions expansion.
You will drive this Senna and more LEGO Speed Champions cars
in an entirely new world packed with inventive new challenges.
New areas to explore and loads of bricks to smash.
The Forza Horizon for LEGO Speed Champions expansion launches this week.
I'll see you there.
Oh it's an expansion.
I wanna like gotcha expansions in this conference.
Oh yeah they're already doing it.
They're doing it already.
I they already did it.
I remember this fucking three years ago.
They're already doing this.
That's the best you're gonna do.
They actually are doing it.
You have to appeal to every single potential customer now.
Now what's the age range for your for your free game or your franchise?
I want everyone to be able to play that game.
I want everyone to buy it.
We're talking diapers to retirement.
One to 80.
We're not gonna just play chess.
LEGO chess.
My mission find the father I never knew.
My mission find a hero I've never met.
He hasn't radioed in days.
He hasn't been seen since the outbreak.
The last time I heard his voice.
The last place he was seen was in Trouble Valley.
Trouble Valley.
I've only heard whispers.
I've only heard legends.
Of unseen horrors.
Here we are the many.
Here we can become stronger.
For so long I was just surviving.
Now people are counting on me.
This was written by a computer.
This is where my story could end.
This is where my story could begin.
I thought we had seen everything.
We ain't seen nothing yet.
It's another fucking gotcha.
What is this?
It's a dated to K2 Heartland.
It's another like gotcha expansion.
Every game has become so diluted together that like I think these are new games
but they've already existed and they're just expansions.
I'm stupid.
Oh my god.
Are we gonna get lego sonic?
Lego sonic incoming.
What is this?
Hold on.
Wait a minute.
Is this actually it?
Is this fantasy star?
If it's fantasy star I'm gonna get it.
I don't think it is.
Oh is it?
I can't tell.
You're in a Gears of War game or like an anime sword fighter game.
I can't tell anymore.
No, no.
Is it?
I don't think it is.
It is.
It actually is.
I gave you a reaction.
Those of you who have played fantasy star know
that this game had influenced many of the most popular games today.
This game was sick.
So with great delight we welcome SEGA back to our stage
and fantasy star back on Xbox.
That's actually pretty cool.
This is a classic.
As we said our goal on team Xbox is to bring you the world's best games.
Meeting with developers,
playing their games and introducing you to their games.
These are the best parts of my job.
Back at E3 2017 when I first met with the creators
of this next game they shared their ambition.
To bring their massively popular game with its passionate community
of 650 million PC players to the entire world.
What is that?
Dota?
I'm happy to announce our partnership with the legendary team at Smilegate.
Their approach to game design demonstrates sheer creative boldness.
Next year you'll discover the newest entry
in this landmark franchise.
On console for the very first time only on Xbox.
This is Crossfire X.
What the fuck is Crossfire X?
Am I supposed to know what this is?
Crossfire X?
Did he make up those numbers?
Did he make that up?
Was that a joke?
What is Crossfire X?
First to console.
I'm gonna get care more about Fantasy Star 2.
That's a fucking pretty big deal.
It's a mobile game?
Oh, wait, a mobile game is the most played FPS in the world?
Is that what he said?
Crossfire X.
So this game already exists and it's existed for a long time.
So where's the gameplay?
Now it's in 2007.
Crossfire X.
Well, I mean, they got the red X on the right spot
because I ain't gonna be buying that one.
World Premiere.
Something we knew as truth.
Wait, that person's mask on their face.
I don't know if you see it.
All right, I'm gonna quiet.
Rise up.
What is it?
Tales of Arise Up.
2020.
There are six sirens in the universe.
I used to be one of them.
My name is Lilith.
Not actual gameplay.
You can't do this in the game.
It just looks cool on camera.
Not actual gameplay.
It's like, all right.
Is this not, is that not gameplay?
Interlacing on this screen.
Like a bad feed or something.
Children of the vault is a psycho cult.
10 billion followers demand we join or die.
We've got another proposal for them.
Censor out a murder figure.
I'm sorry.
That's like Chuck E. Cheese level of sensor and something.
In fact, I swear to God, an employee at Chuck E. Cheese
gave me the finger one time when I was like eight.
I was trying to shake the machine to like three points
and he like came over and fixed it and gave me the finger.
Can't show the middle finger
but you can show people like exploding.
Yeah, it's like.
Hey, I have an idea.
Let's have a person's head like fucking explode on camera
but like no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's have a guy's like eyes get two spikes
like through his head and his brain comes out the back.
But don't say that word.
How dare you?
World premiere.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Even imagine its fullest brilliance.
The Elden were shattered.
Tell me.
Elden Ring.
Xbox One NPC.
Wait, is this an Xbox exclusive?
You got George R. R. Martin and oh, man.
Oh, my God.
What the?
Please welcome.
Can you get somebody to talk about that?
That's a way to sell like a fucking 500 million.
From multi-national studios to one-person passion projects,
thousands of Xbox games are in development for you
right now.
Thousands.
Just today, we showed you 60 games.
We are now experiencing an unmatched expansion
of creativity on Xbox.
Gaming for you means connecting all of these creators
to all of you.
Last fall, we announced our ambition
to empower everyone everywhere to play
by bringing Xbox to the cloud.
We will do this in two ways.
Through Project X Cloud and through console streaming.
Two months ago, we connected all Xbox developers
to Project X Cloud.
Today, unfortunately, it's been hacked.
And 50,000 people that got connected to the cloud
lost all their information.
To experience the freedom to play right here at the show.
And you'll have two ways to stream.
There's a new platform feature.
Console streaming.
It turns your Xbox One into your own personal
and free X Cloud server.
This shit never works though.
Whether you're using a console in our data center
or your console at home, this October,
you'll be able to use our hybrid gaming cloud
to play your games wherever you go.
Yeah, but the same thing with the Google thing too.
It's like the latency is not good enough yet.
Where you play is now entirely your choice.
You decide.
So let's talk about our next console.
For us, the console is vital and central to our experience.
We heard you.
A console should be designed and built and optimized
for one thing and one thing only, gaming.
So they're going to strip all the other shit from Xbox.
The same team that created the world's most powerful console,
Xbox One X, and innovated its groundbreaking processor
and the elite controller.
The same team that engineered the world-class compatibility
of today's Xbox One consoles.
The same team that set the bar for live gaming services
with Xbox Live.
This same team, the Xbox Lizard on a new mission
to create the future of gaming for you.
When we think about the future of gaming,
it's not just PC, it's not just console,
it's not just mobile.
It's really all of the above.
Xbox is all about choice.
We're investing in technology all throughout the game stack.
The games you want with the people you want
on the devices that you want.
Xbox on the blockchain.
It's going to be like Xbox Crystal.
We don't want to build just an Xbox console.
We truly want it to be transformative.
More immersion, more exploration, more detail.
How do we make it easier for people
to get into the game, to stay in the game?
One of the things that gamers and developers
are incredibly excited about is reducing load times.
I'm an RPG gamer, and so like loading screens are a thing.
Sitting there in the big elevator,
because you know that the game's loading in the background.
That's just an elevator ride forever.
That's our goal with gaming,
is that you don't have those pauses.
This generation is going to be a bigger leap
than any generation we've done before.
At the heart of our next generation console
is our custom design processor,
leveraging the latest Zen 2 and Navi technology
from our partners at AMD.
From a pure processing perspective,
this is four times more powerful than the Xbox One X.
We're leveraging high bandwidth GDDR6
to ensure that we're getting the best performance possible.
It's going to usher in resolution and frame rates
that we've never seen before.
It will burn you.
If you touch it, it'll burn you.
Look at frame rates, up to 120 frames per second.
8K capability.
Variable refresh rate.
Next-gen ray tracing.
It's real time because it's hardware accelerated
for the first time ever.
What I'm personally most excited about is the SSD.
We've created a new generation of SSDs.
We're actually using the SSD as virtual RAM.
We're seeing more than 40 times performance increases
over the current generation.
The combination of the SoC and the solid-state drive
are really what gives you a totally new experience.
Now we can take all of that power
and apply it back into the scene.
So we can actually generate more life in that world
and bring it to the gamer in a seamless way
so that then you're fully experiencing
what the game developer wants you to experience.
When you can move through worlds
without waiting for screens to load that speed,
that performance is what the next generation is about.
Sony fanboys backing up into a corner.
Sony fanboys backing up, right?
Sony fanboys get your story.
The next generation, we can bring the world to life
in a way we've never experienced Halo before.
We're delivering four generations of content
better than you've ever seen them before.
This console is especially awesome for Game Pass members.
With the faster load times,
you're going to be able to experience all the games
within just snap of your fingers.
We're giving gamers the option
to connect across devices and across platforms.
It's going to be able to talk to it.
In a way that we never were able to before.
This isn't just a console launch.
Alexa, it's going to be like Janet.
Xbox, Janet.
Your accessories, your console gaming experience with Xbox.
It all comes forward with Scarlett.
The T, the Scarlett, the Xbox Scarlett.
Scarlett, yes.
It eats monsters for breakfast.
Here we go.
You're going to be able to talk to it.
It's going to be able to do attacks.
It's going to be able to order Amazon orders for you.
This is Project Scarlett.
The most powerful and highest performing console
we've ever designed.
Built for creators to unleash their boldest creative visions
and optimized for players
to enjoy the ultimate gaming experience
on a console anywhere.
Immersive experiences begin at the very heart
of the console, at the silicon level itself.
Together with our partners at AMD,
we have co-engineered and custom designed
a state of the art processor for Project Scarlett.
Does it have a CD tray?
Power you could see define previous generations.
Power and performance you can see and feel
defines Project Scarlett.
When we talk about freedom to play,
when we talk about Xbox in the cloud,
when we talk about streaming your games,
Project Scarlett and all of its power
and all of its performance is the foundation
of our future in console
and the formation of our future in cloud.
Latency has got to get better though.
We launched Xbox 18 years ago
with the game reviewers called
the definitive reason to own an Xbox.
Well, because humanity was and is worth saving.
Next holiday, we will launch Project Scarlett
with Halo.
Wait, did you just make like a,
this is going to save humanity?
Oh, it's the Halo, okay.
Humanity is worth saving.
That's why we made the Scarlett.
We're going to save the world.
Oh, that was a Pratt fall.
That was like a WWE fall.
You get like pushed off the top rope.
Daddy's listening.
Can you say hi?
And how big are you?
I'm baby.
Can you tell daddy how big you are?
Two.
Are you so big?
You're big.
And can you sing?
Good singing.
How about I miss you.
And I love you.
And love you, daddy.
And I can't wait to see you.
Can you say see you?
Bye bye.
Is this Halo?
This is UNSC Pelican Echo 216.
Can you hear me?
This is UNSC.
Is he talking to him?
Who is talking to him?
He's like, look over here, I'm floating.
Is that who's talking?
Looks like the main power cells are fried.
Armor shut down.
Is he still in there?
Triggering survival mode.
I'm going to try to overwrite.
Okay, if you can hear me in there, I hope you're ready.
Please don't die.
Here comes the plug the two codes together.
It's Keanu Reeves.
Hey, how long was I asleep for?
Hopefully not too long.
We're going home.
Back, chief.
I rerouted what little power I had into your suit.
Yeah, I'm thinking I'm back.
Looks like there's a problem with the servos in your hands.
Stay calm.
You've been out there a while.
I know I saw something in you to check your armor's diagnostics.
AI knock detection.
That would hurt.
Easy there, big guy.
You're not.
Status report.
He talks?
What?
There's something you need to see, chief.
Yeah, I didn't know.
I've never played Halo.
I haven't ever played one second of fucking Halo.
I don't know.
We lost.
We lost everything.
We're frozen.
Flat earth confirmed.
Race.
Oh no, that's the Halo.
Right, okay, sorry.
No, no, nothing.
We need to run.
We need to fight.
Infinite.
I didn't know Halo talked.
Well, whatever.
The fucking chef, whatever his name is.
Gordon Ramsay's Master Chief.
I'm fucking this up for everybody.
I'm going to quiet down.
I chose you because you were special.
Right?
Pretty cool, new Halo.
And the Terminator is going to be in this expansion for Halo.
Oh, that's too bad.
Master Chief's most ambitious villain.
Adversary yet.
The Terminator.
So what did we get?
We had Battle Toads.
Looks, yeah, I'm not so sure, but maybe it'll be fun.
Phantasy Star Online 2.
Big deal.
Minecraft Diablo.
Pretty big deal.
That's pretty good.
And Madden.
Don't forget about Madden.
I wonder how much money Madden paid to be part of this trailer.
Because why would you put that here?
There is no reason in a million fucking years
why you would put Madden in your trailer for E3 like it was a big deal.
They come out every year, every single year.
There is no difference, there's no announcement.
Why would it be here?
I'm looking forward to that Minecraft Diablo game.
I mean, that's cool, but I didn't play Halo.
I never played any of it.
Are we going to get like a send-off?
There it is.
Hey, now, what was, let me ask you this question.
What was your favorite game that was at E3?
Put it in the comments section below.
Hey!
Man, that was a hell of a conference.
It was.
It was a hell of a conference.
They showed a lot of stuff.
I'm going to pull up.
We had, I'm trying to run it down a dock with everything shown.
Welcome, everyone, once again from Slash.
Welcome, guys.
Where do you even begin with that?
I don't know, Joe.
Like, seriously.
Do we start with Keanu fucking Reeves?
I know!
How crazy was that?
Unbelievable.
Isn't that the entire thing?
Isn't that what's to say?
I can't believe they did that.
God damn it.
I think.
Yeah, I'm going to try to find that trailer real quick.
Co, walk us through your thoughts on what you saw from Cyberpunk.
I'll walk you through it.
So Cyberpunk was seriously, there was so much there.
I know, I had the same reaction.
I had the same reaction when I saw for the first time.
Rational thought right now.
That's what I thought.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Did they put that trailer out, by the way?
Yes, yes, they did.
If I could find it.
I looked up where it was going on.
That was the thing.
But we got to see it for the first time.
We actually got to see it.
Keanu motherfucking Reeves!
Where did that come from?
Hell yeah!
I don't know.
Like, how was that not leaked?
Or how did that work?
That's the best kept secret.
Unbelievable.
100%.
Now, Joe, I'm going to tell you something, Joe.
At that point, all the other leaks seemed like they were not
I know, right?
It was, it's odd.
I got the papers, y'all.
I am fucking shaking a little bit after that one.
Those leaks were on purpose or actually accidental or whatever.
I'm sure they were like, don't even worry about that.
Don't even worry about those other fucking leaks.
As long as Keanu doesn't get out, that shit doesn't get out.
That's the most important.
That's the most important one.
I loved how much fun he was having.
Yeah, he was having a great time.
He was having fun on that stage.
It was just, he was just there.
Guys, I gotta take a shit.
I'll be back.
Just keep doing the podcast without me.
I'm going to go shit my pants if I don't get out of here.
Yeah.
I'll be back in like five minutes.
That's all you had to do is just say cyberpunk.
Just hang out, Keanu Reeves.
It was good.
Could you even think of something that would be more hyped than that?
That might actually appear.
That might actually happen.
I haven't left yet.
I am going to shit my pants about it.
Let me get this out before I go.
That was even on the board for something that could happen.
Well, because they linked it to me, actually.
I'm the only one that knew about that.
Well, we know.
Hell, I gotta go real bad.
All right, all right.
I'm done.
With John Wick hacks as well.
I forgot about fucking the Elven Ring.
That looks amazing, too.
There's a lot of stuff that looks really great.
But I actually do have to pee.
When I get back, here's the plan.
For those of you that are wondering.
I am going to play...
We'll hang out for a little bit.
I'm going to play Cooking Simulator for like an hour or two.
And then we're going to do the Bethesda Conference as well.
So let me just take a piss.
I'll be right back.
I'll see you guys real soon.
Don't go anywhere.
Unless you do.
In that case, hope you have a good day.
See you soon.