Oh shit, people were betting on that. I didn't even see it. I didn't even know. I- I didn't even know. I had no idea.
Two minutes late. Sorry, those of you that thought it was gonna happen a minute and a half ago.
You asshole. Look, you- I- I didn't- Look, I don't know you guys are betting on this stuff.
You guys can't bet on whether or not I'm gonna take a bath today.
And if I decide, unbeknownst to you guys betting, that I don't take a bath.
And half of you guys are watching like the Truman Show monitor going like, he didn't take a fucking bath today.
Fuck him. I'm just sitting- I'm- I don't know. You're looking- I know you have cameras in my house. What are you talking about?
Anyways. Hi guys. 3.3 million.
Wait, will Jerma be live in 24 minutes at exact- at 430 p- No. Oh, right, okay.
So today, we are going to do something that I've put off for a long time.
We're gonna play a game that I tried to stream like two years ago, three years ago.
And it wouldn't work and it was all messed up and I had a lot of trouble streaming it.
But we're back. That game is Spore. And you're probably wondering, why are you playing Spore, Jerma?
I thought you told me two days ago that you were gonna play Paper Mario, Thousand Year Door.
Well, you would be completely correct. I said, hey yeah, that sounds- let's do that next- let's do that next stream.
So, I, uh, I went through the process of looking into Thousand Year Door.
Didn't realize the game was incredibly rare. I thought it was gonna be as easy as just like going and getting it.
It's a rare ass game. And all of you saying, emulate it, emulate it.
You want me to openly emulate a first party Nintendo game and tell you I'm doing it on stream?
You're trying to get me fucking thrown in prison?
There's one thing that Nintendo hates more than anything. It's emulating.
Especially if somebody is actively there with like an audience of people going, yeah, I emulated this shit.
What do I care? A slip will go under my door. It'll have like a bunch of stamps on it.
It'll be from Nintendo themselves.
No, I ain't emulating a first party Nintendo game. I'll find a way to stream it legally.
Uh-uh. I ain't fucking with that. I ain't fucking with Nintendo. They're ruthless if they find out.
Pepehands, he lied to us.
So, I said, you know what? Why don't we play a game that a lot of people have wanted to see for a long time?
We're gonna play Spore. And we'll probably do Spore for the next- I don't know, depending how good it is.
I forget nostalgia is kicking in. I remember it being kind of fun.
But maybe we'll do this for the next couple of days. We'll see.
Just buy it on Amazon? Well, yeah, but buying it on Amazon is easy.
The problem is that a lot of the shipping dates are not till February.
What about the flashing? Yes, okay, I think I have fixed the flashing.
That's since two days.
I didn't say February 1st. I said February. That does not- okay.
Some of you guys are way too literal with all information.
If I say the word February, that doesn't mean February 1st at 1201 AM.
That's not what that means. It could mean, like, February 8th, February 15th, February 6th, February 20th.
And some of them are expensive.
And I will pay $250 for Gotcha Force, but I will not pay $250 to make sure I get a thousand-year door here.
Like, in four days. No. Cheap-ass motherfucker.
I'm not even a cheap-ass motherfucker.
Chat is deranged.
I knew this was going to happen when I looked it up and I was like, oh shit, this is, like, kind of a rare game.
I've got to figure out how to do this.
I'm going to get it. I'm going to get- look, I might even do- I might even get one of the ones that gets here early.
But nothing's ever guaranteed to get here early.
Somebody- no, I'm not even going to read that.
Maybe you shouldn't plan things only one day in advance.
That's how I operate. That's how I operate, man.
This is something that a lot of the new viewers probably don't understand.
So there are, like, huge projects that are, like, months if not years in the making that you will see on this channel.
Everything else is planned 12 hours before a stream turns on.
That's just the way it is. That's just how it is here.
And sometimes it's, like, 30 minutes before a stream turns on.
I go, hmm, fucking what's happening today? Um, leaf blower simulator?
That sounds like fun.
And then you ask chat. Yeah, I'm like, chat, what do you think?
What about Pikmin? You know what?
Because- okay, listen to me.
Because Paper Mario and the thousand-year-old door has been postponed until somewhere in the middle of February,
I'm going to use my IOU card here and we're going to play Pikmin.
I'll give you a date when I figure that out.
Because I don't want to say, we're going to play Pikmin 2 in four days.
And I, like, go on Amazon, it's going to take six days to get her, even with, like, Prime or something.
I can't- I'm not doing that.
I'm going to play Pik- which one should I play?
It's Pikmin 2, right? Should I just do them all?
If I play Pikmin 1, people that love Pikmin 2 are going to be pissed that I played Pikmin 1.
If I play Pikmin 2 first, people are going to be mad that I skipped Pikmin 1.
They're going to be, that's the best one, go play- and if I play Pikmin 3, all of you are going to be mad.
Because that's universally the hated one.
Nobody likes Pikmin 1.
3 is good. Uh oh.
Did I just do it? Did I start the war?
I'll do a poll. Alright, we're going to do a poll at the end of this chat as to which Pikmin I'm going to play.
By the way, I- hold on.
I think I, uh, I think I already have one.
Was I able to buy it twice? I forgot I owned it.
Which one do I have?
I want it.
What's the one that's on Wii?
I have it somewhere. What's the one that's on Wii?
One or two.
One and two are on Wii. Huh.
Both are on Wii. Okay.
Let me see if I can find it. I actually think I really do own it.
Alright. Let's go. We're going to play Spore.
I don't have- I forget everything. I fucking have no idea how to play this game.
Find it.
You have to find it already.
Spore. Alright, so for all you Spore-andies.
Should I?
Should I just play the- start a new game?
Or should we make a creature?
What do you think?
Should I just go with the DNA builder thing, or should I make a creature?
I feel like if I make a creature right now, I'm gonna end up sitting here for the next, like, six hours.
Just new game, just new game, new game, new game, new game, new game, new game, new game, new game, new game.
Okay. Alright, woah, woah, woah, woah, woah.
Make a creature, you dickhead.
I'm not gonna.
New game, please. New game, please.
Do I do a poll?
Alright, I'll do a poll.
Just new game or make creatures?
Oh, you're gonna- I have to desktop capture this.
I'm not supposed to see this shit. Hold on.
That's just the background.
Every single one of your parents' computers, that's the background that's there.
I just gave a bunch of you guys, like, weird flashbacks of going to, like, your grandmother's house.
You want the truth? I gave you the truth.
The reason why I don't have a three- a cool background is because I have three monitors.
And I have no idea how to make it go across all three of them.
And every time I do it, it, like, stretches them and pixelates it and looks like shit.
Even if it's at the right resolution, I haven't figured out how to do it yet.
And I got three monitors, like, two or three years ago.
So I just don't even care anymore.
There was a picture of Carnage up at one point.
And then I think, um, I think, like, the Pac-Man ghosts.
And that was it.
Google it. I tried to Google it. It didn't help me.
Alright, what are we doing? What am I doing?
Oh, straw poll.
Alright, do you want me to start a new game and just play or do you want me to make a creature specifically?
Make a creature or start a new game?
This is important, guys. Come on.
This is impor- what's the difference?
Um, I don't know. I have no idea.
There's a difference. I know there is.
When you start a new game, you, like, have to build, like, a creature from scratch or something, right?
By eating food.
But making a creature, you just get to make everything you want and build one and use it later.
What the hell are you writing?
Make him see this. Make him see this.
Jeremy, you gotta make a couple creatures first. They can be shitty or cool or whatever you like.
When you do that and then start a game, you will see those creatures inside the game you're playing.
They're just the dumbass default Maxis-created creatures, so please make some creatures first.
Okay.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
All right, so we're gonna make a bunch of random- this is gonna take forever.
Whatever. Welcome to the stream.
All right. All right, here we go.
I'm gonna do that and then I'm not gonna make a creature for myself, though.
That sounds like a plan. Let's go.
I have a bunch of cool creatures made if you want to add me as a spore buddy.
I couldn't make an account.
I tried to, like, five times. There's an error. Like, there's a server problem.
All right, so should I do a foal creature or should I do little baby creatures?
Do foal creatures, right?
All right, here we go.
Mmm. New game, idiot.
No, I'm gonna make a couple of creatures!
All right, so this is my- where's the body? This is the body, right?
Let's go with, um, I want a standing creature.
I like- I kind of remember how to play.
Okay, you have to let- you can shrink the body and everything? Okay.
Remember, you don't even know how the animals work.
I have- I don't- I have no idea how to play the game.
I just remember- I remember- okay.
Here's what I remember about Spore.
I played Spore, like, 12 years ago. 15 years ago.
And I think I did this for, like, an hour.
Ran around and danced during the creature stage or something.
And then I- that's all I remember. I don't know anything else.
Let's pull that spine back a little bit.
That's what you do. That's all you do. Yeah, I know.
That is all you do in this game.
Uh, I think his head's- he needs to be-
There we go, like that.
Pull these back a little.
I'm gonna give him, like, a big- like a nice, like, Chad posture.
Align that spine perfectly.
There we go. Yep.
There it is. Perfect fucking spine alignment.
Does he got a gamer neck? No, he doesn't.
Why is this- how is this a gamer neck?
I guess I don't know what it kind of is.
Is he supposed to be, like, a cha- no.
Alright, this is looking a little-
This is looking a little-
I want- I do want to, like, a little bit of a gamer neck.
There we go.
Jesus. Okay. That's not bad.
Do we even- beak?
I don't know if I like the beak.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's a bird. No, but I don't want a bird.
Delete. How do I delete?
I kind of like this. No, no, no. A duck?
Oh, by the way, I- I- Can somebody that plays this game all the time-
I have the new parts, right?
Because I bought the whole package.
I do? No.
What do you mean, no? It's not?
No, no, no, you don't appear to have them.
What? I installed everything. Really?
I don't have all the extra parts?
You do, you do, you do, you do.
I didn't get scammed. Okay.
He does, you do. Alright, so they're lying to me, alright.
What about this one?
Right down here? Two mouths?
I kind of like that.
That's doing it for me.
Give him a tiny face.
A huge underbite?
Got a mask on. Alright, I like that.
I like this one too. But that's alright, we can make more than one.
How do I, um, zoom in?
It's not mouse scroll.
How do I zoom in with the mouse?
Okay, that looks good. Eyes. How about, um-
These are eyes? These are pig eyes.
These are pig nose. These are ears.
Okay, how about, um- I like that.
I like that even better though.
Yep. I like this.
Holy shit, he's evil. Did he be evil? Toad.
I kind of like it with the eyes
down, like this.
I'm very upset.
Or, I don't know, how about-
This is just what your dog does when you have french fries.
It just sits like this, as a statue.
Um, alright, should I do
kind of evil? I'm sure I'll do
french fry dog. I like that.
Alright, now we need- Do I like this body?
I think the body could be better.
Just give him a huge belly. This is just a guy
running around in an alien suit.
Okay, let me see. Arms and legs.
Wait, what's this thing? Ears? No, no ears.
Zero ears. Pregnant.
Should we give him- Should he even have arms?
Maybe he should even have arms.
Grasshopper legs? I want the big stomach.
Okay, that's not bad. He's sitting
on his own- He's sitting on his own
legs. Jesus Christ, what?
It's a flamingo? Isn't that backwards?
Yeah, these are too big. Alright, there we go.
That means it has extra jumping
ability, right?
Try walking. Oh, how do you do that?
Test drive. How do I make him walk?
His neck. Oh, look, it hurts.
He's going like- Ow! What else is this?
Okay, spin. He can spin?
Roar. Alright, how about a flip? Nice.
How about a- Where's the dance?
It goes-
Scared. Sad.
Where's- Where's dance?
Ball, sit, punch. Here we go.
Here it is. Oh, I love it.
Toe tap. That's my favorite one
when they shake their head around. Okay, I like it.
I'm gonna keep going. Okay, we have feet.
Weapons. Oh, shit, hold on.
He has like a saw blade on his stomach?
I'm just making a battle bot. Silent hill
monster. Give him- Okay, wait, that's true.
That is kind of- What if they're on his, like,
arms? What about the little T-Rex saw
blade? Oh, I kinda like that.
These are his hands. No, no, no, no, no.
Mantis? I kinda like this. I'm gonna
flip him around, though, because these are his arms.
No, I don't like that either.
This isn't even my creature. Why do I even care?
Details. Gems?
I put gems all over him? Wait, what is this?
I can give him a little propeller?
Oh, I love it. I love it, I love it, I love it. Hold on.
Definitely keeping that on. What about
some little, like, fluffies on his
shoulders? On his knees? Okay.
This is what every German 985
fan looks like. God damn it, I clicked out
of the chat box. This is what every
German 985 fan looks like. Alright, what we got?
We have singing. He's very good at
singing. Okay, he's got a good mating
call. He's got very good eyesight.
He's kind of- Not that fast.
He's got 40 health, okay. Now, hold on.
Uh, should he have
arms or not? No, definitely not.
Give him some more legs. Maybe I'll give him some more legs.
Hold on. Is his head too heavy, though?
His head might be too heavy. He's doing the
Kubrick stare. I like him. Alright,
good. Let's, um,
change the color? Yeah.
Alright, paint mode. What are you thinking?
Uh, let's see. Marine?
Flesh, flesh, flesh, flesh colored.
I kinda like the, like,
cantaloupe. I
really like the cantaloupe. It's perfect.
Partial styles? Oh, you can do partial,
right? Give him more legs. Alright, hold on.
He's got jumping legs, and
how about- What about these weird ones
in the front? Ooh, wait a minute.
No, that looks ugly. You're gonna
ruin him. I'm just- I'm just looking.
Just one leg in the front. You made
a creeper. I did?
I kinda did. Can he just
do one single leg? It's a creeper.
Even the
flower on his head. Alright, I don't-
I'll have to make a few more, so we're gonna
leave him alone. Doesn't the creeper
have, like, a flower? Who has a flower
on their head? That's a fake fan.
What enemy has a flower on their head?
Oh, it's a Pikmin. It's a Pikmin. We just talked about
Pikmin. Okay, that's what it is. Yeah,
it's a Pikmin. Thank you. I kinda like the
bear claws. Wait, what?
Oh, shit. No, no, no. Should I give him, like, the bird feet?
Bear claws or bird feet? Which one?
Bird feet. Definitely. What's he doing?
He did that with his feet, by the way.
No arms. I like it.
It's perfect. Those are hands. They are?
Those are arms?
I thought those were legs.
Okay, we're gonna- Alright, that's enough.
Name creature. Creature's name is gonna be...
It has to be some type of cantaloupe.
I mean, no. No, no, no, no.
Cantafloat.
Give him feet. Why does he need feet?
Go feet. The creepalope.
That's awful. I actually kinda like it, though.
The creepalope. There we go.
Tags. Who cares?
I don't know how to say yes. Alright, there he is. The creepalope.
Hold A when placing a part for
symmetry mode. Okay. He unironically
needs feet, though. Does he?
Unironically?
Am I buying these now?
Should we webbed feet?
These bird feet. Unironically, yes.
Alright, fine.
He's looking good. I think he's good to go.
How do we say yes? Save and exit.
I need to make another one, right?
So save this one and exit, and then do it again.
I need to make a few, right? This next one's gonna be
a hellish creation, by the way.
I wanna make a big snake. Let's see.
What do I wanna do? I think I'm just gonna make a snake.
Snakes don't have feet.
Let's pull this back a little more.
I'm gonna make a scorpion.
Definitely make it a scorpion.
I want a big, dangerous tail.
Make this head smaller.
Looks pretty good. Mouth. What kind of mouth does a scorpion have?
Not that.
It's just a replace holder.
It's kinda like this gross thing, isn't it?
I kinda like it. Won't he stab himself in the head at all?
It's perfect.
That's perfect already.
Now, eyes.
Not bad.
I love him. Okay.
What about a pig nose?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I think without a nose, it's perfect.
Oh, should we give him one of these?
Oh, I love him. Can this be mine?
Can this be my guy?
Yeah, no nose. Just do nose holes.
How do I do a nose hole? It's fucking angry.
It's not angry.
I like the little ears, too.
Oh my god. What?
Okay, that looks alright.
The ears might be too much, but I really like them.
No, not yet.
He's gotta be lower to the ground. There.
We're gonna give him like a bunch of centipede arms.
What do you think? Centipede legs.
That's what a scorpion has, right?
Eye bones, bug leg. There it is.
Armored bones.
Look at that. Bug legs.
These are huge. These are way too big.
They're gigantic.
In order to get the other parts in the mod,
you have to launch Spore creepy and cute
instead of the base game. Please copy this so he sees.
Really?
Is that gonna fuck everything up?
He already has them. You already have them.
No, he doesn't. I don't know who to believe.
Alright, shrink these legs. Sorry, guys.
Destroyed on heal. He's ignoring us.
No, he has extra parts from an update.
Not the expansion. Really?
Okay, if I save this, can I go back and edit this guy later?
Remember, you have them.
Top left. Exoskeleton. Core Spore.
He doesn't have them.
Doesn't fucking have them. Stop lying.
There's mouths and eyes. That's not them.
That's not it. Chat. Wrong.
Not the DLC. What?
Okay, so I'm just gonna save this right here.
I'm gonna name this guy like fucking Bill.
And then I'm gonna save and exit.
Is that gonna work?
Launch Galactic Adventures if you have it to get both DLCs.
If not, then... Okay.
So we'll have to launch Galactic Adventures?
Why do they make it like this? This is fucking weird.
Yes, yes. Okay.
But what about my settings?
What about my, like, INI config files shit that I changed?
Do I have to...
Is there one EXE? Is there one EXE?
Who knows? There's three EXEs?
Hold on.
Let me just make sure this is not gonna fuck around.
I might have to change a few things.
That's weird. Bro, just open the game.
Open Galactic Adventure. Hold on.
Let me just make sure...
Take a look at some artwork for a little bit.
Take a look at some artwork for a little bit. I gotta figure this out.
Bro, it's just bugs next.
Look what I got.
Catboys!
Okay, let me open this.
They tell me there's three EXEs.
Let's check on that.
Let's see what the heck is going on here.
I don't think there is three EXEs.
Spore. Spore bin. Spore bin F1.
Spore app.
God, what the...
I don't know what the hell is going on.
Spore bin F1.
Spore app. Is that the one that I need to open?
No. It's the orange one. Yeah, that is that one.
Alright, I think I'll be alright.
Let me do this really quickly.
Galactic Adventure is from Steam.
Yeah, but I have to add some...
Resolution thing that I have in the other one. Hold on.
It runs at 1920x1080.
I gotta make sure it does that.
So Galactic Adventure will have all of them.
Is what you're telling me.
It might be really loud. I hope it's not loud. I'm gonna turn it off.
Okay.
Here we are. In the game.
That was incredibly loud. I'm so glad I
just saved all of you.
You can hear it through my headphones.
This shit is unbelievably loud.
Okay, let's try this again.
So, re-8. I gotta go back.
It runs real quick.
Alright, this is good to go.
This is good to go.
Okay, are we ready?
If I go to create, where do I go?
Where's my creatures?
Creature creator, you go to edit.
Okay.
What do you think?
Hold on, not yet. Hey, look at that.
There we go. I have the parts now.
Is this all of them?
Wow, I guess chat.
New creation.
How do I get my old one?
New creation, save.
You must save before sharing.
Where's the top left?
What do you mean top left?
Creepy and cute. There it is. Okay, cool.
Button and bottom left.
Sporpedia, bottom left, lower left.
Top left, bottom left, bottom left, bottom left.
What are you talking about? I don't see it.
Upper right. Sporpedia.
Ohhhh!
Alright, we're good. We're in.
I kinda actually really like the ears.
This is ugly. Well, whatever.
Alright, how do you duplicate? It's alt and what?
That's the hit sound.
Duplicate is what? F4? Just alt.
Copy, there it is. Oops.
How many legs does a scorpion have?
It's like eight. Or six?
I have no idea. I think it's six.
And the back legs are a little higher, right?
Because they're just fucking terrifying little monsters.
Okay.
That looks alright. Now we need
weapons. There we go.
There we go.
This is fucking dangerous.
That's too big. He'll kill himself with this.
What's the survival rate on these guys?
What if it's a limp?
Oh, I kinda like the big tooth thickness.
There's no sound?
Oh, shit. Sorry.
This is his tail.
Okay.
Details.
No wings or anything, right?
Wait, don't scorpions have arms in the front
that come out like big claws?
Dude, don't they? Get rid of these.
They're big lobster claws that come out
in the front. Okay, let's do big lobster claws.
What do we got?
They have six legs and two arms. They have six
legs, do they? How the fuck is that animal
real? You ever think about that?
How is that a real thing on planet
Earth? What a bizarre fucking
creation. Think about all these
animals and all these bugs and shit that just
look at how weird these things are. Look at how
ridiculous our Earth is. Bugs
are fucking weird. They really are. I
don't even know how to explain them. We already went over ants.
Ants are just a math problem.
They just follow code.
Bugs are just living math
problems. It's bizarre.
Bugs are math. We already did this. We already went
over how bugs are math. Bugs
are just a math problem. Like, we already went over this.
It's an algorithm that just plays out as like a
creature. Don't make me go over this again. A lot
of you weren't here a few years ago. I'll do it again.
Okay, hold on. What about sting?
Where's sting?
How do I use the weapon? Bite and charge?
He's just using his head. Why is he
leaning down like that? He needs
two more tiny front legs?
Does he? Two more tiny front legs?
Like that? No, it looks like he's
wearing a tie. Where's bug
hands? Arm plated,
brawned, humerus, tendinitis,
tubular, fleshed?
Like bones? I like these.
Jesus. Those are way
too big. Way too big.
Just absolutely enormous. And they go out
like that, right? Yep. Pull these elbows in.
This is way too huge.
Oh, he's fucking terrifying.
That. There we go. Well, actually, some scorpions
have big arms, like huge
hands and arms and stuff, like the emperor scorpion.
I'm a viewer of Clint's Reptiles.
Okay, I know what I'm talking about. And he gave it
like a three out of, a two out of five.
You don't want, scorpions are hard to have. Okay.
We need like lobster claws.
I mean, that's the closest thing I'm going to get.
Do they have mittens? Do they give them big mittens?
Give poison to the
stinger.
They're like big boxing gloves.
All right. I like it. It's perfect.
He's got these funny ears. He's so cute.
I love him. He looks like a baby.
Looks like Bernie. It does not
look like Bernie Sanders.
Okay. I don't even know where you're seeing
that from. The mittens. Oh, oh.
I was like, how is this Bernie?
Everything is Bernie. Or hold on. Let me do test drive.
I love it so far. All right. Let's do, first
of all, we got to do the point dance because that's
the most important one. Oh, yeah.
This might be the best one.
How about Raver? That's a good one, too.
I think we need to change the stomach a little.
I'm happy. I need a laugh, too.
He's like a donkey.
I love it. That's fantastic.
Okay. So if he's a scorpion,
scorpions are usually like a beige
color or sometimes a bright orange
and the bright orange ones are the fucking evil ones.
Yeah, the orange, the little
orange ones are the evil ones.
Ooh, that looks kind of cool.
The weird kind of like crusty hands.
He has like deep fried hands.
Hmm. I like it.
Could go red. Ooh.
That's cool looking, too. I like that.
That's my favorite so far. I could do patterns
too, couldn't I? Ooh.
I have to pick a clown.
Not this guy. All right. He's good.
I got to check. The body is going to be a little different.
Let me see. I don't want to ruin this. But don't you feel like
the body needs to be a little thicker right here? Just by a little?
He's down. All right. Yeah, just by a little.
Just a little. And add poison to this, right?
What if I put poison on it? Strike.
Ooh. Stab. Fight.
And you can sing, too.
Make it puke in the test walk. How do you
puke? Ta-da. Flex.
Sumo. Hey. Hey, baby.
Cutie. Happy. Laugh.
Scared. Angry. Swoon.
Sad. Where is it? Where's puke?
Oh. Bounce?
Dizzy. Oh, don't do too much.
Slow down. Sneeze?
That was the cutest thing I've ever seen.
Ballet.
Puke. He just stabbed himself in the head.
Lightning? Whoa!
Zombie walk? Oh my goodness, it's so
weird to control. How about bees?
There's an evil laugh?
I can't wait to hear the evil laugh.
Howl.
Banshee scream. Is this Sandperson?
Twitch.tv? Blast.
This is so cool. Okay. All right.
All right. Let's go. Stop hurting him.
This is acting.
I think he's good to go. I think he's perfect.
Somebody put poison on the tip. Can I even do that?
Wait. I could put spit
on this, right? Couldn't I?
He's got like a muffin on his tail? Hold on.
Okay. Let's have him spit.
It's like a combat. Punch. Oh, he's back here.
Bite. Strike.
Spit. Just goes into the air?
It's got to go to the...
Hold on. There we go. Hold on.
So he has like a poison gland that's right
there that he can just spit poison
at people after stabbing them. It's an anti-air
gun. Put it inside the spike.
Can I do that? Oh, shit!
I almost had it. What was it? Poison
spit. It's the muffin. There it is.
That looks kind of good. That looks really
good, actually. That looks cool. He has a strike.
He's got the charge.
He goes wham, then spit. Poison
spitter. Cool. All right.
He's ready. I don't... herbivore.
Why is he an herbivore? Your creature eats fruit.
No, he doesn't. I want him to eat other people
because he has the mittens and has no teeth.
So I guess with no teeth
and mittens, you're not going to be... So he's
just a murderer. Change his mouth?
I am not going to change this mouth.
I don't care if he eats dirt. Change the...
You want me to change? That's what makes all the
personality from this guy. Add another mouth.
Just like a hidden one underneath here?
All right. This is herbivore. Carnivore.
What if I do this?
This is fucking cursed. This is
cursed. No.
I don't want it. He can eat plants.
Yeah, he looks so much better that
way. Yeah, he can eat plants, but if
anyone fucks with him, he's got to...
You can kill them. Make it really small.
Make it just tiny on his tail.
I guess I could make just a little
little pincer, a little tiny one.
Well, this is carnivore. I could put this
like under here. That would just be kind of like
a little thing under his belly. That doesn't
look terrible. Make it small enough.
That's just like a little addition. That doesn't mess up with his face.
Put it on his nose. Hold on.
I want to see what that looks like.
I cannot put it on his face.
No, you know what? I don't even want it.
I think it messes with the look. I want him
to eat plants. I want him to eat plants.
Yeah, I like him like this.
I don't want him to eat meat.
I want him to kill meat.
Like, I want him to stab meat, but not eat it.
This is a defense mechanism.
Okay, what's his name?
About, uh...
Gorp...Vegan?
Vegan. Vegan Bill.
Vegan Bill?
Is that what you want? Build vegan.
Carnivore Bill. How about, yeah, like
Meat Lover's Bill.
No, no, no, no, no. I'm going to make
a circle. I'm going to make a Meat Lover's Pizza.
Alright, that's the next thing I'm doing. Save it.
Vegan Bill is a new creation. Replace Bill.
Replace Bill.
Okay, how many more should I make? Like, two or three?
This is fun. Alright, I'm going to make it to
Meat Lover's Pizza. This will be quick.
It's just going to be a large Meat Lover's Pizza.
Hmm, this is too thick.
I know what to do. Make a tiny, tiny
body and a big circle head and just put all the pizza
ingredients on his head. Throw it in the spine.
Ah, that's true. Okay.
Alright, so this is good. There we go.
It needs to be a little bit, like, there.
Put this in the oven.
Alright, Meat Lover's Pizza. We need, like, cheese and then sauce.
First of all, let's get the base here.
That looks like a pretty good crust.
But hold on. That looks like a...
That's perfect. That's a perfect, like, pizza crust.
Yup, keeping it.
Okay, now we need
details. What have we got?
Definitely some fucking basil on there.
No, that comes later. That comes after the sauce. What am I doing?
Alright, what, like, pepperonis or something?
What looks the most like pizza?
Ingredients. These, I mean, this could be.
Custom paint?
Do custom paint, custom paint, custom paint.
Hold on. Uh.
Paint like, paint like. How do we do custom paint?
Base. Okay, hold on.
A coat? Coat?
Yes! Nope, this one.
And the detail? Uh.
I don't think we need any detail.
I think that's perfect. We need cheese on it, though.
Um. This kind of looks like cheese,
but it's too much. It has to be on top. There we go.
That's pretty, that's as close
as it's gonna get. Or not, maybe. Hold on.
Mmm. Put black olives on it.
Hold on, we're not, we gotta, just wait.
Change the base color?
Disease pizza. Those spots kind of ruin it, though.
Change the color of the detail and coat.
Nice red pizza sauce.
Actually, that, I, I like the other one better, don't you?
This one, do you think this one's better?
The bright one you think is better? Actually, it probably comes up better.
Alright, detail.
Detail's gotta be white. Mmm.
Cheese. I can hold? Oh, okay.
This is probably close to pizza sauce.
Yeah, look at that. That's perfect.
Take the spots off. Yeah, I'm taking the spots off.
Do you use cheese with something else? Yeah, remove spots.
Fix the crust. Hold on.
Alright, let's go back here.
Now, I, the pizza sauce is up here.
Umm. This could be like a sausage
or something. Oh, fuck yeah, look at this.
Can I make these, uh,
like, pepperoni? Can I make them tiny?
Can I change the color of these? I don't think
I can change the color of those. Of the eyes.
Come on, really? Can't change the eyes?
They're just olives. Yeah, but I need
how many black, black olives
are disgusting on pizza?
All, all olives are like gross.
Alright, that's a lot of olives.
I need some, oh wait, wait, we need like basil.
Actually, I love olive oil. I love it.
So much. Umm, how do I
you hold alt to get just one, right?
How come I can't get one? Hold A.
I'm thinking like here, bring it down,
flat it, oh yeah, twirl it a little bit.
That looks good, so nice and cooked.
And then put it down. That, okay.
Twist it up a bit. Nice.
Looks good, okay. One more?
One more like right here. Get a little more.
Okay, cool. Alright, now we need cheese.
We need, there we go.
This could be like weird cheese. That's kind of
cheesy. What's more cheesy, do you think?
Like this? Flowers could be cheese?
What else we got? Horrible.
Hold on. This could be like mozzarella.
Yeah, that's like a nice mozzarella.
Answer me, you flimsy fuck.
What are you talking about? The armor plates.
Armor plates. That looks like
a nice, that looks like a fucking nice
slop of mozzarella. Oh, fuck yeah.
Perfect. Yeah, it's like a Neapolitan.
I need to move these around a little.
Okay, so let me move these around.
They need to be a little bigger too, because it's like the big
mozzarella circles.
There we go, that's better. This is a meat lovers
pizza with no meat. That's just regular pizza.
You should make the creature flat.
How do I do that though? Can I do that?
Can I squish them? What about the pepperoni?
I need something red. Just flatten
them. Miscellaneous parts from the details.
I need red though.
Wait, that could be, no. Flatten the
armor plates. It's as flat as I can get them.
Actually, it's good that they're different sizes though.
Like mozzarella does that on pizza all the time.
It melts different ways and shit. Oh yeah.
Yup. Yup.
Do we have warts all over it? Okay, how about
if I turn one of these upside down
it might look like a pepperoni.
That just
looks fucking weird. I hated that.
Alright, he has eyes. It's technically olives.
He needs a mouth.
Should just have this.
It's just like a dragon pizza.
Now it's a carnivore. Demon pizza.
And it can sing?
He needs feet. Does he?
Even just little tiny ones that you can't
even see? Oh hooves.
He needs legs. Hold on.
Do you have wings? Just a flying pizza.
That's a good idea. Where are they?
Flying pizza. Wings. Wings. Jump
and sprint. Sprint.
You don't need feet. Feet aren't required.
Okay, well I want him to fly though. This is just
unnerving. Does he need a, I don't think he even
needs a mouth. It looks like a watermelon.
Hold on. I take the mouth away. I mean
I like that better. I'm not sure if I'm
happy completely with it. Mouth is one part
that you actually need. Okay.
Ballet. Oh, that's what it would
look like if you dropped a pizza on the ground.
You know what's funny? I bet you there's a ton of pizza
places that have this pizza with wings
on it. And underneath it it says, We Deliver.
I mean, doesn't it feel like
this would be on the box? A hoedown.
He's flipping the pizza around.
Alright, I think I like him. I think that's good.
Mating call. Make the dough
brown. Hold on.
Let's check here. Brown you say. Hold on.
No, the dough's not brown.
It's like this. It's like a pizza crust.
It looks like a meatball.
This one's better. We go into
yellow. Hold on. That's rotten.
There we go. Perfect. How do I change
his face? Alright, looks good.
What's a dragon term
that starts with P? Meat lovers pizza.
Pizza angel. Aerodactyl.
Where'd the sauce go? When you're
in the building mode it goes away I think.
Wood fired pizza. That's just describing
what this is on the menu. It's not an
animal's name. Pizza Griffin.
Oh my god. Ban that person for at least a
minute. Pizza. Wood fired
pizza.
What are people writing? You're writing
pterodactyl with pepperoni in it?
Pizzadactyl. Pizzadactyl.
Oh god damn it. I clicked out of the
fucking screen. Pizza Griffin is unironically
good. It is not unironically good. It is
unironically awful. I like
pizzadactyl. How do you spell it?
Pizzadactyly. Pizzadactyly.
Pizzadactyl. Pterodactyl.
I've turned into
pterodactyl. I am now
pterodactyl.
And he flies
and smashes right into the side of like
Cleveland's house. And then cuts back to the show.
That's good. I like it. Alright. How many more
should I make? Carrot. We're making a carrot. It's a carrot.
We're making a carrot. And we're gonna make sure that
the carrot and the pizza tribes
hate each other. Why are you so hungry?
I don't know. I just kinda am. What the fuck does a carrot
look like? Like that, right? What the fuck
does a carrot look like? It's like that, right? Yeah.
And there's green up top. Alright, here we go.
What should his face be?
It's just one of the birds from Angry Birds.
Why is everybody freaking out? It looks like a
squash. This is what a carrot
looks like when you pull it out of the ground. What are you talking about?
Give him a scary mouth. I like that.
Let's get the, uh, the, let's get
this correct. Too much spinning. There you go.
Okay, good. Yes!
The cabbage. This guy is so
hungry. Why would, okay, let me
let's get something clear here. If
somebody is like starving and really hungry
and they're on stream, they're a streamer,
you think they would be making a carrot?
No. They would be making like steak
and cheese subs and like hamburgers and stuff.
I make a carrot? A carrot.
You guys think, oh, he's so high right now
and all he can think about is food.
I can't think of one person I've ever seen that's ever been
high and you go, hey Ben, you wanna get some
munchies? Yeah.
How many carrots? I got fucking Doritos
and pizza and fuck, and hamburgers?
You don't wanna, wanna eat a carrot?
I've never heard that before. I've never heard,
somebody's never been high and asked me for a carrot. I'm just
gonna tell you guys the truth, that's never happened.
You know how many times somebody's been over here high
or over my, or like hanging out with me
high in my life and they've gone into
like the pantry and they're like
where are the Doritos?
Where are your carrots? You just get
high all the time. He hangs out with
stoners. Ha! Alright.
This is bullshit.
There's no way that you guys have, this is
a gaslighting campaign.
I don't think there's ever been a point where
one of you was asked for a carrot when you were high.
If you were, ever.
No, you reached for like the fucking beef
jerky and the Dorito bags.
I don't do drugs, Jerma. Well, good for
you, cause don't do them cause they're not that cool.
They're like kind of dumb.
All I'm saying is I've never asked for a
carrot when I was high.
Hey man, you got like any bags of like
iceberg lettuce just plain that I can just reach into
and just eat? That's a base
take. I don't think that's even a
I think that's just like, that's not abnormal.
Don't they have like weird roots all over
them?
Let me go for eyes.
Okay, I like it.
I like it. You made a stoner
carrot.
Does make up the eye of Sauron? No.
I love this carrot guy.
Alright, let me uh, we need
like root legs. Armored bones?
These have to be little. No, not even
no legs, right? This is a carrot.
Does it need a leg? Does it need legs?
This is so scary. I don't think I need to do anything else.
Yeah, I think it's just a carrot.
Does it need anything? It needs a stem.
Carrot? What do you mean? Make a baby click the egg.
Oh, that was cool. Hold down!
I don't think it needs anything. He has a mouth.
He can bite. He can sing.
And he has charm. I'm not doing
anything else. Plat in the top? He's perfect
like this. Living carrot.
I mean ruined. Carrot griffin.
Munchies carrot? Oh, I can't wait to go grab
a carrot out of the fridge.
What about texture? Oh shit, that's right. I think it's
actually kind of, I don't think it needs anything.
I don't think it needs any texture at all. Yeah, that's
just a healthy carrot. Okay.
I'm not going to name a weed carrot.
Kakarot. How about just
snipe? I kind of like snipe.
How about crunchy?
Crunch. Crunch.
Orange crunch. Carrot?
Carrot. Karen.
Crunky. Pella carrot.
Yeah, but all these names like, okay, like
Pizzadactyl, Pella carrot.
These are Pokemon names.
You just say what the
thing looks like and then
what its face looks like.
Like what the thing's body is shaped as
and what its face looks like. You just do two words.
Pelican face, carrot
body. Pella carrot. I like
it. It's fine. So I didn't say
there's nothing wrong with it. Alright, um
Pella carrot is done. I'm going to make
one more or two more. We'll make
really quickly. I'm going to make another creature.
A big one. It's like painting.
I'm just letting it flow. I'm just letting it flow.
It's just flowing right now.
I'm painting. I'm sculpting.
I'm just painting. I'm letting the art speak for itself.
What we got? A bigger
bigger, larger, larger back here.
Okay, good. Bend it
a little. Hilt it up. Letting
the art speak for itself.
Okay.
You're making Gary?
I am not making Gary.
Human feet?
It's going to have really long legs and human feet.
This is gonna be bizarre. No, not thundercats can't go back a little more
I want the human feet on their knees bent a little bit pull this back this walk and a walk like this you can
Okay, but that look I don't like that. I don't like the way it looks just standing up straight. There you go
Okay, should I be even taller taller? Okay. It's just like an a TST make it lean lean back back back back back
I messed it up. There it is. Okay, that's fine. Eyes need to be a little bigger
Okay, good this needs to be bigger too, doesn't it? Mm-hmm. Maybe not. Maybe not. They always have cross eyes
They do do they I fixed it see you made of watering can
It's leaning too much a little too much lean. Okay, that's better. All right. Now, what do we got so far bite?
I think I had this thing's gonna be my nightmares. I know it is. All right. What about arms scrappy?
The question is does have really long arms too. Hmm tiny arms
You think just little little arms out in the front possibly like down here. This thing's creepy. This thing's scary
Isn't it like creepy? This thing's creepy. This thing's really creepy. I feel like it's gonna like lean down and grab me
I'm like, it's freaking me out. Ah
Grab you should have a tail too. Yeah, it should kind of tail. Where are the tails on feet?
Where the tails no tail he's a nose. He's given one of these just one like
like back in like the
1800s and they used to like hold the thing up to their ear. I want to flip it. There we go
Don't you feel like people get that animals are gonna like just throw shit into this ear
I feel like somebody's gonna just like throw a
Crumple a piece of paper in there and it's gonna kill him one ear only. It's he's a death star
Yeah, he is. It's gonna be a little further back though. I got here. There we go. Yeah one weak point
It's an awful link. Is it this is an awful link. It's a great link. Hold on. It's horrible
All right. Well, I'm gonna click it and
Hopefully this wasn't a mistake to click this and look what you've done. Look what you've done. Let's see
Let's see if this is worth it
Hundred million off the dead if you let chat create a creature using click maps. No, no, thanks
No, the answer is no the end. The answer is no and somebody said why not?
I'll be very specific reason why because all you're gonna be able to do is click on the parts
How are you gonna make the shape a hundred million? Give me a break. That's nothing. Let us play you dick
This game's on Steam right now. Play with me play with me play with me play alongside with me. I like that. Ooh
Okay, I like that save it what's the creature's name I hate you why what I do I didn't do anything
What about weapon should it have a weapon?
Spikes on its knees. Ooh
No, I don't like it. Get out of it
That noise too is so scary. They're give him a deadly mustache. Yeah deadly mustache like it. That sounds good
It's like this alien singer from Star Wars. It is it is the alien singer from Star Wars. Oh
Goddamnit. Okay. I need uh, I need a tail. I'm pump porn pump palm. That is so small. It's way too big
That's better. There we go. Okay, that's better extend the spine for the tail
Yeah, but if I extend the spine his eyes will screw up and it'll change the way he looks watch ready
That's all I can do. Okay. I like it. He's ready. There's no difference. That's as far as it'll go too long
Alright, let's take it. Let's test them out in the in the tester. I like it over the call. Alright, what do you think?
Should I start playing don't don't so that do not make one of my own, right?
Don't make one just play the game start the game and play and I make it as it goes don't create one for me
That's how what you want me to do. Um
Sniff like a big long nose
Um, lup lup shit. Oh, everyone's on that. Why glup glup sniff. Oh lup sniff. Oh, not glup
Shit. Oh, that's glup sniff. Oh, is it good Peter sniff it?
All right. What is all this stuff make us big create a sea vehicle create adventure. What is all this stuff?
Economic military vehicle. What is all this shit? Just ignore it. Okay. Are you ready? I gotta pick a world
What do I want to where do I want to start new game new game?
All right, we can go around the galaxy here. Which one should I go to or the top left one up here?
This one looks kind of cool spin it fast. Why the fuck are these people game just fucking crashed. I'm here. Okay good
All right. I'm just gonna go to I'm gonna go to this place. Look at this one
That looks kind of cool
Choose a stage sell stage out at the very beginning nurture your own creation from its humble aquatic origins to its evolution as a sentient
Species in the epic journey of spore or go right to the space stage
Choose your diet herbivore or carnivore. Mmm, I want to eat plants. What do I want to eat meat meat?
How do you eat both? I'm gonna do I'm doing carnivore choose your difficulty normal. What does it matter?
That's what you look like. Okay, normal name you a planet planet of planet of Augustus Augustus
It's a lame
Zoellick, it's not like a germa. Hey, let's yep a traven upper deltine
Orissia
valus
Kate's Melee Taka nephon mirrors
Atreus
Moegas zerk what planet of a zircon on if I see another
Peter earthen if I see another Peter
zircon on
Zircon off. I hate this. I don't want to be on the planet of a zircon off. That's us. That is so
absolutely childish
The planet of zircon off why would the planet be called zircon off you made a pizza
Okay, so we're at what point how do you connect pizza to zerk off?
Zorn craft. I almost just named this pizza zerk. How about like the zircon zircon zircon
zircon of
What's the Marvel one was earth and Marvel? I don't know zircon off
or 900
What's the what's our six one? What?
This is the worst name. I think ever zircon off six one six. It's like the Marvel Earth
It's just the planet is a zircon. Okay done
loud
It's a pretty planet. I love the burples the purple and the orange and the
There I am. There I go
I'm going in don't you have to eat stuff. There I am. I don't know how to play
Welcome to the tide pool
Throat spore the choices you make impact your future as a cell
Your mission is to eat grow and evolve growth is measured in your progress bar below
That's your progress bar as you eat you'll earn DNA points
You may spend these points on new parts to evolve yourself as you progress you grow larger and your world expands
Mmm, you need to get DNA points
Then you spend those DNA points on new parts your carnivore hunt other cells or swim over floating meat to eat it
Eat that eat that why did you not eat that? Oh, I got it. I could eat all these other bugs
So I can't eat both. I can't eat that it doesn't he doesn't like it. Okay. Oh, I just grew up now
I can eat the little grubs watch out other cells and meteor bits are the key to finding new parts
Each part is unique abilities that can benefit your cell
When you see the new part appear swim over the token to collect it the game doesn't have autosave
Please please please you'll fucking lose everything
Makes sure say often make beanbag sonic all right saved game on planet zircan is saved
zircan
Zircan what the fuck okay? I got a new part attack and bite
And I use it call a mate to enter the cell creator. Oh, there's a mate where you and me wait
No, that's not a mate. There's a mate come over here
You can change modes in any creative by clicking on the mode button above before returning to the type will stop by paint mode
Okay, cool too expensive I can bit a spike this is not too expensive the same thing though
I wish I put this attack beak hmm right there on the sides right in the front like that right definitely like that
Right there perfect. Okay. What about paint mode? What should I do spotted hmm? I don't know about that dots
I like that a lot actually yeah, I'm keeping it name your species. Oh shit
About a germa bite there is on cells or break open meteor shards to unlock new parts
Just keep eating is there a quick save button eat eat eat eat no okay look for meteor parts
Oh, I grew up again. I'm with the big boys now. Oh my god. Oh my god. Leave me alone. Oh my god
Well, this dude is so hungry. Holy shit get away from that get away from flowey. What the fuck is that?
I'm going this way. I feel like I'm playing agar.io agar.io that game was I played it for like a couple of days
People would just work together, and I'm gonna die
I'm dead three or four people would just work together and just feed each other what just hurt me eat it ow no
No, get away. I'm dead. Oh, I'm okay. I thought there was no saving and you guys say there was no saving
I need to eat more stuff ow
That's not a save come here come here come here eat eat eat up up up up up all right
I grew a little bit eat all these motherfuckers right now eat them. I'll go that way. I'll go that guy go down
Go that way either. I don't know what all that is, but eat this bee come here. Yes, get away from me
Oh a cell that was a bubble never mind those things alive back there little guy right there. Oh
Never mind you have to defend yourself. I don't have any moves. Oh, they're coming for me
They're coming for me look at that huge claw in the background you have spikes
How do I use them? Holy shit? This thing is huge as a job. Oh, it's a crab
It's a big crab
Ramham ooh
Come over here. This guy's way too slow too slow. He's so slow eat the fuck away from it. This is my food
Evolve can I try to call for a mate you have to evolve so I call for a mate anybody here. Let's go come on
Hurry all right. What do I want to do? I filter you get green you can eat you you get you eat green plant buds
Speed ooh, I got 15. I can do that one probably in the back right like this. Yeah extra speed
And I forward anything else add spikes no, I don't want to add spikes right now
I won't be a little fast make them a little smaller remove the spikes sell the I
sell the I
What are you talking about? I'm doing this. Let's go wait. How much do I get for selling the spikes?
No, I'm just going what I mean listen. I'm not gonna listen to him holding it now. I go faster
There we go. That's better. What are they eating there? We go bigger now run run run run
What's that go to the moon wait? That's one of my friends. I eat my own friends should I eat the right cannibalize?
I got a scavenge get away from me. No get away from me. Why can I save the game?
Oh, I don't think I can kill these guys if I smash into them. You're too fast come here
No, you you you can you literally can
Yeah, I know there's a space part of the game you want to fuck run
Flippers that's mine get away with those flippers go already got them all right
I've seven dollars. That's not enough to mate get away from me get away from me get away from me
No, that's but don't kill that person. I need that person. Let's go ooh fast turns
I need 15 I get another I sell the tail sell the I sell the I sell the spikes
Know that what no sell the tail no I need this for speed don't I make him just have sell the I?
Why did I do that flippers are better are they fast turns and then I've got to get an I again get the I
You fuckers all right. I think that's all right for now make these big you don't need eyes
I don't but that doesn't seem kind of weird that I don't why would I not eat eyes I grazed him shit shit
I'm okay. He missed two
Come here get over here watch out for the octopus. I have ten
What do you just do
Give me that I want that run okay save it here. I can kill you. What is it hard skin?
No, he doesn't come here get over come on eat jet hold on
I know I don't want to evolve yet. I need to get um I need some more points. What the hell
Holy shit, that was terrifying all right keep going kill it stave
stave
Scary I want that meat though. Holy shit. I just stabbed him wait a minute. I'm gonna kill this guy
I'll see
It's hard get me in there. Oh my god. You're gonna bounce me into his mouth aren't you you piece of shit. That's good actor
The meteor to the west I was looking at chat. Sorry. I want full health before I go over there
I know it. I wanted to eat that guy. I know that's east. I know I know I wanted to get health
I have like no health there was a huge guy over here. Where is it the current here? I get come here
I'm going for it. I'm going for it. I don't even care in the eye just stay on his backside
He can't turn fast enough. There's gonna be so much meat. Don't let somebody else kill him gold rock
I saw a gold rock, but this is important gold rock. Oh nice
Spit poison cool. I need to kill this guy though. He's almost dead. It's gonna be a frenzy over here when this thing dies
Oh, man. Oh, man. What's that run run run get this fucking block out of the way? What the hell was that?
Do you see that he's too fat to go through here? Oh, dude. He's still chasing me. He still wants to kill me
Oh come on
How can you fit through here? Okay? I'm safe save it spike him
I'm too afraid you thought you're gonna cut me off. I spiked him in the mouth that hurt all right
I need a mate. Let's evolve. I need a mate. Give me a mate quick
I have so many more things to put on come here. Okay. I have 19 points. I got a jet which is 25
I have a proboproboscis you eat green plants or living cells. Okay. Hold on a minute here
This is the carnivore or this is the this is the omnivore mouth take this mouth off. How much is it 25?
I need a can I get a view his face. It's all the eyes. I can't do a single
It is that should be a little bigger, right? Yeah, I can like spikes back here
I've got 14 which is this is a jet
25 I could get rid of these just the jet faster just faster than this, right? Okay
I don't have any eyes. I need eyes. No eyes. It's fine. Shut up. Okay, don't need eyes. Well, I'm ready
Let's go. So you need eyes eyes are incredibly important. Great eyes are an insanely important
Well, not really though get in there eat up all this shit eat that what do you have a proboscis eat it?
I can't eat that. Why can't eat it? You won't eat it. You can only drink blood something flashed. Give me that
Oh, I'm sucking his blood. All right, I need eyes electric too expensive. Okay, I need eyes
All right, let's go. I like that. Look so
Proboscis you just stick it in the E. I have to pee. I gotta pee real bad
I'll be right back. Take a break. I'm back. How are we?
Rat boy, so I have my mosquito tube. I think I'm ready to go. I have eyes now real strange looking, dude
I'll use the pro. I'll use the eat that. Yep. Whoa
Big puffer fish. I just sit here and snack on these. Holy shit. I can
Come on suck his blood
Nice. All right. Good. Good. Good. Good. I don't eat this meat. I don't eat meat. I just drink blood, right?
That hurt suck him again. Oh, he's he's gone. I drank all his blood. Don't even that that's mine. Oh
Most we're gonna hit legs, aren't I drink yet electric look bottom right history. Oh
Look it. Okay German might eight for plant buds. All right, I gotta eat some more plants anymore
I'm not eating any more meat only plants from now on. Hey, hey, hey, hey relax
What are we doing? All right more plants to sit here and snack on this. This would be perfect. Hey get the fuck
I didn't even want to do that to him. He just like I just killed himself on me
I didn't even want to eat that guy. Nice. All right. How are we doing? All right, we're almost into
Omnivore, I won't eat any more people just plants just pieces of algae. Yeah. Are you kidding me, dude? No
They're working together on me get away from me. They're like tag teaming
Seriously, are we doing almost there more plants stop killing get away from me?
Help no more killing. I just want to eat plants
I just want to eat boogers. There they are call a mate to sell creator. Well, hold on not yet
No, it's not time yet. I thought that was a plant we go save. Okay, you're in brown water now
Yeah, I think I'm getting close. Give me that don't even think about it
Wonder how many more plants I have to eat before I'm considered an omnivore two more up here good
I got to save me so close. I'm so close. What is this drink? I didn't drink a person. Did I get away? Oh
Get away. What's going on? Oh, no, I'm a carnivore
I'm a carnivore and I have a brain now
You're on the path to sentience
When it comes to swimming and sludge you rule the pool when you're ready to stretch your legs in the big wide open click
The advanced button not yet. I need a few more pieces of food. I mean, what do I have to eat?
Just keep eating plants eat like 10 to be safe. Okay, should I evolve before I advance or save the points?
Get away from me. I'll kill you. I'll kill you. I'll kill you if you don't leave me alone. They're ganging up on me
I had to drink its blood
Come on
Press T. I'm an omnivore. Alright, so I'm just gonna go I'm gonna I'm gonna evolve one more time
Wait, just one more just in case save the points. No, no, no
Stop save the points. Okay. Oh god, please. No. Oh god. No. Okay. All right. I'm fine
Sell everything save your points. All right. I'm ready
It's timeline shows a history the actions you've taken during life as a cell
You've established a trait which earns you unique abilities that will benefit your future generations
which path have you chosen goes in the path of the killer and then I've
Rescinded my ways and went up to the path of the omnivore cool
Okay, finish the cell stage and clamor on to the planet's surface. Ooh
Okay, here we go. It's time. It's like an airplane
We got like a mosquito a mosquito person beanbag Sonic
I think I'm gonna make a mosquito person make the fly. How many points does this take 50?
Oh, I only have 70 points. Hold on. I gotta think this through
I need I could get poison spit poison spit like on the head electric or charge
How about electric be a slug with no legs sell the fins sell the jet too. Yeah, that makes sense
Okay, these are just spikes at work. That makes sense. They all 50. They're all the same speed
Okay, just make cubert. It's kind of cute. Actually. He's a little lopsided. I'll fix that. Hold on
He needs to be a little shorter. I don't like how tall he is. He's so cute. It's the Pixar lamp
Well, whatever that's fine. He's got a big proboscis, but whatever it is. Don't give him eyes. The horns good for attacking
I still have 60. What can I do? What else poison spit electric electric on the top of his head electric or spit going electric
Okay, cool. Let me see what it does light charge charm. It's a little light bulb. It is the Pixar lamp
This is jump. Well, this is a mating call. Okay, mating call bite sing mating call bite. Okay, this doesn't do anything
Of course it does you need fins for jump. Hold on. Do I fins for jump fins for jump?
I thought I deleted those I put one fin on my back. It's so ugly
Spit is crucial. Well, I mean how many little how many devices am I gonna have on this guy? He's got a
Stabhorn he's got a glowing egg. He's got fins. He's now as his spitter
Yeah, should I get rid of this and put the spit on this motherfuckers gonna be a utility knife
It just spits on himself. Hold on. I actually kind of like that should be bigger. That's a good size. Okay, he's ready
He's ready. He's good. Let's take a look at the color scheme. He's actually pretty good. I like him. He's cool
All right, let's do it. Reach your stage randomizing data arch types excreting gastrodermical system
Reticulating spines. Oh, we got somebody from Maxis Maxis Maxis Maxis Maxis Maxis. Where am I?
Where are my people? Where are the people that I made? I thought you guys said to make a shitload of people
So they would be in the game. You made that for the tribal stage. Oh
They'll show up low. Okay. Okay. We got out. It's time for us to shine
It is the beginning of a new day and for you a whole new strange and wondrous world
Air fills your lungs as you stretch into your limbs in your new home
dry land
The race to evolve has begun
Good luck. Now you are a creature surrounded by your nest mates to evolve
You would need to meet the other species on this planet and earn DNA earning DNA moves your progress by let's take a look
This far they're really ugly
This bar shows your progress fill it by building relationships with other species by forcing them to become extinct
Here are your objectives as this goal suggests food is critical for your survival
Let's learn how to look around to find some food
Hold on right mouse button to rotate the camera left click on the ground to move your creature. What are they doing?
I found some food. What's that? What's this?
Do you forgot a new part imagine the cool stuff you'd find or even bigger creatures or skeletons?
Click the mating call button below to find your mate into the creature creator
This is where you can change your look and add the parts you found in the world. Cool
Okay, eat fruit or meat. I found fruits. Do they eat too? W A S D. Oh, thank you and jump
All right, he'll happen to this guy
Okay, save the game save save save save and this is a thousand times better than that dumb evolution game
You played and I call them over to eat. All right, go find a new species. All right, I'm gonna go find a species
I found a little frogs
Who's this?
You've met a new species care to make them a friend or foe set your stance and get ready to sing or snarl at your
Found neighbor your stance says whether you will attack or play nice with another creature
Before you interact click on the green button
To make friends or the red button to make dinner then use each ability button
I'm letting the self stages earn you a special ability click this button to use it summon flock. We're doing
Nothing happened. Whoa. Whoa easy easy. There's what there's more who are these people?
All right, I want to be friends. Look at that cool light bulb
What do you think mimic the other creature to impress them? We can say who the fuck are these people who are these things?
I didn't make these well done to the victor go the spoilers you are on your way to a bigger brain and a smarter you
Cool. All right. Hey you let's be friends. Yeah, I can't do that. I'm impressed to
Flurgle to ally Oh
Impressed to flurgle. Let's go over here. I can do that pretty cool, huh? All right, so now I need one more flurgle
What do these guys do impress six moon work deeds to ally once allied with the species you can heal at their nest
I guess I'm impressed them. You just sang the raid song
How do I come here? Look at me. How do I tell these people to leave? Don't be mad. I'm here
I'm we're just hanging out. I just stick my
Mouth in his eye and just suck his blood. Oh fruits. I'm here. I'm look. I'm gonna be your friend. Okay, sing
Ah, we're now friends locate your mate the flurgle all your are your allies. Okay, cool
They care if I eat all their food look at the map. Yeah, there's a home nest locate your mate
I have gonna make a new mate
Consume them. No, I'm going back to the nest. Oh a new eyeball. I'm just gonna find parts to evolve, right?
Should I keep eating fruits? There's another species over here that I haven't seen
I'm gonna check this first blind blind blind blind blind women what I wanted to go down there. You missed bones
I did other there. Oh a big mouth. All right, I'm gonna go back to the nest
I was just pushing you sorry eat some more fruits
Can I bring these back to the nest or is my nest at eating his new species over here?
Oh, it's like weird slugs. Hold on. Hello and press three gum to ally. Okay, come here
Well, you like to sing do you me too interesting oops
Why are you so angry looking? I'm very angry. It's an ultra rare item in front of you. Hold on
Um, there's some grasp. I got arms now your friends. You like me. Okay, go into the ocean
Hold on. I have to make friends with the uh, but these guys and that was their king. What's going on?
Oh, my brain's getting bigger. Is this when I make friends with people and then just like
Destroy them brainpower. You got a little smarter and taking your first step towards sentience
You've earned the ability to entice an ally to join your pack and help you on your adventure
Members of your pack will help you attack or make friends and notice you have room for one
Socialize with an ally and they will join you
Mmm, go to the water save the game. All right, is am I gonna instantly die if I go in here?
I'm not instantly dead. I thought it was gonna kill me. All right, I'm good
I don't want to make that anybody my like this friend yet. Wait, who's that move with the keyboard? I know I'm just
Forgetting I was my mate. I have a mate. I don't even have a mate. What's happening?
It's an ultra rare item in the water. It's called dying. Wait, why that's it with both. Wait, who am I?
Another one just get born. What's happening to them? Oh, okay. We can do a new mode play a test drive
Yep, okay. Well, I'm gonna have a different mouth. Wait, what about one of these weird beaks? This is omnivore mating call bite sing
We're getting rid of the thing in the face bite sing level two sing level two rare parts on other cotton
Okay, and then I got the beak. Okay, I got 71 points left still. What about eyes?
I guess it just depends on what you want to look see should I get hands now? It's 50
But I mean I can have arm. I kind of have to have arms. I have to get arms 100%
Yes, and I need another leg too. Oh, let's pull this forward a little like the leg of the foot a little bigger
Yeah, probably he's quite the evolution in one go here take out the fin. Hold on. I need to make this bigger
There we go. Okay, that's better. There we go. That's a little too much. That's pretty good though. I like that
That's not bad the fin on the arms need a second fin
Okay, that looks good sell the fin and just put it back on the hell's this thing in right?
It is different with the fan. I just was using wait, hold on jump and glide wings wings wings ruined. Hold on
Yeah, let's give him these oh hell yeah, you need social skills. Don't forget that. I know this creature fucking sucks
What's wrong with them man that guy for life
How do you glide? All right, let's go still has one leg. We have to wait to get more than one leg
They're all evolving. Okay, cool to learn charm. That was a great image
Oh, I'm gonna move glide jump mating call learn spit
We're just pooping learn charge
Whoa
Now I own this place you should never have taught me that much that quickly I knew parts
All right. I'm gonna go back to that my friends over here. See if they've evolved. Nope. Not at all
What is somebody just right Goku you have no social skills. What how is I do?
I want to see how the little frog guys are doing the glide the goofiest shit I've ever seen have they evolved
Hi guys, don't be afraid. It's me. It's me. Don't be scared. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Look remember my singing voice
Don't be afraid now what hello friend you've added a creature to your pack
Oh, he's hunting singing or dancing around the meadow you lead they will follow cool. You added the worst partner
I didn't I'm just talking this these people suck
I would I you say that how do you know you've never even made them your friend
You have no idea what they're capable of. They might be very smart consume him. That was my food
All right, let's come with me. We're gonna go meet some new people. All right flurgy
I don't know if I trust the people up here now
I'm gonna have to do all the talking just follow my lead. Hello. It is I be friends with us
Oh, I got some wings. It's Sully and Mike saying don't be afraid of us. Holy shit
Yeah, well, it doesn't
That's not even really accurate though. I mean, it's kind that I just he's a green and I'm blue
That's it. It's the only thing right there now my friends cool. The croon are your allies nice shell shard
All right, let's keep going this way. I can only have one ally and sue Mike. Where'd you go? Where you going?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Whoa, what happened over here? What happened? Stop it. Stop. Stop it. Stop it. Stop spit on what happened
What the fuck happened? Why are you fighting? What did he do? I'm gonna die. We gotta run Mike. Follow me Mike Mike
I don't want to die. I don't want to die. I don't want to die. I don't want to die. What happened? I don't understand
Why do they attack him help help fellow Mike?
What's his name? Help me help do something do something do something
Fight for me fight together. Oh my fucking god, he's gonna die. This is rotten food
They're not still chasing me, right? What the hell was that all about? Why'd that just happen? Really guys? You didn't do anything
You killed his no, I didn't I didn't do anything
That was a fake false alliance and they killed Mike get over here and then it don't attack. What are you crazy?
What happened there kill them for Mike? I know I but I need a new team. I'm not strong enough
I need to go evolve. I'm gonna evolve
I'm gonna add like machine guns to my arms and we're going back there guys. I gotta tell you we got a big problem
There we got a big problem. All right, while we have sex just think really hard about machine guns
It should work both of us at the same time just close your eyes and just just picture like just do machine guns
It's like knives and like bombs and stuff. We'll probably be able to add it. What's this plus two health?
Oh, okay. I mean that second leg it's time for a second leg. I don't think why they start attacking him for what was it?
What was why why they do that? They're all the same speed. Just get this one here. There we go
All right. Now I need some I need more weapons or something mace ball strike plus one level
Okay, what do I have right now? I have bite charge and spit I have a hands pose
Strike strike level two for these grubby grabbers. Yeah. All right. I got punches now very strong punches
Claws. All right. I want to put these up. There we go. Take it out again. Get some new wings
Hold on little feet jump dance speed and health charge level one dance charge level two speed two
I have 71 points left. Oh shit hooves. Yeah, make him into a centaur. Not a bad idea
Actually, not a bad idea. We had 50 right? Yep. This is for Mike
He must have like eaten piece of their food or something. He's too top-heavy
Fall down. He's alright. He's okay. You're making a scorpion again. No, no, no, no
Eventually, I'm gonna put his butt down his head up. So he's a centaur
I think I'm gonna sell the wings and just get hooves again. I think that sounds like good idea. Okay, I do it now
Oh fuck now. He's getting real scary. We go put it down like that. Now you're in big trouble
You're making a unicorn kind of you turning him into
Ludwig
My shiny lose the spit, you know, the spit really is kind of terrible, isn't it?
15 points for it. Just give him claws strike strike. All right. These are already the best I have right? You've never used it
Yeah, just let him fight health plus two
Yeah, put some health on no on the shoulders. There it is. Wait, does that plus health look? Can I do this again?
Will this be more health? All right. Do I have enough for something else jump and charm elf and charm
This is gonna bum. Oh, all right turning into Jax
Well, I'm gonna go kick the shit out of all those people at that nest sell the electric and let's put on
The wings back on sprint and charm. Oh, yeah, he's ready right there. He's ready. Sure my bites ready for battle
That's right. I'm ready. Let's go get him a better mouth. What do I have on right now?
This one is sing two and then bite one. This is bite two. Forget this. No, we're good. All right, let's go
Where are they going? Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. No, we just became the peak species on earth
You can't just leave um, why did we hatch a mic your species is migrating to a new nest follow them to find a mate
And claim a new home base is your mini map help you navigate the world
You can find your nest food in migratory path there. Okay. All right. What's this baby doing here? Oh slash Mike
Too nice. Look at he's pissed. He wants revenge. He wants revenge. Look at him you and me. Let's go follow me
We got a bone to pick with these people down here
In fact, I I don't know what direction they were in but I think they were where were they
Looney Tunes run. All right, let's go mike and let's do it sprint shift save. Oh my god
You're right. Follow the map. Follow the map. Where were they? They were like down here
What is right there good pieces of shit where my friends it's time
That's who are these people and why are they my friend everybody go in and attack
This is for mike who's standing next to us kill everyone. Don't leave anybody alive all of them. Thank you
Other bugs, but what's going on over here?
I'll eat them. This is where we feast. It looks like meat's back on the menu boys
I don't even know why this flock is here. I don't know who these people are stick stick
Wait, I have a stick now. How do I claim this nest is ours here? You want this stick? Oops. I'm sorry
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to that was a bad idea. I'm sorry. I didn't know that's what that did
Don't be angry with me. I'm sorry. No, no, no, no, come here. Come here. Come here. I'm not gonna attack me, right?
Okay. Goodbye. How do I claim this I claim this in the name of mike find the new nest
I need bones. Wait bones bones bones bones claim the one your other guys went to. Okay. Oh, here's the no
I never mind. Ooh, those are new sprint and charge. Is it bones behind too? I didn't see them
Where are the bones up on the hill? I gotta be careful. These are little piggies refill your thirst meter in the ocean
Why does everybody want me to go to the ocean so bad these friendly? I don't know. Let's see alpha blue bee
They're very they're not happy press three blue bee once ala with this piece. You can heal it at their nest
Okay, why is it getting so dark? Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. I'm here. Hey, hey, hey, I'm singing. I'm singing
I'm singing stop biting me. Stop biting me. He's dead. Am I gonna die?
Don't be mad at me. This is a no fly zone
This is a no fly zone
Okay, they're not is he coming over here? Oh, the pigs don't care. Hold on. Hello. Hello
Ooh, that was really really cool. You look cool
We're friends. You don't like dancing. You like that? If he doesn't like it, i'm gonna bite him. Uh, like
Mega mics are like invading this nest right now. Come here mega mics
Come on. We're almost friends
No, why?
My social skills are too low. Am I just a brute?
I need to get pose
Well, i'll come back later. All right. I need to go to the nest that we want. Let me go to the nest
Whoa, oh, they're very angry. No, they cannot be reasoned with just keep going. They're not chasing me, right? Those things are terrifying
All right, we're going to a new nest. Oh there they are fellas. I've come big bones just big bones
Holy shit. They're huge bones over there. Are these guys mad these guys? I can't go over there
These guys are like 40 hp. I can't go over there. What are you? Oh, these guys don't care
Just sprint just go get just you just sprint in there and take it just take it and fly away. Okay
I got it
Help me new friends
I mean you no harm. I just stole something
Hello, I don't have that move but I can shake my bum
You don't like me. It's okay as long as you don't attack on sight
Uh, you're too stupid. I need pose
I don't have pose. No. Okay. Well as long as you don't don't get mad
Don't get mad. I'm just gonna go
He's chasing me
Oh bones you soiled it. Oh, I made it to the new nest. I'm good. What are we doing?
Oh an even bigger nest
You have claimed this nest future generations will be born here cool lots of bones too
Buzz muzzle. All right. I need to evolve. I need to mate. I got a lot of parts. It's a really annoying call
What's the t menu? I am currently in um adaptable
Daffodil creatures have many friends and many enemies. They make choices based on the current situation
Please tell me you will stream this again. That's probably what we're doing tomorrow
Should I pick up a stick and throw it in to like learn about it? Just carry this around
All right, let's mate it's time to mate I want that new face
Come here
Hi waving. Oh a present. I got you a stick present didn't like it. Um, what happened? I'm starving to death
I need to eat food right now go into the ocean for bonds
All right
I'm not ever going in the ocean because so many of you are trying to tell me to go to the ocean
I'm never going in the ocean ever again
Okay, so now I have this bite to sing three what do I have right now bite one
Sing two, okay 150 you can hold tab to get better adjustments
Okay, what about eyes over here? Does this do anything though?
Or is this doesn't look this does anything are you getting more legs or anything or feet? I did. Okay
So I can sell
These and put these on charge three speed three because this stuff this doesn't stack, right? There we go
So that's charge three speed three. What about feet with dance? Yeah, okay feet with dance
Tell these or 25 dance speed dance dance dance dance dance level two
All right these or these
Sneak. Ooh, I feel like these look better on the other like up here. Yeah, they do
Yeah, that looks like it makes more sense. Okay, so far so good. I can't do anything else. I got much much better
Charge and stuff sell the spike now. This is kind of worthless, isn't it? What did this give me charge and health?
Well, it gives me health an extra health doesn't it or is it just worthless?
I need 150 for the new mouth strike two. What do I have right now? I have strike two anyways
Get new eyes sell the mouth. How much does mouth sell for 75? I don't have enough. I need 150
Age two. Oh fuck fight two sing one sell the butt plate
And the wings sell the eyes. That's not enough. Keep the butt plate. You need charm all the shoulder pads
All right. I'm at 150. So this is hold on do I want this guy sing three bite two
or sing two bite three same beak or the uh, or the
nasha dating call
Sing. Okay. Okay. And uh, it's thinner. I hate beak put the beak out all the way we go even more upright
There we are. Perfect. Give him a wider ass spine. Looks like it's having trouble here. All right
That looks all right wide beak, please. Let me say again. All right, that's good. Keep that same texture
What do you think wider? I like this texture. Wait, what about this one? Ooh
That's cool looking. I like that. I'll try this one. He's ready. The legs are tiny. I got it
I got it. There you go. A little a little wide though a little too wide. There we go wider beak
What why do you want it so wide? Why?
Whatever. All right, we're gonna learn some new things here dance
Cool I don't have charm anymore though
1924. All right. I'm bringing I want you to be my new friend. I'm over here. I want the 24
I want the big 24 stop flying away. Where'd you go? 24 stop flying away. Come over here. I need a new ally
I gotta pee again. Everybody else have to pee dance dance again. We're saying which one dance again
All right. Now be my new ally. Ah, we are now friends now. Follow me. I pack there you are
All right, I gotta pee saving it i'll be right back pee time
Hello
What do we got here? What's in this bag? What's in this? I don't even know what this is
I don't know what that is
This is I think this is might be bones in the back. I don't know what this is. I mean i'm gonna eat it
This is a bag on my desk
I think this might be wood. I don't even care. I'm i'm so hungry salted wood. I don't care. This dude ran circles around my
All right. I'm good. Let's go
The first rule of improv is to say bones when you can't think of anything to say
Nothing about that's a really good way to look at it when there's nothing else to say
Just say bones. Hmm. I wonder how accurate that really is. I'm that person out for an hour, by the way
At least all right, let's go
Uh, do we already made we already did this an hour
Cool windows fan art. I don't even use I don't care about my background. I don't care
Why am I speaking with a different accent what's going on? I don't care about my background
All right. Next up. Where are these guys? Oh, they're over there. Can I do that? No, where was that species?
Oh, wait a new group. There's three autos. Hello
We come in peace. Hello autos. Look at that. It was so easy to make friends when you can dance. Very cool
All right, who else how about king auto I can sing wow
Oh, I got they they sneak I can sneak now and I have better dancing. Oops. I'm sorry. It's a broken egg. It's okay
Regular speed. Okay, who else one more you how you doing? Talk to me. I've already impressed
Uh, who do I have? I'm not impressed you sing the auto song. Ooh, what's going on?
evolution bigger brain
More brain power another step towards sentience. Your brain is larger your statue grander your pack now has room for two
Mmm, and are you good?
Mmm, got plenty of eyes, but I think I didn't see you later. You guys were kind of cool for a minute
These guys look pretty interesting. Wait a minute. What's that huge thing?
250 health, uh, can I make that an ally? Can I make that an ally? What the fuck? All right, he's stronger
He's stronger. I'm gonna help him. Hello. I like to sing too. Do you like to dance dance with me dance with me dance with me
No
Come on
Oh, I just made him angry. Oh, no, he's my friend. He's so powerful. He's so powerful. Oh my god
Gronk are your allies?
He's so powerful. He's got 247 health. What's this like stat screen? Is he in the party? Who's in the pack?
Why is the second person in the pack? Is this dead person on the ground? Let's do it again. He's sleeping
Come on. Come on. Come on
Come on
Yes
All right. Now I want you as an ally. He's a really good friend, but got him
Now i'm unstoppable. I've got a wild gronk as a best friend. Look at his body
Look at this
That's insane looking now. You got a tank. I do I have a tank and a dps. Let's just kill these motherfuckers. Let's go
Oh gronk
Oh gronk is unbeatable get in there gronk now we feast gronk attack gronk steal this egg
Boom. Oh shit. We just hit each other in the head. He just hit me
Gronk continue the assault actual psycho
Why I did look at that. I just look at that. Look at this guy
Why am I a psycho? Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. What is this?
What is this guy
Why is there his asteroids?
What what's like what's like the abominable snowman doing here?
You don't like it
No, I don't like it
We can sing
You like that?
No, you don't like it dance again for it singer. We got you. We're friends
Look at that
Sexy beast
I think I want to get okay. Can I get rid of you? Yeah, go home go home. Let me try to get these two huge guys
Talk to me talk to me. There's a food. We got plenty of these people to eat. He still he doesn't understand us
Uh gronk gronk twist his head off. I commanded I commanded I demanded
Thank you gronk. He was your friend. He was not my friend. Oh, wait a minute. We got a scout over here
Oh shit, what did I just see?
We come in peace kill the witness gronk
You scared him. Wait
We can dance
This is I don't like this. All right gronk. Come on gronk. We got where's your nest. Where's the gronk nest?
I kind of want to see it and bring him back to my house. Oh my god. Look at the dna
Holy shit, I have so much dna. Can I wait? Can I mate with the gronk?
Can I bring gronk back here and will they will they mate with him? Look I have a new friend
Hey, isn't he cool? This thing is so cool
Gronk is gonna watch watch him to start eating the eggs
All right. So here we are. I have
This is sprint to charge three. This is sneak for dance for speed three put the sexy beak on. Oh, that's right
Is the sexy beak 250 we're just gonna sell this this is bite. Look at that sing too. Holy shit. Nice
I don't be too extreme. I get tiny. No, I had it. No. No. No, I hate that. There we go. Now
Have I put on the these eyes? Look at these. This is kind of cool. Oh, it looks like he's upside down
It's like a turtle now what we got. Ooh, that's all just speed. It doesn't really matter. Does it? Here we go though
This is strike two. This is strike three, which is better than this. That's not yeah, let's get rid of these
It's strike three on there and my eyes were the best part old eyes old eyes old eyes one. Hold on
Uh, these feet need to be replaced with these ones now. I got these super ones new eyes new eyes
I need charm. Uh human feet human feet. You don't like the new eyes. You guys don't like the new eyes fighter or up here
You guys look you want the old eyes. Really? I'm surprised. I'm really surprised. You guys want the old eyes
And that's all I can do he has personality look because he had eyes on his nose
Doesn't mean he has no personality. I learned a new move right bronc just got bigger. What is this?
Why is my pack have this random guy t-posing save it here. It's an empty slot
Oh, all right. I'm now much stronger than I was before what we got over here. Hey grunk. Hey grunk
Got a pack of shitties over here. What do you say? We go rough them up. Hey grunk. You hungry me hungry
Oh a sharkasaurus, huh? Something you didn't understand. You think you can beat us. Oh fine. Just you want to get we have a whole
Fight grunk fight fight fight fight, please
Kill grunk kill grunk kill relentless good. Thank you
Thank god good job grunk. Good boy. Wrong wrong. We have a problem on the left over here. You fucking attack a grunk
Are you stupid?
Oh my goodness. What an idiot grimer. You're a freeloader. What what having a tough friend makes for your freeloader
You're getting carried. So what you didn't help at all. Yes, I did. I got I almost died
I went in there and almost died. Where is his base go this way? He doesn't have a base. He doesn't okay
Well, I don't fuck with us. Don't fuck with us. You gotta love you 40 health going on here
It was a dude. He danced for some reason let's go get these bones. Come on grunk. Ooh, that's a new uh,
All right, I guess we're taking on the entire nest. I'm gonna i'm getting poisoned to death grunk retreat retreat retreat grunk
Grunk retreat grunk retreat grunk retreat grunk retreat grunk retreat grunk retreat
Where's grunk? Oh, he got hatched again. Thank god
There we go
Rogue grank. Wait, it's a different name
Rogue grank grunk to grank. Wait, if we go see grunk
Is grunk still over there fighting I don't see grunk over there. Okay. Well, i'm not strong now. I'll have 31 health
All right. I need to
Go this way. That's his son. Grank. Where's he going? He's just on his own right now
Oh, right at these reptiles these rug rats reptiles are they hate us. It's okay
Uh, let's sneak on rank free stuff. Oh, they're scared of him. Oh good. Let them abandon the nest
We'll take it. What's he doing? You don't want to fight me. I have I have a grunk
Gang up on if we can kill the grunk. I know we can't
No, you can't
I just like got smarter
I got smarter because I was watching battle and i'm becoming a tactician
wait
Bring big strong grunk everywhere
Never have problem take over every base
Your extra large brain means you can now add a third creature to your pack wrong greg grunk grunk
Grunk killed them all
Nice wiped about the people die without your help
It's gonna be fine
You're an awful party member. I don't think so. I want to get a few more grunks. I'm adaptable. I'm good
All right. I want to let's keep going over here. Come on. Grank got bones
Charm three. Ooh, okay
You're a mite. Oh, I need to put that on just me and a grunk walking around hanging out. You're the little brother
That's fine. I need some new allies too. All right. Hold on. These guys look tough
They look strong. Oh these guys again
Oh these guys again, just get over here. We'll be friends. Look just join our crew
We're singing to you
look
We don't want to hurt you. We just want you to be part of our group
By the way, if you don't impress us, we're going to kill you very simple. Come on
Dance only dance again
Nice bronc really hate to tell you to do this
Oh, they that was sneaky while we were in the middle of doing our little thing. You brought over the entire crew
That was pretty smart. Although we kind of noticed halfway through there. No, they can live
Let's try to make a friend here. These guys look pretty strong
We got they like to sing
more singing
That should do it, right? Hey, there we are. Let's be friends and I want the strongest one to join my group
Which of you is the strongest?
raining
You look pretty strong
Goku
I just read it. I just I didn't say whatever let's see a couple of singing
Oh, we don't have we don't know that move. I don't think they're gonna like us
Okay, charm you fool. Give us another chance
Give us another chance. Give us another chance, please
No, you're too dangerous. No, give us another chance
Like seriously though give us another chance
Singing there. We are shit. We don't know that come on dance again. That's a group
You need more friends to impress them. What you meant to say was
ronk kill
Oh, no, they can live. Oh, this is their base. Is this that group?
Is this the the group of the ones that are scared of us? No, these are different
Those are gronks over there. Are they? No, they're not. What's this guy? What's this guy over here?
They're sneaking over here. What is that? What do you think you're doing?
You just snuck over here. You guys want to be friends. I have to be friends with the rats. All right
All right. I hope you guys like to dance
No, they do charm
These are they're cool looking though
Singing we do singing too. Damn it. One more chance dance. This might do it. Let me close
Oh your friend a baby. Come here. I need to be friends with you guys. I want two allies
No, what the fuck? Where you going? Someone flock. Does everybody know what this even means and where they're coming from?
Why are these guys my flock i've never met them before it's your alt this is stupid
Hooray
We are friends. All right. Now i'm gonna have a couple of allies. I want some rat allies. You look big and strong
What's your name? You're an alpha
dance
Should do it. It did. All right one more. How about fucking kidding me? What a fucking idiot
What was that? Why did you do that? What was that for? It was a very dumb idea. I just walked in
uninvited
And I did kill one of his friends, but there's like 15 of us here
gta mugger
They're really bad like that. I just somebody just tried to pull me out of my car in gta
Oh, wait a minute. Wait a minute
Really the alpha is here. Huh? Would you look at that?
Okay
Hmm. I think i'll have a snack
That really really tender and crispy today. Oh, it's so good. It's like the best thing i've ever eaten. I think in my life
Oh all gone all gone
gronk
It's a kermit the frog
Okay. All right. Come here. Oh, you have to die then you have you have to die. You're dead. You have to die
Unto one. Oh, I gotta hunt these cool. All right, let's get some uh, let's get a couple allies. Let's take an alpha
You want to come with me?
Need two more. I'm almost up to um
The other phase right there's a baby. You just ate a baby
We're out in the wild guys. What do you want me to say? All right, we got an ally
Join us the eyeball. All right, who's uh, we need another alpha
Alpha you're with us already, right?
No, are you not with us? No, you're not come with us. Save the game
Oh shit, here they come. Are they invading? They're invading. These guys are invading. Are they invading? These guys are invading
Get out of here. Are you invading? Is this an invasion?
What oh I have to kill that that's mine kill us kill it we need this got it
He just went brah
What was that? What's that? What's going on? What's that sound? What was that? What's good? What the fuck is that thing?
What is that? What is that? Why is there a flying ship over here?
They're not gonna land over here. Are they?
Where'd it go?
What the hell?
It's just floating above us. It's floating above us. It's gonna abduct us. It's gonna abduct somebody
Everybody run for your life. It's gonna abduct us
It's my turn
Um, I think it's time to leave
Gronk get out now Gronk. Don't get Gronk. Don't get Gronk take some anybody else but Gronk take me take me instead
Just don't take Gronk
Gone. Okay. Well, I need another friend. The other one got abducted. I need an alpha. They know alphas. Oh
He took the alpha. Okay. Well, we'll take this one. He's like weirdos his cubits over here
Alright, I got a group now. I got a party. I could go evolve too couldn't I?
Let's move. We need to eat though. I have to eat something. Any dead bodies for the dead bodies seat. That's freaking out
Oh shit. Oh friend friend friend friend a new friend a new friend a new friend a new friend a new friend a new friend
A new friend. He's got two in for the health. He's a bug big fish person. What the fuck are you thinking?
What are you thinking? Get him. Eat. Don't attack. Don't attack. Let's see if we can be friends with this thing
Impress the porcoo. Hey, what's that? Get the fuck out of here
You shitty little
dinosaurs from Jurassic Park that everybody eats
They're literally like the school of fish in Jurassic Park that everybody eats. Help him. Help him. Help kill him
Got him cornered interrogate him. All right, everybody eat up. You see what we go care for the love. Oh my goodness
That was really good. Wow. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, don't do that. Don't do it
Oh, he's eating. Okay. He's scared. All right, come here. Let's try this again. You like us call the flock
I'm gonna call the flock. Here comes a bunch of bugs
He's gonna like us. I think so
He we're not gonna even do the thing. He's doing we're still gonna impress him. Here we go
We have another huge guy as a friend. We have the dad from dinosaurs
All right now be in the all right. I got to get rid of one of the rats go home rat. We're gonna be unstoppable
Yeah, you're level 15. Are you kidding me? You're gonna kill you
Fuck these little
Mutant things get over here
I'm trying to impress somebody. What the fuck he killed. It was bullshit. No, don't run away
It's the last hole with 15 health pack of mosquitoes. Just came over and bit somebody. Come on get out of here
Join the group. Thank you new ally get him in the party
Nice
All right. Now I am actually unstoppable
Eat up. I haven't actually come here. I have a room for a rat
All right, don't be afraid. It's okay. We've got two huge guys now. What a mistake that was nice job
I suggest you run now. Oh, hey, do I do I
Where'd you come from village folks? I have three posse members from different species. Oh cool. All right, we're good save it here
I gotta go back and evolve. We'll get how many points I have back to the base. We all run really fast
Yeah, toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat
I win wait for everybody else save the points save the points
I guess I could because of the I'm about to evolve right about to go to the next stage. Don't save the points
It's irrelevant. Okay, just spend them. It's irrelevant. All right, well then I'm gonna spend them. They don't roll over
They don't roll over. All right. Well, I'm gonna do a last evolution. Hi guys. Let's do it. We're not all gonna do this
Well, I don't know very much about sex do I I don't really know very much about it give us some privacy get out of here
Okay, here we go final upgrade I could keep the beak or I could go on to
um
He's kind of aren't that good. I could change the squidward eyes or no what Gary I need charm and pose. That's right
That's a priority right for wait. Hold on charm and pose charm level 3 health level 3
Yeah, put the germamite on here the butt thing back on. Okay, that's charm level 3 and this is a we need pose
L for I have any pose. I don't think I have anything that's pose hands. Oh is all here we go. Okay
pose
Strike one and pose one. What the hell do I care? I have I have a crunk. This is like a pose to wings
Let's see jump glide jump glide. Ooh
Okay, he's posed. No am okay. I don't really like these. It's who did I do dragon?
Yeah, too much to dragon make them bigger. I can't that's as big as I can get
Is your last time to change how your creature actually looks make sure you're satisfied. Okay, good call. All right
So I need this is charge for whether I have the human feet on dance for char
Okay, replace these and then I need to pose hands. That's all I have
What do I have I have strike strike three right now, but I've charged for and bite three
Yeah, and I got a grunk. So it doesn't matter stats don't matter anymore. That's don't matter
We want you don't use stats anymore. That doesn't matter anymore
Just make my guy look cool making the way that I wanted looks that's don't matter
You don't need stats next stage. Oh, okay. Actually, I'm kind of happy with this
Maybe you stand make stand up a little straighter then a little taller a little thicker health matters health matters
Okay, health matters health matters plus three health level three. I need level four health health matters
Well, I have the germite on the back. Do I have a health for I do okay charm or just get health health wings and spit
Matters, okay. Well, I got the wings. I just sell this and get this one delete the back legs
It what looks cool. You have Gronk. Nothing matters. What do you hate health? No changing him after
Hmm. Is it time to get rid of these stupid eyes change appearance through a whole game? Oh, okay
What are you guys talking about? It looks you spread out. I don't want that spread out
Don't you think so? They're a little too spread out. They're too spread out. There we go. Okay
I think I'm good only two legs, which ones are the important ones speed and I'm up on two legs
No, keep all keep four legs. All right. Well, I'm keeping them and pose doesn't matter. So um, this is good
I'm good with this. Maybe brought in the chest a little more. There we go. That's good. What chin
No, he looks like shit a little bit wider wider and then that's not the ultimate being we're good
Get spit get spit get spit get spit. Okay is a
spit level
Two right here. I mean, I'm not gonna put it there. I don't really have another place for it though
They don't do it coward. Oh, I'm such a coward. I won't give him spitting nipples or like a
Okay, sure. I'm a coward. It's gonna go here. I mean that kind it has to be there hide it under the beak armpits
spitting armpits
Imagine just lifting your arm up and all right. He's ready. He's ready nipples or penis. Take your pick
How about armpits match the feet, please? No, I need this for the speed and the extra agility fix the ankles, please
They're a little fucked up. You're right. I think it looks good. I think we're ready. That's don't matter fix the feet
Well, sorry, I'm gonna do two human feet then there you go. All right, he's ready disgusting disgusting
Here we go. This is a guy's toucan Sam. He kind of does look like toucan Sam. There they go. Oh
Hey, cool. There they are. Hey, save save your species of migrant doing a nest fall into a maiden
Yeah, I'm pretty close to evolving the next stage. We're all good to go. All right, let's move his Gronk
He's right there. Oh, yeah Gronk rank rank Gronk is weak. No, this is this is the Gronk was the last one
This is rank. Remember this is the second one. No more sprint
Oh that sucks said to the new nest and then I should have enough to keep going by the wings goofy as shit ever
The kangaroos. Let's make friends with the kangaroos. He's never gonna get to the ocean. Yes. I am who cares
That's gonna be enough best friends. Well, I'm ready to go. I can do it, right? I can do it
I can go for it. It wasn't enough kill them all literally kill every single person here
Wait, hold on coconuts. I want to let's do it again. So we're made of their potatoes
We still haven't seen the pizza. We've seen any of the things I've made just killed him. No, why would I do that?
Yes, meet us in the middle. Come on. I just want to evolve. Yes. Our brain is now huge too big
Congratulations, your brain is fully grown and bursting at the seams get ready to evolve to the tribal stage
You've made it to the top of the food chain when you're ready to give tribal life try click the advanced button
Here to form a tribe
You'll have one last trip to the crater so you can finalize your look for all time
It's your last chance to add arms. They are helpful when carrying tools still adaptable
Let me I gotta impress one more person ocean ocean. All right, I'm gonna go look in the ocean
Well, who needs to be impressed you I will go I will save and I will go in the ocean
I promise I will get in the ocean thing sing to them
Come on day first muck ass. I will did I mess this up already? How do they mess this up?
Oh, we're good. All right 21 DNA. Oh
That's uh, that's the best human feet you can get right that's the best human feed that exists
Okay, go check the ocean. Sure. Let's go to the ocean. I'll go look in the ocean. Okay, let's go. Yes. Yes
Yes, yes. Yes. Whoa. I need one of these is a friend. What are the new nest? Hold on. I don't know space
I have to get rid of somebody
I have to get rid of I can't get rid of the giant rat. I just want to be friends with them though
All right, that's gonna be friends. You have to I can't I these guys are so strong
Keep the rat fuck the spiky guy. He's got 250 health and he's the strongest guy on the team harvest the beef
Not like that. Well, we'll try again. What do you come here? Where's the big one? There you go
God, just somebody give me a wind force with strafe on it and just
Don't kill the king while I'm in there. I'll be real mad about it. Nobody even on half. You don't even know what the fuck I'm talking about
Remember they want you to pose you dumb stupid dipshit. I know I don't have photos. I'm getting very mad at you. Hey settled
I don't have pose. I didn't buy it. I worked on offense only
Why because I wanted to I don't know I wanted to I wanted to kill I wanted to kill and take over
With my group of murderers
Stop dancing for them. I need to
RNG will play in my favor and they'll start to sing trust me or we'll just we'll just kill them
Flock is here. Let's go
weird guys
All right, let's do it
Copy and paste this copy and paste this if you keep the rat you can have him as a pet
Why does everybody have to interrupt this shit? I think you're just not gonna win. Why are you gonna?
Know why don't we defend this for a second? There it is. There we go. One more one more one more one more
It'll be you. I think this is so terrific copy copy copy. If you keep the cow
You can have him as a pet and eat his eggs. Okay. Well weird that's gross. I don't want to do that and
Best friends the best friends. All right, who am I getting rid of?
I feel like porcupine guy was cool for a while, but I really think we need a cow. I have to have a cow
Porcupine guy was really cool. He's very strong, but he's no gronk and he's no giant rat Dave after the cow
No, get rid of the rat Dave agree get the rat. Oh, we need to pull no no
Dave after cow what Dave after the cow? What are you talking about? Go to the ocean you simple-minded freak
Look, I know I'm gonna walk in the ocean and my games gonna crash and it's gonna corrupt my fucking save file or something
I know so badly you want to ruin this game
You so badly wanted me to go into the ocean and like die and have the game crash
You want like take me to get sucked into the ocean and have everybody die. I got to get it
I'm getting rid of him. I want a cow. All I need is gronk. Gronk is literally all I need is the crew
Spike guy is better than gronk. What did what did you just say? Why did you just say that?
I'm so fucking I'm shocked that somebody would say that run him into a geyser. Here we go. Here's the Wizard of Oz
Oh
Let's go this way follow the yellow brick road follow the yellow brick road
Just follow the yellow brick road and we will find
We're okay
This rat dead
Why did this happen? Why did this happen? Why did this happen? Get the fuck out of here?
Why did that happen? No, don't ow. I'm a mating call. I need to eat
Reload reload reload. I'm gonna reload after I go in the ocean. Okay, here we go. Let's go in the ocean
Cool. All right. There it is. You got to see it
You get the same thing you wanted to see the whole time because you wanted the whole time for almost five hours
How I load don't save all progress will be lost. Wait, don't save right? Yeah, this is the main menu, right?
Let's just get out of here. That's worded real weirdly. That's worded weirdly all
Progress will be lost. So you what? Why are you saying that?
Alright, let's go. Alright, here we are. We're good. It's time for us to progress. I guess I could level up one more time
Alright, goodbye. I'm missing clowns
Bye clowns
You sneak we could sneak couldn't we? Why is the cow not sneaking? We just startled him
Just click the button. Alright, here we go. Three two one go
Your actions as a creature have earned another trait that defines your species new unique abilities await you in the tribal stage
Adaptable very cool final stage. I'm not sure if there's anything I really need to change here
Cuz I already did this you could get the final feat but I can only do one
Sneak and dance our back our back feet
You were the final wings which one actually carries over in matters at all
Keep the human feet stats didn't so stats do not matter at all. Nothing. None of this matters. Okay, so I want the better wings
I don't like these. Yeah, those are much more majestic
There we go. That's much more majestic
Only speed and weapons will carry over. Okay. Well none
Nothing gives me speed here strike five eat give speed these ones don't sneak dance and speed
Oh, yes, they do. Oh shit. Leave one fucking dollar. Okay, cool
Fuck the spit sell your sell the body spit matters the spit matters. Just wait a second
Don't need four legs, you know, that's true at this point
I don't need these feet anymore so I can sell the I can just stand up we can go full stand up
Yeah, let's stand up. Let's go
Here he goes by pedal. We got it and slim him down a little except for down here thigh gap
What is too big? That's pretty good. I'm kind of happy with this
We can involve that away and make it a tail. They make a front tail. Yeah, that's a good idea
I'll do that right now. Okay. Now I have some money
What about the face if stats don't matter then we're looking for health
It's the highest health I have all right eat gross feet gross feet gross stop
But the wings at shoulder height put one wing health speed sneak and spit are good while I have glide
Sneak five sing for five dance rotate the wings
There we go
That's run just to make sure kind of a fucked up walk at the better legs. I'm losing my mind
All right, hold on man. Let me the better legs. These are just speed one. They're all speed one. They look better
I could just they're like crab legs. Look two legs even come out from like here actually kind of good
Oh much worse. They look like melted plastic and then I need the feet. Yeah, it's a little too long
That's a little too long. Don't you think his torso is really long?
Ultimate being I just like squished him a little and now he's all right
Hold on the complete evolution is finished that this looks so out of place
No, that looks like he's wearing a mask or something. There we go
And he's like a little hat or something a little a little hat. No don't like it
I somehow made him look even worse. It's the eyes the eyes gonna change and he's like tilt them. That's better. Okay, good
All right, he's fucking stacked spine needs to be a little more aligned this way. There it is. Perfect. That's it
What about his final?
His final color scheme. So, let's see what we got. Whoa. Whoa
Geez, okay, that's they're giving like the patches need thumbs
Didn't have thumbs I kind of like the stuffed animal look
This is like a muscle tissue get thumbs. Holy shit. This is disgusting. Mmm. What about this one? This one's not bad
That's kind of German on eight five colors. I guess we could make it ourselves, right?
That's a good German on eight five base. Okay, where's green more green? No more teal right here
I need teal and then the coat is gonna be see I've been load and in the detail you just have fucking chicken
I know it is
I
Just purple too in there. That's why you want my logo even look like you're a fake fan
This is like too much though. Let me go back to the base. This is like too much. It's like a light. Hold on
That's my fucking logo lives in my logo look like it's more red than pink your fake fan
Oh, let me see. Hey, you know what? This has to be like a light pink and then make the green the accent
Oh, there it is. Okay, it's like no it is. That's correct. Okay, that was right. It's like this color arms pit arms pit
I don't need it. Go to the ocean god. You're getting old
What are you talking about? What are you? Oh, so what's that supposed to mean at a cool design? Yeah, this is like boring design
I need a cool design wear hats later. Get rid of the horn spots. Oh, okay. I kind of like that
I think he's ready. He's ready keep the horn you fucking behemoth the horns stay in I could put a hat on top of it
It's fine. I'm a better pair of arms. Let me see what we got
Do these two points? Let's put on the Delta points. Nice. These are sick. Yeah Delta points
He's look like shit. Never mind. There we go. I like it. All right. I'm ready. I did it
We're good to go and what I mean by good to go
I mean, we're about to turn the stream off streams over see you guys tomorrow
We'll pick up tomorrow at the tribal stage but this guy and his family five-hour Andy
It's me five-hour Andy you could be any fix the beak. There's a clipping. Well, we'll remind me that's where we'll fix it
Well, we'll just say hold on I saved and exited
We're gonna get this cutscene probably then I'm gonna save it and we'll leave they look like a fucking toothpaste mascot
It's the exact colors of like Crest toothpaste, isn't it? Same exact color scheme. You literally ruined it. You can't change it anymore
I can't this creature is a dumbass. Is this creature a dumbass?
Yeah, sure. I guess the beak is fucked up. They stand out so much to
raspberry flavored gummy worms
Got it. That's exactly what this is
Congratulations, you're about to enter the tribal stage. Oh, I do know I do know those old-school gummy worms
Mm-hmm
Tribal stage. Where am I?
Where am I? Where are they? I may I spent like two and a half hours making creatures and we haven't seen any
The roof over your head and fire at your fingertips you enter the age of hand tools and trumpets
But beware soon rival tribes or form across the globe be vigilant
You now command a burgeoning tribe of three
You may select individual tribe members or a group to do your bidding
You must interact with the other tribes to move your progress bar forward. Let's take a look
This is your progress bar. You must ally or conquer other tribes to
Holy shit. Those are huge advance your own these goals will help guide you through tribal life
Your first task is to dress your tribe in the new tribal outfitter check click on your hut
Those are the guys are huge. All right, hold on save it. I can't save it. I have to do this first
Okay tribal planner
Click on the hat icon to open the tribe member panel roll over your tribe member
Click on the edit outfit button to enter the tribal outfitter. Okay, I will outfit. Okay. How many points do I have?
I want armor first
Body ages this is ten. There we go. Okay
symbol
Spore gears was this mustache a ring
elf social
Gathering social and gathering now. I know what you mean by he shouldn't have the horn. This is a huge hat
Okay, I need a mask combat and social social
Um, this is not gonna fit anywhere. Okay, I did I need this how much I have combat social or health
gathering and then I'll do a
Mustache and
Rings, okay rings here
How about rings here and I don't know rings on the wrists. I don't know like this one more and a feather over
Um on here, I think it's good a cock ring on one
You cannot move the camera freely around the world
This helps you check in on tribe members or groups to whom you have given orders
Let's pause for a moment and learn the basic camera controls. We get RTS now
Yeah, these controls allow you to zoom and rotate the camera. Sure your mouse wheel can also zoom and rotate
Let's try that Oh left and right mouse button and whatever that rotates the camera
This is in and out use the arrow keys or click the right mouse button to pan the camera. Mm-hmm
Good click on the hut icon on the mini-map to focus the camera back on your tribe
Your tribe members portrait in the tribal is to select an individual click and drag a box around multiple tribe members
And yeah, you can do that and RTS. Let's begin to find some food. Okay, save it. You guys said Gronk was gone
No, he's not I got a rat I got a cow and I got a grunt perfect
All right. I'll see you guys tomorrow start probably on the same time. So around 430 or so Pacific. Thanks for watching
We'll see you tomorrow. We'll pick up right here and do the tribe stage and then we'll do probably the space stage
Right. Sounds like a plan to me. Thanks everybody. Here come the subscriptions all the subs today. Thank you. Everybody. Appreciate you appreciate the
Continued insane support this channel gets some like I told you a lot of times
I kind of just don't understand sometimes and I can't believe it. Thank you though. Appreciate it raid. Yeah, we'll write tonight
We'll go somewhere and the pigment pole. That's a good a point really good point. All right, I'm gonna play after spore
I'm gonna play Pikmin. That's not as rare to find as thousand-year-do apparently
So am I gonna start what am I what am I because here's I'm gonna tell you the truth
I'm probably not gonna play all the Pikmin's. We're probably just gonna do one
I don't think I'm gonna aren't they all very very similar. I'm probably gonna play one of them, right?
I don't think I want to play all three or four Pikmin games or maybe we'll I don't know
Which one am I starting with because if I love the one that I play I might be so engrossed
I might play the other ones which one Pikmin 1
Pikmin 2 or
Pikmin 3 is there even a was there a fourth one their fourth game? No, it's just one two and three
This is important. This is very important
I'm gonna let you guys decide this because I really don't know if I want to do like Pikmin 1 Pikmin 2 and then
Pikmin 3 I feel like it's a lot of this a lot similar content similar game
What do you think is after I play spore and we finish that tomorrow
I'm gonna play one. I'm whatever one you decide for me to start with is he not playing paper Mario
I am playing paper Mario still I just have to get it
It's a lot rarer than I thought it was gonna be you want to vote on that. There it is
You also promised you kooza. Oh, I know
You kooza will be coming back. Apparently Pikmin 2 is winning by a very large margin
Seems to be an unreachable margin at this point. You also promised Mega Man Legends 2
Yeah, then I have promised a lot of things. You're right. You promised rage 2. I don't think I ever did I
Know I've never played rage one. Why would I promise rage 2? All right, we're gonna play Pikmin 2
I'm gonna stop just gonna play that one and if I love it and I'll play the other ones, of course
Okay, what if I play it in turns out to be one of my favorite franchises ever, of course
I'm gonna want to play the other two. We'll find out. We'll see you tomorrow for more spore on the same time and
Let's uh, who we gonna raid
Raid somebody take a look
Hmm
see
See okay, I'm okay raid Jerry Seinfeld
Alright, we'll see you tomorrow. Go say hello to Sarkis playing Darkwood. I scrolled through and saw people playing and Darkwood
I played Darkwood and you saw me play it was kind of interested in see how he does
See you guys tomorrow. Take care, buddy. Have a good night