Uh, somebody said, wouldn't it be funny if we could collectively all not chat during the beginning of the stream and freak them out?
You guys are coordinated.
You're not that coordinated.
It'd be impossible.
Somebody would take that opportunity to make sure that they were the only person in chat.
By the way, three thousand of them are gonna have that exact same idea.
It'll never happen.
Start to chant? What's to chant?
Oh, yeah, but it doesn't matter. Look.
Anyways, hi. Hope you- hi. What was that?
Anyways, hi. How are you? How's everybody doing?
Uh, today we're gonna do something I've been putting off for the last like three and a half weeks.
This was actually a stream I was gonna do
before the dollhouse stream, I believe. Or very very soon right after it.
But I didn't want to just be the Sims guy.
Oh, I did. I played the Sims before the dollhouse stream and here back after the dollhouse stream. Gonna play the Sims again.
Uh, so I figured I'd hold on to it for a little bit.
But uh, this is gonna be pretty interesting, I hope.
Last time we did this,
um, I may have given myself a hernia
in The Sims 4.
There's a specific point in time that I remember.
And that is laughing at a dog, uh, peeing in the house. The guy took a- the guy was on drugs.
Took his dog for a walk in his house.
Um, and that was the hardest I've ever laughed in my whole life.
I really think so. That was one of those times where I was laughing so hard
that
like the world collapses around you and you want to get out so bad. You want to pull the plug so bad,
but you can't.
You know what I'm talking about? Sure, you guys have heard me laugh on this channel, like
I have control there.
When you get into one of those laughing fits where you're out of control
and you're not in- you're not in control of your own body at all.
Like laughing is just like, please, I want it to stop. I would like for this to stop, please.
But it doesn't. It- nothing helps it.
Um, that happened during the guy walks his dog in his house routine.
Uh, it may have given me a hernia. So, hernia part two incoming maybe.
I don't- that's not confirmed by the way. I don't know if that really happened. I'm just saying it is.
Um, but this is Sims 3, not The Sims 4.
Hey, thank you. Why, honey, for the 10 communities up? Oh, I didn't even tweet. What the fuck?
Oh, yeah, I did. No, I didn't. I didn't press the button.
There we go. But, uh, this one's a little different because
this one has a mod.
I don't know how this is gonna work out.
But I guess- should I even spoil it? I don't know.
Oh, like the world can end. If I just start playing and all of a sudden the world ends, that's gonna be kind of
a waste of time.
Oh, I don't have any sex mods. Spoilers, dude. Why hasn't it even happened yet?
Why would you want?
Losing viewers. I just started the stream. You know, no one's gonna just leave because there's no
woohoo mod.
Hey, crush lizard. Thanks for 20 community subs. Holy shit.
Thank you. That's a lot. Thank you.
Download them. No.
I also, uh, got on this one, which is-
I may have overdone it a little bit. I got that, um, like total complete control mod that's on the sims 3.
You can edit the actual creative sim file thing
and change the body sliders to be like times 5000.
I- it's- that's active right now. It may be too much.
And you'll see why in about 30 seconds.
But I'm just- I'm just waiting. I'm waiting for people to trickle in.
It's so much that it's- it's not even funny.
You can do it so far that the person turns into,
um,
I don't even know. They turn to like their own like solar system.
Not the slider mods.
What about the drugs mod? There is no drugs mod for sims 3.
I don't- at least not one that you can actually use.
I think there's drug paraphernalia you can put in.
But-
And by the way, I haven't really tested these. I did- I tested all of them like three and a half weeks ago.
But I don't know. I'm gonna be very surprised by you guys because I just put a shit load of stuff in here.
I don't even remember what's in here.
I- I mean, it's- I don't know what's gonna happen. I forget what's in here.
Hopefully I didn't add like a sex mod like as a joke for myself.
Okay, hold on.
Let's- let's like- let's go back here because
It's a joke.
All right, you know what I meant by that though? Like, oh just-
I definitely didn't. I'm certain of that because it pops up at the beginning that says every- all the scripts that are installed.
And it's like, oh you don't- you've got like this, this, this, this, this. None of them were on there. Don't worry.
Oh, it was just- it was just for a joke.
All right, here we go.
I think there's enough people here. We can just kind of go for it.
And...
Hello?
Hello? Oh, there it is. All right, so, uh,
Let's just, very, very quickly,
I just got in to make sure we were ready because it takes- when you have mods, it takes a long time to load the game.
Where's the music? I've been in the menu for too long. Uh, let's just go ahead and show you what can happen here if I do this.
Oh! Oh!
To the point where it doesn't- it doesn't make any sense. They turn into- they turn into like an N64 polygon.
You can make it huge. But look at- look at how far these bars go. I may- I- I over did it a lot.
Somebody just gave a shitload of subs and it immediately got removed. What was it?
Autumn just gave five subs. So somebody just gave a shitload. Who just gave that?
All right, so we have to- I gotta figure out what I want to do here. What do I want to do?
Oh, it's nuclear waffle. Okay, 50 subs. Holy shit, nuclear waffle. Jesus.
Okay, one thing that's important, too, is I know- look,
people are gonna think this is really funny, and I do, too.
Uh, take a look at this.
This is a baby. You can- it's pretty much- you can do anything.
It's- it's too extreme, but we can make a weird baby.
I kind of want like a huge chin baby. You- it can go as far down or- oh my god. My god, I already like it.
Under-
It's turning into the scream face. All right. No, okay. I'm gonna make somebody- I'm gonna make somebody a urinal.
All right. All right. All right. All right. Everybody relax. I'm gonna make a urinal.
It's gonna- the name's gonna be like Bob Urinal. Okay, not the- it's not the baby, though. I'm gonna make a urinal.
Go back. It's basics.
Okay, this guy's name is gonna be like, uh, I don't know, urinal. I'll work on- look, I gotta do this one at a time.
I don't even know what family this is.
I gotta change this a little bit. It needs to be a urinal.
Let's start- the mu- there's no music. This makes this way creepier than it has to be. It's probably wider than that, right?
That looks all right. I need a family name.
What about music? I was in the menu for too long, that's why.
The head needs to be- this has to be lower, and this has to be longer.
And actually, this needs to be wider, too. Hold on. Not that wide.
That's way too much. That's pretty good. A little bit more. Make this guy's name urine Earl.
I put his head- now this part of his face has to be a little wider, too.
Like that. All right, does anybody else- does anybody else hope that, like, fucking
Gary Urinal dies first?
Urine Earl. Now, that's to be in, like that. Okay, that's better.
This needs to be way wa- way taller. Hold on. Cheek. Face height. Here we go.
Holy shit. Oh, oh, I don't like this.
I hate this. It looks like it's Quagmire.
Are urinals anon- yeah, that's okay. It's not Quagmire. I'll fix it. What about his ears?
What the fuck? Ears orbit? Oh, they can spin around. Ears point?
I'm just making an orc.
Okay, I kind of like it. I don't hate it. Oh, what's his name? From Jack and Dexter.
No, from Ratchet and Clank. What's his name? Do you know the one I'm talking about? What's his name?
What's his name? Which one is it? It's one of them. No, not Baby Yoda. What- Ratchet. Yeah, there it is.
This is Ratchet from Ratchet and Clank. Ratchet urinal. I like it. I need to like look up- oh my god.
Do I have this wrong? Ratchet and Clank. And Clank. This is what I'm thinking of, right? Yes, it is.
Of course it is. That's Ratchet from Ratchet and Clank. What about the- hold on. The eyes.
Eyebrows. I like that. I need- I need some- I need the music back. This feels weird that you're
watching me do this without the music. The music makes this fine. How about right there? What is it?
Orc. It's a chihuahua? It's not a chihuahua. Oh, I like the flat. Yeah. It looks like the eagle
for the buffets that doesn't take shit from anybody. All right. Nose bridge. I don't- what
is that even- what is that even doing? Bridge height? Oh, that just like carves a space in his
eyebrows. I actually kind of like that. Wait, I need the music right now. Music. All right, let's go.
Where is it? That's way- that's way too loud. I like it. I put it on. See? No, it's not weird
anymore. You understand? Before it was a creepy weird guy making like creations in his fucking
basement. Now this is like a fun family fun thing we're doing. This is now not weird anymore. This
is funny and interesting. Look, like- I like that. Can they even talk? This is too loud though.
Is this even a song that I picked? The nose is never gonna be- god, no. What does Ratchet's
nose look like? Let me see. What does Ratchet's face look like? All right, it's kind of like down
and it's- it's- it's forward. It's like down here. It's like a little point that goes down kind of
below. Kind of like a height. I'll have to hear that. Nose scale. No, it's gotta be nose height.
Nose area. I mean, that does not- that does not- that does not look like Ratchet. It's too big.
What does this face look- oh, it's got big eyes. It's the eyes. Okay, here we go. All- all alien
eyes? Eye scale. There it is. Oh, this feels like one of those- oh no. Okay, here we go.
You forgot to- what? What did I forget to do? How high are his eyes? Looks like a furby? It does
look like a furby. Okay, his mouth is a little bigger. All right, well, if he's a fur- all right,
this is just a test. That is- I haven't really played with these that much. Mouth corner depth.
Hold on. This is the guy from Family Guy. The guy like this. I'm gonna change that though. It's
not the same guy. Oh, I gotta like this. It's Grumpy Cat. I don't want it to be- oh look,
we can't go too ridiculous, but we- we can't see them. Like, that's ridiculous. This is- this is
like not as ridiculous. I'm gonna say like right here. The- the bottom lip has to come in. Make
Stewie. No! All right, fine. That's actually kind of funny. I'll make- I'll make Stewie.
I need to drop something here because I- look, I don't want all the artifacting.
Yeah, the bottom lip has to come in because it's way too high. How about like this? No, I- it's all
fucked up somewhere. I don't know where. Where is it- where am I getting like the double bottom chin
thing? The hair is gonna be interesting. Oh, I thought this was- I was about to sing the song.
It's not- it's not the song. Okay, let's just- let me- I'm- I'm done with this one. This is a test.
I don't want it to be- okay, that's fine. This is episode of the Twilight Zone.
No, I'm not randomized. All right, who- what- what is this- what's his family?
What's his family? I'm not making the Griffin family.
The human- he's human? All right, what was- it was not the Albertsons. This music is fucking loud,
man. Hold on. I know I wanted it, but seriously. Jesus. That's better. Oh, that's- no, that's way
too low. Okay, that's good. Uh, how about- I mean, this is Ratchet Urinal. Um, what- that's- who
cares? It's just Ratchet. Ratchet Urinal. So the- no, the last name's not gonna be Urinal. The last
name can't be Urinal. That's- is that that funny? You guys- that's that funny to you guys? Is that
the- their last name is the Urinal family? No, it's not. It's not. Flush family. That- to me,
that's funnier than Urinal. How about Ratchet Flush? Guys, these- don't worry. They're all
dead in less than 40 minutes, so don't worry. This- we're gonna do this again. Who cares about
the Flush family? Nobody. We're gonna do it again. I'm gonna- okay. I need to do clothes. Hair and
clothes. All right, let me take the hat off. By the way, I have every- almost every single expansion
thing in the game. I want to take the hat off. Oh, good lord. Um, hold on. Wait, I just want hair.
Take the hat off. How do I take off the hat? Hair. Why is this the- why is this the only hair I have
right next to it? Hair with accessories. Tabs? Oh, okay, okay, okay, okay. How do I get this off?
Am I insane? How do I just remove the hat? To the left?
How do you take hats off? Click it twice. You don't take the hat off. Is it just a re- just take- oh,
wait, this is just hair? So just leave that. Why can't I just take the hat off? All right, well,
whatever. The left hair tab is normal. Hair with accept- oh, okay, I thought this was hats, not like
hair and hats. I hate all of these. I don't want any of these. This is so messy. Hold on, we need,
like, what does Ratchet have for, like, hair? It's like orange, right? Like, yellow, orange?
Technically, it would just be bald. He's got a hat on? He does? Oh, he does have a hat. It's
the guy- it's the dog from Spaceballs. Barf is what you're talking about, and yes, it is.
Let me see if they have, like, a little thing like that. Uh, do they have something like that?
Does it really matter? This? Does this work? No. No, we're just going with the hair.
It does look more like a Furby than Ratchet, you're right, but it doesn't matter.
Okay, any of these are fine. This one's fine. Make it the- make the cast of Spaceballs. No.
Okay, that's fine. Eyebrow, uh, is- I mean, you can't even see them. They don't really matter.
What about a beard? This is not going to make any sense, considering where it is. Although,
it kind of does. I don't look like George Lucas in, like, the 70s. No, no facial hair.
All right, good. Cool. Now, what- what about clothes? No clothes? I'm gonna- I mean,
I have to put clothes on. Oh! Is it, like, an unpopular opinion for me to say I don't care
about any of the clothing in The Sims? Like, is that- I mean, is that kind of bad for me to say?
Every single Sim I've ever made could just wear a white t-shirt and that's it and I don't even care.
I, like, never cared about the clothes. Is there, like, just an option where you can randomize their
clothes? Actually, let's do- the guy with the rose? All right, rose. This is just every day.
Like, everybody's going to spin around and wear the same pajamas. Who cares?
Normal. Look, it's going to be just a normal- normal, right? Just- yeah. Yeah, that's- that's- um,
what just happened? Normal? Okay, um, what is it? Sleepwear? Prunar Dar. Yeah.
Oh, Jesus. Okay. This is athletic. This is swimwear. Yeah, whatever. Every day, you can just be the
guy- be the guy wearing these clothes. Oh, he should've- This dude, absolutely without a doubt
in my mind, carries a pocket watch in his pocket and makes a real clear, clear view for everybody
to see that they're taking it out and looking at it all the time. All right, uh, I don't even
know what this person's name was. All right, personality. Uh, couch potato, that's fine.
Heavy sleeper, that's fine. Uh, traits. Clumsy, that's fine. Is that not- oh, I didn't put it on.
All right, how about, uh, mental? Let's see. Bookworm, can't- I thought this said can't- no.
Computer whiz. I don't- why is- what's my brain doing? I thought this said exotic. I was like,
what do- what? Excitable. I'm like- I'm like combining words. When words are this close
to each other, and anybody else get this problem, when words are this close and this small font,
they can kind of like- I read it like the other way. Is that weird? Unstable for sure.
Afraid of water? Terrified of swimming. All right, definitely charismatic.
And I would say dramatic.
Aren't you gonna look good? Uh, super popular, doesn't matter. A meteor is gonna probably hit
the house, so it doesn't really matter what they- what his aspirations are. Favorite food? Dim sum.
Okay. Favorite music? Roots. Favorite color? Red. Okay. Let's do a voice-
Zondelma- Chabo- Meeyapso. Chabo- Zondelma- Meeyapso. Simchiwani-do.
Astrological sign? Uh, Sagittarius. That looks good. Okay. That's, uh- oh yeah, the name was
Flushes. Okay. Uh, let's do another one. Add sim- or pet. Oh please. Oh god. Wait, create dog,
create a horse. We can have a horse in the house. We can have a horse in the house. I just want
everyone to be aware of that. Okay, here we go. Pre-Nufa. Okay, let's go- Suzzle. How about just
like, somebody that's way too jacked? This just reminds me of- that's huge. How am I gonna make
me? Let's just be so defined. I want to be like the people of those competitions where they don't-
they don't look human. They're covered in like- in like oil. Like they were sculpted out of clay
or something or out of like Play-Doh. Here, I'll- look, look, look, look, look. Now it makes sense.
I want to see- I want to see him without a shirt on. So bad. Let's not go too ridiculous. Just
ridiculous enough where it's funny. This is uncanny. Mr. Satan. Well, not yet. I gotta make me. I gotta
be in this house. Uh, what did 2012 Derma hair look like? I don't remember. It was kind of short,
right? It was like this? No, like this? I feel like it was kind of like that. It was shorter though.
That's kind of close. Spiked at the front and shaved on the sides. I don't know if they have
a hairstyle like that. I mean, not like this. It would be- I passed it? I didn't- that's not
the haircut I had in 2012. I'm just gonna pick this one. This one or this one. It was something
like- yeah, it was like this. Looks good. Okay. Eyebrows. I have pretty thick eyebrows.
I gotta- this is pretty much what my beard looks like, although I didn't really have that.
Body hair. Okay, here we go. This is important. So I'm just gonna be the only like normal looking
person in the house. It's just- it's not even close. This is just Randy Orton. Forget it.
This is Randy Orton. This is not even me. I'm changing it to Randy Orton. It's normal. Should I
just- no, make it Jerma. Stick to Jerma. Look at the mirror, right? Okay. Put the music back on. I
hate that it's not doing this without the music. It's weird without the music. It's- no, where's
my music? I was gonna say it's weird without music, but it's weirder with like classical music.
Put this one on. Oh, create a sim. Here we go. I think this is just- I can't like delete these.
Oh, whatever. Who cares? All right, let's do- how wide can I make somebody's head
without it destroying everything? All right, hold on. Put it back. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait.
What's going on with the forehead? What's this eye? I'm trying- I- it's the eyebrow, I think,
is coming down too far. I'm trying to get the eyes to be open. No, it's do- it's impossible.
Shit. I gotta go back. How do I go back? How do I go back? How do I- is it control Z? I can go a
little wider than that. At least I think so. Is this like a- isn't this like a meme image?
No, don't go too wild here. I don't want it to be too outrageous. I want to use the- I want to
be able to see his face. What does this look like? This looks like somebody. Okay, jaw depth.
No, no, no. By the way, I- I promise I will make at least one like exploding person, but it can't
be everybody. Remove the hair. It's Joe Rogan. No, it's not. Oh, that's facial hair. Oh, I mean,
no, it's not really. Well, we gotta put hair. It's the- it's the- it's from a claymation movie.
What the fuck is the name of that movie? It's from a- like a stop motion movie.
No, no, no, no. That Tim Burton movie? ParaNorman, that's the one. Yep, it's the- it's
one of the- it's one of the guys from ParaNorman. It needs to be a little thinner in the head,
but it's one of the- it's like the guy with the big long head, and he's a big,
tough guy or something. I never saw the movie. Kind of like this, and that's what's gonna stay.
I'm rooting for this character, by the way. I want this character to make it.
All right, we're not done with the face. Shit. Okay, I like it. Looks good. Not extreme jowls,
no thank you. This is barbecue football dad. You mean dad- the dad always manning the grill
at every family get together? Oh, I'll do you one up. Dad that always at dinner?
Always? No matter what they're eating, it could be- you could be at like Chili's or like a five
star restaurant. They eat something that they like? Oh, that's- oh, that's unfair. Oh, that's unfair.
That's unfair. Oh, this should be illegal. Like, you like it, I guess. Oh man, this shot- this shot,
that's unfair. Dad, you've had the southwestern egg rolls from Chili's like 40 times. They're good.
Really good. All right, let's keep going. Looks like Henry the 8th?
I want to see. I want to see what Henry the 8th looks like. Oh, that's also the same dad who
every time you go on vacation and they really like where they are, they'll point at residential
areas around the place where you are a tourist. Oh man, imagine that in your backyard. Oh shit,
imagine having this in your backyard. Oh man, imagine having that in your back- right in your
backyard. Yeah, the Eiffel Tower is there and then people live over there. Oh, it's beautiful. Imagine
having this in your backyard. Yeah, hey dad, now you're reaching. No, it's true. All right, I want
to live this alone. I think he's perfect. How much that house over there cost? Yeah, they always want
to know how much the real estate is and it's either way too much or way too little. Just imagine
paying fucking 600 grand for that house. Stupid. These people are fucking idiots. These people are
idiots. What? 110,000 for that house? Oh my fucking god, they have it easy here. So easy. It's so
simple for you guys here. Like, do I- do we make a cyclops? No, no, no. It was perfect where it was.
Leave it. Oh, that's- dad when he sees self-washed egg rolls? Whoa, meme image. Dad when I get
straight A's on fucking my last test? Oh, dad when it's 50% off southwestern egg rolls night?
All right, I gotta calm down. I'm too- I'm too energetic right now. Okay, it looks good. It
looks good. I think everything's perfect. I don't want to do anything else. Maybe a little bit on
the mouth. Just a little. Not that much. Don't- oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. Actually, it actually kind
of works. This person's wearing somebody else's skin. No, it's perfect right there. Everything's
perfect. I don't- don't touch anything. It's over. All right, what's the- who's this person?
I feel- I'm starting to feel like a song coming on. I feel pretty good. Never mind, it's the wrong
song. All right, every day, let's just put on every day. Now it is Henry VIII. I kind of want to keep
it. All right, those legs though. Yeah, I know. I want to see swimwear because I want to see how
huge he is. What? Why are you in a wetsuit? Um, wetsuit? I want him to be in like a bathing suit.
Make the sus guy- I will. I will. They're dead first though. It's under bottoms. Oh, outfits,
I see, okay. Jesus. He's got a really small ass. You understand- do you see that? That seems- that's
weird. Why is his ass so small? And the connecting part to his ass, to his legs, is enormous.
Okay, that looks good. Let's have the bottoms of the- that's good. Accessories, something like
bare- yeah, bare goggles. They don't fit his head. That's perfect. Oh, what? Maybe we should put
glasses on to go swimming? What is that? What is that? What is it? Gills? All right, I like that.
That looks good. Uh, outerwear, like winter time. Okay, I can- it can be- this is fine.
Actually, hold on. I want- what about like a- like one of these? That's what he has on right now.
Okay. Final Fantasy VII, dad. Oh, just wait. We'll make Final Fantasy VII, dad. This is an actual
Nickelodeon character? Who? Oh wait, it is! It's Arty! Strongest man in the world. But he actually
is huge. Okay, we need some info. This is no longer this person. Oh man, I have no idea.
I don't- I have no idea what this person's name is. This- we- this person was four different people.
Henry, the eighth strongest man in the world? Would- Henry, the eighth strongest dad in the
world? Henry Flush. I mean, Henry's fine. How about Strong Henry? Strong Henry Flush. Henry the last.
All right, looks good. I like the- okay, all right, let's keep going.
We're gonna add- we're gonna make the sus guy. And you bet your ass that within five seconds
of loading into the game, I am- um, I'm gonna literally just like blow him up. Okay, there comes
the sus guy. Sus Flush. Oh man, I had one of those yesterday. What does that even mean? In the moment,
that sounded like a decent thing to say. I don't even know what that means. You had a sus flush,
which means like you had diarrhea. I don't even know. I don't- that just kind of came out of no-
I don't know what I meant to- what I meant by that one. I filled the bowl so it didn't go down.
Sussy Flushy. All right, here you go, sus. Let's make- let's make the sus guy an adult, as he is.
Yeah, this really kind of goes down to whatever- what we can do with the face here.
All right, let's take the hair off. Sus hair was, um, it was really all over the place, right? It
kind of looked like that. Like that. That's pretty close. I need to- okay, I know what it looks like.
Go with mouth. Mouth corners, rotate this. Mouth curve, like that. Mouth definition, mouth depth.
Just wait, don't worry. Uh, didn't really work the way that I wanted it to. I'll- I'll get it to work.
I don't think I can make his teeth bigger. It just looks like a duck. Get a reference pick. Yeah,
I got one. I just don't- I can't make the teeth bigger. The reference image up here. Uh, yeah,
I will. Uh, what do I just type into Google? Sus guy. That should pop up, right? There it is.
Jesus. Uh, sus guy. Derma sus. Okay. Where'd it go?
I- I still look at this and I just get- I'm just like, what the fuck? You know what I mean?
It's the eyes. The eyes are gonna be really fucked up, too. Okay.
I just have to- All right. This is, uh, the chin needs to come down a lot.
Face height. Chin has to come down. Not that. It's only like this.
Jaw has to come in a little. Looks good. I hate this image. No, I had it right. Right there. Okay.
Chin under lip depth. Oh, right. This is like- Okay. No, no, no, no. I don't want to screw this up.
Like that. The jaw is- Turn off the cam. I need it as a reference. Oh, God.
It's a Bob's Burgers character. Did I make the Bob's Burgers sus guy?
Forward's too far. It's like right there. How far is it? Okay. From the nose to the mouth is pretty
short. Just gotta open that mouth. Uh, nose is too small. I know. I'm working on it. I think
when he talks, he'll open his mouth, right? Cheekbone height. Stay down like this. Cheekbone shape.
Pull it out a little bit. Looks fine. Fine. It's fine. Ears are fine.
All right. Eyes. Eye depth. They're probably to be coming out a little bit.
Eye distance. They're tilted a little bit too. Tilt at the corners. All right. How- Where are
they rotated? Like this, right? Just a little. Attack on Titan. How is this Attack on Titan?
Oh, my God. All right. It's coming together. Oh, you know, I think I might feel a song coming up.
What will I do? All right. I need to open the mouth, but I can't right now.
Sing it. I can't. No, I can't. I- What will I do? Choices, they're true. I'm not sure,
but I want someone to really think up. Maybe I'll build a house. Maybe I'll make some food.
I don't know, but it's time to begin the Sims. I think that video is one of the least viewed
videos of the grandpa series on my channel on my 2013. All right. The nose has to be bigger.
It's fine. Okay. Now we got to go here. It's a little bit- It's down. It is down. Not that far.
A little wider. Okay. It's not that far. Okay. Right like there. Change the hair. Yeah, I will.
I got to get the mouth right though. All right. Come on. How do I do this? It'll work when he
talks. Skin mustache. Yeah, it'll work when he talks. So this doesn't need to be that high,
though. All right. Yeah. That looked- That looked way too ridiculous. Let's put this down.
I feel like I have like weird like flesh wings on like a skin mustache. It is. Oh my god. That's
so fucked up looking. It's a- There's a skin mustache. I don't know how to get rid of that.
All right. We're going to change the hair. This one's worse than the original because it moves.
All right. I need- It looks fine. All right. I got to change the hair.
No, it's really messy. Turn down the corners. I don't think I even can at this point. No,
it's got to be messy and dirty. No, I mean that's- That's probably as good as it's going to get.
Yeah, that's good. We got to get him to talk. Let's see. How do I get you to talk?
How am I dressed like a Jedi? Hold on. I got to change this clothes. Add a personality trait. I
will. Hold on. I got to get this right. It was like a- It was a gray tank top.
Gray tank top. That's what we're looking for. No. Wait. Just like that. All right. But it was- Yeah,
that looks good. I don't know. I wasn't wearing pants probably that day. No, I had to have been,
right? I need a bigger forehead. I'll fix it. This needs to be gray. I can get that image off
the screen. It looks horrible. I need a bigger forehead. That's accurate. I think that's accurate.
How much bigger? Like right there. What was it before? I don't think I can even make the
forehead bigger unless I put the whole face down. Oh, just don't do that. Fix the eyes.
Don't touch it. I can't wait for the first close-up smile we get of this character.
Nose needs to be bigger? I don't think it does, man. I mean, it does that.
Corners, please. I can't. All right. Corners. Mouth corners rotate. Oh, that's where the weird
skin flap things are coming from. All right. Yeah. Right there. Okay. All right. Let's do
personality. Pablo Herbie. Pablo Herbie. Pablo Herbie. That's mine. All right. Favorite food.
Cookies. Favorite food is tri-tip steak, classical music, and favorite color is gray. You're a,
what are you, a Virgo? Oh, no. You could be a, who cares? You could be a, yeah, fine.
All right. What are your traits? The sus guy is like scary, right? And he's sus. So we've got,
like, where's like liar? Perceptive. Very perceptive. Perceptive sims make keen
investigators. Their ability to investigate and stake out potential criminals is bar none.
And they're also suspicious. Where's suspicious? Okay. Uh, vegetarian, unlucky, supernatural fan,
shy, schmoozer. I feel like schmoozer, right? Like you have to, you can talk. You can talk,
talk, talk, talk, talk. Yep. Holy shit. It opened its mouth. Hmm. Nurturing? No. Neurotic? Neat?
IT? If you're an imposter, you're a loner. It's only you and maybe one other person. How about,
um, handy? Yeah, I'm looking handy. I can fake my tasks like better than anybody else.
Genius? Evil? Oh yeah. Insane? No, I don't think an imposter, no, that's not insane.
Computer whiz. Eco-friendly? Computer whiz. Yeah, cause they're playing, he's playing among us.
He's really good at it. Isn't that, what do you, what do you mean? Or wait, is he's just supposed
to be the carrot? Wait, he's not playing? All right, hold on. I don't, no, guys, I, the meme is
of my face. I don't even know what the fuck it's talking about. I have no idea what it's even
referring to. I've not played one minute of Among Us. I don't even know what it is. These are things
I've heard other popular streamers say. Oh, my tasks. Okay. I'm just gonna pretend I know what
that is. Oh, I can fake my tasks. Oh, dude, when you were at admin, I don't know any of these things.
It's fine. But if it doesn't fit, it doesn't fit. How about, um, disciplined? You don't need skill
and computers to play Among Us. Insane. Why is, why insane? I thought you had to be like smart and
collected and ruthless and insane. I thought the best imposters are ones that were very smart and
meticulous. They're not like crazy. They kill people. Oh shit, this is modded sims. He actually
might kill someone. Okay. Uh, you aspire to be a master of mysticism, the emperor of evil.
This is actually fine. Okay, there's the sus guy. Uh, all right, let's go. I don't want to have like
more than five to 10 people. So we got it. We got to, let's make up just a crazy, an insane person.
I'll make, I'll make a few pets too. Don't worry. You have to make Stewie Griffin. I can't make
Stewie. Can I make Stewie Griffin? Okay. He already, he's got Stewie here already. What does
Stewie's head look like? It's like, I'm going to attempt this once. I don't think I can press the
head down. No family guy. No family guy. Should we just skip? No family guy. No family guy. No family
guy. Okay. Just run a poll. It's just, it's a family guy. Yes or no. That's it. While you figure
that out, I'm making somebody else. How do I? Okay. Well, Stewie's here. Yeah, run a poll. We'll find
out what people want. Okay. Let's, okay. Let's stick with this. Okay. What are we making now?
I'm just so inclined to drag this bar to like here. I'm not making, I'm not making Lois enough.
Just hit random. I don't know if it's going to do anything. Oh, it doesn't do the sliders.
It does not do the sliders. Make it a different, make a different. Oh shit. Hold on. Werewolf,
fairy, witch. Should this be a witch? I guess it's like October, right?
Halloween's coming up. Make Chris Pratt's Mario. But where do you guys think we're going to go?
Let's talk about the Mario. I haven't even talked about like any of the Nintendo stuff. So the Mario
movie, you didn't know, right? We've got Chris Pratt. We've got Seth Rogen. How, where on the
scale of it's just the actor talking to it's a me are we going to be on that spectrum? What do
you guys think? You think it's, we're just going to get, it's just the actor talking. I don't think
we're going to. You think we're going to get full on fake, just Mario and Luigi. I don't, I don't
think so. Said he was going to do it. You know, when I sit here and I think of a Chris Pratt doing
a Mario impression, I, it's like, I, I could see him doing that. I could see it happening, right?
I don't know if it's going to be any good. No family guy. Uh-oh. Well, he is an actor.
It's like an SNL joke. I mean, should I, should I make the, is Elon Musk going to be Wario tweet?
Somebody else are probably already did like 10 times. I mean, like that's, if I think of something
funny and I go, oh, that's like kind of humorous to me. I think of how many times somebody else
may have tweeted it. And if it's over one to 2000 times, I go, nah, whatever. The N64 tweet was
funny. I mean, let's be honest. Look, okay. I haven't even started playing the Sims and we're
going to get in a small little problem that I have here. So the N64 Sega Genesis stuff,
they're making a big deal out of this, but they, they've done this shit like three times already.
And I think it's just every new generation of gamers, they wipe out the last place you
could possibly do all this and play all this stuff because like a bunch of new gamers aren't like,
they don't know that like you could have got this on the virtual console like 10 years ago.
And it's like the new thing. You can play Super Mario 64 kids. Whoops. We fucking deleted it.
And I am not convinced. I am not convinced that this is going to be a good service because look
at the Super Nintendo shit. What was the last Super Nintendo update? Like three months ago,
two months ago, we get like, what do you get claymates? Like in a quarter, like one quarter,
you get like two or three games. It's just, it's not enough. Every time I see that, like, holy
shit, there's something new on the NES catalog. I forget that it even exists because it takes too
long. Look, they have like 10 games that they want to come out with and then like five more
that they want to add later. What about after that? Are we going to get in the same scenario
where they just release like one N64 game every three months? Like what the hell? What is Mike?
No! Audition for Waluigi right now. All right. Everybody cheated but me, Mario. It's me,
Waluigi. Did I get the part? I love Jerma because I like when he does the intentional quench.
Oh, let's make a witch. What a fucking song. Uh, you know what's fine? We'll come up with
the name after we figure out what they want to look like. Make Gruntilda. Okay. How about just
Grunty? I like Grunty flush. Okay. What Grunty is here? I need a picture of Grunty. Audition
for Gruntilda right now? Okay. Sure. That was good. I don't care who says it wasn't. It was
fucking really good. All right. What does she look like? Uh, all right. So we're going to have to do
the slider. Which, which, which? Uh, unironically good. Hey, thanks. All right. I got to get to the
face. So really, does every character that I make have to have a long thin chin? Is that,
is this just like the trope of my whole channel? It's like, look at how long their chin is.
I make a character that doesn't have a long chin. You have to make hot Gruntilda. Uh, is that what
this image, this Google image search is showing me? Is that what I'm getting on the Google image
search? I was curious. What are you talking about? Uh, I, I'm going with N64, just Gruntilda from
the opening cut scene. Never played it. I did play it. I played it enough to, um, I don't know,
I think I got like 10 puzzle pieces, 20 puzzle pieces. And I lit it up at one of my friend's
houses. All right. Here we go. Really big eyes, like very, very big guys, like huge, massive.
And they're pretty close together and they take up a majority of her entire face.
They're huge. Not that far away. They're pretty close and they're tilted down a little bit.
I got to change the eye sockets like that. They're kind of tilted like that. There we go.
Making an anime character. All right. Can we get a witch's hat? The eyelids need to be changed.
These need to come down a bit. I bet that helped at all, but whatever. All right. Looks good.
I just want to make sure you can still see the eye. There we go. Are her eyes still red?
All right. Here we go. We need to do, this is like a long witch nose. Okay. It's pretty close
already. There's gotta be some weight here though. Maybe not that big. Uh, I'm not, I'm,
I'm not touching this one. Oh, okay. So that's way too big. That's better. Bigger. I think that's
good. Her face is thinner though. Yeah. The face is too, it's, she's too, the face is too thick.
Face height. I gotta get rid of the hair. There it is. It's better. This is how just every crazy
son of a bitch sees people. He's pretty, wait, huh? This is how I see people. All right. Pull
these cheeks in. That's a little better. Better. Better. We're getting close. This is a mosquito.
No, this is Gruntilda. I think the face is even longer. I think I have to go real kind of crazy
with this. It's, it's like that. It's long. This is like fucking pizza cheese dripping out of her chin.
Okay. Okay. That looks good. Now I gotta get a witch's hat. The eye is fine. The nose is fine.
The mouth hold on the mouth though. Wait, this has a mouth hook. I need that. Is there like a
front picture of Gruntilda? It's a, it's a little, it's kind of, it's got a big wide mouth.
How deep is that mouth? Like kind of like that. Definition looks good. Yep. Looks,
that looks good. All right. The width, height and width right underneath her nose in a way,
like right here. Is this the whole game? I would say this is probably arguably one of the more
important. I mean, I'm going to be streaming for a long time. This is not going to be like a three
hour, four hour stream. We're going pretty much all day. I need green skin. I don't know. Hold on.
I gotta get this right first. I don't like how happy that mouth is. You understand? That's not,
that mouth is too happy. There we go. All right. Uh, green Gruntilda. Already wearing purple.
She bald? No, she got long hair under the hat though. Is there a witch's hat? Of course there is.
That. I don't, which one? There's some hair under there. Isn't there?
This is a Karen witch. All right. Now we just need, we did like a cake. Clothing. Let's go with,
uh, yeah. I want outfits. All right. Can I make this black and purple?
Okay. Wait, wait, wait. Remember that one.
The top is fine. All right. Hold on. Shit. No, I need the other parts and it's white on the bottom.
I think this is perfect. I don't, I don't think we're going to get much better than that. Honestly
God. Shorter legs. I don't think you can do height. Yeah. Height is not an option.
I just have witch's shoes though. Witch shoes. They have witch shoes. We can just do these.
I like boots actually. Hold on. I think these are fine. These are fine. This is a black.
I guess they already were. Oh shit. Wait, no. Let's do different colors. All right.
Uh, I believe now it's to personality traits. No, no, no, no, no, no. All right. She's evil.
I don't, I don't know much about her. Piledish probably powered. She's evil and she rhymes.
Okay. All right. Okay. Eccentric evil. I would say great kisser. Grumpy. She's grunt Hilda, obviously.
Okay. How about a loser? Mean spirit. Probably neurotic, right? Hates children.
Supernatural fan. I mean, come on. Green thumb. I'll take away eccentric.
We'll do, what should I replace it with? Rooting. Insane works. Everybody in the house is going to
be insane. Green thumb. Because she's a witch. She's green. Why do you want me to do that?
Family oriented. She eats children. Okay. Yeah. That's, that dislikes children. That's a good one.
She eat kids? What are you talking about? Yeah. What do you, I don't remember that.
All right. We got to go back. I got to remove this. Stuart Flush just got to go.
Unless I change this into something else. How do I delete this person? I'll get to leave. All right.
Hold on. I want to make a dog or a horse. Make young Sheldon. Oh, please let me, let me do this.
Come on. All right. Elder pet. Make the horse look human. I, that's what I'm going to try to do. I'm
going to try to make it a person's face. All right. Oreo cookie one. Shape. Oh my God. Please.
Wait, are there no sliders? There are no sliders. I don't think.
Body. Oh, come on. Really? Advanced mode. Please. Oh God. That's it? What? Do I have to change this in
the, in the setting somewhere to make it so that animals can do it too? Thank God for no sliders.
Click the head. Damn it. Oh, it only does it. It only does it for people, not animals.
Make a pet out of a person. I think I can, somebody said I can pause and edit them in the game and
change them. We'll try that. All right. Well, let me get this right. This is first. That just scared
me. I forgot this person existed. Okay. Let's go with the horse's name here. Let's back it up.
We'll just make the horse face region. Ears scale. All right. Whatever. We'll come back in later and
see if I can fix it. I'm gonna get out of here. Oh, basic. All right. Well, what's the horse's name?
Oreo cookie. I like Oreo. Oh wait, I can do personality. Hold on. All right. I have to make one
just absolute mutant person. Sure. I am not gonna hold back at all. This is going to be insane.
I'm going to try to make this person the most fucked up I possibly could.
Mr. Green? No, it's not Mr. Green. Oh, make sure he's got a big chin. Oh,
at this point, this, this just doesn't even matter. How about all the way down?
What's the cheekbones? Oh, that's disgusting. Looks like the mouth.
He can't sit. I can't, I gotta change this. Oh, I feel like the, I feel like his head just went
through with a hydraulic press video. What the fuck? No. All right. I like that. That's fine.
Oh, it's not, it's so, it's wrong. It's just wrong. I made their face inside out. Keep it.
Where the eyes go? Shit. Hold on. Holy shit. Uh, I feel like this is the, I feel like this
character's from Hellraiser because the eyes upside down. No, I want to be able to actually
even look at this. I'll fix it. This is too much. I don't like this. This is scaring me.
It's scary. This is really scary. I don't like it. I don't, it's Ben 10.
What's the, what's the character from Ben 10? What's the Ben 10 name of that monster? I know
who you're talking about. Ah, real monsters. It's the guy with the armpits, right? All right. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Let's not get too over ahead here. Oh my God. We're
going to get jump scared randomly. Wow. Rotation. I don't even know what the nose is.
Where is the nose? No, not too wild. I want to be able to see the face. You know what I mean?
The mouse. It's a rat of some kind. It's a giant rat. Let's work with it. I'm working with it.
Hard to see what I'm doing. Okay. Nose width? No. Tight. Not that tight. Okay. A little bit
wider. Better. Mouth can be fixed. All right. Let's figure this out. You can cover that up.
That looks better like that. I can bring it forward. Tongue. That's the tongue.
Where's the tongue? How do I make the tongue smaller? It's just venom. It kind of is venom.
Whatever. What about ears? Whoa. That the way it was. That the way it was. That. All right.
We can put the tongue back in his body. Comes out the other way. This is so insane. What will I do?
Choices? They're true. I'm not sure, but I want some time to maybe think about. Maybe I'll
have some food. Maybe I'll build a house. I don't care. It is time to begin the sims.
Go back a little bit. All right. That's fine. I'm done. This one actually might have to be
changed because it's going to crash my computer. This is a rat. This is like a rat. It is a giant
rat. Wait. Can I add fur? Where's fur? It needs to be a werewolf. Will that screw everything up?
It looks like a hammerhead shark. All right. I'm done after this. We're going to play after this.
It looks like an elephant. Do werewolf. Hopefully this doesn't break. It's taking a long time to
load. Is that even hair? Where's the hair? Is that not even add hair? Transform hair. How do you do
that? Change from the button. You can add body hair. Okay. I'm going to take the clothes off.
Yeah. Let's take a shirt off. Let me do that first. Everyday wear. Can I not just be no shirt on?
Love the portrait. You bad gamer. I got it.
Just give him a t-shirt. Wait, one of those with the ripped up clothes.
Body hair section. Cook a pop. Body hair, back, arms, legs, chest, upper chest, stomach.
This is fucking disgusting. Okay. Well, stop this at once. I kind of feel like I have to.
You know what I mean? I have to stop this at once. I have to stop this at once.
You're right. I have to stop this at once. I can't even see this. Just take it off. Delete them.
Delete them. I'm not going to delete them. Are you serious? No. All right. We need a name.
I don't even know what to call. A giant rat? Rat. Transform him please. Okay. We'll transform.
Transform? Okay. Here we go. The, the human form. The werewolf form is
the form that you should stay in. I guess. Okay. What about Gruntilda? She has to transform into
a witch or is she just is a witch? Are we going to do personality and stuff? And I'm going to play.
We're going to go. I've been doing this for two hours. I know it's a ton of fun. It really is fun
just making these monsters. Maybe a cat or a dog or something. Okay. Um, about, um,
Rat Flush. I mean that's so simple though. Those legs. Damn. Rathu? Rathu Flush. All right. I like
Rathu. All right. We're doing one more person, but we're going to do a dog. No, we're going to do a
cat. I'll make sure the traits are good. There's one, two, three, four, five people in the house.
There's too many people. Um, I don't know. Bumpy? Bumpy. Bumpy the elder cat. Uh, how about this
one right here? Tuxedo cat? Sure. Oh, uh, that's fine. About, um, Stinky Cat. You need to have a
black hat with the witch. I don't have to. Okay. Perfect. Fur shape. Import some textures. No,
no, I got to like play the game. I got to make, okay, we got to play the game now.
I want to play. Where's all the stuff? No, you don't have fur shape. Okay. What about actual
shape shape? Does the face lotter work for cats? Nope. Nope. No, it doesn't. Crap.
Cat view. That's fine. It doesn't matter. I, if I can do it, I'll come back and do it again.
All right. Okay. That looks good. Uh, bumpy flush. That looks good. All right.
Let me have one more person. Let's roll the dice. You're a maniac. Why? Come on. I want,
I need to start her. Just make the game. Just play the game. One more. One more.
Play the game. One more. All right. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. There's so many people. You're right.
All right. I got to go. Here we go. I've been, I've been creating characters for two hours.
You're right. All right. All right. Let's play. Let's play. Let's play. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm
ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. All right. Here's the family. What's the name?
Horse. I have a horse and a cat. If I want to add more animals, I will. I just have to make
their personalities. I got to change personalities. And the rat's personality too. This is very
important shit. All right. We're going to do brave, fast and friendly. Perfect. What about the cat?
The personality? Destructive. Cats are great. Cats get into stuff. Hunter. And hyper. Perfect.
Looks good. So, so. This is the rat. I don't know. Absent-minded. Excitable.
Oh, love it. Uh, animal lover. And, uh, and frugal. Oh, that's good. It wants to be leader
of the pack. Of course you do. You like grilled cheese and you like French music. Sure. All right.
I'm ready. Are you guys ready to play? I'm ready to play the game. Except, except.
Ratchet flush family. Choose something to strive for. Um, super popular. Strong Henry. I forgot
about making you. Um, I would say ambitious. A coward. I guess. Eco-friendly. Ouch potato.
And a heavy sleeper. Sure. And you want to be a, um, leader of the free world. That sounds good.
And this is the sus guy. Sus guy wants to be the absolute master of mysticism, I think.
Yeah, I think that makes sense. Tilda wants to be emperor of evil.
Uh, rat wants to be the fairy tale finder. Adopt a unicorn, I guess.
Oh, here we go. I've got, wait, relationships. I gotta make sure we're all like related and we're
all the same house. We're all related, right? Oh, who are we related? Why are we all related
to bumpy flush? Why are we all bumpy flushes children? Okay. All right. Here we go. Time to
pick a place. It's like a home. By the way, I have, I'm going to have to do like Rosebud or whatever
because I have like $20,000 and I have like eight people. I don't remember the mods. I know that
there's like attacking people mods. There's disasters. There is fight. I don't even know.
I don't remember. Save the game now. That's a great, good call. Holy shit. None of them are
related. Good job. 10 out of 10. They'll figure it out. So where do I want to go? I've got a lot
here. This is, uh, 1800 bucks. I got a house here. How big is two bedroom, one bath. I don't think I
want to build my own house. That's another two hours. I'm just putting them somewhere. This one
looks good. Build it, build, build it, build a beach house. Holy shit. What a good idea.
How much is this? Oh, hell yeah. Yeah. We're going around the beach. All right, let's go.
Another two hours gone. Laugh my ass off. I don't know. I don't think so. I think we'll be okay.
Natural wind blows through sunset Valley, creating a mystical weather stone.
Wait, is somebody like already doing something bad? What, is she already casting spells?
All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I need a house. A fucking horse. Wait, where's the
elephant? Lead horse. Wait, you can saddle. Okay. I'm not going to do, okay. Violence and aggression.
Where are you going? Okay. Well, I got to build a house. This is going to be the shittiest house.
It's going to be enough. How many people do we have? One, two, three or the five people
All right. Five people. I need, I should have bought a goddamn house, whatever.
What just happened? Law, body type, hair, instance, ages, young adult, invalid parts. I don't know what's
happened. Something went very wrong. Okay. Oreo. I thought that she said Oreo flush was just
hidden by a car. I was like, wait, not already. Right? Why am I getting a notification for this?
What the fuck? All right. Gruntilda likes, werewolves have two forms. I know. Popular stores,
wedding cake. All right. Will you just leave me alone? I need, let me have a house first. All right.
Walls. What's the, what's the, rosebud? I don't care. Just give it to me. I actually, I really
don't even care. It's a bathroom living area with a kitchen over here. And then this can just come
out like this. This would be like a bedroom one. They're going to be very small. That's fine.
Okay. That's bedroom one, bedroom two, bedroom three, and then bathroom. This is a bathroom
right here. One, two, three. Okay. That's good. All right. Now we just need a little area out here
with like a little den maybe. Done. Okay. I'm just doing this as fast as I can. Build a beach house.
This, I would, I'm on the beach. Two bathrooms. Yeah, that's a good idea. Okay. Let's go. Now I need
a wall coverings. Let's get some, one room with five sleeping bags. There's a hole. I'll fix it.
This is going to be bathroom, right? This is bathroom two. Nice. All right. Bedroom should be,
you know, like, you know, make this nice right in here. Looks good. Bedrooms.
I gotta close that gap there. No, don't exit the goddamn game. What are you crazy?
How do I remove this? Okay. Let's make this, um, I don't like green. It looks like grass. I don't
like it. That's good. All right. Now look at the floor. I'm going fast. All right. Where's the,
okay. I need the floors. This looks like a pretty good bathroom. Bathroom. Really ugly. I hate it.
I want something else. All right. Big living room area. This is good. Let's go with, uh,
I'm going to say something like, um, wood. Ooh, no. Yeah, that's fine. All right. Carpet in the,
we go carpet, carpet, carpet. And we're going to go carpet over here too. Cause it's like a little
den. Carpeted bathrooms. How is that not tile? What? I would just, all right, like this. There.
Okay. Doors. Uh, door and external door. I'm not putting a fireplace in there. They'll all die.
They will literally all die if there's one there. Windows. How about just some regular,
just regular windows. Oh, actually I hate, I don't like that. Let's do low. Hey,
doesn't have to be perfect guys. Yeah. I have to get rid of that. This has to go right now.
There. Light in here. All right. Doors. Uh, okay. Doors, doors, doors, doors. There's right here.
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Simple door. Insta door. How about, um, this thing?
No, I need a bigger door than that. Like a huge one. Is that weird to have like in your front
door of your house? No, it's not. And there's regular doors. It's here. And this is to go to
the den. Bathrooms need to have doors. Nice. All right. Furniture. Easy. Frigerator. Over here.
Oh shit. Where am I going to put this? Oh, this way. So I put the fridge here.
They're not prison cells. Fridge here. And then let's get a stove. Just like a general stove.
There. Counter. Yeah, we need a kitchen counter. Close the counter. All right.
Two more here. I'm just going to cheat. Doesn't matter. Let's get a sink in that counter.
Uh, why can I? Wait, I have to pay sim bucks for that? Get out of here. Okay. Looks good. I need a
small appliance. We need like a microwave, right? A food processor.
It's good. I need dish. What? No, no dishwashers. I need some skunks. Skunks is what are they
called? All right. We just need wall skunks. Okay. Bedroom, uh, lights. These are just going
everywhere. I don't care. My house is going to be so boring. How about just like fluorescents?
Then that. And then I mean, you can, one of you guys can have like a nice chandelier. Who cares?
Um, I don't know what this is, but you can have it. This is, where is it? All right. Wait,
do you have this one? No. Um, how about, no, how about no, get rid of that. I don't like that.
Uh, I just want like just a regular wall light. Yeah, that's fine. It doesn't need to be nice.
Bathroom needs one of these too. All right. Good. Almost done. Press G.
Thank you. Thank you. I appreciate it. Okay. Next I need, what's the cheat code? How do I do it?
Rosebud. Mother load. How do I do it? Control shift C. Mother load. Okay. I'm not doing that
ever again. I just need that because we get eight, there's eight people. I'm not going to just buy a
bunch of expensive shit. No, this is just to get beds in the house. Cheater, cheater, cheater,
cheater. Yeah, I'm cheating. Yes. It's $50,000 cheating. I'm not doing that a second time.
This is just to get beds in the rooms. There's too many people that live here. All right. We need a
bathroom. This is, look, I'm going to blow through this in a second. Hey, it's not a prison. Okay.
Relax. Showers. What is this? Simple shower. Okay. We're just going to do a simple shower.
Simple shower. How does this thing open? How does this thing open? What? All right. Bathtub.
Like just regular tubs. All right. The urinal. It's all right. It needs sinks and that's it.
Oh, mirrors. All right. It's a regular mirror. Nothing crazy.
Outhouse mirror? No. It doesn't matter. Whatever. Sink. Just a stand up sink like that. Wait,
a little bit nicer. No, it doesn't matter. Let's go. All right. That's done. I'll just do a little
bit more. I'm not going to give him any entertainment. Don't worry. Bedroom. I just need a few beds.
I'm not going to spend this money. I promise. Well, they all have to have an individual bed
because I didn't make anybody related or anything. So they all have to sleep in a twin mattress.
Are they all going to have this? What's the rating on this stuff? Energy. That's awful. Bunk beds.
Like what? I can't buy this. Can I? Does it say how much money I have? 164 sim points.
Air bones bunk bed. This is so stupid. I don't. Okay. It's not what it was supposed to be.
That's fine. Is that enough? How many people live here? Five, six. One, two, three, four, five. And
then the animals. Does a horse sleep in a bed? Where's a horse bed? What does a horse go?
Does it make a barn? Where do I put the horse? Okay. Well, that can come. I can figure that out
later. You need a staples? Sort by function. Hold on. Essentials. I have a cat. Okay. Hold on.
The horse is not going to fit in here. Okay. And then a bowl. Okay. Where do I
buy a bed for the horse? Horse tab. Oh, did the horse sleep in the house?
How is this going to have his own bedroom? Hold on. I have to have a bedroom for the horse.
Over here. How big does it have to be? That's going to be huge. Move out of the way. I don't
extend beyond edge of lot. Where? I'm trying to... Okay. Let's try that again. Okay. Now I need a
door to get in here from the outside. It needs to be a double door. Shit. Okay. Hold on. No, no, no,
no. Not lifeboat. Not lifeboat. Hold on. Is it a barn door? What about... Will they be able to go
through the garage door? Does that work? There are no lights. I'll take care of that. Where are the
skunks? Of the floor lamps? We also... I gotta have the ground be an actual room. Okay. Delete
the random wall. It's driving me insane. I don't know how. I don't know how to delete that. Like
control? Like shift? How do I do it? Shift. Control click. I think it's fucked up. This is, I would
say, should be wood or stone? Masonry? What do horses like to walk on? Grass? But it's part of
the house though. Dirt? Gold? It's not gonna be grass. Straw? Like it's gonna be like a cobblestone
room. Holy shit. That's ugly. Oh, that's really ugly. Marble? I'm just gonna do carpet. Who cares?
Okay. Whoa. Easy. What else does a horse need? Oh, water trough. Where does it go? Which way does
he walk towards it? Which way is the front? Hey. Hey. Hey? Hey. Happy horse ball? Okay. Hold on. I
promised I wasn't gonna spend this much money. I'm not gonna. All right. Fuck it. Oh shit. Right.
It's blocking the door. You can just eat it out here. Put the hay in the living room. Should we
give him a TV and stuff too? That too. Can he see? That's gonna be on the wall. It's the only flat
screen. $8,000. What the hell? I don't want to buy that. Can you see that from there? $8,000?
I'm miscellaneous. Okay. What about? All right. I think this is good. I don't like how this is here
though. It's just going over here. This needs to be bigger. All right. I'm gonna. I don't know what
to do. Can he fit in here? Who cares? He can eat it out here. Now I just need a couch and I'm ready
to go. Sleeping bags. Oh, dude. Sleeping bags. All right. Now let's try to beat Star Fox 64.
We're gonna pass the controller every time one of us dies. God, to be a kid again. Make a litter
box. I'm rushing to get this stuff ready to go. We're very close. Okay. I told you I was gonna
just not use the money for anything stupid. All right. Now you need couches. Just like a chair or
couch. Kitchen's good. I don't know. Put it there. I don't know what to do with this. It's so big.
Litter box. Hold on. All right. Are you ready? Is this facing the right way? Which way is the
right way? Oh, we need a table and chairs to eat. That's right. This has to be a huge table.
Oh, what a hot dog. Chairs. I need dining room chairs. Okay. Why is the room so big? I don't know.
I always accidentally. I'm sorry. I make the first room in The Sims always gigantic. I don't know. I
don't know why. It's a weird habit where I just make a huge cube first. Those kids chairs. These
look like plastic kids chairs. Are they? Here we go. Save the game. Time to begin. What will our
Sims do this time? I agree. All right. Who's who? Who's who? Where am I going? Going to check out
the hay. Sus guy's checking out the hay. Okay. What am I doing? What am I doing this for?
You just adopted an indoor pet. Where are they? Okay. They're still just kind of riding around.
All right. So are you the sus guy? You know, what did you hold on? Why did you just do all that?
Does a horse eat that? Getting warm. Okay. Looks good so far. Who's going to get the first job?
Okay. What the hell is that? He's running. Inspect. Hey. Okay. The sus guy is going to go inspect
the portal. What's with it? What is it? Oh, this is pretty sus. Who the fuck is coming out of this?
Greetings. I'm Emmet Relevart. Oh, it's Rick. I'd like to use my time portal.
Oh, thanks for the portal. Help a time traveler out. Great woolly llamas. I was on my way home
to Oasis Landing and my time portal experienced a temporal disruption.
Find and collect the power cells on your lot. Why is he back up? Why is he back up?
Wait, wait. Did I, I think I broke him. Where's he going? Don't touch that. Don't touch that.
Hey, he's puking. He's puking in the bed. He's puking in the bed. I have to take him out.
How do I get rid of this? I want to get rid of this thing.
Summon the time traveler?
Okay. I don't want to, I don't want to collect any power cells.
That was the windmill windup was stupid. Okay. So can you get off the horse? Be petted. Hold on.
I don't want to do this yet. I don't want the horse to break Gruntilda's neck.
You know what I mean? I don't know what that means. I don't think I want to do that.
It's too, it's weird. It's been 10 seconds. I don't care about like punching
the Pickle Rick into the outer space. Suplex the horse, please.
Somebody's coming out. Somebody's coming in. This thing is making sounds again.
Jesus, that car went by fast. Someone's coming out. He's back.
I just like broke a bottle on his head. Wait, what? I tried to strike him with lightning and
didn't do anything. I just broke a Coke bottle on his head. What the fuck? Wait, what?
Oh, am I? Talk to cat. No, I want you to do the tectonic neck crack.
Joke.
What are you doing? What is he doing?
I'm scared. It was sus. All right. All right. I got to relax. I don't want to do anything.
I don't want to do it. What is this? Why is there ice cream? Buy ice cream?
Oh, by an ice cream. Get this guy to leave.
Grab head. All right. I want to get out of here.
What are you doing? I want this person to stop doing that and leave. I want to get this out of
the front lawn. Is he dead? Stop coming back as a different person. I want to get this person out
of the front lawn. I'm going to delete this. I can't delete this. This thing is so annoying.
I want it out of here.
Make it naked.
I'm so. Hold on a minute. Where's punch?
It's trying to figure out what to do.
This is getting way too weird. I got to reel this in. I'm going to reel this in.
I need to reel this in. All right. All right. All right. Thank you for coming. Leave.
Leave. Where's the cat? Okay. First things first. I asked this person to leave. I'm traveler.
What the fuck are you doing? Watch out for the cat. How's everybody's health doing?
We just keep breaking bottles on this guy's head.
I can't. All right. Ask him to leave. Ask him to leave. Ask him to leave.
Close the portal. I can't. Travel to the future. Reset the. I don't.
Just collect the cells. Oh my god. Fuck. All right. Fine. Not helping the time traveler. Who is?
Will you leave if I do this? Let's do town edit and you can move it wherever. Hold on.
All right. There's only one more. All right. Everyone. Everyone's doing fine.
When met the time traveler, even though he's dead. All right. Now talk to him more. Okay.
Oh, repair the time portal, please.
Okay. How's the cat doing? Okay. I've received a mean high five. Cool. All right.
Let me first reactivate the portal.
Thank god. All right. That was so annoying. What time is it? It's currently six thirty.
That was an interesting first day. How do we let the dog? All right. Let the let the dog in.
Uh, enter. I can sell the portal. No. Oh, thank god. Get this out of here.
But does this mean this guy's stuck here forever?
All right. Come on, horse. Let's get everybody in bed and we'll
actually start playing the game. Body slam the ghost. Fine. You can't get in. The horse wants
to get in. What are they doing? Why do they all want to go in here? I don't understand.
It needs to be a barn door. Okay. I need a barn door. Where would that be?
Horse is stuck. I don't know. It's indoors. Top row. Big red thing. Oh, okay. I can't do it.
Oh, shit. This is huge. So big. Damn it. This whole thing's fucked.
Maybe we shouldn't have put a horse in the house. Leave the useless room.
Right on the right side of the room. I don't think I can get it there to open up the wall.
I could try that. Let's see what happens. No walls. You just go in. Get in there. Come on.
Hey. All right. Nice. Okay. You guys have to get out of the way.
All right. So you're going to go in.
You can't go in. He wants to read a book. Oh, there we go. Perfect.
Can we seriously get this guy out of here for real?
Oh, can I bite his neck?
Get out of my house. Get. Leave my house. How do I call a grim reaper?
Cat watching TV. Ask to leave. I don't think I can.
Make awkward drama. Wait, wait, everybody. Wait a second.
What was that? Everybody leave. You want to eat the horse? What's wrong with the cat?
Oh, I bet that probably felt really weird. I have to help the cat.
All right. What does the cat need? Where's the needs bars? All right. Fun. I need to.
What are you doing?
What did you say? What's wrong with them? Eat food. This guy's still standing in the house.
Litter box. What's wrong with it? It's right there.
Somebody take care of this. All right. We have 25 grand. We're going to be fine.
You somebody get up. Grunt held to get up or you wake up. Wake up. Wake up. Wake up.
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up. Let's go care.
Pick up pet and hang out. I think this person's I don't know why they're still here.
I'm here. Come here. Come here. Come here. I'm sorry. I made the cat twerk.
Here. Let's nip hand. Come here.
Let's go.
Litter box. Right here.
Okay. How's the cat? The cat needs to have fun. Run around. Need some toys. Don't I have
something like a cat toy? Oh, wait. Yeah. Give me a cat toy. Oh my God. Okay. That's
at a like a scratching post. Yeah. Oh, one of these things. Look, check it out.
What the hell was that? He just fart out of his head. What just happened? I was on top of him,
punching him. These, they're all insane. I don't even know what to do. Somebody has to get a job.
All right. Stop running around. Where's the horse? Oh, the horse is fine. Okay.
Can one of you actually go into the bed? I go have an evil slumber. I feel like I'm missing
somebody. You're in bed. You're in bed. You're here. You're in bed. Oh, you're here. Okay.
Ask to pillow fight. No, go to sleep. Get over there. Um, where are you going? What a fucking
moron. What a moron. Where are you going? What do you mean sleep in Grunty's bed? It's a bunk bed.
He has to go in from the left. Okay. I have to get rid of this person right now. The beds can't be
against a wall. Oh, they count as double beds. This guy, I don't even know how he did that. How
did you do that? How did you do that? What? This guy climbed the wall into the duct. Okay. Interesting.
All right. So I need to feed the cat. That's hungry. Eat from the bowl. I mean, like I wanted
this guy out of here. No torture. The ladders on the wrong side. Okay. I'll fix it. I'm not dropping
a meteor on the house. All right. Is everybody awake? Straight. All right. You need to go bed.
Everyone's good. It is, uh, currently 3 0 2 a.m. And the game just crashed. There we go.
What are you doing? What are you doing? You're ruining the furniture. Stop.
Stop it. Ask him to leave. Well, I gotta wait. Measel door. Can the cat body slam this guy?
Shift click the ghost to delete him. I can't. He loved that. I just keep re-killing him.
Doesn't the grim reaper come? You have to enable shift clicking. Use the NR. Oh, delete him with
this. Oh, how do I delete him? Just literally ask him to leave. All right. I'll try that.
Oh, okay. You there's Emmett. Why do I only have I can only hurt people because I don't think he's
a I don't think he counts as a person. Yeah, he doesn't count as a person. Just wind up and
punch him out of existence again. Holy shit. That's a great idea. What was it called? It was
demonic powers, telekinetic slam. No, what was it? Violence and aggression. Why punch?
Yeah, that's it. Get him out of here. Get the fuck out of here now.
Fuck off. What is going on right here? What's happening? Why is the horse blurred? The horse
blur. All right. Hold on. Restless. Oh, wait, let's go. Let's go for a ride.
The horse have a phone? Where'd you go? All right, you just run around. Don't even fucking think
about it. I just heard another magical sound. Bronte just met the time traveler. What? Bronte's
asleep. Does this work? What's wrong with this guy? That doesn't work. All right. Somebody get a job.
Have a water balloon fight with everybody. Is he stuck in the wall? What are they doing over there?
I do hear him in the wall. I can hear his spell shit.
Shit. Dirty dishes already?
Check the walls. I don't see him. Is he on the roof? I don't think no. I think he's just glitched.
Need to hire a maid? Yeah, yeah, yeah. I will. Good idea. That might just be Bronte Hilda making
that sound. I need a phone. Phone, phone, phone, telephone. Oh, wait, it's the Sims 3. They have
cell phones. I forgot. I grunt Hilda call. Telephone. Do a service. Oh, service. Call Amelia.
All right, get a maid over here. I think the time machine's trying to spawn back in,
but you fucked with this time space continuum. Okay, maid.
How's the cat doing? Cat's okay. Horse is okay. Can I take the horse into town?
All bear. Let's let's go do something. I'm gonna bring everybody out on the town.
We're gonna bring the horse too. You can go wherever you want. It's open world.
Are we even friends?
Okay, how about I'm just gonna take this guy somewhere. Bring the horse to a bar.
Okay. Can I go? Damn it. How about you go? The spa? Diner. Yeah, go to the diner.
Join culinary career. Become a partner. Eat here with others. Let's all go.
Everybody go to the diner. Make the horse the owner. Are we going? Wait. Eat lunch. All right.
Stop playing. Throw the water balloon at each other. Let's go. All right. Are they going?
125 bucks. All right. Where are they? Slow down. Slow down. Is everybody in that car?
Oh, nice. Yeah, we're all here. We can go in the diner.
Oh, it's like the the weirdos. All right. They all have to go to the bathroom really bad.
So what? Go to the bathroom.
I can't strike anybody with lightning. I'm trying.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. That scared the shit out of me. That scared the shit out of me.
Oh my god. What happened? Is she okay? Is she okay? Why is she laughing?
You would not be laughing. How do I get into the diner? Oh my god. Are the clothes gone?
No, she still have clothes on. She's fine. Can we introduce ourselves?
Hey, Pauline, let's let's introduce ourselves.
Play with magic. Stop playing with magic. I want to introduce yourself to this person.
You're talking to this guy.
Okay, Grunty just yelled at someone.
No, I want a good luck charm.
All right, make ugly.
That's it.
Okay, make ugly.
What? What? Okay, what am I doing? Where am I going?
Um, what? Wait, what are you doing?
Oh, wait, body stomp. What's the time to save the game?
Save the game. Stop bullying him. I just need to see what this stuff does. Murder in the alley.
No, not quite. I need to see. All right. Enemy.
She was taking a picture. This lady was holding up a cell phone.
Wait, it's not over? Oh, is it not over? What? Oh, they're gone, man.
They're still alive. Wait, what? I just want to see what they do. I just need to know what they do.
How do you make ugly? Undo? Yeah, I'm going to go back to the save.
Okay, I get a reload to save. Reload to save. Reload to save. Okay, so keep in mind, I'm not going
to do that again. I'm not going to drop an absolute meteor storm. It just kills everybody.
I just had to see what it did. That was so loud, I know. I have it turned down. I'm actually kind
of... The thing is, it might be autonomous. I think it actually might be autonomous.
It might just be a meteor that hits the house one day. Okay, they're just doing whatever they're
doing. Okay, you've... Aching back? Humiliated, smelly, and enemy. I don't know why they're doing
this. I stomped him? That's so stupid. He's fine. He's fine. I'm not telling him to do this. All
right, we went to the diner. That was fun. Riding a broom is the only way to travel. Wait, what's
the person running from? What are you running from? Why are you running? Oh, you live here?
Holy shit, let's go hang out over here. Let's be neighbors. Visit the roomies. Yeah, come on,
let's go. Hello, nice to meet you. Let's go take a look inside and see how we're doing. Can we go
in? Unfortunately, people who live here have left while you were on your way. Oh, what? They fled?
Oh, here they are. Nice to meet you. Hi. What do you do? I mean, we both... Yeah, yeah, but that's
fine. Are we going in? Okay, did we get invited in? Did we get invited in here?
Like dogs? Okay, we've got to make friends because I want to go and hang out here. This is a huge
house. Is that not invited? No, I can't. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'm focused on the task.
Okay. Okay, uh, Rathy's friendly. All right, let's go upstairs. Let's like go in your house,
right? Oh, okay, hi. Can I come in too?
All right, I guess we're just going upstairs. Am I gonna get access to see the house?
Oh, shit. Nice. How am I doing on bars? I take a shower. Take an evil shower. Yeah, I need
bladder and hygiene. Let's let's get that done. Uh, sauce is behaving inappropriately. I'll have to
ask him to leave. No, get out of the bathroom. Okay, what? I keep hearing noise like a baboom.
Orgo. Wait, what's your sign? Looks like you and I were meant to be.
Hold on a second. Don't don't shower yet. Don't shower. Wait, wait, wait, wait. We have a
budding romance here. Joke about shedding. Romantic. Give flowers. Uh, precious pink.
Hold on. We got to make sure. I want this to work out. How long does it take to take a damn
shower, man? Hurry up. We're flowers. Flowers. What do you think? You just asked me what my sign
was and if I was available. What? What? Uh, you have a really nice home. She just doesn't care.
All right. Um, how about I talk about being a werewolf? I just turned into a werewolf. She
likes that. She likes werewolves. I'm gonna joke about shedding.
Okay. Good sense of humor. How do I turn into a werewolf?
I mean, it wasn't a lot. I got, I got better looking.
Unleash this beastly side into a werewolf. Okay. Ask about your career.
I'm supposed to be scary.
My stomach's in the way. Okay. You trained into your Reddit form.
Is there a specific werewolf thing I can do?
Romantic.
All right. I'm going to ask. No, no, no. Hold on.
Wow. Yeah. Friendly.
Romantic is no, is there a romantic werewolf thing to do?
Saint bro. Okay. Time to ask about your sign. Special werewolf sniff.
I'm jobber.
Am I fighting with somebody?
I'm not going to like crack my work, throw around, slap self slip. Oh, well,
I'm going to do like a comedy thing. Watch.
Wait, that hurts.
Sweet. I just got kicked out.
I got kicked out.
It's time for you to leave.
Oh, can I bless somebody?
Not going to starve to death.
Make punch cell. Make signed? Singed? What is that?
Check the rabbit.
What the fuck are you doing?
What am I doing? I'm tearing up the floor.
Where am I going? Go home. I put on a suit to go home.
Fake pass out?
Why would I fake pass out?
How long do I stay here for? Somebody said you're a snorlax.
Okay. Well, oh my God, that was so funny.
Okay. I think I'm going to level up. Where did I go? I'm back at the house.
I'm taking, am I taking a shower in the house? Yeah. I'm going to leave.
There's no reason to be here still. I'm going to say my goodbye.
I'm going to show off my teeth.
Oh, okay. Go home, dude. Go home. Go home. Go home. Go home.
How one more time and this person thinks I'm really funny. What's this person's name?
Cyclone sword? Faint. What do you mean faint?
I'm so dramatic. What? Get up. Just turn the lights off down here.
Yo, it's 3 a.m. I got to go home. How are the animals?
How are you doing? You okay? Why don't you go in here?
Call the sus guy at 3 a.m. My energy is so low. Go to bed.
Why is there just evil slumber?
All right. You need to turn back to your normal form.
I keep forgetting that's not werewolf. You need to transform back to
werewolf transformed to human form. Stop doing that and transform back.
Okay. Get some sleep.
I need to start working on somebody's career. How's the cat? You all right?
That's okay. Get some sleep. Come on, cat. All right. Good to go.
Horses just running around. Everyone's waking up.
Make dinner or something, right? Serve breakfast. Make waffles.
Okay. Who's the next thing to get up? I want someone else to help make dinner.
It's like six o'clock in the morning. All right. You get up and help make breakfast.
Clean that up. Okay. Take a shower.
Who am I? What do you mean woohoo?
I didn't even put a face cam on. I'm not putting a face cam on.
Not right now. I want to work on the relationship. He has a relationship.
Why is he? He woke up in werewolf form.
Peril instincts prevent that from happening.
Eating leftover waffles. Didn't we just make waffles right here?
Because his mood is bad. Oh. All right. Everybody eat.
All right. Cut that out. Cut that out. Cut it out. Cut it out.
Stop. What just happened? Who punched himself?
I want you to punch yourself. I wanted you.
Somebody just punched himself in the face outside. I want you to punch yourself.
Stop you from doing the weird shit you were doing.
Is it raining? I thought that was film grain.
Okay. We need to have an activity out here. Something fun.
Fire pit. Oh dude. A Ribbit Ribbit Froggy McFrog slide. Are you kidding me?
How are we doing on horses? Good. Go slide.
Come on. You want to have fun. Go out and have fun. Holy shit.
You're going the wrong way. Come on everybody. Let's do it.
Everybody come slide. We could use a little bit of fun in the house. Come on.
While it's raining. It's the perfect time to do it. Who's going next?
That was a straight up belly flop dude. That hurts. This is fun right?
Yeah. Where's the cat? He's running to the bathroom.
Why do they have to pee so much? Do you feel like they all pee and poo like five times a day?
You brought your cell phone into the bathtub. Answer the phone.
Who is it? I thought his pants were at his ankles.
Who was it? I want to take him back to the house where the person was.
Keep doing it. Everybody else is doing okay. You hungry. Is there more waffles?
No, no, no, no, stop, stop, stop. I want those. Oh okay. I thought she was throwing them away.
Go for a pee break. It's been three hours. I'm all right. Let me like in like ten minutes.
I forgot. I think I added a gun. I think I added like weapons and I'm afraid to open.
Hold on, sort by outdoor.
Where is it?
I don't know where it is. Storage.
Oh, I forget where it is.
If I have room, it's like outdoor, I think.
Outdoor cooking, outdoor decorations, outdoor.
No, where is it?
I don't remember.
It's in toys.
Don't see it.
Maybe not. I thought I added it, though.
That's all right. Let's go.
Is it raining in the house?
Jigna.
All right, I want to take you.
I want you in a good mood, so go to bed.
Go to sleep.
Enough playing out here. Let's go.
The horse has to get censored.
Yeah, I don't know why. That's weird.
All right, get in bed.
No more playing. I need you up bright and early.
I want to ride the horse into town.
Ice cream?
Yeah, get one.
What are you going to get?
How about a freezer bunny popsicle?
Nice. All right, cool.
Mount affection, feed produce.
Yeah.
Here, have an apple.
How cute is this going to be? Let's find out.
That's pretty cute.
Egg for carrots.
Oh, horses are so cool.
You got water over here?
OK, I want you to wake up because we're bringing you to town.
What are you doing? Yeah. All right, sleep.
These beds are so bad. Look at this energy.
It's fucking awful.
You have to sleep for like 16 hours to get even half of our energy.
I'm thrown away.
Go in a different bed.
All these idiots just sleep in sleeping bags anyways.
Yeah, here we go. Here.
Wake up. Go sleep in that other bed, man.
Get rid of this.
There we go. That's much better.
Did the horse just do the slide?
What?
That was awesome.
Oh, I didn't do it that time.
The horse isn't really good at health.
All right, go. I want the horse to go to sleep too.
Go to sleep. Go to sleep.
I love this horse.
OK, then I'm going to ride you into town.
We're going to go. I'm going to call that
a concerning amount of water accumulating.
I mean, kind of.
It's taking so long for you to.
There is actually a concerning amount of water coming in here.
This is very this heavy, heavy rain.
It's kind of freaked me out.
Uh, are we good?
OK, now eat something.
What do you guys eat?
Then I'm going to take him into town.
Are you cool to?
What happened to his face?
Oh, I thought his mouth was down here.
I thought that was his teeth.
I think it is.
Oh, God.
Get out of the bathtub.
Will you transform, please?
Transform back to a person, human.
Oh, all right, finally.
Now, what time is it? It's 11 o'clock.
You have to go back to bed again.
Artie's flush just saw what?
Oh, no, Grunty didn't.
I'm one grunty flush just saw a panicked horse for the first time.
Oh, my God. Get inside.
What are you doing?
Get inside. Get inside. Get inside.
Get inside. Quick, get inside.
Get in there.
Get out of the storm.
All right, now everyone's asleep again.
The horse pen doesn't have a roof.
Why? Is there a reason why?
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, I need it.
Oh, OK, how do I fix this?
How do I fix this?
This is OK. I got to fix this soon because this is scaring me.
I have to make a barn over here.
Right. How do I build a barn?
Is there a special thing to do?
Just put a roof on. It needs a closed wall.
Yeah, I can't. If I close this, he can't get out.
What is this even here for? You're right.
What am I? What's this even here for?
I haven't even used this space at all.
No one's been gone inside of here. Why am I using this?
What? Delete that.
Now I need a barn door.
Oh, stop. Really?
Two stories. Two stories.
This needs to be two stories tall.
Make a wall first. Oh, wall.
Are you high? Finish the wall.
What are you talking about? The wall's not finished?
I have to add a story.
That is delayed.
It has to be two. You can save.
Can you say barn door ten times fast?
Barn door, barn door, barn door, barn door, barn door, barn door, barn door, barn door, barn door, barn door, barn door, barn door, barn door, barn door, barn door.
Oh, barn door, barn door, barn door, barn door, barn door.
Nobody can do it better than me.
All right. I actually never added a story.
Never in the sim.
I don't even know how to do it.
They add a story.
Create a room like up here.
OK, that's two stories.
There it is.
Hell, yeah. All right. Barn door.
And now I have to make the outside of this red.
OK, there we go.
Is there still no roof on it?
Was this still OK?
All right. There it is.
Now we're good.
Course is good.
Everything's fine.
Better living conditions here.
It's good.
Actually, inside, you don't have to be scared or anything.
All right.
Is there no food there? Is there food in there?
All right. Bladder. It's time for you to get up.
What time is it? One. OK.
OK. Three thirty in the morning.
That's fine. Get up.
Make breakfast.
How old is this?
Probably two. It's probably old.
Serve breakfast.
TV's backwards. No, it's not.
All right.
Oh, you're mad.
I told you to.
Horses asleep. Why did it groom this horse?
How do I shower?
How does the horse bathe?
He nap the horse.
You don't save the game now.
Why? I think maybe I have to be outside here.
Yeah, probably.
Why don't you come out?
Why is everybody all of a sudden want to go pet the horse?
OK, we got to get in there and clean up.
Clean. There we go.
Newbie. Well, I.
Aching back. Oh, you are cool.
They're shooting. Why do you mean aching back?
What? Oh, there's even aching back.
OK, care.
What are you doing?
Rush. OK, clean hooves.
No, get over here.
Where are you going?
Get out of the rain. Clean hooves.
I can't clean your hooves.
Damn it. Worth a shot.
Yeah, worth a shot.
You know, what was I trying to do?
I was trying to see from the mod editor that I could change
and do a full
whole creative character thing with it.
All right. I need to clean.
Please clean the hooves before.
This is ridiculous.
My body is so stupid.
Why are you so dumb?
Somebody clean the horse.
Clean the horse.
What are you guys doing?
What? I want to kick him in the face.
Why won't they?
Why? Why?
I know.
Nobody will clean the horse.
OK, well, let's keep a toony job.
Go to the bathroom.
Eat whatever this is.
Oh, don't clean it up, you idiot.
Grab a plate.
I got to get rid of these stupid sleeping bags.
Oh, take a shower.
I can only care about one of these people, and it's the rat werewolf guy.
Somebody that's in a good mood.
I don't know why they won't.
OK, it's not raining anymore.
So care rush.
I thought that was a beaver.
Please, somebody brush this animal brush.
Holy shit, it took you forever to figure that out.
All right. Now it's time for you to go out.
I want to go do something.
I don't want to sit here and chase around a horse.
Sunset institution of modern art.
The beach. Yes.
Is it old pier beach with?
Let's all go. Why not?
The sleeping bag causes it aching back.
All right, we all get.
How do you how does the horse get there?
The cat doesn't get a taxi, right?
So many people can't fit in here.
What about the horse?
You can't just leave the horse.
I guess this is exercise.
OK, well, we waiting for you.
Well, it's at the beach today.
Anybody have any friends?
Should I call somebody else to come hang out here?
There's nobody here.
Are we all going in?
Watch out swimming into a riptide.
I don't think that's what's happening.
What's wrong with you? What are you doing?
What? You can stand on the ground.
Can I help him?
What if he's stuck swimming stuck?
No, he's all right.
It was weird and lost weight.
Are you going out a little far?
Wait, did he lose a shitload of weight?
Look at his stomach.
Oh my God, he's actually thinner.
Where's the cat? He's going to drown.
He's not going to drown. He's fine.
Ah, beach day.
Can you play in the water?
Oh, splash.
Wait, am I going to throw a rock at him?
What is wrong with me?
A party right here.
Oh my goodness.
He lost a bunch of weight. It was him.
Don't go too far out. Come on.
Why is it so sad?
I don't think this is sad. What are you talking about?
Um, hello?
What the fuck happened to you?
Who is this?
Why do they just come ashore?
Somebody I hit was lightning?
Wait, what were they doing here?
Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh.
Uh-oh.
What was that?
Oh, people came.
We can make drinks and shit. Awesome.
Oh, make quick drinks. Yeah, for everybody.
That gruntail just talking to is a doctor?
Grana cough, boy.
Somebody just got burnt.
Is that what I heard?
You guys are pissing her off, I guess.
I squished his head with my thighs.
Wait.
Oh, let me thigh-crush death.
Brack neck.
Get out of the way. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't mourn.
I just thigh-crushed his head.
Oh, he's gone, damn it.
What? What did he do to that?
I need to see that again.
It's so stupid.
Damn it.
All right, let's have a quick drink.
Why do you keep doing that?
Who's kids is this?
All right, is it safe to drop a meteor in the ocean?
What else can I do? Hold on.
Hit somebody in the water with lightning.
I don't remember doing that.
Burn, lightning strike.
Make ugly.
Splash.
Zombify. Turn to ice.
Is he going to crush him?
React to meteor.
No.
Why is the kid looking up at the sky?
No, hold on.
Wait, if he runs over here.
Wait a minute.
Where is the meteor?
Oh, shit.
It landed in front of the meteor.
OK. OK. OK.
Wait, I saved it, right?
I thought it was going to land.
I thought. I thought.
I thought it was going to land on him over here.
And I didn't realize. OK.
OK. OK.
Well, I thought I saved it. I don't think I did.
I activated the meteor when he was in the water.
It was a soul guy over here just by himself.
I was thinking I could just drop it and see what happens in the water.
Wait, how did he get fatter?
What? Why is he fat again?
OK, everybody that's like burnt.
OK, I got to get out of here.
I got to get out of here. I got to get out of here.
She's bouldering.
He's hargling, he's hargling.
OK.
Eat her, Ezealus.
Where's the horse?
He's puking. He's puking.
Wait, why is he puking?
Why is the horse puking?
What happened? Is he all right?
It was just a puke just coming out of his mouth.
Who's even in this house?
What?
Ah, OK.
Who's this?
This is a zombie.
Where's...
Wait.
I can't...
Where...
Wait, where is he?
What happened?
Where did that zombie go?
Was it an illusion?
Hey, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight.
Watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out.
This is the stupidest thing ever.
I hate this.
Give permission to ride horse?
All right, this thing has to die, right?
This is a zombie.
Still alive.
Burn it.
What is that sound?
How could a zombie have a ghost?
Why is he...
OK, you just keep fainting.
Is that...
Is he pretending?
Faint.
OK, well, that was weird.
I was going to say he ran all the way back here across...
Wait, is there a...
Where's the cat?
You have fleas.
Hold on.
Where's the other people in this?
Why'd they leave the cat?
Go home.
Come on.
Wait, who's this?
Oh, somebody lives here.
OK.
All right, go back home.
Come on.
We need you.
We need to get this cat a bath.
I think something's wrong with the horse.
Wake up.
We need to feed you and play with stuff.
Drink some water.
Have some hay.
Eat some hay.
And then play with the ball.
That's good.
There we go.
Does the horse have a TV?
There's a TV in the horse room, yeah.
OK.
Have some food and then play with the...
And then you're going to have to pee.
Where's a horse pee?
Just outside?
If you have a horse in a stable, does it just pee in the stable?
How does that work?
It just pees wherever it wants?
Yeah.
If the horse used a urinal.
Oh, it's the cat.
All right, you're back.
Some dinner.
And then get some sleep.
I still don't understand.
I'm deleting these.
This is the only person in the house that's not sleeping on the ground.
There are three full beds here.
Why are we all sleeping on the ground?
All right, yeah, yeah.
We'll do a pee break.
I'll be right back.
I'm going to go pee.
See you guys in like two minutes.
I want to get some water.
Hair all over my hand.
It's Otto.
Otto's hair.
All right.
Delicious.
Let's go.
I paused the game for a second.
What was the last thing at the beach?
I need to start going places besides just dropping meteors on people
when they're in the beach.
You know what I mean?
If I've killed like six people, we laugh out loud, killed six people.
I don't need more.
The colors are wrong.
I'm just picking up on this right now.
Why are the colors wrong?
Why is it purple?
This is supposed to be blue.
What is going on with the colors?
Why is this purple?
It's not it's blue in my game.
Why is it purple over here?
Well, that shouldn't look like that.
Pirated copy on my main monitor.
This is all blue, like blue, blue, bright blue.
This down here is not purple.
Why does it happen?
It looks a little better, but still weird.
Why is it doing this?
It's an Instagram filter.
I feel like I'm losing my mind looking over here at this.
Yeah, I don't know why it's capturing it like this.
Who cares?
I mean, I don't really necessarily care,
but that's just very weird.
It has like a purple tint on it.
Like even the road has like a purple tint.
What about morning time?
What does it look like for you guys in the morning?
It looks better this way.
Because it's night?
Well, but it's blue for me, not purple.
Somebody broke the sink.
Let's fix it.
Okay, so we're back.
But for me, yeah, you just changed back to blue.
It's not purple.
It was, that's weird.
That's very strange.
All right.
I want to take everybody today.
We're going to go over here.
I want to do something interesting.
Whose house is this?
What about like community fire department?
Wait, Central Park Summer Festival.
Why can't I?
What was it, 8 a.m.?
What time is it?
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Let's bring everybody.
Go to the festival.
Here comes a filler episode.
What can you do at the festival?
It sounds like it's going to be fun.
It's like a pie eating contest.
Oh, eating contest.
Who is, I don't even know who this person is.
No, don't go home.
All right, let's go.
Load up the car, kids.
I was just going to drop a meteor on that person's house,
but we did that joke three times, no more.
Can the horse join the eating contest?
We're going to find out.
Oh, you can play soccer?
Why can't you not going?
Why are you not going?
Don't watch TV.
Go join the festival.
Sorry, I'm not going to roundhouse kick the paper boy.
I'm sorry.
I know a lot of people are sitting there going,
oh my God, he's going to like roundhouse kick
the person that delivers the mail.
No.
Like, oh, whoops, I accidentally clicked it.
I'm not going to, no, I'm not going to do any of that.
We're going to go to the festival
and we're going to have a good time.
Oh, Grunty's doing the contest.
It's Grunty versus, who is this?
Why join the contest if you're going to do that?
Why are you even in the contest?
Why are you here?
One, two, three, go.
When do they go?
What are we waiting for?
Oh, wait, another contestant.
Okay.
Go!
Three, two, one, go!
He's going to fist his pants.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no.
Wait, wait, did we not complete it?
Who the fuck is this guy?
He's got like a criminal.
Oh, no.
Okay, three, two, one, go!
And they're off eating their hot dogs.
Burglar, Elephant Man, and Ratchet from Ratchet and Clank,
and Gruntilda.
Burglar gets off to a quick start,
gets three or four hot dogs down already.
He's going really fast, potentially even too fast.
Unfortunately, it looks like he's getting
a little too many hot dogs out his throat.
He seems to start choking.
Hopefully he's gonna be okay.
No, he's fine.
He's completely fine.
He just had to get it down with a little bit of water.
He's absolutely fine.
It looks like, I think he's gonna be okay.
Wait, why is he back to life?
He's still eating the hot dog.
Even after death, the burglar doesn't care.
Still wants to win this competition.
He trained for months, it seems.
Potentially years.
Even after pissing his pants, shitting his pants,
breaking his own neck and choking,
he's still gonna be doing this, he's still here.
We're gonna blame them, the winner.
Ladies and gentlemen, the winner of the hot dog eating
contest is the burglar.
Already stopped this from happening.
Stop it.
Oh, he's fine, but he's getting,
oh, all right, you're fine.
What else can we do?
Did everybody leave because they freaked out
because he was puking and stuff?
What the fuck is going on here?
What is happening?
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Hold on, let me get it.
Hold on, where is it?
Can I even do it?
I'm not gonna be able to do this, right?
Where's he going?
Get away from me, get away from me, get away from me,
get away from me, get away from me, get away from me.
Get away from me.
I kinda wanna hang out with this person.
Here, let's talk.
That's a, okay, it's a fairy, another werewolf.
What'd you do?
Oh, let's play with the sprinkler, let's go, all of us.
There a soccer match going on?
Oh, you're not playing together.
This is sad.
Are you serious?
Just turn around.
Dog, go brush the dog.
That's really awkward.
All right, he's getting naked, this is weird.
Why are they putting the, you have all your clothes on.
What's wrong with you guys?
What's the burn lady?
Wait, what is ice blast?
Ice blast?
I don't think it does anything.
I guess I'm about to do it.
Meshah, dukna, meskah, or tukala.
Susul.
Oh, oh.
Okay, I missed.
Can we turn off the sprinkler, please?
Enough with the sprinkler.
Casted an unknown spell.
What about this other stuff over here, what's this?
What's the sus guy doing?
I don't know.
Let's just do it, everybody.
I'm training, sus guy.
Why do I feel like this would be a real thing?
Some fucking video game convention.
Hot dog eating contest with the sus guy.
And like eight people sign up and we pretend
like there was a shit load of people
that were in line to do this.
And in the audience is, like the people
that I paid to film it is like probably six
or seven people there, like a production crew.
And maybe four of the people in the audience.
And then it eventually gets uploaded to YouTube.
That's part of like a panel or something.
This is the least viewed out of all of them,
out of everything from the convention.
How do I guarantee victory?
Where even?
Should I shit my own pants?
Oh, she won, grunt till the wind.
Don't we have to, why are we still doing this?
Did she just snap her neck?
She just like broke her own neck.
What was that?
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Oh, let's go make a snow cone.
What?
Oh, he turned into a werewolf.
I get it.
You all right?
Fainted.
Okay, well, that was funny.
I guess, oh shit, we've got something going on
over here, don't we?
We've got something going on here, don't we?
Oh, what?
All right, come on.
Made it five feet.
No, no, no, no, what did I just do?
What did I just do?
I didn't save it, what did I just do?
What happened?
No, no, no, stop, stop, stop, don't do anything.
Don't do anything stupid, what did I just do?
He's fine?
He didn't do anything weird?
I just scared the shit out of him,
I thought I had him break his neck or something.
What's your name?
Where are you going?
Oh
This guy I swear to God
Hi
Is there's a horse?
Excuse me whose horse is this?
Okay
What is he doing? Oh, he's reacting to noisy public stare stereo. He doesn't like the stereo
I
Think we're with or it was Oreo or he is fine. Just hanging out with the cat that is
Fine to just hang it out scratch
Wants to scratch. Oh, what I'm doing here. Yeah, just scratch this save the game. Oh shit. You're right
He's scratching post. Yeah, I'll get one in a minute. You guys are crazy
Cats gonna need to go home soon to eat
This guy is currently I guess we're having a problem
You're in among us fan
I
Don't think we have any anything in common here about um, like a praise just like hey, how are you?
What do you want swimming? Where can you go swimming? Okay, how about like funny funny story?
Evil no, not evil about insane. How about
See bondage. Uh-huh. Why aren't you like the conspiracies and Lee about like just
Alright, let's play. Um
Are you gone? Hey, we don't play tag
Listen am I listening to who is this person?
I
Didn't even I didn't even select that he did it in what this sucks weirdos
Hey get your shit together
Oh
Back in the bathroom again. Oh, no, this is in the bathroom. He's getting his face painted
I
Smell can I smell bad?
Zelda well, it's still here and you really really like it in the roller skating rink then it all day
I'm not gonna draw. I gotta drop a meteor. I don't want to though. I don't want to something a meteor but I
Know no, I want to be friends with this person. Is the party just never ends with this guy
No, I can't sleep cuz then the night will be over and I'm having too much fun
Right, I get it, but you gotta go easy on the syrup there. Oh my god
Grunt hill is still here. I'm gonna enjoy the snow cone. Alright, that's gross
There's like a cow or something
We dropped it don't you can pick it off the ground. Oh, I wish you picked it up off the ground
Gonna get another one same flavor. What do you think? Oh, he's going with the grape. Where's the cat? We good?
What's happening here? I need a scratching post scratching post for the cat get in there and scratch
There scratch we need like so many to eat cat walked home
Wait, wait, first of all eat eat eat eat from the bowl and then I want you to scratch this and then when
Wrath you know when
Grantee cut right go home. Well, both you go home. Oh
Aren't you want you to play with the cat?
All right, talk to the cat
Why does the sauce guy keep sleeping in a suit I have I don't know man, it's better
With the cat
Better have fun laser pointer that needs a wash
All right, let's clean
Okay care rush I'm deleting these stupid fucking sleeping bags Oh
Sleep in the real bed
All right
Cats doing good
Now you need to get cleaned
There we go. That's better and then get in your bed
Sleep the night. Where's the horse?
This guy has been in here watching TV in the horse place. He didn't go to the event
He's been in here the whole time
Clean who's that better? All right, nice
You're good. Let's uh, let's you know, let's just go for a let's go
You're hungry. All right, you gotta clean this up. I mean everybody is smells so bad. What's on the ground here?
Onion or the onions on the ground just ate one. Wait, what did I say eat it?
Why did you just eat a raw onion?
I didn't tell him to do that. Oh
How did you ever eat an onion on the ground
All right, let's go you and me going out right now you can do it
All right, let's move
Anybody have any I need some friends. I see somebody in their backyard. I'm gonna ride over there
You know, let Oreo what was doing? Oh, is it let Oreo flush braids?
What does that mean?
No, get on
You idiot give horse free rein
Calling over the cat. Why is it called the cattle?
Wait, what was my cattle? What?
Why this guy smells always even free rain?
Let him go free
All right, we're gonna give Oreo free rain you love him. You must let him go
Let's take him somewhere. Let's get him somewhere. Let's get him out of here. Where should I release him?
We're like up here. Just go for at least him in somebody else's backyard. Take him to the farm. Is there a farm?
Get plastic surgery. No, I wanted to ride in to I wanted to ride over here
No, don't just run in somebody's house. Just wait. I want to show up at the front door with the horse
Okay, there we go. It didn't work
You're not gonna ride over there. Oh, there we go. Okay, let us in. Hey, can I you're gone?
All right, what's going on? Who is this guy's person live here? You're just being a nuisance. I'm trying to go into the house. Oh
Look what I caught on my ring cam
He's grazing, okay. Hi, I'm here with my horse. I'm here to say hello. Thank you. If I'd come in that'd be great
Nice. That's yeah, this is perfect. Look at this. What do you think he petted? Oh nice
Good. It doesn't really like his head to be touched. It doesn't like his head being touched
I tried trying to tell you don't I don't let doesn't like his head being touched
All right. Well, you didn't listen
Where'd he go?
Silking wet sitting on his nice leather couch downstairs. All right, that's the ultimate like my neighbor
My neighbor's dog shit in my front lawn
Okay, I'm kind of getting sick of that you come with the dog the dog shits on my front lawn
Imagine if it was a horse and it was just like eight pound horse dump on your front lawn
That'd be horrible
video games
Why did I do that
Go this way where am I supposed to watch TV? I'm not gonna meteor strike the house not yet
Maybe in a minute. I want to see what's going on here. Hey, we're hanging out watching TV
Tiga turbo Lasha
Bonsal let's play
Reba with
Do something fucking sus
You the TV
I didn't get invited into the house. I didn't get invited in here
You can't wait. What did he get kicked on the stairs? I
Wasn't even allowed in the house
What happened in there what happened in here
Yeah, so what happened was I found him I was I just I went in here and like somebody vented and they I saw them come
and attack
No
Did he make it out of the house?
Did he make it out?
It's like I'm getting out of here
Where's the sus guy? All right. Thank God
Everybody out. Oh quick. Is this guy's food done?
I can't go I can't I can't look in the house
Somebody was making microwaved food downstairs. I
Can't look in the house anymore because they're all out of it. Oh my god. That's so stupid
Holy shit, okay. Well, we made it who's brushing their teeth
Sell the space rocks. No, I can't do it again. Just go into every house and destroy
I'm not gonna destroy every single house. I'm in. Oh shit. You got hit. I
Thought I made it out. Okay. I guess I was wrong. Okay. What happens if I take a shower
Do I do is to clean it off and take a shower?
Where's the horse?
Horses, okay, the horse needs to sleep though. Everyone get out of the way
There we go. He's fine
Germany
Intagious, please kill the sus guy. Okay
Not yet
We need to have a party. It's time to party. How's everybody else doing? It's an enemy. Okay, the cat's all wet
Let's actually bathe the cat
The cat needs a bath. It's all wet and shit
Are you serious until the
Sky is apparently too much of a moron
Why why not do the cat noise all right fine
Cat noise cat noise. Yeah
Dog barking. Yeah
Sure dog bark
Cat I want you to go sleep, please
What are you doing? Oh
Grantees making the onions just creating onions and dropping them on the ground
Dumporka fashion to God
Overgave ten eyes
Chuga yibba cheva
Ploof feel like this is my dog looks like when he's asleep
new face
Zem Zah
Sips of em and da depsel Rooney gosh
Oh, yeah, all right. All right, you're practicing magic
Why don't you go get into some mischief or something? Yeah. All right grunty, let's go. This is pretty cool. What's this place?
Who lives here kill them?
Is this a business this place has turned on all their lights, okay, how do you smell your hygiene spine?
I'm just gonna wait out here. I guess be invited inside. All right, nice. Where are you? Oh, there you go Thornton
It's 4 a.m. Oh, it is 4 a.m. You're right. How'd you?
Go an onion who lives here. This place is crazy
There's nice help I got
War job blog knee, but what the hell
Barnyard or
Enthuse about magic somebody leave
guys like magic
Are you what was that?
Wait, she's got magic, too
Okay, wait
Have a Harry Potter dual
Eyes be careful with those spells. They're very dangerous. I told you to be careful death spell
Ice I didn't even do that. She did. She's about to flex on this girl. Oh, did I hear somebody doing the magic out here?
What the fuck up their toilet casting ice blast into the toilet what I do
Styles McGaw who's this guy? All right. I'm I'm not gonna do that anymore. I swear to God
Wait now they're friends now what do I mourn death high five death
Oh my face
Get me out of here get me out of here. I'm gonna drop a meteor in a second. I'm not gonna get out of here
Where's this good? Oh, he's here. Oh
Wait, what?
Shut up quiet. I'm not doing anything
Ice blast I didn't I'm just turning their AC up. I'm not doing anything else. She's doing this on her own
I didn't tell her to do this. I'm putting their AC at like 55 only in the bathrooms. Why?
So they're gonna go to the bathroom
All right, so just like go sit somewhere and wait till they go to the bathroom, right?
Then somebody's gonna be like, oh my god, it's so cold in here
Poisoned apple. Oh
Guys guys guys guys guys guys
That's what the horse was eating those
Oh
Jesus no
Conjuring poisoned that they were just all over the ground. I thought they would I was wondering why what are these onions?
Why the apples in the ground?
Okay, great. No, no, no, no, no joke about joke about her cooking. I don't even know these people why
This house is so full bloom is horrible
Oh
Wow, you're cooking subtle and that's very funny clue bash. Yes, barge of food. Let me finish it for you
Okay, well here you go, I made waffles
It was chicken
Time rosemary congee like a white sauce in there, but I made it into waffles
But I was cooking it in the sink Barney Duke what's wrong most of the gossip see Gani do you do what leave me alone?
Yeah, have a good luck charm
You have to rhyme everything you say while playing with Gruntilda. I have some food for you over here. Oh
My dear, it's very clear. What our syrup toasty bottom have some
Wash it down with orange juice
Don't you want him?
I'll take a piece of I'll eat it myself. Make sure you're a good boy to please the elf on the shelf
Are they gonna eat this? Oh
Good luck charm. Oh
Wow, thanks for the good luck charm
Look butter get the fucking camera and I got to see what I'm doing all the bugleberry
Apologize
That was that was that
Look at this microwave looks like it belongs in fucking heaven in Diablo 3
It's like terrials microwave. We have a water balloon fight with Thornton wolf. Is this the guy that owns the house?
Let's talk about money. I have a house. I have money
You see this house. It's beautiful, isn't it?
I don't care about your house. I don't care about your money. I think I give a shit
But the door are
We getting married
What's happening right now
But his ass is on fire
Go sit in the toilet like a 90s comedy movie quick
You're gonna what are you doing? I hate doing dishes. Yeah, it's the worst you can freak out when she comes up here
Hold on I'll leave in a minute. I'm gonna go ice blast your bathroom
He's gonna get on a zoom call he's gaming
Oh
Complain about Thornton the guy that's on fire right here. There's burnt to death
Get out get out quick. Oh shit. Wait, I was on the broom. No, no, don't no
No, no, don't don't don't don't don't don't don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it
What's he doing out here? I'm gonna get scolded. Oh
He's pissed at me. He's pissed
I
Made him ugly and he ran away
Hey, I want to do that too. That's it. You only swim for five seconds. Let's do a whole breath contest
Hold breath contest. Come on. Let's do a whole breath contest. That's why you wear shoes
That's why you do what you moving too fast. That's why you wear shoes
Put on shower shoes. Don't run around the edge
Your shower shoes. That's what happens. You know, you got to make sure you can be careful around the pool
What am I doing making her like poker eyes and stuff?
I see that what happened? What did I what did I miss? Does it do even see that? What was I looking for?
I own this pool. No, no
Oh
Here here's a good luck charm
And I'm gonna leave look what's the kill count that mob five
Although like no, okay ten, but like four or five of those were accidental. I don't count them
damn, so
Does anyone else feel like we haven't moved?
Like who's who's next are we gonna pull out of the
Cajun so they go do something weird, right?
They're just waiting in the sidelines for me to grab them and have them go do something insane
Why I one of them has to die
I'm choosing right now. The horse is gonna bite somebody in the neck. That's just the weakest link. I don't think so
I think it's the sauce guy. We've had it. We've had a story arc with
Get a story arc with Gruntilda. We had a story arc with the horse and ratchets just so ugly
I have to keep him around. I want the horse to bite somebody in the neck or the cat
Let's have the cat bite me in the neck
Vote out do a poll. All right, fine. Fine
Who we voting off the island because I can't take care of this many people. There's too many people
There are five people in the Sims you may as well
You can't take care of five people five adults in the Sims is impossible in the same house
You got five people by the way, the animals are not on this list. They are they have immunity
He'll the sus guy back like you voting him out on among us
No, just pretend I did that. I don't want to do that
Remember is the RTS player that thinks having more than one base is cheating
well
The difference in the Sims is if you have multiple households
They autonomously play themselves and you jump between the houses
You don't play all four or five houses at the same time
by the way
Delete that one half-built farm that's in the corner
You're a dick and you were the reason why I didn't play online
I never got good at being able to macro two plus bases in RTS
No, why would I don't want to do that either as long as one builder is alive. I haven't lost
Yep, make a big table with a red button for an emergency meeting. I'm not going to do that. Oh my god
I'm trying to move away from the among us shit
It's all right, it's perfect. I have to do it. What's it like a baseball? What's red? Is there any red button things?
Like a balloon. I mean, that's like a big red thing use the style tool. Is there a style tool?
What do I do it style?
blueprints
Ledgehammer style. Okay. Oh
Really
Can't do that. Is there a hotel bell
It might be if I joined into we're about to do an emergency meeting
You see who's gonna be voted off in the and whatever, you know, the game that everyone's at whatever doesn't there red fire alarm
Hmm. I think it has to be in a wall. I think that red fire truck is fine
Perfect. All right. There's the button
Who we who we uh, we ship it out. Yeah, everybody get up
Now one two three, we're gonna
Henry
Really? Really? I'm surprised. I didn't think it was gonna be Henry. I thought it was gonna be ratchet
Okay. Well, let's have a meeting here
Everybody get up pause the game
Please pause. There it is. Yeah. Okay. We got everybody sitting sauce guy. Make sure the thing in the right chairs
Okay, that's gonna be here, too
Oh
Don't sleep in that sleeping bag, where's Henry everybody get in here? No, stop everybody stop moving
I'm gonna break his neck. They won't
He made it to the meeting what happened was everybody not here I thought we were gonna vote on who who's the one we kick out
What what enough free will oh I do that how I do that everybody sit down
Henry sit down. You're supposed to have no free will I told you to sit down
Oh
All right, sit down
Sit down
We have to have a meeting sit down. Stop getting up. I turn your free will off
Sit down now I
Got it. It's a getting kids back in from recess. Good luck. Okay, where's Gruntilda?
Okay
Somebody got up. No. All right. We're here. It's time for the meeting
Henry first of all, I just want to say
That the sus guy it should have been you
Should have been the sus guy
This is the worst joke taking more than five minutes. Wait a minute. It should have been a sus guy
But I mean you a little weird you have that weird face, but you're funny and everybody likes you
You
Only have to press a button once so stop pressing it twice
Gruntilda you have a pretty good story arc going. We'll keep you here and
Ratchet is everybody sit the fuck down. I was not done. I'm rushing to try to get through this
Fucking break his neck break his fucking neck
You got voted all you're up
Goodbye, he's done
See ya
He was not the imposter you're gonna have to have good luck next time
Oh, what the fuck no way. Oh my god
It wasn't even him. It wasn't even him. I
Wonder who could have been that all has to be pink then
Oh
What just happened
What is he a different person Oh right, he's the werewolf
Can we eat now reddit powers
I
He looks
Horses all right the horse has to pee
I have to kill this guy I
Have to kill him Oh
Free will is off. That's what's going on. Okay, Mike Pence
Cat okay, I can turn free will back on there go back today
He sucks
I
Don't put free will on
Should I put it on low free will I don't want low free will no keep it on high
Give it to this stupid final sleeping bag I need to seriously relax
Freaking out just go
Go sleep sleep go
This is dumb look at their needs
Yeah, it's cool. I just the guy just broke his neck in front of everybody at the emergency meeting. What are you talking about?
What's that? What's wrong with the horse in the stable?
Our energy go to bed sleep you
Sleep you're already asleep. Aren't you? Where are you? All right? Yeah, take a bath sleep
I need another bed just like sleeping that one everybody go to bed. Everybody gets sleep now, please
Thank you
That's guys in bed. Gruntilda is taking a bath. All right, why is the cat not in the bed? I don't know
Oh, I thought the horse was dead. My horse is
Mourning. Oh, no, you guys were wrong
Don't you remember it was Henry that actually took care of the animals. Oh shit. I forgot you have to pay bills
Repo man's coming. Where's the repo man?
Until just stay up. Don't go to bed yet
Where's the repo man? Yeah, Henry took care of the animals. He was actually really nice
Right, like the sus guys funny, right? I
Want I don't want the repo man
I thought that was the repo man. I was like about to speed click
Everybody loved Henry. Look what you guys did
You kidding me?
Let the repo man get up. Nobody wake up. Wait, you still can know you can't what you're dead
You're dead. You're dead. You're dead. You're dead. You're dead. You're dead. You're dead
You can't take my you can't take my bath when you're
Stop give me that
That's not good, what do I do about that?
What's the maid?
The horse it's so screwed up because of Henry it I need to like calm the horse down
Inventory, I can't touch it. I think it's fucked. What do you guys get up?
And take care of the cats and take care of the animal
You're just gonna let this cat do this out here. Oh my god. This household is so awful emergency meeting again emergency meeting
Merge emergency meeting both somebody else off these people these before these they disgust me. I want another person gone
I'm gonna move away from the among us stuff. This place is a mess
Reset the save it's so far back. No, we can't do that. No way testing cheats enabled true
Then click on the repo man thingy while holding shift
That worked
Object delete it. Oh, okay. Good. There you go
This is in use by a ratchet flush how he's asleep
All right, let's go let's do something until the is who has energy sus guy does, okay
Man to guard the bathroom. Oh repairman
Repairman eat something need you to fix the sink. Oh, they're both broken. I
Didn't pay the bills yet. Holy shit really is like four or five hours where the bills not paid
Okay
What's wrong?
Okay, what's your problem get the one where's the mail
Send a love letter
Is the other bathrooms fixed actually doing it
Shower
All right, sus guy eat something and then you're going to do something. Please get new chairs. They hate the chairs
I
Have a soccer ball. I'm good at soccer. We're gonna hang out
All right, let's uh
At the horse chairs are dirty. I'll just get new ones
Why are these so dirty? How does the chair like this get this dirty? What happened? Do you want something?
This is just this
Fix the other one get them to the club or something. I mean stuff taken feeling out-of-sorts
Disgusted germy cold shower morning
You have so much red shit
All right, we're going out. Let's go. I we get we're doing something. Hold back. Let's go. What is it? 9 p.m.
Let's go do something. Oh somewhere. Let's go
Out somewhere a bar or like a club or let's go dancing
There like a club not taken to the morgue. Okay, you gotta go bowling
I'm not taking over the graveyard science lab. Oh shit. Look at this
City hall wait, nothing fun to do in this town
Let's go to the spa
Everybody go get us go get a massage
packages
relaxing rendezvous
Packages
$3,000
All of you do it. We'll get a massage
deep tissue
Go get a body treatment
a volcanic clay bath
and get a uh
You get the full the full rendezvous package as well
All right, pause it for a second. Let's make sure everyone's doing that
Uh spa spa
The cat do a spa thing too
No, let's go in here. Okay, everybody go relax
Do I even have enough money to cover this?
Get your phone off
And I'll go in the building can't see in the building
y'all in there
Now you're a fine
horse
Needs to go to sleep
I need exercise sleep and then we're gonna go for a run and the cat ride the horse
Okay
Get exercise
Yeah, and you know who would do that henry. All right, you must feel a lot better
I don't know
What are you doing go home
I do this shit literally every day so it's pretty accurate
I actually do this like almost every day
The horse is sleeping that's good
Why don't you just go go do something then man? You like you got to go go just go go
I don't care where you go
Is it to go visit the gym?
We'll blow off some steam
The fuck is this?
What why can I do this? Where am I?
Oh, that's weird
Fish in the pool. Yeah, what was that all about? Okay, this feels like a youtube prank video
We're gonna go and we're gonna pretend to fish and somebody dresses up in a big fish costume
And they're in there and they grab a hold of the end of the line and they start moving around the guy's like
Whoa, this is a big one. What the fuck and they just get a bunch of reactions of people
And it chases him around chases him around. Oh my running after me and the fish
Throws him into the pool with his clothes on and you can catch anything here. Let's get a fish
Right again, what was that? Okay
Exercise somebody take care of this horse ridiculous. Just ridiculous scatter that
All right, the horse is doing a little bit better some hay
And then go gallop around get some exercise. All right, good. There you go. Everyone's still mourning
All right. There you go. Good. Good. Good. Don't go back in there run around go for a big jog
Just go for him. Just gallop do it go for it
Very nice. All right, I got one. I'm gonna coffee. I don't even think excuse me go to the bathroom
This is dangerous
He in the pool now inspect the water drink evil soy chai am I allowed back here
Is there blood everywhere? Oh, no, it's leaves
Come on back here back to the house
There
There's a club at the back of town
Now we need you to be socialized
let's do
None of you guys have any like seriously, I can't like just go pet the the horse just pet the horse
No
All right off to bed with you
Can't sleep when you're buzzed
Am I on drugs?
Holy shit. What was that?
What was that the lightning just struck the house?
Everybody okay?
Yet can someone please talk to the horse
Shelby saddle affections finally talk to
Talk to the horse you guys are pissing me off. I swear to god. I'm gonna drop a meteor on this house
Oh my god, I'm gonna drop a meteor on him
Thank you
There we go, that's better all of you go to actually you don't have to go to bed you can be up
uh
Any leftovers in the fridge?
And then take a piss
And then where's this club you're talking about? I'm gonna take him out of the club 8 pm 9 pm
I think we can probably go as a unit here. Yeah
All right, sus guy is gonna be asleep, but everybody else can wake up
You can wake up
All right, so rathy rachet and grunty are gonna go for go to the club
And then i'm done. I'm done. I'm gonna meteor the whole time
This turned into a sad stream it's your fault henry should still veer
Oh my god. Oh my god. Get the cat out of the way
Oh my god, get the fucking cat pause the game pause the game pause the game pause the game pause the game
Get this cat out of the way
Oh my god, get the cat out of the goddamn way
How do I cancel that I need to I need to find a way to get you to move
How do I move? Uh you
Am I fucked it's too late. No, it's not
Oh my fucking god cat
Run tilde. I need you to do something very important
until though
You need to how do I run here?
the horse
Pick up pick up the cat get the cat get the cat get the cat get the cat get the cat get the cat get the cat
Get the cat get the cat get the cat get the cat get the cat get the cat
Get the cat get the cat. Come on. Keep going move. You're almost there. You're almost out of the range
You're almost out. You're almost out. You're almost out. You're almost out. Good. Good. Good. Good. Oh, thank god
Thank god
You made it
Why did it do that? Why did it do that? Why did it do that? Why did you do that? Why why?
What the fuck
Oh my god my head
Why I didn't do that
What the fuck is going on?
Why did that happen nice aim I very clearly
Oh my god
Get all these animals out of here, this is a pig no
Oh, all right, why can't we call the fire department run till it's the only one doing anything finally. Thank you
He's just in the fire
Dude, you don't just you're in love
What this why does this keep happening with firefighters every time?
This happened. I don't know why this keeps happening
Where is life
I don't think
Who are these animals
Cats survived, but i'm glad good looks like everybody made it out go through the portal. I sold the portal
I'm done
Wait, what are you feeding him? What are you feeding him make the cat kill someone? All right
Does anybody live here scratch on door? Nobody lives here. They're all okay. They're dead
Nobody lives here. How many people have I killed?
Scratch on door for a second my brain. I thought that was the cat pretending to be a human
Sneaking around it was weird. I don't know why I was like, why am I a person?
Okay, here we go see if they let me in
You just knock it you know
Wait, let me in what the fuck just happened to that dog. Oh
Why is there a pool that goes through your living room, oh he jumped away
I can invite over people to this house. I just invite three horses over here
Who am I inviting over here using the test sheets? Oh, okay. Let's just see what happens
I invited like three horses over all right. Let me all right. Let's talk about the plan going forward
So I was supposed to play delta rune today
But I didn't and that's mainly because I didn't play delta rune chapter one
And I also kind of felt kind of shitty yesterday
but
um
Okay, here's the whole game of flu just showed up
Uh, yeah, so the plan is I still want to do delta rune
I want to play delta rune
But I need to I still want to do chapter one
so
We're not streaming tomorrow. I'm not gonna be live tomorrow
But I will be live on wednesday with delta rune
And that shop game probably and then we'll be live again on saturday with something
Rain is really loud
Are they trapped in here? What are they doing?
They just zipped away that was ridiculous. All right. Yeah, i'll see you guys on wednesday delta rune and
Uh that pawn shop game. I want to finish that was the sims 3 with a bunch of mods
The sims 4 mods are I think a little bit better
There's a lot more
Um, I think crazy things you can do in the sims 4 just because there's like there's like two or three people that have made
These like total conversion full mods, right?
But that was still a lot of fun. That was really funny. Some of the shit was just outrageous like it usually is
That was my birthday. It was great. It was really really good
So we'll see you in the middle of the week on wednesday for delta rune and then
I'll be live on saturday, too. I was hobbit day. It was great
I would have probably saturday and played a little more but
No, I once you start dropping meteors
Once you start attacking people and just killing like
It's over at that point, right?
That's why I wanted to hold off on dropping a meteor for as long as I could at least a few hours
But it didn't I dropped him on the beach. I just look at this
If you give me the toy, i'm going to play with it. You dropped a meteor five minutes in
Yeah, but then we restarted and I waited like two hours delta run delta rune one or two on wednesday, too
I already played the first one on stream a couple of years ago when it came out
But I forget everything and I don't just want to play the second one without remembering anything from the first one
So i'm going to refresh my brain on it probably play it tomorrow just off stream. Maybe tuesday, but I didn't play it
Yeah, I just didn't get around to it boys for big boys chapter two is about six to eight hours
Oh, wow, i'm looking forward to it. Thanks for the subs. There was a lot of them today, too
I really appreciate it guys. Thank you and we'll see you on wednesday
our light bulb
Bathroom light bulb one trying to figure out what that person's trying to say
There's a super secret easter egg. I don't even want to read that
I don't want to read that
Secret easter egg. I'm just gonna pretend like I didn't see that
All right. I'll see you guys later. Have a good week. See you midweek. Good night. Goodbye. Take care of yourselves
See you soon