Okay, boo, we're gonna have to kill him. All right, here we go. All right, here we go. If you hug the left wall
Keep going. Keep going. Oh my god didn't even need the uber. Didn't this guy doesn't even need the uber
He's stuck on me. Oh, he's gone
Yes, I got you get him. Yeah. Oh wow you did
No, I come back up come up here. We're gonna we're gonna chill out up here
We're gonna be very very careful. That might be a spy. I'm scared of him. No
All the whole heavy shoot him heavy somebody shoot this guy
Yeah
Yeah, you spy you still alive yeah, I just got a couple of them man I've got a heavy disguise this is awful
I'm using the
general reward
Thing that's it. Why did he just do that? That was very odd. Jesus. God, man
You ain't gonna get away with that one. I've been discovered. You ain't gonna get it with that one
You motherfucker you ain't getting away with that one. Where'd he go?
He just killed more people you ain't getting away with that one
Boo, where are you helping? I'm sorry. Oh, like I spy somewhere. He has crits too. This is not good. Where is he?
Oh, it's you. Hello. Yeah, this is spy around here somewhere. That is that him. Yeah, that's not I'm not that's not me
I'm not me
Boo get him
Is he still alive fucking hey, he's still alive just don't watch over the heavy watch over here
He's gonna backstab you dude. He's gonna appear out of nowhere and like in to kill me. All right, watch out watch out
There is there is
He's fucking hey, he'll be
No
I'm like tell you jump on down to jump down to me
This is the dumbest shit. Where are you up here in the room? I'm heavy. Just I'm disguised
I'm as a heavy where like where where are you in regards to the map going up the stairs in the attic?
Okay. Yeah. All right. All right. Same deal. I'm gonna go out that way. No, not what just keep going quick this way
Always a lot of time just go back to the spawn go back to the spawn come to the time come to the spawn
Come to the spawn. They don't they have no idea come to this one's crowd crouch crouch be crouching. You have to be crouching
Okay, get out you get your melee ready. You're gonna wait right here
Panic what what the fuck just happened? I don't know. All right, you're good. You're good. You're good. Same thing
Oh
That was terrifying no no no no no no stay alive boo
Come on, let those shots let those. Oh, you create me with a pallet jack. What a fuck face
Dammit. Yeah, just just stand up here. Yeah, you're gonna go for some like snipes sniper boo. You ready? All right. Yep. Oh
My gosh head shot
The way you just like rolled off that hill you got one
counts
What the
Your body the way you like slimed down that hill was perfect
You shot that pyro twice and then I'll send your body like fucking jello pudding down the side of the rock
I'll tell you when I have the crits. Oh, yeah, I can feel a low speed
This is sniper just waiting to ping me with in the head
Stay healed engineer
No, uber up there. All right, boo. Oh watch out behind you
Oh, I hit him in the face
Yeah, you told me to turn on I just took a pot shot. Are you ready? Oh, let's get that damn
Oh, they got Chris. No run run run. They have crits. They have crits. I'm back this way. Oh boo
I'm good. I'm good. How do they still have crits dude, Jesus
What the fuck I want you to get kills with this fucking thing
Just hang up by the century until we got it ready. It's so safe up here
Are we being worthless right now? Oh, what happened? I just I just got reflect killed
Of all the people that was stuffed in here
Yeah
Oh this isn't happening. It's all my pyro. How is he fucking back here? Why?
I'm right at this point
Down here down here. Yeah, let's see. Who's any who's here. All right, is this pyro?
Shoot this fucking pyro right in his face
He's gonna get uber don't do it get over there
Shoot murder him. He's gonna vaccinate him. Yeah, get him keep getting here
Okay
Wait, wait, wait, don't don't don't don't make it so obvious
Hey
Did I seriously just get away with that?
The pyro's there again. Nice. Nice. Nice. Nice back it up back it up. I'm gonna have an uber here soon
Don't don't be so don't be more conspicuous
We have so many people there. Thank you. Is that a crit screen? That's him
All right. I'm not in there with you. Oh, I think I got another one. Okay. Look out. Look out
Damn stab him boo stab him
All right, come in here come in here we're gonna do this
Okay, are you ready?
I think it's just no no, no, they know we're over here. We're gonna go we're gonna go like this way
That's buys me but yeah
Oh no
Oh, we were about to murder the heavy. Oh, it's all right. They can't get out. They're stuck
Oh look his entry
I can't believe I keep getting away with doing that. Uh, that uh
Oh shit
The scalp walked around the corner and as if he just punched what the fuck am I stuck on right now?
All right. Where's the where's the fucking magic medic amulet?
When are they going to add the medic amulet that gives you half a second of damage reduction? I
The bullets just I