I can't figure out. There's a song. I got a song caught in my head.
Ba ba ba ba ba. I can't figure out what the fuck it is.
Like three days.
Hey, how you doing? Welcome to the stream everybody. Hey, how you doing?
Let's reset. Hey, how you doing?
Can we hear more than three notes? I don't know any of the other notes.
When is Strawberry Magic 2?
You know, uh, you know that was made up.
People got my hopes up so bad.
There is no Strawberry Magic 2 guys. It doesn't exist. It's not real.
Yeah, it's not real. I tried looked for it.
But yeah, I'll give you the plan for the next uh, the next week here of streaming content.
It's kind of in pre-stream 30-40 minutes ago.
We came up with a little bit of a plan.
We're gonna play Wobble Dogs for now.
If the game's fun, then cool. We'll stick with it.
If after an hour or two, I'm like, meh, then we'll move on to the card game.
Mon...
Well, Mon Bozo? Mon Bozo?
If I think Wobble Dogs is a lot of fun, then we'll just do Mon Bozo
later this week.
Mon Bozo. I don't know how to say it.
Strawberry Magic 2 doesn't exist.
All the people coming in here. I know the last thing we did was Strawberry Magic.
It's fresh in everybody's mind. I know it's fresh in my mind too.
Because I had like three or four nightmares about it.
It's been fresh since
we did that stream.
Can you make a Civ 5 reference?
Um, I had never played any of the Civilization games.
Wait, that's not true. I downloaded Civ Rev
on iPad, I think, because it was the easy one.
And I didn't even make it through the tutorial.
I was just like, no, I don't care. I don't want to do this.
Now, let me move my mic. Give me a sec.
Why does everybody keep saying Morbius?
What's, what's, what's the deal here? What's, what's Morbius?
Why are you saying, well, I know what Morbius is, but what do you, why do you keep saying it?
Is that the new thing now?
All right.
Would I like, oh!
Uh, my, my whole, my whole body's fucked up.
Okay. Uh, what I'd like you to do now,
I'd like you to move over to your calendar, whatever your calendar app of your choice is.
I'd like you to scroll over to July.
And I would like you to mark on your character sheet, on your July sheet.
I would like for you to mark July 14th for the baseball stream.
July 14th is the baseball stream.
Don't have a time yet, but it'll be probably in the afternoon.
Here is your hard date. It is set in stone. It is not changing.
Unless something, obviously, like, of course it could, but that's the date that we have picked.
That's what it's going to be.
What if it rains?
Well, I, oh my God, don't scare the shit out of me.
Why them, them were doing it in the rain.
They play baseball games in the rain all the time.
Networking Andy?
How, this is not Networking Andy.
You've known about this show for two years.
I just haven't been able to do it.
Hold on, I gotta clear my throat.
Give me a second.
I don't know what's going on.
My throat's so fucked up all the time.
But, yeah, uh, there's gonna be a lot of interesting stuff on that stream.
I think that stream's gonna be one of my most favorite streams ever.
I know I say that every time there's an event stream,
and I know that I sound like a fucking 80-year-old.
Hey, hey kids.
I know.
You know, they actually turn out that way.
It's weird.
Every show that I've done over the last, like, two years has been, like, my favorite stream.
So, I don't know.
We'll see if that trend continues.
I think it's gonna be fun.
But, yeah, that's, there's your date.
The German Baseball Association, July 14th.
Mark it again.
You sound like you've been taking non-stop bong rips.
I don't smoke weed.
I don't smoke it.
Don't get out of here.
Will the pencil be at German Baseball?
No.
Why on earth would the pencil show up at that stream?
I mean, I'm not gonna tell you what's gonna happen on that stream,
because I think it's gonna be fun.
You already know some of it.
But, uh, as, oh, as Oski had to say, he had hype.
Is barf drinker gonna be there?
I saw you at MGM Grand yesterday.
No, you did not.
I'm just telling you, you didn't.
Will the stream be at 420?
No.
Are you gonna get big poppy?
Now, all right, that's, what was the announcement?
We're not talking about anything.
Any details?
Let's move over here and let's play Wobble Dogs.
That's what they're starting with today.
I promise my voice will get better.
If it doesn't, then it's over.
I don't get it.
But, let's go.
Yeah, hope you're doing well.
Hope things are going good.
Move over here.
Uh, this is, I don't even know what the hell this game is.
I know it's a game where you have, you take care of dogs and they wobble around.
Is it?
I just read the title.
I read the title of the book and then went to the book club and pretended that I read the book.
That was always the worst fucking thing, by the way.
Can I just real quickly say how many, it's been a long time since I've been in high school
or college or whatever, but I do remember specifically getting the reading, the reading
assignment and it was like, okay, we're going to go from page, uh, page, uh, one 50 to one 90.
And we're going to have a class discussion about it tomorrow.
Right.
And we're just not reading it and then having to have the teacher be like, okay, so
when this happened, what do you think was really going through their mind?
Explain that.
What do you think happened there?
Whatever the thing was.
And yeah, somebody said it, but I'm going to reiterate it.
I would pick up clues from what I, if you were the first to get called, it's over.
You're fucked.
Right.
Because then you have to be like, um, well, I, uh, I, uh, my hamster needed it.
I didn't take care of my hamster a lot and then, and I didn't read it.
But if two or three people went before you, you could kind of pick up the Wikipedia article
of what happened in those 30 pages and then just kind of go for it and be like, well, you know,
I do think when, when Lenny showed up and I've might have been, and I, I'll tell you right now
that story, uh, in the, in the barn and when he was, uh, picking the hay up, I think it went,
spoke to what a society in general and how we can handle things and spark notes, dude,
I've wrote, I'm not kidding.
This, don't take this as like a thing you should do.
Don't be a idiot like I am.
I think I've wrote an entire paper of a book I didn't read before.
I did not read the book at all and I wrote a whole paper about it.
And I didn't even like read the cliff notes or spark notes or whatever.
I just wrote a paper about just, it was just a bunch of vague shit that I said about the book.
I got a D, but I passed it.
I got a D on that, it was like a D plus.
And there was a shit load of red ink circled being like, what do you mean by this?
I think the teacher might've like felt bad that like I just couldn't,
I didn't fucking get it or something.
But I wrote an entire paper, like a, like an eight to 10 page paper on a book I did not read.
Don't fucking do that.
Don't be an idiot.
Like that, that take that stuff seriously.
But to be fair, the stuff that in school that I did take seriously that I cared about,
I took very seriously.
Eight to 10.
I was just like a vague kind of anecdotal random stuff about like how I felt about the book.
What classes did you take seriously?
I thought science was really cool.
I always paid attention in science.
Math?
No, I couldn't do it.
I was, I just couldn't do it.
I did enough where I could pass the classes and like, you know, whatever, do the worksheets
and try to get at least like pass in grade plus C whatever on the test, whatever.
But I was, I loved science.
I was, I thought it was great.
Bat chest.
Don't bat chest me because I like science.
I, that's not, okay, it's fine.
Oh, I love science.
Bat chest.
All right.
Okay.
We're gonna play Wobble Dogs.
Um, what else did I like in high school?
I thought, uh, you know what?
I liked logic.
I thought logic was really cool.
Like if, then, therefore, it was like a math problem with language, with words.
It was really actually kind of cool.
Logic was actually really cool.
If you have an opportunity to take, and I'm not fucking around.
This is not a joke.
If you're in high school or if you're going into college or if you're in college right now,
if logic is available, take it.
It's really cool.
It's, it's called logic and it's based on, it's like a math problem with words.
I loved it.
No, not logitech.
That's just philosophy.
No, but it's, it's like a math problem version of like, just look it up.
Just look up like logic class or logic math.
You'll see.
It's really interesting.
Please take it if you have an opportunity.
It'll, it'll open your mind, if it will.
I hecking love logitech.
Why did I just read that?
Because I thought, whatever.
I actually, besides, I'm not gonna, don't say anything.
I, shut up, everybody, quiet.
I actually, that company that makes some pretty good stuff.
I've used it before.
Except the, the webcams I have a problem with.
But that's it.
I only have a problem with their webcams.
That's it.
Just everybody relax.
That's programming?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Hold on.
Let me get an example.
Like a logic example.
Logic class example.
We're learning today.
Crash course in formal logic.
Logic 101, introduction.
Introduction to logic.
Yeah, just fucking go learn.
I don't, just turn, turn the stream off right now.
I'm not doing it.
Just go learn yourself.
It's interesting.
It's like if, that's, then for, then why.
It's, it's like a programming math language problem.
Just go read.
Go fucking learn.
Don't come here.
I'm playing a dog game.
You shouldn't even be here right now.
You should be in fucking school.
What time is it?
You should be studying for tomorrow's exam.
My name is...
I don't know.
I don't even like using my name.
I'm 36, dude.
I don't have exams.
Yeah, but just trust me.
Take a logic class.
I know people will be like, oh my God.
I like the logic bad chest Andy.
Whatever.
It's cool.
How about macho?
All right.
So how does this game work?
Welcome to Wobble Dogs.
This is a sandbox game where you can raise your own little hive of mutated pups.
Let's go over a few basic concepts before we turn you loose.
Let's go ahead and get you with a dog to play with.
I gotta move the can.
My dog's name is Mingle.
Fresh dog.
Hold on.
Dog.
Buddy.
Stub.
Do we need to...
Oh no.
We gotta...
Come on.
Bandit.
Congratulations on your new pup.
Now that you have got a dog, let's learn about the dog storage screen.
This gives you an overview of all the dogs you own and lets you choose which ones are
in the world at any given time.
If a dog ever accidentally ends up being removed from the world, this is where it'll end up.
Okay, so I have like a dog storage.
How come there's no auto-emote?
I think there is.
If being born is hungry work, build a food dispenser and use it to feed your new pup.
Classic food dispenser.
All right.
Build.
You guys gotta love this game.
I already know it.
Okay, so this is...
You gotta go to the fence.
Feed your dog's a healthy treat.
Where should I put it?
Are we in the corner here?
Does this cost money or is it just free?
Your dog will try to feed itself, but if you click on a piece of food,
you can command your dog to eat it.
You can also grab things to drag them around.
Use the scroll wheel or hold control to drag them vertically.
Okay.
Feed your dog.
So it's kind of...
This is like The Sims.
Get over there.
Nutritional pellet of burrito?
French fries?
What?
Dogs love to munch on this nutritious pellet.
Looks like someone's already taken a bite.
Wait, you get it?
Press the button.
This dog's eating burritos.
It looks like your pup's ready to pupate.
Press the pupate?
Also, if you haven't figured it out yet, you have to move the camera.
Help your dog pupate.
How do I get rid of this?
Oh, I gotta get rid of this.
Uh, are you all right?
What happened?
What is going on?
Why does he have a burrito in his mouth?
I had two burritos?
Okay, how do I pupate?
Not flora field guide?
What the fuck?
Standard flora found in nearly all dog-based life forms.
Beneficial flora often used to help acclimate dogs to cold weather climates.
Oh, I get this from eating a burrito?
All right, enough.
This dog is fucked up.
Okay, well, how do I pupate?
Help your dog pupate.
Okay, pupate.
What?
This is weird.
Oh, not on the burrito.
Don't eat those.
Ugh.
This is kind of gross.
Okay, mutations.
Back leg stance width.
Body girth went up and nose and ear gloss went up a lot.
All right.
Dogs pupate several times throughout their lives.
The foods they eat will influence their mutations.
Let's have you build an incubator that you hatch fertilized dog eggs.
Don't eat that.
Oh, something's wrong.
He's freaking out.
Okay, incubator.
He like ate his casing and is losing his mind.
What's over here?
Even though you don't own any fertilized dog eggs,
the incubator always lets you hatch a dog with default genetics.
How do I clean shit up here?
Oh, there we go.
This thing, this burrito, is this burrito like dirty?
Okay, well, let's have a fertilized egg.
What is going on here?
This is, oh, this is Bandit's gut.
This is weird.
Okay, so hatch this egg.
Here's another dog.
I like mud.
Mud's great already.
If you're holding an object,
you can press the delete key on your keyboard to destroy it.
Thank you.
This works on dogs too, but don't worry, they'll be okay.
Last up, don't forget to save often.
The game only autosaves when you travel to breeding mode.
Breeding mode.
Lay around and have fun.
God, okay.
So let's, let's, let's, you want a burrito?
No, I don't want you to eat a burrito.
I want like a nutritional, French fries.
Go eat a French fry.
Here, try this.
Eat that.
Eat that French fry.
Eat this.
Go eat the French fry.
What are you, stupid?
Where are you going?
Oh, he's not hungry.
If you press that button, I'm going to be very upset.
Oh wait, here comes Bandit.
Bandit's going to eat the French fry.
Are you going to eat the French fry?
Okay, so that changed your gut flora.
Oh, let's, um, good, good dog.
Click mud, then eat French fry.
I don't think they really need it.
All right, what about, uh, what's this?
Currences.
A flora found in cocoon drippings.
So what does this do?
I don't know.
It doesn't, I don't know yet.
But it turns dogs into like French fries?
Default collaboration.
This, this is like, unlocks a ton of shit.
This is like, kind of seems ridiculous.
All right.
Oh, do I get more dogs?
All right, you come over here.
Okay, I thought someone's going to eat it.
I was like, someone's going to eat that immediately.
That's, I don't know why they freaked me out.
What do I do with this?
It is edible, by the way.
Randy is waiting for you in storage.
And you get, you can feed with chicken nuggets now.
All right, let's go get Randy.
What the fuck is that?
Okay.
Oh, that's funny.
It's like, I don't know what the fuck that was.
That's genetic code?
Oh, release, spring out.
Okay.
It's DNA?
Hey, hey, why is it blood?
Okay, for a second, I thought Bandit was fucking eating mud.
What does this do?
Hey, stop that.
Stop doing that.
Please don't do that.
What was that?
That was weird.
Okay, relax.
Randy, sit.
I'm trying my best to sit.
Very good.
Very, very good.
Good dog.
So what can I do with the dirt?
Anybody want a burrito?
Just shit on an egg?
There's a dog egg in here.
Why is there, what happened?
Looks like you found an unfertilized egg.
You can use the breeding simulation to inject these with dog genes.
Just breed any two of your adult dogs
and inject the resultant genes into an egg.
Afterwards, you can hatch this egg and use the incubator.
Okay.
So Randy and Bandit.
Are you sure you'd like to breed the selected dogs
and immediately remove an egg from your inventory?
Yeah.
What?
Crossbreed or select final dog?
I don't know.
I don't get it.
What do I do?
Should I select final?
Just crossbreed them.
I don't know who's, I don't know who's got,
they're all like, look, what do I do?
Dog A and dog B.
What is happening?
Whoa.
Oh, they do have different eyes and mouths and stuff.
You're right.
All right.
Crossbreed you and one that's really jumping around.
Holy shit.
That, that, I want this one jumps.
Okay.
We got to, okay, final dog here.
What do we want?
Who has the most energy?
Is that, should we not have the dog with the most energy?
Keep going?
I want the dog with, all right, one more and that's it.
You, you can stand.
Holy shit.
Look at that.
Look at this.
All right.
That's enough.
This one.
It's like final dog.
It's going to pick one from here.
That was pretty sick.
Can anybody else do anything like that?
No, I think it's going to be you.
Rune generation complete.
The hell is going on in this game?
That's got like a Mega Man password.
This is a very elaborate thing going on.
Hey, holy shit.
This is like kind of terrible.
This is so scary.
Okay.
Fertilized egg acquired.
It's like weird sacrifice.
All right.
Dig a hole.
I get weed mix.
Egg novice.
I get cloud wallpaper.
Sick.
We need a pair of dogs for the first time.
I get another day.
I got another dog egg.
All right.
We're going to hold on to that.
I don't want to use that right now.
Wait, I can plant a seed in here.
Seed packets.
Let's go.
Oh shit.
Outdoor flooring.
All right.
Okay.
What is this?
Give me this.
Where'd you get this?
There's a prize inside?
Somebody come get this.
Hey, mud.
Come go over here and get this.
Where's mud?
They're getting hungry.
All right.
Mud, mud, mud.
Open that.
Star hologram?
I have to get it.
Oh.
Mud's going for the burrito.
Perfect.
Where's our other dog?
Oh, here we go.
Loot box.
Hey, don't fight.
What was that?
All right.
I got to feed some chicken nuggets
because that'll give us more DNA, right?
Look at mud.
You're so cute.
I'm getting just achievements every five seconds here.
All right.
I get blue blanket flowers.
Is this ready?
All right.
There's the dog with the square eye.
Um, how about squarie?
Squarie.
You got a lot of flowers here.
Okay.
All right.
Let me, I got to clean this place up a little bit.
This place is kind of a fucking dump.
Okay.
Loves to make loud noise.
The very picture of consideration.
Just wonderful, polite and aloof.
Who's the one we just, we just came up with?
Okay.
Squarie.
All right.
Stop.
Are you going to dig?
Are you going to bury the burrito?
This is going to be the cutest thing I've ever seen.
If you, if you bury the burrito,
then you're my favorite.
Bury the burrito.
Do it.
Come on.
Bury the burrito.
Hey, that's not bad.
That's not yours.
Stop it.
Hey.
Bandit.
Sit down.
Bandit, sit.
All right.
People are hungry.
Let's dig.
Let's get some chicken nuggets.
Chicken nuggets and nutritional pellet.
All right.
Come get the food.
Food's here.
The mouse sensitivity is really high.
I'm sorry.
All right.
Come eat.
No, don't pupate yet.
How come nobody's eating?
Oh, somebody took a bite out of this one.
This reminds me of a viva pinata,
but I kind of feel like there's more I can do.
At least in an immediate sense.
All right.
Go to get off.
But I don't know what they're doing.
All right.
Go pupate.
Wait.
You need to sleep.
Go to sleep first.
Go.
How do you make the dog?
How do you have the dog sleep?
I need a dog bed.
Where's this?
OK.
I need dog beds.
Decorations.
OK.
A star hologram.
Can go over here because it's kind of cool looking, I guess.
Toys.
Utilities.
Walls.
Where's a bed?
I like that.
How do I get a bed?
Whoa.
That was weird.
What?
Did I just delete everything?
I think I just deleted everything.
What happened?
Did I delete the game?
No.
I was like, holy shit.
What just happened?
OK.
How do I get out of this menu?
Cleaning time.
Oh, play pillow.
OK.
There you go.
Now you're sleeping.
All right.
You guys need to eat.
Who needs to eat?
Randy.
Eat this chicken nugget.
Bandit.
Squarrie.
Eat this pellet.
And then everybody go to bed.
There's another egg, too.
Yeah, I don't want to fertilize it yet until I...
I know you want to pupate so bad, but is that bad that you're mutate?
Oh, shit.
OK.
Just don't eat dirt.
Eat the chicken nugget that I gave you.
Why are you eating dirt?
Thank you.
All right.
Finally.
Here we go.
This place is a fucking mess.
I got to clean this place up.
OK.
So now maybe I'll be able to make another dog.
Oh, there's another egg.
OK.
Collect it.
Which of you hasn't eaten?
Randy.
Randy, you need to eat something.
Eat...
What do you like?
Energy easily forms positive connections with other dogs.
All right.
Just eat the burrito.
That's fine.
But eat something else, too.
You like a chicken nugget or something.
I'm trying my best to eat the chicken nugget.
OK.
This place...
This is a fucking mess.
Come on.
Do I have to water the plants?
Breed this.
Pet them with shift.
Oh, you can pet them.
Food.
Look at all these good dogs.
OK.
So you need to sleep.
Everyone's fed.
What is this?
OK.
There we go.
Hatch.
OK.
The body color changed a little.
Head size got bigger.
OK.
That's fine.
Yeah.
I don't want people eating this.
Get rid of this.
You're eating the flowers or are you peeing on the flowers?
Achievements.
Ham.
Hatch or mutate a dog with a very large head.
Phonograph.
All right.
Should I go?
Should I do some...
Oh, you want a pupae, too.
All right.
Go for it.
Let them sleep.
What's this one do?
This is from chicken nuggets.
Big brain dog.
My throat.
OK.
I have an egg.
I could...
Should I...
Oh, let's put that out here.
Foam ham.
Yeah, fine.
Somebody play with that.
Save the game.
OK.
We're good.
Fine.
Yeah, I'm fine.
All right.
Let's give her the dirt.
Come sleep in here.
Oh, a halved tree.
All right.
What do you got?
Squire is now...
Oh, he has a small head now.
OK.
Ears color is changing.
Front leg girth.
Body length.
His head is...
OK.
He got a little smaller.
Small brain.
Don't touch that.
Seriously, don't touch that.
No.
You need something healthy.
First of all, go like...
Go sleep in there.
Everyone's happy.
Good.
All right.
Who wants to play with this?
Delete this.
All right.
Let's make another one.
Let's do some breeding.
Where's the breeding menu?
How do I do that?
Oh, right here.
OK.
All right.
Here we go.
Ready?
Not old enough.
Oh, shit.
OK.
Never mind.
Try to make an abomination.
Oh, I want that.
Definitely.
Let's pet everybody first.
I want everyone to be happy.
OK.
Good.
Where's...
Oh, you're over here.
OK.
You're sleeping.
Is everybody hungry?
It's still french fries if somebody eat.
Make the ball pit.
Let me...
That's a little too much.
I like the clouds the most.
Clouds are the best.
I like that.
That's cool.
Maybe put a tree here so they can pee on it.
What about the phonograph?
I have more than one feeding thing.
What's going on?
Stop.
Stop it.
Hey.
There's dirt everywhere.
You can have...
All right.
Put it down.
Hey.
Look.
I have dirt right here.
See?
There's more than one.
Randy.
Look.
There's more than one dirt pellet.
Right here.
Go grab it.
See?
There's more than one.
Boy story Andy.
Please.
OK.
What should I feed?
Another chicken nugget?
I got to move this.
This is the shittiest spot.
I got to move that.
OK.
That's better.
Now I can actually collect the damn thing.
What the fuck was that?
You all right?
OK.
We're good.
Oh.
You're going for the chicken nugget.
This is a squary.
It's still a juvenile.
You like it?
Like more seeds?
Yeah.
I don't want them to be all over the place though.
Like, OK.
You...
Let's put them like over here.
This dirt patch is so fucked up.
I don't want this.
It's kind of ugly.
All right.
I'm going to plant the...
How do I get rid of this?
This is a squid game room.
It's not a squid.
It's...
This is not squid game.
OK.
I want you to dig.
What is it?
Upgrade kit?
OK.
Dig here.
Oh, you're asleep.
Never mind.
All right.
You're awake.
Dig right here.
Oh, look.
You like the tree.
That's cool.
How you doing?
Just sitting by the tree.
You want a snack?
Kind of.
What do you like for food?
My throat is so fucked up.
I don't know why.
I wish I told...
I wish I could tell you.
You want that?
Have some.
It's been smoking too much.
No.
I just...
I'm fucked.
Weather fluctuations?
It really might be.
It's starting to become like 90 degrees here
and a lot of dust.
I got a filter though.
All right.
I'm going to take one quick silent...
Dispairing for a second.
I'm going to try to get rid of it.
Did anybody hear that?
I hope not.
Because that was fucking heinous.
Rotate the tree.
You got it.
All right.
Did you dig there yet?
Stop.
Don't eat your own shit.
Don't eat shit.
Stop.
No.
Oh, now you're going to be all fucking mutated.
All right.
Stop.
What is it?
Toilet paper?
I want you to dig.
Why did you not dig over there?
Go play with this.
Go learn.
I need someone to dig over here.
Okay.
More seeds.
Very cool.
Eat poop.
Unlocks pizza bagel.
Why would eating your own shit unlock a bagel?
All right.
Everyone, people are getting hungry.
Should I just start putting out pizza bagels?
All right.
Dig right there.
And Randy.
Dig right here.
Very good.
It's a seedbed curse.
All right.
We're gonna start feeding pizza.
You've shitting so much.
Why you shit so much?
Hey.
Now you dig right here too.
Can you dig here?
Oh, what do you get?
Nice.
I don't know what just happened.
Okay.
Randy.
Right there.
I'm gonna plant some stuff here.
Don't delete the dirt.
Why not?
How do I do pizza bagel?
Is pizza bagel not in there?
How can I not move the...
What?
It's a different...
I did...
It's a different dispenser.
Oh, I got another pen.
How does that work?
You need to go to bed.
Okay.
Let's plant some seeds here.
Let's do blue flowers and golden lupine.
And daisies.
What are they doing?
Oh, they're eating food pellets.
Okay.
Stop fighting each other.
Blue flowers, red thorns.
Tell a joke already.
What would you like...
What material would you like me to do?
How about you...
How about you fucking relax?
It's a dollhouse?
Good one.
I just like felt that.
I like inhaled whatever that was.
How do I unlock the cheeseburger?
I don't like where this is.
I don't like this.
It's kind of...
It's in the way.
Isn't it?
All right.
Everyone's doing okay.
What...
I have another pen.
Oh, you can...
Okay.
So if they eat the nutritional pellet,
they'll be orange.
Interesting.
Okay.
You lose a tooth?
Baby tooth?
They can eat this?
Why would they eat this?
Should somebody eat it?
I wonder what happened.
Maybe that'll like give them different properties.
Should you eat this?
All right.
Eat that.
You all right?
Was that...
Should I not have done that?
Whoa.
Okay.
I don't know what that does.
But all right.
We need to breed a squiry.
Stop doing that.
What the fuck?
Isn't this the...
Stop.
Don't dig up the flowers.
Stop digging up the flowers.
You're digging up the flowers.
You're being annoying.
They're digging the flowers up.
Get the cocoon.
Oh, you're ready.
Okay.
Got green ears now.
It got a little fatter.
A little longer.
It's no shrunk.
Interesting.
Okay.
What about you?
Who just did that?
They made like a Minecraft house?
That's kind of cool.
This game is...
This game's cute.
Mutation up.
The flowers are kind of just overgrowing here.
Article board?
Where is...
Okay.
Hatch.
What have we got?
Oh, green.
It's green with a little head.
Okay.
Cool.
I wonder what like...
How elaborate does this go?
Can I get a lullaby?
This is my first stream.
I was...
No.
Look inside.
Are you making this gold?
How do I...
What do I...
Expel?
What did I just do?
This gold.
They found gold and I just deleted it.
They're making a mineshaft.
Lullaby or riot?
No.
You guys are weird.
I'm not doing that.
That's weird.
I think we can do a...
We can do some breeding, right?
Is that possible?
No.
Not yet.
You get it as new.
Whatever that was.
You get it from eating dirt?
We need a bedtime.
No.
I...
I'm not doing it.
And this is not one of those like...
Chat!
I'm not gonna do the thing!
I'm not gonna...
I'm not actually doing this.
That's weird.
All right.
Eat that.
Who's hungry?
Anybody still hungry?
Everybody needs to go to bed.
Right now.
Go to bed right now.
Bounce?
Like this little like...
Fucking giraffe.
Whatever it is.
You just get like...
They have like giraffe heads.
Oh!
You found dirt!
Good job.
Everybody go relax in bed.
Go...
Oh, we can upgrade the den.
Oh, shit.
This is a...
All right.
Somebody eat this.
Who do I want to eat this?
All right.
Let's have Squary do it.
Because Squary is already like...
I don't know.
Squary seems to have the most mutations.
Okay.
Eat that.
Eat that like clump of gold dirt.
This shit is gold.
Please import a fucked up dog.
Play white noise?
Dude, no!
I'm not playing white noise.
It's just the lighting.
It's...
Oh, okay.
Doggy bopper.
Destruct a den.
Oh, I got a jungle food dispenser.
And a dog biscuit.
All right.
Let's go.
I feel like this is gonna start to get really interesting here.
What do we got?
Above or below?
Probably right next to it.
Right here?
Oh, shit.
All right.
Nice.
Very nice.
I want...
Okay.
Ancient relic food dispenser?
That sounds cool.
Ooh.
Let's just get some of these out here.
Banana.
Coconut.
Cut fruit.
Squary, eat that.
Squary, go eat the banana.
And then...
What are they eating?
Oh, they're like...
They're sharing a delicious shit meal together.
What happens if you scold them?
I don't know.
Flowers are coming in.
All right.
Bandit, eat the coconut.
I wonder what you get from this.
Ooh.
Good, good, good, good, good, good.
That's a new death.
That's new genetics.
Okay.
I need...
Randy, go eat the cut fruit.
More mutations.
Go eat this.
Eat the coconut, actually.
Everybody doing all right?
You're not having a good time.
Here, come here.
This is the Sims LSD DLC.
Can you make them have a pink nose?
Maybe.
All right.
You need to eat something.
Come on out.
Come on here.
You okay?
Road carpet?
That's funny.
All right.
We have new mutations.
Don't know what they do.
They're just from eating shit.
All right.
I think we're almost time to breed.
Can I put them up with bananas?
How's everybody doing?
Randy, go to sleep now.
I can upgrade it again?
Randy, go to bed.
How come Randy's just sitting here?
Go sleep in the house.
Come on, Randy.
Get up.
Upgrade to the Spencer.
Can I?
I have to do it in the build...
My god, listen to me.
This is like the worst I think it's ever been.
It's been...
It's horrible right now.
All right.
He's sleeping.
That's good.
Clip.
The Lich King was announced today.
Are you going to stream it when it launches?
No.
Streamer sings chat a lullaby.
I was shit-faced, okay?
What do you want me to say?
No, it's yours.
That was a Fortnite clip.
The end of this is what you wanted to watch.
I was shit-faced.
The POV.
God damn.
That's so fucking stupid.
Imagine if you looked like that.
That's...
All right.
Who didn't eat the...
Who didn't eat their...
Who didn't eat their whole dinner?
Their banana.
There.
This is your lullaby.
This is kind of...
This is just growing out of control here, I think.
Give us a lullaby and wipe away the debt.
No.
All right.
Squarie, play with this.
Go grab that.
Look at how everyone's having such a great time.
I still have two eggs that...
Okay.
I got to...
I'm probably going to put whatever...
I...
Whoever gets breeded here is going over here.
Because we're getting...
This is getting kind of crowded.
He's really rude today?
What?
What are you talking about?
Rude?
How am I rude today?
What do you mean?
I got some other shit, didn't I?
All right.
Let me...
Let me prepare this place.
No, I don't like...
That looks...
That looks kind of scary.
All right.
This one's going to be the ball pit
with the starry background.
There'll be a doggy bopper in the corner.
We'll do this one in here.
And...
Okay.
This one's pretty much ready.
So when...
How...
When do you become adults?
Use the tubes to connect them?
Really?
It's like starting room.
Oh, shit!
That's cool.
All right.
They have...
Oh, they can go wherever they want now.
That's pretty cool.
What the fuck?
What just happened?
Are you all right?
Mud, what just happened?
Who just threw him?
We gotta get...
Hold on.
In here.
Oh!
What?
Okay.
I didn't know you could do that.
It has to be in this room, doesn't it?
All right.
We'll just delete it.
But I'm going to put that in here.
Oh, I have to...
Okay.
There's a big tree in the corner.
This...
Maybe this should be the playroom.
Should this be the playroom?
I think this is going to be the fun playroom.
I'm going to have like an eating...
A feeding room too, eventually.
Yeah, this would be like the fun room.
They want to like play with like toys and stuff.
They come in here.
Okay, because that's the balls on the ground.
Means...
Or...
Yeah, that's better.
I think the hot dog...
No, that's going to be the feeding room.
I like this.
This looks good.
Okay, cool.
All right.
Dev and Chat.
What's going on, Dev?
Big fan of your game.
Are you high?
They left.
Oh, side pupae.
All right.
This is going to be interesting.
Squary has eaten a coconut, a banana, and somebody else's shit.
So I wonder what's going to happen.
Oh, you're ready to go too.
Ooh, ooh.
You ready to go?
All right, let's go.
This is the moment here.
You've never seen a high person.
I wish he was high.
Yeah, I love how acting a little strange means on drugs, right?
Like you're on drugs.
What do we got?
This is Squary.
The only thing that really changed is he got a lot bigger.
Did you, though?
You look still kind of small.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Is your legs too small?
Big head.
All right.
Color changing a little bit.
It got a little bit bigger.
I think it's now we can actually do some breeding here.
So what do I want to do?
I definitely want...
Squary's got some interesting traits.
All right.
Let's do...
You can go to sleep first.
Squary and mud?
What do you think?
Dead body reported.
This is a foam ham, man.
Are you injecting cannabis?
I deleted this.
Why is it still here?
Oh, my God.
There's fucking...
I just threw them around the room.
Why is it still here?
Delete this.
Oh, wait.
You okay?
Speak.
Very good.
All right.
Hang out in the playroom.
That's fine.
Where is everybody?
All right.
It's time.
Dude, what do you mean not old enough?
Not old enough?
How?
Are you hungry?
Just sitting at the food dispenser.
This is like auto.
I have a little...
What's wrong with you?
I have a little cabinet that I keep dog food and dog treats in.
And I'll get up.
They'll be like on the couch or something.
And I'll just get up and kind of walk through the kitchen area.
And he's just sitting there.
He's going like this.
Sitting and looking at me right in front of the cabinet.
Just like...
I don't know how long he's been sitting there.
But he's just like, I'm here.
And it's getting old.
They're not ready to pass on just yet.
But they don't have much time left.
What?
Oh, no.
Randy's getting older.
Oh, shit.
I need to...
We got to breed, right?
We got to breed now.
I got to breed right now.
We got to breed.
I have to do it.
We're going to like...
Our population is going to decrease.
I like...
Okay, I want...
I like the eyes.
Who's...
Very vocal.
Okay.
I think this is good.
Should I keep going?
It's the giant...
It's the rat.
Yeah.
All right.
Let's get you in here.
And let's get...
You in here.
You're funny.
You're doing like a funny thing.
Again?
I think that's good.
I don't think there's enough different genetic mutations here that can happen.
Generate it 50 times.
What?
Is that going to be bad?
Won't that be bad?
Keep going.
Is it a cow?
What the fuck was that?
All right.
Well, we're going to take the cow.
And...
Somebody else?
You?
All right.
They're pink.
Again.
All right.
I don't want to do another one.
That's it.
No more.
All right.
We're at 83% stability.
I don't want...
That's too much.
Who just made the weird sound?
Keep going.
What?
What's going to happen?
I don't know what's going to happen.
83% stable?
This one's huge.
I think...
All right.
This one.
I don't...
But that one might cause a problem in...
More?
No.
Is it going to cause a problem?
He's really kind of rambunctious.
Let's go.
All right.
Now we're going to watch this.
The dev tweeted at you.
Really?
Shut up.
That didn't happen.
Nobody tweeted at me.
I don't see it.
It's not...
I didn't see it.
All right.
We know how this works.
That's cool though.
The president is on the phone.
You should pick it up.
Ah.
I just...
I don't know why.
I just see like...
Oh, what's going on in the White House today?
And there's like a picture of like Joe Biden
sitting in a chair like this.
With his like sunglasses like down here
and he's just sleeping.
And my Wobble Dog stream is like...
On like the...
Like a big TV in like the Oval Office.
Like, oh, your stream is like so boring.
But why would he be watching?
Oh, water.
Why wouldn't he be?
I don't know.
Imagine how...
Imagine any like that big public figure
just doing the...
This thing.
Nobody looks good when they're sleeping
not in bed, by the way.
Everybody looks fucking crazy.
Why is that?
There has been like pictures I know
that have been like...
Everybody has that photo, right?
Like, oh, mom took it or something.
Where you're like in like the car
or you're on the couch or something
and you're like...
Like, what the...
Why do we do...
What's going on here?
Why do we go like...
Like, it hurts to do that.
It's actually hard to do that.
How come we don't go like...
It's always like...
All right, incubate that egg.
I can't wait to see what happens here.
We're unknowingly supporting our heads.
That's weird.
The body was never meant to fall asleep
sitting upright.
You literally showed a picture of you
once when he's sleeping
and he looked like beef?
Beef and cheese?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Oh!
All right, we need a name.
Spam.
Ew.
All right, welcome to the world, Spam.
How are you?
You're going to get a steady diet
of coconuts and bananas.
You must be very hungry.
Go relax.
How's everybody doing?
All right, Mud, you need to...
Is this...
Aren't they close to...
I need to breed again,
but I don't need to.
Not yet.
Well, that...
You're going to die much faster
if you keep doing that.
All right, Mud.
Should I breed again?
I don't think I want to.
You can recycle plastic bottles
by giving them to a dog?
What if you eat this...
Well, I don't...
I don't know, but you should probably
shouldn't eat plastic.
What happens if I eat...
Grab it.
Throw it.
That was a good try.
Try it again.
Throw it.
Come on, you can do it.
Come on.
Get over there and do it.
Throw it.
Come on.
You can do it.
Oh!
That was so good.
You threw that.
Okay, now destroy that.
Oh.
Your dogs can't walk.
There's a baby.
It just came out.
What do you mean?
This is the weirdest one.
I can't wait to breed this one.
He's a baby.
Yeah, the baby...
Oh, sorry.
The baby doesn't know how to walk.
What are you doing?
I want to feed a very good diet of bananas
and coconuts.
I don't want you eating chicken nuggets
or anything.
I want you eating good, nutritious fruits.
And it has lived a long, full life
and it's now time for them to pass on.
Oh no, Randy.
Oh!
Oh my God.
What?
No, don't eat him.
He's going to go eat his body.
No, he's the weird one.
He's the weird one.
Don't...
You're not going to eat that, right?
How do I...
What do I...
Dog head?
Oh!
Should I...
I don't know what I should do.
Is this extra DNA points?
Oh my God.
Do I get DNA or something?
Is this worth...
I don't know.
Is it worth doing this?
I might get like DNA points.
I don't know.
All right.
I'm just testing this.
I don't like this
but this might actually unlock something.
It does.
Okay, don't eat every...
Okay, this is fucked up.
High quality dog core?
What is that?
High quality dog core.
Mysterious orb.
Should I open it?
Cracked open.
What is that?
Somebody should eat this?
All right.
You don't look at this.
I don't want you to see this.
You just stay over here and eat the coconuts.
Lifespan extended.
Oh, look at that.
Okay.
All right.
You need to go to bed.
You guys go to sleep.
Eat this coconut.
It's nutritious.
Don't eat other dogs, please.
Are you ready?
Okay.
Pupate.
You're both ready to pupate.
You want to eat that first?
Eat that first because I want you to get more mutations.
I mean, one of you did.
That was fucking cool.
All right.
You know, go for it.
Pupate.
Where's...
We'll figure that out later.
All right.
What do we got?
You just ate something weird.
Now you're...
Okay.
Adult, back legs, front legs.
He's pretty big now.
Front, bottom, leg length.
I feel like the proportions are kind of wrong.
Interesting.
What happened to you?
Nothing really.
Okay.
You got a little wider.
Very interesting.
You can't walk now?
Yeah, you'll be fine.
It's fine.
There we go.
Oh, God.
You actually can't walk.
You need to go to bed.
Okay.
You're fine.
You can walk.
They do need to go to sleep, though.
All right.
Let's clean up a little bit.
This is kind of a mess.
A mess.
Okay.
I got a lot of things to unlock.
Clean up 10 poops.
A ham slider.
Cool.
Witness of death.
Dog Vision Jr.
Open up a dog core.
Rock Speaker.
Play for an hour.
Space Lab Food.
Oh, hell yeah.
All right.
We got to...
Let's do this right.
What do you think?
Up top?
And then connect this.
Oh, shit.
I can't do that.
This is where they're going to...
The feeding will be here.
I don't think they can connect like that.
Oh, they can?
Can I do that?
Starting room?
Oh, starting wall.
Okay.
Starting room.
How do I move?
There we go.
What the...
Okay.
That works, right?
How do they get up there?
Can they get up there?
I'm not sure they can go that way.
Oh, there we go.
All right.
Now, how do I...
This is fucked up.
How do I remove this one?
Oh, God.
I'm just starting to look at McDonald's play place.
Okay.
There we go.
So, this is going to be the feeding room.
What should I do?
Food.
Let's do like a food room.
Actually, this kind of reminds me like Chuck E Cheese.
Let's do that.
To check the Twitter.
All right.
I'm checking Twitter.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
What am I looking for?
Okay.
We need a nap.
Please sing your fans a lullaby.
They won't stop asking me about it.
Please breed your dogs.
Aren't I doing that?
I'm breeding.
Or please breed your dogs.
Didn't I do that?
Yeah, this actually is the dev, isn't it?
Okay.
Well, that's cool.
I didn't...
I did it, didn't I?
Sing, chat, a lullaby.
When you get old enough, over 21.
You woke up the baby.
All right.
Food.
That was Trump.
All right.
This is the food room.
All dogs will come up here to the cafeteria station.
This is where they will be enjoying their meals.
This is going to be huge.
This is an ugly room.
All right.
Food.
There should be something to eat on.
Oh, no.
I actually don't think so.
Okay.
So now let's go play.
We got alien fruit.
Dehydrated treats.
Moon cheese.
Sure.
Onion.
Oh, okay.
If they're hungry, they come up here.
They just got a lot of food.
They can just eat on the ground.
It's going to mutate the fuck out of them, though.
But who cares?
Whoever's hungry.
Okay.
I need to hatch you now.
Let's go.
Very cool.
Front leg stance width.
Body girth.
All right.
We need to get...
I got to get that egg in here.
Okay.
We got to do another one.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Mud and, uh, squary.
Let's go.
What do I do?
What happened to the fourth one?
Oh, it's dead in the other room.
Definitely this one.
All right.
We got a raid from G4.
G4 TV.
You guys just fucking dump raids on me.
Thanks, guys.
I hope you're having a good stream.
This is like the...
This is the fourth time the G4 has been here.
What's up, G4?
I appreciate it.
Thanks a lot.
All right.
I'll take this one to zero.
Let's do two, like, kind of little ones.
G4 would like an encore.
All right.
This one's kind of weird.
How long should I do this for, though?
These two.
They're really, like, thin, skinny ones.
Do it until zero?
This one's really, like, glossy.
Yeah.
That one.
These two, like, pieces of fucking ham.
Whoa.
All right.
We got...
Interesting.
Again.
This really long one.
What happened?
Oh!
This one's...
Okay.
No.
We're good.
I don't know which one...
Should I take one?
I think I want to take this one.
One more?
Take the long one?
All right.
One more time.
Okay.
This one.
Look at this one.
That's so weird.
All right.
How about one more?
One more.
They're becoming, like, slices of bacon.
These two.
Like, yes.
Uh...
It looks...
Do it...
Keep going?
No, no.
All right.
The stability is going lower here.
I think it's going to be this one.
They have six legs?
What the fuck?
Oh!
All right.
Do not be disturbed by progress.
Okay, Frankenstein.
I mean, the Dr. Frankenstein, not the monster.
Frankenstein's monster is the name of that character.
Stupid.
All right.
We know how this works.
Let's do it.
I'm very excited.
Book report Andy.
How many animals do we have left?
Okay.
Let's get that incubated.
Who's hungry?
All right, spam.
Head up to the designated food room and I want you to eat an onion ring.
Are you hungry too?
No, you're okay.
Oh, Squary's...
Squary's been...
Okay, Squary's eating two people now.
All right.
E-eat this.
We need Squary to live a long time.
Take another egg, please.
Squary, then go upstairs after this.
Oh boy, Squary.
What are you doing?
You all right?
Eat that core.
Go up there.
What are you doing?
Oh, you're just having so much trouble.
What's wrong with this one?
This one can't really walk.
This one takes a very long time to get anywhere.
This is sad.
I'll bring it down.
Can I bring it down?
All right, eat that onion ring.
Eat it.
You don't like it?
You look like you like it.
Okay.
I don't...
Oh, he puked.
Why did he puke?
Okay, wait.
Why?
Why did you puke?
Are you all right?
Oh, shit.
No, no.
Don't eat the puke.
Oh, what's wrong with it?
You don't like onion ring.
Don't eat teeth and puke.
I don't know.
Didn't like the onion ring.
Oh, okay.
Are you all right?
Here, have a coconut.
That's like nutritious.
Sweating.
What's wrong?
Lazy doesn't care for food and rude.
How are you going to stay alive?
You don't like food?
What?
Uh-oh.
Eat the coconut?
Lazy, rude, and doesn't eat food.
Okay.
How about just raw?
Here we go.
I got to put some of this food down here.
Is it like rotten?
Is that the problem?
How do I lift stuff up?
Is there a way I can lift this up vertically?
I know there's a way.
There it is.
Everyone start eating food, please.
Alien fruit.
Somebody eat it.
Moon cheese.
Okay, there we go.
You eat the alien fruit.
I feel like that should be what you should be doing.
Raw.
Just hungry.
What just happened?
What's going on?
What's wrong with everybody?
Why are you all wet?
Eat that like cheese.
The stock.
Okay, has Squary been asleep for like a week?
Oh my god.
This is so sad.
I don't think this is...
I don't think...
I don't think rock and walk.
Here.
Eat that.
You like it?
Okay.
Half eaten food.
Oh, you're ready to mutate.
Let's go.
Why are they all wet?
I don't understand.
Why are they wet?
They're all wet.
There's no AC.
He doesn't like it.
He threw up.
What?
Who's even alive?
Oh, okay, you're fine.
Let me get you a...
All right, hold on.
Hatcho mutated a dog with more than four legs.
Honeycomb.
Hopefully you mutated into something.
Oh, you got...
It's huge.
Huge.
And what else?
34%.
Doesn't care for food.
Lazy and is rude.
Can this dog even fit in the house?
All right, yeah.
Go get some sleep.
Okay, who else?
You guys are doing fine over here.
All right.
Should I do more breeding?
I'm gonna have to breed these two again.
And this time we're going to take them to zero.
Oh, okay.
They sound like snakes.
How about...
Yeah, let's do it.
You should import somebody else's dog.
Well, hold on now.
Not quite.
Salmon.
Okay, what does the stability actually mean?
Can somebody help me out with that?
What does that realistically mean?
Less stability equals more mutations.
Oh, okay.
That's how crazy it is.
Oh, we got an orange.
Orange dog.
All right, we're gonna get an orange.
It's huge.
All right, we're getting weird.
Again?
What happened?
We lost some along the way here.
All right, they're not that...
They don't look that bad.
They look actually pretty healthy.
They still look actually perfectly fine.
How about these two?
34% stability, but they look all right.
All right, maybe one more.
All right, look at this one.
Orange and green and looks very strong.
Keep doing it.
Go to zero.
Again?
All right, this is where it's zero.
We're good.
Oh, yeah.
I got an achievement for that.
You got the perfect dog.
I think I'm getting some cool stuff here.
Okay, get a litter in the...
Get a tiny litter in the breeding simulation.
Okay, an egg.
And then what do I get for this?
Simulated floor.
Cool.
All right, let's get that egg in there.
All right, spam is...
I don't think I want to breed spam.
I think we just let spam die.
Because, you know what I mean?
It's not looking great.
Sad.
What the fuck?
Oh, this is the playroom, right?
You're going to have fun in the playroom?
Yeah, go play with this.
Go bite that.
Here we go.
All right, how about...
Creamsicle.
Butter?
No.
Carrot.
Cheese, brick.
Butterscotch.
Sherbert.
All right, Sherbert.
I want to feed you really weird shit,
so I want you to come...
Are you able to walk?
How are you doing?
Some dogs eat to live.
This one lives to eat.
Not very interested in other dogs.
And lazy.
Why are they all so lazy?
Look, they can't even do anything.
It takes them so long.
All right, what do I want to feed you?
Something.
Oh, mud.
How are you doing?
You want some food, mud?
How about a ham slider?
Let's try that one.
Good to go.
Try this.
You like ham?
You do?
All right, good.
All right, I want something weird here.
Alien fruit.
I'm going to feed that to the guy we just came up with.
Get in there.
Where's the fruit?
What happened?
Climb.
This takes a while here.
Come on.
All right, where did the fruit go?
Where did that alien fruit...
I don't understand.
It's just gone.
It just doesn't exist.
All right, give that a try.
What did you get?
Coconuts?
Oh, Spam actually likes coconuts.
That's insane.
Spam hates food.
Okay, Spam likes coconuts.
That's very important to remember.
I don't have any den upgrades.
Okay, eat this like tooth, too.
All right, raw.
What do we get?
All right, got a little more green.
Legs got bigger.
Legs got...
Actually, this might actually help a lot.
Do you want to eat like a tooth or something?
Here, eat this stuff.
They're all so slow.
They all can't even move.
They all...
Look at how...
Okay, this is the only one that actually walks.
Go eat a banana.
Cool.
How are you doing?
Very nice.
Probably need some sleep.
Go eat some more ham.
Eat whatever.
I don't want to do that.
All right, well, don't.
This costs money because Spam just keeps eating coconuts over and over again.
Go eat this like moon cheese thing.
I want to see some mutations, please.
But didn't I unlock a new food?
All right, raw's asleep.
Can I breed anybody?
Go to bed.
I can, but I don't want to yet.
Everyone's tired.
Iron fence.
Fence.
The good thing is nobody's like kind of...
Nobody's...
Everyone's pretty happy.
Still a few that I haven't found yet.
A lot, actually.
Stop destroying the dirt.
What does the dirt do?
Why?
You have to name somebody Macho.
That's a good idea.
Put the dirt clumps in the dirt patch.
What's that stick bug meme?
Foam cylinder.
What are you doing?
Get out of here.
What the fuck are you doing?
Stop doing that.
Don't do that.
You just woke up your brother.
Okay, fine.
Roll over.
No, you didn't.
See, I did it.
Good job.
Oh, an egg.
Does anybody know any tricks?
Can you do a roll over?
Wow, you can do it.
Mud's smart.
All right, mud.
Um, you need to go to bed.
Do you know anything?
Can you do a roll over?
You can, wow.
Actually, they're pretty smart.
All right, you need to go in here now.
Just go sleep somewhere.
Sleep right here.
Stay away from the incubator.
That's not for dogs.
All right, you want to eat.
You need to mutate, too.
Eat this like weird cheese.
Feed somebody a cocoon.
I can't wait to breed this.
Sir, hello.
I'm writing an article for my school paper.
Would you like to give an explanation
for the events that occurred three days ago
during the strawberry magic stream?
What do you want to know?
Okay, good.
Sleep.
Where are you?
Where is this?
No, not yet.
And all right, what happened?
Not much.
Just kind of grew up a little bit.
All right, so somebody said don't fuck with the dirt, right?
Just leave the dirt.
But did you find this?
This was recommended a bunch of times.
It's been on the list for a little while.
I think it's cute.
I think this is fun.
All right, spam needs to eat.
What should I feed you?
I got something new.
Yeah, honeycomb.
Try this if you like it.
You like it?
Well, you guys both apparently like that.
So let's just put another one over here.
Try it again.
You look more like a sheep than you a dog.
Hey, anybody else hungry?
It's query.
Who is this?
Yeah, you go in there and go to sleep.
You need to sleep.
All right, let's rock it.
Raw, eat a honeycomb.
I feel like that would like fuck you up.
Like your DNA or whatever.
It's very nutritious,
but I feel like it's going to like
fuck up the DNA stuff.
It's going to be interesting.
Sheep.
All right, now go to sleep.
Hey, what do we get?
Berry bros.
Ooh, just got bigger.
Body got glossy.
I think I can breed now.
Can I?
No, not yet.
All right, eat another honeycomb.
Eat that.
And then go in the corner and sleep.
Who else should eat this?
Okay, mud, come out here and eat this.
I feel like the honeycomb is going to do really cool stuff.
Spam can breed.
They're not on the list, are they?
Oh, we can, can they?
Not old enough.
See, not old enough.
Mud, eat this.
Light, loud, and aloof.
That's fine.
What are you doing?
You okay?
How come there's some...
Why are they sweaty sometimes?
Dehydrated tree.
Let's see what this does.
Eat this.
You like it?
Where is everybody?
Yeah, you're over there.
You need to eat something too.
Dry landscape?
This is kind of getting out of hand.
Just eat the dirt.
Or should we?
No.
Let's only give spam.
What are you doing?
How about a cut fruit?
I want a lot of different options, genetics-wise.
All right, try that.
You don't like it?
Vents tool option has something for removing plants.
Okay.
Oh, you like it.
You're fine.
Did I unlock anything new?
I got something to do flooring.
Oh, this thing.
Put it in the playroom.
That's kind of huge, but whatever.
Everyone want to check it out?
All right, you ready to go?
Go for it.
Green shag.
I think now we can breed.
I'm gonna go try it out.
Check out the roller.
Come on, play.
I just bought it.
Come on, play with it.
Play with it.
They don't even want to play with it.
Save the game.
Yep.
How are you supposed to play with a big tube?
I don't know.
Like you get your, you put your arms up and you put your whole body flush with it.
And then you put your face down, you grip with your hands and you put your entire,
you kind of mold all around it and then push forward and like roll, roll, roll, roll.
But you get on top of it and you do like the, like the run thing, like a big log.
Oh, no.
Did that, are you okay?
Oh, I don't think you like this.
Are you having fun?
I don't think this, I don't think Sherbert's having fun doing this.
Are you?
Fight it.
Yeah, have banana.
You don't do CBD on stream anymore?
No, not really.
Okay, what do you got?
Longer legs.
You should.
No, I shouldn't.
I told you when, when I was playing Saw 2, I could not read an analog clock and I realized
can't really take like THC in stream.
I walked in a circle for like an hour.
It was for, it was a long time.
Oh, a caterpillar.
I gotta pee.
I'll be right back.
Break time.
I have returned.
I wanted to refill my drink too.
It's hot.
Crazy thing about Vegas.
Vegas goes from it being 50 degrees outside to a hundred in three days.
It's kind of insane.
Camera, hold on.
Oh, we can see him.
How's that?
Is that better?
Why do I look gray?
I look fucking gray.
All right, there we go.
That's better.
Okay.
I said to add some artificial color.
You guys don't understand.
It was like with the ring light off and me just sitting here, I'm, I'm fucking gray.
I have like dark purple eyes and gray skin.
But yeah, man, we, we, I had a little bit of flush.
Oh my God.
I just, what's been happening?
Everybody okay?
I don't think it was paused.
Ooh, wood paneling.
Oh, okay.
Ow.
Anybody ready to breed?
Not yet.
Spam is handsome.
Yes, but actually I didn't like spam in the beginning, but they're, they're growing on me.
Oh, somebody pee peed.
Ooh, cool.
What's that one?
Very good boy.
That was so cute.
It's okay if you have a tiny head.
That's fine.
Roll over.
All right.
Well, you haven't, you have fun playing with the dirt.
You really are like an insect.
Yeah.
What is it?
That was very, very good.
That was very good.
Spam is hungry.
Well, let's feed.
What a chicken nugget or something.
Yeah, we haven't, we haven't fed a chicken nugget to anybody.
What are you looking for?
What do you want mud?
You hungry?
You want something from in here?
Dehydrated treat.
What do you want?
How about an onion ring?
Oh, you want cheese.
Okay.
What about onion ring?
Yeah.
Right.
Oh, I don't know.
Why did that clip take off so much?
I don't, I don't understand.
It's the onion ring thing.
I don't know.
Why did they take off so much?
Grandma, I love you, but what the fuck is this game?
This is Wobble Dogs and it's on Steam and it is very cute.
It's very fun and it's fun to play.
It's just chill.
I like games like this a lot of times.
It's just cool to hang out and just play.
It's a genuine human emotion.
That's why I mean, this is fun.
All right.
Who wants a chicken nugget?
Are you, you're not eating him, aren't you?
Earned out car.
Why would I want to use that?
You want, you want chicken nugget?
Oh, this is my chicken nugget.
That's so, I love that.
I don't want to eat it.
I just want to take it with me.
Well, where are you taking it?
You should, oh, I, oh, I think,
I think he's taking it away from everybody
because he wants to eat in private.
Yep.
There he goes.
Yeah.
He wants to eat in private.
You all right?
How much more private can you get?
I like mud.
Yeah.
What was that?
Oh, you're going to bury the chicken nugget.
You should eat it.
I'm not going to tell him what to do.
Okay.
No, you should eat it.
Eat it because you're hungry.
Oh, ready for a mutation.
Sherbert takes a long time to level up here.
All right.
What have we got?
Smaller.
I think you got smaller.
Yeah.
Lower body length.
A little bit longer legs.
What happens now to spam?
He's becoming human.
Oh, Jesus.
Even bigger.
Snout rotation.
No, actually didn't get bigger.
Lost a little bit of length in the front but got a little wider.
Oh, no, no, no.
But how do we?
It's okay.
This is sad.
I liked mud.
Okay.
Mud.
We're going to breed mud and spam.
Massive litter.
Oh, what's that mean?
I don't know.
What should we do?
Should I keep going?
Should I make a huge dog?
I don't know.
Wrong one.
This one and this one back here has brown ears.
Let's do that.
Very cool.
All right.
Look at huge eyes.
This one.
I like this one.
I want this one.
I don't want to do anymore.
This one right here.
That's the one.
This next one I'm going to just go absolutely nuts.
Don't crack mud's orb.
Oh, I can memorialize it, right?
Okay.
Now we're going to do mud.
No, we're not going to do mud.
We'll do squary and spam.
Whoa.
Tiny.
Should I do one of the tiny ones?
Oh, these don't look that good.
They're kind of big and small.
You're having way more fun.
Actually, but you're bigger.
Oh, God.
And this one.
Look at this one.
Cool.
All right.
This one and this.
The two big ones.
Now we'll do the little ones.
This one looks cool.
Huge.
All right.
Now we're going to do the two huge ones.
Look at how big this one's head.
Look at this one's huge nose.
That one.
Look at how huge this one's nose is.
No, I like that one.
I don't want any no different.
I want it.
I want that one.
What is this?
Where did I get a ball?
Where's mud?
They said mud was close to passing away, right?
Hey, just go to sleep.
Yeah.
Mud, go to sleep over here.
You want like a treat or something?
Just go lie down over here.
You can lie down.
Go on.
Yeah.
There you go.
You should lie down.
Oh.
Squarry wants to be with mud at the end here.
Oh, this is so sad.
Hey, we're friends.
Get a massive litter.
Industrial.
Ooh, that's probably good.
Pull them down.
Okay.
Well, we're going to leave mud alone.
Don't eat that shit.
Stop eating poop.
Don't eat poop.
All right.
Everyone's hungry.
What are you looking for?
No, no like weird shit.
Just like a burrito.
We haven't had it.
Nobody's had a burrito in a while.
Here, eat this burrito.
And we'll spawn some like coconuts.
A little piece of cheese.
Maybe some french fries.
Yeah.
And come up here and eat if you want to eat.
Eat that burrito.
Oh, I love the nose.
How about like schnoz or something?
Spud?
Actually, Spud's a good name.
Spud.
I love Spud.
Okay.
How's it going in here?
Mud's still okay.
You want to have some food, mud?
Defying all odds.
Mud is still alive.
Interesting.
You seriously can't go that far?
Oh my goodness.
There you go.
Eat it.
And eat like a banana or something too.
A coconut.
Not just junk food.
I have to-
I forget spam cannot move that fast.
So have a coconut.
Wrong dog?
What do you mean?
Spud's fine.
Spud's not hungry.
Everybody's eating.
All right.
Come on out, Mud.
Let's give Mud a-
Like a guava or whatever this is.
Old man.
Guava puree.
All right.
You're kind of just stuck over here.
Get over here.
Go play with the other dogs.
Rude.
Oh good.
Squary.
Delicious.
And eat a coconut too.
Oh be careful, Mud.
You're so close to being like dead.
That's not-
That's so scary.
I don't like when you do that.
What do you want?
You want something?
Why don't you two like play?
Oh no.
This is like-
Actually like it hurts.
Oh no.
Why do they have to do that?
Put his head back on.
Why does his head have to pop off?
Okay.
Now I don't want anyone to eat Mud.
I don't want that.
I want Mud's life orb.
What do I do?
Just destroy?
Or should somebody eat him?
How do I get the orb?
Squary, get away.
Somebody has to eat it?
You have to eat it.
Squary.
No, let's have you come up here and eat.
You-
Can I pick you up?
This talk is fucking stupid.
I think Squary will eat-
You are all such morons.
Okay.
Well, Squary's gonna-
They were friends, weren't they?
You just-
Shit on his-
All right.
I want to get-
I don't like this.
I want to get rid of this.
Okay.
I don't want any-
I'm just gonna move-
Get rid of it.
Right?
If I destroy-
Stop!
Please.
Somebody has to eat it?
Bring this weird one up here.
Where are you?
Get off of that.
God.
All right.
Just eat this, please.
I hate this.
I don't want to eat this.
Spam, get up there and eat it.
Stop!
Okay.
Don't touch this.
Memorialize.
There we go.
Mud, a good dog.
Oh.
He was everyone's friend.
Okay.
I want to get-
I don't-
I want to get rid of this stuff.
I don't want people eating this shit.
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
You all right?
All right.
Who is this?
Oh, this was raw.
Body color going orange here.
Back top leg length.
It's actually gonna be hard to walk around, I think.
Green bamboo wall.
Cool.
All right.
I got eggs now.
Who else?
You're up there.
Spud's up there.
I think I can incubate the other one, right?
Yes, I can.
All right.
Spud, what'd you get?
Not a whole lot.
Eat the cocoon.
Anybody hungry?
Turbo can mutate.
All right.
Loves to eat.
Oh, let's just get you going.
Spud didn't really eat that much.
Spud's never hungry.
Honestly, I don't think Spud really eats that much.
Cocoon?
Yeah, I am.
All right.
I thought that was a french fry on the ground.
Okay.
Herbert is getting a little bigger.
Getting a little glossier.
Okay.
Memorial-
Spooky food dispenser.
Ooh, we got new food.
All right.
What is it?
Let's check it out.
All right.
I need to-
Let me clean this up.
Right.
Like, I don't want to-
This is more-
I don't like this.
This is morbid.
Okay.
A new food dispenser.
Spooky food dispenser.
I could probably change some decorations up, too.
Let me move the-
I don't-
There's already one of these down there.
Let's get rid of it.
I'm very curious about this, though.
All right.
So what can I do with this?
Let me-
Let's do-
Let me redecorate it.
I like this better.
I like the hot dogs.
Oh, down in the playroom.
This thing's kind of annoying.
This is a fun little thing.
The car is-
I kind of-
I don't know if I like this, but whatever.
It's variety.
Oh, I won't put the fan over here.
Pull people off.
How about, like-
You listen to music, listen to tunes,
and cool off a little.
And then maybe, like, a fun little speaker over here or something?
Yeah, it's like a nice cooling fan.
Oh.
All right.
There is-
But, um-
Bubblegum.
Gumby.
I don't know, like, Smush.
Idian Ofnir.
I like Smush.
Welcome to the world, Smush.
How come all the dogs are lazy?
All right.
Raw needs some food.
28 minutes old.
That's funny.
All right.
Go up and eat one of the weird things.
Where's Raw?
Where are you?
There you are.
Let me see you.
A gourd?
Okay.
Eat a gourd.
Try this.
What do you think?
What does that do?
Is that new DNA?
That's very filling, too.
All right.
What about, um-
What about some decorative corn?
Try that.
Loud sleeper.
Geez.
Raise a dog that lives long enough to become ancient.
Burnt dog biscuit?
Wait.
Who's ancient?
Oh, Squary.
Squary is ancient.
I'll turn that off.
I fucking hate that.
Short body and yellow coloration from eating a gourd.
Do I have any more eggs?
All right.
I have-
Let me see.
Can I breed?
I can.
All right.
Um-
Nobody else is old enough yet.
Okay.
Spam.
I want you to eat a candy apple.
Try that.
You all right?
You okay?
I'm sorry.
I did not mean to do that.
Don't bite me.
Eat the candy apple and the decorative corn.
Look at that.
New DNA.
Okay.
I don't think you liked it.
But you got some DNA.
What about the corn?
Do you like decorative corn?
Try the decorative corn.
No?
Are you okay?
Kind of.
Didn't really like that.
What is this one?
Uh-
I just-
This one here.
I don't know what the effects are.
Still don't know the-
Oh, brown coloration.
Okay.
Can I make a centipede?
Um, okay.
Who else should-
Who needs to eat?
Spud's hungry.
Oh no!
What's wrong with Spud?
His nose is glowing.
I'll bring him a candy apple.
All right.
Hey, Spud.
Try this.
Is it hot in here?
What's wrong with Smush?
What is-
Are you okay?
Oh my god.
What's wrong with Smush?
You all right?
Why are you just in the corner?
Um-
Me!
All right.
You're fine.
Need to feed you something though.
Tech floor.
Is it really hot in here?
I'm gonna have a fan going.
How many people need to sleep?
All right.
I need some more food.
Let's get some gourds.
Uh-
Some like chicken and nutri-
Yeah, sliders.
Stop.
Stop it.
What's going on over here?
Stop.
Hey.
Who's causing a problem?
Which one?
Hey.
That was not very nice.
That wasn't very nice.
Get off of him.
That's not nice what you're doing.
Are you okay?
Raw.
That wasn't very nice.
You hungry?
Let him up.
Stop!
Why do you have it out for him so bad?
Let him up.
Why?
Stop it.
Let him up.
Don't do that.
Come over here.
Stop!
Hey!
You sit down right now.
Sit down over here.
Excuse me.
No.
Sit down.
Leave Raw alone.
What did Raw do for-
What-
For no reason.
Don't bite him for no reason.
He's still-
All right.
Raw.
Raw, come here.
Raw, we're gonna put you over here.
You're gonna-
Here.
Here's a gourd.
Try that.
No, don't leave.
Don't-
No, you idiot.
You can't just, like, dominate this space.
The problem is...
Spam is territorially claiming the food room.
Maybe I shouldn't have a food room.
It seems like it's causing problems.
Because he's claiming this is territory.
Are you ho-
Come over here.
Go in front of the fan.
Right here.
Can you not stay there?
All right.
I'm just gonna hold you here.
Because you're, like, sweating.
Okay.
He's sweating.
All right.
Here comes the mean one.
Are you done?
Go sleep in the playroom.
Come here.
Eat a banana.
And then go to sleep in the playroom.
Okay.
Now go over here and go to bed.
You're being bad.
Now go sleep over there.
And leave everybody alone.
We got a ton of mutations coming.
Just smush.
Got a green nose now.
Aw, that's so cute.
Back leg stance width.
More of a-
A little width there.
Very shiny.
Very nice.
What about you?
Turns-
It's all-
It's all yellow.
Interesting.
All right.
Got even longer.
This is like a banana now.
What's going on in here?
Why are they all fighting?
Stop fighting.
Smush.
Stop it.
Everybody relax.
Relax.
You're both very good dogs.
All right.
You're back.
You're-
You're okay.
I wonder, can I breed now?
You don't.
This-
All right.
Raw is kind of scary.
He's having a good time.
So whatever.
He's rolling around and pee.
Sherbert hasn't really changed that much.
We can breed though.
A little more gloss.
A little bit bigger.
Back bottom leg length.
That's actually going to be concerning.
The legs-
His back legs are too long.
All right.
I think it's time to breed.
We have a few adults here.
Yellow.
Here.
Okay.
Spud.
Front bottom leg length.
Interesting.
40 percent.
Smaller ears.
Body metallic.
His front legs are too long.
Eat 10 clumps of dirt.
Mud floor.
All right.
It's time.
I got an egg here.
We're going to do raw.
And I don't know.
Who else?
Spam.
Raw or maybe raw and Sherbert.
But raw and spud.
Squire.
Spud's not old enough.
We get something interesting here.
Or these two.
Go.
All right.
Somehow this one has an even smaller head.
Look at this one.
The legs are so long.
And probably the-
This one just like the-
This one here.
Even longer.
Remember, this is unethical.
Whoa!
Oh, I think this is it, right?
Should I keep going or should I breed this one?
Look at that.
That's like a Giga Chad.
I think I keep this one.
I'm going to keep this one.
One, two, three, four, five, six legs.
This one can actually walk.
Name this one.
Imposter.
Aw.
Smush loves the playroom.
He's having trouble.
He's like, I don't know what to do with this ball.
Why can't I pick the ball up with my mouth?
It's not fair.
It's too heavy.
What?
Who just did that?
Oh, Smush.
You're having such a good time.
Oh, Smush is hoarding.
I get it.
Okay.
Smush, it might be my new favorite.
Spud has not left the top right corner
the whole time we've been playing the entire time.
Oh, got your own food.
All right.
It's a mess up here.
What are you doing?
I'm sure about how you're doing.
Just playing.
Oh, you're building.
Very smart.
Okay.
Very good.
Do that again.
Very, very good.
Very smart.
It's a mess up here.
I got a reward for throwing up.
Garlic bulb.
Want some garlic?
I'm going to feed the gar-
Smush.
Do you want some garlic, Smush?
Oh, no.
He's like sweating.
Stop doing that.
You guys are going to get hurt.
I think everyone's hungry.
Try some garlic.
It's good for you.
Well, no, it's not good for dogs,
but like in the sense of out of context.
Smush wants to eat that, yeah.
Yeah, do not-
Okay, what is it?
Shallots?
Like onions, garlic.
Anything that's like a shallot, right?
That was like cool, so I'm going to praise you.
Onions, garlic, grapes, chocolate.
There's actually a lot of things your dog really can't have.
What's wrong?
You all right?
Something healthy.
There, like eat like a nutrition pellet.
You okay?
Try that.
Yeah, eat something that's good for you.
You know, there's some garlic.
Dave, oh my god.
All right, new friend available, I think.
Tremendous.
That's actually a really good name.
Snacks.
Chowder.
Scout.
Damper.
Porn.
Steak fry.
Tuba?
I like tuba.
Okay, tuba.
What are you going to eat?
How about some healthy stuff?
How about a coconut?
No, a...
I don't know.
What should we...
Come over here.
I want you over here.
Cityscape.
Ooh, let me try that.
Uh-oh, Spam is getting older.
Okay, Spam's getting old.
That's not bad.
Where's Spam?
What's Spud?
Spud's hungry.
I'm going to eat this.
I know, Spud has trouble like moving around, right?
Where's Spam?
All right, Spam's getting old.
We're going to have to breed Spam.
I need an egg.
Spam was mean.
This is penance.
Tuba is currently...
I think they're playing.
Tuba's just a puppy, though.
Um, Spud, are you...
Oh, an egg.
All right, stop, stop, stop.
That's enough, that's enough.
Let go, let go, let go, let go.
Let go.
Oh, okay.
I was like, what happened?
All right, it's okay, Spud.
It's okay.
Go sleep next to your brother.
All right, ooh, sofa.
Can you not sleep here?
Take a nap.
Sleep.
Go to sleep.
What is going on over here?
Leave each other alone.
Stop it.
Who is that?
Smush, leave him.
Put him down.
Enough.
It's okay.
Smush, that's enough.
All right, sure.
We'll eat this.
Put him down?
Yeah, no, I mean, like, put him down.
Like, put him...
He's holding him.
How do you clean the dogs?
Is it filthy?
Is that why they keep on sweating?
Smush, you're kind of a psycho.
Here, have some of that.
All right, we need to do some breeding.
I got eggs.
All right, now we're going to do raw and Spam.
I think that makes some sense.
And we're going to go to, like, zero with this one.
Let me see what we can make here.
This one has a...
Look at this, how small this one's head is.
All right, that's interesting.
I'm moving around.
All right, getting weirder.
Still at 98% stability.
Huge, huge legs too, yeah.
Green.
All right, let's do this.
And I don't know, one of the big ones?
Probably, yeah.
Hell yeah, there we go.
Interesting, I like that one.
And I like this one.
This one, this one's kind of just like...
This one's getting kind of walked over.
All right, how about this one?
And this one.
Whoa, okay.
They kind of look like a truck.
Getting something interesting, that's for sure.
How many legs do they have?
Looks like a garbage truck.
Whoa!
Okay, I'm going to keep going.
This is the one.
John Deere.
Okay, again, we're going to do...
Should I wait?
What about Spam and Squary?
Let's see if we can get something cool here.
Kind of cool already.
One with a huge nose.
I want a dog with, like, a giant, like, nose.
Where's the biggest nose here?
Probably you.
You, it's getting a little longer.
I think you also have the big one.
Okay, I like the guy in the middle here.
And you, keep going, keep going.
Getting a lot paler.
Uh-oh.
Whoa, look at the tail!
That tail is huge.
Okay, hold on.
Oh, wow, that's awesome.
Okay, I think I stick with one here.
Or do I keep going?
Where's the longest tail?
I think this is the one.
I think it's this one here.
One more?
All right, one more.
We lost the color.
Shit.
All right, one more.
All right, we got one.
We got one.
That was it.
Did you see that move?
They're perfect.
These are, these are wildly different.
We're gonna have to do some incubation here.
Okay.
How are people doing?
People hungry?
Anybody dying?
Some food if you want it.
How are you guys doing?
Eat some food.
Everybody needs to get up there and eat.
You can't just, like, sit down here.
All right, so, Spike.
How about, um, people saying courage?
One, two, three, four, five.
How about courage?
How about courage with a six?
Because it's got six legs.
Three is not right.
No, fine.
What's this?
Hatch or mutate a dog with a tail?
Nobody's been burying anything.
Okay, I'm starting to get a lot of dogs now.
We have to start to keep track of this.
Where is everybody?
Okay, I'm starting to get,
I'm starting to get a lot of animals.
Tuba, how you doing?
You want a burrito?
Let me help you.
Come here.
It's right next to you, right there.
Turn around.
No, you idiot.
Whatever.
Okay, someone's mutating.
Everybody seems to be in good spirits here.
Going up.
Did you even, Tuba didn't even eat anything.
All right, we're gonna call this deer.
John Deere, right?
Let's just John.
Okay, I like John.
Ooh, Courage is really playful.
Uh, speak.
Very good.
Oh no, Spam has lived a long full life.
It's time for them to pass on.
Spam is gonna, is going away.
Oh no.
You okay?
Okay, goodbye.
All right, what do we got?
Cool.
Smush has a more green nose.
Lost a little bit of leg width.
Nose size got bigger too, okay.
You do what you need to do.
All right, John.
Um, somebody eat this.
Stop fighting, Courage.
Stop it.
Courage, go eat this.
Who do I want to live longer?
Because I don't think I want a memorial lifespan.
That's kind of, that sounds kind of mean, but Courage?
All right, Tuba's uh, was an interesting one.
Let's see.
Smaller?
Smaller.
Oh my god.
Tuba was huge.
Tuba was gigantic in the uh, in the breeding menu.
What did I feed you to make you do that?
You're so small.
All right, hold on.
I need to, let's just, might as well lean into it, right?
How do I, wide stance?
No, no, no.
I want like shrinking.
Long legs, intense pattern.
A big?
I want small.
This is random.
Short legs?
No, I want small body.
Thin body, skinny legs, tiny tail.
All right, dog treats.
Metallic sheen, legs.
Big from onion rings.
Big nose?
All right, this is from garlic.
All right, I need to feed them a person with a nose, garlic.
Wings?
Small, okay.
Chicken nuggets?
Chicken nuggets.
All right, Tuba, where are you?
Tuba!
Oh, slipping.
Okay.
Green?
Not fatter.
Looking a little green.
All right, can stop, can somebody eat this already and stop this nonsense?
Here, eat this body.
And I'm getting rid of this head.
It's just, it's like morbid looking.
Spud, get over there!
What are you, what are you guys doing?
Eat this.
All right, Tuba.
I want you to eat chicken nuggets.
What are they doing?
Tuba, get upstairs and eat chicken nuggets.
You're on a steady diet of chicken nuggets.
I want you to be like an inch tall.
Come on.
Very good.
You want another one?
Have another one.
Watch out.
Okay, you're good.
What is that?
What did I get this?
Um, yeah, somebody play with that.
More?
He's already full.
I don't want to make a puke.
All right, I want you to eat before you mutate.
What do I want you, what do I want to do with you?
I want, what do I want to do?
Are you crying?
No?
Big tail?
All right, how do I make big tail?
What was it, garlic?
Flat body.
It was make big nose and wings?
Droopy face?
It was big nose.
All right, we'll do big nose.
Big nose is what?
It's no, no.
We'll do wings and big nose.
Long body, yellow body.
Garlic is wings?
What's this?
Garlic?
Uh, courage.
I need you to eat garlic.
Can I come up here, please?
I gotta, this place is a, I gotta clean up.
Over here?
Excuse me?
Garlic is nose.
Yeah, we'll do that first.
I want a huge nose.
And then we'll do wings.
You all right?
What are you doing?
Okay.
All right, you ready?
You kind of look like you smell like garlic.
What the fuck do you know?
Oh, and eat the orb too, yeah.
That'll make him live longer, right?
Okay, you can now mutate.
Go for it.
What about you?
What am I gonna do with you?
Big.
I want you to get bigger.
Very nice, let's do it.
Do an onion ring diet?
Yeah.
It's time to, I'm gonna do some cleanup.
All right, big nose.
Let's see it.
Did it work?
Yeah, it did.
Okay, his ears and nose got a little bigger.
Sorta.
Only 3% get bigger.
Mine is 19% back.
Well, actually that's, I don't know.
I can't tell.
I think it got a little bigger.
Okay, time to clean up.
I'm going on a full cleanup spray here.
I need, all right, build mode.
Get some of this shit out of the way.
Absurd.
There's too much, how do I clean this up?
I'll leave a little, but not all this shit.
I'll leave like a patch over here.
I'm realizing how fucking filthy it is here.
It's no wonder they're all dripping and sweaty and sick and stuff.
Underneath all the grass,
it's been a bunch of puke and piss and shit.
Oh my god, it's like roller coaster tycoon.
Oh my god, that's this bad.
I'm going to leave a patch over here.
I know they're pretty, but I don't like, no, it's too much.
Like that's fine.
Like right here.
They are launching out of the tube and sliding across all this filth.
Okay, oh my god, what a joke.
Maybe that's why they're not living that long.
It was under the, how was I supposed to see it?
It was under the grass.
Shit everywhere.
Jesus!
Sometimes they move way too fast.
I hope they can't get injured that way.
You can't even see it under here.
How was I supposed to see this?
Okay, that's much cleaner.
Looks much better.
What about the other rooms?
That's fine.
Okay, I need the other rooms now.
There's a bunch of, yeah, there's like piss and shit everywhere in here too.
Oh my god, you guys are, what are you doing over here?
Stop doing that.
They're starving.
Oh fuck, they are.
Oh my god, why, go eat, eat something.
Eat a banana, eat something.
Somebody eat, eat, eat, eat, eat, eat.
Oh my goodness.
Why can't you fucking move?
Eat something.
Why, what?
Good, good, good.
Okay, you're good, you're good.
Everything's fine.
This one, good, okay.
Stop fighting and eat.
Put him down.
Oh shit, where are you?
Stop fighting.
Stop fighting and eat.
Both of you.
Hey, put him down.
Spud, put him down.
That's it.
Put him, put him down.
Put him down.
Let him go.
How do I stop?
Who has who?
Oh my god, it's not you.
It's you.
Put him down.
Oh my god.
No, he sounds like a Minecraft zombie.
All right, I'm losing control here.
Oh my god, are you okay?
Here, eat a banana, quick.
It's okay.
What do you want?
You want anything else for food before you do pupate?
Come here.
Um, have another banana.
No, you like coconuts, don't you?
Here.
Wait, this is dirt.
Have some honey.
Spud is not happy right now.
There you go.
Okay.
All right, now go relax.
You.
You're in big trouble.
Smush.
He's trying to sit there.
He's so hungry.
Oh my god, what do I do?
Quick, quick, quick.
Please move out of the way.
Chicken nuggets and shit.
Here, eat a chicken nugget.
I know you want to eat it.
I know, I know, I know.
Here, here, here.
Chicken nugget, eat it.
Have some garlic.
Have some garlic, quick.
Get off the center focus.
Eat some garlic.
Eat some garlic, please.
And chicken nugget.
You, where are you?
You have this food in front of you right now.
Eat it.
Move him.
It's in front of you.
Eat it, it's right here.
What's wrong with him?
Eat that.
Somebody just farted.
Who does it?
I gotta relax.
I'm sorry.
What do you want to eat?
This camera is kind of, come on.
Eat that.
Stop jumping around and piss.
Eat it, eat it, eat it, eat it, eat it.
Eat, eat, it's delicious, isn't it?
Okay, we need some more, we do,
something, that's not just junk food.
There we go, all right, all right, all right.
Very good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Very good.
Very good, it's okay.
I was too busy cleaning.
I didn't realize all this shit was going on up here.
Everybody all right?
I need to, can I hire someone?
You've been doing this for like an hour.
Honest to God, Raw has been doing this
for like a full hour in the game.
I don't think Raw can walk.
Oh my goodness.
No, get away from this, stop.
All right, now go to sleep.
Not seeing very much growth here.
Squarie is getting old.
Okay, all right, I need to see some growth here.
All right, that was tuba.
We wanted tuba to shrink, which we did.
Lost a little bit of size.
Okay, that's what we wanted.
Hey John, okay.
Legs got a little thicker, that's good.
All right, courage.
I kind of screwed up courage a little bit
because I was trying to do nose and ears, right?
It seems like color is kind of changing a little bit.
No size went up 10% though.
That's huge.
Huge.
Okay, I need to start storing people
because I don't have enough space.
I'm going to store Squarie.
I'm going to store two people.
I'm running out of real estate here.
Let's give you like a coconut or something
and then we're going to put you in the storage unit.
We're going to try to try that.
Eat that before I put you in the storage.
Why are they so dumb?
Just eat it.
Okay, who is going?
I need to go to my menu here.
Okay, storage.
I'm going to take Squarie.
We're going to store Squarie.
Who else do I want to store for now?
I want courage out there.
I want John out there.
I want Ra out there.
I want maybe Sherbert or Spud.
Or I think Sherbert gets, is it broom?
Sherbert's cool.
Yeah, well, sorry.
Oh, I have mud as a stored core.
Okay, let's clean up.
Ra's getting old.
Oh, no, we got to breed another.
We got to have Ra come out and breed.
Okay, we might make sure they're happy.
How are you doing over here, Tuba?
Do you want to have chicken nugget?
Okay, go play with something.
There's tons of toys everywhere.
Here, come here.
Play with this.
That's good.
Yeah, play with that.
I don't want to do that.
Okay, well, come here.
Clean up.
Do you understand I spent the last 20 minutes
just air frying whatever it is,
this stuff all over the ground.
It's back immediately.
The broom?
This will remove all physics objects from this room.
Food will be destroyed.
Eggs and seeds will be collected.
Toys and dog cores will be put away.
Unopened capsules will be lost.
Do I have any unopened capsules?
I got to check that first.
I don't want to do that to let me be certain of it.
I'm fine.
Let me just check.
Okay, clean.
Guys, that doesn't do anything.
There's still piss all over the ground in every room.
Oh, my God, you've been in the cocoon for so long.
Oh, geez.
Spud's gotten bigger.
10% back legs.
Too much like two, three percent across the board for body.
Do you spud and raw right now?
I will in just a second.
Okay, everything all right up here?
Smush.
Tube is not doing all right.
Tube, you need to go to bed.
Oh, what's wrong?
What, did he just puke?
Oh, no.
It's okay.
Are they sick?
Oh, courage is going to do it.
Come on.
Yes, very good.
Very, very good.
Jesus Christ.
Are we finally fucking clean?
All right, we're good.
John, go eat a honeycomb.
No.
Okay, we need to breed before it's too late.
I got another room.
I don't have any eggs.
I'm out of eggs.
What do you want for food?
You want a gourd?
Give it a try.
But how are you doing?
You don't look so good.
You're kind of struggling over here.
Uh-oh.
Wait, I wasn't ready to say goodbye.
I wasn't ready to say goodbye.
Oh, courage coming downstairs.
No, don't let John Deere eat that first.
Go eat the eraser.
You don't want it?
Don't eat that.
I'm trying just to get it out of here.
Get it out.
How come I can't take this out of here?
How to expel?
Oh, okay.
All right, we're going to have the memorial be...
We're going to have a different room.
Okay, different room.
This is going to be the memorial is going to be over here.
Is it going to be like a somber area?
This is the memorial.
Not like a comfy dog chair or something, right?
And I don't know.
Maybe like something.
What would a dog, what would like a dog?
No, this is, I don't like this.
Not mud.
No, something comfy.
I'm comfortable.
That's kind of comfy.
This is comfy.
Put a tree in there.
Yeah, I'll put a tree in here.
I'll put, yeah, this tree is going to go up here.
All right, now we need to move the memorials here.
There's one up here.
How do I take this with me?
I like, how do I move this to the other room?
I just remove the core.
How do I store it?
Remove core?
Put away.
Okay, so now, so now we're going to...
Oh, they all need to mutate.
All right, I'll be with you in one moment.
Hold on everybody.
Oh my God.
Okay, where is this thing?
Gravity machine?
Okay, so now where the hell is this here?
Stored cores.
Bring out.
I got to increase my like mouse sensitivity.
This is like horrible.
How do I do that?
Am I not?
One DPI.
I know, I'm like fucking move up and down.
Okay, so this is not bad.
I want to make them a little bigger though.
No one's going to be bigger than anyone else.
Actually, you got to be a little bit bigger.
This was mud.
Mud was a good dog, was one of the first dogs.
And this was raw.
Always made us laugh.
Let's get some mutations going.
Feed your dogs.
Come on, toad, whatever your name is.
Hurry up.
Oh, an egg.
Okay, you come out here because you need to eat.
All right, spud.
Let's give you some cheese.
And then I want you to...
Well, let's just rub your belly first.
Who was about to die?
Somebody was, right?
Some cheese.
Revive the dead dogs.
I think you can use their cores.
Spud, how can I help you here?
Turn, rotate.
How do I rotate them?
Okay, here we go.
Here, eat.
Have a burrito too.
It's way more filling and you're huge.
Eat it.
Way more filling.
That's good.
Okay, you're good.
Let's see what we get.
Color change.
Okay, smush is now an adult.
Smaller ears.
Piss everywhere.
I got to be more on top of this.
Piss and shit everywhere.
Ooh, new coat.
A little lighter.
Oh no, snout reduced.
That's not what we want.
A little glossier.
I want to give courage to wings.
What's the food that gives wings?
I'm a red bull.
What gives wings?
Wings gut bacteria is the yellow one.
Tiny wings.
Okay, this is from onion rings, gourds, and...
Okay, let's see if we can get it from here.
We need a guava over here.
We want you to grow some wings.
There you go.
The yellow one, right?
All right, now you can go sleep.
Eat good, courage.
Not much change for John.
A lot glossier.
Interesting.
Isn't this just bug snacks?
It's a little different, I think.
Tube is still shrinking.
Even smaller.
Look at how cute Tube is.
Tube is so cute.
I got to pee again.
God damn it.
All right, I'll be right back.
No more BRBs after this.
How do I pause the game?
Can you pause?
There's no pause?
Well, then here.
Just watch.
You guys can just watch.
I'll be right back.
What did I miss?
Nothing bad happened while I was gone?
Oh, also, now that there's a lot of people here.
July 14th is the baseball stream.
If you want to see that stream,
mark it on your calendar.
Baseball.
The Germa Baseball Association will commence.
Start and end.
Begin on July 14th.
Mark it.
Okay, you're tired.
I have access to an egg.
What do I want to do here?
I think I want to wait till...
Okay, once Tube is old enough.
Should I do spud and...
Where?
No, spud and smush?
I don't know.
Yeah, wait till Courage is old enough.
Courage and John, I think would be good.
I'll wait.
I think I only have one egg.
Yeah, I have one egg.
All right, spud.
I'm gonna need you to chill out.
Go to sleep.
Get some sleep.
Okay, you're stressed out.
Why?
What's wrong?
You're okay?
Why are you so stressed out?
All right, relax.
All right, wings.
I need to feed Courage more stuff.
Courage, I want wings, which is...
Okay, Courage, come under.
Come over here, Courage.
Get over here.
Spud, please move out of the way.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Put that down.
You need to eat because you need to get wings.
I want you to grow wings.
There you go.
Good dog.
Okay, now you can do whatever you want.
I don't know how you can be so dumb.
Oh, an egg.
He's trying to eat the food, but he...
You're on the wrong side, man.
All right, everyone's doing okay.
One more mutation and we'll be able to do it again.
Here, have some honey.
Have some honey.
There you go.
That's a good dog.
Go to sleep if you need to.
MonkaS.
Okay, everyone seems to be in good spirits.
Spud?
I don't know what's wrong with Spud.
I really don't.
He's not doing great.
He can't like walk around to get food.
You need to get some sleep.
It's so quiet up here.
Just go relax in the corner.
What could he say?
He has some trouble moving.
Why?
Come on, you can eat it.
Now go...
Okay, good.
I want you to be healthy.
Not all screwed up.
Okay.
Everybody seems to be fine.
Easy.
Herd, you want some more guava?
Eat it.
Yeah, because I'm trying to get the wings.
Very good.
The man just needed a ham slider.
All right, you're awake.
Eat another one of those.
I don't know.
I figured out this does something weird.
Eat another ham slider.
Train them to do stuff?
That was a papaya?
That's all right.
I don't know if I want to breed Spud.
Spud can't really walk.
Spud's a really good dog, but he can't really walk around.
He's a lot of trouble moving around.
I don't know why.
His body seems to be proportionally fine.
His body's like perfectly fine.
Maybe they're too far forward?
He's having a lot of trouble.
All right, smush.
Eat something.
Have some.
Go to bed.
Here, eat banana.
No, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Oh, we're doing my Wellington.
Stop.
All right, but wait, wait, wait.
Here we go, here we go.
One more guava.
Let's see if we get wings.
I thought you retired that.
Holy shit.
I, wow, okay.
That would have been a fucking disaster.
That would have gotten all,
that would have dropped everywhere.
It would have gotten all over me.
All right, come on, wings.
I thought you retired that.
Pray for wings.
Wings, come on.
Yes, no.
All right, kind of cool though.
Looks really cool.
Probably the best looking dog we've had so far.
All right, now it's time to do some breeding.
And I'm going to sneeze.
I'm realizing how fucked up that was.
Why does tuba take the longest to do this?
How come I look purple?
I don't, dude, I don't know.
I don't, I have no idea why I look purple.
Your guess is as good as mine.
Are you kidding me?
There's a slide now.
Still shrinking.
Still shrinking by about 5% every time.
Okay, let's see what we get here.
This isn't breeding.
Lost a lot of leg gloss, which is weird.
All right, should I put the slide down?
All right, dude, what are you doing?
Relax.
Okay, let's breed.
Let's do it.
This is where it gets, it's going to be weird here.
Courage and tuba or should we do spud or John?
What would make the most interesting combination here?
All right, let's see if we get something crazy.
Interesting.
I'm thinking I like this one the most.
Look at this tiny little head and tiny little nose.
Yeah, wow.
All right, I love this one.
I can't say I love this one too.
Okay, I like these two.
Huge tail on this one and this one.
Another massive tail and this one here.
The tail just keeps getting longer.
I wonder if I should just take this one.
Oh god.
All right, we're at 89% stability.
Purple but doesn't have a huge tail.
This one has a massive tail and the purple one.
Maybe we get something in between.
There we go.
Rocko from Rocko's Modern Life.
I think I stay on this one.
Oh look, this one's got a Rudolph nose.
Do I dare try it one more time or should I combine Rudolph and Rocko?
Oh jeez, okay.
Again, do it again.
All right, the pool is getting a lot smaller.
Stop saying oh jeez.
Oh jeez.
Am I saying oh jeez a lot today?
Am I?
Am I saying oh jeez?
No, I'm not.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
I think it's this one right here.
I like the red though.
I think this is best of both worlds here.
Yeah, this is the one.
That's best of both worlds.
All right, let's do it again.
This time we're going to do...
Who do we do now?
John Deere and Smush or John Deere and...
No, no, no, no, no.
John Deere and Curge.
What about Sherbert?
I feel like we're...
I think I like the blue.
Let's go for it.
What about Spud?
Where's Spud?
No, Spud is not doing so well.
Cool.
Maybe I wonder what...
Maybe we'll get a...
I think I don't want to do anything else.
This one looks like a squirrel.
I think I want the squirrel.
Oh, this one's fucking weird.
It's freaking me out.
Keep that one?
This one can't move.
Okay, so here comes...
How about as Rudolph?
Rutan is actually a pretty good name, yeah.
I like Rudolph.
All right, it's time to eat.
I still have another egg, don't I?
No, I don't.
Shit.
Why would you do this to animals?
Um, I don't know.
This is...
It's wobble dogs.
What do you mean?
Why did you do this?
Yeah, bro, it's a cartoon, all right?
It's a fucking cartoon.
All right, get rid of this.
Play with the ball.
Somebody just got sucked up.
Yo, bro, it's a cartoon, all right?
Anybody hungry?
All right, courage again.
I want you to eat these.
I want wings.
That's a bad defense.
They all have six legs.
I'm trying...
I want somebody with like nine or ten legs.
I want like a centipede.
What are you doing up here, Rudolph?
Paying your respects to the...
What a good boy.
Want to go sit in the chair?
You want to do some tricks?
Roll over.
Wow, so smart already.
Already so smart.
Do it again.
Speak.
Brilliant, dog.
Roll over.
Brilliant.
Good job.
Do it again.
You can do it.
Come on.
He's having a good time.
All right, I got a deviled egg.
Somebody eat a deviled egg.
What's happening over here?
Why do they have so much trouble getting food?
Here, have some deviled eggs, honey.
Why do they have so much trouble eating?
Like, what's going on?
Eat it.
Come on, eat the deviled egg.
Everybody have some deviled eggs.
Deviled eggs are fucking so gross.
But they're incredible when you want one.
Like, when you really, really want one,
it's like, holy shit, this is the greatest thing I've ever eaten my whole life.
Nine out of ten scenarios that the grossest fucking food
you could ever eat.
You need to eat a deviled egg right when it's made.
And not a second after that.
Not one second after.
If a deviled egg is even sitting out for five minutes,
I won't eat it.
I refuse.
Nope.
I feel the same way about hard-boiled eggs.
A fresh, hard-boiled egg,
you peel off the outer shell,
and it's just hot salt, pepper.
Eat it hot.
When you put hard-boiled eggs in the fridge in a container,
they stink.
All you hard-boiled egg lovers,
listen to me closely.
When you go to the fridge,
and you open up that container of hard-boiled eggs,
you take the container out,
everybody sits there and goes,
when I open this, it's going to be disgusting.
But one or two seconds after you take the lid off,
it stinks like fucking rotten eggs for ten seconds.
And then you go, okay, I'm fine.
It's like that every, it's just had that grow.
Oh my god, you're hungry.
What do you want?
What kind of food do you want?
A burrito, a hot deviled, no, no, no, no.
Deviled, if an egg is in a container for too long,
it smells awful.
Just eat them fresh.
When I used to lift all the time,
I would have like a dozen hard-boiled eggs in a container.
I don't know, I sound like a fucking old lady right now,
but bear with me, something's wrong with my throat.
When I was like 25, I would eat,
I would have a hard-boiled,
I would have like three hard-boiled eggs a day, four.
And it kind of hated it.
It was just like, oh, this like kind of smells it.
Even when they, not even a day goes by, one day.
You all know what I'm talking about,
you just refuse to believe it.
Ooh, new food.
I paused One Piece for this.
What are you, what, you're watching One Piece
and me at the same time?
I like Rudolph, Rudolph hangs out up here
and like pays like his respects to the other dogs.
What are you doing?
Look at him.
Oh, now that's so cute.
I'm telling you that I saw at least a few truths in the chat.
When you put hard-boiled eggs in the fridge
and a day or two later you open the container, it stinks.
I can't wait for you to make hard-boiled eggs,
put it in the fridge and you're going to take out the container.
You're going to hear what I said in your head
and you're going to go like this
and one or two seconds is going to go by
and you're going to go, and piece of shit was right.
I'm so happy.
All right, eat these wings.
You are literally never right about anything.
You don't even know what you're talking about.
He is never right.
I can do this today.
Listen to this.
Wow, I got a good one here today.
This is not taking very much effort at all for me to do this, by the way.
I am just barely gently slowly doing this and I'm not even trying.
Am I really going to be like this for the rest of my life?
TikTok uncle voice.
Give me something to say.
Give me something to say in the TikTok voice.
What should I say?
TikTok TTS.
It's the TikTok voice.
It's not taking very much to do that.
Say it's the globalists.
No, the globalists.
TikTok voice.
I fucking can't.
Just got back from Coachella.
Had an insanely good time.
Here's some pics from the event.
Oh, look at all these toys.
Just got back from Coachella.
It was absolutely busting.
Ooh, you're doing the TikTok of Rocket voice.
I don't know what's going on with my throat.
I seriously have no idea.
Oh, it's time to mutate.
I was going to scream, but I was like, I don't want to hurt my voice.
That's actually the worst joke.
I don't know.
He's dancing to the music.
Yeah, I went like this and I was going to scream and I said,
I kind of braced my eyes for the scream.
But then I was like, mutate.
Nah, I gave up.
Didn't want to do that.
Didn't want to scream really loud into the mic.
Do Voldemort noises.
What are we going to get?
Come on, Rudolph.
Give us something cool.
The reds got redder.
The brights got brighter.
Got bigger legs.
No, the tail went down.
It's all right.
I love how they rock out to this music.
It's so cool.
It's so funny.
They're just having so much fun.
Good job.
That was very good dancing.
Very, very good.
Very good job.
Except you peed your pants.
What is it?
What is it, boy?
Good job.
All right.
Stop shaking around so much.
I can't see.
New creature egg.
Somebody's hungry.
I forgot Tuba was still alive.
I thought Tuba was dead.
Okay.
Let's see.
What do we get?
How about Spud and Courage?
No.
We have too much courage.
We're going to end up having Courage B
in every single piece of lineage, right?
Tuba and Spud.
Let's go.
Ooh.
I like this one and this one.
Mutate them.
That looks like a cat.
Let's take this to zero.
Let's take it to zero.
Ooh.
We've got a mutation.
Another mutation.
Oh, yeah.
Perfect.
Looks good.
Let's do it again.
Oh, the pool is kind of shrinking a little.
It's kind of like Snoopy.
I think this is it.
I think it's this one right here.
Snoopy.
Worst joke 2022.
Jerma says Bussin'.
Ooh.
All right.
I think we...
I don't know.
I think it's this one here in the middle.
This looks the healthiest.
That's the one.
Oh, I said Bussin'.
Were you here the other day when I said...
What did I say the other day?
I said something the other day.
What was it?
Oh, yeah.
I said like sheesh.
I said...
I was like, oh, sheesh.
Yeah, you're all right.
I am now not allowed to say those things.
When I say...
Okay.
If let's say the dog were to go like this.
Whoa.
That dog was Bussin'.
People would be like...
Shut up, you fucking old loser.
I'm at the age where like I can't do that now.
Because people yell at me.
People say that...
We don't say that.
If I were to say like Bussin' or like sheesh or like...
Oh, dude.
No cap, right?
People would be like, I fucking hate this guy, right?
Don't even tell me.
If I were to...
Let's try it.
I want the mods to count the amount of like minus twos, ha-has.
I'm not going to tell you when I'm going to do it.
I want these mods...
Count it.
Count how many times people say something negative about it.
Just watch.
Let's check it out.
You'll see.
I'm going to use it in such a great context.
I'm just going to say it's going to be perfect.
Where's the egg machine?
Oh, my goodness.
I forgot about this guy.
How about like teeny?
Like teeny tiny?
How about like...
I like teeny...
Look what?
Like teeny?
I'm not even going to do it today either.
I'm going to hold on to this for like a few days at least.
Tipsy?
Tipsy's fine.
Oh, look at little Tipsy.
Go in the house, Tipsy.
Are you going to eat that or...
Okay, fine.
Eat it.
I want you to get wings.
That'd be cool.
Should have named him Grafted Scion.
That's pretty good.
All right.
People...
Who wants to have fun in here?
Somebody's not having fun.
John is not having a good time.
Why don't you play?
Yeah, like go play.
Oh, my God.
Spud is like suffering again.
Sweetheart, I'll have another devil egg.
Something healthier, please.
Like a nutrition pellet.
Is it me or is Spud always having a problem, right?
I wonder why.
Why is Spud just not ever having a good time?
Ever.
Spud doesn't like to go to sleep.
I think that's what's going on.
Spud doesn't like to go to bed.
I come up here and Spud is in red for his sleep every time.
I liked over at the mod chat that I have in my Discord.
And I see LOL.
We're not going to do that.
All right.
We don't have...
I refuse.
Okay.
All right.
We don't have to do that.
Somebody said there were at least two when you said it.
Okay.
All right.
Thankfully, it's clean.
Look at...
Oh, can he not even eat?
This was your guy's idea.
I didn't want to do this.
This was your idea.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to do this.
You did it.
I don't think he can even eat food.
Look what you did.
I didn't do this.
I wanted to do it another time.
Maybe I can feed?
Can I feed you?
Like, go on.
Eat it.
Okay.
All right.
No, no, no.
It was fine.
I think I just have to tell him to eat.
What are you doing over here?
Smush.
Leave him alone.
Oh, they're like...
He's bumping his nose.
I think he's trying to make a friend.
Give Tipsy.
Tipsy's fine.
That was very nice of you, Smush.
Tipsy is a baby and you were very gentle.
And so that was very good.
That was very kind of you.
How's everybody doing?
Tipsy's okay.
Tipsy, you should just go to sleep.
Spud?
Looking for food?
What do you need?
What do you need, bud?
Sitting over by here.
How about a dehydrated treat?
How you doing?
Okay.
Well, you have to get out of the way.
I can't press the button.
Oh, god damn it.
Whatever.
Oh, Spud's getting old.
Okay.
Spud's getting old?
Okay, have a snack.
What the hell was that?
Okay.
Tipsy is about to mutate.
But I want to feed Tipsy.
What's...
I need something that looks like leg strength.
What do I feed for leg strength?
What have you done to Tipsy?
I didn't do anything.
Turn on the gravity machine?
All right, Tipsy.
Let's just pupate.
We'll just get it over with.
This game sucks.
It's so sad.
What do you mean it's sad?
Look at this room.
Look at how these guys have been
having a ball up here the whole time.
Look.
Is this sad?
This is great.
They're having a good time.
They've been playing.
These lay love to play.
They're very polite.
I mean, he's a little rude, but it's okay.
Food-averse?
That's all right.
They've just been up here headbanging.
I'm definitely putting that up here.
Oh, hell yeah.
Yep.
That's good shit.
All right, Tipsy, come on.
You got to have stronger legs.
All right.
Front legs got a little thicker.
The body shrink and legs got longer.
But oh my God.
Okay.
I think somebody needs to eat Tipsy.
All right, you're good to go.
You've been rocking out this whole time.
How about a guava?
Here, have some food first.
I think Rudolph might be the best dog
we have besides courage.
We have to decide who's going to eat Tipsy.
That's the big issue here.
I really want wings.
All right, I'll try the gravity machine
in like the playroom or something like down here.
Dog stack, gravity machine.
Oh, this is the new food.
Right.
I wanted to see what was in here.
Moon.
Should I put this in a room with Tipsy
so Tipsy can like actually move?
Mars?
Oh, back to earth.
Oh, that looked like it hurt.
Get that fucking thing out of here.
All right, new food.
Pancakes, garlic bread, chips, lasagna.
All right, lasagna.
Who wants a lasagna?
This thing's got to move.
I need to hold on.
My shoulder hurts.
Okay.
All right, let's start serving up some pancakes and shit.
All right, look at these new DNA strands.
I'm just going to start throwing them down there.
They'll eat them eventually.
They'll figure it out.
Pancakes, garlic bread.
Food's coming.
Doritos or something.
A few lasagnas down there.
Wait.
Spud has lived a long life.
Oh, no.
Spud.
Oh, Spud.
Spud's dead.
Oh, no.
It's okay, Spud.
No, it's all right.
Where's courage?
Courage, you need to eat that.
Tipsy made it up here.
No, you don't touch that too, but get out of here.
No, smush.
Don't touch that.
What happened in there?
I need somebody.
I need...
Where's courage?
Courage, come on out.
End table.
Large tube.
It's a piece of tofu.
Don't eat poop.
Do I...
Oh, my God.
No, Rudolph should eat it.
Rudolph should eat it.
He's my favorite.
All right.
Your name being Rudolph doesn't really make any sense anymore.
That's okay, though.
Tuba, get the fuck out of here.
Tuba's not...
You're not supposed to be doing that.
Eat the pizza and garlic bread and stuff.
Whatever.
You eat that.
I swear to God.
Don't touch that.
Who do I want to eat the orb?
Do I want Rudolph or do I want courage?
Give it a tipsy.
No, I don't need a memorial.
I'm going to feed it to tipsy.
Why would I do that?
That's the fucking dumbest idea we've had all day.
I don't even know where tipsy is.
I'm not feeding.
Oh, no.
Smush is old.
We're going to get tipsy big and strong here.
I'm looking for leg strength.
Thick legs.
All right.
We need deviled eggs.
Oh, sweet.
It's so sweet.
I have some deviled eggs.
Long body.
And this increases growth, too.
This means big.
Can you eat that tooth, too?
I hope you'll eat it.
All right.
I'm ready for tipsy to do a little evolution here.
Get some sleep.
And we'll see if we can get you a little bit stronger.
Get out of here.
It's a menace.
That tube is a menace.
Kind of funny, but it causes problems a lot, I think.
You're fine up here.
All right.
Who else is there?
Don, you need to sleep.
Smush is...
Let me play with you for a second.
Come here.
I'm drying him off.
He's covered in water.
Don's getting old.
Uh-oh.
Oh, shit.
I completely forgot about Snoopy.
Charge is fine.
The positive reinforcement cap for any property.
Proto?
What is that?
Who's Proto?
Whoa.
I got spots.
Okay.
Interesting.
All right.
John, eat.
Eat like some lasagna or something.
Yeah, eat a lasagna.
There you go.
Good.
Eat a lasagna.
Eat like a pancake.
I just want...
I want you to mutate.
Aren't you going to die, though?
Who has not mutated?
Okay.
Actually, you come up here and eat like a pancake or something.
Adult?
Okay.
Tipsy.
I got you.
We're going to go feed you a bunch of pancakes and stuff.
Okay.
Tipsy, eat a pancake.
I want Tipsy to be social.
This is like not fair.
That was a violent sound.
Oh, stop.
Stop, stop, stop.
Come over here.
Pancake.
I'm busy trying to help.
That's not how you eat.
Oh, my goodness.
It's not time for you to cocoon yet.
You have to eat this.
Smush has lived a long life, but Smush is dead.
They're dropping like flies right now.
That's like three in a row.
Hi, Tuba.
Where are you going?
Give Smush to Tipsy.
That's the plan.
Eat it.
All right.
Come on.
What are you going to get?
How are you looking?
Okay.
Color change.
Legs have grown.
Tail has grown.
Body size has gone down and body length has gone down again.
It's all right.
Okay.
I need to...
Where is concrete floor?
I don't know.
What's wrong with you?
Why is he so...
Why is he huffing and puffing?
Why is he so pissed off?
What's wrong?
It's okay.
Calm down.
Everything's fine.
You guys want to play?
Oh, shit.
He's like, uh-oh.
Oh, fuck.
Tipsy is going to be the only one left.
All right.
Tipsy, you got to go eat.
Tipsy, get out.
Follow me.
Dude, Tuba is the first person to come and eat every single person.
Do you notice that?
I don't touch that, Tuba.
Tipsy, eat that.
Lifespan extended.
Okay.
I want...
Where's the other one?
Somebody else died.
Where are they?
Somebody...
Who else died?
They're on the ground somewhere.
They're like a box.
Eat that pizza.
Eat a pancake?
No, eat a chip.
You're so hungry.
All right.
Hold on.
Okay.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's back out, back out, back out, back out.
I got like capsules over here.
I didn't open.
No, no, no.
Eyeball jar and big snake wall.
Okay.
Who died?
Who is this?
Who did this eat?
What happened?
Eat the lasagna.
Where's the other dead body?
Oh, right here.
I'm feeding this to Courage.
I don't want Courage to die.
We need more deviled eggs.
Oh.
Proto and Tipsy.
That's the plan.
No, no, no, no.
No one's eating this.
I like this.
I like this one a lot.
This is a good one.
Putting this in the memorial.
I don't know.
Stop.
Yeah.
This was Smush.
I like Smush a lot.
Smush was really cool.
Smush, a good dog.
There.
A little rowdy but loved everyone.
He's a good dog.
All right.
Go to sleep.
And go to sleep.
All right.
Rudolph, what do you got?
Starting to turn almost all golden.
Are those six legs?
Okay.
I lost a lot of leg gloss, but that's all right.
Tipsy, I need you to go to sleep.
Everyone else is fine.
Where's Tipsy?
Oh, there you are.
Okay.
Get in the house.
And sleep.
Okay.
Good.
Cool.
You look all right.
Upgrade the den.
I don't...
Can I?
Corn dog.
Anyone piss on the ground?
Where's Snoopy?
Oh, shit.
You're right.
Where's Snoopy?
All right.
There's Snoopy.
Snoopy.
I didn't realize Snoopy was this little.
Uh-oh.
Tuba's dead.
Goodbye, Tuba.
This actually is really sad.
Courage is huge.
Should we memorialize Tuba or feed him to Courage?
I don't want...
I kind of want Courage to stay around.
Yeah, I want Courage to stick around.
Disgusting over here.
You monster.
It's a game mechanic.
I want some of them to stick around because they have...
They're really...
Like, he can walk around.
Are you telling me Courage and...
What are you guys doing?
I was going to combine these two,
but I don't think that's such a good idea.
Courage and Proto would be really good.
God.
I don't know.
You know what I mean?
How you doing, Snoopy?
You need some food?
Do it now?
I don't think I can.
Oh, I can.
I can.
Perfect.
All right.
Let's go.
This is it.
Let's do it.
We lost the spots.
Did we?
It was gone immediately.
He kind of looks like a little pig.
Look at this one.
They only have three legs.
I don't know what to do about this.
I don't think we can even...
We can't even fertilize this.
We got to hope for, like, just a huge mutation here.
Still three legs.
Sorry, I realized I was biting my lip,
and I don't want you to see it.
Do Proto and Tipsy.
Uh, Tipsy is not old enough.
I will when Tipsy's old enough.
Tripod?
Yeah, Tipsy's not an adult yet.
Do I even...
I don't even know if I want to hatch.
I mean, whatever.
Tipsy's getting bigger, though.
Everybody seems to be doing okay.
These two are the closest related...
Oh, my God.
I don't know.
I'm going to have to...
I was going to stream tomorrow, but maybe I won't.
I don't know what the fuck is going on here.
How come they're eating dirt?
Save the game.
Yep.
Give Tipsy a bigger body, please.
I honestly...
I need...
What does that?
Feed Tipsy a bunch of lasagna.
Come on, Tipsy.
Let's go.
Wrong room.
Lasagna.
Have some lasagna.
Maybe time to end the stream.
Don't hurt your voice.
I'll be okay.
All right.
Good.
Ooh.
A tooth.
Teeth make you big, too, don't they?
All right.
Good.
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Um...
Want a pancake?
Turn this shit off.
Is it people saying Tripod?
Tripod?
Tripod sounds good.
Is that a raid?
Is there?
I don't see one.
The dashboard doesn't say anything.
Tripod is fucked, dude.
That is fucked.
Can I rename?
You gotta sing, it's Tomar.
What's up, Tomar?
Sorry, my voice is fucked up.
Snoopy is eating poop.
It doesn't matter, okay?
It really doesn't matter.
What's going on?
Thanks for, uh, thanks for stopping by.
Sing the Tomar theme song.
I don't know what that is.
Go to the dog storage, you can rename.
Yeah, that's fucking bad.
I don't want it to be that.
That's so awful.
No, I'm gonna name it, like, Breezy.
Breezy's better.
I like Breezy.
Breezy's fine.
You called one of your dogs Tipsy.
Yeah, like, teeny, like, Tipsy.
I don't know.
Wait, was that, was that bad?
Where is Tipsy?
But I, I was supposed to be, like, teeny.
All right, come on.
Let's see what we get here.
Like, itsy bitsy.
Yeah, I don't know.
I looked over in chat and somebody,
that was just rhymed.
You called the fucked up one Tipsy.
I don't think that's fair because I called,
what's this one called?
Eat one of these.
Worst parent ever.
It's not copium, I'm serious.
I'm serious.
Okay, all right, we got something good.
And you can't get any smaller.
My god, dude, what the fuck?
That was evil.
I didn't even touch that.
I didn't do anything.
Tipsy's been eating lasagna all day.
How is it possible?
That was at least 15 feet.
I think we're on the right track.
That's, I don't like that name.
I actually don't like that name.
That name is so fucking awful.
Something else, something else, something else.
Where's my storage?
Something else, something else.
I don't like that name.
How do I rename?
How do you rename?
Brunch?
I don't know.
Brunch.
There, that's better.
I don't know what you're doing.
I think, I think he's trying to...
You all right?
She puked.
Pretty pumped up about that, by the way.
Hey, hey, you need to breed Snoopy.
I like the color scheme.
Not much change, it's fine.
Okay, so can I?
Let's see.
Tipsy's not old enough.
Can't happen.
One more mutation.
When did the dog stop fighting?
There's been a few fights already.
I had to break up a couple of them.
One of them was really bad.
One just wouldn't let go.
It's like, kind of fucked up.
Just checking to see if something piss.
My brunch is ready to mutate.
Anybody hungry or anything?
Snoopy's tired.
Oops, I'm sorry.
Come over here and sleep.
You don't, you get...
Come here, it's okay, come here.
Stay in the corner.
Courage is a big dog.
Be careful.
Not much of a change.
I don't think they ate very much.
No, they didn't.
Eat some lasagna.
Here.
Lasagna makes you big.
Oh, Tipsy, I'm so sorry.
You need help.
Okay.
Tipsy needs to eat.
I don't know.
I keep trying to feed Tipsy stuff,
but it doesn't work.
Deviled eggs, right?
A couple of deviled eggs?
All right, let's relax for a second.
And you should go to sleep.
French fries?
I know, all right.
Tipsy's sleeping.
I'm gonna leave Tipsy alone.
Eat this coconut.
This is dirt, never...
Okay, well, whatever.
He's delayed it.
How come Tipsy's built like that?
It's because we were doing some experiments.
I kind of just ended up that way.
Hello, brunch.
Sarah, are you okay?
You looking to play?
Here, play with the ball.
Throw it.
Throw that ball.
Oh, jump on it.
Throw it.
Go get it.
You have too many legs.
Nobody can...
This whole time,
no one's been able to do anything.
They have too many legs.
They can't even run.
Is that...
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
I'm trying to move him over to the ball.
Okay, get it.
Have a coconut.
Oh, shit.
Cool.
Play dead.
New trick.
Nice trick.
Very good job.
Good, good, good.
Good trick.
What are you doing over there?
Playing with some dirt?
That's funny.
Throw it.
I don't know what you're throwing.
I don't know what you're...
I don't know what's...
Okay, I think he's falling asleep.
He's sleeping standing up.
I don't have any den upgrades.
Courage is hungry.
I need to at least level up.
Tipsy.
French fries.
Yeah, have another french fry.
Come on, you can get it.
There you go.
You can do it.
There's progress here with tips.
I think we just need to...
The legs need to be spread out more.
I need body length.
French fries should do it, I hope.
I hope so.
Just with a little bit of increased body,
they can move around.
Courage you need.
Eat something.
Have one of these.
Here, eat that.
That was it?
Really?
How about I have a chicken?
Oh, no, corn dog.
Yeah, that's a new thing.
Here, try that.
Oh, shit.
Right, Rudolph.
Interesting.
Much bigger head.
Back length.
Back leg width.
A lot of growth.
Bigger legs.
That's probably better.
That's probably helps.
All right, have one of these.
Have one of those chips.
And the nose is getting red again, yeah?
That looks cool.
I'm supposed to eat a cocoon, why not?
How close are you to evolving?
Have some corn.
You like corn?
Seen but often not heard.
I think we're going to get a good evolution here with tipsy.
Come over here.
Come downstairs.
I want you to participate.
I don't want you to just be up here by yourself.
Come on, come up here.
I want you to participate.
Come have fun.
Let's put on some music.
Let's get some tunes on.
And have everybody come over here and hang out.
Why are you biting his tail?
Don't bite his tail.
There we go.
Look.
This is all right.
Good, good.
Here comes the evolution.
Okay, come on.
See if we can...
The body just needs to lengthen and that's probably fine.
I don't want tipsy to be up there by itself.
No, I'm good.
What are you doing?
Jungle carpet?
That's a screenshot if I've ever seen it.
That's so cute.
All right, come on.
What do we got?
I think that's better.
Yep.
Front top leg.
Body girth.
Body length has increased.
Okay, it's increased by a little bit.
By 3.2%.
Slim down.
Okay.
All right, that actually looks better.
That actually looks a lot better.
I think one more evolution with a little bit of length and...
You lost a leg?
No, you didn't.
Proto, what are you up to?
All right, now we can do this.
We can breed, yeah.
Tipsy and Proto.
Okay, here we go.
Let's do it.
Let's see it.
This is it.
This is the big one.
Got spots.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Okay.
That's when his heart's all over it.
There are two candidates here.
I wonder if I should keep going.
Or just grab the one with the hearts.
Yeah, let's do it.
Very cool.
I could do this again, too.
I want to do Proto and Rudolph.
I want some more spots.
Okay, that's kind of cool.
Anybody have spots?
You do and you do.
Very cool.
All right, the hearts again.
Another variation.
Very cool.
New tail.
Wait, there was a new tail?
That is a new tail, isn't it?
I don't want to go much further here.
I think this is perfect.
Who from this litter though?
Probably you.
Probably this one.
New pattern?
Oh, shit.
There is a new pattern.
All right, we're taking this one.
All right, I'll take this next one to zero.
Oh, I don't have another egg.
Do I?
I'm going to have to store some people.
What do I store?
I don't know.
Who should I store?
I'm going to have way too many people.
It's the one with hearts.
Cupid?
Oh, I like Valentine.
Valentine's a good one.
I'm going to store Rudolph.
That's a good idea.
Maybe store Rudolph and maybe Proto?
I got to clean up a little bit for a second.
Hold on.
A mess.
I'll leave a little garden down here.
That's fine.
None of this is a bullshit.
You've already mutated already?
Okay.
All right, this is...
What's my name?
This dog.
How about like Macaron?
That's a good one.
Sponge?
Sweetie?
Sweetie's not bad.
Jason?
How about Spongy?
Where's Tipsy?
Oh, right there.
Okay.
Tipsy's asleep?
Her just digging more.
Oh, keep doing that.
Very good job.
All right.
Tipsy, go to bed over here.
I got to do some decorating.
I don't even have to upgrade the den.
Doing it for me.
Jesus.
Taking forever.
Holy shit.
Check achievements.
I want to say 34% taller.
Wasn't that tall to begin with, but...
I guess it's a little bit bigger.
All right, I've been playing for five hours.
I have...
Okay, hold on a second.
This is where it gets weird.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
I have to redo this whole thing.
Oh, do I?
No, I don't.
They don't all have to be connected to each other.
Oh, shit.
I'm sorry.
I got so many more rooms.
I need some planning.
I need to plan this better.
This is the starting room, which is going to have...
It's very basic.
I like the clouds.
Clouds are fine.
Messing up.
That's not bad.
All right, I like that.
Oh, I got to figure out what...
Okay, this is the memorial.
I can stay that way.
One of my...
This is the food room.
Let's have two food rooms.
Okay, all the food has to be in one spot.
What the...
I can make them small?
Why didn't I do this in the first place?
I didn't know I could make them that small.
This is pretty huge.
Perfect.
Okay, cool.
Very cool.
Now, this room is kind of ugly.
I don't really like the carpet that much.
It's hard to even see the food on the floor.
What, like a cafeteria?
That sounds better to me.
Pull this room down a little.
Okay.
No, I don't need that.
It looks good.
All right, that's the food room.
So then all other food, get rid of it.
I don't want this anymore.
Put the couch over here somewhere like right here.
The memorials will go here.
I'll probably have a few of those in a minute.
What is this place?
This is the toy room.
Okay, the toy room is fine.
We'll just get rid of this.
Okay, this is the play room.
So it's gonna stay like this.
This is okay.
There's no food.
It's just too much food.
Well, they'll go get the food down there.
Play room, sleep room, memorial, cafeteria.
What should this be?
Is a tree in the way?
Make this the anti-gravity room.
Okay.
No, I don't want to do that.
That sounds horrible.
Make it space because it's an anti-gravity room.
And then this will be the garden.
This is the garden.
Perfect.
All right.
Switch the food in the memorial room.
That's a good point.
Yeah, that's a good point.
So I don't have to go as far.
Good point.
Those still exist, right?
Oh, I'm playing chess while the game's playing checkers.
Like what the fuck am I doing?
Although, do those still exist?
The memorials exist, right?
They're not gone, are they?
They better be.
I think they're still there.
People are hungry.
All right.
Come on, come on, come on.
There's nothing there.
Arm is killing me.
Why am I so fucked up today?
I don't know what the fuck is happening to me.
That's fine.
He's falling apart.
Get nice and cool in here.
Okay.
All right.
Now they can eat.
They can get food.
And now let's put the memorial stuff down here.
Thank goodness.
Sag.
I don't know.
Maybe I am getting sick.
I don't think I am.
That'd be kind of annoying if I was.
Let me clean this up.
Get a tree in here.
This dude's farming his sagges.
Oh, I don't think I feel good.
Um, I don't feel good.
The dogs are starving.
You're right.
All right.
Food, food, food, food, food.
Food, food, food.
Everyone's starving.
Oh, oh my god.
Get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up.
Tipsy, tipsy, tipsy, tipsy, tipsy, tipsy, tipsy.
What do you want?
Lasagna, lasagna, lasagna, lasagna.
Right there, right there.
It's eat, eat, eat, eat, eat, eat.
Okay.
I forgot the game doesn't pause.
Because I've, it's, you're okay.
Okay, back, you can go back to sleep.
Very good.
Think of that we got corn dogs in the corner here.
They're fine.
They've got, seriously, they got corn dogs.
Just taking much more effort.
Okay, cool.
What we got?
I think, uh, brunch grew a lot.
There's a little base now.
Snout rotation minus 30 percent.
Courage is dying.
That don't look like dying to me.
That looks like having a great time.
They have a corn dog.
Dying.
That's not dying.
Ooh, coke got a lot darker.
Interesting.
17 percent taller.
Very cool.
Courage and storage so they don't die.
Pattern metallic plus 20 percent.
What's that mean?
Shinier?
What does metallic pattern mean?
This motivated me to sit with my dog.
Oh, that's cute.
Tipsy, you want to play?
Good throw.
Nice job.
Okay, french fries for tipsy, right?
A little bit more body length and we'll be fine.
What the fuck is going on?
I, you need to go to sleep.
Somewhere comfortable in the corner so you don't,
I don't want you to get beat up or anything.
Under the AC?
Yeah, right here.
There you go.
Get some sleep.
It's okay.
That's all right.
All right.
Right in front of the AC.
Nice and cool.
I love tipsy.
Tipsy is amazing.
Courage is ancient.
Maybe it is time to store courage.
Yeah, I'll do it.
I don't want to lose them.
Make a wind vortex.
Oh, I was gonna make the uh,
okay, everyone seems to be okay now.
This is the anti-gravity room, right?
Yeah.
Mars or should I just do anti-gravity?
Is this fun?
Do they think this is fun?
I think that, I think they're having a good time.
Send tipsy's hanging out having a good time.
No, another french fry and I think we'll have enough length for tipsy to be able to
really just kind of move around.
I think it should be fine.
Very tipsy.
I have one of these.
There you go.
Food in this game is making me hungry.
I'm getting hungry too.
What time is it?
Yeah, end of the stream voice coming up here in a minute.
I'm gonna get some food and I'm gonna try to figure out what the hell's going on in here.
It's way strong.
All right.
Way stronger than like an hour ago.
Like I said, five to ten percent more body length than I think it's perfect.
I think it's gonna be fine.
I'll show you.
It's not my sinuses.
It's like back like here like in here.
It's really weird.
I'm sorry about that.
I didn't think I was gonna be like a fucking chain smoker today.
This is my tonsils.
It's like deeper.
It's like down here.
Like in here.
Take a nap over here maybe.
Yeah, this is a lot more walking than tipsy's done.
So this is the I'm actually happy about this.
That body length was really bad before but now oh there we go.
Hell yeah.
Yes.
Play with the ball.
Spongy play with the ball.
Why ain't I playing with the ball?
Good throw.
That was a great throw.
Wait, that's the anti-gravity chamber?
Where did where did tipsy go?
Where's tipsy?
Oh, there we go.
Look at how happy tipsy is being able to move around.
This is great.
Actually what are as aggressive actually great development.
Look at that.
Yes.
It actually makes me really happy.
That's like I'm glad.
All right.
Be careful.
Look they're having fun.
Yes.
We've got a good ending.
I'm curious with another evolution though.
This is a cute game.
How much is this game?
This is really fun.
This is just like chill.
I loved it.
It's 20 bucks.
Yeah.
This is really cute.
Oh look it.
Go go go go go go go.
They're both doing so well.
Yeah.
Perfect.
All right.
Okay.
Ready to relax.
No more music.
Let's get some food.
Snoopy I don't know.
I think you're like stuck in here.
Snoopy be careful.
I wouldn't go in that room.
Okay.
You're fine.
Is there any food?
All right.
There's a pizza bagel over here.
You can eat that.
Eat this pizza bagel.
There you go.
Eww.
Uh okay.
You need to go this way to get some food.
All right.
Snack time.
How about a moon cheese?
That sounds good.
What else is hungry?
You?
All right.
What do you what do you like?
What are you looking for?
How about a lasagna?
Oh you want a candy apple.
Okay.
Sure.
Take it.
That's what they wanted.
I need it.
Okay.
All right.
I think that's it.
Okay.
Do one more evolution.
Tipsy and brunch.
I don't think brunch is old enough.
Brunch is not old enough.
Not yet.
One more.
All right.
When we'll do brunch and tipsy.
I'll let I'll do that happen before I go.
The next stream we're going to do a Mon Bazao which is like a car game.
It's kind of like my summer car and long drive combined.
I can't tell you we're doing that tomorrow though
because I think I'm going to take a day to figure out what's going on here.
That's a car game.
You come here.
I might be sick.
Well if I'm sick then uh then I'm sick.
Whatever.
I'll figure it out.
I don't think that's the case.
I think it's like some kind of environmental change or something.
I don't know.
I gotta see what happens tomorrow.
Oh a picket fence.
We're just hanging out in here.
Tipsy needs food.
I'll bring something.
What is tipsy's favorite food?
Because I'm going to bring it.
It's definitely like a pancake or something.
Oh shit they dug they dug some more.
Cool.
All right tipsy come on up.
I didn't want to do that.
I'm sorry.
How do I get you to come out?
No fuck I didn't I didn't I'm not I didn't mean to do that.
Oh here we go here we go.
This is um we have some mutations here.
I need tipsy to come out.
See can you come out please?
Come on up.
Oh my god.
I need a lasagna instead.
There you go.
Stop.
Eat this pancake.
Can you not eat the pancake?
Get out of the zero gravity room.
Okay now you need to go to sleep right now.
Very cool.
Let's see what we got.
Do the voice before your throat explodes.
What voice?
Head got a little bigger.
Probably good for balance.
Ooh the spots change.
The spots look like look different.
TikTok voice.
You want me to do the TikTok voice again?
Do the Coachella voice.
That's cool.
Is that good for your throat though?
Um it's kind of like going in and out if you noticed.
It's like sometimes it's like and then sometimes it's like it's okay.
Bigger head and more metallic.
I don't notice the metallic though.
Tipsy's body got short again.
What?
Oh no it did.
What happened?
What the heck?
What the f-
Really?
What happened there?
Uh Tipsy and-
Not Snoopy.
Who was it?
Who is it?
Oh they're not old enough.
They're not old enough yet.
It wasn't-
No it wasn't Proto.
It was one of the spots.
It was one of these.
It's Brunch.
Not old enough.
Oh no Tipsy's a wedge again.
Uh what's going on with the nose?
Did Tipsy's head get bigger?
I think Tipsy's head is bigger.
Okay all right.
I'm gonna save it here in case I play again.
That was fun.
That was really cute.
I was a big fan.
This is how-
I'm definitely gonna save this
because I don't know I might play again.
Although I said that about everything.
I did not think I was gonna play this for six hours
but that was really cool.
I'm supposed to stream tomorrow
but I-
I don't know.
I might not.
So tentatively I would just say
prepare for today's Tuesday.
I just prepare for uh prepare for Thursday
and if tomorrow I get up and I'm fine
I'll just go tomorrow.
But if not then we'll go on Thursday.
So just plan for Thursday
but don't-
Don't be surprised if you see me tomorrow.
This is really fun.
This is a really cool game.
I'm-
I hope I'm not getting sick.
I really hope not.
So see you Friday.
So see you Saturday.
No that-
I don't know yet.
Can we get a fit check?
Checking out my Coachella fit check.
What do you guys think?
I think it's at least-
At least a five out of five.
Stay healthy?
I'm- I am.
Don't worry.
I'll be okay.
Please stop that.
See you in July.
I'm not-
I hope-
No I will see you in July.
You're right.
Because uh July 14th.
Make sure you check out on July 14th.
July 14th is gonna be the baseball stream.
You're not gonna wanna miss it.
Trust me on that.
Gonna have all kinds of festivities.
All kinds of cool stuff.
You're not gonna wanna miss it.
Trust me.
And I'm telling you.
Take a burrito.
Put cheese on top of it.
And wrap it in another burrito.
Boston.
See you later.
Oh what's that?
Oh how many-
How many minus twos do I see?
Huh?
Oh hold on a minute there.
I can't really-
I can't really see that well.
Yeah I'll-
Playing for Thursday.
I'll see you maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe.
Maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe.
Alright goodnight guys.
Been fun.
This game is actually really cool.
I recommend it.
If you haven't played it I recommend it.
Go check it out.
Minus two.
Quiet old man.
I feel like I'm playing Sekiro again.
Remember Sekiro?
If you go watch the Sekiro VODs like my-
The whole time I was playing Sekiro I sounded like this.
Actually way worse than this.
Like a hundred times worse.
Alright I'll see you guys later.
It's been a long time since I've been like quote sick on stream.
It's been a very long time.
It's been at least a couple of-
I think that's the last time that happened.
I hate getting sick.
I hate it.
I hope it's not happening.
I gotta stop yelling.
No more yelling.
Hope your TikTok voice doesn't get worse.
So thanks for the stream.
Yeah thanks for watching.
Take care of yourselves.
Have a good rest of your kind of mid-week here.
Has it gotten worse or has it been about exactly the same since the stream started?
It's kind of hard to tell.
I feel like it's kind of going in and out.
I feel like it's fine but not.
Is it worse?
Yeah well.
I'll shut up.
I will shut up.
Drink some water.
I'll drink some water.
You need to keep talking.
Let's do a raid.
Let's raid.
Let's see.
Let's raid Atriarch.
It's Atriarch's birthday today.
I just figured that out right now because I saw it right here.
Happy birthday to Atriarch.
It's Atriarch's birthday.
I want you to go say happy birthday.
I'm gonna be fucking pissed.
Have a wonderful rest of your evening.
Goodbye.
Sorry that the wrote stuff is annoying.
I probably sounded irritating this whole time.
I can imagine.
But we'll see you soon.
In the next day or two.
Have a great night.
Go say happy birthday to Atriarch.
And good night.