How you doing? What's up? What's up? How you doing? Doing great. Good. Hold on. I got a cough.
Okay. Yeah, we're gonna play trombone champ. Start from there. This game is apparently an hour or
two, right? Did you get sloppy? What? Because I had to cough? No, no, no, I don't turn 37. And
everybody starts calling me sloppy. That's not how this No, no, no, no, I am. I am built like a
fucking some kind of animal, whatever it is. I told I said in pre stream, this was not going
to be a crack stream. And I'm going to stand by it. I don't know something in the air today or
yesterday. I don't know. I'm just like I'm in a weird mood. I have this constant urge to just say
just this weird shit. I don't know why I just say it's like fun to me today and yesterday.
It's because it's a blood moon. Is it? It's co2 poisoning. It's not. You know why I know it's not.
I know it's not co2 poisoning. Because I have a co2 monitor in my place. I know exactly how much
carbon dioxide is in the air at any given moment. So I know I know the exact parts per million
of co2 in this place. Would you like to know what it is? I can tell you right now. Yeah, why do you
guys think I got the water quality test strips? I mean, I pissed on one for a joke. But yeah,
the co2 in the air inside of my place ranges from 480 to like 600 or 700 at night with the
you know with the window closed. You want as long as that number is under 800 or 900.
The typical indoor environment for co2 is four to 800 or 700. It's too much. No, not degrees.
This motherfucker opens his windows at night. Yes. Did you know? And okay. All right. Yeah,
let me out. Yeah, I watched the Tom Scott video where he talks about co2 and I freaked out and
bought a co2 monitor. That's what happened. Like everybody else. People whooing Tom Scott. What are
you crazy? That's not that's not happen. That's not possible. Right? Yeah. So in the Tom Scott
video, Tom Scott was essentially showcasing another youtuber who trapped himself in a air
tight chamber and monitored the co2 and monitored how he felt once it hit certain parts. It's very
interesting stuff. If you have a moment to check it out, I would. So I saw the video, I freaked out
and I bought a co2 monitor. And ever since, I've been keeping an eye on it. And I open,
you know, open up the windows, get some airflow. That's how you reduce co2. Which is actually kind
of hard in Vegas because it gets really, really hot and really, really cold. You're paranoid. No,
I'm not. What? Just simply monitoring the co2. It is what? That's supposed to be paranoid.
Yeah, it's a gas. It's a co2 gas. You think I'm not going to be concerned about it a little?
No, you'd be aware of kind of what your surroundings, you know, be aware. But no,
honestly, the Tom Scott video is actually really interesting. I, Tom Scott's videos are so cool
because it's not just typical stuff. It's just like this water behind me is electrified. If you
touch it, you will die. And I'm like, what, where is this? Why is this water electrified? Who did
this? And then he goes into this whole thing and it's like, and the videos are not like, they're
short. And it's true. If you did, if you touch that water, you're going to get electrocuted.
It's not bullshit. I do. I watched Tom's videos. The average human emits over two tons of co2 a
week. Is that real? Well, the reason why you want to monitor your co2 in your bedroom or whatever,
is because at night you're exhaling in the same room, sometimes with the door closed,
and you are just dumping co2 into your room just for eight, seven, six, seven, eight, nine plus
hours a night. And if you don't have ventilation and the door is closed, you want to get some nice
fresh air in there sometimes. Even if you don't have to sleep with the window open. But you know,
if weather permits, crack the window for a little bit. That'd be all day. Crack the window for a
little bit, just for a little bit, especially during these months where you can. What if it's
too noisy? Also, another thing is airflow. So look, I watched Tom Scott. Okay, I'm going to
give you some education here. I'm a Tom Scott watcher. Let's go. Teacher. But no, if you have
the door open to your bedroom, at least the air can kind of move in and out. Yeah, I just look,
you know, okay, I don't want to like do some fear dropping here. You're if your co2 levels
in your house, you're not going to you're going to be okay. All right. I think it's over what's the
over 1000 over 1200 parts per million is considered like really stale and not good. So most typical
houses sit between a very average, very fine level. Just open your windows every now and again,
just get some fresh air in. Oh, that kind of reminds me of a story. Actually, it's a tweet
that I never tweeted out. So one time when me and Holly first started dating, I, I had what did I
tell us already? Did I already tell this? It's about me opening the door for a reason. Okay,
well, I'll tell it anyways. Okay, so when me and Holly started first dating, I obviously didn't
want to like fart near her. So what I did is I she was in another room. And I went to the front door
and I opened the front door and put my ass out the front door and went like,
and like farted. And maybe a full half second after I farted, Augusta wind blew from my back
back into the house. And I freaked out. I was like, No, not the whole reason why I did this.
Sure. Well, no, nobody. Okay, I don't care what anybody says. Nobody in the first three to six
months of their relationship goes to the bathroom. Do you know what I mean by that?
Like in the first three months of a new relationship, nobody goes to the bathroom.
Nobody has to take a shit. It doesn't work that way. I like, oh, yeah, okay. Yeah, yeah, come over.
Yeah. Okay. Hold on. But like, before you come over, though, I've got to like work on the car
in the garage. It's like, I need like, I'm going to spend like 40 minutes going to the bathroom to
make sure I don't have to like farting in front of a new girlfriend or new boyfriend. That's not
going to happen. I'm sorry. If I have to take a shit and like my new partner is over, my new
girlfriend is over, whatever. I have to go work on the car. And oh, hey, by the way. Oh, by the way,
like downstairs, I had this an electrical problem. Don't come down here for an hour.
Don't you can't come. Don't come. Don't come into this room for like an hour. There's an
electrical problem. Just like, freak him out. I don't do that. I'm fucking kidding. This is a joke.
There's CO2 in that room. Don't go in that room. Imagine being a neighbor walking by and your
neighbor opens his door and rips ass out the door. Or imagine being on like a security cam,
like somebody else's security cam. Like imagine like, oh, what happened on the security cam today?
It's like, wait, what's going on? Ring doorbell. Oh, my God. But anyways,
yeah, I don't like to just like rip ass in front of a new girlfriend. I don't think anybody does
that. Why would you have to give me the benefit of the doubt here? Most people don't really do
that immediately. It's not like, oh, hey, yeah, come on in. Oh, yeah, this is my place. Oh, yeah,
let me give you a quick little tour. Sorry fart. It was loud. Oh, be careful. Oh, come on over here.
It's like, what the fuck, man? What are you talking about? That's not going to happen.
I don't think any of you will do that. Who is going to do that? I don't know what I don't know.
Jupiter is in some kind of blood moon right now. I'm sorry. The last two days have been weird. I've
been very, very like overly energetic and shit. What's going on? Dude, just fart like everybody
else. You just turned 37. Yeah. And I'm trying to tell you how I'm a considerate person.
I don't want to invite somebody over and fart on them. What? How did you draw this this quickly?
You've been talking about arts for 10 minutes straight. Yeah. OK. If you want to play the
you're 37 while you're talking about arts card. OK. I want you to open up every every television
show in the last two decades and I want you to find me that the only time that there's no like
art jokes in that show in the last like 20 years and those shows are written by like 40 year olds
plus 50 year olds. Simpsons. Simpsons had a ton of fart jokes. We talked about Breaking Bad had a
huge fart joke. Remember when when when Walter put his legs behind his head and took a lighter and
farted into it and he did a flame. That happened. I just spilt shit all over me because I'm trying
not to laugh at that. I'm sorry. The reaction. All right. God damn it. Hold on. In Game of Thrones.
Yeah. You don't remember in Game of Thrones when when Grand Maester Pycelle did the lighter fart
flame joke. All these old bones are hard to move but he puts his legs behind his head.
Let me ask you a really quick question though. If. OK. Be very honest and I want to poll for this.
If Grand Maester Pycelle did that in the final episode of Game of Thrones season eight you would
have a better you would have a better view of that whole show. I guarantee it. People wouldn't care
that it ended terribly and like the last season was terrible. It was like holy shit we got like
the Grand Maester Pycelle dumb and dumber Jim Carrey fart scene. I don't care anymore that the
show was terrible. I get we had that now or he doesn't he doesn't have to like kill a skeleton.
All right. I got to clean. I spilt shit all over me. Hold on. Have I been sitting here for 20
minutes doing this. What the fuck man. It's been seven. It's been for 17 minutes. I need like a
producer in my ear. Just being like hey dude it's time to move on. Hey hey move on to something
else. I think I would probably ignore the producer. I probably would. You guys you guys would honestly
think I was even more unhinged because I would be referencing the producer without even telling
you that I was talking to anybody else. If I was sitting there talking about like farting out the
front door and in my ear was hey dude no no no no move on. I'd be like I'm not going to move on.
Don't tell me to move on. And you guys be like who the fuck is that. All right we're going to play
uh trombone champion. Trombone champion. Uh it's a game requested to play. Looks like it's really fun
and interesting. I don't know. I don't really know much about it. What I do know is other
streamers played it. So my turn. Is it. So I know. It's fun. Well let's go. All right so how does it
work. It's funny. Northern Lion played it. Fucking love that guy. All right let's go. Are you sure
you want to start a new game in slot one. Yes. And so it comes to pass. Ages after the twin vessels
were forged a new soul appears. Brave soul. One day you will stand before two baboons.
One day you will rent the very fabric that binds this land. But until that day comes
you must toot. Toot your trombone brave soul. And you may yet become the trombone champ. Cool.
George Washington. Was that like Thomas Jefferson. Who was that.
All right. Welcome to trombone champ. Choose play to play the main game.
Many secrets await. All right. Try. Do settings or anything. Uh mouse speed. I think that's fine.
Annoyances. Funny jump scares. What should I do with this. Turn up the baboon quality. No.
We're not. I'm doing normal. I'm not going right into this. Let me just play it first.
I'm just going to play it. I'm not going to. Oh turn on this like funny mode. Why would I turn on
like DK whatever it is. The big head 007 mode right now. Okay. Choose your tromboner.
Okay. Boomer. Yeah. I mean you guys remember 007. Goldeneye had the cheats where you could
what you can make people's big head. I'm not doing that immediately. You play the game first.
All right. Let's go. Trombone. There's other instruments. All right. I don't even care.
I'm going to 100% this right now. Are there licensed songs in this.
Move the mouse forward and back to move the slide. Line up the dot with the note lines.
So you go this way to go. Press left. What's this better mouse or keyboard mouse. Press left mouse
to button or any letter to toot. Play well. You build combos. All right. Let me just let me see
how it works. Watch the breath meter. If you hold a note for too long you'll run out of breath.
Okay. Have fun. Okay. Enjoy the beautiful succulent. It's supposed to be inverted.
It's inverted. Can I change that? It's inverted. I got to change the inverted thing. I feel like
there's a like this kid in the in the in the house really practicing for their like band practice
tomorrow. Okay. This is fun. Oh what. Okay. All right. I get it. That's funny. It's fun. I actually
think this is cool. All right. Let me. I don't want it to be inverted. I feel like I'm like
flying a plane or something. Not inverted. Is that cheating? Is it cheating? I just want to
make sure it's not cheating. All right. This is. Oh this is. There are between two and four spiders
living inside the average trombone. That's not real. Do characters. Characters. What? This is
the New Year's Eve party and little Timmy's been practicing for everybody. If I see one person
smirk you're fucking kicked out of the party. I will throw you out myself. See right now. I'm
not even enjoying the music. I'm looking around like this. Seeing who's laughing at my son.
All right. That's it. How long is this old thing? You were laughing at your own son.
Oh I wasn't. I wasn't laughing at my own son. I was merely enjoying the song. All right.
Uh dudes. This is trombone. Holy wow. Oh Canada. Why don't we. How many songs are there?
This one's really hard apparently. Wait. We need to do Oh Canada because this is like.
This is not hard. Wait. Go back. Character two. What? Cool. All right. Let's do uh. That one's
apparently. That's pretty hard. Let's do Oh Canada. The first trombone was invented in 20 million BC.
It's a game. It's a game. It's a game. Do they all have like a remix? Is this going to be like.
And then go like. And then go like kind of crazy. I hope so. Oh the last one did it.
Cool. All right. So this one is beer barrel polka. God save the king. Beethoven's fifth
scabbard stars and stripes. William Tell. Oh I know this one. The star spangled banner.
This is actually quite a lot. Sugar plum fairy.
Ball game. Wait is this. Oh yeah. Okay. I'm going to 100% this one.
Go. Give me an S. Oh. All right. I'll do entertainer. Everyone wants. Everyone wants me to do it.
Wait. I want to do William Tell. Let's go. This one's going to be nuts. Oh this one goes.
No way. No way. But that's all right. No way. But it's okay. Oh yeah. Let's go. Oh fuck. Hold on.
Oh my God. Why am I messing this up? Oh shit. My arm. I can't. Okay. Who hired this guy?
I got an A on that. I could probably do that better. I could do that much better.
Yeah. I can 100% do that better. You know I got to find a different way to sit. You know what I'm
saying? I feel like I want to be putting my arm forward more. Like leaning back and holding my
arm out like this. I have my whole arm and wrist on the mouse pad. All right. I'll do entertainer
now. Okay. Okay. Where is it? Entertainer. Okay. Here we go. There's over nine songs that feature
trombone. That's interesting. I didn't even think about that. That's a good song. All right. Now
let's do whatever. Do gladiators. Gladiators. Is that true? It takes a thousand people to make
one trombone. There's not enough room on my mouse pad. That song's called gladiators. Interesting.
How about skip to my loo? You know I'm going to get my keyboard off the desk area here. This is
better. That's like a mad Mario character. This piece of shit's not tuned. This piece of shit's
out of tune. That's what it was. This is really fun. Okay. What else is there? Is it this one?
Long Tail Limbo. Let's do it. Let's just do them all. Empty your spit valve.
Oh. What is this? Is this like Beethoven? Dude, Mozart was fucking lit. Don't ever say that word
again. Okay. Don't ever say that word again. All right. What about this? I want to do them all
before we do anything else. You know what I mean? Why not? What was Mozart's last word?
I had to get a Super Mario in there. That wasn't me. I didn't do that. I got an S on that one.
Actual fart. All right. One more. One more and then we'll go back and see what else we can do.
Professional trombone can cost over two billion. That's not even real.
That's gotta be an S. I was gonna say it has to be, right? It has to be. All right. So what else
can you do? Block. Jesus. Okay. What do I do? Collect? Welcome to your collection. Play the
main game to earn toots and then spend them on trombone cards. Can you collect all 50?
I've not done that. What? This is crazy. It's cards? What is this? Can I play with them or
something? This is so cool. This is so cool. This is not what I thought it was going to be,
by the way. This is like actually just collect interesting cool history on the trombone. That's
cool. You could eat up to 30. Wait, they're fake? Composer of more than 600 pieces. Mozart,
one of the most well-known classical composers of all time. He could eat up to 30 hot dogs in
one sitting. Oh, it's made up. Oh, maximalist electronic composer and producer of bespoke soups.
In addition to long tail limbo, he produced a trio of critically acclaimed albums,
which you should purchase immediately. American jazz trombonist who played with
Count Bassey was known for his plunger mute technique and literally wrote a book on plunger
techniques. As an American, he probably ate a ton of hot dogs. What's a hot dog thing?
Why? What's with the hot dogs? Oh, we already got Roswell all wrote already, right? Legendary
tromboner and composer who worked in free and avant-garde jazz taught ethnomusicology performed
with Malian and Mongolian musicians and could eat 900 hot dogs. What's with the hot dogs?
Whether or not he ate hot dogs is unknown. He ate, only ate hot dogs in private. One of the most
powerful tromboner cards, the red eyes black baboon is a representation of the bass clef
as it relates to Babi, the Egyptian deification of the sacred old world Hamadryas baboon. Did I get
it? Favorite clef of the primordial baboon toot-seeker tom. This clef represents light,
but there can be no light without dark. This has got to be some kind of inside joke with the devs,
right? He ate hot dogs sometimes, maybe. J.S. Bach invented the hot dog. The air horns are killing
me. What is a turd? A coward's trombone. Double his power level. He's a master of orchestration
and could eat a whole lot of hot dogs, although. Okay, let's just boom, open them. A glissando is
a slide from one tone to another. The trombone is one of the few instruments capable of performing
a true smooth glissando. This is, wait, 16th century Italian painter who painted what may
have been the first artistic depiction of a woman playing a trombone. Oh shit, there it is. It is
the alpha and the omega. Why? The trombones of the animal kingdom and are the descendants of Babi,
the bull of the baboons, who is a relative of the primordial baboons that watch over the twin toot
vessels. Legendary Jamaican Scott trombonist with a true history of mental illness and murder,
ultimately ending with his death at Bellevue Asylum in Kingston. Jeez.
Honestly, I thought that was Milhouse Manastorm for one second. I was like,
that's a funny joke. They put Milhouse Manastorm in here and they did. That's what the joke is.
That's what the joke is. I didn't read further than that. That was what the reference is.
I'm an idiot. Okay, Mozart music storm. This Austrian mage holds the key to the ear wing
of tempo keep. He will light you up with the sound of his sweet keys. Cool. Ancient Egyptian Babi.
I've got like five Roswell ruds. Very cool. Wait, should I do it like a Hearthstone pack opening?
Guys, okay. So we're looking for epics or legendaries. It's not here. What is this one?
Oh, all right. That's all right. That's a good one. That's okay. Very cool. This I could use
this in my I could use this in my in my warlock deck. I think what's under this one. You know,
I what I really want is I really hope that and by the way, this this takes like four hours to open
like 50 packs just in case you were wondering. Oh, okay. It's not it's it but it's close to
Mozart Manastorms. All right, come on. You always have to go somebody else click the button so I
can stay like this. Oh, do finger snaps. What is that? What is finger snaps?
Do people do finger snaps when they open packs? What did I do when I opened like crates in TF2?
What did I do? Did I do that? Did I go like this? I think I think I did. I did. Yeah, I actually did.
All right. So what else is there? Free improvisation. What is this? I don't understand.
I'd play music. I don't know how to play music. That's a sound effect in a Chrono Trigger or
something. What is that? It's a it's a move in Chrono Trigger or my RPG or something.
You doy doy doy. That's a mega. Oh, you got it. Thank God. I was gonna drive me crazy for the
next two weeks. It's the Mega Man charge up sound. They're like, dude, it real. Oh my thank God.
Thank you so much. That would have drove me nuts. Wait, I have to do it. I have to do it right,
though. I have to do it right. Otherwise, I won't be able to go to sleep. It's like it's slower.
Don't go so high. All right. I'm going to people going to leave. That's like annoying.
All right. Kirby. Yep. What's the hardest song in the game?
Crunchy. Very cool. All right. There's still more Trombone Skies. Let's go. Oh,
there's more to the songs. All right, we're good. I didn't blow it, right? Did I blow it?
Yeah, I'm good. Hell yeah. Let's go. Go back to Baboon. Go back to do it again. Click Baboon in
the menu. What the fuck is this? Are are thou the one who's been knocking on my little hatch?
Yes. Okay. I stick the Trombone champ. Is there a design wish to become the champ? Yes.
Yes. Primordial Baboon. Toot Seeker Tom. Feast eyes on the toot vessel.
What is it for? How does this affect my life personally? These are questions for which I
have long since forgotten answers. My bad. Feed it toots. Okay. I spent all my money on card packs.
Why did I do that? It's framped. Seek the Lord Vessel. Come back to me and feed me items.
You must succeed Lord Gwyn. All right. I spent all my money on card packs. That was dumb. All
right. Well, now I have to do it. I have to get it. I want to do every song I haven't done.
Fingers are cramping up. I thought this was. I thought this was the.
Hold on. I can't concentrate. Are you so red? Because I'm red. I don't know. I'm very flushed.
Did we do all the songs? Wait. This one is. This one's pretty crazy. Let's do an easy one.
We're gonna do an easy one. Hold on. Isn't this. Oh, wait a minute. Isn't this. Yeah, it's the same
song. We stole that song. All right. Skybird. Beans on toast? No way. What's that old Nickelodeon
show? Kablam? It's Ka-Blam. That's what this sounds like to me. That song was fucking awesome,
by the way. I like this a lot. I lost it a little bit there. Strawberry Magic 2 Waiting Room. True.
No, you. Everybody hated that. There was a huge chat war from that game. All right. That was fun.
All right. There's only a couple I haven't done. How about this one? I don't know the names of
these songs, but I recognize every single one of them. I look at them and I go, what is that?
And then I. You can do that? Never mind. All right. I was trying to see if I could
chain them together. I still got an ass. Who cares? All right. Let me do the one song I haven't done.
Oh, it's not this too. All right. Okay. Come on. This one's going to be crazy. I'm ready.
Why don't you ever blink? Good luck blinking during this. Oh, oh, that was cool. I like that
one. Blink. I have your stream muted. Well, I hope you're playing along with sheet music or something
because I don't know how you're watching. All right. I got this one. Blink once. You're going
to go crazy. I'm fine. I'm paying attention. Now I can blink. You give me one button,
you give me two buttons, give me three buttons. You give me up to four and I'll be fine.
Once we cross four buttons, I can't do anything. Give me a, you give me four buttons and I will
destroy it. Is this the only one we haven't done? How good are you at guitar hero? How many buttons
are on the guitar hero controller? Sorry. I don't play guitar hero very well at all. I cannot do
the fifth button in guitar hero. I can't do it. Is this why you played arcane mage? And wow,
that is such like an insane detailed insult. I thought I got an F. I thought I got an F.
Just play guitar hero on medium. No, I can't play it on medium. Oh, there's another one.
Old gray mirror. Not a real American, not a perfect score.
I was taking a sip. I was drinking my drink. Oh, that was nice. Imagine waiting for the weekend
Breath of the Wild stream and he just plays Snore Rancher 2 and Fart Simulator.
I'm playing Breath of the Wild in like half an hour. I think that's it, but it's not. I'm not
done. That's all the songs, right? Wait, let's go pay the trombone. The trombone thing.
All right. Is it trombone? It's trombone. Trombone. It's trombone. Snore Rancher. Yeah,
come on, man. It's trombone. Trombone or trombone? Trombone. Trombone. Trombone. Yeah,
trombone. Not trombone. The trombone. Maybe I guess you can say it either way, right?
Jesus. It awakens. New instrument.
Probably gone. Oh, I can do it again.
So I have to do this three times because look at where it's filled up.
Oops. Mute the game. I got to do it one more time. I got to get asked on something. I got
to do it one more time. Wait, muted. It's an instrument. Hold on. Let me try. So there's no
sounds. Sounds like chaos. What's his name? Animal Crossing. Slider. Did I miss one note?
KK Slider. Yeah. Should I get an S on the warm up? I want to unlock one more thing at least.
Play as the new character. Oh shit. Okay. Do it again. I can do it perfect. I got to do it
perfect. What's going on? I didn't miss a single note. All right. So that's, that's perfect. I
didn't miss a single one. Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
All right. How many points do I need? 2,500, right? All right. It's going to jump scare
everybody. Just be ready. Be aware. One more. The game looks fun. It is. Do the new character,
new character. All right. All right. Where's, oh, all right. I need more points. What was that
really cool one that we liked? What was that? What was the really cool one? Oh yeah. This one.
Yeah. This one. Wait, am I going to get points for doing this? I already got an S on it.
Do you get points if you completed something and you do it more? All right. Fuck that. I thought
the song was over. Sorry. That's better than the last time. Way better than the last time.
How come you're not singing the song? All right. Oh, oh, Langstein. Oh, Langstein. I wasn't ready
for this solo. That's better than the last time. Please blink. I'm fine. I'm blinking. All right.
Do I have enough points? He's a lizard. Wake up. I was a lizard. I'm just going to make,
I'm going to clear the record here. If I was a lizard, I would not be streaming. I'll be
lying outside on a fucking rock with my eyes just closed 14 to 15 hours a day, right in the sun.
You look like Shaggy. I know because I'm wearing a green shirt. It's a solid green shirt. You just,
you're Shaggy, I guess. Every time I wear this, people say Shaggy.
Eight bit. Oh, that's actually kind of cool. There's more. All right. I want to do that.
That sounds fun. I know I said I was going to play Breath of the Wild, but I want to hold on.
I'm not done. I can click on something here. Build card. Turd card. Wait, don't I? Oh,
these are my doubles. Should you ever have more than two? The chaos candle.
You're playing the clout chaser game. I'm having fun, man. That's a fun game. That's my legendary
trombone card. Oh, this is how you, okay. Silver trombone. So let's do it again.
Man. Let's go. That's got to be fastest ever. That's the fastest ever. I don't think anyone's
done it faster than that. Wait, what? No. Shit. I need, I just want to see what it looks like.
I want to see what it sounds like. All right. Let's do it. Let's do eight bit.
Why is your face crooked? I don't know. Blame God. I didn't get S. I started over. I fucked it up
and I got all fucked in my, I got all fucked up in my head and my head got all fucked up.
Let's do it again. I'm going to try space bar. No, that's, that's scratching your head and
rubbing your stomach at the same time. A little bit bad. I got at least an A. It was a B before
I got an A. All right. I want to take the eight bit sound effects off because it kind of hurts
my head. All right. We've got to get at least A, right? Entertainer. I got to get at least an A
and everything. That would have been an A. One more try and that's it. That's A. I think that's
it, right? Any more B's? No, I got all A's and S's. That's it. Can I afford anything else?
I can go higher than that. Not enough. I got an A on this. I got it. The ones that are easy,
I should be able to get S's on, right? Let me go back to this one. Seriously. Like I can do this
one. I screwed this one up big time. Here we go. I'm definitely going to get at least a better
score on this one. My finger hurts. I'm so mad. My, my finger started to like, I was like made of
a stone. I couldn't click. Use the keyboard. I can't. I have to use my right hand. You know
what? When you do, when you move too many times, it's like doing reps. The lactic acid like builds
up and it's just, I can't click anymore. 160 second break. My fucking finger hurts. Oh,
you just can't, man. No, you got to start with, you got to start with that one. I got a better
score. I got a better score. That's fine. It's the like, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, and having to click
and move. All right. What about, um, how about this one? I'm going to get this one to S. Take a break.
I'm a gamer. I can. That's an S right? Yes. All right. One more. That's it. One more and I'm done.
I thought it was going to be different than that. Start. Good start. Is that better than the last
one? Not by much. Fuck. It's all right. When you, it's just the, you know what I mean?
All right. Let me unlock my thing and then I'm going to switch to Breath of the Wild.
What do you do with that? I got everything out of that. What do we do with the key? Oh,
there's one more secret. Okay. I'll do it. Click this a bunch. I would have never figured that out.
Am I going to get a tuba? Okay. I just wanted you, I wanted you to give me the secret. I
didn't want you to leave. Yeah. All right. You said that.
Should Bassmaster Ben not stop in stopping the story? Did he not stop? Yes. Not. No.
The toot vessel and the turd vessel. Toot master Tom. I feel like that's, I feel like that's like
a hacker name in Dark Souls. I get invaded by that. It's like, okay, he's going to, he's
going to crash my computer. I got to be careful. There's like fucking toot master Tom or like turd,
turd vessel Tom. All right. Okay. I got the key though. Can I put the key somewhere?
Do you not want me to not repeat this full tale again or should I not simply continue?
Just tell me the answer. I don't even care. It's yes, right?
Build a vessel with turds. I don't have any turds. How do I get turds?
I have to dust cards. Oh, really? Should I just turd everything? Things I have doubles of?
This duplicates. Okay. Okay. So I gotta get some more packs, right? Okay. Cool. Any doubles?
Do you have enough turds? Yeah, but I'm going to need, I'm probably going to need to do it more
than once, right? Only do it, I don't have to do it once. Sound set in the club. I kind of,
I kind of need to do that. I'm just saying the amount of omega lulls that I've seen in the last
one straight minute that you tell me that my fart joke about farting like this star spangled
banner or something or like the fart thing with Holly that I'm, but I'm so, I'm so low brow,
apparently. Count the amount of omega lulls in the last one minute.
I don't want to hear it. I don't want to hear it from anybody. I want, I want the,
I want the mods to keep track of every chatter that omega lulls in the next
five minutes. I want you to keep track of every omega lull you see in the next five minutes
and then time them out for an hour. How many people are getting timed out? It was a lot.
It was including Twitch staff. Oh, fatigue is setting in. Oh, okay. That's better. All right.
I only, I want enough to unlock all the turds. All right, let's do one more. Only one more.
Just one more, one more, one more. Everyone relax. One more. Shut up. I did it. Perfect.
Well, 2.2 million dollars. Come on. That's gonna be better. It was a little bit better.
Oh my God. I forgot to blink. Look at this. Holy shit. Jesus. Oh, all right. What do we,
what do we got? Do I have enough? I'm just going to sell a lot of these. All right. What if I just
sell all of them? I need 750, 750, which is what? 1500. I need 1500. I'm close. I might just get it.
Can we omega all of these turds? Yeah, that's fine. So what is it?
Character, servant of Bobby. Okay. That's pretty cool. You know what I really wish was in this
game? And I know it's probably impossible, but there's probably so much money. But
imagine this was licensed games, not licensed games, licensed music. I feel like that would
be really, really funny. It'd be really cool. I think it's funny. There are mods for custom
songs. All right. That's really cool. I have a blue key and a red key. So what do I do with
the two keys? Okay. So I, I did everything with the turds. Now you are ready. You will need a
power level of 10 before combating the forces of order. Really? I have two keys now. How do I get
shit? The candle is the last one. Oh shit. You dare challenge me? Prepare thyself,
tromboner. What's going on?
You must yield the horn of legend. I must have a power level of at least 10
Okay. So you have to come here with the legendary trombone and beat it. Okay. That's cool. Um,
I think I'm done. You got to unlock everything. I don't know if I'm going to unlock everything.
My God, it's got chills up my whole spine. You never turned baboons up in the options.
Oh, I didn't. Yeah, that's true. That boon quality inferno, a boon preference, all of them.
Let me see what that does. I'm just curious. What the fuck is this? Is there more songs? Is
that a secret song? What was that? Where did that go? Where did that just go? If we go again. I'm,
I'm not even playing. All right. Goodbye. That was a really cool game. Fun game. Liked it a lot.
Very good. I would say it's a quality experience. Very fun. That was really cool. I liked it a lot.
I'm glad I played it. All right. Now, sorry, I slapped in your head. We're going to play
Breath of the Wild. I'm going to go take a piss break, make sure I get the switch set up correctly
back in like two, three minutes. See you soon. Be right back. Just kidding. Okay. Now I'll be back.