Yeah, it was exactly on time. To the second. Right in the window, I'm telling you. I'm not
going to miss the window. My desk! This controller is so dirty. I want to kind of show this to you
guys. This is the controller I've been using the whole time. This is embarrassing though. I'm not
sure I wanted you to see this. This is disgusting. For some reason, I feel like this is going to
break terms of service. I feel like this is going to break terms of service. It's so gross.
This is the gamepad equivalent of showing like my asshole on stream. I need to clean this. This is
the problem. This is dirty key bindings. Dirty keys. Dirty buttons. This is filthy. This is the
reason why I couldn't beat the fucking guy last night. I don't have any alcohol wipes. No. I'm
going to furiously clean this at some point. But we're going to tonight try our our very hardest
then relax and try to get to the end of Sekiro tonight. I'm going to try as hard as I can.
I'm going to try to be laser lightning focused. Don't get mad this stream. That's well that's
asking a lot. Here comes rage. I haven't been raging. All right. I've been upset. There's a
difference. Yes you have. No I have not. There's a difference between agitated and rage. What about
the headless? Well that was that was another. I was going to a different dimension. That's not
anger. My soul got ripped out of my body and got put in a parallel universe. How am I supposed to
be mad at that? It just kind of was happening. Hysterical is a good way to put it. Yeah.
Jerma you've outpaced me so much. I haven't been able to even get to fountainhead palace yet.
Stop being good. No I'm just do it. Do it at your own pace. There's no there's no correct way.
Don't let anybody tell you. Don't let any like elitist video gamer tell you
that you're doing it wrong. You got to go faster. No do it at your own pace.
Don't have somebody go over your shoulder and go hey man you should be like you should have
killed that thing already. It's just a fly. Don't listen to them. This is a game that's meant to be
taken slow and seriously. Like for instance this guy beats Owl and Genichiro first try but dies
too headless and then they laughed three times. That's three separate laughs. That's all right
though. Skip everything. We spent a significant portion of last night's stream making sure that I
saw all the things that the game had to offer. I went back yesterday. I skipped. We went back for
like six hours to like do optional content. Oh you guys are just giving it to me right now.
And just wait till I get even angrier in about 30. I'm gonna I'm not gonna get angry today. I'm
gonna be positive today. We're just gonna talk about how positive everything is. It's gonna be
fantastic even if I die. Even if I look over here and I see people like making fun of me.
Which that's not very nice okay. It's not very nice when I see die to tutorial boss. I'm trying.
That's not a nice thing to see. I'm just kidding. Anyways let's uh let's go.
Moral of the story is you're not supposed to beat the game first try. You're supposed to persevere
and get ready and I already don't want to do this. I tried to talk myself up so much before the stream
started. I just already don't want to be here but we're gonna go. Here we go. Just I'm not
gonna stop anybody. By the way spoilers. This is a very very late game optional hard boss. If you
don't know what that is then I would look away. Why does it feel louder? Is it louder than anybody
else? It's really loud. Why? I didn't change anything. Oh it wasn't it wasn't even turned on.
Sorry about that. It's it is louder though. It is. It actually is louder.
Here we go. Not good. That was just like dust. Come here dog.
Watch that foot. Watch that foot. Okay fine fine fine fine. Watch out for the blast. Watch out
for the blast. Blast incoming. You guys never listened to me. I told you the blast was incoming.
All right shut up here. Not today. That's the best attempt I've ever had. Here we go. He's got the
he's got a new move right? I gotta I gotta jump. This is the one right? Does he do it now? I wonder.
Yep. Fuck. No I gotta go earlier than that. Go way earlier than that. There it goes. Right? Okay
let's see. One. Two. Is it just a good throw? Whoa that's new. I haven't seen him do that.
How long does that last for? Damn okay. That's the first time I've ever seen him do it.
He's gotta get out of the corner here. Get out of the corner. Come on.
This is such a bad spot. That's just not fair. He just stopped in the corner.
Like seriously I don't I like get out of the fucking corner.
He just stood there standing on the wall where the cliff is and here's the worst part about this.
If you get any distance at all with this motherfucker you're dead. So standing behind him
I'm just gonna go off the cliff. That was a really good first attempt until
I ran into the bullshit. He's already at an eight. Oh come on. What the hell was that?
Oh that didn't do that in a while. That just healed me. I didn't press that.
All right I hope you don't stand at the edge of a cliff for two minutes.
All right let's see if I can get this. I gotta go even earlier than that I think.
Side. Let's see. He like winds up. No you can't just run. I thought you could maybe I would
run it but it tracks you the whole time. Dirty control. Is it really the dirt?
Calm down Jeremy. I'm gonna get distance on me. All right here we go. Is he gonna do it?
Phase three. Let's see it for the first time ever. Ever. Let's go. Phase three. Come on.
What is he doing? Phase three. Oh fuck.
Oh he did. He did. It's a. It's a. Whoa. It's a jump rope. I don't know. I guess.
Oh shit. I have such trouble with this. Wow it's a sweep. That was different the last time.
That's also different. No. No. Get up. Get up. Get up. I'm gonna take it. What the fuck dude.
What the. I don't know what he's doing. No. No. God. What the fuck. Oh my god.
There was a flame wall in front of me. I couldn't even go towards him.
The whistle didn't work. Maybe it was too close for me to be able to use it.
Man. Hold on. I need a second. Fuck. I'm so like. I'm so. Nervous up right now. Damn.
I wonder if I can. Is it might just. Maybe it's just cosmetic.
If I run through that I wonder how much damage you take. Or is it gonna knock you back?
I don't know. Oh that's. That's weird. Maybe I just have to run. He does that weird like
jump rope move. I don't. I maybe. It's. It's a. It looks like you just sweep it first and then I
fuck all know what the hell it means. All right let's go. Fuck. Nervous up. That's really the
only thing you gotta worry about here. Balls. You got out of that stunt quick. Again. See if I'm.
The reason I'm not healing is I'm trying to get a uh. See now. See I thought I had a second between
phase two and three. No. Not you. You. It's like an instant. So I can't do what I'm doing here.
I still don't understand how to get away from that. I still don't understand. I gotta figure
that one out. Otherwise it's gonna be the death of me. I still wouldn't. The only move in the
first two phases that I don't get. So I thought maybe you could jump over it and grab him.
Fuck man. I have no idea. I tried running. I tried jumping. I tried running directly away.
Maybe she's gonna. I just have to stay with him. Just fuck it. Just start to run up to him.
Just don't ever let him get that far away. That was. No. What? Too far away.
Too far away. At least I know that. That's why it didn't work last time.
I'm just like panicking and realizing that I just beat it. I just beat that.
Hold on. I need a second. I jumped over it. It landed and I like jumped. So I have to run to
the side and jump over it when it lands. Okay. Whoa. That was weird. That was really weird. I
like froze in the air. Oh fuck me man. I got it. I do. See if I can get it. Let's practice it.
Just like all time stuff. It's the worst part about this man. These fights take so long that
if you just get so tense. I gotta fucking relax. Or here we go. Okay. I'm gonna ring. He makes a
ring. Fuck. It's. Ring again. Oh now I'm in trouble. Now I'm in trouble. Oh god. He comes back the
other way. Through the fire. So on phase. Okay. Phase three. When he jumps away. He's either
gonna do like a barrage of meteors or a double slide. The double slide is. That usually happens
first. Meteor didn't happen till the second one. I don't know how random it is. Honestly I'm trying
to parry now. I'm trying to change things. Just kill me. Kill me. How am I gonna do it again?
Like I gotta. I gotta just do how I know. And not try to add things.
I got to the phase three pretty reliably there. I'm not. I'm not gonna do like. Oh let me try parrying
now. 25 attempts later. Like no. No. No. No. We're just gonna. He never reads useful shit.
Well I need to figure it out on my own. It's really easy for somebody to say hey go get this
item and beat him. But that's. Why would I know that? Unless I found it or hit it. You know what
I mean? I'm at the point of no like spoilers in chat. I want to beat him. That's. If I need it I'll
ask for it. If I. I can do it. I'm doing it. You've seen it. I'm in front of you right now.
I got it with like 30. 20 percent phase three. I got. I got it done again. Okay here we go.
I had it so close too. That's so unfortunate. But you gotta do what you gotta do. Oh he's of course
to go in the air again. Man come on. Great third swing. This is all you need.
Fuck. Oh that caught me. Didn't throw any missiles. What a fucker. Running out of these somehow.
Forgot about that. Okay here we go. Here it comes. Run. Okay it's right when it hits the ground.
Easy. No. What was wrong there? Fuck. I gotta go backwards with it.
Backwards. It's gotta be longer. It needs travel time. Otherwise you're gonna get hit by it. Stay back.
No. Why did I slide? Why would. Why did I slide? I tried to jump. What? I slid into a tree.
Here we go. All right. Don't slide into a tree this time. Thanks again.
Let's go. Phase three. Frank. Watch out. He's gonna do the thing. He's gonna.
I don't know. Fuck. Fuck me. Damn it. That fucking stupid swing.
Fuck. I don't know what it is. He's gonna throw. What? What? Why? I that's.
I did. I've done that the same way every time. Just run at him. Apparently. So running at him
every time he's ever thrown the meteors. I get insta-killed that time. I just run forward.
She's changing the speeds of how fast he throws them. Sometimes he throws in a fourth swing there
and it's impossible to know when he's gonna do it. It's just randomly he does a fourth swing.
I've not noticed a single reason why he does that. Sometimes it's three. Sometimes it's four.
Three. No. That's it. Three. Why? Why? I don't get it. First phase is easy now. Yeah.
Really it's the combo going from two to three. It hurts every time you do it.
Dodged into it. I gotta parry them. Oh no. Bad. Bad Jeremy. Bad Jeremy. Oh.
Oh. Make one fucking mistake. It's over in like a 15 minute boss fight.
One piece of human error just fucking ruins it all.
I'm getting closer when I don't get fucking caught up in the bullshit.
This first phase is I barely even have to use a fucking potion.
Get out of the corner here. It's a bad place for all of us.
Stop. No. Don't be stupid.
Caught in one move. You got. I gotta be. Excellent. Excellent. Let's go.
Fuck. So. Fuck me. Why? I was waiting for the fucking.
More perfect. No. All right. Is it gonna be the fucking meteors? No. It's this.
This is a huge wind up. Hey, come on. What's it gonna be? Meteors? Nope.
I gotta grab him too. I can't step sideways because the fucking fire. Oh my god.
Dude, what the fuck? It's instant. Jesus. What? The fucking hidden box was bullshit.
Daddy. What? He's gonna do it again? No. God. Why? Oh my god. You gotta be kidding me.
Oh no. Oh my god. So close again. When he gets the. When he. The. The. The. The.
Barrage. You can't run through him. You gotta dodge him. God. This guy sucks.
Ugh. If it just didn't take so long. It's like the longest fight in the whole game. Dude's got more
health than Medir. From fucking Dark Souls 3. With like four people in the party. Give me a break.
That was such a decent attempt too. Like I really had it. That was such a good attempt.
Jesus man. I got the mortal blade in my hands. You sure? Are you sure you didn't buy this from
the fucking party store? Because that's what it feels like when you play this game sometimes.
Is this. Are you sure this isn't the wooden trading sword from fucking Legend of Zelda?
You sure? This is the mortal blade. Just want to make sure you're aware of that secure.
I hope you have the right one. Not the eBay knockoff that you spent like fucking 39 dollars on.
If I heal in phase one it's pretty much over. You know. I don't know how that wasn't a dodge.
Is this the final boss? No. This is an optional boss.
Somewhere in the corner in the fucking world somewhere.
That was quick. That's the fastest you've ever done that. Go back to being a Fortnite stream.
If only. If only that's what I was doing right now. That was happening. But he's in a bad place.
I took the fucking god damn wall here. There's no. I can't run around in here. Stupid fucking boss.
From Software. I like the game you came up with here. Sekiro.
That'll die twice. It's a really interesting concept. A game that can only be completed by
a computer. It's like. You made it for AI. That's great. I like it. It's great.
From Software makes the first video game that is completable by artificial intelligence. They made
it for the robots. I guess the robots have taken over. They're already getting video games made
for. Sooner or later. You guys are watching me playing this game. No. You're going to be buying
games for your computer to play them. You're going to be like. Oh shit he just got him.
There's going to be lines of fucking code. You're going to be watching me watch a computer
beat this game. If I don't do it this time I'm going to. I'm going to go farm for resurrection.
Because I feel like I wouldn't have been able to do it by now. I know what the slide is.
I know it. I know that right. OK hold on. I'm pressing the left thumb stick again because
it's so intense running around. And we have four actions tied to the same button.
Whoa. I don't like where you are. Video games. Time for video games. All right now I'm pretty
quiet. Nobody talk. No. What the fuck. Here we go. What's it going to be. He's done it. I did it.
I'm a computer. I get to be a computer. I get to be a computer. I get to live my life as a computer
now. Oh that was fucking insane. The battle memory of an extraordinary foe lingering in the mind of
the wolf. Commune with the sculptors out and confront memories of battle. Yeah the one-armed
demon prowled the battlefield consumed by flames of deepest resentment. And a lapis. Was that
actually harder than an orphan. No. I said that last night that I think it was the same type of
issue that I had with orphan. I just think he has a lot of health. I just think he has a shit load
of health. And here's the thing. If you take the health down by like even 10 20 percent it actually
might ruin that encounter because here's the thing. I always I never really like phase encounters in
these games because you take you spend so much time trying to learn the new moves that they do
that you almost forget the old ones. That's what kind of happened in the three or four times I
saw phase three is I was so desperate to figure out and learn the new move that he gets that you
almost just fucking completely forget about the other first two phases. But I think it's by design
what there really only is about five moves that are just difficult to understand. And that's what
I'm saying people look when people were saying oh wait why are you not doing it like this. I'm
gonna I gotta figure it out you know I'm gonna just do it. You know I could I've made that
encounter way easier by going to get like item x maybe. We don't want to hear your life story.
What? I'm like defending myself. I got 15 000 fucking souls. Look I just beat one of the
hardest encounters in the whole game. I you know I can't. On to the next one immediately.
I can't sit here for fucking two minutes? Really? Really? One guy said that.
Any regular circumstance I would go fucking take a bath right now. In fact I might just have to
control her in my hand and be in the bath. Mob that guy. Come on like this is a fucking wildly
focused encounter. It's like a full almost five to ten minute straight boss fight.
I think I should be able to sit here for like a couple minutes and just talk.
The battle memory of an extraordinary foe. Okay a man who failed to become Shura instead became a
vessel for the flames of hatred. As fate would have it he was bound stubbornly to his world.
It wasn't until he became a demon that he was finally able to depart for the next.
Interesting. Why no face cam? I don't like face cam. I don't really do face cam if you're new.
Sealed shut why? All right so I did it. Now I have to go. I did the two snakes because there was a
giant fuck-off demon at the door. I guess that is why you would seal the door. He's wearing I'm not
wearing the same shirt again. I'm wearing a like workout shirt because I knew I was going to be
like freaking the fuck out and talking about like AI and shit. Um is this that lady? Is this the rice
lady?
You know don't you know who the one-armed demon was before?
See it might be better that way. What a fate to be set ablaze in the fires of hatred
and suffer eternally as a demon. You put an end to his misery. That's all it was.
Okay so the hatred he channeled has lost its vessel. The longer the fires of war rage on
or ash it that does not mean you should step into his place. Maybe if I bring him some sake.
He sure did love that. No more sculptor at the at the idol. All of a sudden I gotta fight this big
guy over here. Do you know who that was? Better that you don't. Knock one back for him. I will
right now. Pour out a monkey booze. He did like like he did like all the booze we brought on.
Interesting. Well that was fucking hard. That's the I'll be honest with you. That was the hardest
boss I think I've bought in a like From Software game. That's like maybe Orphan and well Madeir.
Madeir was just hell because it just took too long. I feel good though. I do feel very satisfied. My
soul was ripped apart. Is there anything else I can do here? I just walked off the edge. Thank
god there's like an idiot wall because I was just gonna walk this way. Prove you're not wearing the
same shirt. No I don't have to do that. I don't have to prove I'm not. I don't have to prove
anything. I think we go back to the estate. We have to go through the door right? Anything else
is probably something secret here. Let me go back to the idol. Wait hello. What do you got?
No I've already seen you. Two heavy coin purses. Computers don't wear clothes. How far am I? I'm
at the end of the game. So if you just popped in here to be like oh did he just get out.
You don't want to be here. I'm literally at like the final probably an hour or two of the game
and by hour or two I mean I'm probably gonna get my ass kicked for like at least two or three
hours but that's fine. I'm willing to go crazy. I'm gonna lose it. I barely started talking about
how computers are gonna take over and that's nothing. You ain't heard anything yet. Still
don't have one of those. What about skills? He still doesn't have the spear. No I'm not gonna
have it. I'll be the one guy that doesn't have the spear. That's fine. I don't care. It's not
necessary with a video game end game. All right what. Get that off the screen before somebody
screams at you. Okay so I have. Why is this not available? This I need that to get this.
Living force is through here which I'm gonna need this and that. I don't know what to do with these
points. Maybe the midair tool because we're at the very end of the game unless there's something I
really desperately am gonna need here. Midair combo maybe or vault over. Maybe midair combo.
I don't know but there's only like a couple maybe more of the emblems.
It's one. Yeah fuck it. But I feel like maybe that it's only one right. Is that gonna be enough for
me to. I can do both. Combo arts while in the air. I mean just if I. I feel like that it's
necessary at some point. And then shadow rush. So I need three more. Have I ever used a combo? Yeah
I use this thing pretty frequently. I use this pretty frequently.
Ever since I got it. I use it on. I don't use it on bosses though.
Oh a box. What the fuck is this? Phantom Gunai can be used to upgrade the loaded shuriken.
And I think I got. It's the spear. I got Luigi. How many prayer beads do I have? Come on where's
my prayer bead? I have like I need two more right. I have to pay money for the spear. What do I got
for cash? Let's see. I have no. How much do I got? I got thousand two thousand twenty one hundred.
Not enough. I could sell some stuff though. Dragon Rock cured. So I have zeroed for
the worst part. I feel like I've missed so many prayer beads. How you doing? You good?
I don't think there's any more business for you right now. Okay I think I'm ready. Let's continue.
Now where was it? It was not. Was it Kuro's room? No there was like a secret door or something right.
No no no it was the reservoir right. So I gotta go back to the reservoir. When you feel like you
missed something but you don't know what. Yeah it's always like that with these games though.
What do you have? I already bought it. Okay there's mask fragment two. Mask fragment one is over there.
Where's the other one? Five thousand dollars. Guys I'm not gonna buy that. May the departed
rest in peace. All right so we're gonna go back to the reservoir which was um is it this way or that
way? What's the mask for? I don't know. I also got two. I spent all that time getting the snake hearts
and I have no idea what those do. No this is wrong. This is the castle entrance. This is like the
giant moat. Why does the mox keep popping up on the screen man? The snake hearts are for a true
ending. Oh how do I do it? So then I can is it down here? It's this way. I think it's down here.
This is like the moat right. I gotta go down. Is this the right way? Um I don't think it is.
Is it? I need to get like a higher. I need to get a better view. I wonder if I can still get
there from here. LOL moments with Jerma985. No this is more desperately clinging to
trying to be good at a video game. Eight five. What? Oh they're just fighting.
No this is that's just where it was. I just I was just here. Stop caring. All right this is just a
mess. It's pretty this may this may as well just be dark so it's pretty bleak here.
No I don't even want to fight you guys. I just want to go to wherever I need to go.
It's like that beginning area of the game with a huge bridge.
Uh and I can't teleport here. Oh I think this is it. Is this it? You don't want to do that. That's
what I'm trying to stop. Oh fuck who's the boss? All right. Two at the same time. It's a backstab
but I guess okay well um come back. I have two. This is no way. Like I have to backstab one of
them. You know what I'm gonna try something. So that guy's turning though. Okay how do I fucking
jump on that guy? Do I just have to kick that guy's ass first as fast as I can? Let's fight him. Let's
go. You and me. He kind of just he just hit me. Okay I should probably back up a little.
He doesn't know which way to go. See? How much does this suck buddy? Doesn't it suck to have to
fight two people at the same time? Yeah it sucks doesn't it? Yeah you see it in real time how hard
it is. Come on. No that that whoops. Don't go into the fire. Don't go into the fire.
I don't know how hard this guy was. I mean yeah I did have I did have something helping me but
fairies. I remember that guy giving me so much trouble. Even uh yeah I did have a co-op partner
but still. You live? I tried to talk to him. He apparently didn't want to talk. Okay well I tried.
Uh I'm gonna just revive my shit because that guy's not gonna come back. One of them will but
it's fine. I don't care. I'm just gonna leave anyways. This looks like the correct way to go.
To the secret door and there's a new idol there but exploring this area is probably a good idea.
Oh no. Why? They make it look so it's so it's right there. It's just right there for you.
Waiting for you to do it. No apparently not. Now I can do it. Wow that in no way anyone can do that.
That's superhuman strength right there. Hell it's nothing else to do. I think I'm just gonna go.
He has a robot arm. I mean I guess so. He does have a robot arm. You're right. He is made out
of robotics. See he's fucking AI already taking over. I told you who they made this game for.
Uh what about up here? Nothing? No. All right here we go. Rest a bit. Secret passage key has
been used. Let's take it to the next area. Activate boomer bot. Okay. Is there a reason why every
FromSoftware game has an end zone like this? Dark Souls 3, Bloodborne.
This is lightning guy right? Oh shit I really did buy mine on eBay.
I have the real one. You bought the one on the convention floor.
No one has the right to the dragon's heritage. It is no one's to bear.
I wish there was another way. It's all right. We started here. We end here. We both have mortal
blades. Wait does that mean if I die then the game ends? Yes. Let's finish this. That seems kind of
weird. Wait but we both have mortal blades. I can't lose this fight.
You got a long wind-up time here. That's a thrust.
That's also a thrust. No it's not. What he just reversed my reversal?
Wait a minute. He reversed. I reversed you and you reversed me? That doesn't work. What?
What? Wait a minute. Wait a minute. I'm dead. What? He can't reverse that?
Is that? That's a thrust. Was that a thrust? Well game over. I lose. Okay.
Wow I dodged it somehow. Okay he's gonna get his moveset down. It's hard to get a moveset down
when you die instantly. Okay here's the grab right? Coming up. I'm not sure I can block those.
That? No fuck. I'm against the wall here. I can't move. There we go.
It's hard to see through the grass. Like the high flower is making it hard to see what he's doing.
He changes it up a lot. He's got a sweep. He's got a thrust. He's gonna grab and he
there's different thrusts. He has two different thrusts. All right this is fun. Let's go.
No the sweep. I thought it was thrust. Fuck man. Heal. Sweep again. Jesus Christ. Oh my.
It's an instant. I'm dead. Instantly. Fuck me. Okay. I was thinking there.
I tried to jump but pressed two buttons at the same time. Jesus.
That move is the best time to get any games in. All right. Goodbye. Mortal blade. You got your
mortal blade taken from you. I'll take it. I can't wait for the centipede to blow out of the top of
his head. Right? That's definitely not the whole fight. He's gonna cut himself in half.
I was in there for so long.
Pitiful grandchild. It stinks in here. What? How? The person can't fit in there. Who the fuck? How
do you fit in there? What? He just like shed that guy. What the fuck? Ishi- Ishi- Ishi- Ishii was
dead. Three health bars. No. Easy now. Oh you're fast. And that's okay. That's a slash. One, two,
three. He's got a couple combos. Okay. Um. I gotta see as much of him as I can. What the fuck? Okay.
It's a long charge. I think he'd probably dash around it. I'm also just realizing something
really important. I gotta fight this dickhead every time. No. Do I have to fight Ginnituro again?
No. Like you haven't figured it out like after so long. Like I don't wanna fight these four people.
That's four health bars. Eventually this is gonna get to a point where this guy is not even a problem
anymore. It's just an annoyance. I got it. It's not even- It's four- It's a four health. Just think of
it as a four health bar fight with cutscenes in the middle. And we're gonna have- We're gonna- All
right. See. Uh. What time is it right now? It's like 5 30 pacific. All right. I'll see you at like 10
p.m. when I maybe eventually get this guy down to one bubble. Fuck. I thought I could get it right
there. It was sloppy. Bring on granddad. I don't know why I'm not watching the cutscene. All right.
All right. Here we go. Eight flasks. Sweep. Jesus Christ. Just give it to the bottle.
What the fuck is he doing? Damn it. I got it. Oh boy. He's gonna do it.
Come on. Let me get to phase two. Let me see it. I tried to. I'm an idiot.
Fuck me, man. Oh, I still got health. No. I don't- It's hard to tell sometimes if he's dead or not. He like
lies on the ground for something. It's too long. Sometimes you spend like an extra second like you do
like the- I died. I had like 0.2% health. Well, very obviously it was becoming very obvious.
This guy, you have to just go in. You see what happened that first thing when I was doing right
there? Not with you in particular. Now I'm just fucking being stupid. It happens. That happens
every single fucking time. I heal right when he's about to do that move. Just do it again.
That has happened every time. I heal. No, when he's going for the slash. He's reading my inputs.
The thing it seems with Isshin is his posture wasn't that great. If you stay up on him,
let me just get there. Speaking of posture, mine's pretty bad right now. Oh my god. Oh my god. What
am I doing? I beat it- I did it so easily like two tries ago and now he's just kicking the shit out
of me. What the fuck? My god. What the fuck? Why? I had it so- when I par- I deflect the fuck out of
him and my posture gets destroyed. I deflected almost every attack he did and my posture is gone.
I will restore Isshin to glory. Fuck. Now he- he ducks in the grass, man. Oh my fucking god.
Get out of here. Look like the real boss, you chump.
You gotta stay up on him. Damn it. Look at me. Look at his posture.
He's got a dash around it when he goes up in the air like that.
I tried. I tried to grab it. Slash. Fuck. Jesus, man.
He's so good. His moves are so hard to predict.
Holy shit, he's insane. And this is phase one. Oh my god.
I'm gonna need to deflect the first one. Good luck. Good luck. That's all, I'm dead.
You are in hell now. This took me 52 tries. See you in five hours. This took some people
six to seven hours to do. Holy shit. Wow, that's ridiculous.
All right. Wow, that's unbelievable. No, he does it every time. Jeremy, what are you doing?
He does it every time you eat. Me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me. What? He's hiding. He's like
behind the fucking turd. He's on the fucking turd. Can this kill me? Like, that was fucking stupid.
I just got, I got LOS'd by the giant shit rock in the middle. I love when you username it
third person. I'm trying to tell myself to relax. Dude, how many, how many dings am I going to get
in a row? Jesus Christ, why? What is he doing? God. Ding, coming at you. Ding, coming at you.
Ding, this time I'm going to do it four times in a row. Oh, what the fuck?
His posture is nearly full. Yeah, but all it takes is for you to get hit once.
Sekiro. Shadows get hit two times and die. That's the new title of this game.
It's not even worth it to resurrect. It really isn't. If I, if you, because you have to fight
grandpa, you have to fight hyper grandpa with three fucking bars.
Why did I not? Fuck, really? Letting me hit you. All right, seer old granddad.
I didn't even know where he was. That was a weird camera.
Nope. Look at that posture damage I'm doing to him. It's not even, it's nothing. It's like touching.
I'm just like tapping him on the shoulder. What? Wow. That was a huge sweep. Wow. I tried to block
it. I did though. Thankfully. Oh fuck, no. God damn it. Oh my God. Die in one hit. It's a, I don't
even know, man. It's so hard. He puts the thing in the sheath and then who the fuck knows what he's
doing? Holy shit. You know, we talk about like people that will complete this game and somebody
said, who is this game for last night? I, I wonder what the steam achievements will be for us.
Or like somebody that was beating Isshin. I wonder how many people would stump it
and get this far. It's gotta be like 0.2%. What the hell are you doing? I thought it was,
it was a little early, but I still got it. God, grandpa. Is it a slash? Yep.
No, I don't even, man. It's so, he's such a variance in his move set.
It's almost like you can't even predict. You just gotta, you have to block everything he does. It's
hard to determine when he's gonna fucking do anything. We got no telegraphs really except
for the dings. God, man. No. All right, can I just like accept that he's better than me?
And we'll watch the YouTube video at the end of the game.
No, it's so fast, man. You don't even get a second to react to it. I gotta get like burned into my
brain. Holy fuck. God. In front of him? In front of him for that move maybe? I don't know. Maybe
he's standing in front of him. What? No, I thought it was gonna get a ding. Just don't get hit. You
underestimate how hard this is. Let me get some shit here. I don't really want to use anything
until I have, I'll get this off the bar. I don't really want to use sugars until I can reliably
get them at least down to like the first phase. I'll get them on the bar just to have them, but
I only have three. How many do I have in storage? Eleven. Play the inspiration music? Oh, we're not
ready for that yet. I can't even get this guy past the first bubble. Yeah, I'm not going to use any
of these until I can reliably get him to at least pass first to second phase. I have no more spirit
emblems. Oh wow, that's bad. Well, there goes my whole shit moment. I'll be honest, I think I have
to take a break. The demon of hatred was so un-fucking-bearable that I think I have to
take a break and like come back in like 15 minutes or something and do it. Like just, just chill for
like 10 minutes. Though these two back to back is like no way. Not gonna happen. I'll try it one
more time and then I'm gonna need like spirit emblems. This is gonna be a nightmare. I thought,
wow, I thought I was in the right. Did it hit me with the handle? It hit me in the head with the
handle. Posture is gone. No one can come. No, man. Posture, please. I'm so sweaty right now too.
This is like, this is the hardest work that I've had in like three years. Your posture will break
if you miss a parry. You know how hard it is to block a parry every move? That's like unreliable.
I'm trying to parry these guys. It's just so awkward. He hesitates on half of them.
Fat tracking. No, I thought it was this big sweep. Oh my fucking god. Not even scratched on him by the way.
No, I thought he was putting it in the sheath. I thought he was going right in the sheath.
Now I'm dead. And I can't even second.
Fuck. One bubble. Let's see phase two. Let's just look at it. Let me just see it and then I'll watch
the rest on YouTube. I'll watch the rest of this on YouTube. What happened? He has a gun.
He's got a gun. He has a different weapon. They already did this in the last game.
I'm just gonna use the fucking turd rocket. Christ. He pulled out a gun. Whatever.
That's ridiculous, man. Oh my goodness gracious. This is fucking wild.
They know how fucking around these last few encounters. Especially like these last two.
They were just like, yeah, you know, you like thought things were hard, but
we're on like AI level of difficulty now. Just kill me.
All right. Last. Last. Last time. Last attempt. And then I'm gonna.
I'm just gonna fucking stare at the screen for five minutes. I don't even know what to do.
I wish I didn't have to do this.
Uh, and you come on. I'm like, you come here with the fucking last little bit of that.
All right. I gotta take a break. This is insanity.
I'll be back in like two minutes. I'm just gonna. I'm gonna go walk around for water in my face.
I'll be right back. I haven't had any pause in the game. I have to just memorize everything.
I have to play space channel five with a sword. Left, right, left, right, chew, chew, chew, up,
up, honda, honda, honda, chew, honda, store. Oh, he got me with that. I get out of here. My posture.
Oh my God. I was trying to be tracking from dark souls two.
Dark souls two is he's gone. No, I think that he thinks he's going to keep going around.
He does that big long. He does a big long.
We'll talk about it after I die in like 30 seconds. Let's try it again.
Look at this posture already.
Oh, Jesus fucking Christ, man.
No, it's a. I don't even know why they have healing boards for this fight.
You don't have an opportunity to do it. Damn it. No, I just didn't know. He's back.
Hesitation is defeat. Hesitation is defeat. But Sekiro.
Hesitation is defeat. But sorry, you haven't memorized every single animation the developers
have made. Sekiro, why didn't you memorize every move I do? I didn't even get to respond before
he started that animation. Young Sekiro, don't let me hit you. Forehead.
Stop hesitating.
This is so ridiculous. This is a case study. They got hired by like the government to make
this game. This is like a government project. What if he's fucking with you? Hesitate before
doing anything. Maybe let's just run the fuck away. You know what I mean?
Oh no, it was. I thought it was the big one. Is there any way to tell? Because seriously,
he puts the sheath in and oh, is it a sweep or is it the big one? You got that like 10th of a
fucking second to react to these things. Like in human reaction time. It's just what the fuck?
It's because it's human reaction time. That's what I went so wrong.
That's how you do it. No, but that's that's this one. See, it's so weird. I thought it was done.
Can't. The heal is like a is a vulnerability. It's like hard to get yourself out of that mindset
where don't ask me. I'm trying guys. It's sloppy. What? No. Oh, yeah. Could have blocked it. Yeah,
but here's the thing. They put in this rock, paper, scissor gameplay that I'm like waiting
to see that emblem because I can't. I have to do the whatever I have to the technique is to get
away from it. So when he goes down here, I come for a sweep. Nope, no, no, no, no. It's just regular
text. It's just like fuck, man. Makes it so much harder. Like, see, he did the sweep at that same
thing last time. And it wasn't that you know, like he ducked down and did hurt. But this time,
the indicator popped up. He did that before and he went into a combo kind of win the lottery with
the number of scratch tickets. I didn't get any of those. I'm just hesitating now. I'm
just getting exhausted. Fucking playing this. I thought he was gonna
can't jump over that. Trying to test it if I could. See, my reaction time is just dwindled
from doing this for so long in a row. No, I don't have the demon thing on anymore. I crushed it.
This took me five hours to beat somebody said.
That's why I'm telling you this is a government experiment.
Okay, he's still got that. I think I'm gonna go get spirit emblems and just take a second
because when you do it so many times in a row, you just, it's everything's blend together and
it becomes impossible. Yeah, I'm lost. I've drained every ounce of my energy at the demon
fucking hatred. And now I'm just like fucking on fumes right now fighting this.
I need like a second wind or something, man. Give me like a second wind.
Inject caffeine directly into your bloodstream. I don't know if that's a good idea.
Oh no, I thought I could, I thought it was a big circle around you.
You can parry it, but I just wish I could fight him and not have to go through the first guy
every time. This is like, the phase two is like fucking 10 times worse than this shit.
The first guy's a weakling. Yeah, I know he is. But remember what I just said about how
doing the same thing over and over again, your brain just starts to hate it. Like I don't want
to fight Genichiro every time. I already killed him. Start me like right when the grandfather
cutscene happens. We don't have to do this again. It's reaching a seven. Oh shit, it is frustrating.
He said a nine. Well, this is the last boss in the whole game. So I mean, like, of course,
of course with their computer, they wanted to make the encounter fucking like
2% of every player will ever beat it. That's fine. I'm going to try to be one of like the 3%
of every human who's purchased this game to beat it. I have to actually like go get spirit
emblems or something. This is all blended into my brain. Like everything's the same. Everything,
the whole world is going together. Every color, every flower is turning into the same flower.
All right. Don't I have a thing? There it is, right? Now this kills me. Where's the thing that I can
give myself spirit emblems? Is it a combat art or what? Ceremonial tanto. I only have three of them.
I mean, what? Plus five. That doesn't seem like very much. I only, I can only use once per life.
I guess I could buy them too. How much money? How much do they cost? 50 for one. Well,
what else am I going to spend my money on, right? 500 coins is 10. What's, what's the point of this
even being in the game? This is like 500 bucks. No, I'd rather just go grind the money. Yeah,
I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm taking a break from this shit. I'm going to go do something else.
Fuck this final encounter. I know there was a couple of mini bosses I could fight.
There's still like two or three. Are there any more bosses left? No, this is the last one.
There was something here. This is with the stealth section, right? In the manor? How many prayer
beats do you have? I couldn't do this with at least eight. Um, let me see. Where are they here? One,
two, three, four, five, six. I have six. Am I under postured? You don't need eight.
Uh, I feel like I'm just delaying the inevitable. I'm missing a, a gourd too, somehow. There's no way
this game has nine gourds, right? I missed one somewhere. There is 10. Yeah, I would assume.
Um, yeah, gourds really don't matter. That's true. It really is true. Like healing is, I,
when I die, I have like seven or eight healing gourds. You just have to, you gotta be like on
point. See, like I have nine healing gourds.
Fuck! I thought I had a second. Take a heal! Why am I crouching? Crouching! Here we go.
Good luck. For a second time, I've seen it.
And it thrusts right after him. What the fuck is this? The amount of effort it takes to get there.
Is like, I, I can like build up some strength for like one or two attempts.
The second phase is like, don't parry him. I'm just gonna dodge around. Right? Like, I mean,
maybe? I don't know. I feel, I feel like I'm confused to help do that second phase.
Okay. Remember, just reflect the bullets.
Come on, man. Just die. I don't even know how he hit me with that.
Wrong. I have a fucking bunch of dumb fucking moves. Swing 400 times. From something ashy him.
Oh, you go from such a different rhythm. Painful.
I thought it was the thrust, but it wasn't.
All right, two. I'm just gonna take it. Let's try some dodging.
No way. No way. No fucking way, man. No. No, no, no, no.
How many attacks do you have in that sequence? It's almost like you're not even attacking.
Shit's just happening around you. I don't even get a chance, even with a parry.
I'm trying to run, but of course, stuck on the wall. Of course. I, I'll tell you. So it's,
the dodge button is the McCurry counter, right? So anytime someone says, why are you dodging
into him? Don't dodge into him. I'm trying to do the McCurry, but dodge is also on that button.
So it just, it happens. Dodge is this button. McCurry counter is also this button. So I'm not
trying to dodge into him. It's just happening because it's the same button. And yeah, the time
is probably off, but that's people looking at it and they go, what the hell is he doing?
That's close. I already fucked it up. I wouldn't be surprised if I died more here than I have in
the entire game. Like how many times, how many, okay, how many deaths for the whole entire
experience? Like a hundred times? Do we even have a counter? I'm looking at chat right now. This is
a mistake.
Parried it already, but oh, it's so frustrating. Fuck me.
Oh, you crap.
Maybe you'll restore Ashina to glory. I don't think he will though. We've had this conversation
over and over and over again. I keep killing you, but yeah, here we are. I have to see your face
again. It's great. I love it. He restored Ashina to glory this time and what's going to happen
this time? Maybe I'll prevent him from restoring Ashina to glory. Let's do it again on boss before
the boss. See you next time. Whoops. No, my reaction times is zero. This is it.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna play a different game for like an hour or so. And I am at, I am at a two
for reaction time right now. Damn it. Lentless. I wish there was a stamina bar in this game.
I'm able to manage half these motherfuckers better than I can now.
Pull me out of your neck. I'll fight this whippersnapper for you.
Let me just reach into my neck and see what I got here.
This young secco though, try me again in the second phase. Let's do it son.
Even the fucking parry is ridiculous.
Let me get a follow-up there. No follow-ups allowed. Huge move. No follow-up. No, it takes
too long. Parrying any of his moves with the spear, you can't do a follow-up. It just does
posture damage to you. That's all it does. Fight! I just barely can get one. See what I'm saying?
I can't. You gotta get the fuck out of there.
I'm so fucked. No, no, no. I just can't.
Didn't make a fucking break. Give me like a fucking break. And I didn't catch that one.
What the fuck is happening man?
Isn't this supposed to be a stealth game? Yeah, I guess. He's already starting with that shit.
So if you heal, you're dead. They have a way to- every time.
I thought it was the- this is next level. It really is.
Uh, prosthetics? I have to grind for spirit ammo.
Okay, I can tell you something. I parried like
98% of every single move. And like still, this motherfucker is still gone.
Fuck. Let's see.
That was not it. I would have caught it. It just was so slow. And that's it. You make one mistake,
strike the whole fucking thing over. Um, this is great. Wow, he's already up here. Fuck. Not
dealing with that. Shit in my face. Back it up. Where- oh, I'm on the fucking end of the bridge.
No, no, nope, nope, nope.
Wait. No, I need to see phase three, motherfucker. Phase three. Oh, this is going to be horrible.
What does he do? Wow, it's lightning. What the fuck? Just lightning to strike random places?
Oh no. All right, I'm gonna beat this motherfucker. This guy's dead. I'm gonna beat this.
I'm going for it. I can do it. I'm gonna beat him. I'm gonna beat this guy. I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna- I'm gonna have to get some fucking Durango juice or something. I'm gonna get like
an apple juice. Bring it on. Let's go. I'm ready. No.
Fuckin' let him fuck you up.
Posture. Bad.
No, I tried to do it. I tried to do it. I tried to do it. I tried to do it. I tried to do it.
Oh fuck, I forgot he did that shit. Out. Bye. Jump.
No, fuck, fuck, fuck. I thought it was fucking dive. No, it wasn't. I thought I had- I tried
to do the fucking Makiri. Just to- it was too- I saw it. I tried. That's so slow. The delay on
something scared me so much. Un-fucking-bearable. Sometimes he's just like, what? Never comes.
No! Holy shit, I made it. I was sloppy as hell, but all right, come on, old man.
Caught me there.
Whoa, that was bad.
Didn't get that.
No, god damn it. Give me a fucking break. That was horse shit. Oh my god. One mistake.
Just don't make a mistake, bro. 12 minute boss fight. Don't make any mistakes, sir.
I think I just jumped off the camera, yeah? Computer reactions.
Sweep every time.
I gotta back up a little. Not a great trade there.
Oh, I got a bad start here. I gotta get back into this shit.
No, I thought it was the spin. It's just so easy to get caught up and get hit by one of those.
They both have the same wind up.
Eight fucking goids. Oh yeah, crouch. Please crouch. Yeah, can I disable that fucking button?
How do I- I'm gonna disable crouch. Seriously. I'm gonna disable it. It's so easy to press it.
Like, why the fuck is this even a thing in the game? Like, get rid of it. I don't want it.
No crouch. Get- get the fuck out of here. I can't even unbind it.
No, that doesn't matter. I can't unbind it. Really? I didn't fucking anything else up, right?
Yeah. Like, get that fucking off my bar. So unnecessary.
Every time it's at the little palm block, it's a thrust.
Crouch. I've used crouch like three times in the 45 hours I played this game.
No, I fucking ran into it. Man. I fucking thought it- ugh.
Because of that whole third- I don't even know what he does. That's the worst part about this
fan is just grinding to fucking get to the third bubble. To see the new move. That's going to
instantly kill me. Fucking government project. It really is. I swear to God.
Like, see how susceptible they are. Fucking repetition. I tried to jump,
but the fucking fat ass finger just hit the button.
That was quick right off the bat. Whatever. I got nine of these fucking things.
Mistake. That was a mistake. I gotta run.
What? How did I not parry that? I wish that jump follow-up would work, like, even half the time.
Dodge instead of what I wanted to do.
Sometimes I forget I'm playing from. Every button is the same button software.
From soft from every fucking- there's three actions on one button. Am I playing red dead?
That was fucking dog shit. Dog shit is what we call it.
We'll just do this until you stop.
What? Listen to me. Listen to me. Listen to me. Every single ledge in the game. Every single one.
Go back and watch every vaude. Every single ledge you can't run off of. It stops you. You have to
jump. I just walked off that one. No fucking way. I even tested it. I was running into the fucking
wall like an hour ago. I don't have any gourds left. Oh, that's so fucking stupid. Why can you
even walk off the edge here? Of all things to add to this encounter, being able to fall off the
fucking edge. Right now I'm in like phase three or some shit. I'm screaming right now. I mean,
I could use my pellets, but this is- I'm dead here. I'm gonna- he's gonna come and just smash me.
Really? I can't believe that. Now we're at the edge again. Make sure you don't walk off the edge.
My posture's recovering so slowly right now. Fucking god damn it, man.
You know, they're gonna make a game somehow harder than this one, and then nobody will play it.
They're gonna keep going until there's no way you can beat it. The next game from From Software
makes, uh, it might be, it might be like times five. Because blood- all right, remember Bloodborne?
Everyone's like, holy shit, Bloodborne is crazy. And then everyone- but here's the next part, right?
Once everybody figures out how to play this game, and more than two weeks go by,
we'll figure out every little cheese, everything to do. It's- you have to learn how to parry, right?
But man, going from iFrames to this, holy shit, it's like completely different. You have to
relearn an entire new video game. Like, not even just a new video game, but like, an entirely new
thinking. A lot of games don't even come close with the kind of mechanics that are here,
in regards to how it feels. It's fucking amazing! This is fucking awesome! But my goodness,
does it take a lot to fucking forget everything you've ever learned? Playing most of your games.
I- seriously, I got- my reaction times just went to shit right there. I was waiting for it.
You're not supposed to beat this dude in one night. You're supposed to come back like six
times and beat this guy. You're supposed to play it blank and process the fucking encounter.
Let's go. That's all I did? It's back to healed. Whoa, whoa, hold on here. What was that? I got
like- that was strange. It like turned me around.
That back pull, fuck that. Oh, come yoooon.
More of this fucking combo?
All right, what the fuck have we got now? I've got to see it. I gotta revive.
Didn't get it? It didn't get it. I didn't get it. Risky, but it worth it. No, I thought he was doing
the thing. No, what? He did it twice in a fucking row. How am I not getting this? Fuck you. This
is not- this is- I got- no, I thought it was the lightning move again. No, it was- I thought it
was the lightning move. Fuck, man. No. I thought he was doing for the lightning and I'm just gonna
try and time it. You have to jump so much later than he does. Oh, painful. Painful, painful,
painful, painful. I got- come on. That was the best attempt all night. Oh, trying, guys. I really am.
I'm trying. I promise. I'm trying. Okay, come on, man. I gotta use the buffs? Yeah, but the thing is,
duh. They take like a couple seconds to work and knowing me, I'm gonna use them and get hit
by something and die. I know me. Well, that was dumb. I'm still like fucking shook up from that
last one. See if I can get a decent attempt here. No, I'm getting too close, I think.
I just teleported into one. Let's just use one now. Back up, back up. Not worth it. It's bad.
No, man. I have no way. I- I couldn't get up. Fuck me. That combo, you gotta just run away.
You can't be stopped. This one right here, man. It's just no fucking way.
It's really neat. When he does that, like, he does like four or five moves in a row,
and even if you parry him, you're just dead. You have to just run. Next time. Just gotta relax.
Whoops. I fat-fingered that. Yeah, I fucked it up. My hands are like covered in fucking water
right now. I gotta like fucking wipe them off with something. This controller is fucking filthy.
I'm gonna get him. I'll beat him. Positive thoughts only here. Only positive vibes today.
That's not true. I've been fucking talking shit this whole time.
I thought that, uh, getting sloppy. Not really actually getting sloppy. Like, for real getting
sloppy. I'm still a lightning run from that fucking lightning run. Yeah, look at me. My,
like, body is, like, nerves up. Just making mistakes. Let's go. Bad. I have six heals left.
I'm fucked here. Nope, okay. Oh, fuck. No. I just jumped preemptively like an idiot.
No, no, no, no. This first phase fucks me every time. Seriously. Now he's back to fucking zero posture again.
It's slowing down. I gotta fucking. Couple more tries, and then I'm gonna grab some water.
Damn. I'm gonna grab some water. I'm gonna slam like 16 outs, and I'm gonna come up fair.
Did you ever lied about Minecraft fair? Thanks for the five community subs.
Thank you so much. Every stream has seen me give subs, dude. Thank you.
That's not it. Oh, I keep, you know, I never see him do that, so that's why I keep getting
me. I usually. It's all right, just get the fuck out. Sloppy.
That combo gets me every single time, and he starts off with it every time, man.
That, like, one, one, two, three. And snap, I never parry it.
I didn't dodge that. How is that fucking possible? I looked like I did.
God, that was not what I thought it was. I almost got fucking hit by that, too.
That, look at how far away I was.
See, there it is, man. There it is. No, no way can you stop that. It's not. No way. No way.
Even if you want to parry everything. No fucking way. Clean, too. Real clean.
Back it up. Don't stay in here. Don't stay in. No reason to. This is bullshit.
Spin, spin, spin, spin, spin. Let's do it. I'm ready. What do you mean? What's wrong with the
audio? There's a buzzing sound? What? Are we good? All right. Here we go. Here we go. Stupid
fucking mouse. Oh my God. Get the mouse off the screen. Why can I not? Oh my fucking God.
Why is this even a thing? I thought I was. No, no. God damn it, Jeremy. Fuck you.
I got no opportunity. I have to just fucking go. Yes. He's dead. Yes. Fuck you. Wait, no.
Face four. He's face four. I can't move. No, face. I don't care. Just give me the credits.
Oh, that was fucking crazy. Damn, what a fucking game. Initial P thanks to the five community subs.
Oh, I could like cry right now. God damn it, man. That was fucking crazy.
One fucking mistake. Your body just gets so, so beside itself. Okay, here we go. Let's read this.
The battle memory of an extraordinary foe lingering in the mind of the wolf.
Commune with a sculptor's idol and confront memories of battle for attack power. At his peak,
Ishina Ashina devoted himself to deadly conflict in pursuit of strength, a single-minded killing
machine of a man. Dragon Flash. Oh, all right. So I'll tell you, Mike, you want to talk about
like a final rating for the game? We're at like an eight seven last night, right? Yesterday.
That fight was so ridiculous. I had, I think that bumped it up to a nine. I hated that,
but I loved it at the same time. Oh, it's so exhilarating. I think that I think I get,
I think I'm going to give this a nine. In his younger years, Ishina was a devil with the
sword, spending his days in pursuit of life or death combat. He often ruminated on how a cut
should be made, but his blade always moved first. He ain't going to get up, right? Is that,
he's not going to like stand up and turn into an ape. Look, bucko, we don't want to hear your life
story. I did it. I did it. Yes. I was, I had some thoughts there that maybe not. You know,
I was getting a lot of self-doubt halfway through that fight. And I'm just sitting there going,
oh, am I going to be, am I going to be one of the people like the, is there anything else I can do?
Oh man. It feels so good to just know that it's over. Well, not, oh, well, not that I,
I'm glad the game is over, but that fight is over. You okay, Kuro? Give divine dragons tear.
I mean, I have it here. Your side. Oh, it's ridiculous. I can't even get over it.
Take the dragon tears. I can't wait to play Picross for like another hour or two. We're coming down
hard here, guys. I'm going to come down and play Picross and just hang out.
Now sever these ties of immortality. Well, that kid's a bad-ass, not even like a,
wait, wait, wait, what? I become the sculptor now? I think it is best that you have this.
What is that? No doubt the day will come when a shinobi arrives seeking strength.
Oh, the cycle just repeats. So wait, what? So I, was I the sculptor? You are the sculptor. So you,
the shinobi then shows up and you do the whole thing again. Well, I got the two snake hearts,
but I didn't use them apparently. It's the same story as Dark Souls.
Oh, that was exhilarating. It was, I had a, I said a lot. I talked a lot of shit,
but it was venting. I hope you guys understand that because that was truly like a fucking ridiculous
experience. Here's the, you know what? I'm going to tell you something right now.
They're going to have to do something. Is anything going to be able to,
I feel like every other video game is, let me turn this down. After playing through Sekiro,
I feel like every other video game is just not even going to be easy. No more video games can
be made. Video games are easy now. I'm going to be so spoiled rotten. I'm going to go play another
game and it's going to be like, this is not as hard as Sekiro. This is easy. I'm just, I'm ruined
forever. No, but for all my venting complaints, frustrations, that was, that was fantastic.
I am very, very happy to have that experience. I think some of these bosses, a couple of them
were probably my favorites of the whole series, just in the way that they're, you play them.
Ludwig from Bloodborne is my favorite boss ever made, but I would probably say
that the ape, the first time you fight the ape was just crazy. That was so cool. It was really
kind of out there and frustrating, but it was, the guardian ape was a very interesting, cool encounter.
Sekiro isn't a Soulsborne though, I know. The owl fight was awesome. Even some of the, just the
mini bosses were really, really interesting too. Kill Demon of Hatred, I did. I did that before this.
How would you rank it compared to Dark Souls 1 through 3? Well, it's kind of not fair to make
that comparison though, because they're just not the same. It's, Bloodborne I think is my favorite
still, but that's, I'm so biased for Bloodborne. It's like one of my favorite games ever made
of all time. It might even be my favorite game ever made, but Sekiro is probably, I think it's,
I think it's better than Dark Souls 3, just in regards to, but it's also new and Dark Souls 3
really did kind of feel like they really wanted to end that series. So I loved Dark Souls 3,
but I think this is probably a better game than Dark Souls 3 in regards to just overall package.
I think it's better than Dark Souls 3, but I think it's not as good as Bloodborne.
I'm very biased on that. Bloodborne is a full straight up 10 out of 10 for me.
With or without the DLC for Dark Souls 3? The DLC in Dark Souls 3 was cool.
The ice area was really cool. Was the game harder as a whole? I think so, because this game forces
you to play the game the way that they want you to play it. In all the Dark Souls and Soulsborne
games, you can approach any situation however you want. You can put on a full set of armor,
you can get a hide behind a shield, you can use eye frames, you can do eye frame abuse,
you can build a certain character based on one-shotting bosses. You can't do that here.
You can go grind souls and go over level for a boss. Can't do that here either.
So I think this is much harder than any of the Souls games, just because you could build an
entire character and grind to beat any boss in like three hits. So in that regard, I think this is
five to ten times harder than any of the Souls games. Not because the game is harder, but because
you can't play it the way that you want. You have to play this game. You have to do it the way that
they want you to. And if you don't, you're dead. Good, see you later. I don't like the overleveling
shit. I think this game makes for better bosses and balance. That's true, but you also, you have
to understand though, is a lot of people kind of just want to play it. And if something's really
too fucking hard, like sometimes you'll hit a wall and it's just like, I can't, and no summoning,
no co-op. How many people do you know that played through the Dark Souls games that had to do bosses
with partners? You can't, do you have to, you have to play a bunch of casuals. Yeah, but like I said,
when I was in the middle of this last fight, what's the percentage of people that are going to
beat that? What, has somebody said that the demon of hatred was what, six percent of players that
have the game on Steam that have that achievement? That's not very much. That is so small of a
percentage of people that have the game. And it did just come up, that's true, but I don't think
that number will get any more than, I don't think that number will go higher than like 20 or 30 percent.
It's about two percent for Isshin right now. Wow. So, I mean, so yeah, I know, I know the philosophy
is get good, get good, but maybe some people don't really want to. You know, what if you only have
like a couple hours to like really sit down and play a game? You know, oh, I just got off of work
and I got to grind and get good. It can be hard. So that's why stuff like the co-op, having a friend
come in and play with like a party, being able to overlevel yourself just to kind of play it.
Now you could say, well, that's not the way the game is supposed to be played, but judging by
the percentages that you see, some people have to do it like that. But in all those regards, all
those things that we talked about, that's why this game I think is much harder. It has nothing
really to do with like the game's physical mechanics as much as you have to play the way
the game tells you to. No friends, no fucking item abuse, no iFrame abuse. You've got to fucking do
it. And it can be very frustrating, very, listen to me talking, very frustrating. All right. If you
choose to start playthrough two now, you may do so by accessing the large sculptor's idol in the...
Um, is there anything left I could do? Or that's a new game plus. Well, I'm not going to start it
now. Oh, there are other headlesses. Oh, he's still alive. You're still alive. Well, let me
bring everybody back to life one more time. Oh, there we go. Start playthrough two. Isshina Isshina
at 2% is the bad ending. Not Sword Saint Isshina, who is at 8%. Okay, that's still very little.
There's an optional boss in the estate. Let me see. 221 total deaths. 52 deaths at Isshin. Damn.
52. That's so many. I can't believe I kept my fucking composure and kept going. So 220.
God, how did you guys put up with me for that long? Seriously. I hope I wasn't too fucking
obnoxious during that. Seriously. I can imagine I would be, I was probably so fucking annoying.
I hate doing that, but it's just frustration coming out. I don't mean fucking any of it.
I muted you for a while. I'm sorry. It was fucking fun though. Isshina, if you gotta do
what you gotta do. Thanks for still sticking around and watching though. Appreciate that.
I had to get good and I tried and I did. So 220 deaths. I was gonna do a scratch ticket
for every death. I'm not buying 220 $1 scratch tickets. That'll take two weeks to scratch them.
So we're gonna do like fives or something. Yeah, we'll do five. Wait, hold on. How many is that?
That's still a ton. What about $10 tickets? The higher the denomination goes, guys,
the more chance to win. You don't win shit with a $1 scratch ticket. No, I'm not gonna scratch
220 tickets. Do you understand how stupid that is? That'll take two or three straight streams.
That's gonna be like 15 hours. 22 $10 tickets and one $1 ticket or $44, $5. Depends. Now I still
have to make sure that that's like a legal thing to do for Terms of Service because then whatever
happens from there goes into community subs. It's gonna be called secure scratch off for community
subs. It's gonna have to be a whole stream. It really is. That's gonna be the weirdest stream
or charity. Yeah, that's probably a better idea. Whatever I get
from the scratch offs is going right to charity. That's better. All right, I think that's it for
this gambling for charity for securo death. People are gonna stumble into that stream and just be
like, what the fuck is this guy doing? Oh, right, right, there's a boss apparently that I missed.
Let's just go look at it. Dude, imagine if I won like 50 grand. That would be an awesome charitable
donation there. Imagine winning like 100 grand on one of those tickets. Did you do the ape fights?
Yeah, I did both of them. But there was one here, right? Let me just take a look. It won't be as
weird as the labo streams. What? Why are the labo streams weird? Just because I got shit faced and
started like karate kicking the camera. All right, let me I'm gonna just run around. I know
there was something. Is that weird? Or is that just like a Saturday, you know? Oh, no, it's with the
the flute guys, right? Do the lake headless. I did the lake headless already, didn't I?
The one that was in the water there. The dog just killed me. I don't think I'm in the right spot.
I think it's a different one. Flower viewing, great sakura.
No, it is this one. Oh, 222 scratch sticks. No, we don't let's don't count anymore. 221.
My like my like relaxation is starting to like kick in. I'm like, oh, oh, it's I did it.
What a fucking tough game. Uh, where are we going? Did I fight Owl? Yeah, I think I did all the
optional like major bosses. Now, I feel like because I ran through this. Scrooge.
Scrooge, what the fuck is happening? Oh, oh, yeah, I rage unbounded. Why can I not? No,
that's the wrong one. Oh, what a psycho. God, I hate being like rage streamer. Like, I don't like it,
but it's all right. Sometimes you have to have some of those moments. Where uh, where is this guy?
I think there's only, no, just this guy, that guy. Oh, no, they're lightning. They're lightning.
Oh, I probably can just run through this to be honest. Yeah, dude. Okay, for people that just
came here, I can't do it. I've been stuck here for two straight days. The stealth section is so
irritating. I can't fucking do it. I don't know what to do. I don't know where to go. It's just so
fucked up, man. Right. Okay, so I didn't wait a minute. Did I go down here? Yeah, I don't think
I'm going to be able to complete this. Oh, it's a gourd seed. Relax. That was weird. I really got
clipped inside of him. First impression, I don't like the stealth part. Doesn't like stealth in a
samurai game. I don't like this part. I don't like it. Stop banning people. Somebody actually, I
didn't mention it because I was just kind of, I was kind of tilted during the last fight, last boss,
but somebody said, I'm going to paraphrase it here, but they said, damn, he's getting so salty.
I wonder if he's going to actually start banning people. You know, like look over and see somebody
be like, oh, dude, you suck. It's already salty. When is he going to start to actually ban somebody?
Never done that before. We make jokes on this channel all the time about, oh yeah, like get
banned. It's a permanent ban. And it's like 10 seconds, right? It's a joke. I've never done that
before. Imagine just getting so upset and just so just tilted and raged that like somebody says
something that I just like fucking shut up and like ban somebody. No, I don't know if it would
ever get there. That's the thing. I don't, whenever I get upset at a game, I don't take it out on other
people. I take it out on like myself mostly. Like I'll say like, what the fuck? What an idiot. Like
I was a bad move, but I don't think I would ever like be so angry that I would like tell like a
viewer like, dude, you're wrong. Shut the fuck up. Like I don't, I don't know. I don't know why I
would do that. Have I ever been banned? It's like from you mean from a chat? Uh, um, I know. I don't
think so. All right. This is the place that I didn't go to this. Oh my God. He's looking over
here. No, we're fine. Um, this is good. Will this work? Cause I feel like I'm going to do this and
then I got to put the shuriken on. Cause all right. If you get to that point, right? Let's say you get
to a point where you're really actually starting to get mad at viewers and like telling people
like to fuck off and shouldn't start banning people. The cycle is just going to go on. It's
going to be horrible because nobody likes to hear that. Like, you know, I need, nobody wants to be
told like, Hey, shut the fuck up guys. It's like, Whoa, come on man. And then all of a sudden,
like people start to get angry at you being angry at them and then they get angry at you and you
start to, it just cascades. All right. So I didn't go over here last time. That's why even if I do
like look over and see something that somebody says, something that's like mean or something,
for the most part, I know that people are just fucking around and I wouldn't want to like
escalate something just because somebody was like, dude, you like kind of suck at this. It's like,
yeah. All right. All right. Whatever. Because I know a large portion of why I'm upset is
because I'm not doing well, right? So if I looked over right now and saw, holy shit, you suck.
It's like, Hey, I suck. Hey, fuck you. It's like, you know, jokey. But when you're mad,
when you're angry and you look over, there's a very high chance that that same message,
instead of making you laugh, we'll be like, I don't even know what it's like. It's hard. This
is a fucking hard game. And no, you're, you're wrong. But I obviously never want to get to that
point because I like to have fun here and not like get fucking pissed off and like hate streaming or
something. We didn't ask for your life story. Yeah, you did. All right. Where is this thing
that I'm supposed to be finding? This is the only place I didn't really explore. I like sprinted
through it after I didn't play. I'm looking for the boss. There's a boss somewhere around here.
That's what somebody told me at least. Go to the idol and take a left. I've already cleared so much.
Well, it was cool to see everything. Ooh, wait. I think I found it. It's right there. That's the
noise. Okay. That's the noise that was, remember we were over here before and everyone was
monkey. There was like a bunch of monkey from the loud noises. So I have to go around this building.
So it really is just kind of to the right here. The great Lord Walden just gave 20 community subs.
Thank you. Great Lord Walden. That's an insane amount of subs. Thank you. I think I missed
bits and shit too, during that whole process. I'm sorry if I missed like a lot of money.
Did I beat the game? I did. I'm just kind of going back and cleaning up some stuff just to see it.
So this is not the right idol. What is the idol? It's this one. No, it is. It is. Okay, I'm on the
roof. Wasn't it like right here? No, it's this way. Right? It's like straight ahead here.
No, that's not it. Jerma lied about Minecraft VR. Five more community subs. Thank you. I feel like
I've done it completely wrong. Have I lost my goddamn mind? There's none. It's right here.
So the idol's right there. The bowl is right here. Here? I'm sorry. I'm like, I know he's like
right here somewhere. Here? I found it. Right here. Oh, Jesus. Okay. I thought he was caged up.
He's just free to be here out on the bright side. I wish I found this earlier. That's a lot of money.
Okay, well, he says he has terror shit on his head. So let's, let's get that out of the way.
Let's see. Did he just shoot an arrow at me? Somebody is shooting an arrow at me. Oh, right.
The guy up on the roof. Okay. Well, maybe I gotta clear the roof then before I do this.
It's pretty clear at this point. Maybe not. Oh, here comes another lottery ticket. What am I
doing? I have no, it's not even. You don't count as a beast? Why did it not work the first time?
Really? You're not a beast? Bullshit. You're a fucking animal. You're an animal.
Probably should start parrying these things. Just dodge.
No, not a place I want to be. Ow. Come here. Come here, dog. Oh, out of gorge. He's out of gorge.
That really isn't even any terror. Oops. Okay. I'm getting really, really dumb here. Oh, I'm getting
real dumb. Round and round we go. Just stay right up his ass. Oh, he kind of popped me there.
Oh my God. I just looked over at chat. I saw somebody say Thanos. Well, what the fuck am I
doing, man? I just got like, I keep giving him such a good opportunity to hit me, to stay behind him.
Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Oh, that hurts. Hi, Gorgi. Oh, that would have been nice. That would
have been nice to have. What is it? 16? That's not really that big of a deal. Cool. All right.
Well, hold on. I can get this. Finally beat the palace. No, guys, I'm just grinding.
I can't do it. The boss in here? No, I'm just trying to grind for beads. I did. Okay,
I'm talking about areas. This area was my favorite. Not that part over there. Like, not that part.
This part. Not that actually. Not this part either. That not the stealth part.
The part where you walk down the mountain. So pretty much this is not my favorite zone. I just
like the way it looks. Worst area, in my opinion, just in regards to how hard it was for me to do.
That optional zone leading up to the demon of hatred. It just was kind of brutal going through
that. And I'm trying to think of other areas that I had just trouble with.
This area was hard to do and it was kind of frustrating with the weird lightning guys and
people kicking the ball at you. But I don't know if this is the worst area. Well, I'm here. I might
as well just try. Isn't there a headless down here? Yeah, they're right here. Ow. You actually
don't really need confetti here, huh? I'm gonna use that. Tag team headless. You know, before,
I've already seen the end of the tunnel. This doesn't even bother me anymore.
Nothing can compare to that final fight. Like, it doesn't even matter. This is just like funny
now. This is like, this is a comedy. Whatever this is, I didn't get it. Didn't even use any sugar
or anything. I was just, I remember, I'm, you see, the last boss and even the demon of hatred.
Use the items. Use the candy. Use this. Use the, you gotta do it, man. Imagine if I had, if I had
stopped and used like the candy in that third phase thinking I was, I should have, I would have
probably died. My brain is just, my brain is fucking just a mess. All right, so we got this guy.
Now there's how many, how many swings? The yellow one's throwing shit at me now.
Whoa, that goes across the whole place, huh? Um, I wonder if I should kill the
illusion first. Let's see. How hard, how annoying are you? Yeah, you got way less health.
You're just annoying. Okay, all right. I can't take this down here? I can't, oh, I can't use that.
All right, well, no, get out. He's almost dead. There it is. One down. Okay, now I wonder. I'm
already almost dead. They can't respawn, do they? Walls. Boy, I see where I'm at.
Surprise! Oh my god, what am I doing? I'm dead. Goodbye. Actually, I might be able to get it
if he does the grab again. All right, no health. Nooooo! Game sucks. Game sucks. Game sucks. Game
sucks. been a while since you heard that. mad because bad. mad because gab. gab. gabby? they're
both back. game actually sucks. what? what? no god damn it no no no no no no no underwater level
suck underwater level suck underwater level suck they always suck always suck because like i have
look at this shit like get me up here and then out i'm just gonna bait the uh just bait the grab and
he gives free hits on him grabby grab me yeah you're not so bad not so bad oh that's a double
terror come on grab me fine i'll just do what i do again with this shit oh my god hey so
i was just getting bored there i'll be honest waiting for a goddamn grab and i had my health
is so low what the hell am i doing like that was just like i'm just sitting there waiting for him
to do a move not even looking at my health bar he's gonna do the fucking like magic missile span
three times yeah he's a stationary target don't you guys understand the people that move the
slowest i may as well just give up you the slower you are the harder you are for me to play in these
games you could telegraph and move for 15 straight like now i'm just getting angry again like these
slow slug ass fucking people takes him like three full five full seconds to a move you just sit there
with like your fucking hand up your ass waiting for him to do something he telegraphed the whole
way around oh fucking headless man this dude's not even hard it's not even hard i'm making it
so much more difficult god die die die die die die die die die die seriously like they get it's not
even a fun game like that's the problem i have it's like i it's the game is like i was a nine
and this shit is just but just part of the reason why i oh my god okay no more jokes i have to hit
him once hey you got it no actually uh kim also baked cookies and she said hey do you want some
cookies from nine to one there it is oh they get the gates aren't even fun if you get has anybody
ever said that this is a game it's not even fun any other streamers these are actually pretty good
so that's the sugar oh these are good hey thank you this is like oatmeal
hot hot all my mouth oh all right i think we did i clean up everything this is like the securito
cleanup before picross get away from me get away from me it's not even fun the big fish can you
kill the big fish interesting so yeah i get i do have bait let me see is it a consumable
or is this blind streamer that already went by it what do you think is it is that a case that is
the case isn't it what is happening oh it's it is it's a key item you guys got me here can't be
thinking i'm saying this is precious bait something resembling horns seem to be jutting out of it
just the kind of bait the master loves ring the bell drop the bait what the hell does that mean
i can't even select this is there a spot where i can put this i missed this in his cave
well here's the this is where he came from right so he jumped and crashed here
is there something i'm gonna do up here bait bait find a way to the roof spawn at the palace
grounds and find a way to the roof why don't i just fucking get on the roof right now like this
this an accidental button press oops a daisy oops he's not gonna get back up there is he
nope uh-oh cocks really that's not good whoa whoa whoa whoa i just got a surge of like
wow what's happening right now all right that was weird so i have my i i stream at 6 000 up
and for a few seconds right there i was just had 11 000 up i don't know how that happened
that was great gimme up there really okay top of the castle which which side should i get up here
uh you know what let's just skip this shit that i already finished yeah i did i'm just going back
and checking out some of the optional stuff that i missed all right this one this one this one
this one thinks that johnny kich this one says uh main hall which one's at the top
intersect them oh no no no no i'm in the wrong place which one of these great sacra palace
grounds i think palestine pickross isn't going to help this is i can't graduate fourth grade
level mistakes oh okay wait come on all right we're at the top there's like a canister here
put it in here fourth grade what did i walk into your sword no okay i thought for a second that was
i got hit with an arrow all right we're at the top of the palace
so if i'm a place to put bait down there i don't think i did very much exploring over here
like that way how would i can i get up there on the roof i don't think there's a grappling
point up here i'm up here can i make this jump i think i tried this before it didn't work is there
a branch let's see a branch over here but where's the there's no indicator i feel like i'm not you
know i don't see an indicator do i like the cookies the cookies are great i don't think i
could reach that god damn it whatever just quickly that takes so much longer than any other soul
software game okay let's try this again what am i eating uh i went outside and i took a shovel and
i brought some dirt in here and i figured i would chew on it for a while and like swallow it and
shit is your eye is your uh no i'm confused grapple from the bonfire area like back here
definitely from back here on the roof of this building we didn't ask you for your life story
yes but is there a point i can get to from here i don't see anything from here
have to go around here probably around this way right let's see a place to go ah right there
i can't get there from here do i do i have to jump oh hold on really that's kind of that'd be
really difficult to know to do that no i was gonna say just jump over like jump out you know what i
mean there it is just to go through the building journal lighter about minecraft br five more
community subs adding to your total there thank you so much all right now now i can reach this tree
almost didn't fucking get it that was really close all right here we go
oh in the air thank god i had forward momentum yeah you just stop doing that and just bite me
all right so let's keep going across what am i up to now i am just doing exploring areas that i
didn't get to see the whole thing fighting optional bosses that i missed doing optional content
that kind of thing so now there's no grapple point here i guess i'm just gonna go over this
way this is all the way across leads to down here oh is it just a bridge do i just go to the bridge
i'm just gonna go to the bridge it looks like a place i haven't gone oops i mean that it looks
about right okay so what does this do for me is it not this bridge oh fuck oh my god this i remember
seeing this guy right okay i remember this remember i looked over here and i was like who's that
guy okay cool i never even i just went right by there's the bell noble fish feed the fish
okay bell must be rung i only have four of these so uh what happens when i do this is he gonna
jump up here and i have to like shoot him in the head am i about to play duck hunt with a fish
very good all right how do i feed him use precious bait here you go how much is it
do i have to do it again feed it again wow i get it i like this guy feed the fish
treasure carps okay we're gonna do it again we have to do we're gonna do it again
wait let me ask them we talked to him one more time feed it feed it feed it we're gonna keep
feeding it let's see what happens when we do it twice all right here you go have some more
oh he's got human teeth that's just weird he's got like dentures in another scale again this is
fun what do i get for doing that another scale draws fat wait say it again he's gonna get fat
so i don't feed him again let's do it again you'll get it again you have some more
oh stop feeding i'm fucking frames and dying right now i'm bad
go back to pot guy who's pot guy pot guy pot guy damn what's going on with my internet
it's crazy it's like surging all over so i'm going to like 2 000 up to like 12 000 up it's going
crazy the fish scale pot guys you give give you more bait now you guys talk about the guy
that's in the trash can but the guy's in the pots there's one two in this area but it's well hidden
where is he here am i in there am i like warm or do i need to go to another idol
because i have no idea what the hell he is all the way in the right so what you're talking about like
my right or his right you know what i mean like that way all right my right or his right my right
this way like over here i said my right i said my right like over here
he's not gonna come in the water what are the palace grounds idle and then go right after the
double doors yeah i'm totally fine with like back sitting and shit right now that's fine
i the game's over i completed it so so go right through the double doors i'm cool if you guys
just want to tell me whatever you want that's fine so go right through the double doors and then
down like here somebody says i hate you i'm sorry man up up up up up it's well hidden
what the fuck oh i see right here yeah that is pretty hidden isn't it i hate you know i hate me
too i hate me too that's like the same color as the the leaves here so it can be kind of deceiving
and you lose the indicator oh crystal lizards cool look at this little hidden zone over here
so many sequits i love this where the hell are you found him hello hello please as i have i
thought the corrupted monk you know i might i probably should just put this here just because
people probably trickling in asking about if i beat it or not let's just do this because we're
just kind of sticking around uh game completed uh just tying up loose ends there we go no like
i don't like where that is right here that's fine that's not horrible looking it looks good
all right so change the title of the title is yeah the title is inaccurate we're almost done
though was i lied to who lied to me he'll give it to you um all right we'll hear
the other one
so the other one tried to kill the car so i have to talk to the
all right i'm gonna pick this guy up and like throw him down the stairs
uh so i i spent like seven scales here
does that they have to talk to the other one talk to the other pot i'm like a messenger for these
two all right let's go talk to the other one he was at i always forget where he is ashina
with not depths um outskirts which one is he at castle gate he's right in somewhere in the
beginning i think it's castle gate isn't it or ashina castle that was way off do you dragon spring
thick ross waiting room hey all right there there you are down there there he is let's go
i just fucking pancaked on the ground do you have any more scales you talk to my brother
i wish i could be a cop like him you just broke your weenus it's me zabon there it is truly
precious bait if bait has hair you know it's something truly special the herata noble in
the pot is obsessed with thoughts of becoming a master he who receives the scale of the carp
becomes closer to a carp himself i bestow upon you my secret treasure all right okay let's go
don't forget to use the bait let's go talk to the other one what a weird questline near pot noble
he sounds like bugleberry hi no but i want to ask you a question
okay well i just have the bait i wonder do i have to do anything else with this guy or can i just
kill the fish how many scales do i need i need three more scales let's just go fish for
all right look no let's just kill this motherfucker this guy's too pushy
okay am i gonna enrage this dude there we go ding ding come get food pot noble harunaga's bait
uh let's see okay oh no oh no i feel this is like kind of sad
i'm sad i like wish i didn't do that no he's so sad do nothing that's just mean
what is he in there what do i get for doing that is he just dead on the ground go to the travel to
a different arena the eighth boss somebody's gonna be washed up down like down here is it gonna be
so sad oh the other one uh where's the other one uh great white whisker priceless white whisker
taken from the great colored carp while the great carp is naturally immortal if killed its whiskers
can be plucked the sound of the whisker being removed is surely magic music to the ears of
certain people some would feel relief at their sound of their mission being completed others
the joy of having their heart's desire granted couldn't go in i know it would be really cool
let me tell you something how from software take a note here if you walked in here and it was
enough zone optional zone in like this magic stomach anything else that's really ridiculous
though i feel bad all right so i can i'm assuming i can give the whisker to either the guy that's
sad or one of the guys in the trashcans and i think i'm gonna give it to the guy that's sad
because that's like that's fucked up he spent his like whole life with this fish why would i
give it to that guy why would i give it to the guy that's like please i want to be a fish kill it
why do i keep calling picto pics picross because this was called it's picross is the name of the
puzzle i have something for you take it yeah i need to give this guy peace right you gotta
have some closure here even though i did it this is sick
divine grass that's all i get
it all right full charge fucking slash that huge quest line for a piece of grass but hold on
wait you did this you did this what the hell what did you do to my muppet friend oh damn let's rest
again anything else all for some drugs you're a monster but wait wait he's still around right
there'll be another one it'll be small i thought it was gonna be a little koi fish or something
all right let's go talk to the dumpster guy uh he seems to be out of his dumpster
alapis and there he is what how did this work ha i don't understand how this works
so he was in the bucket i killed the carp and then he becomes carp no sea man what about the
other one i want to talk to the other one it's just like the giant rat didn't get any of the
mask pieces what a shame all right we'll get what are the three what does it do if you get all three
i mean that's they're very expensive five thousand dollars like 12 carps 12
that's a lot what does it actually do you can level attack power with five levels it turns skill
points into attack points oh that's kind of useful i'm so confused by what this any of this even
means this is dead why there's a boss there's a boss in there it's a new world okay so one lives
one dies cool all right well i think that's gonna do it sakira i've tied up pretty much
most of the loose ends somebody must be to go dive in the water here there's at least see the
optional boss in the estate okay well it's in the water that's this is where the headless is is it
dive in the water here i mean like over this way other way you can't get the estate boss
so did i go too far you guys know who jerk is gonna stream today
is the grave there's two graves here now picked out pics you promised
i know i know i did what was this body water over here time of like this way over here
yeah no i killed this already there's one down here yeah i already killed this one
i already got that one so i can i can't do the uh the optional boss in the estate
is the lottery thing still happening if i can do it yeah so where in the estate just out of
curiosity see if i can see it no that's that's not it's very different ending okay all right
so i've seen pretty much everything i need to see game's fucking fantastic
picto pics waiting room yeah i thought i was gonna be i think we're just gonna call it i think we're
just gonna call it i'm gonna get out of the game and open up picto pics that's it calling
siciro that's the end sad because i don't see another playthrough in the future for me
maybe eventually but what an experience it was view the memory what are you talking about here
like this thing oh no never mind watch the other endings i don't want to do that
because if i ever uh if for some reason i ever want to play it again i kind of want to do a
different thing one who returns from the great beyond does so at the peak of their prosperity
issuing coveted strength in all manner of techniques throughout his mortal struggle
he wished for war until his final hour and that is precisely what he got the end the only one that
made it out alive was the random vendor i got a new skill too yeah uh where is it is it a combat
art mortal draw was this it which one was a dragon flash read us a bedtime story draw your sword
from a sheet to slice at high speed and then holding them this dragon flash draw your sword
from a sheet to slice at high speed concern all right let's take a look ah that's cool
charged up so it's the thing he was doing he's stalling for picross
well okay one more for the road okay i'm gonna take a break
i'm gonna grab some water and i'm gonna open up picross just chill for like an hour or so
one more for the road i'll be back