Hey, how are you? Cool. Okay, what about the rest of you? There's a few of you that didn't say
anything. Okay, welcome back. Do I like... I don't even know what that is. I don't know what the
latest meme encyclopedia I have to look up. I don't know what that is. I'm not gonna read it.
Garden Flipper tonight, like yesterday. We're back at it again. This time it's a little
different because this time they changed over. We're on static IP and we got a new DNS server.
So I don't know how this one will turn out. It might not do anything. I was testing for the last
hour and a half or so just streaming to the test server and it was okay. It was okay.
I'm gonna hold my breath on this though because I'm so used to
the last week straight of it being all over the place. It's probably not gonna do anything
but I dropped like 1%, like 2% of frames when I was doing the test which is not great but
it's not terrible either. Am I on the sleep deprivation drug again? No, not really. Not
today, although I haven't been getting much sleep. I don't know what it is. Maybe I'm going
through like, I don't know, what's the thing you go through when you get older? Menopause, right?
I don't know. Maybe it's that. Manopause. No, but I'm honestly just sitting here for a few
minutes just to take a look and we look pretty clean. I got the green light. Green means
go. Red means stop. Yellow means I don't know what to do! I don't know what to do! Should I
go really fast or should I hit the fucking brakes? So, we're gonna go. We got green.
I scared your dog. Hey, turn me up a little bit. Turn the volume up a little.
I'll make it right. I'm probably on your television set. Turn me up.
Hey, who's that? Who's that good dog? Are you a good dog? Yes, you are. You are such a good
dog. Are you a good dog? Yes. Okay, you can turn me down. You can lower the volume now.
Let me get this on the screen. Hey, that's where we were. Your dog didn't react. That's impossible.
I don't believe that. Every dog reacts to that. What is W? W, W, W, W, W?
Why is everybody doing W? Oh, because of the ground. Right. Oh, because of the ground. Right.
Like I always am. Right. Okay, right. Right. So, today, I kind of want to do something
real quick. I just want to go look. Yesterday, we had a... I don't know. Let me go see what would...
I think I kind of need a clean slate here because where's the one that I already... this one,
right? Go to the house. House price $74,000. I've spent $6,500 on renovation and $36,000.
How bad is this place? We got five community subs from Tori. This is cool. No, this is
terrible. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I need to do a little walk through here.
Thank you for the five community subs, Tori T. This is not... this is terrible. This is not right.
What was wrong with me last night? This is like what happens when you give insects drugs.
Wasn't there a video where they gave like a spider like crack? I am the crack spider or like
the the fucking cocaine spider. Jeff, thank you for the five community subs, Jeff. I made a big
playground. This place... all right. I don't want to do this one anymore. This is horrible.
I don't want to do this house. I, in fact, want to get rid of this house. I don't want this one.
I was on like drugs last night. I was on sleep drugs. None of this works. I hate all of this.
It's making me feel bad. Finish this house. Finish the oven. Oh yeah, it was supposed to
be an oven. Can I not do this? I don't think I want to flip this one. I want to start over.
This place sucks. I'm selling it. The art looks all right. Restart this house? No, no. I'll come
back to it. I'll come back to it. I don't like really anything about this. American Crop English
Modern. English. It has a free raw layout. Flower bows with blooming colorful perennials
and naturally shaped bushes are dominating. Yeah, this is pretty natural. Romantic corners
don't have any of that. What about these crops? I mean, this is pretty, there's no equipment,
but excellent. A lot of plants, various surfaces, cleanliness, mown grass. All right. So I got a
3% bump on my, on my offers. All right. I'm, I hate this place. I don't want anything to do
with it. No, no, no, no. I like this place. I kind of want to keep it. I keep it for now.
I'm not going to keep it. I want to start over and I want to do it right. Browser. I
got tons of money. Oh, who cares? I just bought a house, half flipped it and then
walked out the front door, turned around and went, who cares? Almost only a garden. Okay.
New house. Are you going to lose your gamer license? I'll take care of it. This is,
this is the one. This place is, look at this place. This place is bad. $183,000.
The home alone house is $400,000, guys. This is a lot of money, but there's no
garden in the home alone house. How do I even, isn't, this is just a regular house.
This doesn't need to be flipped. I hope that wasn't a mistake. I don't have any money left.
None of this is garden stuff. All I need to say is that a movie was filmed here
and the price already went up. Can I say that? Be careful. Is it trapped still? Oh,
I can just sell this stuff. It's not a movie, Jeremy. It's real. Well, I just wasted a
bunch of money. I'll probably just get it right back. This is, okay, this is going to be a real
flip job. Holy buckets, 800 bucks. All right. Let's start here. This is already done. This
house is already made. Look at the Christmas tree. This is not a house flipper. This house
was flipped before I got here. Maybe a fuse is blown. I'm just like, I'm just cleaning up
this way. I have to do that with every single one of these. Yeah, the fuse is probably
in the garage. I'll take care of it. Just hold on. I'm busy. I think I'm replacing LEDs with
like the internal mechanical lights. Why would you replace LEDs? Watch out. Nothing's going to
happen. There's no traps. Nothing's going to happen. Oh, look out. A paint can just hit
me right in the fucking mouth. Yeah, this is, it can be, it's not dirty. So much trash here.
No, this is not. This is what you think trash looks like. You need to come to my house.
I mean, whoa, whoa, it's a lot dirty. No, I'm actually pretty clean. I'm a pretty clean
individual. There's three people living here. Yeah, we've got our own domains. So, okay,
somebody tell me, give me the TLDR here. Was there a reason for me to purchase this house?
Are you guys waiting for like the oil to be on the ground and for me to slip and break
my neck? Is that what's going on? I don't think you're going to get it. I'm fairly certain that
you're not going to get it. I open up this one and it's just crossbow shoots down the hall
right by my face. Now, this is done. That looks fine. Yeah, I think it's clean. This
house is clean. How do you flip a house that's already done? Maybe a fuse is blown. Yeah,
I'm going to go look for that. Hold on. There's like trash over here. What's behind the
tree? Oh, just glass. All right, let's go turn it all on. There's probably a fuse blown.
Probably. Press E. All right, stick it back in. E. E. Can you play the piano? All right,
so that's fine. Everything's good. Just have to turn the fuse on. And then is it going to
turn into like a clown show in here? What is all this? Oh, what? Isn't there a basement
in this movie? Kitchen. The knife. Anything with the knives? Nothing. Pizza. It's just a
little bit of trash. Not a big deal at all. This ain't a big deal. It's a viscera cleanup
detail. It is like viscera. There's only one difference. You can plant trees and you can buy
furniture. It's very similar, but also different at the same time. All right,
dispose, dispose, dispose, dispose, dispose. Everything's clean out here.
Is this snow? All right, well, I gotta go down. This is the garage, right?
Destroy this house. Let me just get to the gotcha moment. There will be a gotcha here,
and everyone will scream. Let's find it. Here's the fuse box. All right, hold on.
It was possible that something was going to run down the stairs at me.
One's broken. This one's nice and fixed. Turn it on. All right, now we have power.
Ooh, wait a minute. What? Dead? No, very much alive. Why? Why do I have this in the house?
All right, let's turn on the Christmas tree so everyone can laugh. All right. Can I have my
money back? I want a refund on the house. Can you do that? Can you do a refund if you buy a
house? You got 30 days to see if you wanted it or not. Yeah, I'd like to return a house,
please. Reason for the return? Uh, I just, no, I'm not feeling it. You guys have like that,
like 30-day policy, so I'll just, I'll try another one. Imagine getting a free trial house.
You get 30 days. Why don't they treat houses like they treat mattresses?
You know, you can sleep on a mattress for fucking like three months, and then you just,
if you don't want it anymore, you send it back. All right, let's see. What am I,
can I please at least get, I just cleaned it up a little. Nobody does that. No,
I know nobody does that, but like look at all every mattress you could ever purchase.
They do like 180 days, like 200 days, some of them. Some of them do a year. Why?
The Smoothe family. All right, I made a profit. $66,000 profit. Positive options,
negative options, okay. Uh, I'm gonna accept, let's negotiate. I mean, come on,
this movie, this was made, this was used in a movie. 30,000? More? What do you mean
increase? That's no, just $30,000 is enough. Why is everybody saying increase, increase,
increase? They're gonna, all right, you guys are right. Okay, sure, I will take the
extra $49,000. Literally scammed those people. Yes, 500,000 and still living here. I get 600
grand. Yeah, I, I, I pretend I'm one of those people that I, I'm like the guy down the street
that doesn't ever buy anything but he just sees a secret millionaire. Didn't they like
a do a show about like this, the millionaire, like millionaires in the shadows, whatever
it was called, or like the secret life of the millionaire. They've done it before.
You should have re-booby-trapped that house. All right, now let's go for real.
That was just a teaser for you and that was a teaser for the internet being actually fine.
Well, all right, I'm not gonna hold my breath. We got this piece of crap but I don't want to
do that one. This is, here's the big one. This is the big one. The pizza oven house is,
I'm just, I'm sorry, that's just gonna have to sit on the shelf. That thing sucks. I had
no vision there. I was just like drunk. I was just sleep drunk. At least sell it. I will. I'm
gonna clean it up but this is the big one here. Do the nuclear house. He didn't read the asshole
part. What? Yeah, because I, what do you mean? What are you talking about? I'm gonna do this
one. Does this, we got, we got garden flipper. I'm gonna make a good garden. I'm gonna make
an actual really nice one. A large house with a separate garage for two cars in raw condition.
I will sell it right away. Two floors. This is a big one. I'm going for it. I just made some,
I just made this. Let's see how bad this is.
Oh my god. Imagine living across the street to this.
You know, we were really thinking about selling it in a year or two but uh,
our property value. Can you at least get rid of the fucking bricks? This house is,
probably shows up on those top 10 scary lists. Top 10 scariest abandoned buildings.
Top 5 scariest things caught on camera in abandoned houses. Eventually those people are
gonna, you know, here's what you understand. You know those people are gonna run out of
shit to make lists of, right? Eventually they're gonna have to start listing very boring things.
Top 5 types of wood to build a bird house. Here's the top 10 cities in a one mile radius
of London. Top 10 towns within five miles of Boston. They'll have to come up with some weird
shit, man. How do I get rid of them? What do I do? What do I do? What do I do?
How do you get rid of the mole? Dude, I did like, I just tried to like spade side down,
like shovel vertical on his head. Oh my god, that would have been horrendous.
Why is the mole so big? I don't know. Well fed. You got plenty of trash around here.
Plenty of ways for him to grow. Do I need to find him again?
What's the garage look like? I have to get a vision here. This place is huge. This is a
ridiculously large project. See you guys in nine hours. This is so big. I really do want like
screenshots though because I'm gonna put time into this. I'm gonna make this real. You ready?
Keep that in your memory. This is gonna be nice over here. Keep this part in memory too.
This is gonna be a nice long path. I want to start, should we go inside out or outside
in? I feel like you need to go, I don't know. Where do you even start here? You have to just
pick a corner and just start there. All right, we'll start with a dumpster. We'll start with
this corner first and I'm gonna get this corner to the way that I like it. I'm gonna
do a nice little garden here in the corner right here. We're gonna do like reds, purples,
weeds. I have the weed wacker too. Where is it right here? We're gonna get some nice grass. I'm
not gonna fuck around on this one. We do have a tree here though which ruins everything.
I have to put down new grass. Can you add water features? I'm not actually not sure.
That's a good question. Okay, let's get this out of here. Move it all. I'm gonna, I got a
vision. I don't want to turn around either because the second I turn around it's all,
it's all bets are off because it's like looking down when you're at a really high height.
I'll fall off. I'm just going for this quadrant right here first. He's sputter walking again.
It's gonna happen, okay? It's, that's just gonna happen. All right, don't bite off more
than you can chew. Just easily, easy, easy, easy. Go back here. I'm not supposed to turn around.
All right, that looks all right. Just this side. Well, I gotta lay, we'll lay the grass down.
I'll measure it. I'll get the tape measure. Sputter walking champion. Hey, I'm, I, I'm
gonna look. I got, I'm doing my garden the way that I want to do my garden. You want to do
your garden the way you want to do your garden? Get some tools and get out here.
All right, I'm almost ready to start this section. New gardener skill. Thank God.
I can't, should I not even press this? Is the text coming soon or is the tool coming
soon? I, why would it be? I don't know. Visible moles. 100% faster unfolding grass.
That's a big one. I'm doing this one. You're gardening like my grandma. I can't name you
anybody else that gardens. I, I just, all the gardeners that I know are over 50 that like plant
plants and garden. They're all like 55. I don't know anybody personally that gardens. My
grandmother used to garden. My mother gardens. A neighbor I had before was a gardener like
really into it. Not like a, wait a second, hold on, there's a difference between like a
professional gardener and like you go outside and you plant plants and stuff. We're talking
like hobby gardening or we're talking like you pay me a thousand dollars and I make your outside
of your house look nice. Like a professional gardener. Oh, there's plenty of them. Yeah.
When did I say that hobby gardening was invalid? I didn't, I didn't say that.
I said the gardeners that like the gardeners that I know are all older like my mother and
her friends and stuff. When did I immediately follow that up going they're invalid? What?
You should know more gardeners. I'm sorry. I don't know very many gardeners. I'm not supposed to
be over here. I'm not supposed to be over there yet. Dumb streamer doesn't even know 10
gardeners. I don't think I know 10 of anything. I don't know 10 plumbers. I don't know 10
firefighters. I don't know 10 gardeners. I know 10 like different people that do different
things. I don't think I know 10 people that do the same thing. Is there more than just this one?
Let's see. Rug grass. Big turf roll. Let's get this right. Top 10. Top 10 workers.
This is going to screw me over here though. The tree being in the way. I think start here
go out. I can patch that one up. I'm just going to get it to here. This is going to
line here for now. This corner. Yeah I can't name you 10 of any profession that I know.
Okay that's all good. Or any hobby or whatever. Streamers that I know. That I like personally
know them. Maybe like six? I don't know. I think you guys are severely overestimating
the amount of people that you may know that do a certain thing. That's as close as I can
get it. Let me just make sure this is going to work. You can't lay turf on this surface. Why
not? Is it because this grass has to be cut first? That can't be why right? Can I really
not lay it here? Can't lay turf on this surface. Wait what the? Okay that was weird.
Oh there's a fork on the ground. Let's see if this rolls out. How fast it goes.
Come on. Come on. Why? Like that's perfect. That roll's not even there. I'm not enjoying
the hitboxes on these because you're always going to have fucked up lines.
Always. I can't ever put something here. Never. All right I got the hammer out out of
accident. Like I can put it here. This is going to look so shitty now.
So apparently it can't go here. It can only go here. So I'm going to line it up. Can't go
there. It can go here. All right. Right there. Right here. Let's see if that fixes it. Yeah.
That's kind of annoying. Yeah because I will forever have this. I can never lay any grass
there. It's ruined. It's beyond repair. Yeah I know. Look this is not going to be grass.
But I mean look. I can. This is going to be grass. This is going to be grass. That's
going to be. I mean I'm trying to save my rolls here. That should overlap enough to give me
no line. Just knock the fence down. If you could. You can't. Receding. Receding grass line.
I might as well move this trash out of the way. Cut. Nice and clean. All right we're making
progress. Can I stop the night cycle? I only want it to be day. Day and night mode. Real time.
What time is it? It's going to be like this forever. All right. Real time. Oh wait. Was
there another one? What was the other one? Game time. Disabled. Got it. All right. This
is good. I want to work out in the garden. I don't want to go through day and night cycles.
These are to see my immersion. No one's going to be out here at four o'clock in the morning
doing gardening stuff. All right. Yeah. And oh. Jeremy makes another generalization about the
gardeners. Apparently according to Jeremy they're all old ladies and they only work in the day.
He's a monster. Did you hear what he said? But that's not what I said.
All right. Look at it. Look. Look how much better this is looking than last time.
Now here's the problem here. This is going to be an issue. All right. Hold on. Let me line
it up. Line it up. Line it up. All right. No. No. No. No. Which one was it? This one.
It's like moving around. Stop moving around. No. What am I fucking bumping into? Oh my god.
Yeah. This is causing collision. You would just stomp on this. Anybody want a glass of wine?
What do you think? Anyone want some wine? Why are you doing that? Look at. Look at.
What am I bumping into? All right. I'm just putting it down. Fuck it. I'm putting it down.
Gardening is a dumb. I'm just kidding. I just went off on gardeners.
I don't like gardening. I don't like it at all. I think it's stupid. It looks nice.
No, I will tell you, you know, gardening takes a considerable amount of skill.
It's one reason why I know this. I used to help my grandmother do it.
Oh, there he goes again. I used to help my grandmother do it. And I would be trying to
even just something as simple as planting, like actually getting the soil ready and then
it's hard to do that. It has to be the right consistency. It has to really hold it up.
It's going to be because you can really make it look like crap. Let's get this here.
I don't know how it would. No, I'm just going to do them one at a time. That was a nice story.
Nice story. Yeah. Let me tell you something, guys. Gardening is difficult to do. And here's
why. The soil, you know, you've got to get it in the. So you got to get it. It could
fall over in the soil. That's it. That's the whole story. All right. Just again, don't look
behind me. I mean, you can, but I don't want anyone else to. This is going to go straight
up all the way behind me. Don't look behind you in this game. I don't know what's going on
in your real life, but in the video game, we're trying to keep a positive attitude towards
our house. No lines. I've gotten pretty good at that. So what the hell? Why couldn't I do
this yesterday? I was like freaking out yesterday. Using the big roll. Yeah, because I got a big
roll. You know how many stacks I got? I got like hundreds rolled up here. I have so many
hundreds rolled up like this and I'm bringing to the bank and rubber bands that they get to
get like two managers over to help. OK, let's not get to Orphezelis over here. Oh, yeah.
You're flaunting your money. No, I don't think so. How do you get it? I got to deposit it
somehow. My Chad aura is growing. Damn, you're still rolling grass from yesterday.
Yeah, it takes a long time. I haven't gone to sleep. Let's just get it like this.
Make it nice and clean. Great. No, that's going to get blocked. That is not going to get
blocked. Use those surgery FPS hands. There you go. I've got one more little slab here.
What's going on here? Is there a line? What is this? There's a line here. What's this line?
Did I tell you guys that I'm really into sardines lately? I don't think we had that
conversation. Yeah, I'm really into it. Now we can get a little roll here. A small,
little small one. I just want to get this line. Is that going to get the whole line?
Is that getting it? No. What is this line? This is pissing me off. What's going on here?
Oh, oh, what is this? Oh, no. Is it? It's a shadow. No, like clearly look in there. You
can see the ground. Like right here. That's it. That's clearly grass. That's not a shadow.
That's not a shadow. There's a bump here. That's not a shadow. Look at right there.
And it was, oh yeah, sardines. They're pretty good. And I've been, I've been mashing them
up and then put it on toast. It's pretty damn good. Really good for you too. No,
it's not a shadow. Get this off. Disgusting. Why not just buy tuna? Cause
sardines have more selenium and they're also not a predatory fish. So they don't have as much
mercury. Welcome to the school of German. I thought you made that up. No. Welcome to
gardening school. First things first. Welcome to gardening school. Put your tools away.
Everybody put your fucking tools away. Who ate sardines this morning? Raise your hands.
None of you? None of you? How old are you guys? Everybody in the room is over 55.
Grandma Tilly, what did you have for breakfast this morning? Well, before I planted my
macadamias, I had a small two egg. Wrong. Wrong. I want all of you to go home and
I want you to eat sardines for breakfast tomorrow. All of you. What is it? What is
it Edna? I'm allergic to sardines. Do it anyways. Oh. Later that evening,
German 985 was arrested for having a fake gardener's license and yelling at old people
to eat things that they are allergic to. That was the P.T.? No, that wasn't P.T.
That's not a shadow. Look at that. Oh, that's a shadow. Bullshit. Give me a break.
German, you're dumb. It's a shadow. That's not a shadow. That's like bird feathers. Zoom
in on that. This is a shadow. I can see this clearly. These are like bird feathers.
It's all right. It looks fine. We use green carpet on the lines. I think we're almost done.
This is starting to look a little better. This is where I got all messed up yesterday.
Yesterday, I was just going like this. Um, what do I dig over here? What should I do back
here to the plant? No. So what's your vision? Where's the purple? Just hold on.
I have it all up here and I'm going to do it slow. We're going to be here for the next like
six to 12 hours. I'm going to go eat some sardines, marathon gardening, get to water
the grass. Probably not. All right. So let me, this is what my, this is my vision here.
My vision is to have, I think I want, don't do anything yet. I need to like, I need to
like block it out. I don't like these trees being in the way. I'm thinking they like
descending. Can I build surfaces? Can I like go up? Can I build like up paving slabs?
Do mini golf. No. Have a mini golf course. What a dumb house. What a stupid house.
You're the guy with the mini golf course in his house. Should there be a mini golf
in the house too? Should that just be one? No, you don't. This is what happened last time.
Last time I was doing this, it was like, oh, what about like a pizza oven? Yeah. Pizza oven.
Let's make the whole house a pizza oven. Let me fix this. Can we get, all right, but hold on.
Can we get like the book ending and like the show ending? Can I do like the, can I do like
the books first? I want, I want to do like a garden over here. They're going to be like
two. You're going to see like, can we do like a full metal alchemist here? There'll be
two shows. All right. Everyone's getting in my head. Don't let them get in your head.
Don't let them get in there. I'm in. I'm in. Let's start with this. Let's do,
let's get some concrete here. Let's take a look. Stair. Oh, let me just take a look. I need to
see how this works. Oh, dumb. Hold on. So I can, can I actually do it? All right. I want
to have like a, okay. So I can, that'll be for like another like mini golf hole. I can't
fucking believe I'm doing this. I don't know if I can go that high. Okay. Well,
let's have a staircase to build up into our neighbor's yard. What could this person possibly
be doing? I should put a hole in the wall over here. Oh, shit. Shit. Shit. Hold on. Hey,
Bob. What are you doing over there? What are you up to over there? Oh, nothing. Oh,
that's as far as it goes. It's not. I don't think I could, I actually, can you, why is that I have
to, how am I ever going to delete all this? The game is starting to not like what I'm doing
right now. See, it's really not liking this. Oh God. I think I'm getting into the skybox.
Hey Bob. Hey, what are you doing up there, Ted? Oh, you know, just trying to reach God.
That's all. Got a thing or two to say to him. Hey, why you have to see if you can get
tomorrow's lottery numbers. Okay, Bob. I can't, I can't go anymore. I'm not allowed. I'm at the
box. Should I just make Jenga? I cannot leave this inside. Leave what inside? No, I wait,
I think it thinks I'm in the house. Wait a minute. We got a new plan. Yeah, it thinks
I'm inside the house. So we have to go this way. Where's it hit? Right here. Okay. Ow.
Oh, what have I done? Am I standing on anything? Hey, it's art. Yeah, because see,
I gotta like change that so it's not going in the house. So much for the nice garden somebody
said. What you meant to say was the garden's gonna be up here. I'm making another house up
here. See, this is the front. There's gonna be a beautiful house up here. God damn it.
I'm just telling it. It's whatever. No, I need those. I need these. I need these. I need
this to get up there. Thank God. I can, oh, I want to see if this works. Just breaking
kind of every law. This is so dumb. Uh, hey, Bob, what is it, Ted? You got a rope?
Let's try and jump. No, fuck. Oh, I hate it. I can't, it can't be there. It can't be there.
It can't be there. I can't leave that. It's gonna fucking drive me crazy. All right. Now,
how do I get rid of this one? I can't go straight up because I have to jump over here.
I gotta delete this. Oh God. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. I think I can make it. All
right. So here's the plan. Shit. Oh, that's not good. I gotta, I gotta go up higher than this.
Wait, wait, hold on. This is not, I don't want to fuck this whole thing up. Just hold on.
Relax everybody. This will just take a second. God, fuck, no. I, I have to restart this
fucking whole thing. Is there any way it's, oh, there has to be a way I can delete this.
Why did I fucking do this? I can't reset it. No, no, no. I can do it. Oh, just get me
up there slow. I'm trying to go too fast. Am I bumping into something? I'm making like
these giant towers just to delete somebody. I saw one person said leave one and just fucked
up the whole thing. I can do it. I can do this. Just wait. I can do it. I'm just going to
start going this way now, make it clean so I can get rid of it. Okay. How far until
there's going to have to be a part two to that. I just wanted to make a garden
and somebody had to say mini golf and then like my like fucking clown meter went to a thousand.
I was doing fine. Okay. My money. Oh, no, not my money. Can I reach it? Oh, I'm not falling
again. If I fall again, I will have, I will reset it. I would have to. Okay. Slow. Thank
God. I have to think this through. Think it through. I've got to go up, but then how
do I delete these? Um, I, I think, hold on. Can I, that's not true. Can you, can I actually
do that? I'm afraid to do that. Hold on. Let me get back to where I was. I'm going
to get rid of this one. I can't reach that. Fuck. I don't, I have to delete this first.
I've got to one at a time, one thing at a time. Okay, hold on. So you, what you tell
me you, uh, here come, might be a loud noise, loud noise, potentially incoming,
turn your volume down. Nope. Doesn't do anything. I have to sell it. Okay. So the idea,
here's the idea. If I can build this this way, a couple more, make it clean. So I can,
I can actually walk on this. The cleaner this is, the better,
because then I can actually use it and walk backwards and delete it.
Almost there. Okay. I should now be able to do this. Not yet. I need to build this
one. Okay. Here we go. Come on. Use that brain. Okay. I did it. It's done. Now I
just have to, we're going to go down here and then know which one, what do I do first?
I've made, yeah, I've made this a puzzle game. I have to start over here. Don't
fall off. Falling off ruins. If I fall now, it's fucked the whole thing forever. My heart
should not be beating this fast. What's wrong with me? Why? All right. I'm doing it. I'm
going for it. I got it. I'm so paranoid because if I fall now, see, look at,
I fucked it up there. It's all right, everybody. Calm down. Oh, mini golf.
Oh, we're going to build stairs now. Just going to nowhere.
They're getting denser. I have to, oh fuck. It's like climbing Everest. I feel like I'm really
standing on these. I don't like this at all. I'm never doing this ever again. I'm never doing
this in this game ever again. Why would I ever do it in the first place? Now there is a lip.
Can I cross? Yep. Thank God. Oh, all right. That one's done. Now we have to go all the way up.
Part two. We have to go, now we have to go from here. All the way up and then all the way down.
As long as I do it right and I can sell them each one as I go down.
All right, here we are. Right here. Bang. Straight up. Don't fall off.
Don't make me laugh. If I fall off right now, you understand that the whole thing
was to get this one tower and if I fall off, I have to do it again because I made two now.
Fucking Jesus. And then I have to make three and then I have to make four.
Don't! Where am I? Oh no, where am I? What am I standing on? Okay, I made it. I made it. I
can't jump. Okay, here we go. Okay, I'm good. I did it. I actually did it. Oh, thank God.
Oh, thank goodness. That whole crisis can now be put behind us. Seriously. Oh, fuck. Easy.
Uh oh. Oh! I missed one? What are you talking about? I did not miss one. Wait, did I? Lie.
I will not have that. It's clean. There's not one up there. Oh man, that would have sucked. Okay,
what? What are we doing? All right, I got those in my vision. There's one near the tree. No,
there is not one near the tree. They're all gone. Build a roller coaster. What do you mean
the tree? Nobody sees it. It's a lie. All right, here we go. I want to make a garden here.
I'm gonna say, let's start from here. I want like a nice little patch right here coming out
to here. But the trees are in the way. Why can't I just get rid of the trees?
I don't want those trees. Make a roller coaster. No. All right, I'll have to incorporate
the trees. So, I want, I want like, God, I want. Anybody want some wine? I think I'm
gonna get a glass of wine. Just like one. I want to sip on it. I haven't had like a good
wine in a while. Yeah, go get, go get some wine. I'm gonna need your help here. I'm gonna need
your help in creating this garden. In the comment section, what do you think I should
put in the next episode? A tree? A moat? You decide. All right, I'm gonna go, let's just
have a glass of wine. I'll be right back. I'm just, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'll be less than,
I'll be less than 30 minutes, I promise. Time. All right, I'm good. Let's go. Two minutes? Five
minutes? Three minutes? How many minutes? 89 seconds? I feel like it was longer than that.
We want you to build a ferris wheel in time. In time. I got 399,000. So, wait, let's see.
I'm getting overwhelmed. I'm overwhelming myself. Slow. I'm not going to even look at
Chad for like another 25 streams. Okay, what did I want to do? 103, 104. Stop counting. I'm
breaking my own rule. Okay, I'm gonna test. Architecture. Oh, oh, round gazebo with a dome.
Let me see. I like that one. Hold on. I'm gonna have such a rich house. Cobblestone
circle stair up a little stairway up to the gazebo. Three level garden stair. I could have
just done these. Hmm. I don't know which one. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. How about this one?
Let's just see what it looks like. I can just sell it. That's too big. I think it's too big
to put anywhere. Maybe here? I need the mini one. But I can't put a garden in here.
This is bigger than the other one. No, that didn't say mini gazebo. It was minio gazebo,
not mini. I don't think maybe I don't even need one of these. What if it was like a
little entryway off of the okay. So hold on. Here we are. Here's the front door. We're gonna
get some nice stones here with a little another walkway that leads over here into the garden.
So it goes you go through here. You go through the metal detector to make sure like
and then you come to the garden. It's crooked. Yeah, I just I'm just placing it there.
Well, I didn't maybe didn't pick the right color. Well, not. Yeah, get out of here.
Just I'm gonna put it there for now. I need a front entryway here.
Entryway over this way leading into the garden here. There can be a nice garden here
right here for you to look at. And it starts right here like this.
I'm gonna I wanted the I want the purple scheme that I had. Why are you fail fishing
me? I put a I I put a the wooden stand. What's wrong with that? I placed it on the
ground. It's not going to be there permanently. No, you're getting out. You're getting in the way
of my vision. All right, so we're gonna have I want the purple, the red, the I want the purple
red and the and like kind of pink scale going up. Watch what I'm doing here.
Pay attention. Close fucking attention. Nice fence. Let's keep it that same color.
Looks awful. What if it looks awful? It doesn't look awful. I haven't even done
anything. No, it's gonna be it's gonna be to here. What are you guys on about?
What are you guys on right now? Why does this look wrong? That's better. The car guys,
the cars have to be able to go. Wait. Oh, fuck me. Okay, no. Um, no, this is still fine.
This is fine. This is this is the gate to the backyard. Everyone has a gate to the backyard.
Gate to the backyard and there's a nice walkway garden. Everyone that's talking all
this shit and typing all this shit in just under 12 to 15 hours, but would take a normal
person probably six. You're gonna eat those words. Why do you have an entrance in the middle
of your front yard? Because this is not the front yard. This is now the backyard.
This is the backyard. Here's the front yard. And then boom, backyard. Well, technically,
actually, it should be lined up here. I used to do this shit for money. Okay. I used to
move fences for money. I think I know what's going on. I knew it was wrong.
Is there like a snapping feature? Because I can't get a good look as I have to.
I'm gonna sneeze. There's nothing I can do. I'm gonna sneeze again. I can't press any buttons.
You don't like people sneezing. Just close it. Come on. Flush. Flush. Damn it. Don't
make me get the plunger. Toilet humor. That wasn't what? How is that like a toilet like
poo poo joke? I could have been flushing anything. God damn it. Can I add like a
section? Half fence? No. Fuck. No. Why? Why can I not extend this? I'm gonna have to
have a tree right here. This is a doggy entrance. No, this is the entrance to the back garden.
Just use hedges. There are hedges already here. That's gonna look fucking strange.
There's already like a line of bushes. Oh, just put another one right here.
No criminal will just like wedge his way into it. Is it straight? Let's give it a good look.
It's pretty, it's pretty straight. I cannot delete these bushes. No,
we'll put something there. We'll figure it out. All right. Anyways, so here,
bang. Nice little garden to start. In fact, I'm gonna do bingo. Bingo. This is gonna drive
me fucking crazy. It's gonna drive me crazy. Oh, God damn it. Just roll it out there.
I'm just gonna have it go all the way. Jermis, please stop. Please stop what?
What? Why? Just stop it. What do you want me to stop exactly?
The grass is crooked. Once it's all laid out there, you're not gonna know. That
would be different. I'm getting there. It's gonna look really nice. I promise.
If there's one thing I can promise you, is it will look good.
Pick up the trash first. I'm just going one at a time because if I,
just stop. Don't make promises you can't keep. I see you mean like over here.
Because I need to, I need to get it finished as I go. Yeah, I'm supposed to be in the other
corner. What situation should Jermapup be used in? That's at your discretion,
whatever you feel. Good, good, good. Come here. All right, that should be enough.
Let's get the edge here. I don't see any more on the mini-map in this corner, at least.
So I think we're good. Except it's behind the hedges though, which is,
how the hell would you even see that? There's no way you would see that shit.
I can't get it all in one pass, unfortunately. Come on, look at the mini-map. It's right here.
Did I get it? Yeah, I did. Come on, get it. Get it all. Oh, yes. Okay, there's one last
little speck right here. Got it in one more right here. All right, we're officially completely
clean on this right side. Now the only question is just getting the grass laid out here so I
can start building. Look at how much more of this is going to be so ridiculous.
I'm never going to stop streaming. Well, the internet has been pretty decent so far. So,
I mean, if I got internet, I ain't fucking turning it off. Congratulations, you mowed the
lawn. Be nicer. You're being very mean. I normally mowed the lawn. I picked up
3,000 pounds of trash and I'm rolling out new grass. That's a very mean thing to say.
See, it just happens sometimes. It just does it. There's so much Z-fighting on that fence.
What do you mean, Z-fighting? Z-fighting? What is a Z-fighting? Like anti-aliasing? Are
we getting a bunch of aliasing? What do you mean, Z-fighting? I don't think I can
get it all in one roll, but it's worth a try. I have no idea. I have no idea what
you're talking about. I don't know what Z-fighting is. Oh, the grass in the back?
Why would I know what Z-fighting means? It's like being in the doctor's office.
Doctor comes in. Do you know what this tool is? I don't know. Is it a stethoscope? No,
stupid. Why do you not know that? It's a hydroscope. What, are you stupid? You're
pretty dumb. Oh, okay. Ha, I'm an idiot. Right chat. He's got a fucking GoPro on.
He's like looking away while he's doing like an exam.
Everything seems fine. Doctor, my stomach is hurting. You're touching my neck. Oh,
sorry. I was looking at chat. What'd you come in for? That shit's gonna be real.
You think that's me fucking around? Give it like another 50 years.
What would his alert sounds be? A flatline. Hey, thank you, flatliners. Welcome to the
flatliners. Am I okay? Yeah, he comes in. Your leg hooked up. You're like just had
surgery. You're sitting there. All of a sudden the flatline comes on. Is something wrong?
What's happening? Thank you, bddoc21666. 25 months. Welcome to the flatlining patients.
Yeah, you just flatlined, didn't you? Oh, here, take these. This would help for the
pain and oh, thank you. Hey, whoa, 20, 32 months sub just came in from oh, hey, doc should poison
the patient. That's a funny username. But no, seriously, take those once every four hours.
This is not gonna work. What even is this room? What is this? Room 86 M2. All right,
hold on. This is the front door and then this is so this is a back slider and then
this is like another two car garage. No, the staircase is here. There's another back door.
Oh, this is a sub. Hey, thank you. Thank you. Room 86 M2 for the 12 months. Appreciate it. No,
that's not the garage. The garage is over here. It's a normal living room. Is it though?
Because you have two, three back entry ways to the it's kind of odd. I don't think that
one of these this would be normal. But this is seems like kind of redundant.
Somebody just gave $115. That's $115. That's Hayden clip fell for the 115 bucks.
That's a lot of money. There's no message here. You've just flatlined. Welcome. You've just
flatlined. I've just flatlined. No, no, idiot. I'm looking to chat. You're dumb.
It would be a scenario. Doctor's doing surgery. But first of all, before we get into this,
that's a fucking lot of money. There's no message here. You just gave me a ton of money.
Thank you, Hayden. That's a lot of fucking money. Thank you. All I can say is thanks.
That's more than I could ever ask anyone to ever give me in in dollars ever. What's
going on here? Why? Strange. But yeah, imagine the doctor's doing surgery. He's got the chat
open. And he's doing like, like a gallstone removal on somebody. All of a sudden, he like
misses one blind, blind, dude, I can't can you not see that? How can he be this stupid? He
can't see that other gallstone. What are you guys talking about? I got them all. Wow. Holy
shit. He's so bad. He like moves it moves the organ over here. I don't over this way.
Is he pretending? Is he pretending to be this bad? He's faking it. You know how people like
overreact and stuff like, whoa, jump scare. Actually overreacting twitch doctor. Yeah,
somebody comes in, they get like, oh, yeah, I feel like really strange recently. Like I was
outside in the woods outside the woods. Oh, yeah, what chat? I wonder what it could be.
Let's guess it. What should we do? I'm gonna put the clicks on the screen. What do you think
we should test them for? I think tick-borne tick-borne. I think so. Get some results back.
Yeah, it was tick. Yeah. Yeah. Tick-borne illness. We got it. Chat. We got it. Pogchamp.
No, no, no, it'd be something else. It'd be like, it'd be like doc champ. And it'd be
like him with a stethoscope on like having his mouth open like what? I mean, the small
look like cigars or no, they look like those little Debbie rolls. You know, those chocolate
rolls. What are they called? The swirls like the little Debbie rolls. Swiss rolls. There it is.
Yeah. No, not turd rolls. Swiss rolls. The doctor's been screaming for like fucking
eight hours straight in the middle of like fucking surgery. Oh, that's going to be it.
I think I'm just fucking beat, you know, I'll see you guys tomorrow. We'll pick it up for
where we left off. Just keep this guy in sedation. I'll just just save the game.
Yeah, I'll save it here. Fuck, to take some wine breaks. I don't think I can get over here.
Same problem from last time. There's going to be this one tiny little stupid patch that I
can't get. Oh, that's annoying. Oh, that's annoying. I hate that. Come on. Nope. Just
gravel. Yeah, I'll have to. Oh, that's, I hate it. No, this collision here for some
reason. Delete the trees? I can't. Oh, I fucking thought I had it. Oh well. Can't get them all.
But I can do this. Sell trees. Sell, you can't sell trees. Look, look, look, look, look, look.
See? Cheaty. Looks good. I mean, I know I did, I said I wasn't going to do this,
but I might as well. Jerma, please, I'm a fan. Concerned about your, I've been adamant,
in the past you've been adamant that you've been fine, but now it seems like you need
at least one glass each stream to get by. Is it us? Do we make the stream harder to get
through? Jesus Christ. Is it us? The last time I had a glass of wine on stream or alcohol
on stream was Nintendo Labo. That was like three and a half weeks ago. Almost a month ago.
More than that. Uh, so I, I don't know what stream you're talking about because that's
not this one. Hammer the tree? It don't work. Watch, I'll prove it. See? Told you. Told you.
Oh, Jebaited. Chat, you know, you don't understand. It doesn't work. I'm not going to use the,
the saw on his bone, on his leg. That's not going to work. It's not going to fix his,
uh, it's not going to fix his gallbladder. Do it, do it, do it. Oh my God. All right, fine.
See? Oh, did I just get Jebaited? Oh, he used drill on toe. He's still on the doctor bit.
Yeah, I'm kind of stuck on it. I just, things just keep popping into my brain. So I have to
just say them out loud. Right, wait, right there, right here. Oh, come on. What do you mean,
clear the path? There's nothing in the path. The path is already written. Come on. I'm the
best. I'm the best. I'm the best at what I do. I'm the best. I'm the best. I'm the best
at what I do. What is it that you do? Whatever it is I do. I mean, that's, come on. That's clear.
Look at how far away this is. Patch notes. Garden Flipper. 1.104. Remove collision around
trees. Come on. Come on. I'm just going to have to like go like this. I shouldn't have to
do it like this. Yeah, I'm done. I'm done. Yeah, I'm, no, I'm done. That's it. I
somehow made it worse. I know. And that's why I gave up. I'm going to do one right here.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, stutter step, stutter step, stutter step. Maybe I should just
clean it all up. But then I'm going to be overwhelmed. I'm going to look around and go,
fuck, this is too big. I'm just going to make a pizza oven as the house. All right. No,
it's clean enough for me to do what I want to do over here. Now I've got to get my vision
to unfold. Come on. Think about something. Okay, I got it. Get this out of the way.
We're going to go one step at a time. I need a entryway. First of all, we need a door here.
First of all, give me a door so I can look at this the way that I should look at it. No,
not yet. Cause I need to, I need, um, we're going to go stone, stone, stone, stone, stone.
Um, no, I won't put the surface. No, not the terrible tablet that fucking crashes every
five minutes. I want one of these. Hmm. What I want for a walk. Maybe take the gravel.
This is nice. Let's see what this looks like. I'm thinking the beige. I think there's a bigger
version of this. No, that looks like dog shit. I don't want that. I like this. How does it feel
to be employed by thousands of people? I mean, I'm a man of the people. Hmm. Orange,
orange isn't bad, but dark gray is not bad either. Let's see. Let me see what this looks
like. I need to get paving stones, painting stones block without a curve, paving stone.
That's going to get paving stone, paving stones. Here we go. All right. That looks all right.
Ooh, we can do a little trim too. Ooh, that is a really, really nice blue and white
paving stone. Hmm. That's a beautiful blue and white. What are you talking about? You see,
you see gold and where's the gold? I don't understand what you're talking about. Golden
and blue. What? I don't see that shit. What are you crazy? That's not the color of that dress.
Your brain is wired strangely. You guys don't know what I'm talking about. That is like,
this is the exact color scheme of that picture. What? That's like, this is the same exact
color scheme. Golden, white, blue. Yeah, come on. Did I see this joke on Facebook? I saw
the picture on Facebook. I like this. Jeez. Fucking rough crowd tonight. Rough crowd out
there. Be careful. They're all like drinking wine. Uh, should I go into the house with this?
Let's get a little bit more here. How's this wrong? It's not even wrong. Wrong. This is
actually very incorrect. If you were looking, no, this is not wrong because look, guys, guys,
guys, guys. If it is, if it's lined up perfectly here, then it won't be lined up
perfectly with the door. Uh-oh. Have we reached like the event horizon here? We're
at the event horizon. How does this look? That's not bad. No, no, no, no. What happened
there? Okay. Then we're going to go like this. Okay. What color do I want for gravel? Two-tone.
Look up, look up. We got like a, let me just see what this would look like.
I can't just put it. Why can I not do that? Well, I can. This is grandma's rug. It's
not grandma's rug. It doesn't look like, I know, we already made the fish tank reference,
the bottom of the ocean reference. I need to do rounded, I think. Do the other side.
Uneven laughing my ass off. Oh, get out of here. Get out of here with that. What do you mean
uneven? I got, it's, yeah, it is uneven. It's rocks. They're rocks. You can't have a straight
line with rocks. Uneven. Oh my God. It's uneven. Those crushed stones. Hey, better
than your house. I love that argument. Better than what you have. Better than what you did.
Dude, this stream like sucks. Oh, better than your stream. Have you streamed before?
Better than your stream. I don't, fuck you buddy. Actually, I want to go a little, a little more.
Hey dude, on the webcam, you had like something in your teeth. I did, like a bunch of asparagus
or shit. Yeah, better than your stream. Do you stream? You don't fucking know. No, I'm, okay.
I should probably do round. Hey dude, I, did you just like punch a guy in the face on stream
that didn't do anything? Okay. Yeah. Whatever. You don't stream. Where's your stream if it's
so easy? This is not good. What? I'm just starting. This is going to expand out a little.
Give me some, give me a day. Do you even stream? Do you even know what it's like?
The fucking Dreamcast sucks. Laughing my ass off. The Dreamcast, what was it? It was the Dreamcast
fucking sucks. Laughing my ass off. All right, I did fuck that one up. I'll give that one to
you. I'll give that one to you. Yeah, I fucked it up. Dad, what are you, okay. Thank, great. What, why?
Actually, hold on a second here. I think I can, I'm going to do some sculpting.
This is gonna, this is gonna be actually kind of cool. They didn't go out of the gate. Bad
illusions of sculpting. No, I'm gonna start out big here and we're gonna put a couple of
bushes in the shit. Just bear with me. I'm gonna do some sculpting. This is not ruined.
You guys have ever been to a house in Las Vegas? That shows. You guys, no, never mind.
I'm gonna, just watch. Wait, just give me a second. Guys, Rome wasn't built in a day.
It looks like the house is puking. I want that guy out of here for life. Comparing this house to
Rome. Yes, I am. If there's a problem with that, you don't even know it's like to stream.
Okay, I'll stop that one. Okay, hold on here. That's why I need enough to like
carve. Okay, here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
Dude, I can't help that it makes like the jagged Minecraft pixels. Okay,
you guys want perfection? Fine. It's not possible. Perfection doesn't exist.
Get that out of your head. Perfection doesn't exist, he says. Okay, now here I wanted to
go like this. All right, right here. Make it look a little more natural. I wish I could have the
like Photoshop. Why is this not Photoshop? I really need to, I need to get like here.
Okay, you see that line? Pull this in a little more. Okay, it's hard to do this when
you can't start from the edge. You have to be on top of it. This ain't like a brush tool in
Photoshop, guys. It's not gonna do what I want it to do. Yeah, yeah. Okay, same thing over here.
So it starts, curve begins here. I need a little more, but it goes like this.
It's got to be up a little more. I'm gonna put some bushes here. You can't just skip
all this shit. So this is way too much. I got a misleading line because the pixels
are being deleted. All right, look it. Don't tell me I did that wrong when I had a clear
line here that's being shaved as I step back. Right here. Right, almost there. I can,
I can fix this. Don't worry, just watch. I'm gonna have to add some more in here.
It's getting there. Look down and move backwards because it doesn't matter.
Because if I move backwards from here, like this, it's already, I'm lined up. And if I
move backwards from here, it's, there's no, it's not possible. Watch, I'll show you.
Like I'm gonna start right here. Like I can't, there's no way, unless I have like an
angle meter on my right hand side of my screen. I have no idea where I'm standing.
So right here, if I step back, like see, I've already moved to the left.
And I have to hold the mouse button down. So I, it's, it's going to move.
There's no clear way to make sure I'm like on the plane.
Plus CLA, it's like console aiming. No, you can't, it's no way. Like, no, it's not going to happen.
Use the mini map. How do I do plus and minus on the mini map? I just did? No, I didn't.
I did not just do that. It doesn't need to be perfect. Rome wasn't fucking perfect.
They did, they did, they took their fucking time and like Rome was like kind of sloppy.
Sloppy Rome was built in a few days. I need to add some here. There. I want it
to be circle though. I'm not, cause it starts like here. Why did you, why are you stopping here?
Why are you doing that? Why did you do that? Why didn't you just go forward?
I hate that. Close enough. That's close enough. I can add a little bit right here.
Got it. I did it. I did it. That's, that's good. Got it. Good. Okay. That's very close.
It's like this hard line right here does not match up exactly with here. I mean, it kind
of does. It's the same as when you started. No, it's not. It's a little different. What are you
drinking? All right. So now we're going to dual color here. No, we're not. We're not going to do
that. We're going to do bushes. I gotta go back to the garden setting. Let me do the bushes
first. It's dumb. Looks like shit. Incredibly ugly. Like I would never have that in my
house. Throw it in the trash. Is that all of them? No. Oh, that's a normie bush. How is that a
normie bush? This is the shit that's in fucking Las Vegas. Normie bush? Is it a, no, this is a
normie bush. Like one of these. The bush, a normie bush is a cloud that is colored green.
That's a normie bush. Oh, I like these. I'm gonna, I'm gonna move these around.
A couple of hostas. I feel like I want these to be a little bigger. I want something bigger
here. Let me see. I need like a little bit bigger, but I still want it to be like desert
Vegas style. Let's go down here. 0.5. I need like a couple of meters, I think. A palm tree.
No, that'd be weird in your house. I could get a big one. Wait, hold on. Ooh, not bad. Let's
see. No, that's not a big one. How about get these? No, this just looks like, this looks
just like Canadian leaves. Oh, this is not Canada. No, maybe one of these. Creeping dense.
These are trees. Dwarf shrub. No, these aren't bad. How big are these? I like that kind of
greenish. Um, could go like here and then here and then have like a big one right here and
a big one right here. These are the worst plants. All right, I need something bigger,
large. Maybe a ball bush. No. Ooh, yeah. Yep. Mm hmm. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. These are everywhere
out here. What color should it be? None of these. This is, this is good. Like kind of
that little off green kind of like baby shit color. One here and maybe like one here.
Let me just see. No, got to be a different color. I think I want a different color. I
think I want a green. I'll get a couple of flowers in here too. Yeah, that's a good idea.
I think I want to, I think I want to just straight up green though.
Let me see what that looks like. If it looks any better. Move these out of the way.
Oh man. Oh man. Man. Wait a minute here. Man. Wait. I'm not happy with the placement.
Symmetrical house. What? I like symmetry with plants. This is a tutorial on rails
arcade shooter house. What? What an insanely specific thing to say. Yeah. Can we make,
we'll make a little pond here. Everyone likes to just talk shit. That looks stupid. That looks
terrible. I think that's not even good. You should have this kind of plant and then you
should bury that one in the sand. What an ugly display. You should see my display. It's
marvelous. We unlocked a new voice. Nice. Power Ranger bad guy voice.
Oh, that's fucking hilarious. It's true. That is a hundred percent correct. After 10,000 years,
I'm free. It's time to conquer earth. Oh, I can plant it. These, these don't plant. Are
these just sitting in the, okay. Do I not plant them? I guess they don't get planted.
All right. Nice. Okay. Let's grab a flower or two, a nice desert flower because we're in
the desert. We're not. Do Zordon. Power Rangers, it's me Zordon. There it is. That's all you can,
that's all I can do. We can do like pots. That's cool. Matilda has landed on earth.
She's trying to take it over. I can't believe that. What was his name? Ooh,
I need a different color here though. No, this doesn't work. What idiot hired this
landscaper? This idiot did. I hired this idiot landscaper because I'm the idiot that
owns the idiot house. I can't place it. Oh, is it too, it's gotta be smaller. I need,
I want it right here. Can I make it, is there a little one round shaped pond fountain? Should
I just have like fucking fountains? Like up here, two fountains right when you walk in the
front door. Yeah, I like it. I want a pond here. Actually, no, why would you have a pond
at the front door? Should I just have a bunch of these? Like these things are cool. No, no,
no. I'm blowing my whole budget at the front door. I think that looks nice. We need a pond,
a little one. I want some flowers though. I need, um, stop the symmetry. What's wrong
with symmetry? Are they cactus? I don't think they're a cactus. No, unfortunately no cactus.
It's very old fashioned. There's something wrong with that. I think I want, I mean this looks
like shit. You'd think it looks like shit because of this. The house needs work. You know,
we'll go on inside out. There's a bug on me. No, there's not. Jesus Christ, I'm out of my
mind. I'm something wrong with my brain. I'm losing my mind. I've lost my brain. It's gone.
I don't have it anymore. My headphones touched me in the neck and I thought there was a
scorpion on me. I don't do any drugs. I, I'm, I'm like sober. I'm, I don't understand.
All right, I need to get rid of those because this just, this is bringing the whole thing down.
I don't like the color on the outside either. We're doing, I'm doing a Vegas house.
Vegas style. Can I not open the window from out here? To climb to the roof?
How am I supposed to remove these? How do I get there? This, I think this is impossible.
Uh, can I just reach them? Yeah, I can just reach them. Okay, so now there's no boarded up
windows. I mean, it's ugly in here and the, I gotta get the outside. I'm, I'm either painting
or I need, um, I need like that, like Adobe look. Let's see here. No, um, walls, right?
It's too dark. Plaster bucket. No, wood brick. I mean, it's, that's not like
wood though. You know what I mean? Like, no, that's not going to look right. Can I like,
no, I'm not sure I can do it. This is the closest thing, but this is going to look really
strange. Let me just see. Is he going to do what I asked for the past 50 minutes? What
am I doing? He's doing it. What, what are we talking about? He's doing it. No, that's not
going to look right. No, not 3d. It's gotta be that like beige kind of orange reds like this,
but that's not correct. This is a floor tile. What about maybe paint? Let me check the paint.
I'll try to paint it something. It's like this. Let me just see what happens when I do this.
Although there are a lot of houses in, in, in like apartments and complexes that are
this color. Let's see what this looks like. Wait a minute. That's no, uh, no, that's,
that's good. I say it's got to be, no, it's not a flesh house. The walls just look like
this stained. Well, I can't do the thing I want to do. How do you even have something on the
outside? Why ceramic tiles classic green? Why can't I just pick the color? Why just,
oh, we got a screen. Sorry. Only green wall panels. All we got is grandma paper and wood.
I need like outside walls plaster. No plaster is, is to fill holes. Use ceramic. Yeah. But
ceramic, these are, these are the floor. These are wall tiles. Yeah. They,
this maybe is close enough. Ceramic orange. I'm going to try it. Drink the plaster. Okay.
What's going to happen if I do that? Oh no, that's not good. I need a lighter than that.
I can't, well, I can advise it only this one color. This might be it. I think I got it.
No, Garfield house. No, this is, I got to get this right. This is important.
The tiles are too small. What about this one? Like a light. This could be it.
This could be close. Don't use ceramic on the exterior. Yeah. But I'm trying,
I'm trying to find the closest thing to the house that I'm trying to make.
It's either wood, ceramic or tile. Those are the only three materials that exist in this game.
I have a way, do I want or brick? Yeah. But the brick just looks,
this, this is like the pizza house again. I'm just going to lightly paint it,
but what is this? What are these? What tiles are these? Which ones are these? I don't,
I don't see these anywhere. What are these called? This is just a concrete slabs on the
side of the house. It's a paving slab. Can you even paint over concrete? I wish there was like
exterior walls, just brick. This is just this, these two colors of brick. It's hiding. No,
package of panels, package of panels. And it's all these like Dracula walls.
This is, I'm going to have to paint it. Yeah. This is a Dracula wall. That's the
inside of Dracula's coffin. So is that. So is this. And so is this. All right. Let's see.
Let's take a look at what these look like. This is, I think this is it.
This is it. And I don't, it doesn't matter. This is what I'm using. This is close enough.
Yeah. Close enough. House is not ruined. House is, it's going to look fine.
Just wait. I'm making my desert getaway. You're not in the desert. Yes, I am. There's no,
do you see any town symbols or anything here? I could be anywhere. I am where I choose to be.
This is my fantasy. I can fantasize about wherever I want to be. It's the digital
internet world. And I fantasize to be right in the same place that I currently am in right now.
Pretty boring. It's coming together. It's coming together. I can already, I can,
I know it. I already know what it looks like. Cheesecake flavored brick house.
You guys are judgmental. What does, I wonder what your exterior walls look like.
What does your house look like? And why is this here? Are these made out of like bleach?
Why is it grass dead? Oh, better than your house. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Look up stone. Uh, and no, it's too late. This is, this is what the house,
this is fine. Does it look nice? Once I get it all done, I think I need a stairway though
to do this because I am not like 30 feet tall. No, this is, it's going to look nice.
Don't crash. You're talking that you are 24, what? 24, what? 34, what do you mean?
First of all, get all these napkins out of the way. Paint the windowsills dark. Yeah,
the idea is I want to paint these like a, like a red, like a maroonish, like orange maroon.
Yeah, like rust red. Yeah, that sounds good. See, you get it. You get it. You
understand. You get like the, like, this is like a house in the desert. This is like
Vegas, Arizona. You get it. God, VIP that guy. Shower tiles. All right. Shuttle down.
Shuttle down. That in Arizona, where boomers go to retire and where sick fucking awesome
dudes in their thirties go and have like a blast and have like tons of cool things to do and like
cool fun days. Get rid of these fucking square hot dogs. I can't believe you guys are making
fun of this and you wanted me to have the hot dog house. Okay. Well, just make sure we're
clear on that. Pick that one. Pick that one. The hot dog house, like the grilled hot dog.
Fine. Is it true that Americans eat whole butter bars as a snack?
Um, I think I can answer this. I'm American here. I don't know what that is. What's a butter bar?
I don't know what that is. I love how it's something I'm supposed to be eating as a snack
and I've never heard of it before. Sorry. Is it a sardine? Is it I eat? Well, actually like
no, like not fucking around. What is it? It's a stick of butter. I've never heard of that.
A stick of butter. It's a bar of butter. I feel like this is some fantasy world made-up
thing. I've never come across anyone in my entire life that's ever eaten a bar of a stick of butter
for a snack. No fucking way. No way. I, yeah, no way. I agree. Okay. Yeah. I'm gonna paint this.
Can I, can I paint these? I hope I can. Otherwise this is a pain in the ass. Okay. Looks
good. The stray window is driving me crazy. Oh yeah. That is really weird. Yeah. This,
but I also said this is weird but this is not weird. The stray window right there but like
the back door and then the other back door. Two huge sliders that are right here. That's not
strange and a window. What? That's not weird. This is not the garage. Garage to the backyard.
No, the garage is right there. I'm gonna make that look real nice too. I'm telling you, this
is a whole entire project and it's gonna look good. It's gonna look good and I want comparison
photos. I, hopefully somebody took them. I didn't. Just get a ladder. They don't exist in this
video game. Don't cut that. Gotta get up here. Sometimes you gotta do the tedious work.
I'm not selling this house by the way. This is mine. Somebody wants to come take this from
me? You'll have to take it from my cold, unused hands. I gotta go up. I gotta bring one
of these with me. What the fuck? Oh. I was like, why is it bleached? No pictures? No,
there's no pictures. I'm currently putting up new exterior walls. Sorry, there's no
paintings on the wall yet. I'm not selling. Who's that person? I'm not selling to that person.
Even if they're the top bidder. Okay. Kind of be impossible, isn't it? I actually am gonna
have to build those stair things. Yeah, I am. I'm not gonna be looking at the last two or three.
First of all, let me do this. Let's get a good rust color here. Copper coin. We'll try it.
And then we'll also try biscuit. No, biscuit's too light. Cream. Raspberry. It's probably
gonna be nice. The copper coin. Try pale pink. This is kind of like rust. Let's see. Let's
see what this looks like out here. Oh no, that's not good. I can't paint these. Fuck.
You can't do new windows either. There's no such thing. I can't like replace them.
No. No, why? No, this does look bad because of the gray. Ah, fuck. If I could do a rust or a
red, like a maroon, it would look so much better. Oh well. Too late. I'm just gonna have to do it.
That's just the way it is. I can't paint these windows out here. No. That's unfortunate. Well,
let's go ahead and do stairs so I can at least finish it. Why do I have to do this?
Here we go again. No, I didn't even bring the damn things up here. How am I gonna do this?
Oh, come on. I'm gonna do more ladder, ladder, ladder, ladder.
This ladder's tiny. Gym ladder. That's not gonna work. This is so much higher.
A scaffolding? I don't. No, I don't. What? Oh my god. You gotta be kidding me. I still need to...
All right, give me the damn thing. Oh, what an eyesore. All right, I'm gonna tell you what I
would do if this is my house. Do you see? I would just take one of these panels and flip
it horizontal and cover the whole thing. Like, does it really matter? Bricks would be the wrong
way. The customer wouldn't even know. I would get away with that in a heartbeat.
What's going on up there? It looks like the bricks are the other way.
No, that's just the sun. Reflection from the sun. Is it an optical illusion?
That'd be a check, please. That's a check. I take checks only.
Actually, I'm just kidding. I take cash only. All right. Well, I can't do the thing I
wanted to do. What happened here? Is the grass growing through the rocks?
Why is that happening? What is going on here? There's nothing even there. All right, let's do
this. Can I just get bricks? I don't think I can do brick. I can... No, I can't.
Maybe this. That's kind of huge though. No, that's absurd. Let's see. Like,
stone. These ones. Herringbone. Oh, wait a minute. Okay, hold on. Nice. Hold on. No,
that's got to be a different color. They're huge, too. They're really big. Like, too big.
What we got in colors in here? These are just gold bars. No, that's very out of place.
That's better, but... Which way should it be facing? I would rent. Use bricks? There are
no bricks. I can't lay bricks down. It's only these. But look, it's like a stack of them.
That doesn't work. Look at this stuff. I can make it do stones. I can do this. This doesn't
look terrible. I feel like I should flip that. That just looks like this. Let me just see.
This needs to be a different color, then. That actually doesn't look bad. I don't hate this.
That doesn't look bad. Hold on here. This looks okay. Was it like this? A little bit over the edge?
Was it in a little bit more? That's not matching up. That's not matching up. I'm going to freak
out. I'm going to freak out. It's not matching up. It needs to be in a little more. It needs
to come in like a half an inch. Now, what do I do here? I can't just do that again. It'll
look awkward, won't it? No, I can't do this trick more than once. A couple of stones. Maybe
some rocks? Maybe some bigger stones? Like a plant bed, maybe? Let's see what looks like with
rocks. Okay, rock. No, I don't. What are you doing? Big stones? Stepping stone? Chopped? No.
Stepping stone? Chopped? Small? This is kind of an erratic pattern. How big is it? Oh,
bigger than ice crystals. Let's see what this looks like. Smaller and a little darker. Can
I make them? How about this one? Hold on. Wait. Hold on. This is important. Should I do
them spread out or should I have them kind of right in the line? No, that's ugly. I think I
need more stone. I need like something. I need pebble? Wait a minute. Why are these different
colors? Just put rocks all over the whole yard? I need like a flower bed. No, no, no.
Everybody, I got it. I'm going to just make a line of flowers. I wish this was even 20%
smaller. Poo. I think I can just hide it with a couple of little bushes. Twix bar. You guys,
it's so judgmental. Now I'm going to do some small bushes. A line of small bushes.
How big are these? Some orange? That might not look terrible. These are huge though.
I'll put one of these. Yeah, there are no cactuses in the game, unfortunately.
They do not exist. When these are in the ground. No, they need to be smaller. They're
too overbearing. I think I'm just going to say, fuck it. Here we go. Got it. Along the whole
thing. Let's just see how these look at first. Hold on. All right. Yeah, I'll take care of the
corner. I just want to make sure this looks all right. Yeah, this will be all right. Looks
better than the rocks. Yeah, it does. Yeah, that looks fine. No, that's bright enough here.
Leave the holes and see if anything else gets planted. Like, wow, my time off. It's like,
I'll see you later. I'm going to see what happens. I think I know. All right. And then
we're going to do one big bush here. One big bush here. Different bushes though. So the
symmetrical people that don't like the symmetrical stuff. You know, they'll have some say in this.
Spray hose and hose. Ah, we already did that yesterday. We did that joke already.
Just get rid of the shitty gravel. I like the gravel. I like the stone. I like it.
Once there's a bush over here and a bush over there, it'll look a lot nicer. I like it.
I like, um, stone. You don't like stone?
Raisins. Yeah, yeah, yeah. That was for the guy that said to do that. All right. Hey,
look at that. We need something little right there. Something little right here.
Something big. Something big. And then we'll let the front door will be done. And we only
have like another fucking entire five acres to do. Okay. I'm going something big, large,
very large. Oh, fuck. Yeah. Oh, fucking hell. Yeah. I always did it. Oh, fucking hell. Yeah.
Look, we got up. We got down. It looks fucking dumb. LOL.
All right. Thanks. I think it looks cool. I'm not even done. You think I'm done.
I'm not even close to being done. Now we're going to get some more, uh, kind of like,
like almost pinkish, like, like in some way in between orange and, um, and red, right here,
right here, right here, right here. Let's go plants.
I wish I could change the color. Oh, I think so. Oh, I think so. These are the same color
of these. Damn it. Nevermind. Wait a minute. Oh no. Should I? Is this, is this too much?
This might be too much. This is too much. Too much. Is that too much? Too much. Yeah,
it is. Oh, you dickhead. Why? Now something has to go there. I'm almost done. Just need
little flower. Just something small. Something little. Something that really just brings it
all together. Like one of these. Get in there. Come on. Get right in there.
I might not even need it. I might not need it. I think I'm done with the front here.
I need to put something a little over there. Uh, what do I? I don't, I have no idea. These,
I don't, I don't know. I don't know what these are. Now that's too,
wait, hold on. I just got lost for a second. Hold on. Tree. Spherical tree. Plum tree.
Maybe one big tree on the right over here. Just a huge tree. A very big one. Like one
of these huge ones. Oh, that's enormous. No, that's a, that's a good giant pineapple in my house.
Small. It's got to be smaller than that. Here we go. That's better. Right here? That dumb tree
wasn't there. Start a riot. Our palm tree isn't here. Hey, relax. You already have one. No,
we need to have like a walkway going over here to the right. Yeah, there's nothing over here.
There's going to be like the walkway. Um, I don't know. No, this would be like a little,
little pool or something. I don't know. How about a rich person fountain? Something ridiculous,
like right here. A projector to the house. Outdoor cinema screen. A fire pit. That's go,
that goes in the back. No, Jeremy. No, that goes in the back. I'm sorry. Okay. Front,
I thought it was front yard. No, it's backyard. Okay. How about, um, playground,
but I don't have any kids. Swing center is very homey, but no, no kids. Recreation,
accessories, fire pits, hammocks, maybe. Back it up. Decorations. Japanese lantern.
Which do you prefer? On the outside or on right on the, on the inside or in the gravel here?
Number one, number two or number three? That'll give you a good view. I'm seeing a lot of
threes. That's all right. Looks like it's going to be three. How many, how many steps?
Like here? One, two, three, four, five or four? You're going to want to fucking come to my
house. Uneven, uneven. Fuck. You don't want to come to my smelly house? There's nothing in here
yet. It doesn't, how could you tell it smells like anything? Come on game. What are you doing?
Why can I not play? Am I standing on it? Huh? Straight down. There we go. I can just do it
like that. Everyone's going to want to come to my house. I can already just see the invitations
I send out. BYOB. God damn it. This is wrong. Um, it's not wrong. Which one of these is wrong?
This one? That's that one. It's these two. How do I turn them on? Yeah. Oh, I'm so fucking happy.
I actually don't mind this, but it needs to move. This, this tree right here is really
fucking it all up. You know what I mean? This doesn't look right because of the tree.
It looks better. Your front lawn is going to have so many bugs. Unfortunately, I have to
patch that up. So the thing is you're missing pizza ovens. This is the one, right? No,
it's bigger stone. Wait, that is the big one. Why does this look so odd? Oh, there we go.
We're good. Any of the little patches I need to do? Maybe come out a little too,
just like to make it so it's more natural here. Right on the edge. Maybe have this
come out here a little more. Like here and then go out and around. Hear me out.
I fucked it up. Saved it. No, I didn't. Fuck. Can I crouch? No, why? Oh, god damn it. Well,
whatever. At least I can clean it up now. That looks natural now. Yeah, and then I
can just put that one here and hide the bullshit that I just did. What was the name
of this thing? What are these called? I forget. Go back up into the sky. That was funny.
What were those things called? These? What were they? No, I have like a palm tree garden in the
back. Anyone remember what those were called? What were those called? You had to plant them,
right? What were those things called? Not these. I think it was at the top. I think
I had it already. Spring? Damn it. What the hell are these called? Spreading bush?
You got it. I think that's the one, right? Yeah, this is correct. Let's get this in a good spot,
though. I'm thinking like right here. There. These are like not even. There's like a little
too much space here. This is a retirement drug den. That's not the same thing. That's not
even the same bush. That is not correct. And it looks very close. Is it? Is that the same
thing? No, this one's not the same thing. This is called Acer palmatum. Is there another color?
It is this one. All right. Now that we have the front front pretty much done,
I would call this is pretty close to like nice garden, dude. I need something right here,
though. Like nice job, man, is what I would say to the person that made this if they were
in the ninth grade. Columns? Pond. That would be good, yeah. One of these ones. Let's make it
a good color. Which way? Facing how? Facing around the tree, I think. That would be kind
of nice, right? And maybe put something next to it. It's a hot tub. This is not a hot tub.
I think right up here against this tree. And if you don't like it, you can just go watch
another stream. You know what I'm saying? How long is it going to take to dig? All right,
then. Making a skate park? Oh, you actually have to fill it with water? I thought it was rain. The
pond was mounted and filled. Just kidding. All right. Now this is bad because this needs to be
like bigger. There needs to be something around it. This is how it starts. Now I know what
gardening is like. Now the tree fucked it all up. It needs to be bigger. I'm going to do
the big one. Dude, if that fucking tree wasn't here. If that tree wasn't here, this is
perfect. I can go this way. Yeah, but I don't want to put it here, though. People will drive
by and throw cigarette butts in here. You know how many baseballs are going to go in here?
It can't be this close. No, it's got to be the smaller ones. Um, there's this one,
though. What does this one look like? This one's okay. It's cool looking. Yeah.
Shit. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Do not go into here. Remove, please. Please
remove. Cancel. Cancel, please. I just want something to like be right here or something.
Hold on. How's that look? Could put something right here. Let me just see what it looks like.
Yeah, I can't delete the tree. It's there forever. That's not bad. Wait a second. Wait
a minute. Oh, this is just, hold on. Can I? Can you connect them? No, you can't connect
them. It's going to be right here. I'll put like another fucking tree or bush over here.
That's okay. I'm okay with that. We'll put like a little something. I need like enough
space to walk this way though. That is enough room. All right. Um, what do I, what goes over
here? How about a big, huge pond like right here? No, that's too much. That's even more pond than
house. Uh, do, do more pond. A huge fountain. Paris fountain. I'm going to put a couple of
little shrubs like here and like one here and here. Um, can we get like a preliminary
screenshot here? Just real quick. That looks pretty nice. Something nice. Something cool.
Something interesting. Something daring. A giant gnome. I'll put him here. He belongs over here
in the pool, in the water. There's a little spot back here. That's cute right here. Yeah,
I think so. Sculptures. Wait a minute. You can sit on the rocks. You can sit down on the
rock. Just chill. Hold on. Move this one a little bit over here. Put something right in the middle.
Got a little seat rock. What do you mean no one will do that? You wouldn't sit on that?
They're drinking out of the pond. Put a god damn tire swing. Hold on. By the way,
half the shit's gonna get stolen. Someone's gonna walk up here and just fucking take these.
That's why I would never have like something like this. Someone would just reach over
the fence and take it and walk away. Need to get a juped up security system. This is so
cute. Look at how nice this looks. Look at that. Don't take a picture yet.
That doesn't look good. That was like your mother came over to give her a tour of your new place
and everything looks so nice and pretty and you cleaned up but for some reason something,
a coin drops on the ground and it rolls underneath the couch and you have the panic
attack where she's gonna look under the couch and she's like oh let me get that coin. No,
don't. I'll get it and you try to race her to get the coin. Everything's in slow motion
and she finds all the dirt that you sweep under the couch because you don't feel like
putting it in the trash and all the porn DVDs that you sweep under the couch.
I could make a whole D&D game. Pour out the water. Like the birds are fine. Can I paint
them? I think the front yard is done. I do. Maybe we'll come back and clean it up a little bit.
Wait, most importantly, come on. Looks like a welcome mat. This is the worst game on Steam.
I think so. All right. Furniture. Wait a minute. Just a mat. Wait. Look at these.
Come on. You tell me I'm not gonna have these too. That's in the way. Something's
gonna be like right here. It's looking a little too busy. Is it? You think so? Yeah,
you know, it is getting a little busy. It's getting busy. It's getting a little too busy.
You are right. Yeah, this is getting busy. This is getting very busy. Yeah,
this is becoming, this is becoming a hotel lobby busy. All right. Yeah, hold on.
Too many rocks. I like them. I like them. I really do. I really do like these. I like
them a lot. Did I move, did I fuck it up by moving that? Maybe. No, put it back. No, no.
Doesn't work. No, you can sit over here. So what do we got on this side? Oh, Jesus. I don't want to
look at that. All my fucking socks and my dirt and my porn DVDs. No, I only want my mother to
see the hotel lobby. It's a dump back there. Yeah, right now it is. Look at how much work
there is to do. The stream's never gonna turn off. It's all right, guys. I, I ate sardines
today. They actually get, they literally, literally give you superpowers. They think I'm
making that up. That's not a joke. I'm not making a joke. They actually give you superpowers. It's
real. Start eating them. I'm serious. Mole? No, that's not a mole. Where's the mole? Is these
mole tracks? All mole mounds are gone. Mole's gone. Mole's gone. We're fine. It is so easy
to eat too. I would take a sardine sponsorship. I probably would. The only sponsorship you
would ever see on this channel would be for like sardine cans. Ever have them on crackers?
I have not. I've had it on toast though. Wow, that's what a great idea. I can't wait to do that
tomorrow. Streamer ate sardines once and is now hooked for life. Like today. They give you
superpowers. I had them today. What a placebo effect. I could do anything. I think I could,
I think I could probably fly. Do not get up there. No, I had sardines today, man. I
think I can do it. You versus the guy she told you not to care about. He's losing it. It was
already gone before you got here. Don't worry. What else? There's a lot of weeds over here.
It's hard to get around these trees. Speaking of trees, why can I sell these ones but I
can't get rid of the huge annoying ones that are all over the place in the ground? Well,
it's almost clean and mowed almost. Do a sardine review? I already did. I've been doing it every
hour. I've already done that. Let's make this side of a house a swamp. What brand do I get?
The one with the guy that looks like Dr. Roker. Yes, somebody did say that. Why would
I even say that? We're 100% clean as of right... No, not yet. Hold on. Hold that
thought. You have to eat a sardine and show your superpowers. Are these dog bowls considered...
Is this considered dirty? I know. You just deleted the dog house. The dog house.
What about the dog? Don't worry. I knew it. I told you. I'm just going to put down
grass here and put the dog park back. I knew that was going to happen. You can't ever
delete a dog house on stream. Yes. Yeah, I think so. I do. It needs a door. That's what's missing.
White? Why is this so fat? This doesn't look right. Why is this too big? Hey, and then that...
Hold on. It's not done yet. Stop screaming at me. It's not done. I can't do that.
Now it's a home. Except for the left, back, and right side of the house.
What am I gonna do over here? I gotta have something fun over here. Definitely gonna have
like a barbecue section. Do a roller coaster. Make the dog park. I could have a little dog
park over here. Yeah, I'll have like a little separate dog place. Hold on. There's definitely
trash everywhere in here. Is there a car? The house comes with a car. I just want a car
in here. They got a pool table? They got a ball pit. That's too small. All right. One step at a
time. I need to do the rest of the paneling in the house. I gotta fix this dumb, stupid idea
that I had and I should be reprimanded for it. What the hell was this called? It was a panel.
We must riot for a ball pit. You want me to put a ball pit in the garage? Now I know the
scaffold. I know, I know. I'm just gonna do the bottom first. This doesn't look right. Yeah,
it's the same one. This place isn't even dirty. I bet the outside was, but thankfully the inside
is nice. We can do some decorating. We can have, look, the outside, I'll make a separate
little circus area. Everything's gonna be fine. I'm telling you, this is the big house. This
is the one to go all in. I went all in. This stream will not stop until it's all done.
All in. I, I'm going all in at the fucking table, dude. I've got 36 bucks at that table.
All in. Everybody at the table is gonna be like, oh that's a lot. What the hell is he thinking?
You and your gambling fantasies. You know, I mean, dude, I was thinking,
I'm thinking I'm getting a tat. Seven on one eyelid, seven on the other eyelid,
and seven on the top of my tongue. So I'll just close my eyes, stick my tongue out and
be like, ding, ding, ding, motherfucker. I mean, the efficiency is just off the fucking charts
right now. You can tell that there was some type of fish based nutrients that he took today.
This is fucking up the grass though. That's annoying.
Tiles look weird. You should do brick or stucco. Um, I think it may be far too late
to change this now. These aren't tiles. They're panels. They're wall panels.
Are these tiles in this wall panel? These aren't bathroom tiles. Yeah, just these are pine panels.
Yeah, this is fine. I'm not doing this again. This is like a long time. It takes a while to
do this. Damn it. I know people are gonna give me shit for doing the double dare technique,
and it's like running back and forth, placing, run back over here, get some more milk,
run over here, put it inside their hat with the eggs. I know, but I'm just trying to get
this done. Still on this house. I'll be on this house until the stream turns off. That is a fact.
I mean, that is 100% truth, but it's going to be the greatest thing I've ever done in this game.
It's going to be really well done. We're not going to put like a Best Buy in here.
It's going to be a beautiful, fantastic, actually made house with a wonderful garden,
wonderful backyard play area, patio with a barbecue, a small circus, not a big one,
a small circus, a dog park, and maybe a gym. It's going to be a fun, it's going to be a regular
just house. All right, slow down. I'm going too fast. Still going to make a hot topic?
No, not this time. Okay, almost getting there. Phew! It's hard work. It's hard work pretending
to do hard work. Don't you guys think? Now we need this scaffolding after this,
and it could be the other side too. This house is too big. How many rooms are in this house?
Look at this. What is this all for? Why is there brick over here? Okay, so this,
what is this supposed to be? What is this room? Here's the front door. Got a nice garden,
but you know, okay, front door, the closet, the den, the closet where you hang your coats
and shoe rack or I don't know. And then this looks like it could just be a big living room.
Now what is this? Second weird brick room. This is not a bedroom. Bathroom? What would
he, what the hell would, why would there be brick? All right, up here. This house sucks.
There's no rooms. It's just, there's two brick rooms. I'm going to have to build out some
bedrooms. You build the room, smart guy. Yeah, but this, what, look at the weird layout here.
Everybody has a balcony? Up the stairs, balcony. Whose balcony is this? Just a balcony. And then
there's another balcony. You got too many balconies. I want to in fact remove this balcony
and turn it into a circus. That's more normal than this. Now front balconies, I, no, I don't
think so. No front balcony. Don't think so. No, no, no, no, no, no. This is how you get sniped in
Hitman. I, nope. We can make it work. I'll make it work. Don't worry. Yeah, that's where like the
target comes and smokes a cigarette for 15 seconds and that's your opportunity. All right,
what were we doing over here? Your power's been off for two hours. That's not good.
Oh, let's get a reveal. Hold on. I need to get a big reveal. Somebody just came back after
two hours. They weren't here. You ready for this? Okay. That one person that's here, you
ready? They just came back. Take a look at this. You remember what it looked like before,
before you left. Take a look at it now. And it's not even done. There's still much to be done.
Ah, I love it. All right, for real, I left when you were doing the Jenga thing. I came back and
it looks great. See? Yeah, thank you. Yes. Ah, welcome back. Hopefully the power situation.
So, under control. Yeah, we're gonna do something fun over here. We're gonna do like
a circus maybe. That's a paid actor. We should build something. Build Jenga. Wait a minute.
Is there actual drop in the game? No, they're not the same pieces. They can't fit. It has
to be two. It's not real Jenga. Unless there's three. Yeah, sorry guys. It's not real. It'll
never be real. Well, let's just see what happens. Well, there is no drop. What am
I talking about? One floated in the air for like 35 minutes. How do you play Jenga with
two rows? Yeah, you don't. That's what I'm saying. The panels can drop. Does it reach?
Can't stack them though. I don't think they can be stacked on top of each other.
No, sorry. Theory busted. Paint the top half of the house. That would look pretty odd.
Two-toned house. How's the um, how's the internet been? Looks like I haven't
dropped very many frames. I mean, I still have, but I've dropped like 3,500? Seems
like it's all right. At least for today. Maybe um, maybe it's more manageable now that we have the
new DNS and new static IP. Well, that would be really swell if that were the case.
No, I said it. Now it's gonna happen. I know, right? All right. Uh, I need
to put this away. I need a scaffolding. Let me buy a few of these. No, let's just get it.
Let's just get this actually ready to be done in one go. Don't paint the top half. Wait,
why do you think I'm gonna paint the top half? Just because somebody in chat said that?
What? I'm not gonna paint the top half. I do that a lot. Not today. Today's different.
I need more of these panels. No. Please fall. If there's no fall damage though,
so it wouldn't matter. I could fall right now and we could just like laugh hysterically
about me falling. Wouldn't really do anything. I'm sorry. I know that could be disappointing.
There's no funny health meter where I could die and, you know what I mean? I know everybody's
expecting it to happen, but it's not gonna do it. Sorry. Wait, there's more here? Why can
I not? I'm not close enough to get these. That's not possible, man. Come on. Well,
I have to move the scaffolding again. I mean, this is just like doing the
grass. It's tedious, but once you do it, it's over. And you end up in a magazine. Gardener Weekly.
Come on. That's such bullshit. Just move. Is it these things in the way? All right. Dude,
how the fuck? That's even further away. I'm just gonna have to jump. Did I not get it?
Okay. Cool. Cool. Very cool. Nice. Check around for bald spots. We have a few bald spots over here
that I'm gonna take care of. So I just sit back and relax while I take care of these walls.
And go. Come on, fill up that bucket. Come on, Anderson family. Okay, that's it. How many
panels did you get up? God damn it. There's an entire side of the fucking house.
I just got insane deja vu right now. Right here. Why? Did I miss one up here? No, I got it. I'm good.
Is this though? Oh, that was gonna be just barely a perfect exact number. And it wasn't. Oh,
this is gonna take so long. I can do that when I go upstairs. I gotta bring this over here.
Too much paneling. I'm gonna do the inside and the lawn on the house. Oh, I'm prepared.
I am very prepared for it. Wake up. Wake up. Painting it so much quicker is sandstone
cocky and just roll all of that shit on. Yeah, but it would look pretty ugly. It would be that
one weird solid color. It would just look like a cartoon house. This won't be much longer.
See, right now some of you guys are like, oh, we're just chilling out? No. Okay. All right.
Some of you guys got like dinner. Like eating right now. So we have plenty of time. I had
dinner already. What am I gonna do? What am I gonna do for dinner? That's a really,
really interesting question. It's gotta be something I can eat fast because I plan on
going for a lot longer than this. I need one more panel. Are you kidding me? Grilled cheese.
That doesn't sound bad. Bingo. Still have to do over there, but I do have the scaffolding
here I can bring over. All right. Looks all right. What have we got? Two? I had two. How
I just like rage bought all these. Grilled cheese and tomato soup. That sounds pretty easy.
Sounds pretty quick too. I'm not sure we have that here though.
Need to go to the grocery store. It's been a while. Pick up some essentials like cheese
and tomato soup. All essential things to have in your household. Got it. All right. Let's do
this too. Can I reach from here? No, I can't. How am I doing on money? Oh yeah, that's right. I
bought and sold this stupid home alone house for like $600,000. All right. What do you guys think
is the fastest way to make $500,000? Legally. Legally. The lottery? I said fastest. You could
play the lottery for like 50 years and not win. Like what is a guaranteed way to make
$500,000 in like a year? If anybody knew that everybody would just do it. Play Fortnite. Be a
Fortnite player? Is it? It's not that easy. Is it? There's a lot of people that play Fortnite
and some a lot of them aren't like 500,000 dares. There's a lot of people that play that
game. Get out of the way. I'm just gonna jump. Write an AI. Like code an AI. Work a $50,000 a
year job, but 10 times. Like so to have $10,000, $50,000 a year jobs at the same time. Okay.
Work a $500,000 a year job with an IQ thing. Win the German rumble 5,600 times. I don't do
that many in a year though. Coming together. Okay. So you could work for a year and get
$50,000. Go to the casino and put it on red 10 times. No, double it up so you get $100,000
and then put it on black $200,000. Put it on black $400,000. Put it on red $800,000.
And then you leave. You get your $400,000. Ask $500,000 people for $1 and lose everything.
Now do not do that. That is very bad advice. Get good at Jeopardy. Now that's a good idea.
That's thinking with your head. Get really good at a game show and then go win the game show.
Write a Star Wars movie, but you have to get hired to do the Star Wars movie. You don't
have to get hired to... there's $500,000 right there. Uh, no, but seriously that was 50 bucks.
5,000 vids from VoidSpace123. Thank you VoidSpace. And VoidSpace says,
Hey Jeremy, just wanted to give some appreciation for all you've done for me
over the years. If in times of your streams the only thing keeping me going and words cannot
describe how you've impacted me positively. Love you, man. Keep doing what you're doing.
I'm gonna keep doing it. Thank you so much for the 50 fucking dollars and
the incredibly kind message. Thank you, VoidSpace. I need more of these. 50 bucks is a
lot of money. It is to give somebody on the internet. So, and if I can impact you
positively, that's great. I'm very glad I do. I would hate to negatively impact somebody,
so I'm glad to hear that. Oh no, why is this happening? Okay, I just have to squeeze it in.
Almost done with the paneling. Ah, it's so close to not having to do it anymore. I'm so
happy. Ah, that's it, right? All right, now redo it. I don't like the color, Jeremy.
Let's just make sure. Is this really not a bit? No. What, you thought the whole,
this whole thing was a joke? Uh, no. Wait, wait, wait. Is it the family guy house?
It is not the family guy. Let me look this up. It's not. Family guy, that family guy house
is white. It is. The roof is also the same. Should I make a red door? No,
I don't want to have a family guy house. No. You can't even have a red door. There is no
red door. This is a refrigerator. Fucking family guy house. Why? You can change the door color?
You can? Internal door. Front door. You can't change the color. Paint the door. You can
paint the door? No, you can't. You can't paint the door. Got him. Yeah, I mean,
you can't paint the door. All right, I can't believe it's a family guy house.
And even the top is like green, isn't it? I think the top is this weird
off green kind of gray. I can't, I, I can't even look at the house now.
I seriously can't look at it. It's all right. No, no mini golf. I'm sticking through this. I
don't care if I have the family guy. Fuck. I hate this. No. Second floor. I know I'm going
out there. I'm going out there to finish my family guy house. Fuck. Whatever. Oh, sorry.
It's my other balcony. It's my other balcony I have on the other side.
We have three balconies. Hey Peter, do you remember the time that we built that house?
Yeah, it's my house, Joe. And this is the whole episode. Hey Quagmire, can you pull the
car in the garage? Okay. Sure thing. I do that all the time. Oh, you're all about sex, aren't you
Quagmire? This is like kind of cringe. No, it wasn't shut up. What are you talking about?
No, it wasn't shut up. What are you talking about? Don't say that. What are you talking
about? My Peter Griffin was like pretty good. I thought my friends told me. All right. Is
everything done? I think that's it. I can't paint the window frames. It doesn't work.
The garage. Should the garage be different? I don't think I want the garage to have these
same panels. Maybe like a... what's wrong with the front door? Well, it's kind of fucked up.
And in there? That's fine. Play the family guy theme. No, I'm not going to do that.
If anything, do you want me to do like this loud voice crack Peter Griffin
laugh? I mean, I'll do that again. When you start to get like a little rambunctious.
All right, I want something different out here. Add doors to the house. Hold on, hold on.
I feel bad for the people that I turn away. Stop writing the things that you're
saying. That's not the problem. It was nothing to do with being tired.
Oh, there is a doormat right here. All right. I need some sliders. I need a few of them.
That one. I might change this. Okay. What are you guys doing? Why are you
doing that cringey thing in chat right now? Is there something cringey going on in here?
All right. In turn, let's do... I don't want to put the doors. I'll put some placeholder
doors. I'll put some $246 placeholders because I don't know what the color in the paint and
stuff is going to be in here. Anybody have a clip of me doing that? I want to see what it
sounded like. I'm going to mute the audio though. That's just for me. I want to hear it.
Make that the front door. No, that's fine. Place the fridge on the front lawn and it'll
be a true Vegas house. Fridge on the front lawn. What does that mean? Nobody has a clip
of that. No one saved that. How many people are here? There are 3,652. There are 3,600
fucking people here. No one fucking clipped it. They must have hated it. You guys must
have hated that. Is this it? Okay. Here's a clip of it. This clip has one view and it's
me. Somebody had to go back and clip this because it was so... They hated it so much.
Hold on. I'm muting. I want to hear this. It's not that bad. Why did everybody hate
that so much? What was wrong with that? I thought that was pretty good.
I won't put you through that. Don't ever do that again.
All right. Let's go like this. Move office here? No. The internet here sucks. I have
to move to my office. This is pissing me off though. Seriously. How do I fix this?
You know what I'm saying? Like, why is it like this? What's... Why do I have Tetris
pieces in my front lawn? This is... Recreate the Family Guy interior. That would be
committing so hard to something. That was never supposed to be that. First it was
mini golf. Now it's a one-to-one internal Family Guy house. No. That's gonna be worse
noise of 2019. I already know it. I don't even need to do any more noises ever again.
All right. I want... Let's get the grass rolled out here. Family Golf. What do I need? The
turf. All right. There's some turf here. It looks like shit. I gotta go this way.
I'm trying to write an essay. Can you stop streaming? Yeah. Thanks for coming out
everybody. Does somebody making an essay don't want to like fuck up this cool thing? So
I should be careful doing that because I wonder how many people what like the
percentage of people that just click off the stream when that slide comes up. It's probably
pretty high. I'm just gonna buy it. Look, you know what? Okay. I actually kind of like this.
Maybe I'll keep a couple stacks. All right. Let's go back here. Get it lined up. It's a farm.
Why did I do that? I did it because I was sick of going into the menu and buying them.
So I'm gonna just use these and not have to buy them. See? They just... Right here. Done. Go.
Roll. It doesn't matter. It could be uneven. I have a ton of them. Wait. This is the driveway.
Hold on. Yeah. Fuck it. Go for it. That's driveway.
He's still on the lawn. No. Did you? Wait. Wait. Somebody just came in. There's a big reveal.
Ready? You saw what looked up before. Yeah. He's still on the lawn. Just what? Not the
lawn anymore. Ready? One. Two. Take a look now. See? All right. So then from here
to here needs to be a driveway. This is... No. Why would you do it like this? This is too...
This is a huge driveway. This is like... The whole side yard is gonna be a driveway.
The driveway comes to the... It hits the side of the house. This is too much driveway. This
is more driveway than any yard. What I'm gonna have to do is I'm gonna have to have the
driveway come down here and then go to a single lane. But that's gonna look ugly. Hold
on. Yeah. And I'm not gonna... Just hold on. Let's do the dog park. Get rid of some of these.
Just curb it. Yeah. Doesn't have to be a garage. It could be a tool shed. But what
do you do with your car? Park on the street? Yes. But if I... No. I can make a... I can
make... I can do it. If I have a two-car garage, why would I park my car on the street?
Don't hit the tree. Don't hit the tree. Don't hit the tree. Don't hit the tree. Don't hit
the tree. Don't hit the tree. Yes. Didn't hit the tree. Don't buy them. You don't need it.
Just park in your neighbor's garage. I don't think they would be too happy about that.
A, they will. A, they will. Oh, I'm just making these patches. I got an idea for back here. A
little barbecue section. Out and around. More garden this way. Of like millions of dollars
worth of shit back here too. Because it's protected by the fence. And then a little
plague area back here. It's gonna be insane. Let's just get this over with. Let me see
what this would look like. I need like gravel. Is there like driveway? Gravel.
No, you don't like drive on crushed stone. Stone? Like this? Like pavement? Is it just
a pavement? As concrete? Yeah, but like pavement. They don't have like pavement.
It's like one of these. I don't like the designs on here though.
I just want it to be plain. That's not bad. The pebbles. It looks good. I don't hate this.
Why not search for concrete? I already did. It's like these weird... I don't like this.
I don't like the... I want like it to be just plain. There's no asphalt either.
No, this is not bad. But it's too small. That's not bad. Composite board though. No,
just break cobblestone circles. I'll just go with... I'll go with what I was doing before,
the pebble one. I like it. How big is it? 50 by... How big is that? That's so tiny.
Gold driveway. What about cat's head? Gold? This might be like kind of cool looking.
Is it spot surface? Spot surface? A sports surface. There it is. Yep, there it is.
This is fucking ugly though. I actually like that better. I like the weird like rich,
crystal one. It's called cat's. It's the biggest it can get. The first one was correct. Okay,
by many. Here we go. This is gonna take a hundred years. I have to match up the pieces.
Sand? A sand driveway. It's like the house fell over and planted its forehead into the
ground. Bark? Single color gravel. I want darker than this though. I want red. Wood cuttings.
Like black. Wood chippings? This is as dark as I can get it. There we go. This is perfect.
Perfect. Hello? Size is small enough. We want sand. We want sand. No. No, you can't always get
what you want. But what about what I want? What do I want? This is what I want. Fucking huge.
Tear down the garage. I don't think I can. It's like it's a structure that can't be moved,
I don't think. Move it closer to the road. Tear it down and make it closer.
This is as big as I can get it. All right, so I'm gonna change this in a minute here. This
is straight over here. So the car, you have to have enough for the car to turn in here.
Car comes in. Straight through. Yeah, that's fine. And then, yeah, it turns into the two car garage
right here. Because this is too close. This is right here. It's too close to the edge of the
house. Let me see what happens if I do this. Come on, get it. We're keeping our sand. Where
are you gonna get the sand? Where you get this magic sand? So then here, I'm gonna go like
this. This can be changed. It's hard to, look, there's not specific tools I can paint well with.
I can't like brush it like this. I have to put it all the way over here, see? They're not the
best tools. It's not gonna be exact. Plus we're gonna put stuff on the sides anyways. No,
look, look. All right, I'm gonna show this to you one more time. I can't start deleting.
Look, look it! I can only start deleting when it's there. And if I click right now,
you know what's gonna happen. Even when it's tiny. Look, like.
I'm just covering this up with fucking bushes. There we go. Flatliner raid coming in.
To fix this over here though. All right, let's put some grass down.
Because then there'll be like a bush here. Like a little fence or something.
All right, time for grass. Are you looking? Here it comes. This actually is gonna suck.
I should have done this first. This is gonna be horrible. I can't tell. Is that right?
Is it running the edge? Yeah, god damn it. Why can't I just paint the grass? Why,
why can't I just like have a grass tool? Why do I have to roll it out in a straight line?
That's not even. Get it. Get it. I did it. Thank god. Oh my goodness. Stop,
stop. I did it. I got it good. It's good. What are you talking about? Stop.
I got it. Crisis has been averted. Don't worry guys. Everything's just fine. I can't wait to do
everything and then look back at just how amazing it was. I can't wait to look back
at some of the real highlights of this stream. You know, disposing of all the stuff. Putting
up the plants. Asking for you guys what you think. Doing probably the best peter driven I
think I've ever done in my life. There's been some pretty good highlights from me here.
He's gonna get one more. One more. One more. One more. It's too addicting.
Just gonna keep rolling. Oh, Jesus. Dr. Low Note just came in with 10 community subs. Thank
you, Dr. Low Note. That's a lot of subs. Thank you for the huge amount of community subs. Dr.
Low Note. I, don't worry guys. I will, I will satiate your sand appetite because there's
gonna be a big sand play pen over here on the, to the left. You guys are making flat lines?
That's so stupid. Let's go straight up. A big litter box. Oh, it's gonna be like a little
sand castle thing. Is there any dirt back here? Did I just line that up perfectly first try?
Tell me I did. Oh, that was so close. I love how I just said first try. It's actually
like 400th try as far as I can get it to here. Let's try. I'm gonna try to get this
little edge. It's gonna be rough. See if I can do it. Dude, what's with the Z fighting going on
in the back? I know. That's what I was saying earlier. So that's Z fighting right there,
right? That's what you guys are talking about. He's wasting money. I have $374,000.
I got plenty. I'm gonna sell this house for like a million dollars. So don't worry. I'll be
fine. This is gonna be really, really horrible though. Oh, this sucks. How am I gonna take
care of this? What's the reliable way to do this? It's alright. You have 500k before the
Jenga debacle. Yeah, I'll get it all back. This house is gonna be worth a lot of money.
Get in there and clean that up. Let's go with a small one. Not just a regular one, right? So
I can just get it right on the edge here. How am I gonna do this? I'm gonna have to
start like here. I'm just gonna have to add gravel. That's two. No, I'm just gonna add gravel.
I got enough grass here. What I can just do from here and it'll be fine. And then I'll just
cover it with gravel. When am I gonna do the swamp? Swamp is gonna be on the other side.
Wait, what's swamp? What are you talking about? The swamp. What are we doing? I guess
we're doing a swamp. By swamp, they meant circus. I still have to go. Remember we tried
that yesterday? Putting the little wood chips and stuff and it doesn't work because this is
its own hitbox. It's on collision. I have to put a bush in front of it or something.
Alright, last one. This should do it. Let's get a regular one. And I can just, I actually
can use this to make its own line. I'm kind of in crooch here and it's no, I can't.
I can't. I'll just do it with the gravel. That'll be fine. I'll clean it up. Don't worry.
Oof, perfect. Exactly what I was looking for. So I'll get the square and I will just square it
up and then move down and square it up and then move down. Looks pretty good. Which,
what color was this? This is the dark one, right? Crushed stone. Is it gravel?
Two. This one, tiny little pebble. That doesn't look, that's a false advertising.
I need to square as well. Hey chat, is this your precious sand?
What a shame it is if somebody would have covered this all up.
Not very much left, unfortunately.
This music is really not making this as sad as I want it to be.
He's just playing with us now. He's toying with us now. He's toying with us.
This is already a sharp edge. What are you doing? Okay.
There's going to be a bush anyways, so it's okay. Is this the sand here? I can't have that.
All right, there's going to be some bushes. Finally, we're, no we're not. God, we're not
done at all. I need more turf. A small one to get over here. Did I get it right?
No. It's okay. I can clean it up. It's fine. Give me the, give me a bigger one.
It's the regular one and we'll be good here. Right there. Plus I will have something on the,
maybe a couple, maybe those kind of tall hedges. What do you guys think?
You guys picked this time, not me. Sand around the edges? That could work. It's not ruined yet.
Not yet, not yet. Because I'm gonna, just like I did over here, we're gonna fix this.
It's not ruined. I want to know, like, when you do the smile like this,
are you doing that in real life too? I bet you aren't. I bet you're not. I bet you're just
sitting there tightening it. You don't actually mean it. I'm just going to put some, there'll
be bushes here. I'm not going to spend like an eternity trying to get this perfect. We're
going to have bushes, hedges. There's no reason to do this. Not at all. All right.
Hey, you guys still awake? You guys still with me here? We have what is the beginning
of a driveway? A tree? I need, I kind of like these things. Those tall, every maybe like
right next to each other. I could go all out and just line it with these or with these.
What do you guys think? Don't worry, the carrots will go to the circus. Don't worry.
I know everyone's going to freak out when they see that. I'm thinking a line of these
right next to each other or these ones. These ones here make them flaming hot
Cheeto flavored. What do you think? Or I don't think it should be green.
Regular Cheetos or flaming hot Cheetos? You need to combine these to heal. God. Flaming hot
Cheetos? Let's see. Let's take a look and I'm talking back to back here all the way down.
Now that'd be like kind of like monarch, right? That'd be royalty. Too royalty. Too much royalty.
Uh no, I don't like it. I don't like that either. It's gonna be bigger. Maybe these?
Oh Jesus, these are fucking huge. Okay, does anybody feel like these are too big?
Is it that I got like a weird scale here? They're that big? These? I don't know. I don't
mind this. Although it's kind of big and annoying. This might be too annoying. Maybe.
I'm afraid there are no cactuses unfortunately in one of these. Let's see. That's a little less
insane. Let's, I got money so let's just play with it. Ready? I need to be close enough to
be on them. What's that one? It's not a Christmas tree runway. It's, there's gonna
be other stuff in between. Two more. Where's the reindeer? Stop. Shut up. Stop it. Hey,
leave me alone. Oh man. Oh man. Let's look. See it's, it doesn't look, it looks fine.
That looks okay. That looks fine. There's nothing wrong with that. I'm gonna put some
flowers in the middle. I'll put a row of like red flowers down here. Or orange. I'm doing it.
You know, I don't care what the haters say. Oh, the haters are right this time.
The five people who are on the left have all fallen asleep. They haven't commented
over an hour. Is that true? Just stick with me guys. Stick with me. I've got a, I got a plan.
Just the back, this is just the, we're gonna finish up the back here. I don't need anything
on this side. In fact, I am gonna put this one here. No I'm not. Put it back. I haven't even
planted this. Where was it? It was like right there. That's okay. That's good. I haven't even
planted this. That looks good. What, what's wrong with having all these trees? You're losing
the casual audience. Should I spray myself with a hose? I actually kind of like this.
You can call me a boomer if you want. It looks fine. It looks good. I think it looks all right.
I really do. And we're gonna do a huge, a couple of huge ones over here.
No we're not. No, we don't need anything over there. No, no. Watch this.
Ladies and gentlemen, these look like they're too tall. They're too tall.
They gotta be shorter. Just by like, not by very much. Here we go. There we go. There it is.
Okay, if they were symmetrical. It's not a clown garden. It's not a clown.
This is not a clown garden. This is a normal garden with fun things. Still a clown.
And then back here is gonna be a couple of other things. It's not a clown garden. Hey,
that's a pretty nice clown garden. Back to orange. I just got here. Why is he making a
clown garden? I think it looks pretty. And then we're gonna do yellow. It's five, five,
and then bingo. This one had to be six because it was a little longer. That looks kind of nice.
And then I'm gonna get, watch this, a cinnamon apple tree. Apple trees down here. Get them
in the middle. Those are clown noses. Oh, fuck. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm flatlining. Please
switch to the pre-recorded track. I told you it was gonna be all night. I gave you fair warning.
I warned you like four hours ago that we were gonna go all night and I was gonna make an entire
fucking done house. It's gonna be unbelievable. Your jaw's gonna hit the ground. Dude, I got
beers to go. There you go. What time is it? It's like nine o'clock Pacific. Oh, it is
midnight. Whatever. All night. What is it? Friday? What are you doing tomorrow? It's
Friday night. What do you got going on tomorrow? It's a weekend. I think that looks cool. Yes,
sure. You could tell me that this looks like Baby's First Unity game. I, okay, I would,
I might laugh at that. I would chuckle at that for a second. Did you see what it looked
like before? Okay, and now, what am I gonna put the red frid, wait, what's the deal with
the red fridge? I need something on the other side. What should go on the other side here
on the right? Maybe like a hand rail, a railing. Is it gonna hand rail? Something, this is missing
something. A flower bed. Yeah, that's probably a good idea. A red fridge. I'm not putting a
red fridge. Why would anybody have this many plants? All right, let's be honest. Why would
somebody have this much, this many plants? Dude, this is a full-time job for like 10 people
to maintain all this. To take care of all this stuff, you would need fucking like 12 employees.
All right, so let's put some flowers in here. Flowers. Nice ones. Strawberry flower. Large roses.
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. There we go. This is so much time and energy.
How would you even know one of these died? Would you even know? I feel like you wouldn't
know when one of these died. I already blew it though. Does it move the whole thing?
Thank god it does. I need more gravel here. Look at that. Better. Looks better. I need one more here
I think. Move this one back. Move this one forward. Gravel. This trash in the garage,
doesn't it? Some gravel. Go right to the edge on this one. I wonder if I should just
put that around here? Yeah. Hello, can I get an estimate of getting my lawn done? I'm sorry,
I add in the paper. Uh, $500,000 in one payment. Something's missing here though.
I got my trees. I got the, maybe something else right there. A big boulder or a fountain.
A fountain. I like a fountain better than a boulder. Which one? This one looks kind of good.
Try the blue. What if we did two fountains? Fountain, fountain, and fountain in the middle.
Wait a minute. Hold on. No. No. No, don't work. This might go over here. I'm gonna
sneeze. I'm just boring you. Maybe just one of the big ones. Like one of these. Stone.
Green. That. Let's see this. That's not terrible. Turn it though. I think it's the same color as
the grass. I don't think I can even do that. You guys want me to change off of Sandy? Is that
what you guys are saying? All right. Something right here. I think in, I'm thinking something
cool. A little decoration. Maybe you have a big, big tulip, blamp, birdbath, rabbit cage.
A big rock. Another pool? Yeah. Move it over a little bit. You're gonna have so many
mosquitoes. So extra. I figured out what I'm doing. I am desperately trying to have the
coolest house on the block for their Christmas decorations. I'm trying to make one of those
houses that you drive by during Christmas. And you go, holy fuck, that person's insane.
I have to have the most ridiculous house on the whole lot. Except all year round. Yeah,
that's it. This is too, okay, I'm getting way too super extra extra. Let's do something
over here too. This house is gonna be worth a fucking trillion dollars. Bird feeder. Perfect.
Make it not ash. Right near the tree. Right here. Right here. No, no, no, no, that goes
over here. That goes in the backyard. So you can look out the window from your fucking weird
dungeon room and see the birds eating. All right. And then a gazebo. Never mind. Won't
fit. Can I have a bridge go over the driveway? How do I? Oh, there's too much here. Garden. Um,
fences. No, uh, architecture. No recreation. Um, yeah, something fun. No, that goes in the
back. A hammock. Right here. Right in between the apples. You come out here and enjoy the
pond. Grab an apple. You can just like bite into it. I'm going to turn this actually.
Just a little bit. Pull it forward. This is fucking insane. Nice. Ruined. Change it back.
All right. This is coming together. This looks really interesting. By the way, interesting is
a fake compliment when something looks terrible, but you don't say it looks bad. It looks
interesting. Which means bad. All right. I think we're done with the driveway portion. Well,
it gets over here later when we leave the backyard. I want something secret back here
that the only I know about nobody else does. Yeah. I want a secret grill back here. No,
I want a tire swing back here. I want a fire pit back here. No, that goes in the backyard. I want
a secret grill. That makes no sense. Remember I told you I needed something here. This is
what we needed. This is what we needed. I need to move this. How do I move this?
Too much. Is it too much? I feel like, um, I feel like this is okay though. Does this need
to go? No, I think that's fine. You're gonna go up a ski lift. But a fire pit needs to go here.
No, that needs to go in the backyard. Can I put this here? There has to be like a table. Give
me a table. Table. Something fun. Something cool. Something swanky. Something chic. Here
we go. This is turning into a grandma house. It's turning into an old lady house. Real quick.
This is really quickly. I need something over here though. It looks all right.
I like that color. Um, I want a little, I want something over here. Edible plants. Um, pumpkin?
No, that makes no sense. What can go right? Nothing. Nothing needs to be right here until we
get over here. And then we got, bang, here's your walkway. Walkway. Let me get this going
here. I need like a good pool and a pool fit back here. Why is the front yard way bigger
than the backyard? All right, here we go. I want a sick patio barbecue. Bring your friends over.
Chill. Have a couple of drinks. Talk shit about the game. Last game that came out.
All right, here we go. I'm going to go with out these doors. This is like the, this is
like a cigarette den, right? You go out here and you have like a cigarette. This is where
the people that go have cigarettes. This is not like in the, who cares? This is stupid.
Out here, though, is the whole thing. So I'm going to go with one of those.
Um, what are they called? What's the thing that, um, not a gazebo. What's it called?
Yeah, there. Okay. Yeah, there it is. Perp, gondola. Isn't it? What is a gondola?
God, the gondola is a boat. I'm going to say we want something a little lighter.
Maybe, maybe white. I like this bank. Shit. That actually is ruined. Yes. I know. I know.
I got it. I got it. I fixed it. I got it. Everything's fixed. Come on. Come on. Killing
me here. I know. No, God damn it. It's got to be closer to the house somehow.
Right there. Got it. Finally. Holy shit. That's too long. All right. Now let's go
ahead and let's make a little bit of a, I think I'm going to do a little bit of mulch.
I'm going to do some mulch that goes around here and like stops here. Let's mulch it.
I need some walkway. I need some paving stone here. That's an interesting design.
Paving stone, uh, symphonia. Which one? I like this one. Use the stepping stones.
I will. We're going to do these, uh, sandy. I need something. I need something out here first,
though. Stepping stones is later. Perfect opportunity for our cat. Is it not flush?
Can it even be flush with the house?
Saved it. It's too big. What the hell? Why? I can't do anything about that. Is this going to
have to be there? I can use the small pieces later. It's not matching up. I need the smaller
one to do the front here. What color do I want? This one, this, and then this, right? Right here?
Beige and dark gray. I thought that should do it. In fact, I'm going to make sure it does it.
I'm going to come out again. No, get rid of this door. Oh, hello? Why? Hello? What was
that happening for? Starting. I got it. Okay. Now I should be able to do the bigger piece.
Beige and dark gray. Now will this line up correctly in here? I'm going to have to just
sacrifice. Yeah, it does. We're good. That's all right. I can, I can work with this later.
Right on the edge here. Come on. Come on. Why? Give me a break. I'm going to have to do
little pieces. This thing's in the way. It took so long to get this flush too. All right,
it should work now. It should be good to go. There we go. Okay. Are we lined up? Do we
have good, uh, what's the best way? What do you think? Right there. Thank God. Finally.
I can use the little piece and I can go in the middle here. I think. I hope so.
No, it's not going to work. I could just fill this with rocks.
I'm just going to gravel this up. We're going to do two-tone. Gravel, gravel.
All the way out. Here we go. We can do it with like sand or graph. We'll do it.
We'll be fine. Now I can just build this out. It actually might look kind of good.
It's not going to look bad. That's for sure. It's going to look, you know, you know what I'm
saying. It might look pretty good. Come out. I wonder if should we do it like that and just
have the middle there have a little bit. Maybe put something in there and then go across
here. Let's see what this looks like. This is kind of fucked up looking. That's not going
to work. It's got to go closer. I'm not sure I can. Can I even go closer with this one?
I don't think I can. Oh well. I tried. I failed. This can build out here. I think I probably can
just do this now. Let me see. Is it going to work? What do you guys think? Thank God.
Thank God it worked. Now we just have to do the skinny one down here.
He genuinely loves this game. I think it's fun. I mean, all jokes aside, I think it's fun.
It's not going to take it to the edge, is it? Is there another one that's
as big as this? I don't think there is. We're just going to have to deal with it.
There's going to be like a, there'll be the big grill over here or something. You won't even
know. Yeah, you won't even know. There's like, there'll be a fucking grill right here.
We'll cap this up with some stone. Now let's see. Stone, sand, gravel. What do we got?
What do you guys think? Surface, let's see, wood cuttings? Do sand? Let's see what it looks like.
Looks a little weird, but not horrible. Let's put the gondolas back.
Gondolas go well. Yeah, they do. They actually really do. Put a nice stream of water in the
middle. Now you're talking. Now you're talking. That sounds pretty great. I must feel like,
no. It's not, it's not the same size. I can't build it out anymore. Can I?
Because essentially I would need one of these on each. Let me see. Although not yet. No,
don't freak. Don't have to freak out yet. It's possible I can get in there again.
Dark gray beige. All right. We're good. Thank God. We are good to go. It's going
to look a little sloppy, but it'll work. Somebody said the pattern's really all over
the place anyway, so it wouldn't be hard. You can't really tell anyway. The room is ruined.
What happened? What did I do? Ruin? What's wrong? What's wrong with it?
There's gonna be a grill there. You're not even gonna, you're not even gonna know.
There's actually gonna be a bunch of random things in here. So why?
Oh, now it is ruined, but I can move it up. All right, we're good. I think it's still
gonna be a little too long though. It's almost like this thing in the middle is not,
because this is longer, so it almost needs to be longer, but it can't be longer. Maybe
just bring these forward, but that wouldn't look right. It sounds like I need another
part of the wall. I can't do that because it's an external wall too. Damn it. It'll be all
right. Plus I can do a little bit like, I can do some of the crushed stone around here.
Have like a little path leading off and yeah, we'll be good. We'll be here very much.
We'll do some crushed stone. Because there's gonna be something here too.
Mm-hmm. All right, let me, let me ask you guys what's worse. Ready? What's worse?
That or this? This is better. The sand actually is causing the problem.
Yeah, it's the sand. It's the sand. Because the middle point is,
you know, I don't even, you can't even tell. That's fine. Look, take it. Ready?
If you're walking around, you talk, oh yeah, cool. There's gonna be some stuff here. There'll
be like a, you won't be able to really tell. Yeah, this is fine. Look, I'll take it. You're
gonna, I'm gonna take your eyes off it right now. You're not even gonna know that it existed.
How do you turn them on? Isn't this supposed to be water? Water wall? Lights. Here we go.
Yellow. We're gonna have like water waves. You won't even be able to know this is going
on here. Urinals. I just want to see what they did. No. All right, let's build it.
Let's build it up. Come on. Here we go. Grill. The most expensive one. A bed grill. What?
Here we go. Take a look. Grill. In the corner. Fire pit. Right here. Bingo. I want a bigger fire
pit than this. Here it is. I like it. Right there. Get that out there. This needs to be
over here though. Out further. Like back here. There we go. Nice grill. Got a couple of chairs
there. Can I turn it on? Turn it on. Talk to the grill. I actually just pressed E.
All right, now we start to go. Okay, grill. Fire pit. Give me some chairs. Give me some nice
chairs. Chair. No, we need some better chairs than this. These look all right. All right.
This chair's ugly. I'm sitting in one of those chairs. What about back it up? Other.
Ooh, what's this stuff? A sprinkler. I'm sorry, guys. There's only one,
there's only one starburst that I like. Fod. Furniture. A little table. This is nice.
This is chic. Got a blue top. Can I connect them? I might want two of these right next
to each other. All right. Do I have to kneel at this table? It's a table to kneel at.
Why is everything yellow? Everything's not yellow. Just the house, the chairs,
half of the plants. I need a little garden back here. Better table than this. This table
sucks. Just one of these. This is cute. How about one of these ones? Yeah, that's okay.
Perfect. Now you can eat your burgers over here. That table's way too big. Table alvar.
Oh, that's nice. Yeah, that's fucking sick. Definitely. Just some stools.
Take a little breakfast nook. All right. Got the grill. I need like a little table
here for the grill. Grilling table. Just like one of these. How big is this? Yeah. Boom. Right.
So you can put like the, you can put his stuff there, his utensils. This is the birdhouse.
I want to put this like over here. Right at the window. I need some bushes back here. I'm
going to need bush here, bush there on the back. Just to have a little area to play.
A red bush or a green bush? Let's go green. Get a couple of red ones in here too.
Are these ugly? I can't tell if these are ugly or not. Yeah, they are very ugly. I need just a
standard hedge. Maple trees. Oh, these are nice. I could put a few, like a handful of
these back here. They're not going to be in pots for very long. Oh, those are huge.
Those ones are already out there. Ball bush. I'll get to the pool. You want a pool? I'll make you a
pool. Just hold on a second. Oh, this looks nice. Yeah, you guys, you guys have this already.
But by the way, who, why is this house yours? This house is not your house. I don't have room
for a pool actually. Hold on. Yeah. I have enough room for like a kid's pool.
The pond is bigger than the pool. Yeah, but get this over there. This is the worst backyard
landscaping ever. I have, I'm just barely getting started. Hold on. I need more yellow.
I don't need any more yellow. What are you doing? Those flowers are going to get no sun.
That's fine. They're not real. I do want to get around. I can't, can I reach this one?
Get back there and reach it. I need to reach this flower. I need to pull it back. I'm not,
what do you mean pool? I already have a gnome. Did you not see the gnome? Can you find it?
You sure you can't find it? I need something right here. I'm going to do a line of bushes.
Small bushes. Just the same bush. A line of them right against those. 0.5 rose bush. Done.
Bingo. Now this is huge. Um, never mind. Hey, there we go. Better. There it is. Okay. Nice,
nice, nice. Check this out. Watch this. I'm going for something beautiful here.
It's terrible. What? No, I, wait, guys, I just typed into Google beautiful garden
and I'm just trying to replicate it. I'm just trying to replicate beautiful garden. All right.
I just need just regular bush pleasure. This is plagiarizing a garden. Oh man,
I can't believe you. I, you know, I thought I liked you. I can't believe you're plagiarizing
a garden. Where is it? That's close. That's close enough. I can't do another color.
There we go. Is that right? Not really. No, that looks bad. This used to be a swindle stone
stream. Yeah, you haven't been around in like four years. Lettuce? There we go. That's just,
no, this is like candy. I need like dirt or something. It's something here.
I feel like I'm getting too obsessed with the fact that it's a garden flipper and I'm just
putting tons of flowers and plants and shit everywhere. I might as well just go to the end
here. Make a swamp. I don't think I even can. These need to be closer. I have not even
remotely been inside the house. No, I still need to put grass down here. Hold on. Wait,
wait, wait, wait. Fuck the grass. Smokers get graveled. Wait, this goes here. My stomach.
Somebody said graham cracker. That's not even what it looks like.
That does not look like a graham cracker. I don't know why, but
it's funny to me for some reason. All right, let me lay grass down in the last few places and
then we can go in the house. By the way, I don't give a shit about anything inside of this house.
We're gonna, I spent so much time like out there. It's all right. I'm still going. Anymore
graham cracker? No, we can do grass here. Give me the roller. Turn the inside of the
house into a garden as well. I wish you could. You unfortunately cannot bring anything that is
an outdoor tool inside. I know. And I got that perfectly. First time ever, first try.
Almost did it again. Oops. Dog house? I know. I'll get the dog. I still have to make a circus.
I don't have enough land to make a circus. How was I ever gonna do that?
There's no way I can make a circus. You can do it in the garage. I guess, yeah, I guess
I could do the circus in the garage. A garage circus. Come on, get the last little bit of grass.
Right to the door. Come on, right in the corner. Got it. All right, nice. Gravel the house. I
can't gravel in the house. See, look. The game doesn't let you. The game doesn't want you
to be able to do that. Oh my god, what the hell. All right, I need to fix this and then
we can finish up the outside. What was it? It was the two-colored, this one, dark one,
all the way. Tiny, right. All right, here we go. Done. All right, all right, all right,
all right, all right. So we got pool, clown pit. I have to still plan all these. I didn't
even do anything over here. That's fucking hard work. We're far from done. No, I told you
I wasn't stopping. I'm not stopping till the outside is completely done and there's at least
a couch inside the house. Don't tell them. Don't tell me what. Don't tell them. I was,
what are you guys not telling me? I've been playing this for almost seven hours
and that's the first skill point. I think it's seven hours. Hey, when it gets there,
I'll have it. That looks all right. Just a little filled in back there. I can put
something else back here though. Big tree, couple little trees. Just five trees in
a square meter. I still don't understand this. All right, I'm going to have to do
something interesting here because I'm not putting any more flowers. Okay, no more flowers,
no more. I got to, what am I putting here? The dog, the dog stuff. Holy shit. Wait a minute.
How is this an outdoor cinema? It's, this is just a giant TV. Why, what does this mean
outdoor? Okay. And then you could build a real life backyard projector. What are you guys
talking about? What's wrong with the projector? Oh, you talk, you, yeah, but this has to go on
a table. I'm not just going to sit, $700. All right, hold on. No, give me, no more gravel.
You're right. What are you doing? Hey, wrong side. Just hold on. You'll see. Give me it.
Why is this crooked? What? Drive-in movie theater.
It's a motorcycle, it's a two motorcycle parking lot drive-in movie theater. It's a bicycle drive-up
movie theater. Yes, it's a bicycle movie theater. And if you want to, you can stop at our garden
on the way over here. Pull up your fucking bike. I mean, yeah, the bricks, the bricks
just go another way, but that's fine. Oh, what, what? Why is everybody freaking out?
I'm just making a little walkway, but that looks much better. What are you talking about?
What is wrong with this? I don't see the problem here. I'm going to make one more here and you
can like take a little stroll. You won't let me do gravel. I went too quick. Give me a table.
What's wrong with the simplicity of grass? Nothing really. Nothing. I see it's a thinner
table. No, this is fucking ridiculous. Come here. Simple table. There we go.
Is that level? Okay, here we go. What is a gym rope? Punching bag? The projector's facing the wrong
way. It's fine. Fresh pizza ready for you. Get this in here. Plant tomatoes. Plant tomatoes.
That's actually not a bad idea. We want food. Edible plants. What can you put on a pizza?
Nut grapes. Plums? No. Cherries? No. Apple? Apple? Blueberry? You don't put carrots on a pizza.
You don't put pumpkin. There are no pineapples, guys. I'm just kidding. Jesus. The eight cents.
It's not a big deal if I pretend to do this. All right. There you go. Okay. I need something
here. I need like a tree or something. This is empty over here. Very empty. Besides my little
dumb walkway. No, I don't think it needs anything. I'm going to put a gazebo. A gazebo will not fit
here. No, I'm not fucking doing that. Let me make a nice little thing here. Hold on. Let me
get the wrecked shrubs. The default ones. They look okay. I'm just going to let the brush
just go on the paper. I'm not going to think about it. Just let the brush flow across the
canvas. What am I thinking here? Where am I going? Okay, something else. Let's get a nice little
display here from these little ones. This is what I had before. That's the same one I had before.
I'm not thinking about it. I'm not thinking about it. Let's just go. I'm not thinking
about it at all. Okay. I don't think that's that bad. Attention streamer, you have too
many plants. Oh, I mean the name of this game is Garden Flipper. I'm going to make a huge
elaborate display. Think of a water bill. This is not called Don't Put Plants Anywhere DLC. This
is the Garden DLC. I'm going to make an elaborate fucking piece. I'm going to go back over there
and we'll do some more cleanup. Million dollar sprinkler system. This is it for plants though.
This is going to be it for plants because then I'm going to put the fucking clown stuff
in the garage and you'll be happy. Imagine if the neighbor was allergic to pollen.
He'll be okay. I need to buy one for like a couple of rock or something.
This is like a lot here. I'm going to move this. This is why you think it's too busy
because it's too far up. Better. Much better. Maybe a little bit of gravel? No. I think
that's okay. This needs something in here. Something to take it. Hold on. I need like
something in here. You're going to be mad about this but I'm just adding a couple more.
Like one, two. Rocks maybe. Some little ones. No, I think that's all right. This one's
going to go. That one's fucking the whole thing up and that one and this one and that one
and that one. What about over here? Something's going to go over here.
I've never had a house like this. I've never had a garden. I'm just trying to make a
cool garden. I've never had one before. I've never had a cool garden. Water walls.
I've never had this much money to make whatever I want. You have five gardens.
Play some windmill. I've never had a garden before. That looks good. Look at that. That
kind of ties the whole thing together. Now it's finally mini golf. All right. I'm no more. I'm
done. I'm losing my fucking mind. Okay. I'm not. No more. I just need to clean this part
up. Fuck no. I need to tie this together here. I need this because I don't hate this.
What about a path? I could do a path, but that has to start from over here and yes,
it will. That's not the right one, mom. Did I say ma? Like calling you guys mom?
That's not edit. Edit the right one, ma. It's this one, right? Okay. Here it is.
Let me see what this looks like. Is that right? Is this one?
Okay. Not bad. Not bad. I gotta, I gotta clean this back up though.
Because this is now, now this is no longer. Don't need this. Couple more stones. Yes. Give
us a tour. Not yet. Not done. I'm not done. Not done. Not done. Something's got to be here.
Something's got to go right here. I'm sorry. It does. That's just the way it is. That space
is freaking me out. I need something. I need to hide it. Uh, how about it's like a light
or something. No, no, that's fine. Negative space. You're right. What about one of these
stones to go away? Much better. 10 times better. See, I am removing things. You guys thought
I was just throwing shit. I'm removing things. Don't turn it around. I think this is good.
Put that rock back. No, I can't. Uh, what about here? This feels pretty empty. I don't like any
of this. I don't like this. I want to redo this whole thing. I don't, this is, I don't
like this. This is too much open space. There needs to be more of this. I need like a,
no, that's okay. That's fine. That looks all right. That's better. That's better. I feel much
better now. A nice lamp. Let's get a big lamp. How big are these? There we go. That's a, uh,
that is a street lamp. So yeah, nevermind. Is this knuckles? No, I can't put it inside.
Ball pits are the only thing that can go in here apparently for some reason.
Can a carousel go in here? Okay, you can. Carousel, the little kid's house,
little fun playhouse. All right, I gotta assemble it. What's going on? Can't do,
I can't do that now. What can you not do? This is the garage. I can't put the circus in here.
No pictures. I want a place for my documents. I think I'm, I'm ready to go inside. Would you
like a tour of the outside? Not yet. No, no. We get to do the whole thing. Let's make some
walls here. What do we got? This room sucks. Change it. Uh, this is going to be a bathroom.
No, closet. Watch this. I don't want that. I don't want, this looks ugly. Let's do some
paint. I'm thinking light biscuit on the walls. Maybe let's see what light biscuit looks like.
Yeah, it's been seven hours and 15 minutes and I finally made it inside.
That was a seven hour garden. Now it's going to be like, this could be a home office.
Yeah, this is an office. You'll get the whole, the whole tour is going to take like
25 minutes. It's going to be a long tour. Flesh walls. These are the color of the walls
in my room right now. This is what it looks like in my room now. A flesh wall. It's a
yeah, I don't know, tinted cigarette ash, whatever it is. Cigarette. Yeah, I would call this a
cigarette yellow, like cigarette tar. It works good for an office or a closet. I can reach it.
I'm fine. Did I just shrink? Did I shrink? Look at me. What? Maybe I should use a scaffolding
to get to the, that's not, I don't need to do that. Why would I put a scaffolding in the
house? It is not too high. I'm not going to get shown up here. Too high, huh? All right,
this wall here, we'll get an accent color. Maybe a, what should I add? What a little accent.
What do you think? Kappa? Let's see one gray. Why do I need a scaffolding to reach this shit?
That's so stupid. I have a long pole. Did my, my character shrunk? Okay, what do we want
for an accent color in here around the windows? Gray? Silver glacier? Steel gray? Purple? Purple?
Like a lavender or quartz? Lavender. Quartz, quartz, quartz. Um, this looks like a fucking
jelly donut room. You picked it. I didn't. I mean, I'm, yeah, you guys picked it. Why is
this wall, I swear to God, this is a weird optical illusion where it looks, I feel like
I'm shrinking, but I'm tall enough over here, but I'm shrinking over here. This is freaking
me out a little bit. I'm not going to lie. See, look at, I'm not even, something really
fucked up is going on. Cause like, I'm tall enough over here? Why is this house, how tall
are these ceilings? These ceilings are like 30 feet tall. I'm standing on the paint can.
Okay. All right. Carpet color. The first color I see in chat is the one that's going
in here. Carpet color. What do you got? First color I see. Don't care what it is. Red.
Why does that have to be red? Can I even do red? Okay. There's no red. I don't, there's no red.
So we're going to have to do something else. This looks like shit. No, that looks all right.
I like that. Oh, I like that because that's, look, that's the wall. Yeah. The blue. All
right. I'll try the blue. I'll give it another chance. It's all right. What color
is this carpet? This carpet is like a white with beige, beige, white, a little bit of tan.
The walls are like a sand. This is a Pee-wee Herman room. All right. Well, this is supposed
to be, this is the office. So we need a desk. A nice one. The nicest one you can buy. This is
the desk that I currently have right now. Is there walnut? How could you not have,
it's on walnut. All right. Okay. Let's get a chair. Office chair. Looks pretty good.
I like that kind of sandstone look. Computer in here. Good computer. The computer brushy.
Computer Phoenix. Computer Sphinx. Well, that's the best one we can buy. So we're going to get
it. Let's get the monitor. So we need more. I mean, a lot of them. We need at least two.
Okay. I didn't think it was going to be that big. That is a very large monitor.
Now you're gaming. Yeah, we're dropping a bunch. How are we dropping this many frames at like
11 o'clock at night? It's like, that doesn't even make sense. We had like seven hours of like
green internet and now at like 11 PM? What the fuck? Are you serious? This is literally
my boyfriend's setup. It's an interesting setup. Press C. How long was I crouched for?
I may have been crouched the whole game. No, I didn't notice because
you look it. You walk the same speed. You just lower to the ground. That's why I couldn't reach
the shit like eight hours ago. Oh my god. I'm just gonna finish my office please. All right,
I need a mouse. And it's in gamer grub with my sardines. Why do I have it in the office
so I can snack on them? I just mute the microphone. I just start eating. Dwarf soup.
It's odd. A propane tank under your desk. All right, that's good. We need a little bit
of a, let's see, furniture. We need, I don't know, maybe like a little bookcase. Yeah,
this is nice. A little drawer in the corner. What else? What do I have? What's in my office?
A fuck you table. A closet. There's nothing else in here. There's a keyboard. There's not
really a whole lot of room for this. All right, well, new plan. You reach over and grab the
mouse. All right, like at what point, at what point do you just figure out how to
get, get a smaller monitor? Okay, you have to tilt your head to the left. You need to have
a windmill in here to power the PC with clean energy. I don't think so. I don't think I'm
going to do that. All right, we need paint. Living room. Sierra Mist. Young Fly. I like
this one. Peach. Peach might look alright. Peach or Velvety Peach? Which one? Velvety?
I'll give it a trial run for you. How about Bright Peach? Let's try that one. It's a little
lighter. It's better. We're not the same. No. You got to do clown stripes. I just need to
get a couch in here. The couch is the finishing touch. That means that, that means
the house is done and we can do our 35 minute tour. What about the ground in here? I'm
thinking basil. Hey Lois, I'm a clown now. There are no lights. I'll put some lamps in
here and stuff. No, we're not doing another ice cream shop. This is just going to be
a regular house. House was so fucked up. It was a mall at the bottom floor, an ice
cream shop at the top. You guys thought I was on like drugs this stream. What the
hell was wrong with me on that one? Yeah, this is like standard apartment building.
It doesn't matter. No, I'm not doing the family guy house. Where did you get
that information from? Is he really doing the family guy house? Where'd you get that
info? I didn't say that. That's not info from me. Am I still doing this? Yeah,
this is, this is, this is going to be a long one. This will be at least, this is
going to be like at least a nine hour stream at least. Hey, I've got the internet.
I'm going to use it. Skill point. Max upgraded painting. That's quick. Have a
few stripes to break it up. Yeah, but once I get it all painted, we'll do a
little bit of a detail work. I'm not kidding. It does look like the family guy
house even from the inside. Oh my God. Oh my God. It is the family guy house.
Here's the door that like and then this couch and the TV and the stairs
and then the kitchen. It's the family guy. Somebody look right now. I don't
know how you can do this. Is there a door right here next, right here to
the front door? This is not, no. So it's not the family guy house. See all these
similarities. You just, you're making them up in your head. Holy crap, Lois.
It's the famous streamer, German nine eight five. Oh God. Where's Chris's
room? No, I'm not doing that. I don't care.
I'm an orange hell right now, but you have to wait. I have to break it
up and do accent work. Yes, you're currently in orange hell, but this is
what painters do. They get ready and then they finish with other colors.
It's not. It's not. All right. All right. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. I'm thinking like a darker purple or like a white. No, a white
guys. It's going to be white. This is ultra generic. Well, we have to
mute it a little bit because look at the fucking clown circus that's outside.
We have to have the normal house on the inside and this is too boring for
you. Is it too boring? I'm not going to do rainbow walls. You guys are
fucking crazy. What a shitty house that would be. I would throw up in every
room. If every room was a rainbow, it would just be like, you wouldn't be
able to look at it. He's doubling down on being boring now because the
outside was so fucked up. I'm, I'm sorry. Here you go. You want your
fucking, you want your donut house here. Each room is themed around a
different fucking filling. Yeah, this is strawberry. Now you're pandering.
Actually, I kind of like this. I really actually like what I just did
over here. I do. I do. I actually don't mind that at all. All right,
so let's take a look. Although I could have it without. I could do
without on this wall. Yeah, no. In fact, we're going to go from there.
We're going to go to sunny orange. It is a circus tent. Oh fuck, whatever.
It's not a circus tent. It's not a circus tent. A circus tent doesn't
look like this. It's a house. A house standing on four legs,
breathing pure oxygen. That's too much. Uh, it's got to be a morning
yellow. Let me see what the, let me see what the red actually looks
like over here. It might not look terrible. Try blue. What kind of blue?
Like a light blue, dark blue, like a royal blue. That looks good.
Family guy blue. No, family guy blue is a little darker than this.
You guys are fucking hilarious. I swear to God.
Stewie's room. How do you even remember that? How do I don't even
know what that, how do you even remember this? That seems almost
impossible to remember. Why is no door leading to the yard? Because
as of right now, I had to put down these and they've been getting in the way.
So I had to pull them up. We watch family guys so we can make the
references on your stream. Well, nice job. You got it. Those are pretty good references.
This needs to be redone. Is this the right color? No. Residrator. Right there.
I mean, yellow and, I mean, blue and brown go together very well. They just do.
Tons of schemes are with blue and brown. Let's get some appliances in here.
No, we can look at a tile of ground. Floor, floor tile for the kitchen.
Uh, we could do checkerboard. We could do, is there a beige?
This one? Sepia? That's giving me a headache. How about this one? Not bad. Could be worse.
Something's going on over there. It's a bathroom. I'm not going to have a brick
bathroom. No, this is Rocco's Modern Life. It's really easy for a house to turn into
Rocco's Modern Life in this game. Uh, let's just go with this one. Just wood. Wood floors.
Looks good. Except for over here. Now the paint doesn't match.
Well, I'm going to do, uh, let's see. What am I going to do? A carpet in here?
I'm thinking a, one of these. Let's see how this looks.
What is this doing? This is the carpet in this room right now.
No, let's go with, um, rug gray. Rug pattern. Rug gray. Let's try the gray.
What? Oh, these are just rugs. Floor panels and coverings. I mean, pine.
I just do wood through the whole house. What's, what's, what's, what's with millennials
and wooden floors? What's going on there? That's a millennial thing. I want the, the high,
the, not the low cut. I want like the really fabric-y carpet around my whole house.
The long haired carpet. Carpet is disgusting, revolting. Yeah. But when you walk around on wood,
everybody in the whole house can hear you. It's, it's boom, boom, boom, boom. You're like an
elephant up there. Carpets. It's like, it's funny. I'm, I'm being like a fake internet troll
right now because I love wooden floors. I'm just being one of those just like fucking
accounts that just goes on and just says whatever the, it's just anything that they
do. Anything to like get sort of be like, what the fuck are you talking about?
I'm just like a LARP. Yeah. I'm LARPing right now. Dark wooden floors are my
favorite thing in the world. They really are. You guys are making me like laugh too.
What's with like the comedy troupe here? You guys have been like on point today with like
the comedy. All right, let's go. Please put more in the computer room. I will. Don't worry.
I will. I will. Let me just get this down. Got doors here. This is closed.
I gotta put the other doors on here. I'm going to do dark. Nevermind. Can this not fit?
Why can this not fit? It's because of this shit right here. The lip. It's all right. I got it.
I got it in. Hungry. What do I eat? I'm hungry. I'm forcing myself to stay awake to
watch you. Don't fuck it up. I won't. Do you see the garden that I made?
You're in good hands here. All right. Computer room. Bathroom. Eat the sandwich that's been
in the car for eight months. I don't even have that car. I don't have that sandwich.
I'm not at that house. So many windows here. What is seriously with the windows?
Is the window? They're everywhere. This house is so bizarre. Tile. Wall tile. Hmm.
I'm interested in what this does. Let's see. All right. Yeah. I didn't even give you a warning
on that one. I'm sorry. I didn't have a warning. Why am I sneezing so much today?
I don't sneeze this much ever. The carpet. No. It's not the carpet. What do I feel like
eating? Dude, am I going to get a pizza? I'm going to give you guys a little bit of an
insight here. I know that people think I eat pizza every day because I always say,
you know what? I'm thinking about a pepperoni pizza. I don't, I don't do it. I don't get it.
Like three out of six streams. I say I'm going to get a pepperoni pizza delivered to the house.
You guys must think I'm like a sicko. I actually, I like this. This looks nice.
Just need a bathtub. Thinking about eating pizza is not weird. No, but saying I'm going to
eat pizza every day is a little weird. And then I go downstairs and I have like spinach
and pasta. I was thinking about getting a pepperoni pizza today. I am hungry though.
Am I going eight hours here? A quick question. I've only left this room one time in eight hours.
Is that true? Yeah, that did happen. Okay. All right. Yeah. I went to go get a glass of wine
like seven hours ago. Let me go pee and like get some water and maybe grab a snack.
I'll be right back. Didn't even pee. Yeah. No, I'll be right back. We'll finish up here.
See you very, very soon. Literally walked downstairs and Kim made pasta. He was already
ready. Beautiful. Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful. So I'm going to be a piece of crap
and I'm going to mute and paint walls. She's wonderful. Yes, she is. Oh, let's try this.
Paint the walls with pasta. Don't mute. No, I'm going to mute.
But 20% of the people that think this is funny, 80% of the people think this is
the worst thing they've ever heard in their life. It feels weird to sit here. I can't do it.
I'm so used to just talking. They're just staring at this. Hey, what's up? You guys
just hanging out too? I'm doing the equivalent of keyboard turning in World of Warcraft.
I'm playing with one hand. How's the pasta? I haven't even tried it. Let me try it.
Let's get a piece on here. Oh! What? Oh! It's the noise of all those bones breaking.
I can't even say this because that wouldn't even do it.
Cad said toenail in the pasta. Why would it make that loud of a noise? No, that was,
that was somebody dumped sand into your pasta. A lot of it. A point where you can visibly
see it on the plate. Let's go back to it. Sand pasta. That's disgusting. Just disgusting.
What was I doing with this? Oh, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right.
Then what should I do for the ground? What do I think? By the way, upstairs is going to be
just a giant bedroom. There's going to be a bed at the end of the hall and a bunch of
potted plants. Nice. I always hate when people have windows into the bathrooms. Especially,
maybe some of you guys have a house like this. If you go to somebody's house,
just making sure it wasn't crushed, who has a window in the bathroom at penile level where
you're peeing and there's a window that is at, it's like, it's at like balls level.
If that thing is not closed, if there's no curtain or even curtains, I feel like
somebody could see right through it. That's way more common than you think it is. I have
this weird fucked up fear of peeing in somebody's house that has a penile window.
And for some reason, I just think like the curtain or the blinds, somebody, you know how,
you don't have to go far enough away from blinds. You can kind of see a little bit.
I just have to feel like somebody is going to see right through one of the little cracks
of a Venetian blind and just see my penis. They don't even need to see me. They might
not even know who's in the bathroom. And like, I get out of the bathroom and it could have been
anybody. But that's, I don't like that. I don't like that. That's just, I don't want that.
He likes that. I don't like that. I don't like that. But it is, it is a little bizarre
when you go to a bathroom that is like that. Okay, almost done with the bathroom.
What are these doing need? Do they only, no, I'm just saying like through one of the
little blinds, they just, you know what I mean. This is a PG-13 stream. We don't have
to get into our related details. Yes, we do. No, we don't. PG-13 is not family friendly.
They say the F word. They say the S word. They say mean things. It's the same. Yeah.
You can say fuck at least once in a, yeah, you can say fuck one time in a PG-13 movie.
That's new. He did it twice. Oh no. All right. Remind me to not tile a wall ever again.
This takes as long as it takes to eat a bowl of pasta. It's a long time. A very long
time. Done. All right. So let's take another bite. I'm going to make the bathtub shower
and sink in the bathroom. Hmm. This is like a weird digital pixel room. I don't like it,
but whatever Stan. Actually trash. All right. Let's do a shower. Shower plumbing system.
What is this? Oh, we have to, oh, do you remember when I was talking about this game
and how I said that I really wish that it was, everything was pre-installed, everything.
This is like a year ago when we played this last. You couldn't do that before. Now you can.
So that's good. You can actually place the shower where you want to, not where they
deem it necessary. That's cool. It's a good change. A lot of sauce on this one. No, I'm
talking about on my pasta. That was a saucy one. I don't have a right flush against the
wall. Yeah, it's all right though. It's okay. In case like water gets back there and mold gets
back there, you can throw a towel back and drag it. Get a little mold. Beautiful toilet.
This game saves all the time now. Hmm. Ooh, this is nice. I need a mount. I need a mount
for the sink. Where's the mount for the sink? There it is. There. Okay. Now we can get that
cool sink. What was it down here? Yeah, this one's nice. No, no, that's not the one.
Here it is. I like this. It's got a weird bowl. I like it. Yeah, this is kind of a restaurant
bathroom. It's true. That's all right. Restaurant bathrooms are fucking awesome.
What do you mean? Incorrect? A nice restaurant's bathroom is really, really awesome
when they have these cool sinks all over the place. You don't think that
nice restaurants, bathrooms? I'm not talking about a Burger King. Toilet. A flatty or a standard.
I'll go with a flatty. Two toilets, two toilets. Yeah. You guys don't like that? I mean,
you guys use the same toilet every day? I usually use a different toilet every other day.
Keep the other one clean. I would have a toilet for every day of the week if I could.
All right, bathroom. Let's get some stuff in here. One for each cheek.
If that were the case, then you would just go right down in the middle.
If these were right next to each other, you would just go straight down.
Millionaires just buy a new mansion when theirs get dirty. Yeah, you don't have to be a
millionaire. They have two toilets in the same bathroom. Why does this stink so much? It's a
sink. Well, I heard the word restaurant bathroom, and then I got thinking, this house
sucks. And there's no, there's no room for another bathroom. Upstairs, there's not gonna
be, there's a, there's a, it's bedroom, bedrooms. I have a toilet to the kitchen.
The possibilities do open themselves up though. I have a toilet as each seat at
the dining room table. I think that's a good idea. That looks good. There's no mirror.
Uh, only one person gets a mirror. Actually, you can have one too. You, uh, just get to look
out the window. Okay, so this is the bathroom. The two stalls and the shower. This person doesn't
have very much privacy on this side, but, uh, you're okay. All right, so now let's get the
dining room table set up. Too far, right here. End of the stream. Joke. This is the end.
It's the end of the stream. I should have bought a table first. Hey, Lois!
We should put toilets in the dining room. Oh, freaking genius. Oh my fucking God.
That was fucking hilarious.
This is a nine, yeah, we've been going on eight and a half hours here.
This is a long one. This is a long one. Stop going through with it. It's too late now. Look,
I can easily just point a money gun at this and turn it off. Let's go black. Now it's a
torture house. Why would it be a torture house now? Okay, these are all the couches that are
in the game. This is that. This is a big couch. I don't think it was that big. Okay,
let's get, um, it's all right. Let's get a bookcase. Uh, this one here. Just to, you
know, brighten it up a little bit. A bag and a painting. What do you think? What's a good
painting? What do you guys like? Which one? The pink trees? Yeah, I agree. Look at this
little place. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Fridge. What is this? Oh, I thought this was a walk-in fridge.
I was like, what the fuck? That would be awesome. Oh, there's the red fridge.
Somebody wanted this really bad. Now you got it. Stove. All right, you need to have.
All right. I forgot. That's an old stove. Stanley fan. Nice. Looking good. Yeah. I'm
gonna put it on the counter. I'm in a sink. Mm-hmm. LOL. That was funny. All right,
let's get a counter. What the fuck is this? What the fuck is this? Get it up there.
Yes! Wow. I need like a little ladder. And I have an outdoor deck here. All right,
let me get some of the, hold on, some furniture. Like a chair, couch. Couple of
these things. These things are interesting, I guess, right? Yeah, some of these. Get a few
of them. This is a sick like recreation pool room. Hold on. And a gymnasium. Gym shit. Cross
trainer. That's fine like that. I can't put this inside. Outdoor gym. Okay, I need a bed.
This is not like the big pool room. And I'm painting up here like lightning electric rain.
Spring grass. Can the bed go on the balcony? I don't think I can put inside things outside
and outside things inside. Got it. Stop chewing. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm trying to discreetly do
it without anybody hearing me. Let's glitch to a well. Just painting over cinder blocks.
Kind of. Kind of, yes. That is true. Okay. No drywall. No, drywall. That's not really in the
game. You just pick what you want and do it. I actually like that color. This is a nice pool
color. Why does the paint make that noise? It's actually very accurate. It is shockingly
accurate to what it sounds like. Get those paint cans. We're getting close. Maybe like another 20,
30 minutes and we're going to be ready for the tour. And then I want to compare. I want
to watch a clip. I'm going to walk the same path that I walked in the clip. Do we have a
clip of when I did it? I want to watch it and then walk the same path. I want to put
it on screen and do it at the same time. Almost empty. He's going to react. Yeah,
I'm going to react to my own clip. I'm having a weird spot. I like the pool room.
It's a $12,000 pool. Seriously, if I don't get $600,000 or $700,000 with this house,
I'm going to be pretty upset. Let's do that thing again. Uh-oh. I think we're doing too
many assets in the game. It's starting to freak out. I have like 150 assets outside.
I might be slowing the engine down. I just saw the family guy clip from earlier and
wow. What do you mean? Why are you seeing that? Who is linking that to you?
You guys are already sharing that?
That's a lot. People will be mad if I miss these. It's happened before. All right,
one more wall and that's it. And then I got to put a bed downstairs.
Be mad. Why are you? Why? My clip has 66 views. Yeah, but I was doing like a dumb ironic stupid
like look at my Peter Griffin. I know how to do Peter Griffin. That's not my actual Peter
Griffin. That's not fair. Ironic. That was being ironic. The new slap. Hey, you don't
think that shit's intentional? Now I got some embarrassing fucking thing that you guys are all
sharing. No one's talking about the slap anymore. Pretty good tactic, don't you think?
All right, our pool room is done. Just need a bed and the floor needs to be done. It's
gonna be tile up here. If it's a pool, it's gonna be like that pool tile. Like this stuff
right here. It's not floor tile. God damn it. I thought it was floor. Floor tile. This one
looks kind of like a pool. No, it kind of sucks. This one? A little bit better. No,
it's gotta be white. Just classic white. White tile. That's better. You need to have stairs.
Yeah, I'll put stairs in the pool so you can get up and get up. How much is this costing?
A lot of money actually. Why do you have a YMCA in your house? Why not? Almost done.
Kind of awkward because I can't really reach in here. Over here. I'm no longer worth half
a million. I will be very soon once I sell this place. All right, I can't paint this because it
is glitched out, but here we go. Nice little pool. Let's actually put this in a different spot.
I have more room over here. Are we doing the same house? Yeah, we've been on the same house
for just about nine hours. I've spent what some would consider an entire day on this
house. An entire day. A whole day. I couldn't be happier with the outcome. What's the most
expensive painting you have in the game? That's actually pretty cheap. Upload a photo. I did that
last time and you can make it like 200 million dollars. I thought that was going to be a lot
bigger. All right. No, we're not going out there yet. You can't see out there. Let's get some
lights in here. Lamp. Go just like a standard cube lamp. This is fine. Make it like blue to
match the room. Wait, I need the stove counter. No, I'm not doing a second pool.
Um, what's it even called? Furniture? Installations? Kitchen? What is it?
Kitchen cabinet. Here we go. I was saying counter. That looks nice. Let's get a stove in here.
Let's get, yeah, let's get two of these. Let's do three. Get the stove on there. All right.
Pretty cool. Wait, why does it look odd? I already have a pizza oven. I don't need
none. All right. Let's get a light in here. Lamp. Skunk ball. Let's get a few of them
right up here. These are ugly. These are very ugly, but it's okay. It is light. That's all
that matters. And I got a lamp there. Let's get some recessed lighting up here, please. Thank
you. Tube. There we go. This place is ugly as sin. Any lights in here? Yeah, there are.
This is very ugly. It's very, very, very ugly. But, you know, we're at the end here.
I'm kind of tired. So are we gonna have a very ugly house? It's okay. It still looks all right.
It still looks good. All right. Are we ready for the tour? It's time. And I want to do this
at night and I want to do this at dark. Reverse that. I want to, okay. I want to do
this at night. I want to do this during the day. Don't look! Nobody look! Don't look at
nobody look. Okay. I want it to be daytime. There's no lighting in the garden. Oh, it
doesn't matter. Bed. Bed. I need a bed. Come on. I need just a little thing. There we go.
Perfect. Nice. Very nice. Wait, that door's open. Doors are closed. Closed. Closed. Closed.
Closed. Closed. Okay, here we go. All right. Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for joining us.
I'm not gonna play the family guy theme. No. There's the before clip. Let me see it. Oh,
it looks like shit. I'm just gonna have this loop silently so you can understand what's
going on here. Let me just get it on screen. Did anybody get any? I really do want like
screenshots though. So I'm gonna put time into this. I'm gonna make this real.
All right. Here is the before. Take a look at this dump. Trash everywhere. Boards. The whole
thing was condemned. Weeds growing all over the place. It was uninhabitable. This is the front
door right here. Dumpster over here on the right-hand side. You've got just dead grass.
Looks terrible. I was ashamed. But now. But now I am no longer ashamed. Here's what we have
here now. Let's take a walk to that right side where that dumpster was. Remember that dumpster?
Now it is a stone walkway with a nice picnic area for you and your kids. All that trash.
Nice fresh grass. We have a windmill farm here in the garden taking us to the right.
Some more little flowers there. Fucking door was open. When I do my tours,
you close all the goddamn doors. Through here we have the viewing area. This used to be with,
you know, as you can see. I'll put it back on the screen just so you can see just how bad
it was. Take a look at this right side here. Now there's a couch. Now there is a projector.
Two pizza ovens. Looks a lot different doesn't it? Looks much better. Yeah there's an outdoor
projection TV. Man but look at this backyard. Look at where we are. Fresh green. Trees. An
outdoor patio. A grill. A pool. A little kiddie pool. Completely redone. A fresh pond
with our little friends here. And our little group of flowers over there. We got a little
birdhouse. Small garden over here. Smoking area for those of you that smoke. Only smoke out
here please. And nowhere else. Letting us out to the garage area. This is the driveway.
Take a look at that. How do I turn the damn hut off? Another pond here. Hammock. I think
it looks phenomenal. Fresh driveway yeah? I'm like no I'm not crouching again. Can I go inside
the garage? Yeah just a second. All right in the garage we have nothing actually because
there was nothing built. There was something in there. Not letting the dog live inside. The
dog does live inside. Never mind. No what do I? No! Close this. Go back out. So let's take
a look inside your new home. You don't have to knock here. You own the place. Come on in.
This is yours. Close the door behind you so don't get too much drafty in here. Ah close that to
your left. Your space. Your area. Gaming lounge. You got three connections here. That seems like a
lot of cable. For what? Pretty believable off believable is the word that comes out of my
brain here. Pretty believable. Can we get a look at what it looked like inside? I don't
think we have that. We can get that off the screen just so you can you know we don't need
to see it anymore. Uh if you're wondering is this a joke? Well the no it's not. There actually are
toilet plumbing here. I just want to make sure I proved it to you in case you just didn't believe
me. Which I don't know why you wouldn't. Hold on just give me one minute. I gotta reinstall
the toilet here. Uh this is here for any family guy jokes that you'd like to make
or if you want to be at the table and use the bathroom at the same time. It's very
possible. Here's your kitchen area. You have uh right here this is a very interesting fridge.
Uh this is the fridge that uh one person over the last eight and a half nine hours
told me to put the red fridge in the game uh every 14 minutes. Get it finally. Over here
you got your stove and your freeze musical cabinets. Microwave for those nights that you
just don't feel like cooking. There's a no oven. No oven. Well we passed the two pizza
ovens so but the real treat is up the stairs. Careful now slowly. Okay okay you can take the
blindfold off because up here oh wait no fuck um no no no no come back downstairs come back
downstairs come back downstairs all the way back outside god damn it. Why'd they have a fucking
blindfold on you? Okay take take take the blindfold off and look at what you see. Didn't
look nice look over on your you know just get back in here get back inside. I love god they
make these stupid ass shows. I just want to show the fucking house. Up here yeah yeah whatever
you guys there's a pool it's a big pool up here it's a nice pool. I forgot to put stairs on
here hold on a second. Pretty handy. You can't. Hey you're gonna have my handy ladder.
All right there you go. Some of the crew left it. Out here you've got your whole entire zone
you can see it all. What about the front? Let's take a look at the front of the balcony.
Oh yeah. Don't jump don't jump don't jump off there. There's your house. Now let's see what it's
worth. What is your house worth? American Crop English. Modern. I got five stars for the layout.
I mean zero. This you can't even get this on Yelp. That's not fair. And I picked the wrong
category wrong category wrong no no don't do not. Reparticipate in the garden competition
in 10 minutes. Is it 10? It's 10 real life? What does that say?
What does that say? Get good. I don't know if that even says. Fix the wall. What wall? There's
a lot to fix man. There's a lot more than just it ain't just the wall. Add some plants for
fuck's sake. Oh I know that's you just messing around. So uh we're gonna do the bits and
I'm gonna try again. So this is gonna be 10 hours. This might actually be it's it's been a
while since I've done 10 hours. Move the office here? I absolutely will move the office here.
I had a perfect opportunity to do like a pretend Skype with grandma show her the house thing.
Okay you're walking up. You see grandma? This is the neighborhood. Oh wow that looks great.
What's that over there on the right side? Oh here here. I want to see that.
Oh is it are those real animals? No grandma those are those are stone that's made of the stones.
Oh yeah it's red beautiful. That's absolutely beautiful. Come over here grandma. Okay I'm not
gonna do the whole bit again. You know you get it. My friend did the virtual tour with
this place before it was annoying. Yeah hey take a look around I've got this room and that
room. All right let's do the bits. I will see you guys later. What's today? It's Friday.
Can't sell it? You can sell it. I'll just move my office back to the dump. That's fine.
Oh it is technically it is currently Saturday. Friday night house flipper? No no no no.
Sell it now? I but I want to do the garden thing again. I feel like I picked the wrong
one. It's only like 10 minutes. We've been here for nine hours. What's another eight
minutes? So what we'll probably do is this one will take us to about 10 plus hours.
I'll probably just I'll probably take tomorrow off and then we'll come back on Sunday.
Technically well today is Saturday technically right so Saturday is technically now
so Sunday so tomorrow technically which is Sunday. Yeah or maybe I don't know maybe not.
Maybe. Maybe we'll just go tomorrow. It depends. Depends on what time I fall asleep
and get up you know. Let me see what's going on tomorrow morning. Come back in 10 minutes.
Yeah we'll see. I mean if tomorrow my you know my energy's up I'm good. I do have to plan
around. I need to look at a calendar again because this is gonna get weird
because I have to take the end of this next week off because of my colonoscopy.
To yeah we'll see just just keep an eye on the sus so I have to I'm gonna I have to like move
some things around but there may or may not be a stream where I'll just check the sus tomorrow
afternoon and if there is if I stream tomorrow then we're gonna do a DOS MS DOS. Go back to
DOS night. Are you serious? Yeah I gotta I have the colonoscopy yeah the whole thing
they're doing the whole thing how long has it been can I not do the garden thing yet
I think I have to just wait all right I'm gonna mute this and we'll do the bits while we wait to
do the garden one more time I'm gonna pick the other one and then I'm gonna sell the house
can't wait for the colonoscopy stream that's not gonna happen so if you want to see how
much the house is gonna be worth stick around for like another 20 30 plus minutes or so
and that'll be the last thing I do before I turn off the stream see you probably Saturday
Sunday see you tomorrow at some point whenever that ends up being thanks for watching as always
thankfully the internet was able to be stable for most of the stream I'm very happy to hear
that so much love to you if you're taking off if you're sticking around we've got some
bits to do earlier rewind the clock almost the whole day ago we had uh four dolls from
Noxy excited for scare Saturday tomorrow fortunately there will not be a scare Saturday
oh fuck the game is paused holy shit thank you for saving me
thank you for the four dolls and no scare Saturday sorry sticks renegade thanks for
the 255 no matter where you are in life even if you have nothing to your name
always get the two ply toilet paper yeah Charmin Ultra Soft is I think you get that
it's like get that or we'll go home that's the best one it is good you're all right
uh Juno upseto thanks for the two dollars and 50 cents you're being upset about a shadow on
your lawn is like old man yells at a cloud yeah but I wanted to make it look good I got a
little neurotic I tend to do that though ultra strong I actually don't use ultra strong these
ultra soft but thank you Juno thank you after looks atrix for the 250 without letting
chat know I said this ask them okay well who would get this wrong watch the geniuses debate
this they they asked what is two plus two I mean everyone would get that I would get that
wrong not very many people uh rambling jan thanks for the five dollars a house-sized pizza
oven as in a house-sized pizza um yes please no just regular pizzas but a lot of them
at least like seven or eight could fit in there but thank you for the five dollars
rambling jan smelly boy thanks for the 250 is this the streamer that turned house flipper
into Minecraft accidentally but yes it was on accident the 115 dollars it was 11,500 bits from
Hayden clip fell it was a lot of money it was earlier it was way earlier I'm not even sure
if this is still here but that was a shitload of money thank you for your huge bit drop there
much appreciated also thank you to invader z21 thanks for the five dollars hey Jeremy
your videos always make me happy when I'm upset or have had a rough day at work thanks for helping
me relax and have a laugh sometimes absolutely thank you for being part of the community
thanks for thinking the videos and the streams are worth watching thanks glad they make you
happy thank you for the five dollars thank you frody and weapon for the 250 I've done a voice
that sounds so similar to that one it's scary talking about Peter the Peter Griffin the ironic
Peter Griffin laugh that people thought I was that clip is going to get deleted thank you for
the 250 though appreciate it for rhodium firestar thanks for the 10 bucks germa can you fix my
parents marriage I cannot I'm sorry uh complicated relationships I can't help you there I can't sorry
I'm just telling you the truth we appreciate your honesty yeah I'm not a professional I can't
help awful streamer not a licensed therapist uh no but thank you firestar for the 10 dollars
if serious then I'm sorry that you're going through that right now but if joke
fucking laughing about it a little bit right now thank you for the 10 bucks
hey winz rind thank you paint the top story a different color than the bottom
yeah people are saying that maybe I should have just that I made the family guy house
like an idiot but thank you uh dr low note had 10 community subs earlier thanks for the drop of
10 a lot of subs thank you dr low note thank you dork cube for the 250 um back with bits
thanks for doing this family guy stream peter is my spirit animal and I want to be a cool
gamer just like him hey could you do some of those voices again like lois thanks maybe next
you can do cleveland no I'm not going to do any one of those thank you for the 250 and
I'm happy to give you the family guy stream thanks for the 250 no I'm not doing family
guy voices those get me in trouble even when I'm doing them ironically they get me in trouble
thank you have gun for the 350 hey germa I graduated from law school last Sunday
and your streams in second germa have helped me keep me mentally stable for the last three
years your unique brand of comedy and insight has helped me stay free of depression and has
encouraged me to do well I now go to face the bar exam in two months thank you germa for being
the great guy that you are there are lawyers who watch I'm telling you a lot of smart people
watch this stream lawyers doctors scientists uh good luck it seems like you've been working
real hard to get where you are now so hopefully you ace it and good luck in the future there
that's a really really promising career thank you so much for the 350 70 IQ chat is a hundred
is a bunch of lawyers we better get the colonoscopy streamer I can't do a colonoscopy stream I'll get
banned from twitch uh flim flam gave 30 dollars earlier thanks for the 3000 bits 30 bucks
really appreciate that they say hey oh hey jim hope you're doing well my birthday's coming up
and my wish is for you to try a wine I like oh absolutely it's called 19 crimes it's a red
blend mild flavor and smoother than your voice's bounded bounced off a baby seal oh I thought red
blend mild flavor smoother than your voice bounced off a baby seal made of silk also lucky 19 crimes
I will buy it immediately the next time I find myself well I mean we usually go to the liquor
store is it widely available or is it something I have to get specially ordered online or
something because maybe once every few months we'll go to the liquor store and stock up on stuff
I see it everywhere all right 19 crimes red blend I love red blends my favorite red blend
and uh malbec are my two favorite wines malbec probably a little bit more than a red blend but
malbec is also something you don't drink just sitting here streaming you just drink it like
at dinner it's common all right yeah I'll definitely try it that will be the next wine
that I buy I promise hell yeah thanks for the 30 bucks and happy upcoming uh birthday
that was flim flam thanks for the 30 dollars what was that whiskey that you like uh blue
yeah johnny walker blue if you like scotch johnny walker blue is the it's my favorite
essentially I just like it I mean I don't drink it all the time my boomer dad drinks
that johnny walker is this like four or five different kinds of johnny walker I would
definitely say johnny walker blue is my favorite yeah how is johnny walker boomer no like crown
royal is boomer I know they're different but like when I think of like a whiskey like a boomer
whiskey I got a crown royal nice I love crown royal and I'm young see what did we learn
today we learned that these assumptions are don't are meaningless fireball uh no no I
can't do fireball it's just like I mean I can but I just don't they I did not sell the house
yet again I'm only a little bit longer to go but thank you flim flam happy birthday uh zalks
thank you zalks for the five dollars hey just graduated high school today thought I'd give
back for the years of entertainment take care of Jeremy thank you congratulations on
graduating high school that's a big step in your life time to turn the page I wish you
the best of luck congratulations on graduating high school thank you for your five dollars
allow me toast allow me toast thanks to the 250 while I was watching your stream a man broke
into my house through my window and said germa is a terrible builder and shouldn't be allowed
in your homes now the man's name was grill master xbbq how do you know that did he
announce himself as that was he wearing the same clothes did he have like a bag on his
head and how do you who is it how do you know hey silver flame thanks for the 250 germa
I'm really drunk right now and I can't stop eating toast don't eat too much of it
toast is good but you don't want to eat too much bread but I just want to say that you
are a funny man to be deep for a moment you helped mold my sense of comedy you're a great
dude and I'll watch you until the day you somehow get yourself banned from twitch kind of
good luck with the colon surgery you're in my thoughts anyways I'm going to tell that
girl that I mentioned yesterday that I'm interested in a relationship wish me luck
or don't you'll always be my true love but and it ends
but what happens what what happened next I need to know what's the next part
what happened after that that's a yeah that's a cliffhanger thank you silver flame for the 250
I'm honored to be somebody that you think is molding your sense of humor
I would just hope that I hope that means I hope that means a good thing
and I hope I don't get banned from twitch I don't plan on it
but thank you drink some water we also had ten dollars from velemi
velemi ten dollars germa this yard is over designed I just was making like an amusement
park thank you for the ten dollars I agree I think it still looks nice zero out of ten
not enough plants uh thank you the jewish bro for the three dollars germa you got to see this
um I'm just I'm sorry I don't click links the only links that I click are very clear
imger reddit or youtube links or clips this is like an app.goo.google with a bunch of weird
letters I have a very clear policy that is not stated anywhere that is not written anywhere
google goo goo they just say germa you gotta see this why is it such a weird link
images.app.goo.goo why is it such a weird link it's a strange link paste it I'll take
the bullet don't do it don't I don't understand sense danger I know it's not malicious I mean
this uh they've been around for a while I just I never like to click links that are not
clear imger reddit or like youtube links I'm sorry that's just the way it is I'm sorry
link shorteners can pull you they just can same but I'm also desensitized by exposure yeah but
if we can get that in a uh like dick okay I'm I'm just gonna pretend I just said uh my friend
my friend dick my friend Richard he's a cool person he's really nice is it it's the picture
of me kissing myself now I'm glad I didn't open it and I'm chewing I'm sorry I've seen that
image like a thousand times have you guys seen the speaking of google and AI and robots
did you guys see the thing where they can now take a photo even a photo from like the 1800s
and they can make it look like the person's moving around and talking have you seen that
shit we're going to get to a stage in the next 10 maybe five to ten years where somebody will
be able to make you do and say whatever they want in 10 years we'll have such unbelievably
good doctored footage we already have that yeah somebody can just put your like take an
image of your face and with a computer it's just wild I when I saw somebody like tweeted
or something I looked at it and I said well this is our children's children will be making each
other fortnight dance even when they didn't want to I mean can you imagine a world where I get
tweeted at me me doing a fortnight dance that I never did and me being like fortnight man cool
fortnight default dance and I didn't do any of these things imagine that was possible right
now the agony that I would have to go through oh shit now they have the voice
I can be manipulated now but thank you to honeychain for the 250 can you tell the story
about the time star left an empty coffee cup in your hood I don't think I've heard it from your
perspective you know what I mean it's just one it wasn't that big of a deal we were at like a
computer store and we were walking around asking questions and he put his empty coffee
cup in the back of my hood I didn't know it was there so walking around talking to
employees of this place and finally after like it was at least like 10 to 20 straight
minutes or so I don't know maybe less than that of me looking like a dickhead I just have an empty
coffee cup in my hood and I'm like walking around oh can you show me like the i7 4770k please
oh yeah sure right this way sir they just I had to I walked in front of him at least a few
times I didn't know we put it in there so eventually I he was laughing or I don't know
somebody was looking somebody was looking at it or I feel it was there I knew it was there
and I just grabbed it we were with a bunch of like employees and a couple of managers because
they had to get the key to open up the thing to get like the cpu processor or whatever a
graphics card and I just grabbed the coffee cup and I looked at him I said you're a
fucking asshole and then everybody stopped and it was just like whoa and I was like no I
did like what I just I called it like a fucking asshole oh well I was like oh you're
a fucking prick it was something like that no like yeah in a jacket like in my hood
something he's got a photographic memory I mean I remember a lot of things and I don't know he
thought it was the funniest thing ever because I was I shut the whole store out I turned off all
the manager all the managers faces I went like whoa holy fuck and like 10 seconds later we were
fine it was just like oh so what's the i7 70 oh yeah right here hey that's crazy I remember
things too can you believe it we have a superpower we already went over this but thank
you honey chain uh Vilemi again thanks for ten dollars thank you Vilemi you did all that
gardening while spy crabbing I can't believe I spent a majority of the stream crouched
that's unbelievable it had to have been at least a few hours at the very least but thank
you almost to the end of the bits and then we'll do the garden contest sell the house
while we run the credits uh thank you cad cad btv 250 honey I think the real estate
agent is stoned smelly boy thanks for the 250 dog woke me up because of storm it's 3 15 a.m
and I guess I'll be here till like five good morning germ of pain honey I shrunk the real estate
agent I'll give that one to you you can have that one but uh storm hopefully it's not too
bad welcome though thank you smelly boy I've always wondered if you guys you like star
italics call each other by your real names outside of the streams it's actually kind of
hard it's kind of hard to do to do that it's weird to explain that but I I call like for instance um
orb you guys know incredible orb right he was here for edc and we hung out he's the person
that I picked up from the airport I think did I say that or maybe I didn't uh because he's an
old friend we know each other for a long time but I don't I call him orb it's just orb hey
what's up orb I call him it's just it just that's all I've known him as my friends call
each other by our online names my sister and her husband too it's not weird not that weird
it's understand it's almost like a nickname it's a nickname that has been um it's almost like
you know in the game of thrones like oh you're a bastard but I could make you uh like you
maybe in the world of like a song of ice and fire right a king can make somebody well
you're no longer like this person I'm going to name you you can be like named back in like the old
like 1400s you could be like named to have like your actual name instead of just be you know the
your online id this is a really bad analogy I think I'm too tired to explain this because
I here's what happened I'll tell you exactly what just happened right there so I was just
talking about I didn't want to like go off in a game of thrones because I was terrified that
I didn't want to like have anybody say anything because I mean the show just ended so I
started to talk about like a real a really good analogy but like I didn't want to talk about the
show so then I was like I was like so I have a bit of an evil so I don't want to talk about
that and then I kind of gave up 1400s is medieval times so I didn't want to like
have people talk about like oh game of thrones let's talk about that you know what I'm saying
long story short uh it's not like that weird I don't think to call somebody people come
in germa all the time even like personal friends of mine but even before being online
germa germa hey what's up germ like my father my like parents call me that hey germ so I mean it's
not out of the ordinary thing I don't think yeah it's just a nickname the infection is spreading
all right we only got a couple more we got uh cad btv for the 250 I can't wait for the
colonoscopy stream here's a working title down the germa hole you can have that one for free
no I'll get I will get permaband from twitch if I stream my colonoscopy and plus I don't want
to stream that because like what if there's like shit that I need to talk to the doctor about
what if there's stuff that's it what if like something happens no no I don't want
anyone to know that that's like no streaming on youtube then no I'm not streaming it at all
but thank you hey night team 14 thanks for the five dollars and one cent the stream was
amazing as always you never fail to make my day better even if this year has been the absolute
worst thanks for everything I really mean it I'm sorry that you're having a bad year hopefully
it turns around for you soon uh thanks for hanging out I'm glad you think this is fun
and entertaining and interesting that means a lot to me so thank you for the five dollars
hope uh hope shit turns around for you I really do but thank you uh thank you pair
pair pair for the five dollars could the colonoscopy stream be audio only so you don't
get I'm not doing a colonoscopy stream you guys gotta get off this I'm not doing a colonoscopy stream
yeah that's somehow worse yeah it is he won't let us into his life oh god all right and last
but not least clueless sniper for 250 thank you thanks for the two dollars and 50 cents
clueless sniper right at the end here so we're gonna throw the credits on the screen
while I sell the house into the garden one more time and I will see you guys it is 1 a.m
pacific we'll be out of here in about 10 minutes probably uh so keep an eye on the sus I'm gonna
get some sleep and we we may or may not it's like a 70 30 like 70 percent yes we will 30
no so it probably will be a stream tomorrow we'll just maybe it won't be as long because
we've been going for like nine and a half almost 10 hours now so let's do the garden
contest I'm still here I did not pause the game so uh how do we do this change the tool
how do I sell the house oh no the computer hold on wait what is this oh this is our this is
oh we get wait we have to do this too hold on let me um where's my laptop make this the office
oh I forgot we this is what we did yesterday look at how this is not that bad I'm still
learning look at this I didn't quite figure out how to roll the uh the turf out had a
little problem here too a lot of real estate out here oh shit there's a mole I'm not like
it matters I hear the different ovens this is the charcoal oven I don't know and then the
wood fire oven what was in the house oh yeah this is the weird cramped weird pt house I
didn't like this at all yeah yeah this place sucks you'd have to knock down a few walls
to make this place really any good all right so let's go back and let's do the garden
contest so this one was a hundred and eighty three thousand dollars let's go here how okay
let's see hundred and eighty three thousand twenty three grand for renovation and thirty
one grand for furniture so it's three four fifty yeah so I spent a lot of money here
yeah that's what it looked like before this was nine almost nine plus straight hours doing
this I mean maybe I could have done it faster but we were just kind of having a good time
so all right here we go so what should I do I did modern should do English crop let's get the
credits on these are all the new subs thank you everybody let's get you down here while we run
this everybody for stopping you guys are fucking amazing thank you as always should be American
there's no pools though English oh what equipment what am I missing for equipment here
I'm gonna sell it I feel I but should I this took a long time I want to be able to visit
this house though to 20 or 25 that's like nothing 11 grand I made more money flipping
the home alone house no I refuse what I'm keeping it mine time to move in again all right
I'm sorry but the pool alone is $12,000 oh this one bed that's why right and you shit at the
dinner table yeah I mean that you these things are saying are not untrue getting the pool out
of this house alone makes the price irrelevant yeah let's get this back up in the middle here
that's a good spot for it also there's no toilet paper why do I have to provide the toilet
paper to a new owner of a house that's not a deal breaker wait they didn't have toilet paper
on a roll in the bathroom no I don't think I want that house all right guys I'll see you later
keep an eye on sus we'll see what we do tomorrow if there's no stream tomorrow then
there'll be one on Sunday we'll see see how I feel in the morning take care have a great night