Is it really appropriate that we're both naked men?
Yes it is. It is appropriate.
Nah, you ain't taking that box. Put it back.
Come here, can I bash you in the face with this?
Oh shit!
Alright, explain what world does a box do more like knockback and damage than a fucking showerhead?
Dude, I'm gonna kill you!
No! Up!
Hey there!
Wait a minute, I can't even lift you up.
I need to get food!
I need to get like Cheetos to like rescue you!
No!
Where's the Cheetos?
Is there like any like dirty sodas anywhere around here?
We haven't gotten out of like the tutorial.
If you hadn't killed me with that cardboard box, we wouldn't be in this situation.
Oh wait, hold on, I'm coming. Hold on, don't worry.
I brought you some like potato chips.
This should heal all your wounds. A bag of fucking potato chips.
Oh, thanks, thanks.
I can't find anything.
You're gonna be there for a while. I'm in like the game right now.
Hold on, just hang tight.
So far my perspective of this game is like a concrete ground.
These cabinets over here look great.
Hold on, I'll find you something.
This cream.
There we go. I got you a large soda.
What if I can make it? Oh shit!
Get off me! I gotta bring my friend like a drink!
No shit, I just drank it!
Shit!
No!
I benched my...
Oh shit!
Hold on, strong attack was what?
I just saw strong attack.
Oh shit, I'm sorry.
Did I seriously just almost kill you again?
No, dude. No, no, we're not gonna do this again.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Just go, just go, just go.
We're gonna cause way too many problems here.
I can't believe I almost just killed you.
I'm gonna throw this at you.
Yeah, come on, come on. Come fuck around.
Yeah, nice toss. Nice toss.
It actually pains me.
I can't believe I'm gonna make you like the Incredible Hulk.
Don't kill me, don't kill me.
We've had enough. I have a propane tank.
Oh, you have a propane tank, huh? Is that what you have?
Why can't we stop this?
No, if I go die, we're gonna have to do this all over again.
It's all up to me. Go get the drink.
It's all up to you. Just go get a drink.
And it's all up to me, he says.
He's all up to me and then he dies.
I didn't even get out the door.
You didn't even get out the fucking door.
Please stop killing each other.
No, no. When you give people this type of freedom with this amount of items,
there's no way you're gonna get out the front door.
Grab a bunch of stuff.
All the food's in here, like orange juice and shit.
Oh, you wanna have a little breakfast party?
Mustard.
Let's go, let's go. I got enough water for the both of us.
Hey, do you think we can get any computer games you can play out here?
Move.
Dude, oh.
Move, I want this milk or whatever.
Oh, you want this? Yeah, okay, thanks, I'll take it.
Careful!
No, I want, can we just please, can we just please play Team Fortress 2 on the computer?
Can I get the damn milk?
Hold on, I don't wanna play, look at this.
Okay, here we go.
Do-do-do-do-do, boom, boom, boom.
I got a more headshot, I got a, I'm the best.
Get me out of this room.
I don't think we can keep this person alive.
You don't think we can?
I won't bet money on it.
Okay, well.
Because we're not gonna, we're gonna get distracted by something.
Well, just try, I want the extra points.
I want like the double points.
I want the triple points.
Let's go then.
She is being surrounded right now, do you not see this?
And then all my stuff's broken.
And someone's biting my penis.
Uh, maybe not.
Maybe not.
I'll just wait over here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, there's more people in here.
They're having like a reunion.
They're like hugging each other and stuff and there's zombies everywhere.
What the hell are they doing?
Dude, you don't like, you don't hug it out during a zombie apocalypse in like a room full of 30 zombies.
Let's go.
We don't have time.
Let's go, Gordon.
Come on, Gordon.
Come on, Gordy.
What the hell are they doing?
Oh, shit.
What?
That's not what I thought I was equipping.
What do you mean?
Aren't you so pretty.
They look like, I don't know, just like plaid shirts.
Well, can you stop like trying on like women's clothing and come like fight these guys?
These people are dying.
I gotta take care of them.
Oh, my God.
We got two people dying.
I'm fighting off a zombie apocalypse and you're trying on women's clothing.
I have the only loaded gun.
Yeah, you're the only person with a gun.
Thanks for the help.
Oh, shit.
Don't worry, I got you.
Well, Lashandra's almost dead.
Can we just go?
I would really appreciate that if you would get over here.
I don't have any weapons left.
And Lashandra takes a wild swing at my face and kills me.
Dude, what the hell was the point of that?
Will you quit trying on shoes and get over here?