Hey, what's happening everybody? Jerma here with something a little different today.
This is not my typical video that I would make, but I decided to do it because I got
approached by this company. They're a super cool bunch of guys over at DorkCube and it is
the DorkCube. Take a look at it. This is a monthly subscription box that comes in the mail
and you buy it, you open it, and there's all kinds of nerdy, geeky, epic, kind of funny
gamer culture type stuff inside and I thought I should get one and you should open it for you
and you know give these guys a shout. Give these guys a shout out and give you guys a shout out
and we'll give them a shout out. This is DorkCube. I don't know what's inside of it. I have no idea.
They sent it to me so we're going to see what's inside. A link will be in the description.
If you want 2% off your next order, it's $20. So save a little bit of cash, you know, save you guys
looking out for you guys. You know what I mean? All right, you know, let's make this let's make
this a little interesting. How about that? Right when the box opens, how about everybody writes
hashtag in the comments, LOOTGAP. You know what I mean? Like we got loot, you know, that's what
we'll do. So in the comments section below, right when this opens, everybody say LOOTGAP!