I was here. For the game awards? I was here. Hi everybody. Welcome to the game awards pre-show.
And the game awards pre-show, I thought the game awards started at 5 30. No, it actually starts at
six. So I mean, I guess we could see what's gonna happen before the show starts. But I think we'll
probably just talk about Minecraft for like a half an hour. Because I was gonna do that anyways.
Now people probably going, why would you talk about Minecraft for a half an hour? This is a
perfect opportunity to do it. But I want to make sure a lot of people are here to see it.
We have a lot of important things to discuss. Because the fuck the king stream is very, very,
very rapidly approaching. We're going to go over it. We'll talk about it. We'll see it. Well,
actually, what are they? What do they do? They start on time? That's a better question. Did
they start on time? No, it's a black screen. No, that's like an ad. What is this? What's this?
What's this an ad for? I can't even hear it. What is this? To the Twitch partner program.
We got partner boys. Twitch ad. Should I not be showing this? Who just gifted like a thousand subs?
Wow. Thank you so much for the 10,000 bits. Thank you so much. All right, we're gonna
let's go back to this. Wait, hold on. The whole purpose for that was to see what was going on
on their stream. Don't do it again. They're late. They're late. It's supposed to start at 5 30. It's
going to start at like 5 36. See? See? Even like a multi-million dollar production is six to seven
minutes late. So come on. Their broadcast probably costs like five million bucks. Right now,
Jeff Keely is about to write in his chat. Oh, gosh. There's internet problems here, guys.
Cox is fucking up. I gotta let Otto up. Hold on. I'll be back. I forgot to go to the bathroom today,
guys. Give me like another 10 minutes. Have I eaten food today? No, I haven't. I ate a
microwave burrito three days ago. I have to eat. Facecam, please. Everybody wants the facecam
turned on for some reason. We got three minutes to the game awards. Oh, we gotta talk about
Minecraft. Right. All right. Minecraft. I gotta get something on the screen. Forget about the game.
The pre-show. It's like the it's going to the movies. Okay. If you've been to the movies more
than once or twice in a month, you've seen all the previews. So, but the third movie you go to
in the month of December is going to be the same previews that you saw two weeks ago. You know,
who cares? You've already seen it. You've already seen the trailer for Gemini Man 15 times. You
don't need to see it again. So we're going to talk about Minecraft. Yes, I do. No, you don't.
I got to turn off actually. No, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. This is important.
This is really actually important to me. What time is it? I'm sitting here for two minutes.
I want to see if they start in two minutes. I hope the counter goes up. I hope the counter
goes up like another three minutes. I'm going to sit here for two minutes. We're not going to
watch like a second of the pre-show just to make sure we're clear on this. Why is everybody calling
me a villain? Because I decided that today I was going to relax today. But that makes me a villain.
Oh, you want to just like take a load off and relax. Don't comb your hair back. It's it sets
there. I like the way that it sets. It's this. This is what I do on my days off. Listen to this
epic music. People are giving subs and shit. Splarg gave five community subs. And, and,
and something else happened too. What else happened? Right now something happened.
I don't have notifications on because this is a video game award. So I'm just going to give
a hundred dollars. Uh, Freddie Dredd, 10,000 bits. Thank you, Freddie Dredd.
A hundred fucking, uh, 10,000 bits. Can I be in that ad? 10,000 bits.
What? Uh, no, but seriously, that's a lot of fucking money. Thank you, Freddie.
40 seconds. Thanks for the hundred dollars. We haven't even gotten started yet. There's
nothing on the screen yet. All right. Here are my predictions for game of the year.
Game of the year. I got to say it now before we, before everybody else comes on the camera,
that's not me and tells you their predictions. Game of the year. Resident Evil 2. If Resident
Evil 2 does not win game of the year this year, games, gaming is dead. Video games are dead.
It's over. If Resident Evil 2 does not win. That's a fact. Okay. Let's see. It's five,
it's five 36 right now. Here it comes. Oh, it's not ready. What's going on?
Host for the game awards 2019 pre-show. The game awards will begin at the top of the hour
featuring musical performances by Green Day. Green Day's here? And brand new looks at ghosts
of Tsushima and Gears tactics. But while the Microsoft feature fills in behind me and the
world gets their popcorn ready, we've got 30 minutes of awards, special guests, and world
premieres of our own right here in the pre-show, including a brand new trailer for Final Fantasy
VII Remake. Haven't they shown a new trailer for this game like the last five years? By handing
out our first trophy of the night. And this is a special one. The game awards have a new category
this year to honor the teams that honor their community. The best community support award goes
to a game that listens, reacts, and responds to its players with respect and transparency.
The nominees for best community support are Apex Legends. Best community? Oh, okay. This is the
company that patches their game the most. But what if the game is broken and fucked up from the
beginning? And the winner is? Does that make you, I guess, what patches? It's gonna be Fortnite
season two. Destiny 2. They were right, they were right there. Congratulations. Thank you very much.
This is a, this is really an honor. I gotta acknowledge the people at Bungie who've worked
so hard to, you know, support our community, starting with our community team, who are on
the front lines every day interacting with our fans, the core development team, our operations folks,
like, everyone up and down just cares so much about this game, and I just, I gotta acknowledge
all their hard work. I don't play it, no. The only thing I'd add is everyone here creates
entertainment, and what use is creating entertainment if you don't have awesome fans, so
special thanks to our fans. That's amazing. Well, congratulations again. Thank you so much. Thank
you. What, was Reggie playing Destiny 2? I didn't know it won. Huge congratulations to Destiny 2
for winning our first ever best community support award. I'm sure it's no coincidence they are also
up for the best ongoing game later tonight. Now, the game awards is a show about celebrating all
of gaming. I haven't paid any attention so far. Throughout the night, you'll see unexpected
additions to games you love, check-ins on games you're anticipating, and reveals you never saw
coming. Here's the first of many world premieres. First preview. I can sense a great cosmic
disturbance. We must be prepared for the worst. Time to change history for the better.
Oh my god, that was so fucking loud, and it was all my fault. I'm so sorry guys, that was all my
fault. I turned it up by turning something up over there. That was seriously like somebody just
punched you in the face. Like, I just punched you in the face. Oh my god, I'm so sorry.
Our first world premiere. Didn't this game already come out? I thought this game already came out.
I will blend things. Rise of the feast. Oh, there's no Marvel Ultimate Alliance. Right,
right, right, right, okay. Oh, I gotta turn the camera off when that happens.
In 2018, the game awards teamed up with Facebook Gaming to honor global gaming citizens. People
from all areas of gaming who use the power of games to create a positive influence. Tonight,
I'm joined by one of the global gaming citizens we met last year who has a new project to show us.
Please welcome Luol Mayen. Thank you so much. Thank you so much. Yeah. So Luol, what have you
been working on? Yeah, for sure. You know, as someone from Africa and also as a refugee,
I want to thank everybody that has been supporting me to come up with a game today.
Facebook Gaming, Eisenbeck, and Luol Deng. I've been working on a game that actually put a player
in the shoes of a refugee. It's a game that actually talk about journey and helping people
to understand their empathy and this is something that video game can be able to do around the world.
We can be able to change the world and help people around the world and see what whatever
they're going through through playing video game. So it's a game really that put a player in the
shoes of refugees and bridging the reality world and what is actually happening on the ground.
So I'm really so excited about the project. Incredible. Well, let's take a look. Yeah,
sure. We got a trailer? Why would I turn the camera on for the trailer? Because games are
very powerful to create empathy and to help people understand a journey of a refugee.
Growing up in a refugee camp, my mother spent three years looking for $300 to buy a computer.
Then I taught myself how to create a video game. My mission in creating Salam is to let the world
know what it's like to be a refugee. When you buy medicine and food in the game, it goes to real
refugees, refugees like me. Together, we can take small steps to make a big difference.
What is Facebook Instant Games? It's so great to show you games like Salam. We have such a unique
opportunity here at the Game Awards to shine our spotlight on games big and small. Look forward
to seeing some more interesting Indies later tonight. This next Game Awards category also
demonstrates this kind of diversity in gaming. The nominees represent completely different budgets,
nationalities, and genres, but they all share one thing, excellent music. Here are the nominees
for best score in music. Cadence of Hyrule. They're really running. They're really sprinting.
Death Stranding. It's going to be Kingdom Hearts 3 because of like, it's going to be Kingdom Hearts 3.
Devil May Cry 5. It's going to be Kingdom Hearts 3. Kingdom Hearts 3.
Right. Listen to that. Listen to me. And Sayonara Wild Hearts.
And the winner is... This is unfair though. See, even she's like, yeah. Death Stranding.
Oh shit. I was going to say it's like Disney songs. You can't compete with Let It Go.
I don't know what to do. I like your colors. Oh my gosh. Thank you so much. I like your colors
as well. How are you feeling? I've been nervous this whole week and I can't believe this is
happening right now. I just want to say big thanks and shout out and also a congratulations
to Low Roar Churches and Southern Poets for helping us. I'm talking about Minecraft. All right.
Why am I talking about Minecraft? I'm just super happy to be here and I'm super thankful
for all the fans who inspired us to do something super weird and I hope we can
keep on doing weird shit going forward. All right. We'll do it after.
I think we all hope that. We only got like 16 minutes. I needed like 30 to talk about this.
For the past two E3s, there's been one game featured in the PC gaming show that continues
to fill our imagination with endless possibilities. I'm talking, of course, about Maneater,
the game where you are a killer shark that eats people. If you're hungry for more Maneater,
here's a new world premiere. What is Maneater? This is the first time I've ever heard anyone
talk about this. Hey, gamers. You know that thing that we've never spoken about? Here it is.
But only five humans are killed by sharks. It's time to even the score.
Isn't this game on Newgrounds right now? It's a Newgrounds game.
Can I evolve legs? I'll play it if I can get legs to walk around and I get in a car and drive
around. All right. Stephen Curry will be here tonight to award the best esports player of 2019,
but for now, I have the honor of acknowledging the winners for some esports categories.
For best esports coach, the nominees are Adrian, Kane, Koma, Soksha, and Zonic.
And the winner is Zonic. So do we only use handles now? The nominees are the 2019
League of Legends World Championships. I based this on which one of these I actually watched,
and I didn't watch any of them. I think, no, no, no, I caught like maybe two hours of EVO.
How many, how many fans does this game have?
I wish they would show what they're like in brackets their name. And for best esports team,
the nominees are Astralis, G2 Esports. I'm so removed from this. I have, I don't know any of
these things. You know when like the older generation gets old enough and then they look
back and they go, I don't, I don't know what this is. I'm in that moment now. I mean, I think this
is cool as shit, but I don't know any of these things. I don't know any of these things. I think
it's cool shit though. He's a boomer.
Where the game awards are part of a special double feature with Jumanji the next level.
We're about to take a short break, but first here's a little message from a couple of the
stars of Jumanji the next level. Jumanji? What's up game awards? What's up PlayStation?
We checked out dreams. Oh boy. It was trippy. We're in a game. Yeah, no kidding. Especially
your face. That was sculpted in dreams by the way. You can be the judge when you see it for
yourself. Oh, that's crazy. We can't wait for you to see Jumanji the next level. That's actually
insane. I can't say this enough. We're in a video game. I'm not gonna watch this movie, but wait,
this is Jumanji single. What's coming up next? What's the next, what's the next preview? Now,
these are video games. That's, now this one was good. I actually really liked that one.
That one was, not so good. I'm sorry. He hated it. I didn't hate it. What's next? Tell me so much.
Back to the game awards pre-show. This summer, I had the pleasure of joining Jeff to co-host
Gamescom opening night live. And one of the games we revealed that night was Amplitude Studios
Humankind. Here to unveil a new gameplay feature and the first trailer with gameplay,
please welcome Jeff Spock. Hey Jeff. Hi, thanks Cindy. I'm very excited and kind of terrified
to be here. I'm here to answer a question we've been hearing constantly since we announced the
game this summer. And the question is, who am I playing? Am I playing a king, a queen, a historical
figure, leader of a civilization? He knows we're talking about Minecraft. Tonight we can announce
that you are going to play you. The idea is that you're going to create a highly customizable
avatar that will evolve visually as you play the game. So as you make gameplay decisions,
as you win achievements, as you select cultures and that sort of thing, you'll see that evolve
on the avatar itself, which means that at the end of the game you'll have sort of a record
and a trophy of how you changed humankind. We have tons of ideas of where the avatar system can go.
We're very excited about it. But if I talk about them, the programmers will literally disembowel me
when I get home. So in order to avoid that, we put together a trailer. So we have a game experience
and gameplay trailer to showcase the human avatar system. Beautiful. Why don't we take a look?
All right, here we go. I'm ready for this. This actually sounds like it could be good.
It all started way back. Back to basics. Ah, days. Gathering, hunting, and well,
back to gathering. We switched from a cold to a cool place to settle. And I found the perfect
spot for my people. At first it was just a few walls to keep the bears out and the pigs in.
But you know how it is. One district led to another and it kind of snowballed.
Now the problem was the neighbors thought the grass was greener on my side of the fence.
But we saw them disembowel me. All I had to do was give the order. It really hurt. Their first
mistake, bringing infantry to a cavalry fight. Next, losing the high ground. Final mistake,
not keeping up in the arms race. But eventually peace prevailed. They surrendered and I let them
live. It turns out we had a lot to learn from them. And together we became more than the sum of our
parts, a unique mix of cultures and beliefs. So yeah, I would say I left my mark on humankind
and I'm just getting started. Is this civilization?
That's just my story. Tell me, what will yours be?
Oh by the way, what the fuck's going on with the Apple Arcade? I bought Apple Arcade and it's like
a hundred games and we add, they haven't added anything. It's been like three and a half weeks
since they've added a new game to the Apple Arcade. What's going on there? I keep checking
it and it says nothing there. It's the same like 80 games. They honestly haven't even told me what
it is yet. So I am just as in the dark as all of you right now. And I got to say it's pretty
exciting. I really have no clue what to expect right now, but we're all in this together. So
let's all kick back and enjoy this one. Another world premiere. Oh, look at all these world,
go ahead and world premiere, world premiere, world premiere. I thought that was Eric Cartman. For one
second. I was like, that's Eric Cartman speaking. What? What the fuck? 20 years he's back and he's
here to take over the world. He's back to take over. Who? You? Damon. I love you. Do it. These
superheroes are popular and they're gonna jump on that. What are you? I'm a goddamn superhero.
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Okay. So I'm glad they're actually making that game and not like that weird top down VR fake
reality. Ghostbusters top down game. I don't even know why they did that.
If you're on TikTok, get off now. Get off now and secure your data. Change all your passwords.
Fortnite VR? Why is there Fortnite VR?
I talked a lot of shit about this game like last year. Let's see if I'm proven wrong.
You've seen this. They keep re-editing the same footage three years straight.
What if this never comes out? What if we keep getting re-edits of trailers for the next like
six years to keep Square Enix's stock up? This is an earnings call thing, guy.
This is an earnings call thing. This is never coming up. All right, it's coming up tomorrow.
Best fighting game? Mortal Kombat 11.
Samurai Showdown and Super Smash Brothers Ultimate. And we're gonna get the final DLC
character. The gentleman right here, they're gonna reveal the final DLC character. It's gonna be
Scorpion. Super Smash Brothers Ultimate. Congratulations. It's heavy. It is, isn't it?
They're just right there. Thank you Game Awards and thank you everyone out there very, very much.
You know, Super Smash Brothers Ultimate is really more than just a fighting game. It's an experience
that brings people together. It's also a showcase for some of the most famous characters, music,
game worlds, and video game history. And the fact that all of this comes together so seamlessly and
so beautifully is really a testament to the dedication, to the hard work, and to the skill
of Mr. Sakurai and the development team. This award is for them. Thank you very, very much.
I like them. I like them. I want to see the other, I want to see the camera pull out.
We are now just seconds away from the start of the big show. How excited is everybody?
There's just like a queue up to the stage. The Game Awards orchestra is prepared. Jeff Keely
is buttoning up his tux. They pull back. Everyone here in the live audience seems ready to go.
Fuck, this is a long line. Yeah, let's hear it. It's going to be such a special show. Green Day,
churches, and Grimes will all be performing. There are a bunch of world premieres that are
going to amaze everyone and I honestly have no idea who is going to win Game of the Year.
But that's a wrap on our pre-show. I'm Sydney Goodman. Have fun and enjoy the show.
The Game Awards starts right now. Yeah, that's it. I'm going to get up and leave the theater now.
I just bought my ticket to see the previews. That's all I care about. I'm just gone.
When the movie starts, I leave. Gemini Man is still in theaters? Why? Tell me something.
Why is it so hard for you to kill this man? Every move of mine before I made it.
What a cool trailer. What a good trailer. That's all you need. Wait, what is this?
Is it raining? Well, this isn't accurate. Let me make this accurate for you. All that equipment is
destroyed. I always feel fucking weird when I'm sitting. You know what I mean? Like, ready?
Like, it's cool to do this when you're in the audience, but you let me here just like...
Look, I'm a much bigger audience member. I take up more space than anybody here.
I'm just a huge fucking audience member. I'm doing what everybody else is doing.
The show is for me.
Pay attention. Pay attention to what? The tuba? Pay attention to the tuba.
Listen. You listen to music. You can listen to music.
Where's my reaction commentary? That's what I'm saying. When you go to a concert,
you're not sitting there going, awesome show. Very cool work. No, no, no. This is your
commentary. That's what you get. This is what commentary is at a show. You applaud. You say,
good. Cheer. Yeah, excellent work. During the performance, you're not going, cool.
I love this show. I'm a big fan of this show. Hey, hey, hey. Hey, you're doing good. You're
doing it. That'll get removed from the audience. How about that you're a heckler? What is this?
Death Stranding 2? Oh, by the way, there's like 10 years of Warcraft spoilers right there,
so don't tell me I'm spoiling a movie for you.
Jeff Keighley. Yeah, Jeff. Woo. Yeah. Woo. Yes. Go for it. That's what's acceptable commentary
right now. I'm Jeff Keighley. Go for it. Woo. Shut up. I can't believe this is the fifth
anniversary of the show, and it's so great to have all of you here. We've got so many amazing
special guests, Mr. Kojima, Reggie, Mr. Miyazaki. It's so exciting to have everyone here with us
tonight to celebrate games. First of all, let's give it up again for Churches and the Game Awards
Orca Show. What's not beautiful? Ninja's sitting right behind Reggie. You know, tonight, one of
the things that really amazes me about this show is how we connect the world around games.
Do you like at some point during this thing when you're getting up to go to the bathroom?
I'm having to get back to my seat. Reggie, I'm a huge fucking fan.
And then you sit back down. How do you come together all to celebrate video games? Now,
our show tonight, yes, we're going to have awards. Yes, we're going to have a lot of brand new game
announcements and surprises for you. So stay tuned for that. We know you like those. And we've also
got performances by Green Day and Grind. So stay tuned. It's been an outstanding year for games.
But to kick things off, let's get to our first award. And right now,
let's bring out our first presenter. He is a screenwriter and producer known for The Dark
Knight and also the co-creator of Westworld. Please welcome Jonathan Nolan. What? Why is
Jonathan Nolan here? Good evening. I'm here to present the award for Best Narrative.
We talk a lot about narrative in Westworld, where our guest characters choose their own paths with
branching storylines that change based on their actions. It's an idea that we invented all by
ourselves. You're welcome. By the way, I could write circles around everybody here. Just wait
till I make my game. I saw that year was my answer as often as not isn't a movie. It's not a show.
It's a game. Games like Fallout, Bioshock, Half Life, Red Dead Redemption,
all hugely influential on our work. And you can see the echoes of those games
in our show. Everett Rachel Wood's character, Dolores, has more than a little in common with
Elizabeth in Bioshock Infinite. James Marsden's character, Teddy, was, of course, based on
James Marsden's character in Sonic the Hedgehog. And of course, I'd be remiss if I failed to
mention the debt of honor that Ed Harris's character, the Man in Black, owes to Kuber.
So it's a true honor for me to be here tonight to recognize the amazing, thoughtful, and
groundbreaking work in narrative this year. Here are the nominees.
Everyone. And the winner is Disco Elysium.
Tonight, Disco Elysium always wins the Game Award for Best Role Playing Game.
Imagine if one of the tech directors actually just leaked every award nomination to everyone.
It's absolutely surreal to be here. And honestly, it makes me really speechless.
But I definitely want to thank everyone who believed that this game exists when we first
started talking about it, because a lot of people didn't. And I want to thank the industry
for welcoming us. It's been absolutely amazing. And of course, I want to thank our fans who
really proved that these kinds of narrative games have their place in this industry.
And yeah, thanks a lot. This game's good, right? Would I like this game?
Those of you that know this channel and you're welcome. Would I like this game?
Congratulations, guys. All right. We have such a big show ahead. Now I wanted to mention right
now on Twitch, we've got over 900,000 concurrent viewers watching the show right now, including
co-streamers. So sounds like you guys are excited about what we have going on. And of course,
6,000 people here. I'm like 2% of that. What? Wait, where is it?
Where is that?
World premieres are a big part of this show. And you guys have a lot of expectations on
the internet for things or lots of rumors, lots of leaks. And then sometimes there's surprises that
I don't I don't know. I don't know any I don't know any of these people.
I can't I can't I don't know. Let's suppose that you were able every night to dream any
dream you wanted to dream. And then you could have the power within one night to dream.
And what if you died naturally as you began your adventure of dreams? Would you still do it?
But now let's um, let's have a surprise. Let's have a dream which isn't under control.
We'll get more adventurous.
Further and further out gambles as to what you would dream.
You guys are telling me to be quiet. And finally you will dream.
I knew this wasn't a fucking reveal. There's another ad for xbox. Wait, that's the console.
The xbox dell inspiron. The xbox all the way to the left at best buy pc.
So it's just a computer. He's the head of xbox. Please welcome Bill Spencer. Is it just a computer?
That's a computer. That's right guys. It's a computer. It's a computer.
It's a computer. For 18 years and three generations, we've designed xbox consoles
to power your dreams. We see a future where you're instantly absorbed in your games.
Where worlds are even more like-like, immersive, responsive, and surprising.
Where you are at the center of your gaming experience.
Next holiday, xbox series x will lead us into the future of console gaming.
Our fastest, most powerful xbox will set a new bar for performance, speed, compatibility.
Developers around the globe are already hard at work building games for xbox series x.
You've revealed the console at a game award.
Our 15 xbox game studios are developing the largest and most creatively diverse lineup
of exclusive games in our history. Tonight, I'm proud to reveal a project early in development
from an incredibly talented creative team who are no strangers to the game awards.
What you're about to see was all captured in engine as being built
to take full advantage of xbox series x. Conquer's bad for day two.
Is that game any good? I didn't play the first one. Do I play video games? I don't play any
fucking video games. Who should I vote for? Oh, I missed the voting period.
All right, the fun is just beginning. Let me assure you, we've got some other great surprises
coming up here at the game awards. Now we just ran a poll on twitch to see who you think is
going to be recognized as the best esports player and the results are in. Twitch community picked
Faker. All right. 40% of the vote. Did you guys put that? You guys can do that, right?
You guys called it correctly. And still to come in the show, we've got performances by Green Day
and Grimes. More amazing music from the game awards orchestra. Special announcements from
League of Legends, Fortnite, and Apex Legends. Norman Reedus is here. Gotta make it count.
Reggie's in the house, of course. And we've got a lot more surprises that is all coming up.
But first, last year, we started a new initiative with Facebook to spotlight unique stories about
the gaming community around the world. This year, we've got three new amazing stories about global
gaming citizens. I'm so proud to have these in the show. And I just can't wait to share them
with you tonight. Here's our first gaming system. I'm not talking. I told you to shut up. I didn't
say anything. I was born an Afghan refugee. Growing up with the fear of am I going to be able to go
to school or not was always with me. I'm not able to go back to my country.
Afghanistan is a very traditional country. There is a huge problem here for women accessing
education. So I decided enough is enough. And I thought about coding. Code to Inspire is the first
computer coding school for girls in Afghanistan. We've developed so far more than 20 games.
Our students told me we are very tired of playing games that the men are superheroes.
And it's always pretty white men. So I was like, then why are you just going to create your own game?
When they see the game that they are playing, I'm made by women. That's an empowerment itself.
They understand that they have a voice and they should be heard.
Is it possible that the past and future are colliding?
This thing's sick, by the way, but just don't touch it. Be careful.
Up to 50% off.
Wait, the Joker and Harley Quinn.
And aren't you just as creepy as?
Don't they have their own game made by the same company? Rated M for Mature.
That guy just destroyed her.
To play any time, anywhere.
Somebody in chat did real good. What is this? I'm interested in this.
Wait, it's only for Oculus? No, it's not.
Do you exclude VR exclusives? Come on, the thing's like 700 bucks.
Some of these headsets and peripherals, it's like 800 bucks. The Rift is 400. I could buy two PS4s.
PS4 is 299. I could buy like one and a half PS4s.
Can I have your half PS4? What's going on? No, it's mine.
As some of you may know, I have my own gaming related injury recently.
I went for that triangle button and next thing you know, I'm on the floor hot and
2k is no joke. So once again, esports is the fastest growing sport on the planet
and still breaking records with massive multimillion dollar prize, uh, prize pools and
the award for best esports player recognizes both outstanding play regardless of the game
and also good sportsmanship. So here are the nominees.
Best esports player.
Your Fortnite world champion, Boogaloo.
You got a huge throat. No, I don't. My throat is normal. I have a normal throat.
Best esports. All right, I'm going to say what's the highest skill ceiling? What game has the
highest skill ceiling? And the game award for best esports player goes to Boogaloo.
Thank you guys so much. How do you think I can do all these powerful voices?
I have extra thick airway. My family, my friends, my team sentinels, and most importantly,
Epic Games for making any of this possible. And I'm so glad to be a part of this community
and I can't wait to see what the future holds. Thank you guys so much.
Those patrols are actually kind of cool. Ninja sitting back there going like,
should have been. It don't really matter though, because ninja is at that spot in celebrity status
where you don't have to win anymore in anything. You just, you just participate in everything.
You know what I mean? Like he doesn't, it doesn't matter.
What is this? Beautiful, deadly, right in our way. That's about right.
Destiny 2. Destiny 2 again? It blends together guys. It does. It just blends together. No,
it's something else. It's, you know, it's the same like lights, the same like blue and pink,
bright, like refracting lights. I feel like, like the armor and the lights, it's the blue
neon and blue and red and green neon refracting lights. It's something about it. I don't know
what it is. It's in every game now. Oh, you noticed that. Yeah. PlayStation 5. All right.
This show is on fire. I'm here with Keith Lee, the CEO of Counterplay and Steve Gibson,
the president of Gearbox Publishing. Guys, brand new announcement, brand new IP new game.
What is Godfall? Godfall is a brand new IP set in a brand new fantasy universe
filled with heroic knights and mysterious magic. We call it a looter slasher. All right. So,
looter slasher. Tell us a bit about like, how is this going to play? So, we're here to reinvent
combat for loot driven action RPGs. We'll have third person real-time melee combat as you hunt
for awesome loot. You can also play the game in solo as well as in co-op. It's going to be
fun for everyone. Well, it looks absolutely incredible. That was all in-engine. You know,
you can see the game that we're going to get to play there. Steve, you know, from Gearbox's
point of view, you guys nominated tonight, obviously, Borderlands. Congrats on that.
Thank you. But how do you guys fit into this picture with Sony and with Counterplay?
Oh, man. You know we love our co-op and our gear at Gearbox. So, here we are, man. And when Keith
showed us Godfall, it was so amazing to us. We had to call our friends over at Sony, our friends
over at Epic, say, hey, help us make this work on your technology and your hardware. Keith,
we're going to do everything we can for you, man. And we're excited. We're so excited. Announce
this is going to be announced. This is launched exclusively on the PlayStation 5 and Epic Game
Store this holiday. Holiday 2020. I didn't say anything. Shut up. This is amazing. Well,
guys, congratulations. I was molding my face like it was clay. You sure will. Awesome. All right.
Congrats on the announcement. Awesome, guys. All right. Well, we'd like to welcome some,
we'd like to recognize some other of our winners tonight. I got something bored. All right, get
up. The category of best audio design for best in-game audio and sound design, those nominees are
Call of Duty Modern Warfare. It's the neon green and red neon lights. Best stranding.
Here's five. Resident Evil 2. Okay, fan favorite. And Sekiro Shadows die twice.
I mean, Mr. Rex walking around. If it's not Resident Evil 2, the game's dead. Call of Duty
Modern Warfare. No, no, no, the game's dead. The game is dead. Call of Duty Modern Warfare.
For best strategy game focused on those nominees are 10 years.
Fire Emblem Three Houses. Total War Three Kingdoms. Tropico Six and Wargroove.
And the game award in that category goes to Fire Emblem Three Houses. All right. In the category of
content creator of the year, content creator who made an important and positive impact on
the industry this year. The nominees are Courage, who's in the house here, Dr. Lupo, Ewok,
Gref, and Shroud. And the game award goes to Shroud. Fortnite. The game award goes to Fortnite.
World premieres and announcements to start off the show. And we've talked about Xbox,
we've talked about PlayStation, another platform we probably should talk about now.
We have another world premiere, brand new game announcement that I don't think you guys are
expecting, but we're really excited to share with you here on the Game Awards. Check this out.
Hitman Switch. It is time to choose. Accept your fate and await oblivion.
Or make a stand and fight for survival. Step into the light, young hero. Be brave.
During the movie you can't, you can't, you can't go to the bathroom during the movie.
I like the 3D on top of 3D on top of 3D. Looks cool.
I think people probably gonna, new poll has started. What's the poll?
What poll? Who do you think should win the 2019 best play on Twitch?
Best play on, what was the play?
What was the play?
My fellow Canadian, Rebecca Ford, live operations and community director at Digital Extremes.
Is that for Canada or for Rebecca? For both of them. All right,
Rebecca, welcome to the Game Awards. You've been up here before. Warframe. Tell us,
what's the latest on Warframe?
You know, we've been making this game for seven years and each year we update it with
space ninja flair, but we think it's time to go space pirate and this whole
Empyrean thing is what our community wants to know about.
Yes, I know you guys have teased that. What can you tell us about it?
What's gonna come out?
Well, we were thinking on PC.
What is this?
Right now.
Oh, okay. Here we go. So I'm here live right now. All right. That's fantastic.
And people will get their hands on it tonight.
Anything else that we should be keeping in mind?
Yeah. Our PlayStation 4 and Xbox one 10.
Oh, have the rising tide update, which means we are now
following anyone. Yes, I do. I follow Vinny. I follow Vinesauce. That's bullshit.
I don't follow literally anyone.
Where's my stream?
Where's my stream? All right. Who cares about my stream?
I am coast.
I do though.
Oh, it's because I'm not logged in to this. I'm not logged in.
This is just a browser plugin. Okay, I get it.
Stop it.
Tonight, we're happy to welcome Samsung as a new partner of the Game Awards.
And throughout the night, you'll be hearing from my fellow Canadian,
lots of Canadians tonight, Linus Tech Tips about Samsung's QLED TVs,
which are optimized for the best gaming experience. Take a look.
I'm Linus from Linus Tech Tips, and I'll be talking about some of the ways living
room gaming is better than ever. When I was a kid, my first gaming TV was about this big.
And it had a VHS player built into it.
Me too.
Not very immersive. With a Samsung QLED TV, not only can you see more than ever before,
but at 4K resolution with sizes of up to 82 inches.
Linus, you're sitting too close.
Unbelievable.
Linus, sit back. You're going to hurt your eye.
You can game without worry.
That's too close.
See, that just hurt me. And I'm like far away. This is like a 25 inch TV.
And I play Fortnite and I'm 14.
Linus, you're sitting too close to the TV, man.
A very small following.
In the past 14 months, everything's really taken off and it's been absolutely incredible.
I mean, I've become the first woman in Faze Clan.
My goal is to see many more females playing and considered at an equal level.
And I really want to see that explode in the gaming world.
I think that would be really nice.
And he walks here with us tonight. We're so glad to have her with us.
All right.
Oh, I can vote on this one.
He's the senior art director for Magic the Gathering.
Dan, welcome to the Game Awards.
Thank you.
Probably no more Heroes 3.
You're our brand. What's next?
Well, Jeff, I'm excited to tell you that in January,
Magic will be returning to one of our most beloved worlds.
So the last time we went to Theros, a world of gods, myths, and monsters,
we saw our hero, Elspeth Tyrell, my favorite planeswalker,
betrayed by the gods and banished to walk the underworld.
But now our hero is ready to defy death and escape her fate.
And I'm here to give you a sneak peek at what's in store for her.
Now with music by Ramin Jawadi.
This is the trailer for Theros Beyond Death.
All right, check it out.
Watch this trailer. I'm going to run and pee and be right back.
This is probably why I lean into my friend.
I'm sitting next to the movie and go,
what happened?
Something fucking major happened.
And your friend is just sitting there going,
I, the guy with the green hat came in and there was a firefight.
And I don't know, I couldn't, it was fast.
New game announcements.
Just keep rolling here at the Game Awards.
Eventually we'll get some games you already know about,
but let's keep going with things you haven't seen before.
Here's another world premiere.
Why do they do this?
Yes, we know it's a big movie screen.
Why do we have to pull out?
It's almost like to prove how big the screen is.
What?
What the fuck was that?
She's a creative director and the lead art designer from the Evil Within series.
Please welcome Ikumi Nakamura.
What was the, what was the last thing?
There was some dogs barking.
Please bear bear with my English.
Okay, good art can change over time.
But great art stays great.
Great art, great art sparks joy in our brains
and helps us to change the way we think.
Because sometimes we need to change to survive.
This year I had a big change in my life
and it's been a crazy year.
Is it Evil Within 2?
Evil Within 2?
But I'm alive.
Was it a crazy year for you?
You are not alone because I'm here.
And we have great games with great art.
But here are the nominees for Best Art Direction are...
Look at it!
Best Art Direction.
Best Art Direction presented by Samsung QLED.
Samsung, you didn't make any of this stuff.
Please.
Yeah, Sekiro was.
Sekiro did look pretty great.
It was pretty good.
Yeah.
I would say it was probably Sekiro.
As you know, I am a fortune teller.
I can see, and the winner is...
Did you just show it?
Control!
Control is amazing.
I didn't play it.
This is incredible.
Trying to avoid any explicit language right now.
Instead of being Sekiro.
I think the big thank you goes to the art director,
Janne Polkinen.
He is an amazing person.
Was the art director not there?
He's worked at Remedy for a long while.
And he had this crystal clear vision of what he wanted to achieve with Control.
And he did amazing things together with his team.
Also I have to thank Stuart MacDonald, who is the world design director,
and Aunty Boomi who handled the characters,
and all the creepy monsters that existed in this game.
And I can't imagine a better group of artists,
intelligence, creative people to work with.
And this is thanks to you guys.
Thank you so much for your work.
Does Control look good?
They're...
I don't even know what Control is.
I know it's like you can manipulate the world with your hands
and you have all the superpowers, right?
You have all the superpowers, you can probably climb the walls.
Something like that.
Congratulations to the guys at Remedy.
We've got lots more words coming up.
But right now I'm here with Donald Mustard,
worldwide creative director for Epic Games.
Donald, welcome back to the game.
It's a yearly thing, I feel like.
Here we go, season three Fortnite.
Here it comes.
Well, you guys have built quite a franchise in Fortnite.
And the last couple years have just been so crazy for you guys.
But what I love is that you're constantly innovating with this game.
That's what we're trying to know.
It's, you know, we think we're all just trying to make stuff that we think is fun,
that we think is cool.
And you never quite expect something to take off the way that Fortnite did, right?
But once that momentum happened, we're just like, man, how do we just...
We've got to lean in.
And how do we find ways to really just push the idea of what
a persistent virtual place can be?
And so that's why even this year...
A Marshal concert wasn't...
The concert, yeah.
We start the year off with a concert that has, you know,
over 10 million people in it.
You know, we roll into huge monster fights.
And we've got a thing we've been fighting forever to like,
how do we find a way to suck the entire world into the zero point black hole
and turn the game off and like all this stuff?
But that all in some ways, I think,
pales in comparison to what's about to happen this weekend.
Right.
Yeah, something pretty cool is gonna happen in a few hours, you know, and on Saturday.
On Saturday, you guys probably have seen teasing a little bit about
something that's happening at Risky Reels tied to Star Wars.
Yeah.
If you do Fortnite VR, isn't it just gonna be like this?
Yes, and it's pretty cool.
What can you tell us about it?
Like, don't you have to like look down at it?
You know, I probably can't tell you much.
But I have a friend who can.
Okay, let's take a look.
How do you do Fortnite VR?
Thanks, Donald.
Hey, everyone, it's JJ Abrams, director of The Rise of Skywalker.
Join me in Fortnite on Saturday for an exclusive look at the movie.
To see the whole thing in the game.
So I'll see you in Fortnite on Saturday.
Thanks.
Yeah, I see you Saturday for Fortnite.
And I think, you know, some people online are like,
oh, you're just running a clip or whatever.
And I don't know how much you want to reveal,
but you and I have been talking all year about, you know,
building a live experience around this.
I'm excited. I'm going to get to actually be in the game as well.
Kind of interacting with JJ.
And I don't know how much you want to tell us about it,
but it's going to be a live participatory experience, right?
I think it's going to be like something that no one's ever seen before, ever.
I mean, JJ and Jeff, we're going to be live.
Oh, and that's the glider we're going to get, I think.
There's also going to be that.
Exactly.
Wait, so hold on.
That's what happens when you do it live.
So you never know.
There's an attack happening.
Everyone who shows up, like as you drop out of the battle bus,
you're all going to pop those out.
Like everyone that shows up is going to get Thai whispers.
It's awesome.
You're flying around and JJ and Jeff will be there live in the game.
And we're going to see this awesome clip from Star Wars.
It's a brief, but I've seen it many times.
From Star Wars.
Very, very good.
What clip from Star Wars?
And then some other crazy stuff is going to happen.
It's my favorite part of Star Wars.
It's when Han Solo said Boba Fett.
I'm really excited about sort of what this means, I think, for sort of
programming inside of games.
That's better.
Use that one.
Shared experiences like the Game Awards.
People all coming together watching this.
But this is inside the game world.
I'm really excited about what is going to happen on Saturday.
So right from the Game Awards to that.
But before then, I know you've got some other, some cool things that people can
pick up in Fortnite.
We do.
So there's one more thing.
So right now you can go to Fortnite and these are now available in the game.
And they're some of my favorite characters of all time.
Rey and Finn and the awesome new Sith Trooper.
And they're in the game right now.
You're going to get loaded up for Saturday.
Amazing.
Well, I got to say, we are really excited about what you guys have put together with
you, Lucas and Disney, to have this come together.
So the Sith Troopers are just never easy to pull off.
Dairy Queen Cherry Dip.
I'm really excited about what it's going to be.
So Saturday.
Saturday, 2 p.m. Eastern.
And it's live.
Like we're doing it live.
And it's going to be amazing and crazy.
Just like this.
I was going to say, we'll be there and there'll probably be TIE fighters.
There'll be other crazy things going on.
Donald, thanks as always for coming by the Game Awards.
Good luck.
I know you guys are up for a bunch of awards tonight as well.
And we've got much more Game Awards coming up.
Thank you.
So where's the Star Wars clip?
I want to see the clip from Star Wars.
All right.
Well, we've got a lot of brand new game announcements tonight.
Where was the Star Wars clip?
Did they not show it?
The next one comes from a team up in my home country of Canada.
I keep mentioning Canada, but this is a game that I think you'll be surprised by.
I thought he was going to show his favorite Star Wars clip.
It's a pretty cool thing to announce at the Game Awards.
So am I stupid?
Yep.
I don't want to live forever.
Demons.
What?
Is that a demon?
Sons of the Forest.
Sons of the Forest coming out end night tonight.
We got some cool stuff tonight.
Well, one of the most played games in the world is League of Legends.
And tonight we're happy to have Riot and its new Riot Forge division with us to
reveal their first single player experience for the franchise.
What happened to the one that they were making?
What happened to that Monster Hunter game they were making?
Is that still going on?
Did they can that?
My king, long time has come for revenge.
My master, Azmogand, away with the prey.
Ruin King, Airship Syndicate, I'm here with Joe Mad.
Joe, you guys have made some amazing games over the years.
First of all, congratulations on working with Riot to reveal you guys making the first game,
what it is.
Tell us more about what we just saw on that teaser.
How do you do single player League of Legends?
I'm so excited we can finally talk about this.
I was sure I would leak it before now.
But we are doing the first ever Riot Forge game.
And as you saw, it is the Ruin King, a League of Legends story.
We're basically building on our experience making Battle Chasers and Darksiders
to create a story-driven turn-based RPG.
We have a new take on turn-based combat that's really cool.
Obviously the visual, the art and visuals that our studio is known for.
And the story takes place after Burning Tides.
So everyone believes Gangplank is dead.
Bilgewater is in chaos.
And you'll actually play as some League champions and explore Bilgewater,
the Shadow Isles, and we have a lot of other surprises as well.
And Poros.
They're mandatory, apparently.
All right.
Well, it sounds like this is something you've been working on for a little while, too, right?
We have.
We have, yes.
And I can't say any more.
Okay.
That's all you're allowed to say.
All right.
Well, it's so exciting to have Riot with us here at the Game Awards for the first time.
That's all I can say.
Do you like the green swooshes in that voice actor?
Well, thanks so much for announcing with us.
I really love the green swooshes.
I know all the League of Legends fans around the entire world who are tuned in tonight.
So, Joe, I can't wait.
I don't get this.
I don't.
And it's an indie-free weapon.
I will.
I'm good right now.
Thank you very much, Joe.
Great announcement, League of Legends.
Fantastic.
Talks over, like, 12 seconds ago.
When we come back, a performance by Grimes.
The award for best action game with Norman Reedus and a special announcement from an
Apex legend still to come.
Ninja presents best multiplayer game and an extended look at Ghost of Tsushima.
This is the Game Awards.
Don't go anywhere.
What is the break?
Chat, because tonight is the Game Awards.
Hold on.
You have got to be kidding me.
Is that great?
Courage?
I said no.
Come on, Harley.
We've been here training for weeks.
Don't take this the wrong way or nothing.
Okay, that's pretty good.
Hold on.
That's pretty good.
But I love you.
Wait, didn't they delete this?
I thought that Suicide Squad was what they did.
They deleted it.
Something hit someone.
Tensions like violence.
Then the very end, right when it says coming 2020, you hear, ah, where is it?
What did I just save it to?
Wait, you want to, like, see what's going on on the screen.
Over 75 awards and nominations.
Oh, this is Doom Doom.
A lot of stuff coming out in March, huh?
Ditch vape.
I'm vaping right now.
You need to cut that shit up.
Stop doing that.
I'm looking right in the eyes.
What are you doing that for?
Don't eat a banana.
Just eat a banana.
Don't do anything else.
You could eat bananas.
You could eat banana for every meal.
And then smear some peanut butter.
Spoon side up just on the roof of your mouth and swallow it.
You'll be fine.
I remember that level.
That level sucked.
Back to the game awards.
All right.
Music is a big part of games.
And Cyberpunk 2077 is one of the most anticipated games coming out next year.
You shouldn't have given me that image.
Working hard to finish the game.
But right now, we've got a behind-the-scenes look.
I have to stop talking in mute because people will literally scream at me if they...
Even in the dystopian future, hard rap lives on.
We want to provide you with the soundtrack to fucking shit up.
I mean, we're not here as refuse.
We're here as samurai.
It's a very interesting thing to be part of.
We really work on these songs, trying to make them as good as possible.
I think my music fits with my city because both are scary and pretty at the same time.
My music will be featured in Cyberpunk 2077.
I'm super excited.
It's quite rebellious and it's quite noisy and aggressive.
I think industrial is the word.
I can't wait to see how the two worlds actually meet.
I mean, it's been a lot of fun playing these beats.
It's very punk rock in a way in its approach.
They're building these systems to make really rough, edgy music.
Psychedelic, trippy, yet plifting and engaging.
And you can see a lot of kind of industrial stuff and revolution happening.
Sort of mixing punk music and like what electronic music could be in the future.
So we have some tracks that are super dirty, super heavy.
And then we have some tracks that are very beautiful and ambient.
That was just a glimpse of what we have in store for you.
See you in Night City.
I promise I won't do it again.
Oh, I gotta say it.
I'm deleting it off my OBS.
Oh, it's Cyberpunk.
Right.
Wait, you're doing the Wolverine?
Are you gonna get in and do Wolverine?
This is how Wolverine was created.
Don't do it.
X.
Into the Faith Coffin.
This is the future of Cyberpunk 2020.
You put on your gamer headset and your gamer glasses and your VR
and you lie down in a fucking fake chamber.
And you have an IV of like gamer fuel and Doritos and shit.
I love it.
I'd love that.
I'd love the Vape Coffin.
And every time you sneeze, blood fucking shoots out of your nose.
And that's what it's gonna be like.
People are like, oh, the future.
It's gonna be so interesting.
No, no, no.
Every sneeze blood's gonna spray.
Blood spray out of your nose every time in the future.
Shut up.
I'm trying to hear the subcar music.
Why is he standing?
What is going on?
The camera's on me.
And now, he's the star of The Walking Dead and the best performance nominee tonight for his
role as Sam Porter Bridges in Death Stranding.
He was so torn.
He was like, do I stand?
I don't know why would I be standing?
I guess I'll stand.
Hello.
He did that thing.
He did that face.
Hi.
All right.
It's time to present the award for best action game.
These games are all wildly, wildly different.
Some new franchises, some beloved sequels, all with their own unique adversaries and
objectives.
But the one thing that they have in common is that they set the bar for lively combat
and thrills.
All right.
Ready?
All right, all right, all right.
Here's the nominees.
But that's, that's, that's like hair game.
No, those, that's hair goals.
You're right.
Keep up.
How am I doing?
Kick some ass.
Jeremy, you didn't play this game.
Yeah, you didn't play that.
All right.
This is heavy.
And the winner is Devil May Cry 5.
All right.
That's actually, that was good one.
That was, that was the best one on that list.
Boomer May Cry.
You're being snubbed.
I didn't play this game.
I didn't play the game.
I know it was good.
Thank you so much for all the fans who've been supporting us.
And thank you so much for waiting 11 years for the sequel.
I was really happy to stick with my roots and try to make as pure of an action game as possible.
Say no.
DMC is back.
Thank you.
Yeah, it's uh, I, I, I can say that again.
Congrats to DMC guys.
All right.
I'm now joined by Jeff Hadam, the studio lead and founder of two games from Canada.
I don't know how it all works out that way, but a lot of cat crimes, Canadian, Jeff.
All right.
Anyways, uh, tell us what you're working on up at two.
Thanks, Jeff.
I'm super excited to be here with the world, the air of the game.
We've been working on up in Montreal.
Salut tout le monde.
Um, when we started working on this game, we, we had the idea to put action back in action
RPG and what better place than in dungeons and dragons, forgotten realms, less action.
Am I fucking crazy together with your friends?
I want less action in my action RPGs.
Too much shit happens on this one.
Dark Alliance.
Check it out.
I don't, I don't want like a bunch of shit on the screen.
A bunch of explosions in action every second.
I like it when it's slowed down a little.
I don't want more action.
I want less action.
Why do they have the like fear factor cameras when they're in the haunted house?
I'm going to put the action back in action RPG.
We're also going to put the camera somewhere else too.
We want the, we want you to be right up in their faces, right in the action, right in their face.
All right.
Up next is the award for the absolute best.
It's the most wonderful time of the year.
Wow.
It's a little pitchy on that one.
I should keep practicing.
Looks like it's mirage.
Everybody.
What's up?
Mirage suction.
Hey, Keely, my man, what's going on?
Well, we're kind of in the middle of the game awards right now.
But this guy like attached to walls.
Oh, is that tonight?
Tell me, tell me.
Did they already win for best all around competitor in a battle royale based on skills?
But mostly good looks.
That is such a specific award.
And as I told you on Twitter, I'm sorry.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
I see what you're doing.
Keeping the mystery alive for the audience.
I get it.
It's a secret award.
I get later.
Wink.
It's not like I haven't been practicing my acceptance speech.
Wow.
These things are really heavy.
I'd like to thank my mother for my exceptional good looks.
Mirage, we have a show.
We've got lots of announcements to get to.
Is there a purpose of today's call?
Oh, right.
Well, I know everybody's always asking for more Mirage content because obviously.
And I think I speak for everyone when I say we've all had enough of crypto.
So Keely, I'm here tonight to just give the people what they want.
Oh, a decentralized way to have a mutual credit system.
I'm a captain.
The captain of what exactly?
The Mirage Voyage.
Oh, yeah.
It's my big holo day bash.
You get it?
Holo days because the and I do holograms.
And anyway, can I put you down for a plus one?
Fine.
Oh, that's the best.
What game is this?
This party starts right now.
Oh, I see.
They really they tap it into the court.
And I've got presents for everyone at the awards.
And all you beautiful people watching at home.
Join me at the party and you all get this free.
Makes sense.
Exclusive legendary skin of my matching G7.
Sexy, huh?
And the gun doesn't look bad either.
Yeah, extremely generous of you, Mirage.
Thank you for that.
What can I say, Jeff?
I am a giver.
All right.
Well, listen up.
We do have a show to get back to.
So thanks, Mirage.
OK.
OK, best buddy.
Can't wait to see you and everybody else at the biggest
celebration in the outlands.
It's party time.
This is a big holiday update.
You'll warm up in the respawn chamber quicker than you think.
I enjoy the winter months.
Is he gonna fart on him?
What was that?
Let's do this.
Hog train?
Things called the hog train?
Why are you looking at me that way?
Up next, Dr. Bunsen, Honeydew and Beaker present games for impact.
Oh, yes.
Reggie is here and he is ready.
Oh, that's gonna be great.
We're getting a Bunsen and Beaker presentation.
The Game Awards.
We're getting a Muppets present.
All right.
I'm gonna be quiet for this one.
Is this in Fortnite?
Adding every sport to Fortnite?
Sport night.
Yeah, no, we really decided we wanted to add a full 9v9 baseball.
There you go.
Apple Arcade at the Game Awards for the first time.
Ultimate Rivals.
All right.
We have so much more show coming up.
I don't like that service because I bought it.
And there's only, okay, this is gonna sound withered and fucked up and pretentious and shitty.
I can't talk because we have...
Holy shit, they added Ori and the Blind Forest to Fortnite.
That's pretty cool.
How many players are on each map?
Play it with Xbox Game Pass.
My favorite thing about being a game designer is I didn't have to pick one subject to specialize in.
I'm able to just follow my interests and spend lots of time studying galactic evolution
or urban planning or psychology, whatever it is.
And then I just kind of turn that into a toy, into a game.
Part of my job is just enjoying exploring the world
and letting my interest take me wherever they go.
And there are not too many jobs that I think let you do that.
This is like a...
When it comes to upping your competition...
This is a Gary Larson comic.
Warframes per second makes a measurable difference.
Trust me.
That's why Samsung's latest QLED TVs feature native support for games,
running it up to 120 frames per second with very low input lag
and this sweet auto game mode that detects when you're gaming
and turns off any extra image processing.
They've even got AMD FreeSync for smoother animations when the frame rate dips.
Edit it onto the screen.
The war had just started when I arrived to Iraq.
We did our thing.
We had some experiences.
And when we came back, when we got off that plane,
before we can even embrace our loved ones,
our fire team leader says,
do not tell anybody what happened to you
or what you saw or what you experienced.
That starts the stigma of mental health.
StackUp is a military charity supporting US and allied veterans' mental health and gaming.
Overwatch is our newest program and it is simply having a chat client up.
Somebody comes in and says they need to talk or they're interested to get into a game.
We have somebody available for them.
They may not want to come out there and see a counselor for an hour once a week,
but they may come out there and play a video game
and start talking about their experiences of war
or the struggles that they're having right now.
It has become my passion to end the stigma of mental health.
Please welcome two of the most innovative visionaries in the history of gaming.
I can't wait to see this one.
And just about everything else.
From Muppet Labs, Dr. Bunsen Honeydew and Beaker.
How are we?
Oh, we are eight on each other's TVs.
Thank you.
Greetings, fellow gaming enthusiasts.
It's great to be here at the Game Awards.
I am Dr. Bunsen Honeydew and this is my assistant Beaker.
Beaky, where did you go?
Oh, I guess he's stuck in the lobby.
Nothing?
In just a few moments, we will reveal the winner of Games for Impact.
But first, I was hoping to...
Oh, here's Beaky now.
He's in VR.
Good to see you.
I forgot we have a basement.
Beaky, I'm so glad you're here wearing VR goggles
to demonstrate our brand new game.
Yes, as you can see, Beaker is wearing Muppet Labs proprietary
next generation technology, VR super gluey goggles.
You can put them on, but you can't get them off.
And now we will premiere the exciting new Muppet Labs game.
Oh, Beaker, that's not funny.
That's terrifying.
What are we calling it?
Of course, the Untitled Beaker game.
Excellent choice.
Let the game begin.
Let's play this.
Where does Norman Reed us off the thing?
Here are the nominees for Games for Impact,
recognizing socially conscious and progressive games in the industry.
Roll the nominees.
Games for Impact.
Me to hate this whole town.
Why is it so dark?
I find Life is Strange.
Life is Strange 2 has like magic in it.
And the winner is...
Wait, that's it, don't...
What are you doing outside the game?
You just please, hey, hey, give that back to me.
Beaker, get him, get him, Beaker.
Oh, no, that's me, that's me, Beaker.
Where did he go?
Where is he?
Get him, he's behind you.
There.
You've got him under control?
All right.
Okay, okay.
Thank you, Beaker.
I don't care if I'm a two-year-old.
This is cute.
Hold his beak sharp.
Hold his beak, Beaker, that's it.
Get him, get him.
Good.
Sorry about that, folks.
The award for Games for...
Would you...
Have you got it?
Fight his nose, fight his nose.
Fight his nose.
Stop it.
All right.
The award for Games for Impact goes to...
No, not...
He's...
Breeze.
I really wanted this, really.
I wanted to start fighting Beaker's like, neck and face and shit.
I hope...
Wonderful.
It's gonna honk, thank you, it's gonna honk.
Thank you to the Muppets.
I shared this award with, first of all, Conrad, our creative director,
with all the team back at home.
We made a really good team and we could have never made it without them.
We have to thank Devolver for allowing us to do the game we wanted to make.
Yes, well, first of all, I mean, I would like to thank,
especially to all those people that share their stories with us.
They send really, really moving stories when they were playing Greece.
That's something that, obviously, when you create a game,
you try to do these kind of things, but you never know if you're gonna get to someone.
And we, pretty much, are so moved when we receive this story.
So, please keep sharing it with us because it's amazing.
And thank you, everybody, that play and support Breeze.
Thank you very much.
Thanks to Bunsen and Beaker.
Lifelong dream to have them here at the show.
That was a good bit.
I like that.
I also want to mention something called the Game Festival.
I don't know if you heard about that online,
but we're launching a new thing tied to the game where it's called the Game Festival.
And the vision for that is to give all of you around the world who watch the show,
you watch trailers, you love games, a chance to play a bunch of games.
And this year, we're partnering with Steam.
And if you head to Steam for the next 48 hours,
a little bit less than that since it started this morning,
we have first look demos of over a dozen upcoming games that you can play for free on Steam.
And I think that's kind of the future where this all goes.
Bringing demos back?
Not necessarily these local events where you have to travel somewhere to play a game,
but actually bringing games into your homes and the places you work and live to play.
So, play all those games.
The Game Festival concludes Saturday at 10 a.m. Pacific.
And next year, we're going to do it across all the platforms.
I don't know why they went away in the first place.
A big thing.
So, we're looking forward to doing more with that.
All right.
Well, now we're going to present some more awards.
And let's get into the best family game.
The nominees for that category are Luigi's Mansion 3,
Ring Fit Adventure, Super Mario Maker 2, Super Smash Brothers Ultimate.
They're all Nintendo games.
And Yoshi's Crafted World.
It's just best Nintendo game.
Kind of like Nintendo's chances in this category.
And the game award goes to Luigi's Mansion 3.
Why even have this category?
Why don't you just have an ad up here that just says buy Nintendo games for families?
Just have a Nintendo ad.
Have to close my eyes.
And the game award goes to FIFA 1 Crash Team Racing Nitrofuel.
And for the best mobile game, the nominees are Call of Duty Mobile, Grindstone,
Sayonara Wild Hearts, which we announced last year, Sky, Children of the Light, and What the Golf.
And the game award in that category goes to Call of Duty Mobile.
Congratulations, guys.
All right.
Well, now I'd like to welcome the co-creators of Dishonored and Prey.
Raph and Julian are here.
You may have seen online that they've just announced their brand new studio.
Wolfi and Seth here at the Game Awards.
They're going to reveal their first game.
So guys, welcome to the Game Awards.
You've been here before, but you've got this new studio.
So tell me a bit about Wolfi.
What's different about it?
So, well, we took a long break, but it looks like we can't stay away from making a game for very long.
So we're just back at it now with Wolfi.
Yeah.
Well, what can you tell us about the game?
We know the studio.
We don't know anything about the game, but that's going to change now, right?
Yeah.
So you've mentioned Dishonored and Prey as some of our past games.
We have passion for interesting worlds to explore.
We have passion for depth of interactivity.
And of course, we have passion for simulation in general.
So this new game has all of these values.
But this time, we have a bit of a different approach.
We brought a glimpse to show you through a teaser.
I'm pretending.
It's amazing.
One of my favorite programs to show tonight.
That was pretty incredible.
You're going to see the real game here, guys.
We can't wait to hear more about this.
Let's take a look.
What do you do?
First look at the first project.
Nice.
I was pretending.
That was, you can call me out on that.
The West, the land of opportunity.
A place where you can be a hero, a scoundrel, and anything in between.
This ain't quite the Wild West as you know it.
There are ancient powers that war with each other.
Strange entities lurking in the dead of night with their own rules
and their own peculiar motives.
Welcome to the weird West.
Weird West.
Wacky West.
All right, action.
Action RPG.
The only out here could be the best thing that ever happened to you.
If you can survive, that is.
What's with the on the phone late at night?
Talking that that was.
All right, up next, a brand new MMO action RPG game from a legendary franchise.
Check out this announcement.
Firefists.
Spiders.
What else?
Magic Legends.
Magic, Firefox?
What was that?
Magic Legends.
Coming up, the first look at a brand new game from an exciting new studio.
And Ninja is here to hand out the award for best multiplayer game.
And still to come, more premieres, more awards,
an extended preview from Ghost of Tsushima and Green Day performs live.
The game awards will be right back.
I want the Muppets to come back.
Can the Muppets just present every award?
Hi, I'm looking for...
Stadia?
What?
What's Stadia?
Stadia is only the newest, most logic-defined, mind-bending, absurd gaming platform on Earth.
I'll take conversations that will never happen for 100 plays.
And this electric air is Stadia.
Unlike console, Stadia doesn't take up any space.
It makes no noise.
It has no smell.
Watch.
Go find Stadia, boy.
Don't worry.
You'll never find it.
Okay.
You can play Stadia with this.
What games are on there?
With Stadia, you can go virtually anywhere.
Unless you want to play Tomb Raider or NBA 2K18.
Stadia is gaming for free-range humans.
Stadia travels across screens.
No downloads.
No updates.
No waiting.
Stadia bends time and space to take you straight to your game.
So, Stadia is the platform.
Technically, this is Stadia.
Stadia's streaming pipeline leverages decades of Google research.
Is that a dog?
He actually found it.
But so does every other platform.
It doesn't matter.
As I don't get, Stadia has the games you're looking for.
So does PlayStation 4.
So does PlayStation 5, Xbox, PC.
I can download a game on Switch and it won't have like 0.4 seconds of input delay.
I don't understand why this is here.
And I actually have a theory that the Stadia, they know that it's not good enough.
But in 10 years, maybe the internet will get to a point where they'll be the first movers
when everything is like 7G.
They'll be here.
That's a 10-year play.
But I don't like that.
PUBG Mobile?
Why not just PUBG?
PUBG Mobile only.
Fight for the Amazon.
Oh, by the way, I played Luigi's Mansion for like an hour or two.
I could never play that game for more.
I can't do it.
I can't play it.
I will never play Luigi's Mansion for more.
And I really don't talk about this.
I'll try to go as quick as I can.
Luigi's Mansion 3.
The vacuum cleaner mechanic.
I have to suck up everything.
I cannot leave a single room unless every single fucking object is in that vacuum.
I can't play the game.
It takes me hours.
I played the game for probably two and a half hours.
And I got through maybe the first five rooms.
Fitness or just taking control of their health in general.
And if one of your goals is to quit vaping,
Truth has a program that can help.
It's called This Is Quitting.
It's free, anonymous, text-based, available any time of day right on your phone.
And it's already helping as thousands of people quit.
All you have to do is text DITCHJUEL to 888-799.
And then it texts you.
It texts you to stop.
But you don't have to do it alone.
Visit the Truth information and enjoy the game of words.
Vape coffin.
All right, now here's a brand new game announcement from Oculus Studios.
Check it out.
Hey, it's Jeremy here with the vape coffin.
I feel like the bar fighting game was like a better version of that somehow.
...is one of the most watched streamers alive
and the winner of last year's game award for content creator of the year.
Please welcome Ninja.
What's this for?
Thank you guys so much for obviously being here.
I've been playing video games my entire life.
And there's something magical about a solo player experience.
And the only way to enhance that
is to play games with your friends.
I've literally defined my entire career by playing online multiplayer games.
And here are the nominees for the best multiplayer game of the year.
If you did like the Coke and Pepsi test with me
and you put me in half of those games on this list,
blindfold and just put me in.
I don't know if I'd be able to tell you what one I was playing.
The game award for best multiplayer game goes to
it's a lot more difficult to open up than you think.
Apex Legends.
Tetris.
All right, blindfold me.
Let's see.
I don't know.
I could be in a this is like a VR.
Tetris lost.
Wow.
But Tetris is also like 60 years old.
The last four years has been transformative for Respawn.
They didn't have game awards when Tetris came out.
That's the real sad part.
They should do a retroactive game award.
Thank you to the fans.
Thank you so much.
I'd just like to thank the team at Respawn of crazy, passionate,
super talented individuals for going with us on this crazy journey.
We changed our genre.
We changed our business model.
We made our first character based game and we changed IPs
while we were shipping a AAA shooter.
So thank you.
I love you guys.
At the end of that, all he had to do was go like this.
Congratulations to Respawn.
Great to see Apex winning best multiplayer game now.
This year, TikTok has swept the nation with its hashtag challenges.
No, no, no.
The past few weeks, fans have been celebrating gaming on TikTok
with over 450 million views so far.
Tonight, you can use the hashtag to join the celebration of gaming
and esports biggest night in the contest.
Cheesy C64.
He's the guy that wanted right there.
So congratulations to him.
All right.
We've got so much more game awards coming up.
The gaming on TikTok contest will continue for the next few days.
Cheesy C64.
The next Twitch poll is open for best ongoing game.
You can go vote now and we'll see who you think is going to take home
the game award in just a bit.
But right now, let's talk about a big PlayStation 4 title
that's coming next year from the guys at Sucker Punch.
Ghost of Tsushima.
You probably saw this teased earlier this week.
I am so excited about this game and what Sucker Punch is bringing to life.
We have our longest world premiere on the show tonight,
as I've been saying, a true cinematic look in joy.
Why is it not coming out in the PS5?
It's been developing for like seven years, guys.
That was a really powerful...
Some say.
Others say he is a storm made flesh.
When the wind freshens their tents and boats, they know he is coming.
Okay, as a weapons expert, half of this stuff is not even possible.
Are we getting Final Fantasy VII here?
I feel like I've seen this.
The leaves are...
Oh, that's a bad idea.
The leaves are gonna stop blowing around and like hitting people in the face.
People are gonna find him in their hair.
Right now somebody has a big like 7-up.
No, 7-11.
A big 7-11 big gulp and one's gonna fall right in it.
It could be 7-up in there.
Imagine drinking a big gulp at the VGAs.
What's so wrong with that?
Guys, I got news for you.
If I ever go to the VGAs, I'm going like this.
And I'm gonna have a fucking like 47 ounce big gulp.
And I'm gonna have big sunglasses on.
Like I just got out of the eye doctor.
And I'm gonna be sitting there like...
The Game Awards Orchestra.
Let's give it up for our incredible conductor tonight.
Max Arouge, the Game Awards Orchestra.
They'll be back later for an incredible montage celebrating our Game of the Year nominees.
And Game of the Year will be presented by some very special guests.
Are you sleeping?
Surprise guests.
So stay tuned for that.
No, just like go cool.
A look at Gears Tactics.
Check it out.
The game for us invaded every part of our world.
So we did the only thing we could.
We set the world on fire.
The war begins against the monster that created these monsters.
Come in the beast.
The mon- the mon- the monstars.
That's the monstars.
And it's time to go hunting.
I thought that was them.
Oh, gentlemen, get shitheads.
My newest creation thinks of your little plan.
It's a long ass time.
Just once I want a game company to just blatantly fall on.
Fucking lie in their text as much as they lie in their gameplay footage.
600 hour long campaign.
Let's turn back to Twitch.
We asked Twitch to predict the winner for the best ongoing game category.
And they chose Final Fantasy XIV.
We will find out when we present that award in a little bit.
That's not a- that's only 27%.
That must have been close.
A performance that's going to rock the house by Green Day.
The award for best game direction and of course, game of the year.
Right now, here's a world premiere of a brand new game from a team in China.
It's a multiplayer melee combat game that you're seeing for the first time.
Multiplayer melee combat game.
I feel like that's every game.
All footage captured at Gary's house.
Or all footage will be deleted.
Or do not re-upload this copyright, you know, anything like that.
Welcome to Magic School.
Now that we've covered flying, let's talk about giant angels.
Not to be confused with bird people.
Bird people are their own thing.
Play Magic the Gathering with me.
Download free.
Free?
A masterpiece.
How many years have I waited for this moment?
Walmart of excellence.
For the one that stood alone against the storm.
For the one they of light.
Is this the one that won?
This tragedy, greater even than the Seventh Umbral Calamity, must be undone.
I- I- I- I know people- I'm late.
This tree must be-
I don't- whatever, I'm just gonna say it.
Just drop the numbers from Final Fantasy.
It's getting so fucking confusing.
Just drop the numbers.
It was- Final Fantasy VIII.
It's not coming up.
Just drop the numbers.
Just start doing colons.
Final Fantasy XIX, X1V2214.
Just- just start making up other fucking titles.
I made this tweet, like, five years ago.
But, like, eat- like, when you have more numbers than the Jason movies.
Like, it's time to change it.
My game's called Let's Be Well and it's made with the Roblox Studio game engine.
It starts off all grey.
This guy, it says he's depressed.
As he plays the obstacle course, he learns about the depression.
So this is to get people talking so they don't bottle their feelings up.
I was pregnant with our youngest son and my late husband got very, very sick.
The doctors call it a major depressive episode.
His mental illness overtook him by way of suicide.
And so we lost him when Luke was two years old at the time.
It's kind of hard to explain.
Like, how my dad died when I was very young.
I just wanted to spread a positive message that it's okay to talk about mental illness.
I hope I've helped people.
Now, she's a host and producer for IGN.
Please welcome Sydney Goodman.
To present the award for best ongoing game.
Recognizing that-
Final Fantasy.
Year after year and acknowledging the teams that keep these massively popular franchises
fresh with new content, more experiences and evolving ways to play.
Here are the nominees.
I thought we just did this.
Best ongoing game.
I feel like we're seeing the same category.
Destiny 2, Fortnite Call of Duty.
Am I going nuts?
And the game award for best ongoing game goes to...
Fortnite.
You don't know.
She was just immediately like, you don't know.
I know.
But yeah, it's Fortnite.
You got it. You got it right.
What's that one that goes like this?
This is amazing.
Thank you.
What's that one?
One that goes like this?
So...
I don't know.
So like last year, we represent just like the teeniest portion of the...
Now over a thousand people who work to make Fortnite.
What does that mean?
It's like a thousand players every single day.
We'd like to thank all the thousand people that are spending millions of dollars on the store
to have the opportunity to even make something like Fortnite.
It's incredible.
I think that, you know, as I was saying earlier, right?
Like this idea that we need to lean into what a persistent virtual place can be.
And the more that we're trying to experiment with stuff and try different things,
we're finding more and more that our goal is to try to create a metaverse.
To create a place, right?
Where all IP can live together.
Where all kinds of experiences can happen.
Where we can create a thing that is totally new.
A totally new emergent type of media, really.
And we are so inspired by everything you're doing.
I'm just blown away by what we see here tonight.
It's truly astounding and incredible.
Thank you for all the work you do.
Thank you for all the people who play Fortnite.
For who come up to all of us all the time and give us your incredible ideas and your feedback.
We just can't wait to keep making more.
I'd be remiss if I didn't take one little personal note to thank my wife,
my daughter, my family, my party people.
We love you.
Thank you so much.
See you guys Saturday.
And you got to do, you got to get credit for credit.
They took a game that was a like third person plants versus zombies,
like dumb third person shooter.
And they made it a BR that every single human role.
The developers who worked on Max Payne, Quantum Break, Armor 3, World of Danks.
And they did that pursuit mobile.
But it's because of.
Intel is located.
Okay.
Thanks, Jane.
But the competition is sending their team.
As expected.
Let's get this job done.
What have they even shown?
There you go.
That's nine to five.
And I'm here with Red Hill Games.
They spent more time on the fake trailer than they did at the video game that they made.
What can we expect?
Thank you.
I'm glad to be here.
Nine to five is a new first person tactical shooter.
It's set in a world where corporations rule everything.
And being a mercenary is just another job.
Now a lot of modern shooters can be a little bit chaotic.
And that's kind of what makes nine to five special.
We really put a lot of focus on the strategic gameplay of the team and playing together.
Making your changes and your tactics from round to round.
And obviously all that triumphs over brute force at the end.
All right.
Well, when can we expect to hear more?
Next year or?
So 2020 we're launching the alpha.
But you can actually sign up today at nine to five dot game.
So go ahead.
Enjoy and download.
All right.
A little bit of a tease.
Nine to five.
All right.
Thanks very much for being here.
Thanks.
Appreciate it.
All right.
We're going to hand out some more awards right now in the category of esports game of the year.
The nominees are Counter-Strike Global Offensive, Dota 2, Fortnite, League of Legends, and Overwatch.
What was it last year?
And the game award goes to League of Legends.
Congratulations to Riot.
This category is the same category every year for the best VR AR game.
Those nominees are Asgard's Wrath, Blood and Truth, Beat Saber, No Man's Sky,
and Trover Saves the Universe.
And the game award goes to Beat Saber.
Congratulations to Beat Games.
Why is Trover Saves the Universe?
Awarded to an individual for voiceover, acting, motion, and or performance capture.
Seriously.
The nominees are Ashley Burch for the Outer Worlds, Courtney Hope for Control,
Laura Bailey for Gears 5, Mads Mikkelsen for Death Stranding,
Matthew Peretta for Control, and Norman Reedus for Death Stranding.
And the game award goes to Mads Mikkelsen for Death Stranding.
Congratulations, Mads.
This year he also added a fan category over the past few days.
He's going to get told he won that tomorrow by somebody that works with him in an office or
something.
Your favorite game.
This was 100% in control of the fans.
And the winner of the fan vote is Fire Emblem Three Houses.
Congratulations.
All right.
Well, throughout the show, you've heard incredible stories about global gaming citizens.
And we're so honored to have them here with us tonight.
Please join me in recognizing this year's class of global gaming citizens.
We joke, but that's not even true.
Because didn't Mads Mikkelsen actually say that he was like excited for like where the
medium is going?
And that's not that's unfair.
That's unfair.
Congratulations, guys.
Beautiful.
A selfie.
All right.
We're so proud of that program.
We intend to continue that year after year.
I love telling all these stories of amazing people around the world who I think represent
gaming at its best.
All right.
Up next, we've got music from Green Day.
Reggie's in the house to present.
Reggie's in the house.
We've got more world premieres.
Reggie's still here.
I thought I laughed my ass off.
Actually, they're like, Reggie's here.
Reggie's here.
And the show's charity's just gone.
But he's left.
Black Desert has only been available for PC and console.
Oh, Reggie left.
What the fuck are we doing now?
You can download it tonight and get a true MMORPG at your fingertips.
Check it out.
Somebody just said, I can't believe they actually showed the Xbox.
The new Xbox.
That's insane.
I haven't even processed that.
There's somebody at E3 right now that organizes E3
that did a double hand on the desk go through the center of the table.
It's just bent in half.
At E3, we've decided.
They already talked about the Xbox.
And the PS5 is leaked already.
Shit, what do we do?
All right, we're going to come up with a console.
The E3 console.
Make sure it's more powerful than the Xbox.
We can run our own damn show.
The EEB.
The Electronic Entertainment Box.
Launch it.
I wonder.
I wonder who paid the most money on this particular game awards.
Can't be magic together.
Joe, back to back.
Back to back.
HDR is where it's at.
Quantum dot technology.
These two paid for half this fucking show.
Full array local dimming allows the brightest and darkest parts of the scene to look their best.
Features like these are why Samsung QLED TV was a Best of Innovation honoree for gaming at CES 2019.
He's so good.
And they're nominated again for 2020.
I just wanted to turn around and face the camera, but it's just like.
Play this game.
Letters written in the first couple months.
Which is just we were not prepared.
Words is a game about writing nice letters to people.
All real people anonymously online sharing their worries and making each other feel better.
Pushing the definition of games is something that I really get excited about.
Endless world.
Endless heroes.
This music is perfect.
You'll never stop spending money in our fucking endless game.
You're gonna try.
But once you run out of gems.
You're gonna have to pay money.
Or wait 25 minutes to continue playing.
Oh, it says it's free.
But you and I both know it's not.
WD Black.
Fine tuned for performance.
Purpose built for gaming to play without limits.
Storage solutions with the capacity, speed, and reliability to win.
WD Black.
Drive your game.
The Undertaker will take your money.
We are excited to welcome WD Black to the Game Awards as the official storage sponsor.
All of tonight's world premieres have been safely stored on WD Black.
And is Reggie still in the audience?
For a chance to win a decked out gaming rig and WD Black products.
All right.
Now I'm very excited to introduce our next performance.
One of my passions outside of gaming is live music.
Whenever I go to a show, I'm always thinking about who would be perfect here for the Game Awards.
Here it comes.
Am I allowed to stream this part?
Is this Vaude getting immuted?
Do I have to mute my Vaude?
I have to, I can't, I can't stream this part.
I actually can't stream this part.
Can I?
Live stream.
Just sing it.
Oh, he's standing up for the first time all the way on the warm show.
Get the glasses.
Oh, a lot of people are just like, they keep going.
I forgot the words to the song.
Somebody come, somebody go to the mic.
I don't remember the song.
Everybody loves Green Day.
How could you not like it?
Everything's different.
What do you mean?
Yeah, how could you?
I mean, no.
There's at least one Green Day song that you actually like.
I know there is.
You added it to your Spotify playlist.
At least one.
And I know this because almost every single high school commencement ceremony ends with a Green Day song.
And you nodded your head to it.
Please bring Bunsen and Beaker out here.
Please get Bunsen and Beaker out here.
Look for it, look for it.
This one, it's the one, you know what I'm talking about.
It's gonna be like elbows in, out, out, bend, bend, bend.
Watch.
We'll see.
Follow my finger.
You watch.
There it comes.
It's the, and you bend up, down, that one.
No, fuck.
Somebody doing it.
I don't even give a shit about the song going on.
I'm like looking for the Fortnite dancer.
I'm the only one doing it.
I'm the only person doing this.
Now, do I have to put them down?
But I can't because that means that I've been admitting defeat.
Nobody did it.
I was, I was.
How about that?
Green Day, everybody.
The world's virtual reality and rock just collided like never before.
Beat Saber and Green Day, the collab we've always wanted.
And you don't have to wait long.
The music pack drops tonight on all platforms.
Soon to be able to play six of the band's iconic hits
and brand new singles from the album, Father of All,
which is out on February 7th.
Thank you so much to Green Day for playing the Game Awards.
We have a lot of shows still coming up.
Of course, we've got the award for best game direction.
You got, all right, game of the year.
And yes, we've still got some announcements and surprises for you guys.
He's trying to, at gaming's biggest night.
It just gets bigger and bigger.
He's trying to make this a big deal.
I, you gotta, you gotta give it a try.
He's trying.
Yes.
No, they're not leaving.
They're going back to their seat.
It is an eternal island of legend.
Place of unimaginable beauty.
Where the forces of death and life.
Constant conflict.
Listen!
What?
For centuries, many have come in search of power.
I'm not doing this.
Am I doing this?
Only to fall to its corruption.
I'm not playing this, right?
I'm not, it's not, the video's not open.
It's real.
To this place, lured by the promise of power and immortality.
This will claim you.
Do you really want to live?
Oh, I love it.
That's New World.
And I was just down at Irvine at the studio visiting the devs a couple months ago.
Had a great time playing it.
Looks really cool.
And you can get more info at newworld.com.
All right.
Well, now please welcome to the stage a good friend of the Game Awards.
He's been here every year since the first show with a perfect attendance record.
Of course, he's the former president of Nintendo of America.
A friend to all of us.
Let's go!
Bring him on!
Give it up for Reggie Fesemek!
Got the cool glasses.
And he's got the cool glasses.
You all made fun of me for that?
Fesemek is in the house.
Thank you, thank you, thank you for that warm welcome.
It was just over 16 years ago that I joined this industry as an executive.
But truth be told, I've been around as a fan and as a player for so much longer.
Like you, I've witnessed the growth of our favorite form of entertainment.
And now video games are bigger than the movie industry.
Bigger than music.
Can he just be the president of all video games?
Bigger than television.
But most importantly, video games continue to innovate.
Not only as entertainment, but also into areas far more profound.
Experiences with their foundation in video game technology are being used to help surgeons
practice before a difficult procedure.
And to enable college students to simulate business situations and develop real-world skills.
I may no longer be an executive in this industry,
but I'll always be an ambassador for video games as a force for good and a force for fun.
He's quitting?
Don't think you got the memo.
In this category, fresh indie game,
you can see how games are continuing to evolve as entertainment.
I think this is the most important award of the night.
Because I believe indie developers are the most important creators in this industry.
Why?
Why, who wrote that?
Because every nominee this year and every year at one time was an indie developer.
In the same sense that everyone was once a kid sketching a superhero in the middle of class.
Or lying in bed at night thinking of worlds and challenges that no one had ever dreamed of before.
For my friend, Shigeru Miyamoto, those ideas began around the woods near his house in Kyoto.
And for my dear departed friend, Satoru Iwata,
those ideas led him to invent his first video game on a portable calculator while he was still in high school.
These guys fucking made everything.
They both became fixtures in the history of video games.
But first, they were dreamers.
And they began with their imagination.
So like everyone else, at the start, they were true indie developers.
Any awards event is, by definition, a look backwards.
Who's done something great in the preceding year?
But in this category, you can look forward.
If you want to see the incubator where future game greatness is evolving,
it resides right here in this indie category,
recognizing brand new independent studios who released their first game this year.
Really?
Fresh indie game presented by Subway.
Oh shit, this is really?
They're all good.
And the game award goes to...
Disco Elysium.
Disco Elysium also wins Best Independent Game.
Tonight, they're taking home a total of four game awards.
So I'd like to thank all the great people that came before us.
Ilya Repin,
Vladimir Mayakovsky,
Viktor Tsoi,
and Marks and Engels for providing us the political education.
Thank you.
Well, come here.
I've been looking back, looking back my whole life.
Back to my family, my friends,
my son.
They say you can't change a person, but a person can change with time.
Change a mind, change a heart.
Yeah, that might be good enough for you.
But I can change anything.
Is that a game?
Is this another single player League of Legends game?
Alright, surprise.
There's a second League of Legends announcement tonight.
I'm joined by the creative director of Double Stallion Games, Lee Thomas.
Lee, why don't you tell us a bit about what we just saw?
Sure.
Well, that was quite an experience.
So yeah, we're here.
It's been an amazing time keeping this secret,
but we are working with Riot Forge making Convergence, a League of Legends story.
So what is it?
It's a single player action platformer where you play Echo.
Echo is a young inventor who has created a device that can manipulate time.
And we're going to send you down into Zorn, into the depths of the sump.
And we're going to deliver a rich story experience about perils and consequences of
League of Legends has so many fans and people really, really love these characters.
They wouldn't just like Disney style, just make like eight different Mickey Mouse shows.
All right.
In just a moment, five of the nominees are going to go head to head in the best game
direction category.
We'll see who wins that one.
And we've still got some surprises left.
The game awards will be right back.
So they've like how many no stadium?
No, I'm sorry.
I am talking.
How many champions are in League of Legends?
Like 250.
That's 250 different separate TV shows they could make.
Stadia is a gift that won't ever stop growing.
A gift that doesn't take up any space.
The gift of a gift that gives you games anywhere and everywhere and anywhere
and any everywhere with Wi-Fi.
You can even ask yourself for Stadia and give it to yourself.
Get the unthinkable, multi-screenable, no downloads, no updates,
self-giftable gift of Stadia.
One place for all the ways we play.
When are you ever going to do that on an iPhone screen?
Be real with me for a minute.
Why would you just bring it to you and take a shit?
But then you have to have the controller.
So you have the controller in your hand, but then you have an iPhone that you hold in your mouth.
I go, gee, can you use the iPhone to do it?
Is the iPhone a controller?
Do you have to take the phone and do a thing?
No, I don't want to just put that.
I don't want to feel like a big AAA game on the toilet.
When I sit down to play a game, I sit there for like fucking two hours sometimes.
I'm not going to sit on the toilet for two hours.
I've done it before.
Oh, that's actually kind of cool.
I would play that.
Nintendo Switch has worlds to explore and adventures to conquer.
But that trailer was kind of bizarre.
I would probably play that game.
Find your adventure on Nintendo Switch and Nintendo Switch Lite.
I forgot that came out.
We heard you may want to quit vaping.
But we can't help you.
We can barely hold these protest signs.
But we can tell you about this is quitting.
An easy text to quit service.
It's the least.
And most we can do.
I don't need to say it.
Oh, it's back.
Look at all the information on the screen.
Did I count four health bars?
This is like when you go to someone's house that has a World of Warcraft.
And they have like 30 mods installed.
And you can't even physically log in with your character because everything is so fucking strange.
The UI is so different.
And they have like a million things on the screen.
I played all games like that with no, uh, you probably can't hear what I'm saying.
Never mind.
What's going on, everybody?
I'm professional esports host and commentator Goldenboy.
And since 2017, Samsung and Xbox have worked together to deliver amazing experiences for all gamers.
That's why I teamed up with them to create something special for the fans.
The ultimate FTW sweepstakes.
And I want to give a huge shout out to our winner, Isaiah Yanez, also known as Buddy Roy.
You are the winner of the upgrade FTW sweepstakes.
You won this killer Samsung 75 inch Q70R QLED TV, a Q70 soundbar, an Xbox One X,
and 12 months of Xbox Game Pass Ultimate.
Safe to say that's a lot of nuts.
Congrats.
And thank you so much for joining us here tonight.
Now, everyone, let's just enjoy the game award some more.
I would.
I did it.
Thank you, Goldenboy.
And now it's time for a world premiere, a re-announcement that I think you'll be excited about.
A re-announcement.
Elden Ring.
All right, if it's Elden Ring, I'd be real happy.
There was a time when you were heartless, brutal monster.
And I'm proud of you for changing all that.
But I'm here to ask you to be those things once more for them.
For me, can I count on you?
Who the fuck is making this game?
Bigby.
Can I count on you?
Is that Ghost Written by Telltale?
Now, she's an Emmy-winning writer and an accomplished voice actor.
Please welcome Ashley Birch.
Didn't say somebody bought Telltale, right?
Hello, everyone.
They purchased Telltale.
The best games start with a single person asking a single question.
What if?
And when that question excites other people and they start asking what if,
it's a snowball of creativity and passion
that pushes games to be the best they can possibly be.
These are the nominees for the Best Game Direction.
Best Game Direction.
Who's making that game?
I can't get over it.
Who's making it?
So hard to pull a connection.
Yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup.
Resident Evil 2, hands down, is the best one.
Hands down.
If it loses, Alex will be mad.
Death Stranding.
All right, that makes me actually, I'm actually upset about that.
I never get invested in this shit, but that actually makes me irritated.
I'm actually irritated by that.
I am.
Resident Evil 2, from start to finish, was close to perfectly paced.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
It was a start from zero four years ago,
but I'm very happy to come back to this stage tonight.
I really want to thank a lot of people who started the ship going.
Sony started out with us and also Guerrilla for providing the game engine.
And also, it was a small boat, but all the cast came on board,
the musicians, the artists, the people who collaborated.
Thank you so much.
Konami right now is crying somewhere in slot machine revenue.
Came to work together.
I would really like to thank them and also my family.
And best of all, the fans who waited four years.
Thank you so much.
Konami looked at their balance sheet and said,
hey, we made more money in one day with our slot machines than in a decade of video game revenue.
We've got some very special surprise guests here to do the honors.
Over on Twitter, you guys voted for the gaming tweet of the year.
We've got the winning tweet.
Check it out.
And we'll be right back with game of the year.
It's over?
This is it.
It's coming up.
This is the end.
Resident Evil 2 has got to come.
It's got something.
Mr. X is like the best.
Mr. X.
Mr. X is the best video game antagonist for very, very, very long.
I think it's the masks because this is not Destiny 2,
but it's the Destiny 2 mask with the blue lights in it.
Yes, that's the problem.
Is there every game has the mask with the lights in it, the green or blue lights in the mask?
What is this?
It literally said it was ESO.
Is there a best VR game?
Why?
Why is that strangely absent?
Is that not here?
It already happened?
Why was super hot VR not on it?
Oh, super hot VR came out in 2017.
Excuse me.
Room temperature IQ.
Have you guys heard of Magic the Gathering?
Check it out.
Play right now.
All right.
What was that?
That looked cool.
Is it a Predator game?
No, I see the honeycomb.
I'm not interested.
You can guarantee I won't play a game if it has the honeycomb on it.
That's just personal preference.
I'm sorry.
Download a bunch of free games.
I keep them forever.
Now she's an actress and producer.
Please welcome Michelle Rodriguez.
That's how we add a game of the year.
How y'all doing today?
I've invested in this.
How are you?
I'm happy to be here.
There's one last game announcement to share with you tonight.
And I'm really excited about it.
Allow me to present the world premiere of our latest expansion to the Fast and Furious saga.
I'm inflated.
Is it a movie?
I'm going to split.
It's the only way to keep you both safe.
I think I know someone who can help.
You ready to ride?
I'm hunting anybody.
Revenge.
We want justice.
Vin Diesel did not voice act in this game.
They just pulled samples from the last 10 movies.
You know how many times he says that?
Let's go.
For sure.
Come on.
When in doubt, do what I do.
See?
I've seen what you do.
That's why I'm kind of terrified.
And I don't need a finish line.
I'm in my own lane.
Vin Diesel will live off of royalties that people are using.
Vin Diesel will live forever with his just generic free sentences that he said.
He will be collecting just revenue forever.
I'm excited for that one.
Everyone wants to live forever.
From a little article in a newspaper to a movie to a video game.
It's pretty cool.
I'd like to now introduce a surprise guest and also one of my friends for life.
Is it Vin Diesel?
Vin Diesel.
I hope he just speaks in one-liners.
It would be great.
I want him to speak in one-liners.
Do it.
Michelle, we are in our crowd.
We have been gamers.
We have been gamers forever.
And we are at an award show.
Of our people.
Why is he leaning down sideways?
Literally.
Me and Vin used to just like literally spend all night playing like
Tekken Fighter games or Street Fighter.
Yeah this is uh it's amazing to see that that trailer finally.
I didn't tell you before.
Yesterday I saw the four-minute trailer to Fast Night.
What is he doing?
Turn this way.
Why is this back to the audience?
Back to you guys.
Um I love all of you.
Uh okay so.
Like at this point Vin just grabbed the mic and lifted up from the base.
Here to pay tribute to all of the nominees.
Game of the year once again.
The Game Awards Orchestra.
Is it nailed down?
Just her reaction was awesome.
She's just like.
That little like yeah.
I am not certain of very many things.
But I am certain of this.
More than anything.
The Outer Worlds is not going to win Game of the Year.
I have never been more certain of something in my entire life.
It just will not.
Does that make me a villain for saying that?
That's not going to win Game of the Year.
That makes me a villain.
Apparently.
I mean but like Smash is like a pretty big achievement.
There's so much stuff in Smash.
There's so much in it.
There's like a thousand characters.
They keep adding them.
I've seen some.
That kind of startled me.
I mean it could be that too.
But I don't think so.
That wasn't it.
Sekiro was a really polarizing game.
It was very polarizing.
There's like a you either really liked it or you hated it.
For Sekiro.
Or a lot of people.
That was pretty polarizing.
I liked it.
Yeah.
And which game on this list.
Had no polarizing.
I mean besides this guy.
I don't know what.
Where did he come from?
He's the only one on that list that makes sense to me.
Come on.
Sekiro is good. It was. It was very good.
Smash Brothers.
Really good achievement in video games.
But Resident Evil.
The remake.
What remakes can be.
They keep telling me don't lean down.
As my daughter would say.
Dad.
But it's not.
It's very good.
The game of the year award.
Goes to.
Sekiro.
Tonight Sekiro Shadows Die Twice.
Also wins best action adventure game.
The knife just hit behind me.
Boom.
The tomahawk just hit the fucking wall.
I agree.
He's very moved.
If it wasn't Resident Evil.
I agree.
So Sekiro
has a lot of difficult
and complex elements that made us a little
unsure.
When it was about to come out.
And we were both surprised
and overjoyed at the reaction
that we saw.
So I'd like to share
the joy of receiving this award
with the staff at From Software
who pulled out all the stops to make it happen
as well as the team at Activision
for their ongoing support throughout.
It was good.
We're sad that Resident Evil
didn't win anything.
And finally, I'd like to
give out a huge thank you
to our players.
We couldn't have done it without you
and it was a huge honor to make.
So we will continue to try and make
the best games we possibly can.
Thank you.
Congratulations from Software, Miyazaki-san.
Game of the Year for Sekiro.
Alright guys, well that's going to do it for the Game Awards 2019.
Thank you so much for joining us.
We'll see you again next time.
Thank you.
It's December, to keep celebrating games.
Have a great night. Thank you very much.
Good night everybody.
Here are my thoughts.
I don't remember any of the games.
I don't remember anything.
I remember
No More Heroes 3.
And then I remember the Gemini Man trailer.
So if that means anything,
that means
that No More Heroes 3 is probably
going to be cool, I think.
That's what that means.
Constant conflict.
We did get a constant conflict, you're right.
The Muppets came out, yeah.
They were there.
And The Goose was there too.
What else happened?
I don't know.
We saw a bunch of MMOs
and some mobile games.
Reggie was there, Green Day was there.
Magic the Gathering.
I'm kind of sad that
Resident Evil 2 didn't win anything.
The time that I had...
Let me get the headphone out of here.
I don't want anyone talking to me.
The feeling of real dread.
It was a remake.
So what?
It was a remake from 1998.
It was a really, really
good game.
It was the feeling of dread
going around corners.
It was brilliantly paced.
It was the revitalization of Capcom as a company.
They came out with Monster Hunter World.
That was great.
And then they had Resident Evil 2, and now they're coming out with Resident Evil 3.
You said that already.
Don't you know that when you lose,
you just go on repeat until you
go to sleep that night?
When the stream's over, I'm going to be in the mirror going,
the sense of dread that I had.
Turning the corners, Mr. X
was so brilliantly, brilliantly
cast. And then I'm going to
turn the shower on, like lean backwards
and have cold water just hit me right in my eyes.
Sekiro won. I know, I know.
But I think Resident Evil 2 deserves something.
Even if it was just like
they brought him on stage and gave him a fucking
like, you got a shot lollipop.
I thought it was Game of the Year. I thought it was.
I thought it was, but you know, whatever.
You can't win them all. You can't win them all.
Because I obviously had something to do with that game.
So I'm so invested.
You know, you can't win them all.
Alright, let's talk about Minecraft.
He's a 10 on the German scale. No, it was a fuck chill.
They're trying.
Alright, you guys ready?
Talking about constant conflict. I don't even know if that game was.
I just know it exists.
Okay, so
those of you that don't know what we're about to talk about
I actually have to change to just chatting.
If you just stuck around for the game awards
thanks for sticking around.
Those of you that are still here
we're going to spend a little bit of time going over what's going to happen
this weekend.
I never played the Claire campaign.
I didn't stream the Claire campaign.
What? I'm not allowed to play something?
I didn't, I did not play it off stream.
I'm lying to you.
No, I'm kidding.
My god. You think I would say something to Game of the Year
if I didn't do it all? I played half the game.
Hey, I played all of Sekiro
and I played half of Resident Evil 2
and I thought, uh oh, that's bad.
Somebody's going to be like, what the fuck did he just say?
Anyways,
take a look at your screen here.
We're going to do some drawing.
Take a look at your screen. We are going to talk about
what's happening this weekend.
What are you doing this weekend? What do you mean this weekend?
This weekend we're going to play a little game
called Fuck the King.
I didn't even change category. That's my bad.
I'll just keep it as obnoxious audience member.
That's fine.
So on Sunday,
there'll be, you'll, uh,
that's the next stream that's going to happen.
So you will not see me
until Sunday.
About an hour before the stream starts on Sunday
because there's a lot of stuff that we still need to do.
We will begin the process
of putting people into the server.
Show your Resident Evil 2 achievements.
No, I don't have to do that.
So, what is going to happen?
First and foremost, let's start drawing.
On Sunday, if you are
a two month
long subscriber,
why am I doing this?
The only way that you will have
access to this game
is if you have been subbed to the channel for two months straight.
The reason why this had to happen
is because of very obvious things.
We're trying to protect the server
from getting
just overloaded with people.
We're trying to protect the server from
insane amounts of connections.
And we do already have things in place
to help with that.
There's a lot of stuff that these guys are pros.
They know exactly what they're doing.
You have to be subbed for two months to play.
Now what does playing mean?
Playing is
opening up your Minecraft client,
going to the server,
and starting
in our little town.
Our little town is going to look like this.
Our little town
is going to look like this.
There's going to be a castle here.
Like this.
And down here there'll be some houses.
Probably, you know, just random little town houses.
There'll be a little garden over here.
No.
It's an apple.
It's a spider.
Will you guys just relax?
Alright, I can't look at chat. You guys are making me laugh.
So in this town,
there's a castle, right?
Ooh, look, the castle was here.
Inside of this castle is going to be
me. I am
the king of this kingdom.
The goal that you guys have, by the way,
there are, I gotta write this down too because I want as much
info as I can.
The server holds just about
just over 500 people.
Can be on this Minecraft server.
That's important. Two months substrate.
500 people can play at once.
And it's going to cycle out all the time.
Because we have a
some code and an API in place.
For, if you are a sub,
if you are a two month plus sub,
you just simply have to log into the server
and authenticate your, with Twitch.
That's how the whitelisting
is going to work. There's going to be a
separate little site that you're going
to link into.
And you'll get a code. And it'll verify
that you are subbed for two months.
And then you can join the server.
When you join the server,
you are going to be
zero years old.
Now what does that mean? That means
there's an aging system in the game.
It takes, as of right now,
ten hours
for you to die. This is, by the way,
it is a hardcore server. If you die
you're out. If you die
you cannot come back in. You start
at zero, you're going to age, it's going to take
ten hours. You have ten hours of time.
When you are zero,
you can't talk.
You're essentially a baby.
You can't talk.
You can't build. And you can't hold
a weapon. How could you?
And, by the way, you walk
at minus
probably, we're trying to still figure out how
fast, probably like minus a hundred percent speed.
All players
I'm going to like make this smaller.
The age from zero
to, probably like zero
to two, zero to three, is
going to take probably about twenty
minutes. Because you age
zero to a hundred. So let me
add this here. Start at zero
and die at a hundred.
At about ninety years
old, you
slow down.
You can't craft that many
materials anymore. You can't
swing a weapon as fast as you used
to. And you're probably saying
wait a minute, why are you doing this? Well
if you start at zero and can't
talk, and can't do anything
that prevents you from being
able to just try
to come kill me immediately. You could.
You could.
You can still punch.
You're just not going to do very much damage.
Good luck. By the way, if you die you can't
come back. So
I would be careful if I were you.
A baby rush.
I'm not going to tell you how to play this
game because this is an experiment.
Baby rush the castle.
Well, if you do that
just be known that
you can't come back and you are going to
get all new players.
I already wrote this. All
new players.
All new players.
I'm going to outline this.
Start at zero. There's going
to be a separate lobby where people
can hang out. Potentially even a separate server
that you're going to connect to.
Whoever dies, the next
person in line is going to come in
that has a connected Twitch account.
So let's say that there is five hundred people in the
server and a hundred and fifty
of you decide to communicate with each other
somehow and do a baby rush.
And all of you just don't make it.
A hundred people that were next in line that have their
Twitches connected that are in the lobby will be put into
the game at zero. Do these
rules apply to you?
No. The king, which is
me, has double
health and
double armor because I'm
the fucking king. Oh, sorry.
Forgot to mention something else. Very, very,
very important. Let's put it over here.
There is a stamina
bar. You have to eat, guys.
And you have to sleep.
You have a stamina bar. It's going to be
in replace of the experience bar.
If you get to zero stamina, well
you're going to be very useless because that
means you haven't eaten. All
actions, and again,
all actions
require stamina.
That's putting a block down.
That's swinging a weapon. That's
walking. That's running.
If you do not eat,
you're not going to be able to do shit.
I have to eat, but I have
the three or four caches
of steaks in my trunk behind me.
What do I care? How are you going to eat his babies?
Don't worry.
There'll be ways to eat. Poison the
king. There is going to
be another spot.
So this is all, we'll slow down here for a second
here. When you join the
game, when you join the server,
like I said, you're going to have to connect to your Twitch, see if you have two
months up, you can come in. We're going to spend about an hour
before the stream truly
begins, just getting everybody
connected. So once everybody's
in place, and we have
commands, and we have plugins, we're just going to
keep you, we're going to keep you staying put.
Outside of these
walls is the wilderness.
Outside here, right?
Let's just like a million
meters outside.
The real important shit happens inside
the town. Outside
the town, you are free
to go get resources.
You can do whatever you want. You can go build
whatever you want. This is kind of like
out of play. But you can
use it to get resources.
We are actually still toying with the idea of having
a couple of different servers.
That the town is one server,
the wilderness is another
instance, right?
Who's going to protect the babies?
Kind of rot in the wild.
Can babies kill babies?
What you guys
are doing in this game,
remember, if I die,
it's over. You have to
remember,
these two age groups here are
really only in place to
prevent people from just
like detonating the whole server
instantly. So
if you have 10 hours to be
in the server, realistically
only about 30 or 40 minutes of that
time, if you stay alive, is
going to be at these more constrained
parts of your life. People who are
age 3 are just going to slaughter people
who come in.
Well, it's funny you say that.
Because we're also toying with the idea
of having a
tag on people's heads that kill
innocent people for no reason.
I'm the king. And I'm
going to have a bunch of kingsguard.
And a bunch of loyal people.
If there is a crime that's committed that needs
to be brought to my attention, I will go investigate
this. I'm going to have a team
of people that are going to be keeping the peace.
I'm not just going to let my kingdom
fall into total ruin. Why would
I do that? I'm going to, I will
come out and I will solve problems. I will
teleport the perpetrator into
the throne room and we will have a little
trial. Well, you're going to be
teleporting a bunch of people into that throne room
because nobody's going to stop killing
zero aged people.
It's going to be very, very fun.
For a lot of different reasons.
I kind
of want to just see how this
plays out. When is this happening on
Sunday? Do the kingsguard
age at the same rate that you do?
Yes. When I kill
your guards, will they respawn? No.
Nobody respawns.
How's it going to be streamed?
So, there's going to be a separate
mobile studio that is made
that is going to be
streaming the event
and we're going to have like three or four different
cameras, free cam flying around to
cut to, and my perspective.
Because I want to be able to see what
some of the other shit that's happening. I want you, for a viewer
perspective, right? It's more
interesting if you guys
get to see a ton of different perspectives. If you're playing
the game, sure, just you're playing the game and you're
participating in the little experiment, right?
But you won't just see
my point of view. You'll
hear me talk and I'll be
going over the things that need to be
going over with my kingdom.
How do you join? When this
server launches, like I said,
there's going to be just a little lobby that you can
just be in. You then
connect your Twitch with a separate, there's going to be a
separate website that you're going to
use, that you're going to connect your Twitch API to
it. It just pulls
how many months you've been subscribed to
my channel. That's it. Doesn't do anything else.
Can the guards betray you?
No. Jeremy,
you're trying to get my data.
No, let me be very, very clear
about something. This
is not, oh yeah,
I'm just like running a server.
There's a lot of resources
put into this to make sure it works.
There's a lot of protection,
there's a lot of servers.
It is not just
running in my basement.
This stupid experiment
is really important
to me. I don't care
if I die in the first five minutes
by falling down the fucking
stairs. I don't care.
By the way, this
first iteration
of, it's called FTK, it's called
Fuck The King, FTK. The first
iteration is very much going to be
an alpha beta.
We're just trying to see if it works.
After we do one, we'll have
a lot of, we'll have
a lot of info. I want to do
this more than once. I want to
add more stuff to it. I want to make it more interesting.
I want to add more, I want to add
like quests and shit eventually. I want to
do a bunch of random shit with this server.
And going back and forth with
some of the developers and the people that are making the
plugins and the server and everything,
they're excited too. They want to do
more stuff on top of this as well.
But the first one is just to see
if we can do it and how long
I can last and how
democratically this whole thing can
play out or not. And it's just chaos.
And 500 of you
rush the front door.
And die.
And then the next 500 people will
then know that that cannot
be accomplished.
Maybe it can. Maybe you can
sneak into the window in
my bathroom and break in and
shoot me with a bow and arrow. Which,
by the way, let's go over another thing.
I'm not even going to write this down because I can't.
I'm useless.
Weapons. Oh, Jerma, I'm just going
to make an enchantment table and I'm going to make
an enchanted bow and you're going to die in one click.
Nope. The only
available weapons are bows
and swords.
You cannot do that.
TNT is something we're still fighting
with to figure out if we're going to
do it immediately. Probably not immediately.
Just melee weapons
that make sense and ranged
weapons that make sense.
I might walk out the front door and get
exploded by a creeper. It's very
possible. Potions? Not yet.
No. Like I said, the first
stream of this is going to see
what happens when
500 plus people are told,
hey, you live in a kingdom now and there's a
king in there. Go get him.
Or don't. Or don't.
Good luck. It's going to
be fucking calamity.
Can you live in the wilderness?
Do whatever you want. Is there voice chat?
There's not going to be voice chat. That would be
impossible with 500 people.
This is very important. What Minecraft version?
The Minecraft version
is going to be 1.8.
It is not going to be on the new
Minecraft. I was told there's
a lot of, for having this many
people in a server, it's just
not possible to have like 500
to 1,000 people in the same spot.
It's just impossible.
We could have done maybe like
30 people, 50 people maybe.
What's your plan to get 500 people to sleep
at the same time? You don't have to sleep at the same time.
And also, let me, I got to make
sure that I'm saying this correctly. I think
once the server is live, it
won't matter what version you have. You'll just
connect to the server and it'll just run it
from what I've been told. So
I think it's going to be running on 1.8
but I don't think you need to have
somehow
1.8 something.
Doesn't work like that. I'm
completely wrong. Is there safe
areas? No. Can you
be guards? No.
Is chat going to be localized? Yes.
That's another thing. When you
talk, it is only going to be the
people that you are in the exact
vicinity of.
There is not a complete and total
always global chat. Can you be
promoted? Yes. I have the capability
to make anyone in the server anyone I want.
Does the hardcore death bar you from future
streams? Yes.
But, this is a very, very
large, huge in quotations
but, we're going
to see how many people
are trying to join the server.
So, let's say for instance
after we do this once or twice
it's very clear that
there are no more players that can even
queue up. That's when we can be like
alright, it's from scratch, let's do
it again. But for the first stream or
two, no, it's permanent.
Because remember, here's another thing.
I might not die in the first stream.
We keep going. We keep going.
We'll do it again next week. And
this is not a persistent server.
This is not a 24-7.
It's just on. No, no, no, this
server is only turned on when the stream
exists. Everything is
saved. Everything is locked in.
This is not a 24-hour
just Minecraft server that's going to exist. It's only
going to happen on the streams. How long
is the first stream going to be? I don't know.
It's up to, because
of how many people are involved, because remember
there's three or four cameramen.
There's two or three server
admins. And there's a lot
of people that are in a lot of moving parts.
So I would say this stream would be like
up to probably two to four hours.
It's not going to be
more than the first one. We'll do it in like
three to four hour chunks.
Potentially like I'd say up to four plus maybe
five hours total.
Because there's a lot of people involved and there's obviously
a lot of their time. So how do you
replace AFK players? That's a great question.
I'll bring that up with the, for the next
three days, this is all I'm doing.
So I, like, this is the only
thing I'm doing for the next two, three straight days until
the stream. So I will
bring that up and it will probably have a certain time limit when
they get booted and it brings another person in.
Feeling you can die in the first hour?
Possible. Very possible.
Do I die at a hundred? Yes.
I could just die in the throne
room at old age. I could
just be sitting in the throne room and be ninety-nine.
You didn't get me.
You'll never kill me. And then I'm just going to start
burning like money and food
and shit. I'm going to be buried with
the stakes. No, no, no. I don't want to give up
funny, funny fucking scenarios.
How are you, are you a
zero-year-old baby king? No.
I start, I age
slower. Not by very much, but I do
age slower. But I do
start at a normal, like
twenty, twenty-five.
Something like that. Just so I can actually move around. I'm not going to be
a baby king.
Who's going to take care of the babies?
I don't know. Maybe you.
Maybe you'll take care of the babies.
Maybe you should make that your thing
that you do. But
Jerma, we're going to kill you in five minutes.
Sure you're not just going to kill each other?
Jerma's going to die in ten minutes.
You think so?
This, I already know
it's going to happen. And I don't
even need to say it because you all know. The first
ten minutes of this is happening.
Two hundred of you are just
going to be as zero-year-olds.
Just go storm the gate. And
we, and then we just freed up
two hundred more spots on the server. So
just be aware.
You're going to zero-rush.
Maybe it'll work.
If you leave the server
or you crash, we'll use the, yeah, it's
not tied to me.
Every time we stream this, there's going
to be a couple people who are going to be running
the show in the background that are running
the server. And they can help with problems.
They can fix things that happen if I crash.
It doesn't just, if I, oh, the stream
crashed. Oh, it's over.
Like, it'll still exist.
We can pause it. I can come back.
There'll be somebody on call that's taking
care of it. If you live for ten hours
and there's three hour streams, then you can do it
for three streams. There's also,
it might
not be ten hours. We can make that whatever
we want. I can make that six,
right? You make that six, seven, five.
If a player crashes, can they
reconnect? Yes. There's going to
be a certain time frame when you can come back.
Do you have to worry about dying as a baby
from an older player? Yes.
But, just be aware,
if you are just causing
problems, it's real
easy to get rid of you.
I am going to have at least a
dozen people that are in the
best armor times two
in the whole game and are
stronger than you.
They're coming
for you. We've also,
there's also the idea
that maybe, for the
first five, the first
year of your life, maybe you're in
invincible to other players.
That's another idea that I'm
going to throw out to them. That maybe
for almost like a spawn
protection kind of way.
So the first fifteen, twenty minutes
that you're in the game, you can't be killed
by another player. You can still
die from the environment maybe, but I don't know.
We might just see what happens.
I want to do this more than once. I want to do this more than
twice. I want to do this at least
a few times. I think it's a really, really
just fun idea. I do.
Baby Rush with invincibility.
Will you be okay with people streaming
it?
I guess. I don't
see why not.
The thing about
if you were to like play and stream,
the camera angles will be
that would just be your perspective.
Yes, it's the Java
Minecraft. It's the Java Minecraft.
Not the Microsoft one.
Is there a reward for someone that kills you?
Yes, you turned off the stream.
That's your reward. If we all start as
babies, who takes care of us?
I don't know.
Ask the cavemen.
How did they do it?
How did the first man? I don't know.
Figure it out. You have to take care
of each other.
Here's another thing that I was thinking.
Remember, this is all not set in stone.
The other thing that I was thinking is
have some designated
community members
that are not just
going to kill everybody.
That can be trusted.
That will just be
like 10,
15.
And that's it. But you can still eat
and move.
Remember, when you see
like the, oh, I'm zero years old.
That's just essentially your time
in the server.
So you can still do things.
You can still move around, but you just can't talk.
It actually scrambles your
text like it does in games like
World of Warcraft. If you are a baby
and you write something for the first 20 minutes,
it literally is ineligible.
So it's basically one hour.
I would like it to be more than five hours
in server, in game, for a whole
life. Between five and ten, we're still trying to
figure it out. But there'd be a thing that hides
player name tags. Not sure
yet. Not sure yet. There's going to
be a HUD. There's going to be a little HUD
that'll show you your current
title, your current name, your
your current health. You'll
have a little HUD in the corner.
When is the server going to become available?
It is not
ready. The town
is still being built right now.
So it's not going to be ready
till the day that we do it.
But
for testing purposes,
obviously, I might
pull in some people, like a few.
Maybe like the day before
or like the day of,
like in the morning. We don't get to build?
Yes, you can. There's
a whole town that's being
built right now. It looks awesome.
It looks unbelievable. Where do you guys
see this town? Do we own property?
Not immediately.
Remember, this is a very
this whole thing is just a
alpha like 0.5.
It's very much an experiment
in work in progress right now.
What is available right now
is getting all the people there, having the
age system in place, having the
people, the amount of people that we want,
having the stamina bar in the food,
and having the town.
And having the outside.
Those of you saying, well, can I like
own property outside
the town? Yeah, this is going to be just a whole
area that's kind of just
to whatever. It's going to be, you can do
whatever you want. But it's also going to take
more materials
to build. When I say materials, you have a stamina bar,
right? So you can't just
build dirt everywhere.
You can't just, oh, I'm going to pick this up and make a
giant like dirt dick.
That's impossible because you'd have
to have stamina to build.
It costs stamina for you to place a block.
Let's just put it that way. So you guys are going to
have to work together to build houses. You can't
just make a dirt dick. It's not going to happen.
You could, I guess,
you could pick your little spot in the wilderness and make a dirt
dick. But that's going to take you
like your whole life.
Don't give them ideas.
It's worth it.
My whole life
was dedicated to making a dirt
dick.
I can rest peacefully now.
There's ideas to eventually
add. And pretty much what you see
on the screen right now
is what the stream will be
at first. Once we get one
under the belt, there's going to be so much data
that we'll have to do it
again. We'll learn
so much from the first one.
We'll just keep it moving forward.
There's nothing for us to install.
Nope. There, you do not have
to get any mods. You do not have to get
anything special. You just have to
go in the server. Entering
the server will be putting in the
server IP.
Right? Like always.
Once you get in, you will be
in a separate little lobby, which you
will then have. It isn't going to be
a separate website that's going
to generate a code for you. It's going to check
to see how many months you've been subbed
to the channel. Completely separated.
It'll see.
You'll get a code. Put it in.
Very simple.
There you go. Can we make our own kingdom
next door? Sure, but I'll just come destroy
it. Does it have to be an active
sub? Yes. If you guys
go make your own kingdom, are you going to make your own
kingdom? I don't think so. There's only
one kingdom here. Me.
I will squash this
rebellion. If you do one, I will just
squash it. We're going to rise
up. Are you though? Because
there, I'm not going to be a bad king.
I'm going to come
out and talk to the people
and there'll be events. There are going
to be events planned where, you know, we
go and check out the garden that's being built
and created. You just said
I'm going to be a very fair king.
Are you going to get poisoned? No, I will
not. There's going to be ten people in front of me that will eat
before I do. I'm going
to have a stash of a hundred steaks.
The first ten are going to be eaten
by my royal kingsguard
and then I'll eat the eleventh one
to make sure it's not poisoned.
How's sleeping going to work?
So, sleeping,
you can refill your stamina by sleeping
and also eating. You'll be
doing it mostly by eating.
But if you lie down in a bed,
you will recharge at a very fast rate.
But you have to lie there
for at least a minute or two.
You have to lie facing up to the ceiling
for like a full sixty seconds.
Potentially up to two minutes.
Just lie down
for like two years.
You have to determine what you want
to do for time. No, not everyone
has to sleep at once. It can be tied
to just the person's ID. That's not
a problem. Until we're strong enough
to kill. Just sleep your whole
life. You could do that if you wanted to.
You could spawn in
as a baby, slowly
with four or five other babies, build
a small baby house,
make a bed, and lie
in it until you die. You can
sleep at any time. It's just simply
a way to make you have to
not participate.
You know what I'm saying?
If you lie down, if a bunch of people
have to lie down for sixty seconds,
two minutes, that's not time that you're
storming the front gates
with your knives.
You've got to play by the rules.
If you have zero stamina,
you can still move around. That's fine.
You can still walk, you can still
punch, you can still grab, you can still
build. You just do it at a
times five slower rate.
You could be walking on at zero stamina
and you swing at minus two hundred percent speed.
What's the point of the server of when you die
within the first hour? That's not going to
happen. You guys don't know the things
that I know. I know a lot of things.
That's not going to happen.
There is no chance in hell
that I die in the first hour of the stream.
Not a chance in hell.
You guys are going to be babies.
What, you're going to surround me?
Five hundred babies are going to surround
the castle? That's not
going to happen. I can
see it. I could look out my window
and see
the baby zerg rush
and know what's going to happen.
Is it going to be a two beat?
I don't know what that style queue. I don't know what that means.
This, the queue system,
the server, it's being handled by
incredibly competent people.
So there, they know exactly
what they're doing. This
is not the first time they've done large
scale servers.
They have a lot of experience. So
they, I'm assuming, if it's something
that would be good,
it's there. They actually are very,
very highly qualified. We'll just put
that way. Imagine the lag.
That's another thing that we've already talked about, that we've
already figured out. There is
going to be selective rendering.
So if you are
standing in your house,
you are not going to render
what's happening at the castle
because you don't have to.
Do the kings go get fancy outfits? Of course
they do. That's default to
Minecraft. Yeah, see?
How will redstone work? I don't think there's going to be redstone.
There's actually
talk of being able to not render
people that are under two or three years
old, if the server
load gets too big. There's a lot
of stuff, and these are very powerful
servers too. Like I said,
this is, this is not,
I didn't just go to servers.com
and buy one.
They're very, very, very powerful servers.
Invisible ghost
baby rush. Is there a
currency? No. That's something that we might
want to do eventually though. Remember,
it has to work
first. It has to work.
And this was just based off of
some just stupid idea
about World of Warcraft and not doing
anything and just having people play the game around
me. And it just, it
became a stream. This is just
we, I gotta, I gotta paddle
right now. And I'm just kind of
paddling around somewhere in water that I've
never been in. I think this is
going to be a lot of fun. And expect
after the first one,
for some of the, I see a lot of people saying,
hey, what about this? What about
the currency? What about, what
are the titles going to do? In the
future we will have lots of things.
It does have a lot of potential.
Okay, I will just say this.
It will be worth,
it will be worth doing once.
Just to see what happens.
And that's worth it to me.
Regardless of how
time intensive, how many people are
involved, how much money or resources,
I think it's just worth trying. It should
be fun. I'm pogging
so fucking hard right now.
I refuse to let this die after one
attempt. What's the kingdom's
name? That's something I haven't
even thought of. I don't know.
I have to think about that.
Germacraft. We'll figure that out.
But the next thing that you need to hear
is, when Sunday
comes along, the
stream is going to be starting, I believe, at about
4pm Pacific. We
still haven't locked that down 100%, but
it doesn't really matter, because
the first
at least
two to three hours
before it, and the first hour
of the stream being live, we're
going to be getting people in position to start.
This is not going to be a case of
okay, the stream is on,
okay, let's go, get in the server, let's go.
Are you guys ready? No,
this is going to be at least an hour
of getting people in.
This is on Sunday, Sunday afternoon Pacific.
Sunday the 15th,
that's the next time you will see me live.
I will be around
in the Discord. If you are very interested
in this, hang out in the Discord
over the next couple of days, because I'm going to be
around for three days straight here.
I'll give updates, I will tell you guys
more things that are being added, maybe some
things that might have to change last second.
If you would like to keep up to date with
that, I'm just going to make another
channel. It's just going to be
FTK, and it's just going to be
just info, and if there's
any server info and stuff like that,
it'll be there. You're going to
leak the plans.
What is this?
Here's the attack plan.
Let's see what the attack plan is.
Swordsman and Archer's attack
term. Baby sword blocks retreat path.
Hold on a minute.
Let's go over this incredibly flawed
plan. What do you say? Okay, let's see.
Dermal walk path,
bait location. Swordsman are hiding
in the house as Archer is at the top.
Swordsman and Archer's attack term
of baby sword blocks retreat path and attack
run behind. Base of operation.
Yeah,
guys, do it. Do it.
Form alliances.
Make plans. Do it.
I really, really want you to.
Good luck.
You're going to need it. Dirt-dick alliance.
But, that's the plan.
Any other questions,
we will go over them in the
Discord. I just wanted to give a basic
understanding of how this is going to work. Is there a
jail? No. Not yet. Not on the first one.
Think of the first one as an
experiment, like I said before. It's
the first iteration of an alpha
essentially. And I'll see you guys
on Sunday. Good luck.
See you in the Discord possibly.
And that's going to be it for me. Be
prepared. Oh, I've been preparing
for the last three,
four weeks. You don't, what, you don't
think that I,
you don't think that I have
some tricks up
my sleeve? What, I'm just,
I'm just going to die?
You don't think I have things
in place? You don't think I
have my own plans?
You don't think I know these things?
I ain't just going to let you
walk in the front door.
I ain't going to let you just come in the
back door. Not
going to happen. Good luck.
But I'll see you on Sunday. We'll give it
a try. That's the next time you'll see
me. Thanks for hanging out for the game awards.
Let's get some music on here, huh?
He's going to play self-destruct buttons.
Maybe. Thank you for watching.
See you Sunday. 4pm Pacific.
Great Canadian Fuck Club
thanks to the five community subs right now.
There was also, I think I saw,
yeah, Great Canadian Fuck Club gave 5000
bits on top of the subs.
$50 from
Great Canadian. Jerma, King of the Andals,
The Royner, and The Short Men.
Thank you,
Great Canadian, for your massive
contribution here. Thank you.
10, 20, 15
community subs at least.
And $50.
He's short. Splard, thanks
for the five community subs. I think we got it.
Freddy Dread gave $100 at the beginning of the stream.
Huge thank you.
Sad Vega, thanks for the 300 bits.
Death Stranding's soundtrack was comparable to Hipster
Kitchen Music. My God, they are going to win
so many undeserved rewards.
What is Hipster Kitchen
Music? I don't know, Kitchen
Music was its own genre. The Dirt
Dick Alliance is coming for you.
Alright, well, fine.
Thank you, Maddie, for the
$5.30.
530 bits. Jerma, you're always going
to be my content creator of the year. There's no doubt
you make the world a brighter place. Thank you for
all the laughs. We all appreciate it more than you may think.
Love you.
Thank you, Maddie. I don't need any awards.
Appreciate that.
Thank you, Teypan,
for the 300 bits. 300 bits.
No message, just
three dollars. Thank you.
Sad Vega, thanks for 300 bits. My heart
broke hearing you say you will never play Luigi's Mansion 3.
My ADHD
and obsessive compulsive
nature makes me unable
to complete that game.
Malto, thanks for the 500 bits.
Thank you, Malto69.
Imagine a game so big it actually sells
as its own console to fit all its
content.
That would have to be...
That would have to be a very big game.
VR.
Well, the VR was only
doesn't live in your house simulator.
Thank you, Platadonius
Platadenius, thanks for the 500 bits.
Vin Diesel had to lean down to
speak into the microphone because he's tall.
Jerma, that's just how it is for people over
six feet tall. That microphone was
probably four and a half feet off the ground.
Vin Diesel is 5'10".
Okay.
Thank you, Castelion
for the 300 bits.
Hey, Jerma, I hope this TGA show, though awful,
convinces you to try Disco
Elcium in future. I'd love to see you
as a terrible degenerate detective
in this very little conflict.
Really? Well, it is not a constant
conflict. Why would I even want to play it?
I even said the name wrong.
Thank you, though. I'll have to
give it a real look.
Gnarly, thanks for the 250.
Sekiro was my game of the year, so I'm glad it won.
Also, I guess I'm the only League of Legends player
here because I'm super hyped for the new
League of Legends platformer and RPG
games, but no one else in
chat is. Still was an
underwhelming show, though.
I don't even have an opinion. I don't
play League. I don't really know the characters. I don't
connect with the world. I don't know anything about it, so.
Thank you, Nearshrew, for the five
community subs. And again,
great Canadian come in with a huge amount of money. Thank you,
Canadian. 25
Dr. Pepper, thanks for the 250 bits.
Fuck the king. That's treason.
I want to be the king's friend.
You are the exact reason
why I think people are very seriously overestimating
how quickly I'm going to die.
Remember, you've only got
like six-ish plus hours
in the server total.
You don't want to enjoy those six hours.
Six plus maybe
hours. You want to come kill you, but
if you're just going to die, you can't come back in.
You want to protect that person
that keeps that going. You want to protect
my kingdom and me.
You get to stay around.
You rush the front door in the first
20, 30 minutes of the game, then
you're just throwing away your game time
and you can't come back.
Think about it before you choose
these things. What happens if
everyone dies except the king?
It's just going to pull the next people
that are in the queue.
Let's say, because let's say there's 500 people
that are allowed in the server, and
three, four, five
thousand people all want to sign up
at the same time. They'll always just
be somebody else that can replace.
And like I said previously, if it gets to a point
where we're out of potential players,
we can wipe the slate clean
and just do it again.
If there's no more people left in the queue, then we'll just
refresh it.
We may even
it really just depends on how many people actually try.
1.8. Version of Minecraft is 1.8.
Is there going to be a queue
waiting room? Yes.
It'll be separate from the actual server.
Is it going to replace normal streams?
I don't, I mean, I don't know
what you mean by the word replace.
It's just a stream.
Is there an age limit?
A hundred, and you die.
I imagine this would be something I would want to do at least
once a week. For the first
do it three or four times and see how
good. Even if I die.
Do you age when offline? No.
You do not.
And we're going to make sure,
just to add to what we were saying before,
in that initial queue lobby system,
I'm going to make sure that there are a
shitload of rules that are just
put there for you to read
and kind of
compress them in at your own pace.
What happens when I die?
When I die, it's over and we do it again next week.
Now there are some
rules where if I die certain ways,
then I would just
come back and reset it. Because
if there is a weird
disconnect issue, or if something happens
to my game, or if there's an actual
glitch or something and I shouldn't have died,
then I come back.
If I disconnect
and I die because I was disconnected for too long,
then no, the king isn't dead because he
DC'd. He's going to get
crystal killed. No, there's no crystals.
There's no crystals.
There's only bows and swords
and small melee weapons. You can't
create magic fucking potion
bombs. We're going to
drop an anvil on him. Summon
a wither on him. That doesn't
exist. Only
creepers, skeletons, and zombies
are the only
enemies that will exist in the world.
No endermen,
no magicians,
no teleporting monsters. Oh yeah, spiders,
yes, yes, yes. Just the
basic enemies that don't have
a special mechanic
that instantly kills you in shit.
None of that. Because we don't give a shit
about that anyways. It's us
that we care about, not what monsters
are spawnable. Let's keep going though.
And again, questions,
comments. I'm going to be around
all day for the next few days
jumping back and forth. I'll be
in the discord. I'll make a separate channel. We can talk.
Go check it out.
I want a graffiti of your castle. We'll give you buckets.
Probably not immediately.
But thank you gooberry juice.
Why am I ruling a city of just babies?
Whose babies are we? Did you
kidnap us? Are you employing babies?
No, it's not. It's just
the time that you're in the server.
And it's in place
to prevent
immediate griefing.
Of the immediate nature.
I spawn, turn,
and kill the guy
standing next to me in five seconds
of spawning. That's why it's
there. It's battle royale.
I don't want this to turn into a br.
I don't want this to be baby br.
The first 10 to 20 minutes
of your time in the game, you're almost
100% useless.
This is just br. Kind of.
Thank you sly161 for the
250. Really looking forward to this minecraft stream.
Let me know if you need a royal food taste tester.
Yeah, we just gotta get one off the ground
first. And then this can progress
in a million ways.
Hey, Phil White, thanks for the thousand bits, Phil.
I'm really excited to see what I can
do to serve my king till I'm old of age.
But in reality, I'm probably
just going to be one of the bludgeoned
babies during the dark age.
Alright, let's talk about
something else real quick.
The first few hundred people
that come into the server,
you're the pioneers.
It is the dark times. It is the pioneering
stage of this game.
Because you
are the first. Whoever
comes after you
is going to have seen what happened
to you. And they
are going to have to maybe change their game plan
a little. Everyone in that first
wave, I don't know
what's going to happen. It is not going to be
a persistent server. We're going
to save state the server when the stream turns off
and turn it on the next time.
Are there going to be secrets?
Yeah, I, yes, yes.
I want to, eventually,
this is all eventually stuff.
I want to add little missions that people
can go on. Any way
that I can distract you.
This is called Fuck the King. But what
if things are more interesting than
Fuck the King? We'll see.
Distracting us from the
slaughter. Hey Sad Vega, thanks
again for the thousand bits. I cannot wait to watch
this shit show play out. Here's
some more bits to the cause. Hope when
I can get out on this. Do you plan to do other games
for FTK?
I'd love to see a
Conan version. The idea
is there. Minecraft was just
the easiest to have a bunch of people in.
You're aware this is going to be an
unmitigated disaster, correct?
Yeah, I wouldn't have this any other way.
That's sort of intentional,
I think. I think that's part of the plan.
If it goes completely smoothly
and it's
almost unexpected at this point.
All babies move north to build
a dirt dick city. We will create an opposing civilization.
Gain strength, improving our weapons
and armor. Then we will come commence
the assault on the kingdom.
You're going to tell what your plan is.
Again,
I don't know what you guys are doing.
There's going to be a bunch of cameras that we're
cutting to that are showing the world.
Zooming in on stuff, seeing any interesting
thing happening in the town or outside in the wilderness.
I don't know those things. I'm
playing the game with you.
If you guys made a new civilization
that I didn't know about,
how would I ever know it existed in the first place?
If I find out about it,
oh, you're fucked.
Is the town destructible?
I don't think so.
Not immediately.
I think certain things can be
destroyed.
We're not sure yet. We're trying to see how that would all work.
I don't think you can
build in the city.
We decided to do that to keep it
pretty clear.
The out of bounds area
is more designed for you to kind of make
your own little houses and have your own little communities
and stuff.
The actual town with the castles
and the little shops and the walkways,
that's more for
participating in the game.
What does the king do? Whatever I want.
Survive. Exist.
Participate.
Play. Engage.
All things.
We're talking about the capital.
To give you an idea,
the actual capital, the town,
is I believe
2000 by 2000.
And then outside of that is a much larger
area. It's pretty big.
I just want to make a house and live with the Germanites.
I don't think that many
players can play on that, on your idea.
It is.
Like I said, the people that are running
this have a ton of experience
with very large scale servers.
And there are plans for us
to beat the ever living
shit out of these servers
before we even try to have any players
come on them. So there are things we're going to
be doing. And somebody just kind
of wrote it, this is the stress
test. Right.
That's also true. Am I gonna play
a game? No, not tonight. This is
the end of the stream here. I'm
literally, I'm literally
I'm gonna get off stream and just go
right back to what I was doing before the stream started.
Shitty viewbot, thanks for the 300 bits.
I'm buying and installing Minecraft for the first time
just for this occasion. You better not
fuck this up.
Jesus. Smelly boy, thanks for the
250. If I make a nice
Minecraft farm, will the king come out and
look at it and tell me how good of a farmer I am?
Probably.
Better not have any landmines under the corn.
I'll be checking.
He's gonna destroy it.
Oh man.
Hey, permanent marks, thanks for the 250. Can I
exchange these bits for bald coin currency in
Minecraft? No, I'm sorry.
Gromicus, thanks for the 300
bits. Hey, Jerma, my little nephew Tucker is your
biggest fan. Can you please shout him out as
Tucker?
It's, there's a
I think this is a different language. I don't know what
is it. I don't know. Is this
He's searching right
now what this is. It says
please shout him out as
this the this.
Why can't I, I can't. Okay, let me see who this is.
This the this.
He can't. Alright, it's T
T-U-C-E
space
What's that? And then
D-D-E
Yeah, yeah, yeah. What is that? What is that?
Why you guys, why you guys writing that?
Why you guys writing that? Okay, yep.
Thank you Gromicus for the 300 bits.
You see those questions, people write in the
question marks, what's he talking about? What's he doing?
You understand.
Thank you Panda Poploin for the
500 bits. I made a YouTube playlist of
all Jerma videos and streams and called it JermaTV.
It's got
805 videos
and a total run time length of
2916 hours
or 121
days. If you were to
start that playlist as it is now and
leave it running, it would finish on April
11th, 2020.
Holy shit.
That's an interesting bunch of facts here.
3000 hours
pretty much. Well, here it is if anyone's curious.
Just start that and then
finish it on the cyberpunk release day.
Yeah, that's right.
Just in time.
Thank you that Panda. That's actually
really cool. I've never seen
that data presented to me before.
Interesting to think about that.
121 and a half days
of video footage.
Very cool.
Socktrot, thanks for 500 bits. Please help.
I don't know what Pog or Jebaited is and no
one will tell me. I can help you.
Pog is
holy shit and Jebaited is
we got him laughing.
That's all you need to know. Apple Shift
thanks for the 250. Hey man,
today I quit my shitty job, which is kind of bittersweet
since I'll miss my coworkers.
But hey, here's 250 to
new beginnings. If I also be able to catch
more streams now, which is great.
PS, I've got to go to a thing on Sunday
so I won't be able to make the Minecraft stream.
But I'll be there for the next one for sure.
Godspeed, good sir. Best of
luck to you. Best of luck to you.
Seems like a pretty major change.
Best of luck to you.
Godspeed to you as well.
Thanks for the 250. Let's hope you
start something else soon here.
Something that you're more
happy with. Thanks again for the 250.
CadBTV
thanks for the 500 bits. I cannot wait to cut down
murderous babies in defense of my king.
Yes, you have to protect me at
all costs. Murderous
babies. This streamer
is fucked. Hey, the Dinkster.
Thanks for the 500 bits. I like this
man. I'm happy you do.
Thank you. That's
the end, guys. No, it's not.
I forgot about the credits. What am I thinking?
I'm too caught up with all the other stuff going on.
Ow, ow, ow.
Holy shit, there were a lot of subs.
I'm looking over at how
many people subbed today. That's a lot.
It's because of the server.
Yeah, but you, there's no, you need
to be subbed for, for the first
one, you have to be subbed for two months.
That might pull back
when we do another one. Are there going to be baby
player models or are we just going to be the same size?
I believe it's going to be a different
model for the first
30, 40 minutes of your life.
That was still tentative when we talked earlier,
so I'm not sure. People didn't realize
the event was in three days.
Two months in a row or total? Two months in a
row. Yeah, I had that on,
I had that on screen. I had that on screen
for like 40 minutes.
They said two plus months
in a row.
Barely made it.
Did it have to be an active sub?
Yeah, remember, the whole purpose
of doing it, we've talked about it
three or four times already here.
The point of having it be two plus
subs is because if somebody
catches the stream
and they say, oh
wait, you're telling me I can just,
I could pay five dollars
and try to ruin a server?
That's the point.
To make it so nobody
can, at least on the first
one, it's a preventative measure.
You know what I'm saying? They need to pay
ten dollars for two
straight months. So
good, alright. In two months
from now, if you
wanted to pay five bucks and try
to ruin the server,
we're also still working on that too.
It just had to be in place.
It's just too, it's too exploitable.
It just is, I really didn't want to do it
but it had to be done.
I honestly would have done six months.
I think that's too much.
Guys, remember,
the subs have to exist
and I'm not even sure there's that many
six month straight subs.
At that point it would be six months total.
But I'm not sure,
it might be hard to pull that
data. But as it stands right now
it's just, you have to have been subbed for two
months. Like the last
sixty days essentially. I'm a
seventeen month sub repeat sub but it doesn't
count because it's prime?
That's not true. Yeah,
of course, yeah, prime subs count. Of course they do.
Yeah, yeah, no,
prime counts.
You just had to have been subscribed.
It doesn't, it's not.
Yeah, that's fine. Uh oh, the babies
have doubled. So if it says my
current streak is nine months even though I missed
my last sub by a few days, I'm fine.
Yeah, it should be fine. It's just
pulling what Twitch is reporting
out, right? The streak window
is like forty days.
Yeah, so that's fine.
People are gonna be really salty
in chat when they die.
Yeah, but that's kind of inevitable though.
Alright, look.
You're, look,
listen, you're gonna die.
Okay? It's just
gonna happen. You're
gonna die. If you join
the server, you're
dead. If you're
maybe not, but you have to
go in with
wow, really? No, I'm just saying
this is chaos.
This is, you
can't go into the server and be like,
I can't wait to live a long, fruitful life
in here. It's gonna be anarchy.
It's gonna be controlled anarchy.
But it's,
I can't guarantee you that you'll last
ten seconds or you'll last five
hours. I don't know. I don't
know. You need to have a grave
keeper for all the deaths.
So I hope you
don't get upset if
you spawn in and within twenty
minutes you haven't been fed
and somebody kills you.
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna do my best to run the kingdom
as well as I can.
And that's, if you're watching
the stream, I know, oh,
I wish I could participate, but it might
even be more fun if you just watch.
This is gonna be an absolute joke
of the stream. Potentially more than
three or four times. See you Sunday,
though. Join the Discord. There'll be a channel
there soon about this stream.
Have fun, because that's all I care about.
See you soon.