Okay, hello. How are you? We're going to move on to Cities Skylines. I gotta change this title to
Picking Up Apples and Carrots for Five Hours. It doesn't make any sense anymore. So we're going to
name it Back to Wink Dink City. Cities Skylines. You didn't play for five hours. I played for four.
So I think I got my fill of Animal Crossing for the day and we're going to do that every day.
Well, what I mean by that is every stream day we will finish with Animal Crossing.
So that's kind of what you can expect. At least for the next couple weeks, I would assume.
All right, back to it. Here we go. And you'll be able to see it on your screen. See it? Yes, you do.
Okay, so Cities Skylines. We're going to load game. This is before. That was very loud. Make sure I
turn this down. Which one? Not the autosave. Where's the one before the explosions? It was
yes. Yes, it was this one. Okay, so first of all, we had a ton of money come in. We had 5,000 bits.
50 buck drop right now from Filactory Lich. Let me just take a quick sip of water. They say,
hey, Jerma, you're really bad at making roads. Just so you know, you can download pre-made cities
just to fuck with them. Download a copy of Boston. No, I want to make my own shit. I don't want a
pre-made city. No, I want to make my stuff from scratch. I don't want to go open up the freezer
and go take out a fucking kid cuisine and put it in the microwave for 25 seconds. No, I want to go
get the batter. I want to go get the chicken and I'm going to make it from scratch on my stovetop.
Even if it's easier that way. And even if this food comes out to be poisonous and not edible and
it'll hurt and people will get hurt if they eat it. But thank you for the 50 bucks. Appreciate it.
Just let's try to figure out where we were before. Change the title. The title's changed. Back to
Winged Ink City. The city is beyond saving. Yeah, it was left in a really bad state. I gotta work on
the trash. Forget about the fucking roads. We'll do that later. Forget about the roads. All right,
it's been a full day. This is awful. Who fucking made this? I don't even feel like I did this.
I think I fell asleep and somebody took over. This is working as intended. Those of you that,
okay, those of you that were not here yesterday, I made it so the highway, any cars that are on the
highway have to have to go through the toll and go through the scenic Statue of Liberty.
And when they have to go this way, this is the only way to go on the highway.
You go up there. There's a toll every 15 feet. This keeps going. Every toll is as high as the
price can possibly get. And eventually that leads you to, you can go left. Left takes you back all
the way around, which will eventually take you down here back to the actual highway.
If you, this is what happens when you take the highway. Or you bang a right and come and join
our little town here. We have a nice little community. Okay. Oh man. I kind of don't,
I kind of want to just, this is bad. All right. We're fine. What do I need? I'm not enough
educated workers. We need industry. A lot of it, but we don't have enough fucking workers.
Not enough buyers for products. No, we need commercial. Commercial. What do we look like?
Terrible, terrible, terrible commercial buildings. Okay. All right. I know what I want to do.
We are going to build out from here. We're going to have some commercial out this way.
That's the plan. That's what I'm doing. I'm going to be a bunch of commercial. Double roads.
Uh, right over here. What's this? Double down on the tolls and legalize weed.
I want a curved road to go like this. Why, why is there so many palm trees? And you got a toll
to come in here? No. All right. Commercial. High density commercial around the whole thing.
We need more goods. Here we go. All right. This just had to build up. I need a ton of industry.
I need more commercial for industry though. Just keep going down this way with commercial. Just
make a ton of it. Like this don't matter. Just make a bunch of it and then I'll make some industry
down here. This is all in this. Is this industry? What is this? What the hell is this? What is this?
These houses? Oh, they're not labeled. Oh, it's high density. High density. Okay. I got to,
fuck. Wait, how are people going to go to these businesses? There's no way people can't go to
these. There's a dirt road. Are these all going to be drive-throughs? Uh, fuck. Just make them houses.
No, I can't. This is fucked up. How do I delete this? Just delete them all. This is the, I can't
do anything right here. I got to plan this shit out too. All right. How does it look over here?
All right. Commercial buildings going up. There's plenty of this web street. Okay. All right. There's
enough room. That'll build out. Then, oh, we need water and shit here. Good. Okay. Electricity is
already here, right? Yes, it is. Is there electricity? There's electricity here. There's no,
no, there's not, there's not shit in the water pipes. I fixed that. Remember? I have the cleaning
unit here. Another 50 fucking dollars. Holy shit. That's like, this is like three 50 dollar
bit drops in a row in the last like hour. Oh my God. This is from Trans Scout TF2.
Thanks for the 50 fucking dollars. I say, hey Jerm, I hope you're doing all right. I want to
drop in and thank you for the silly shit you do. It really brightens my day. Things have been kind
of upside down since my mom got diagnosed with ALS. Sorry if that's weird to mention.
Uh, but watching your streams helps things feel more normal. Also, the city makes me want to scream.
Well, me too. It makes me want to scream too. But I'm really sorry to hear about your
mother's diagnosis. I'm really sorry to hear that. I don't know that much about ALS, but
it's manageable from what I've heard. I'm really sorry to hear about it though,
at least enough. Steven Hillenberg died from it. Yeah, that's horrible. Unfortunately,
it's not. Oh, maybe I'm thinking of a different one. A different illness, but
I'm really sorry to hear about it regardless. But yeah, take care of yourself. I wish you the
best. I wish your family the best too. You're probably thinking of MS. Yeah, probably.
Probably. But thanks for the 5,000 bits. Completely unnecessary. But thank you.
Let's get rid of these houses. Okay, I have a question. If a house is abandoned,
does that mean... is that because there are too many... is that because... what am I doing wrong
here? I mean, don't answer that question because very obviously the thing you're looking at right
now is... that could be one of the reasons. It could be one of the reasons why. Don't answer
that very immediately. I need industry now. Oh, fuck those commercial buildings. All right,
up, up, up, up, up. Industries down here. All right, let's do it. Let's do a double road.
I'll work on toll road once this is done. Steve, what the fuck are you talking about?
All right, industry. A lot of it. You're making a maze. I wish it would stop. It's been raining
for a year. Will it stop fucking raining? You don't need more industry. What? High demand for
industry. That's what that means. The Statue of Liberty is trashed. Wait, hold on. Garbage. Oh,
yeah. You got a garbage truck. I can't get here. Wait, is there a garbage truck on the way? What's
going on here? All right, I need a hospital. How many hospitals do... okay, I don't have any up here.
There's a hospital. There we go. Right here. Another one over here. I don't have enough money.
How much is a... fuck, a hospital is expensive. We'll do this. Crematorium. Wait, that's a hospital
for one street? Yeah, but they're so disconnected. Remember the ambulance that drove around the
entire city? Medical clinic. I'm just trying to work things out here. All right, what's going on
with this? It doesn't even need to be here. What's this? Not enough fuel. Coal power plant.
No, no, no, no. I didn't even do this one. I didn't even do this one. No. What's this?
Not enough raw materials. Wait, we're out of materials. What's a materials map? Should I
sell all this shit and move it? A thunderstorm is battering the city. Stay indoors until the storm
is passed. Everybody get inside. Stay indoors. Don't come out. No, not the university. Everyone's
fine so far. We're okay. How long does it last? I mean they can't go inside. Why is there no power?
No. Consumption 290. What the fuck? How come this is not connected?
It's because I deleted the power plant. Well, it said there was no more fuel so I deleted it.
All right, I think it's time. I gotta make a new city. I gotta start over. I'm gonna make a new
city. I'm gonna make it better this time. Okay, we're doing it. I'm gonna make a new city. I'm
gonna be quick about it. This place is fucked. I'm doing another one. I'm gonna make a new one. I'm
gonna make it smaller and more manageable. We're gonna do this in... Wow, the snow. That'd be cool.
Winter Hills. Snowy coast. Do Dust Bowl. Two rivers. The Dust Bowl. This is just green. It's
always Dust Bowl. No, I want to do Frosty Rivers. A nice little snow town. Yeah, Frosty Rivers is
the one. That's what I'm doing. Change the name? I will. Wingding City. I don't know. They all
started eating each other. We have a new city now. Snowy Crest. Here we go. Hello. Let's start. I
already know how to do this. Okay, so let's start with... This is the highway to come into the city.
We're gonna have a nice snowy crest. So this is coming in. Let's do... Where's the music, man? I
want some cool music. Rock City. All right. Oh, I can't do any of this shit because I have to level
up my city. All right, here we go. So when you come in, you make your way in here.
Then we're gonna have... You know what? Come all the way down here. We're gonna do a straight line
all the way. Can we out on this? Just wait. You'll see. There's gonna be just a big straight line.
Pause the game. Is that too long? Why? I was thinking about having it come this way and then...
I said you're gonna make it small. This is small. It's gonna be like this.
Here we go. Ready? What? What? What's so bad about that?
What? What's wrong with this? These are just little side streets. What's wrong with this?
Make angle. The angle. What's wrong? What's the matter with an angle?
Don't you slow the fuck down. Only do rectangles. Look, I'm fucking working on it.
I'm gonna go a little further. Hold on. Go look at a Google's map street view thing and look down.
And this is what the shit looks like. Another one. Here we go. Houses. This is all houses.
All of it. This is where the residential is. Over here. So now we have... Do we have any bigger
roads? Okay, so now this is like... We're gonna get out of... Okay, here's like the intersection
where we get the fuck out of here. And here we are. All right. This is how you get out of here.
Wait, is this one way? And this is where like this shopping area will go. Go over here. He's
occupied. Okay. Christmas tree. Rib cage. I just want it to be efficient. I don't... I don't... I
don't... I don't... It's efficient because everybody's over here and everyone's over there.
And we go up here and all the industry is up here. Okay, good. Up here. Maybe some more commercial
buildings. Over here. And then put this up. How much do I got? 27,000. Here we go. Because this
is where the water is. This is where the water is. You have to explain it to everybody. Wait,
was it frozen? Highway traffic is going down residential. Oh, right. Fuck. I don't... Okay,
so here's how we're gonna fix that. Now they don't have to go down residential. You can do
like a rotary. Just make it one way. Six lane, one way. Okay, there we go. There we are. There
we go. Okay. Now they've got a choice. You build utilities before you run into money. No money for
the infrastructure. I got money. I got money. Curved road. Okay. Because I wanted to be able
to sit on here from the water. Up curving roads and build a power plant. What's wrong with curving
roads? Well, looks like we're doing wind. Time for some wind farm. Up here. Is there a hill or
anything? Wait, I need, I need, I need wind. They gotta be over here. Like right here on the coast,
right? Eight. I need like eight, eight, eight, six, seven, six. This music isn't very good. Well,
change the channel then. Okay, I don't even have money. How fucked am I? I can't even take out a
loan. I spend too much money building this out. I forgot. I'm not soft locked yet. Not yet. All
right. For the free houses that are here, we're going to increase taxes. It's 200 bucks. I'll be
right. Okay. Now increase taxes. I can't increase taxes. Fuck. I can't believe I fucked this up.
Okay. Can I refund all this shit up here? Why did this cost so much money? All right. All right.
Pause, pause, pause, pause, pause, pause. I don't even have a water pump. I'm okay. I'm, I was
building as if I was on the last city with like 50,000, a hundred thousand dollars. This is only
the second city I've ever made. Roads are expensive. I had like eight hours in the last city. We just
started a brand new city and I'm building as if I had the money from the last city. This is not the
third city. That doesn't count. The tutorial didn't count. All right. At least these people will be
online. You can't live without that sweet, sweet, tall money. This is so expensive. I've got to do
it though. How much money do I have? This is so fucking expensive. Don't worry. It's salvageable.
Hold on. Okay. We're going to start generating money, generating taxes. Why do they not have
electricity? Okay. Now, wait, they have to be heated because we're in the fucking goddamn
winter wonderland. I fucked it up. Whatever. They use extra electricity. Okay. So now remember,
I don't have like $180,000. I need to build one street. A lot of water here. We're going small.
We're going small and manageable. We're going to start with a rotary. I can't even build a
fucking rotary. God damn it. Okay. Very, very small. Connect the freeways together. Why did
somebody tell me to connect these together? Why? Yeah, somebody did say that. I was like, sure.
All right. I actually kind of like this. People come into the city. If they want to fucking,
they can what? Go like over fucking here. Connect it. This is confusing. No, they could like go like,
connect it like this. You know, fucking whatever. You go around in the goddamn.
You go around in the goddamn. This is fine because then I could just keep it going this way.
Truck stop town. They buy trees. I have to, I have to do this. Stop. Stop. No, no more.
Now we're going to make a small little area over here. Why couldn't I have used this from the very
beginning? How come this is locked? I want it to be bigger. Wait. Oh no. I want it to be,
I want it to be one way. There we go. Okay. And then they come up and they take a left.
This is why you go bankrupt. This is another restart. No, it's not. It's making an off ramp.
Like I have, I can't, I have no options. Everything is, everything's okay. Now I can do this.
Why is everything blacked out in the first? I don't understand. This was fine. That is fine.
Play with, why would I not have everything unlocked right now? Like, I don't understand.
I can't like make an off ramp because I have to do, I have to do a single lane road first before
anything else unlocks. How the fuck do I do this? Can I not do this? It's in the main menu. Well,
whatever. It's already open. It's cheap money. It needs to be in the mods menu. All right. Well,
whatever. We're going to, look, I'm going to, I'm going to keep going with this. So this is one way.
I'm going to make a roundabout up here. That's one way, right? It is now. Okay. Roundabout,
right here. Roundabout over here. Why roundabout here? Because I want to have people go around and
spin. Roundabout should connect both of the roads. Exactly. That's what I was going to do. Why can
I do this? Just do what you want. You know what? I'm going to go over here. I'm doing this. It's
going to be roundabout town. How do we get rid of these trees? Four lane road with parking spaces.
That's not what I want. This is what I'm talking about. Like what this is. I don't, I'm not going
to get, I don't want to get overzealous here. Okay. There's going to be another roundabout
in the middle here. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's, that'd be sick.
No, no, that's too many. Too many. Way too many. They can connect here if they want.
What do you mean if they want? I can't see shit with these trees.
Okay. You're making crop circles. It'll be interesting. You'll see. All right. That's enough.
That's enough. It's two people holding hands and leaning back and putting their other hands out
in a dance number. $50 from phylactery lich. Thanks for the 5,000 bits. You know how you took
a pottery class for a joke? Maybe go ahead and take some city design classes. How would I ever
do that? Play this video game that I've played for like six hours. I'm just making fucking roads.
Like guys, you, you, this is not your city that I'm making that you're going to live in tomorrow.
Like you don't, you don't have to live here. You don't have to live here tomorrow.
Like what the fuck? Oh, I don't want to live here. You don't have to. This is not real. This
is a pretend video game. This is make believe. I'm just kidding. I'm sucking you all up in a
fucking digital vacuum and you're going to be, you're going to live here tomorrow. Just trying
to make you have a little bit more false sense security for the next few hours. All right. Here
we go. This is rotary side B. All right. Not too much. Hey, how many of you guys want to live on
B side? How many of you guys want to live on A side? Let's see. All right. Okay. The plumbing
here. Did it correct? Okay. I still have money. I'm good. Put all the garbage on the B side.
Okay. What about power? We need to do power now. Wait. Okay. I need to see where any resources are.
I'll just do it across the way here. This doesn't matter, right? Just do wind. A bunch of wind over
here. Wait, how do I, is it a bridge? Wait, it'll be a bridge. Huh? Hold on. Holy shit. Oh wow.
It makes a bridge. That's so cool. That's awesome. Nice. All right. Right in the middle. Right there.
Yeah. That's cool. $18,000. Kind of cheap for a bridge. Okay. No more. I need a small road.
I need power plant. I need some commercial buildings too. Um, where should they go? In the middle?
Yeah, that'd be nice. Look, take this out. It's like a little street, little what the commercial
shit is over here. Go like from here to here, right? No, but I don't want the traffic over
doing that. Click link, please. What is it? Twitch viewer integrator. This mod integrates
your Twitch viewers to your Cities Skylines game. It retrieves the current viewer list of your
channel when a game is started and loaded and stores them to an internal list of which the names
are generated. Uh, apparently, though there's three comments on this and I think it's only been,
it's only been downloaded like fucking 12 times. This is pretty sure something went wrong. How do
I know this is working? I want to live there. Uh, Twitch integrator config, configure the mod. It's
built in a config key value mod based on functional. All right. Stream key stealer. No,
I'm hold on. We don't do this. There's literally not even any houses yet. Why did I build a fucking
$20,000 bridge? I need houses and money and power plants. All right, I'm ready. Here we go. We're
going to build some wind farm. Need some wind. No, no, that's too close. Eight. We go eight right
here. Yeah. Eight. Is eight the max? I kind of want all the infrastructure to be over here.
No, I'd give me a power plant. 19,000 for a power plant. Just put it on the road. I'll fix this later.
Just need it on the road. It's going to be just like a light industry up here for now.
Light industry. And then of course, our plan. How could I forget? Go power plant plumbing.
It's going to go. How was this flow? What's this flow? What's this flow? Is it flow this way?
So we want the shit to be pumped over here. So this is the shit pump. All right. And then
here's the regular pump right here. Why is this doing this? This is fucked up. Mike, can I get
this on here? The shit pumps on the side. Well, that's, I've reached this. I hope so. Yes. There's
that. And then the shit pump. Okay. We're good. Now we just need electricity to come that way and
we're done. And I can get my town that's ready to fucking roll. Power's going to come down here.
We just need to wait for this shit to be actually built so I can do it. That first city. I'm already
out of money. The water pump is out. It's because the fucking bridge. Why is all this shit locked up?
Okay. I did the tutorial yesterday and didn't have this problem like two or three times in a
row. What the fuck? Delete the fucking bridge. What? What? How did I lose money by refunding
the bridge? It doesn't refund? You didn't, what do you mean I didn't refund? That's how you do it.
It just says refund on it. What? It only refunds if no time has passed. Oh fuck. I didn't know that.
What's the cheat to give me like $20,000 right now? You can't refund a bridge.
What's the cheat just to fucking type it to give me $20,000? No. No. No. Save this.
I'm not going to be under the fucking locked bullshit in the first 10 minutes. I've already
done all this. I don't want like the single lane roads and you can only build this. Where is it?
Editor. Assets. Content warning. Content manager. Okay. Give me fucking like $50,000 right now.
This one. Custom assets. Wait. I can save this. Mods. Card mode. Unlimited money. Money never runs
out. Done. I'm only going to use it for like five minutes. Unlock all. Thank you. Okay. We're good?
That should be it, right? What do you mean no? That doesn't work? All mods are global. Activating
mod. Loading a SEGA mod. Yeah, we're fine. Let's go. Cheating is god tier. Well, I just don't want
to sit here and unlock everything again. He's scared of creepers so he turned on creative mode.
Okay. Thank you. All right. Unlimited fucking money. Build the bridge again. Thank you. Power
on. Good. This is temporary. It's temporary just to get this shit to turn on. You in? It's not in.
Okay. All right. There we go. That's good. Commercial buildings. I want to do them right
in the middle. What do I want to do? Down with the stream. I'm going to turn it off in a second. I
just need to generate at least like a fucking dollar. Center the- I don't care. Here, look.
There'll be businesses here. That's cool. All right. Then you're going to have your own little
area over here and right in the middle. Check it out. Watch this. There we go. Medium roads.
Four lane road with bicycle lanes. I don't know. I don't want that. I just want a four lane road.
And what do I want to do with it? Leaders don't deserve respect. Okay. I want businesses here.
Kind of a broken neck, but that's fine. All right. More houses. No, there shouldn't be any houses in
here. No houses. Houses here. Around the edges. No houses in the middle. And then some more.
That's fine for now. Okay. Pause it. Connect this shit. Not connected, is it? It could be.
Electricity is going here. Good. All right. Now let me just generate some money.
And I'm going to turn off unlimited money. Why am I losing money with unlimited money on?
What are you guys doing? Wait, is this bullshit in chat about center the bridge or we're not
going to talk? Is that what this is? The center of the bridge or we're not talking? Why are you
guys not talking? Because you cheated. Get out of here. Whatever. This doesn't matter. Center the
bridge. That's up in my brain right now, don't you think? Now, how are taxes? Increase a little bit
What? What are you? What are you? Oh shit. Nobody can breathe. Nobody can breathe up here.
They have electricity up there. All right. What's going on over here? Build these houses.
All right. Once I have, okay. Once I get to like a nice plus like thousand, turn it off. I'm going
to turn it off. I just want to get this plus thousand. I'm going to turn it off. I promise.
We need to make like a fucking hospital. Hospital going to be right in the fucking middle.
It'll hit every community. Look at that. Smart. And then we're going to have a
sauna. Oh, I can spend as much as I want. We're going to have a gym. Dude, I got a blank check.
How about a community pool? Oh wow. Right in the middle. Everybody gets a community pool
when you have a blank check. It's great. Look at this community pool. A community pool over here
too. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. Only one community pool and then one
helicopter depot. No, I need a police station. All right. One police station. Police station.
Hospital. Police station. All right. And now, all right. Okay. All right. Now I'm out of here.
I'm done. A fire station too. Just for free. All right. All right. I'm up. Look at that negative
money. I don't like that. I don't like that. Why am I getting negative money? And let me do
school too. Elementary school. And then just one high school. I'm ready. Wait, is the pool
costing money? Holy shit. Wait, what? Why is the community pool costing so much money?
Okay. Get rid of the community pool. Get rid of the community pool. We don't need it.
What do you mean stop these fires? What the fuck are you talking about? You're not supposed to
have the community pool yet. Yeah. It's okay. We're going. Let's extend this out. Let's put
this neighborhood out. Um, hold on. People are going to freak the fuck out when I do this. I
know they are. No curved roads. I'm going to do a curved road. I like them. Oh shit. I can't. Yes,
I can. No, that's cheating. That's actually cheating. No, I just need a baseline. That's it.
All right. It kind of looks like a moth. It's all right. Okay. All right. All right. More
residential. I'm going to do big houses over here. I'm not supposed to have these yet.
Stop. Stop. This is cool. This is cool. All right. Speed up. I need to put. All right. I'm done.
Time to put the, uh, I'm going to wait for the community to grow a little bit and I need and
then I'm going to actually turn off this all the cheating. I promise there will be no more cheating
after this. I promise. I won't cheat anymore. I promise. Oh, we're doing electricity. I need
more than this. I'm going to need to put some shit up here. How many M how many M M M's is this?
Whatever it is. Eight. Okay. We can do some here. Okay. That's good. Fine. That's that's enough.
That's all I'm done. Oh, we need trash. I'm going to get that done real quick.
We're just a second here. We need to dump. Dump will be, um, down here. Check this out.
Oh, we got to have a place for the dump. Six lane roads for the dump trucks. They can come this way.
Um, dump truck. Dump truck. Where's the dump trucks go? Where's the dump go? Where's the dump go?
Where's the dump go? Dump over here. Um, where's the dump go? It's got to go on the right side.
What happened? What happened? Okay. All right. That's it. Plenty of room for them to go.
It's not symmetrical. I can fix it. Don't worry. There we go. Hey, look at that. Our town is looking
a good start. It's a good start. Now we just fast forward until I can collect enough taxes to not
be in the red. And then I turn off the cheating. I can't fucking believe that shit. God damn it.
All right. I'm in the green. It's time to cheat. Time to stop cheating. Content manager. All right.
Mods. Unlimited money off. Okay. Unlock all off. I can't turn unlock all off. I already have stuff
that I'm not supposed to have. I'm not, this stuff that I'm not supposed to, I don't want that.
I'm keeping it on. Another 50 fucking dollars came in. You guys, why are you guys giving me so much
money? This is insane. This is like $500. Goiki, another 50 bucks. If the bridge isn't centered
in an hour, I'll, oh my God. If the bridge isn't centered in an hour, I'll blow up the hospital.
Joker. What's going on? Why do I have this much money? That's too much money. How do I get donated?
Look, I have an idea. You, I have an idea. Don't worry. You want, here's the idea. You ready?
I have an idea. Just make a bunch of expensive shit and then delete them. Here. I'll put like five
statues. Oh yeah. Our town has a Statue of Liberty. Oh yeah. So does ours. We got one too. Oh,
wait. No, we have, we've got the Sherp X launch site over on our side. Wait, who's cooler? Wait,
this is a spaceship? Okay. Now just wait and I'll just delete them. Why am I losing money? I
shouldn't be losing weekly money. Wait, these take so long. Okay. When can I delete it? Delete it so
I don't have to, I want to, don't want to refund 150. Delete it. Launch something. Launch. I don't
have a rocket. Pass launch operations. Launch preparation. Wait, launch a nuke at the other
town. Okay. I have to get rid of this. I'm going to fucking, this whole thing's going to get fucked
up. Build the rocket. I don't have any money guys. This is like end game money. Default windows,
fucking color selector. I have to, oh, sorry. Okay. I'm going to have to live with the money.
All right. I'm going to, here's how I do this. Just, okay. I'm going to, I could delete this too.
Here's how I'm going to fix this. Okay. So everyone's going to live tax free for like a year
and then I'll be back to normal. No taxes for a fucking year. There. Now build. Put a couple
of the stores here. Uh, I want to put, yeah, I gotta do this again. All right. Good. Okay. Good.
Let's make some more industry. I need it. More industry. I'll pick up these roads. We need some
bigger roads here. That's too big. Uh, four lane road is fine. Just make a square over here. Okay.
Industry. Use your limitless wealth to center the bridge, you. What the fuck are you saying?
Report that a devastating meteor strike the city in the near future. Residents should seek shelter
immediately. If any is available. If it lands over here, I'm going to laugh my ass off beside
forever. Why? Oh my God. It's actually going to land up there. Okay. That's so fucking unfair.
A meteor strike has occurred. Avoid the impact site and head to shelter. If any is available.
What am I supposed to do now? Did you just turn off the game? Why do I feel like one of you guys
did that? Like I downloaded the Twitch integrator and somebody hated this layout so much.
Fucking double rotary thing is a stupid bridge in the middle. He wasted so much money. He's a
cheater. Nuke it. Wait, this fires. I need a fire door. Where's my fire department? Of course I've
picked the level with all the trees. Fix the bridge. There. I fixed the bridge for you.
Fire department. Fire department. Fire department. Fire department. Fire department. Fire department.
Go. Go. Get out there and do something. Go. It's spreading. Oh shit. Wait, why do we need
electricity for the fire engines to run? Sorry, boss. We can't go find those fires. There's no
electricity in our gasoline using trucks. What? Excuse me. Um, how did this happen?
I'm going to make two squares. One square on the right, one square on the left and a small power
plant right there. So we're going to build this town over here. B side. Turn cheats off.
Left square gang. Cheats are on. I think I can use this. Not one way. Fuck. That way? Okay.
It's going to be a dead end road. I don't fucking care. What happened here? Uh, all right. We can
fix this. Just clean this up a little bit. I want this to be one way. Like if you're going to go
this way, I don't want, I want it to be one way this way. I don't want this. Like this doesn't
make any sense. No. What? I want to go this way. One way. Where's one way? Highway. There's no escape.
Six lane, one way road. One way. So I can't make it go the other way. Oh, if you right click. Okay.
That's fine. This is good. Why ask if you're not going to, if you're not going to read chat?
I am reading chat. What do you think? How do you think I'm seeing everything you're saying?
Okay. Then this goes down. This is all right. I don't hate this. You can fix this part.
Feel like a fucking school over here.
You must have not given a fuck. It's going to be a neighborhood.
The fridge is not even physically possible. Well, it, it is now. Somebody said this is
a Mario Kart track. Pause it. Okay. I mean, this is not horrible, but this does, this has to go.
Maybe this could come over here. This wouldn't be insanely terrible if it did like this.
And it's just houses, just homes, maybe a couple more that come off of it.
Uh, actually I want this.
I don't want to connect it. I want it to be a dead end. I'm making the J.
This is okay. This is just the J if somebody dropped a fucking boulder on his head.
This is too harsh. Too harsh. Less harsh. Make it less harsh.
I'll keep that as whatever. Okay. Small houses here. A couple of large houses here. This is too
harsh. Fix it. Just make a football. You have the laces already. That's shit. One way fix this.
This shit's one way. I want to like have this go out. This is like too fucked up. It's got to go
like that. And then this has to go over here. This is just too fucked up. One way. Uh, let's do
four lane road, but I want it to be one way. I know. Can I only, can you only do one way roads
with six lanes? The roundabout. How far out do I want to do this? Far enough where I can
move this out of the way. Clown town. Why is this a two way? Where? Why is this a two way?
Because if you drive down this road, if you live here, you'll have to all, you, you, this is how
you get into town. Look, I'm just trying to salvage the fucking mess that I made. Otherwise you're
stuck here forever. If you live here, this, you can never turn left. Like you can't turn left here
ever. Unless I get rid of, this is one way to get to the highway. This is just for highway only.
Uh, this isn't straight. I know. I know. I know. I know. But what do you want me to do?
Now this is, uh, okay. God, no way. I can't even play this. I can't even do this.
I have to delete everything from here on out. No, no, I can't. I can't.
Why did I have to get a bomb dropped on that town? It was starting to be fine.
I was going to start building out. This is fine. I'll keep that. But this shit's gotta go. This
has got to be changed because I cheated. Well, whatever. Okay. This is the houses. We're going
to build houses here. I'm going to have big houses here and then we'll have an area where you can go.
You can go this way if you want. We'll connect these two. So now you can like get access to the
fucking wacky bridges. More houses over here. This will be the commercial center. This will be where
we do all the... No, this would be industrial. No, fuck that. There's no way this will work out.
This has to be industrial. This has to be residential. Industrial, residential, commercial,
residential. Good game. Okay. Cool. Good. This can be a straight line. Why can't I make a straight
line? It's too big? Dude, how do you just make a one-way road that's four lanes? Six lanes.
Six lane, one way. Six lane, one way. Is there four lane, one way? Can you only make a single
lane? A two lane, one way? That's not enough traffic. Highway can do it. Highway with sound
barrier. Highway. A three lane, one way road. Okay. Yeah. Now we're going to change this. We'll change
this out to four lanes as of here. A little bit further out. Now you can either go over this way
or you could go this way. Wow. You have so many options. But you can't... Hold on. You can't get
in here from there. When did I switch to this? When I ran out of stuff to do an animal crossing
because I have to... A full day has to go by before I can do anything else. This has to connect down
here. It's so far away though. Yeah. I'm killing this. This is so fucked up. It would take me like
six hours of gameplay to get up here. This is impossible. Putting a rotary right here.
Should've done that down here. Drive all the way down here to get to the rotary that's right here.
That's so funny. I like that actually a lot. That's so stupid. Okay. These are small houses.
Large houses. How much money do I have? I'm good. Is football street gone? Yes. Because if I can't
connect it... This is so huge. Look at how fucking enormous these are. This is like three miles.
Then commercial. Low density commercial right here. Maybe a few little pop-up shops right here.
Commercial here. Commercial here. Commercial all over here. All commercial. Commercial. Looks all
like a little fun zone. Industry over here. Industry over here. And now we have our original first
layout of our S... I don't know. Shit. I don't know why anyone would go over here, but we're
gonna have to figure it out later. In fact, there's absolutely no purpose. This is funny,
though. I like that it's a comedy bridge show. We're gonna keep it. All right. Now, power and
plumbing. And then I'm able to at least spend two minutes in my fucking town that I built without
a meteor hitting it. Okay. And then we need over here. Pump will be right there. Make sure I have
enough room for it. Whoa. All right. Cool. Electricity. I need water pumps. I actually
need to have the pump... Wait. Where's it going? This way? Down this way. So I have to have the
shit over here. Over here. And then the actual water pump over here. But wait. Why is this not
taking water? Is it not in? Not... Wait. Hold on. Is it not in there? That's in there, right? Is this
one in there? No, it's just the drain pipe. Okay. Let's go. Connected to anything. Don't matter.
Connected to anything. Don't matter. All right. Wake up. Electricity time. I know it's for free,
but people are gonna get really mad at me. Oil. There's no oil on this whole map. We're gonna do
coal. We're gonna do coal and wind. And the industry section over here. All right. And wind.
Water wind. Because that's better. Okay. Why did that happen? So what do you guys want to do
tomorrow? What do you guys want to do tomorrow? What's the plan tomorrow? I should have started
getting built up before I do this. Somebody just say Dark Souls 2. All right. Come on. Let's go.
I'm not gonna play Dark Souls 2 tomorrow. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. Here we go. Connect this
to here. And then connect this temporarily over here. Temporarily over here. It's just temporary.
Until everything gets built. Is your electricity being used? Here we go. Here are the houses.
Nice. Power is coming in. No. It's not connected. Like, is it in? Are you in? Like, what the fuck
are you doing? Consult the list? Yeah, there is a pretty significant list of stuff to do.
These are not connected. Temporarily do it. All right. Hey, look at that. Our town makes even
a ten percent sense. Our car is not coming in. Nobody wants to live in Clown Town. Hey, rent is
fucking pretty cheap in Clown Town. All right. Build up. Let's go. Build it up. Wear a helmet.
Like, this bridge. Oh, not bridge. Use this thing. Okay. Now we just wait for our city to build up.
What about? Oh, no schools. All right. Schools. Schools. Schools. Where should the hospitals be?
Elementary school. Okay, right. Somewhere in here. A lot of children to teach.
And we'll do one over here, too. Over on the corner. Well, right here. And then a high school.
High school reaching into here. It's just somebody's house. Whatever. I just don't think
your direct neighbor is a fucking high school. You can like mow in your lawn and there's just
kids out there going to class. Okay. That's normal in real life. Well, no, not like high
schools usually in their own little areas and their own little campuses. If you live
on Heather Jackson Street and your neighbor is a high school and the neighbor next to that.
I mean, no. No high school was literally like that. There are houses across the street from high
schools. There's a high school literally across the street. I can hit it with a slingshot.
Well, don't do that. He went to a ritzy high school. He's so coddled. It's a spoil. He went
to a high school with like a cafeteria McDonald's. There was a Wendy's in his high school, too. Did
you know that? Oh, this motherfucker here. He was homeschooled. Yeah, cry to your butler.
No, I did not. All right. I'm going to defend myself here. I did not go to a fucking school
like that. I went to a fucking public school and that public school that had fucking those
little shitty milks that nobody liked. I know those little cups of juice that were always icy.
The ice was they were fucking frosty and they weren't even juice. It was like slushy.
I would I know that shit. There was I didn't have any of that. Those gross cups. Don't talk to me
like you think. I like I don't know what I'm talking about. Just because my school happened
to be set back in a larger driveway. Sorry. I did I did not go to a private school. What the fuck?
What even you do? Who cares? I did not go to a private school. I went to a public fucking school.
Homeschooling is private. Fucking guys. You brought your own lunch to school? No, I got to I've
I've got the fucking steak homes. That weird mystery meat with cheese on it that they put
in a sub role and gave it to you. I ate that like fucking two days a week, three days a week.
There was like these these gross meatball subs you could get every day or like the like fucking
90 cent steak of sandwich thing. He got steak. No, you don't understand.
Surf and turf school lunch. Oh, it's not true. Now you guys are making me hungry. Catered lunch.
Yeah, that's what a lunch is. It's fucking catered. The lunch ladies cater your
school with their expertise. And I don't know, why is nothing being built up here?
Yeah, it's a fucking crazy billionaire child. No, this is working out pretty well. I'm fucking
hungry now. All this talk about expensive lunches has made me want to go eat a lunch at 10 o'clock
at night. I got a lot I got some stuff in the fridge. What is this? Don't make him hungry.
He'll leave. Why did you make this? Why did you make this? Why can I even show this on stream?
I love the little smile that you gave me at the end there. Look at the smile.
See that? I caught that. All right. Imagine exporting that and being like, yeah, that looks
good. This streamer getting toilet water shot in his fucking mouth. Yeah, render. You have to watch
every frame of that as it renders. That's pretty good. Oh, that's fucking disgusting.
Not using a render farm. Omega lull. Oh, we've got activity. We've got activity.
Okay, what do I want to know? Finally, people are coming in. All right, now we need to buy like a
park. About here. Playground. Park with trees. This would be cool. Right here. Double park.
This is Park Avenue. Here. Parkway. Six lane road is the name. No. Parkway. Froggy street. All right.
How about um, we need like a police department here and then we need a uh a prison off the highway.
How about another prison? Two prisons back to back. I see power and shit. What the fuck just
happened? Hey, how many people are in prison? Zero. I don't think that's gonna fill up very much. I
need a uh, yeah, we need um, fire fighters. Right here. How far do they go? Uh, put them over here.
That's better. And then a hospital. Hospital can go here. It'd be, all right, right here. Hospital way.
Okay, good. Money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money. What's costing so much money?
Money? You're right. Wait, taxes at zero? How much is it? Prison's 2400 bucks a week?
Okay, uh, that's way too expensive. By local ordinance, I decree that we will remove every prison
and every hospital in our city. Good luck motherfuckers. Of course they're not gonna like
that. What's still costing? 5600 bucks a week. Where's my spreadsheet? Where's the spreadsheet?
The budget? The fuck is taking so much money? Weekly police department expenses. What? What are
you talking about? This game is so fun. Now I imagine a world where you're not a total fucking
idiot and can make interesting cities and towns and stuff. I'm not a right-brained person at all.
In fact, if you were to take a probably a brain scan of my brain, the middle part with like the
left and right of your brain, you know, you get the two, the two hemispheres, left brain, right brain.
I would probably, the line in the middle would be as, it would be like one slice of cheese length
of the right brain. All of it, the rest of it would be left brain. It would be like one craft
singles thickness of how much I have for right brain. Right brain is, wait, is that the other
way around? Which is the one that's like your big math and and like log, logistics and logic and
shit. That's, is that right or left? That's left. Cheese brain. That proves, that proves your right
brain. What? Hold on. Right brain or left brain? I actually want to know. What's the difference?
Left brain versus right brain. Okay. All right. Left brain is like math and, and hold on. Right
brain is expression, emotional intelligence, and imagination. Left brain is language, numbers,
and analytical thinking. I'm right-brained motherfuckers. Here are my, my, my emotion.
I'm an incredibly emotional person and I've, I can, I've, I can make up fucking animals in my head.
How about this one? A dwarf. That's a giraffe and a hippopotamus together. Could you do that?
Right Twix. Right Twix streamer. That's fucking hilarious. Okay. How are we doing over here?
Got the parks. It's still minus a thousand dollars a day. I'm a psych major. That's a myth,
Jerma. Will you let me have this? All right. I need a garbage place. We need two garbage places.
But what's going on with the, whoa. What's going on with the water? What's going on with the water?
Why is this happening? What is this? What's going on? Why? What is that? This doesn't make any sense.
That's something's landing here. Okay, dude. There's, I don't know what that's supposed to mean,
but whatever. He parted the seas. We will make it across the Moses river. Follow me.
What else can I do? This town sucks. I like, I like the A side and B side town way better.
Holy shit. Look at this person. This person's got a little droid. First electric transport ride.
What the fuck? Look at this thing. That's too bad. A side and B side got hit with a meteor.
I need to spruce this up a little. BB unit. Okay. Let's speed up time. Time for an expansion here.
Expansion is going to go out. We've got some commercial buildings. Industry is going over
here. I want to go out this way. Bang. More residential and then more commercial. No,
more residential, more commercial. Check this out. Don't hold your breath. This is a one way.
Okay. More houses. This is going to wrap around into a mall. Commercial everywhere down here.
Mall. Does this make sense right here? Super commercial. All right. We need more industry
after this. Good. Cool. We need power and fluids. We are connected already. Now that's going to come
out here for something. Industry. More of it. We can go this way with this. All industry out here.
Factories. Build a dam. You can build a dam. Oil industry. Where's water? How do I build a dam?
Unique factories. Warehouses. Oil. Barracks. Boar. Dam. Farm building. Whoa. There's so much
cool shit in this game. Milking parlor. Where's the dam? Pumping service. Eco water treatment plant.
Where is it? Under power? Geothermal power plant. Ocean thermal energy conversion.
Hydro power plant. Oh shit. Okay. Where should I put this? Where the water flows?
Like here. How much production? How does this work? It didn't do anything.
Is it not long enough? I need to connect roads to it. Is that why this is happening?
I need to connect. It's facing the wrong way. Oh, it's backwards. I can refine it, right?
It's backwards. What do you mean it's backwards? Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Oh, it's just barely
touching the bottom. Everything's fine. It's just everything's fine. That's why those legs are there.
It's not going to come all the way down, right? Do not wipe out the bridge. Do not wipe out the
bridge. So what am I doing wrong here? We're fine. It's all right. These are businesses. There's
nothing here. It's just road. It'll dry. Oh, it's right at the lip. Put up a flood wall.
Okay. It's, it's fine. Power is disconnected. What? Oh, no. What? No, I'm trying to connect up.
I understand. That's what you have to do. It has to be big. It has to be connected to the wall.
I don't turn it around. I can't, you can't turn the fucking thing around. What? What do you mean
turn it around? I paint it. I, how do I turn it around here? I paint it. How do you, I can't
turn it around. You're talking about a seat. Look what I'm talking about. You guys, what are you
talking about? All right. I'm going to try this again. Don't listen to chat. It needs to be
downstream. Isn't that what this is? This is downstream. So what's, what's wrong with it?
Why is it, you have to build the land up. I wanted to go the other way. That's okay. Don't
fucking ruin this up. Scoop it back in. Scoop it back in. Not enough soil. Okay. Too steep.
Fucking hundred thousand dollars. I don't care. I'm almost out of money. This is connected already.
Somebody died at the dump. Who died at the dump? A dead person is praying. Somebody dumped a dead
body at the dump. That's so stupid. This is insane. I have to drive to the next city for
a painkiller prescription or pay big bucks. Wait, where's the hospital? Where's the doctor's office?
Oh, there is none. Introducing the doctor's office. All right. Is there anything going
up here? The commercial and the houses. We need people to be smarter. I need an education building.
I need a high school. Is there, there already is a high school here. There's a fucking high
school already. Why are they not educated? Public library. We'll do a public library.
I need college. College is too expensive. All right. Public library. It's not hitting enough
people. Public bugleberry. Warning. Experts predict an earthquake could hit the area soon.
I've gotten more random natural disasters in the last hour and a half playing this game. Just
dicking around just after playing Animal Crossing than I did in almost seven and a half hours straight
in the same map last night. Why not turn off? Oh, it's good. It's good. It's good. It's not
gonna hit anything. An earthquake is occurring. Don't panic and wait for help if you are in the
affected area. All right, we're fine. No, it's gonna go. We're okay. There was only one tube got
disconnected. Oh no, there's an earthquake. Everyone lost plumbing. No, it's okay. Like,
attach the end here is the only thing that happened. No, power. Okay, that should be fine,
right? We lost the comedy bridge. A little dead person to dump. I know. I know. And it's sad. We
lost the comedy bridge. Okay. It's a radio station I haven't listened to. Why is this one? I don't
understand why this one is a copyright claim. Building is flooding. Oh, it's still wet.
All right. Industry is going to go up there eventually. Let's build more residential over
here. I need it from here. We're gonna do a single road out and then down and then out
up and then take a look at this. It's simple, simple, simple squares, simple squares,
simple square. That's how is that? That's not a 90 degree angle. I don't care.
And these are going to be just small houses. Relaxation station. Okay, plumbing here.
Are we hitting everything? Yep. Yes, we are. Yep. How's everything over here? Good. Electric.
How much electricity am I pumping? 107. Bring me those houses. Bring them to me.
Delete these broken things that are attacked by the earthquake. Okay. Act normal. Get a cemetery.
What does the cemetery look like? Monument. Where is it? Medical. There it is. All right,
we got a cemetery now. We do have a hospital, right? Did he not like animal crossing? No,
I did. Just like ran out of stuff to do and I didn't want to just fast forward time over and
over again. I wanted to play it kind of every day. I decided that was going to be the thing I do at
the end of streams now is just do chores and animal crossing and go for bits. It was really
fun though. I like it. Are we playing it more? Build this up. This is, I'm counting on this.
Oh, another park. Jumpy house? No, something cool. What's this? Floating cafe.
Floating island? Put it over here. Nice. Does this cost money? How do I get this to...
I don't get it. Wait, is it a walking path? How do you make a walking path? It's got
multiple problems. No road acts. Make sure cars and pedestrians can reach the entrance.
Um, okay. Square packages. The packaging specialists are proud to present
the untold story of the invention of the box and the family rivalry that nearly destroyed
going from over here about opening your acceptance packaging. Whatever. Oh, that's so ugly.
All right. How do you use this thing? All right, here they come.
Vacation finally. I should do like 10 of these. No matter what stage of life. Oh, I'm out of money.
Okay, I have no money. Do a cafe too.
Floating cafe. Floating island. I don't have enough money for a floating cafe.
I do know. It literally means fried noodles. I took too much money.
Floating cafe. Wait, what? Wait, can I put it on top? Nice. Oh, cool, man.
Cool, man. Nice. I'll give them like a walking path. Why does this hurt my finger bones? Is this
hurting anybody else's bones? Just hearing this? Just looking at this? All right, so this is ready
to go. It is, right? These are ready. All right, we need some customers. Oh, I need a path. The
amusement park path. Okay. Amusement park path. That doesn't count as a path? Oh, all right. Now
we're going to do what we got. What's this? Park plaza? No, no, no. Cafe. Souvenir shop.
Rotating teacups. Perfect. Is that a park area? Isn't that expand the park area? Park area overview.
Zone it. It's own zone. Office zone. D zone. Is it the district? Is that district? City planning?
No. Where's the district? Cool. The zone. District scenarios. Okay. I want this to be an amusement
park. Campus. Commercial. What was it? Pleasure. Office. IT. Self-sufficient building. Is it creepy
mask? Tourism? Does it be tourism? Parks. Paint park area? Wrong. Almost. You have to expand out
of the existing area. What the fuck? Okay. The Myrtle experience. Okay, cool. Let's go.
Let's make our amusement park path. All right. We're going to go to the entrance is in a really
fucking weird place, but that's fine. Here's it. Ride road. And then here's cafe centers.
Rides over here. Trying to curve off. Okay. And then maybe one more down here and we'll
start from here. Can I make a roller coaster? What the fuck? Wait. I'm not doing a zoo. I'm
not making a zoo. Pendulum ride. Okay. Ferris wheel. Roller coaster. Nice. House of horrors.
Two more roller coasters. And then like a family fun center. Antelope enclosure. And elephant
enclosure. Okay. Nice. Okay. Now, uh, make a road to here. They're angry about that. Wait,
what did I just make? What the fuck is this? Look at how loud this is. Oh, this is upgrade.
Please. All right. Come on in. Six bucks. Seven bucks. Okay. Hold on. This is really important to
me. It's very important to me. I have to have somebody's backyard be the fucking
elephant enclosure. All right. Anybody coming in? Oh shit. It's dead. What is this little guy?
Anybody coming in? He cares. I spent all his money, but he's leaving. Oh,
I'm waiting for some crime rate is high. There's nobody else here. Only people
at the park of the mascot. There's no one else here. They're all just cartwheeling. Hey, kids.
Nobody on the rides. Wait, are the mascots riding the ride? This is only $160 a week. I would have
think that elephants would be like thousands of fucking dollars a week. Oh, well that makes sense.
That's right. Okay. Isolated. I just want someone to come in. I just want one person to come in
and then I'm going to go eat food. I just want one person to see this. They're multiplying. There.
Now go arrest them. This way. Arrest. Dude, look at that sea cafe. It's actually pretty cool.
Customer. Customer. Come on into foot land. There you go. It's you. It's collectively you.
You're going to the pendulum ride. Are you guys ready for this shit?
You're the cleaner at Frank's fish stick factory for over 20 years. Get there. You think your phone
is ringing whether you have a new phone, an old phone, or just make sure you always hear your
phone. Why are there this many? They don't need to be this many. This is a sad fuck.
Oh my God. You went all the way to the end.
Come on in. Come on. Have some fun. It's your turn. By the way, fuck this ride. I would never
get on it. I like amusement parks. I like going to Six Flags. I like Disney World or whatever,
but these rides are only designed to make you feel awful. They're not fun. They just
only are made to make you feel like shit. They're not fun. This is not... Humans aren't supposed to
be doing this. You don't see like the lions in the animal kingdom fucking swinging around in circles
like this. We're not supposed to be doing this. No, they would not if they could. Your organs
are not designed to be swam around like this. It's not supposed to be like this.
Your kidneys like smush into each other when you're on a ride like this. When is it your turn?
All right. Give me a second. I've got something very important to do. I'm just trying to make
as much noise as possible. Where'd you go? You're just still waiting. How long does the... Okay,
hold on a minute. How long does the pendulum ride last? This thing has been spinning for like three
weeks. These people are dead. Does it stop? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Where are you going?
I can't even click on you guys anymore. You're waiting to get on the pendulum ride.
There's people on it.
I don't matter. Goodbye. See you guys. See you guys tomorrow. I'm gonna get some food. See you
tomorrow for... fucking mystery game. Who knows what it's gonna be. Actual mystery game tomorrow.
And then Animal Crossing before the stream turns off. See you tomorrow for the mystery game.
Spin that wheel. It could be anything. It's gonna be an actual mystery. Because I don't know either.
McChicken review? No. This game is so much fun. I just... I'm not capable of doing anything that
makes any sense. It's very fun for the last couple of days though. Maybe if I really sat here and
like studied, I'd be able to do it. But it looks so much fun. This is a great game. I hope you
guys like it. Double the disaster rate. It's so hard for me. I think it's hard for people that
aren't smart. Or is it just hard for people that are stupid? Or no, it's hard for people that don't
put the time in necessary to learn all the mechanics. Thanks dude. No, no, no, no, no.
Shit. No, no. I gotta, I gotta fix that. No, no, no, no. Let me fix it. Let me fix it. Let me fix
it. Let me fix it. Let me fix it. Let me fix it. Let me fix it. Let me fix it. Let me fix it. Let me fix it.
Just hold on. That's not what I meant. I meant to say was start with me, not you. See you guys
tomorrow. What was that? I don't know. I think something was wrong with your computer. You should
do a fucking virus game with MauraBytes. I'm sure you'll get some potentially unwanted programs
or PUPs. See you tomorrow. We're gonna do the bits. We'll hang out for a little bit
and there'll be a mystery game tomorrow. That's right. Fucking mystery. See you soon. Thanks for
watching. Thanks for sticking around. Fish and Animal Crossing. I will. Don't worry. Tomorrow night
we're gonna hang out for like probably at least an hour or two and just play it to end the stream.
I need to go get food. Anyways, um, we had, I think I missed this earlier, but
Ryobate gave 10 community subs earlier. I think I missed it. I always hate missing those. Thank you.
Pixel Mike, thanks for the five hundred bits. You sound insane today. Are you okay?
I think like one or two people in the stream asked that. Does that mean that it's that I'm
insane every day? I don't know. I think I'm fine. I think I'm normal. I'm a normal person. I ride
my bike. I eat scrambled eggs just like you. Peaceful Haley, thanks for the two fifty.
Jeremy, if it makes you feel any better, I named my island The Island. This is Animal Crossing.
Never good at naming my towns. Don't want to sit there for hours trying to think of a name.
I'm not very good at it either. I'm not good at it either, but I do, I do like salted crest.
What's the name of the town? I have no idea. I already forgot. What's the name of the town?
Salt Crest? Yeah, thanks to the two fifty Haley. I'm also bad at naming things.
Sukhoi Flanker, thanks for the five hundred bits. Hello Jeremy, I want to apologize a bit late
though for pressuring you to play stalker. I was drunk like right now. It's all good. It's all good.
Remember, you cannot buy, you cannot buy me anything. You cannot make me play something
but money for the monetary purchase. Flanker, I do appreciate the insane amount of money you gave,
although it's completely unnecessary, but thank you. I hope I use it well. Thanks for the huge
money, as always. Sticks, Renegade, thanks for the two fifty. Oh, so you draw the Joker on your shirt
but you don't draw my fursona. I see how it is. Fuck you, Jeremy. Fuck, fuck you. Fuck you.
I'm never gonna draw a fursona. I'm never gonna draw somebody's fursona. It's not gonna happen
unless it's mine, which is not gonna happen either. I'm never gonna do that. I'm never gonna do it.
I can't, I can't, I'm never gonna do it. Ever, ever, ever. Thank you though. He has one to draw,
confirmed, whatever. I don't. Shadows1, Disciple, thanks for the two fifty. BaseStreamKing,
heard this new team already has millions of fans. The Cincinnati Clowns. It's true though,
I would watch every single game if they were a bunch of clowns that played football or baseball
or something. Wouldn't you, wouldn't you go there and cheer them the fuck on even if they were zero
in a hundred? If they lost every single game, I wouldn't even care. Who cares? I'm seeing a
lot of nos and it's, I can't believe it. I can't believe that you guys would not go support
the Cincinnati Clowns. A full baseball team where they're in full clown makeup and full clown
costumes. They just play regular baseball though. And sometimes like the pitcher will like take out
like a magical scarf before he throws a pitch. Like with a magician thing in the hands where
it comes out a million times and he throws the ball. I guess that wouldn't be a regular baseball
game then. Oh that would be so funny. I would, I would, if I ever had like hundreds of millions
of dolls and I could run like a movie studio or a tv studio, I would make a tv show where there was
at least one segment where the Cincinnati Clowns were just in the background playing and it was
just there. It's not even really addressed. It's just they're there like somebody gets a fucking
home run. Somebody falls down and shit and there's like car-tartoon noises and it would just be in
the background and you wouldn't even know it was there. Why can't I just have a fucking hundred
million dollars? You're a sucker. But what? Anyways let's look at their logo. This is a hockey team
apparently. That's pretty good. That's very good. Thanks to the 250 though. Hey dragon breath thanks
to the 250. So that bot spam earlier linked to some guy stream playing Fortnite. I went to look
and the guy seemed to have no idea what was happening. Everyone just started harassing him
and saying awful shit. His viewers jumped from two to two hundred when the spam happened. So I can
only assume the harassing was coming from this chat. Just want to let you know and make clear
members of chat that they should probably not do that. It was like a targeted bot campaign.
That's fucking horrible. Why would you do something like that? That doesn't make any sense.
Were you just like spam stuff like as if it was them doing it or something? I don't know. That's
unfortunate. I feel bad. That's too bad. No no it was not. Big thick ass. I forgot I said that.
I didn't do it papa. I swear. You better not have. I would be fucking upset about that. Leave people
alone. Hey lemon thanks for the ten bucks thousand bits. During my beg of you please stop picking up
weeds. Yeah yeah less than chump change and you get more from fish or bugs. Yeah I remember I
we brought it up. I know. Oh I know. Now I sold like 300 of them. They'll come back. They'll be
plenty of weeds tomorrow. Don't worry. We'll get them. Thanks for the thousand bits though.
Two scoops thanks to the 250. Fireman they say. Fireman's great. Two scoops again 250.
Dermot if there's ever a villager you don't like you can always harass them by hitting them with
your bug net until they get mad enough to want to leave. Try it. It's fun. I don't want to do that.
What's wrong with you? Rock writing thanks for the 300 bits. And everyone that heareth these
sayings of mine and doth them not shall be likened unto a foolish man which built his house upon the
sand and then rain descended in the floods and the winds and beat upon that house and it fell.
Great was the fall. What is this? Is this the bible? I don't remember there being a fast car of
speeding through the bible but apparently it's bible prophecy.
Peaceful Haley thanks for the 250. Time traveling in Assassin's Creed. Time traveling in
Animal Crossing. Oh you motherfucker. Time traveling in Animal Crossing has always been a thing.
I don't know why people are acting like it's the end of the world. Sorry but when you
got no friends and AC's all you got time traveling is the best. Doesn't screw anything up.
Also German do whatever you want ignore chat. I was thinking about it then I thought
Animal Crossing is a game that you can't really just play once and be like oh that was fun bye
turn it off. If you want to play it you have to play it over the course of at least a week or two
you have to just give it the time. So it makes a lot more sense instead of just skipping time
and streaming it for like six seven eight hours and being like oh it's cool we'll do it again
some other time. Just play the game the way you sleep your character gets up in real time and
here it is it's eight nine ten o'clock eleven o'clock pm pacific at night and we're just going
to do it for like an hour each night. I'm going to log into it every right now like these parts of
the streams is when you'll see it and I'll just be looking over at the dashboard and reading bits
and stuff while we do weeds and pick up stuff. It should be nice and chill. Thank you. Hey big
thick ass thanks for the 300 bits good stream son this was a wonderful family reunion. It went
way better than that thanksgiving stream most because I didn't have to see your uncle Lou in
person. Next time though please don't say my username out loud ps this really is your dad
and not some guy named Tingy. You guys are crazy. Hey time for a high five thanks for the 1500 bits
15 dollars for time for a high five you're my 18 year old cat's favorite person
more than me or my husband she watches you all day thanks for making my husband and I laugh
constantly cheers oh that's nice little cat little cat 18 years old that's a that's an old girl huh
18 god lover right that's great thank you so much thanks for the 15 dollars uh hey
thank you yifey boy for the four dollars can't wait to see how you screw this one up sorry
frozen crazy tuna thanks for the 500 bits jerma I was wondering if you would load up dark souls
right now with a new game and rush pinwheel to prove that it's an easy boss I've been a big fan
of yours for years I don't even know how to get there I don't I don't remember how to get there
I have absolutely fucking no idea I will humor you here I'm gonna humor you humor you I'm gonna
humor you here um if dark souls is installed right now I'll do it it is not sorry I do not
have dark souls installed it would take probably 20 30 minutes to install so far he knew it wasn't
installed I didn't because clearing out and uninstalling your steam library is like cleaning
your room you do you guys really I'll prove this to you go to your steam and find out a game that
you have installed that you may not have opened in probably six or seven years let's see installed
games okay just to show you Grand Theft Auto 3 is currently installed on this computer I don't know
why yeah I'd give it did I buy this recently did I did it has just been installed for like
three years I don't know what else we got uh we have uh jackbox party pack three is installed
what else we got here and I'm usually pretty good about uninstalling games I don't play anymore
waltz of the wizard which is a vr game that I never played it's still up still here oh shit
holy fuck I forgot I had this game um I know the mystery game is tomorrow I know what the
mystery game tomorrow is and it's gonna be fucking awesome it's gonna be awesome you want me to tell
you you know you want to know what the mystery game is I don't know if you want me to tell you
this supposed to be a mystery game all right okay all right I'll tell you all right all right that
was 88 80 like 9 to 90 percent no uh don't tell us but I'm gonna tell you anyways the game we're
playing tomorrow is casino ink this game is not what you think it is it is a it's a casino tycoon
management game where you have to like make the tables and no you don't gamble the people come
in and do it's an old game and a bunch of crazy shit can happen apparently everyone either that
or uh oh so no rain world I already beat rain world off stream and it was fucking incredible
story the art I loved it it was awesome I can't play it on stream I already did it what the fuck
lie detector lie detector I love I could press that button is be an idiot it's fun the virus
has been detected hey thank you too it's boo thank you boo it's boo here we want to say thanks for
streaming during a time like this seeing how vegas is going I got a pretty bad immune system
it's got me worrying I get my mind off it's been continuing my binge of vods from the stream
archive from when you started now I'm in the middle of your blitz little league of odds
oh I love that game just want to say you're the best entertainer I know and thank you for the
distractions and shout out to the stream archives as well for all they do true they do a lot and
they've been doing it for a long time too so that's good even before they've just been doing it they
just that channel has just been uploading just just take the raw stream put it on youtube that's
really really great great great great thank you we are almost at the end we have jack the mysterious
for five dollars no message just five bucks thank you cun pal for five dollars been having a real
bad time recently and the stream has helped cheer me up thanks thanks for hanging out we'll never
know about the first stream ever what was the first stream ever did anybody know what was the
first thing I ever live streamed was it 10 million is team fortress are we are you sure I don't know
no I mean this is like this is like eight years ago I don't know no my first streams were not on
twitch they were on the original youtube live back in like 2012 2013 maybe some founders will
know it was tf2 okay interesting time flies when you get old d warden thanks for the thousand bits
10 bucks hey jerma what do you what do you what do you do if you think your friends just act like
they like you what do you do if you think your friends just act like they like you what do you
mean like they don't they're like for they're pretending to like you I say you gotta try to
make some new friends that doesn't sound maybe if there's somebody's pretending to like that that
yeah I would move on to some another group of people or try to find some new friends
how do you make friends well um it's not really that's it's kind of a hard question because
I honestly I'll be completely completely upfront with you I I haven't made a whole lot of new
friends in the last five to ten years I'm also a lot older though I have a lot of long
term long-time friends that I met a long time ago that I've just it's they've stayed around for
decades 35 you should be making children but when I was younger it was really was just based on
interests for me it was when I'm when I was in college or I remember just you know yeah I played
a lot of video games and it was other people that played them too and one of your one of my roommates
had consoles and it was like oh it's a nice cool console you gotta play s3 yeah cool what do you
play and you just base it around interests make it you make friends because people that you want
to spend time with the people that also think the same things that you think are interesting that's
how you kind of hang out with them in the first place or people that you spend enough time with
that you can get to know them to be able to call them a friend somebody that you spend enough time
with and you like them and you actually genuinely don't you know if you don't get along with one of
your co-workers or something then it's like okay well then why would you want to be that person's
friend you got to base it around your interests and stuff that you have in common as that really
is the only advice I can give only because I haven't really spent that much time making new
friends I just have a I have a lot of old friends and it's almost like I made a bunch of friends
when I was younger and they that I don't really need to make anymore if that makes any sense
I got all these buddies back in in Massachusetts I've known for decades like decades fucking 20
30 plus years and I'm incredibly close with those people and then there's also people that I've met
on this platform there's people that I've met on like YouTube and Twitch that I I would call
pretty close friends all right but not recently not in the last probably five plus years is it
hard making friends being quote famous no no I mean that I wouldn't even I don't think that's
accurate because I don't think I'm that I don't think I'm famous I think I'm a person of interest
on Twitch I don't think that makes me famous I think famous would entail like 50,000 concurrent
people here or like I make a post on Instagram and it gets like seven million likes I think
at that point you're famous famous entails I think a lot of like public knowledge right but
no I'm I doesn't I I've told you this before when this stream turns off I'm just I'm a regular guy
that sits around eats potato chips watches tv goes to the fucking store Lil Nas retweeted rat
movie though yeah so so a famous person retweeted a thing that I had something maybe to do with
that doesn't make me famous right you know saying but you created it yeah but the rat's famous
not me right and that I kind of prefer it that way Lil Nas doesn't even know you exist bro I
well what do you think I'm saying that's what I'm trying to say yes he retweeted a thing that I did
I don't think he knows who I am that's that's what I'm telling you that's what I was just saying
how many people how many people deep dived that and found out where it came from I don't know
you might be watching right now that was insane when it happened though that was on the new year's
eve stream but let's keep going hey goiki thanks for 500 bits please reunite the dru crew tomorrow
I'll do anything and reunite the dru crew oh I can't no not tomorrow no I can't no I did
dru crew got reunited on the channel point stream and then they were immediately skipped after
having about 12 minutes of their reunion sorry hey the debo thanks for 300 bits hey jerma feels
a bit like my whole world is crumbling around me at the moment I just want to say thank you
for being such an incessantly positive part of my life for eight years and I love to everyone
in chat and hope everyone is healthy I'm sorry to hear that I'm not sure what you're going through
here but hopefully you get through it I am absolutely honored to have been a part of your
life for that long you've been watching for that long that's almost as long as I've been doing this
for you that means you've gone through you went through like the facecam fortress era and you're
here still now a lot of you guys are there like that that means a lot to me I'm absolutely
fucking honored that people would stick around for that long people don't even watch tv shows for that
long people watch like the first four or five six seasons of like people watch the first like three
or four seasons of a show like breaking bad and they're like yeah that was fucking phenomenal but
nah I'm done I'm shocked that I can potentially keep some of you guys attention for almost nine
years now it's crazy to me it only has five seasons yeah but I'm sorry I said three or four
but thanks a lot I really hope shit turns around for you thanks to three dolls let's get the
credits on all the subs tonight all the community subs all the regular subs all the long-term subs
thanks again problem tomorrow we will be doing probably casino ink unless I last minute pre-stream
psycho flip it on you and don't play that and do something else done that before it's a possibility
psych a dictatorship school thanks for the five dollars I think this is how you donate on mobile
you gotta figure it out love you streams even though the real germa has been hidden in the
basement in st louis for the last year anyways here's some shit I made yesterday while you made
the toll boots it's not about money it's about sending a message everything burned and then he
that then he goes this is when he goes with the and he goes and then all right this is spoiler
for batman okay oh and sport yeah spoiler for batman robin is his sidekick spoiler for batman
uh remember the movie that came out 10 fucking years ago that every single person in this chat
has seen there's no way nobody hasn't seen it yet if you haven't then I don't know what to say
I mean what what point do you not talk about the like the oh the heath ledger joker best batman
ever movie I mean at what point do you I don't know when do you when can we talk about it when
do we talk about the best movie ever okay well here comes a spoiler for batman the dark knight
here come what did I save this as about money is about sending a message never do it for it
thanks a lot hey reaper 500 thanks for the 250 hey all let's not let this pandemic make us forget
that germa not only died to pinwheel but also lost on the tutorial of plants versus zombies
but no the the losing to the tutorial on plants versus zombies is because in my ear there was a
producer telling me we the bot is broken you have to burn time and talk our everything is
fucked up and everything's broken and I'm sitting there just going wait a minute everything's
broken this whole stream this whole thing the fuck everything's fucked up I don't care about
placing fucking plants and shit I'm sitting there listening to a guy in my ear talk about
how the stream might need to turn off because everything was fucked up so sorry I wasn't
paying attention to plants versus zombies one until you prove it to us you lost to the tutorial
I could turn on plants versus zombies right now and beat the tutorial with my eyes closed do it
fucker no I don't feel like it I'm kind of tired and fucking kind of wants food I'm kind of tired
and tired and shit thanks for the 250 I didn't even die to pinwheel that's a funny fucking joke
that we all like hey Keith King Crimson thanks for the 250 a lot of the times people feel like
their friends are just pretending their friends really do care about them and do like them people
don't usually pretend to be friends with someone these kinds of feelings usually come out of a
place of paranoia and self-esteem issues I've experienced it a lot maybe the other chatter
how to talk to their friends about it if they're real friends they'll care enough to confirm that
they're not faking it that is true too that's true too I saw him died and you did not you did not
you guys have no idea which top but anyways let's get back to let's get to the real shit here
yeah the thing is it's everyone we kind of get in our own heads sometimes because you know all of
your insecurities but nobody else does so it's it's very easy for you for all of us to kind of
project our insecurities because we're up here in our own heads and we think that other people see
and know some of these things they don't you implant thoughts in people's brains that they
don't even have sometimes that does make sense actually that's pretty good advice thanks Keith
King Crimson for the good advice hey goo berry juice thanks for three dollars hey wow cool
germs playing animal crossing let me just tune in and oh my god what's wrong with your face
oh man I needed a break after seeing that okay he's playing city skylines now that's cool oh
my god what's wrong with your town geez dude it felt like your it felt like your face and
animal crossing in your town and city skylines both got fucked up and went through the same
rough party this guy it's the oh I'm back you're doing another thing and it sucks a bit
died to pinwheel confirmed yeah who do you think made these where do you think these came from
that's better I should have been using this from the very beginning that you know you know I'm not
even gonna you know I'm not gonna take the fucking cover off I'm not gonna take put the curtain up
behind so you can look at the wizard no these I this was fun oh yeah it's I know it's fucking
hilarious I think it's really funny you're not getting you know I'm not pulling the curtain out
no sorry you don't you don't want to see the wizard no you don't and that's the end but I
run the credits I did right I want to thank all the fucking people that subbed did I did that
right yeah I did I remember saw the name slime boy you did not yes I did please do bb unit before
you go HM zinc one more before we go hey German not to bug you but do you have any update on the
germa rumble now the whole virus thing is probably postponed the boston marathon
please tell auto I said hello yes I do have an update for you the new apparently as of right now
I believe September is the new deadline for fundraising so if everything stays
and with the same plan and this goes back to normal that stream will happen well before
September that'll probably happen maybe somewhere in like July or August something like that
somewhere probably around August let's just hope that this um this virus is under control by then
but that's the plan now all right I gotta get some food I'll see you guys tomorrow for a mystery
game it could be casino ink or it could be it hey it's a mystery game therefore it could be casino
ink and it could be super mario galaxy or if it could even be could be beautiful joe or it could
be no more heroes too but it won't be because that's gonna take more than a day to finish
and I got a lot of shit going on next week and I'm gonna take some time off to do all this in real
life shit it's not gonna be no more heroes too you're relied about no more heroes too within two
weeks I know I did uh it could be super mario galaxy too we might just go right to the sequel
it could even be I don't know I gotta stop saying super mario galaxy because I don't
I don't even own it I haven't I don't I don't own it I don't have it to say it is a mystery
game it could be anything it could even be oh it was obvious he's a red spy oh wait my audio was
delayed you didn't hear me say goodbye goodbye two three okay you should be okay you should
have heard it by now okay good night