Hello, how you guys doing? Welcome back to the stream. The stream is currently bopping. I mean,
it's on. I wouldn't necessarily say the stream is bopping right now because, I mean, it's not
there's not, it's not like anything crazy is happening right now or anything cool.
I mean, I guess the planets are cool. Nobody dancing though. Well, I mean, the jay is kind
of dancing. That's me. It's bopping. I retract my statement. When I say nothing, I mean nothing like
cool on that. This is the starting card and it is cool, but I'm talking about like nothing's
nothing cool happened yet on camera and the pre-stream voice. That's yeah, that's it.
Moving on to the real thing now. No, hope you're doing well. Before we get going, I want to talk
about a couple of things because they're very important and it is going to affect the streams
and I want to keep you guys in the loop of things because you know, that's that's what we do here.
So I am currently on a couple of new medications for my stomach
and one of them is kind of hard to manage. We'll just put it that way.
So the streams over the next week, there are going to be more streams, but they are going
to be shorter. So instead of streaming a few times for six, seven, eight hours,
I'm going to stream more than a few times, like probably four or five times in a row here,
but only for like three or four hours at a time. So more days, less time because the medication
that I'm on is kind of makes it hard to sit here for more than a few hours at a time. It's sort of
difficult to do. So I figured that's probably a good way to do this. We actually like that. Well,
it's just for this week because I do like to stream for at least six hours or so.
And we're going to start with fear. We'll not start with, I mean, we did horror stuff last week. So
what you can expect over the next week, the original fear is what's going to happen now
and then into tomorrow and the next day or whatever, you know, how we do this,
how long it takes to beat fear. I am not going to move on to fear two and I'm not going to move
on to fear three, at least not now. I've been told that fear two and fear three are not very good.
I've heard that fear one is great, but then the other two are really not even close. I'm not saying
I will not play them on stream. They're just not a priority. I also have the thing on PC. If you
don't know the thing, it's supposed to be the sequel to the movie, I guess. It looks like it's
going to be crazy. I've never played the thing. I've heard it's wild. There's also a couple of
PlayStation two horror games that I have, which we will try and mess around with. And then there's
a bunch of rhythm games and then it's Halloween. So that's kind of what you're looking at for the
next couple of weeks. But without further ado, let's get started because I don't want to sit
here for more than a few minutes because I'm kind of up against the clock. I will not go into the
gritty details on this, but we got to go. You know what I mean? We've got to start. So here we go.
I think there's a camera on. It's not. Why is the camera not on? Well, you can see that.
What the F? What the F? I really don't want to start saying F words. Like,
fuck. Did you guys know? I didn't even know this. I didn't know that you could say the F word on TV.
Did you guys know that? I thought I thought it was just shit. And, uh, and I didn't think you could
say that for it on TV. You could do it once once over a whole season or just once in an episode.
Do you have to pick the one place you get to use it once per episode? When are they going to get
rid of that? I'm just thinking about this right now. Like shit, dick, fuck, asshole. Who cares?
You're like seven-year-old kids and not watching The Sopranos. So why? The demographic for these
TV shows are for adults. We just pretend that adults don't say swears. I don't get it. The rule
is with the boomers. Yeah, but what about what your kids might hear? Okay, so if I have a DVD
player and I put an R rated movie in my DVD player and I press play and I watch it really loud in my
man cave, they're going to hear that too. What's the difference? It's like it's my house. I decide
the swears that come through my speakers. You know what I mean? Like, sure. Like, oh, this is
mature content in it, right? That people do that. Why can't I determine the kind of square words
that I have in my house? I'm just realizing this right now. That's fucking weird. Don't say shit on
TV. What? Why? Oh, fucking the world. You know what I mean? I'm supposed to go. Dude, my mom is
watching. Your mom probably says the word fuck a hundred times a day. You're just not in the room.
You're at school. Your mother like probably like stubs her toe and it's just like, fuck,
fuck, fuck. And then you walk in there like, honey, how was school today? I know this because I
caught my mother swearing. She was like making up. She was doing like a, she was making something
like a, she was baking something. And I just heard, she didn't know I was in the room.
This is when I was like, I don't know, I was like 17, 18. And I just hear like, she didn't know I
came in and I just hear like this fucking recipe is so fucking stupid. What the fuck is with this
fucking fucking recipe is fucking stupid. And I was like, Holy shit. Wow. And then she turned,
it was like, Oh, and she was like, sometimes when people get at, I gotta go. All right. What am I?
Low difficulty, not low, but made fun of. Not extreme. No. This guy, this guy, this game is
like 15 years old. Extreme difficulty means it's impossible to beat. You die in like one bullet.
I'm not doing that. I'm not doing extreme. No, we're going to do moderate. We're going to do,
we're going to do somewhere high increase enemy action. We're going to do weapons image
recommended for veteran players looking for a challenge. Moderate default enemy actually
weapon damage recommended for experienced players. Novice and casual. I ain't one of those. I'm an
experienced player. It's too late. There's no confirmation. I'm an experienced player.
I would do high. Well, we can change it on the fly. I think. Okay. Situational high level alert
has been issued. Mission fear teams to report for emergency briefing on the situation. You've
just been transferred to the unit as a point man. This will be your first assignment with fear.
He's going with two today. In 2002, the U S army formed a secret unit dedicated to
combating paranormal threats to national security. The unit was named first encounter assault recon.
Oh, for short, an iPad strategy game that just came out on the app store last week.
Sierra entertainment. That's an old one. Ma Monolith made this. That's right.
This is way too low. I can't even hear this. Hopefully you can. Nope. Oh, they're the ones
that made shadow of war, by the way. It's a great studio. That is so small. It's an eye exam.
Hope you guys like the subtitles. Pretty good movies. Sound clip too. We're going to be
criticizing this whole time. I hope you understand. Grant good Eve grant. Wait, the TF2 engineer is in
this game already plus five letter grades. Who's the, who's the, who's grant good Eve?
What the fuck did I do that for? What's that guy? Is he going to do it to you?
Oh, that's, that's the ATC of alcohol, tobacco and cheaters. Like it's cheating in video games,
the ATC. I know that one. I have to like not laugh today. Currently got a lot going on down here.
We can still resolve this discreetly, but we have to move. I don't think so. We got to find,
we got to find grant good Eve. This wacko's name is Paxton Fettle. He's the key. If we contain him,
we contain the situation. Fucker's got an appetite. I think he has an agenda. It's not just
you got to turn on VSync. Essential vitamins and nutrients. It's not looking good. What's his story?
Property of Armicam technology corporation. They're working on a military contract to develop
an army of clones that respond to a psychic commander. Top secret, of course. Fettle is one
of the commanders. You gotta be fucking kidding me. This is why nobody takes us seriously.
A full battalion of them, highly trained, heavily armed, full battalion. What are we supposed to do
against a thousand super soldiers? Like I said, we put Fettle down and it's over.
Fortunately, the whole point of the program is to give commanders firsthand knowledge of the
battlefield. That's not Boston. What are you talking about? Knowledge of the commander without
having to wade through all those soldiers. That's like Wisconsin, Boston. Planted a transmitter in
his head. Should lead us right to him. That's awfully convenient. Assuming it does what it's
supposed to. What about you buddy? Ready to go to work? You're putting him in the field?
Are you crazy? He just transferred in a week ago. Of course. His reflexes are totally off the charts.
I think he can handle himself. Whatever man, it's your call. Goddamn right it is.
Why do I feel like that's the kind of hat like a guy at the gym is going to have on?
Okay, car plus one letter grade. No sign of enemy activity on the satellite, but don't take any
chances. Jenkowski, you in position? Just say the word. All right, move it out.
Situation. F.E.A.R. mission coordinator Rowdy Betters has tracked enemy commander Paxton Fettle
to an abandoned building in Auburn District. Hannibal III spy satellite in Geo Synchronous
orbit shows no signs of replica soldiers in vicinity. F.E.A.R. combat operatives will
infiltrate target site from two separate entry points and attempt to neutralize Fettle. According
to Armachem, technical advisor, once Fettle is contained, replica soldiers will become inactive
and can be rounded up without incident. Investigate area for signs of Paxton Fettle. I could have just
read that part. Let's turn the volume up a little. Let's make it a little louder. I came in here
earlier. I'm trying to make it like a nice level for you guys. I don't want you to have your ears
hurt. And yes, I did get the I got the 90 FOV changer. So this should be at a good FOV. All
right. Do I have a map? What do I got a gun? That's very loud. That's like so loud that I may have
just scared the shit out of a lot of you. And I'm going to change that now. That's an explosion.
That that to me is the hearing that and how scary that was and how fucking abrupt it was.
That's like, what did you put in the microwave that exploded?
Like how long did you leave the bag of popcorn in there for? All right, well, how do I crouch?
Okay, made it. C. C and then it's, I guess you could shoot it too. Do you have infinity ammo?
Yeah, you just sprint normally. All right, so let's go. We gotta get in here.
Okay, no, we go this way. Thank God I could put toggle on. I did that before we started.
Press use to open doors or activate objects. All right, so use.
Really? Okay, I thought I was just I was about to make a joke about me being on fire,
but you can catch fire. Good to know. Tutorial. Wait, anything over?
Fuck. What the fuck are you doing? Wait, is it back for like vengeance?
How do I have flashlight, right? Plus V to use flashlight. I have a battery in the flashlight.
That's great. Please help us keep this room clean.
Why did you punch the glass out? Try to find a way around.
Rendezvous with Jan Kowski. All right, find a way around. Hey, bro. What a trash in here.
Come here, you little fuck. Wait, I can slide? Holy shit, he exploded. Oh, man, that was terrible.
I, okay. I just need to, it's a tutorial. I need to test, see if I can do that stuff.
Pick up a hammer. Wait. Oh, what? No, I thought it was pick up hammer. I can't use hammer. Oh,
that's a permanent health upgrade. I'm assuming it's like half life.
Come on, open for space to jump. Wait, open it. I can't. I can't open this. Touch door,
Easter egg. I can't like fit through that. I don't have an okay. The print is so small.
I cannot, I don't see. It's like I've 71 in that. What? All right. My accuracy rating.
Oh shit, I can knock him down. That's wasting ammo. Right. All right. Right. Right. All right.
Okay. I'm not going to waste ammo. Why'd you bring me here? Why'd you bring me back?
That was a delayed reaction there. All right. When were we supposed to just go around to find
that guy? Jan Kowski. Is it ammo anywhere that I should be? All right. That just,
I thought that was somebody coming to get me. Shoot the padlock. Sure thing. First try. Ready?
Shoot the padlock. Holy fuck. My God. All right. Where's Macaulay Culkin?
Hey, you would have had me. You would have killed, you would have killed me right there, Macaulay.
Didn't saw that one. Thin enough. Hold on a second. I was just, I just crashed the game.
You ready? Find a neutralized pack of Fettel. Go. And what's going on? What's, what happened to you?
Uh oh. Uh oh. I think that might have just been an Infinity Wars,
uh, an end game Marvel universe happening in the world here. If you have, it's, it's a spoiler
for Infinity. This is not even Marvel. Forget it. Jin, we need you up here. Looks like we're too
late, boss. Just leftovers. Gotta be around there somewhere. I'll wait here for Jin. You take a look
around. You guys are fucking hilarious. Infinity. No, I'm not going to make that. That's legit. Get
going. I'm talking to somebody in my earpiece right now. For all you know, I could be getting
some extremely important info. Dude, take a look around. Am I going to hit him in the face?
What are you, chicken shit or something? Look, you're the FNG. So you do as I say. What? Since
when? All right, let's go. If somebody here, we're outside. Let's turn the flashlight off.
I'm trying to prove that I can shoot in video games and they're giving me all these
fucking stupid little opportunities to show you. Give me a light gun. I would have had that. Okay.
What about up? Maybe up. That looks, can I get in the window? That would hurt so bad. No,
I want to jump and hit the window. Okay. I don't know what I knocked. I know. Well,
I can't get back up there ever again. Oh well. These things boarded out. I'm making a mountain
out of a molehill here. I killed him. I would have killed him. I got him like four times in the chest.
Makes no difference. He deserved to die. They all deserve to die. Come in. Over. What's going on?
Last pedal signal. Rejoin the team. Tom cast? What kind of situation?
Let's head back down. We'll be ready. What was the whole, what was the point of me going up here?
Just to look at the roof. By the way, I have 47 bullets left. I have shot like 30 and there has
not been a single enemy on the screen. So I might need to restart the game and just run through this.
Hey, back already? See anything? You guys about done up there? Our day's just getting started.
You boys run along. I'll be busy here for a while. Why? Because the guy's dead. Breathe.
I've tried to forget. I've tried so hard to forget.
Okay. These men are from fear. There are special attachments to our unit for the duration of this
up. They will be on point. Their mission is to assess the nature of the threat.
Our job is to keep them alive. Do not engage the enemy. Remember that we are not dealing with
ordinary bad guys. Team one will move in from the southwest. Team two will approach from the north.
Once our recon is complete, we will rendezvous and wait for further orders.
Okay. Let's saddle up. What if you're not on any, any team? Do I just stay in the helicopter?
Oh, right. Yeah. James, right. You, you go ahead and you open up your iPad and find us a good
place to eat after. Really important job. Okay. I guess. Yes, sir. Open up Google maps and just
type in food. That is actually pretty good.
Oh, yeah. This is little bird. We're on the ground. Let's go.
You're on point. See if you can get this kid open. Okay. I'd send one of my boys,
but I think we need a specialist for this one. Yeah. Stupid. Yeah. Since we got a Tweedledee
and Tweedledum over here, I think I can do, I'm going for it. Yes, sir. These two idiots. All
right. Uh, I think it might be over in here. What was it? A price scanner? Reflex booster.
Reflex is permanently boosted. Okay. Anything up here? No. Hey, I didn't, I didn't find that. I
found a reflex booster though, dude. Cool. It's not over here. You know, it'd be good if we all
looked instead of just telling me to do this. It doesn't work. Shoot the, shooting the gate doesn't
do anything. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Why would anybody do that? Did I miss it over here? Maybe
it's, yeah, I can keep going. I think there we go. Okay. Can I use this? Does it explode? Yep.
They just hear, they hear that downstairs over there. They hear a fucking explosion.
Dude, you just have to press a button. What are you doing up there? Okay. Hey, I found the button.
It's up here. It's going to be, yep. Coming. They're all skeletons.
If you look at her, you die. You turn it. That's like super Medusa. Medusa just turns you to stone.
This peels all your skin and muscles off and melts you. That's kind of fucked up. Status unknown.
Both teams have gone silent and fear teams. Life signs monitors are offline. Interference
is preventing satellite reconnaissance. Surviving operatives should attempt to rendezvous in an
exfiltrate mission area until reinforcements arrive rendezvous with Jan Kowski's team.
All right. Um, that's an interesting, how do they, okay. Warning. These premises are monitored.
Trespassers will be prosecuted. I probably just got pressing a button. Yeah. Don't have to worry
about. I know what that's like. The kill command activated. Okay. Yeah. Is there any stuff in this
game? I like this game already because it's not stuff to pick up. I have problems with games with
when you have stuff to pick up these people. I thought we were not. Oh, these bad. Okay.
Okay. Wait, what? What happened? Hold on. Did I lose? Did I lose the game?
All right. Okay. For a second, I thought we, I was rendezvousing and I stood there and exploding.
There was explosion that way. All right. I get it. Let's go.
I just started.
Do it. Good. Here we go. All right. Good. Ammo. Please listen closely as our menu options have
changed. It's been like that for fucking seven years. I think people know by now.
I don't know what's in here. All right. He's dead. I should be peeking way more often than I do.
All right. Wait, hold on. Everybody up there. Health kits, health bleach. I don't know. I'm
going to go up. It seriously is fucking home alone. What's in here? Oh, med kit to use med
kit T to restore some of your health. You can carry up to 10. Okay. Well, that's good to know.
I think I've got a med kit. I want to upgrade the flashlight. I ain't going that way yet.
There's another place to go down here. Is it fall damage? Nope. Best game ever. Okay. Nothing
out here. Can I not break through this? I can't just turn sideways and slide through there.
Oh, well, I guess not. I'm too, I'm too fat apparently. Yeah. That's all good. All right.
I got everything I needed. Uh, let's keep going. T is health kit, right? Uh, I didn't really mean to
do that, but it's okay. No, don't. Oh, wait, no, I want to go that way. Okay. That's how you get it.
Why am I sliding on this? Oh, that's how you get out. Very cool. Let's go. Checkpoint. That's not it.
Mouse three is mouse three is different because I changed it. Oh, I can't, I can't laugh that hard.
Oh shit. He was smart. What happened to that guy? What was that explosion? All right. I'm good.
The gun play is actually pretty fun. All right. I got a pistol. That's a, that's a double pistol.
We've got health 95. Any, uh, potions. It's fun. That's fun to shoot.
Right in the head. All right. I gotta be careful. I need armor. I gotta take flashlight off of V by
the way. It's getting in the way. It's me. I'm hitting C accidentally because I don't know
where the CV and X are on the keyboard and I'll laugh it up. It's fine. I don't see anybody. No,
don't break it. Hello. We all right. We good. Okay. Pacific rim. He's just like tripped. Check
it out and go see what happened. All right. We're good. Do you get a shotgun in this game?
Cause damn, that would be fun. Yep. Oh, good. Good. Good. Good. Fizzy Cola. Dice. Dicked. Squish.
I feel like the, the, that's like what you guys write in donation messages.
What? Oh, that's a grenade. How long did you hold that for? The timing on that was incredible.
What is mouse for? I have to heal. They have these insane grenades. I have them too, but
they blow up really fast. They are cooking these things for a full seven or eight seconds. Use the
slow mo. Oh, the camera's in a bad spot. Hold on. On the next save point. I'll move it. The game
hasn't, the game hasn't taught me to use the slow mo yet though. What's that? So I need to be true
to the video game. I can, I don't want to break that though. Oh, fuck. That's like super slow mo
videos. That guy's head rocked in a circle like five. That's how, you know, I hit him really hard.
That's like when you punch somebody in the face, like slow motion, it's like,
your face like turns to fucking yellow and you can see their eyes and skull pulsate and rock back
and forth. That's so bad. Okay. That's a good strategy though is slow mo punching face.
Anybody else in here? Oh shit. Pick up. What is that? It's an assault rifle
and another pistol. How loud is this? It's actually pretty quiet. It's like underwater.
Cool. All right. I'm not going to use it yet. We'll stick with the default. Is this a new pistol
or is this just two of these? Tri-wheeled. Hold the other one in your mouth, just like with your
teeth. They hit you with like feet. Pop on one foot and like, that'd be so funny. Why hasn't a
video game done that? Like laugh out loud kind of humor. You got three pistols. Oh, here comes like
a foot on camera up there. What a fucking hilarious moment that would be for all these streamers and
YouTubers. If you could see, if you could see, what did it say? If you can see the blinking,
it means what? That it can be activated. Okay. Loud noises. Anything else? What if he's like
blocking something? Nope. You know, there could be something under there. Like it could be any
situation where, oh, there's a grenade under there because you did that. All right. Let's go.
I, it's, I can't do this. It's a puzzle. I don't, I didn't think this was a puzzle game. I don't
want to do it anymore. I think I'm done. What? That's so much better than me. That projectiles.
Oh fuck. Okay. Don't fuck it up again. God damn it. This is far. Okay. Med kid. I didn't,
they all just kind of spawned and came at me. Are you, why is it on pulse fire now?
They were not this many before. Did it add enemies? All right. Let's go. Fuck. Okay. Is there,
oh, there is a save. Okay. I didn't know. Is it, was it F5? Quick saving. All right. Well,
now, well now I know. Whoa. See ya. All right. Where are those grenades? Quick save.
There's grenades in here. I know there is. Okay. Got that. Where are the grenades?
Come on. That can go off. There's nothing behind there or anything. Really? Okay. Fine. Whatever.
All right. Got that. There's no grenade. There they are. That's kind of cool. I'm going to do
that to somebody in slow mo. Quick save. Here we are. I made it. Wait, wait, that's got armor too.
They drop armor. That's, that's pretty sick. All right. All right. Here we go.
That guy, that guy like threw it like this. Why did he go like this? Usually you throw, you go,
all right, man, let's like throw it. No, he went like this. Here we go. Like he said, oh, I'm going
to windmill. He threw it right into the ground. He reversed softball pitch that good back upstairs.
Here we go. So he baseball pitched it. No, no, no, you don't pitch like that in baseball.
Nobody does. Nobody goes spin, spin up here and let's go up here. Nobody does that.
You do that under and you let go for softball. You don't do that in baseball. I know this.
I can't climb through that. All right. Let's jump kick. Wait, I think I got him.
I think I did it. Did he say, oh, slow mo. He didn't say that. Right. Am I just injecting that in?
Ah, why did my motherboard come out of the fucking monitor? What? Oh, he was so psyched.
Oh, shit, no way, dude. Slow mo. That's so cool. Okay. Here we go. Listen to the message.
This is it. They come out of the door. Get it ready. Ready? Hold on. Check this out.
They come through that door, right? Watch this. This is gonna be cool. It's gonna be cool. I think.
That was pretty cool. I mean, it was pretty cool.
Hey, dude. Look at it. When did this game come out? This actually is pretty good. This is like
pretty advanced shit for a game that had a future being 2002. When did this game come out? Like 1999?
The year is 2002. Like that's supposed to be the future, right? When does it come out?
2005. Okay. Yeah. I mean, that's still, that's more than 10 plus years ago. All right. Hold on.
Did I miss anything? It said 2005. Well, sorry. It's in six point font. Gun, armor. Nice. I'm here.
Did he say Pog? I'm telling you, you guys have ruined me. Grenade of Pog. Okay. Let's keep going.
Did I miss anything? I want to make sure I don't miss anything. No, it's just some boxes.
Rifle, rifle, rifle, rifle. Yeah. That guy's got a rifle. I'll get it. What?
It's got a shot in the head. Oh, a bullet in the head. What the fuck was that? Did a fly just fly
into my visor? What is it? Damn it. How many healed? All right. Assault rifle. Upgrades.
Games with upgrades. I love them. When does the game get scary? It kind of already has been,
don't you think? There's been like a few weird, scary. I mean, this, this is doing the scary
little girl thing back when that was in the height of its scariness. That looks like an exit.
I want to get this stuff. Nothing else. And telephone that's not off the hook.
And then, but they still, they're still doing the scary little girl thing. They just turned it into
a doll. It's evolved. Your height and reflexes will give you an edge against enemies. Press
slow mo to enter slow motion. See, I told you, they didn't give me a tutorial for it yet. And
you guys are trying to get me to do it. I didn't know what happens. Oh, the recoil. All right.
Let's end this guy with a kick. Damn it. Where the hell are you? Where's this guy? Did he die?
No, there's somebody still over here. No, he's dead. Good. Checkpoint. Save. Let's keep going.
Do a side kick. Ooh, what's that? Same thing I had? Yeah. Crouch and melee. A slide kick.
Do I have to be running for a certain amount? All right. Free slow mo. I could use it. Fucking
idiot. I just had to do it. It's like my attention problems. I thought I was far enough away.
Let's keep going. All right. Hold on. Um, doesn't look like you have anything.
No, dude, turn your own stream off. What are you fucking an amateur?
They don't have any stuff. This looks safe. I would highly doubt that, but you know, it's all good.
So slide kick, huh? Do I have to hold crouch? How do you do a slide? Double tap. We've got to be
sprinting first. Am I not sprinting already? Oh, I probably should run. I thought it was a cut scene.
I thought it was, okay, I thought it was a, I thought it was like a thing that we were watching.
It was playing music. It was like, I thought it was one of these kind of scenarios.
Someone, someone, there is nothing here. Just get to the turnaround and didn't do it first
try. That means we don't do it at all. All right. Part two, quick save often. You're supposed to die
there. So then the game can tell you, Hey, I mean, just want to let you know, you probably should
save all the time. You see, I wouldn't have done that unless you guys told me to. So you know what
I'm saying? Okay, here we go. Did I make it? I was trying to go through the door, but I got,
I jumped out. Okay. Cool. He's alive. He doesn't appear to be injured, although I don't know how
we survive. Injury level three escalation.
You can't send him in alone. That's crazy.
When we're just, I was just in there doing the go, I could go back in. All right. I'm going back in.
Can we trade your standing out here? You better get going. You're not in any immediate danger.
You're sending me in to go kill this guy. I want the better gun. You don't have to give me your
helmet too. It's the same gun. No, it's not. His is bigger. Let's compare guns. Well, whatever. I
want your ammo. Just take your clip out. Wait, what about, where does it want me to go? What was
that? Oh, okay. Dead guy. Okay. No, this is our choice. Not our choice. This is our chance.
What's this? Fuck. That's such a, I want that so bad. Bad guys. Now I see three tubes. That's an
explosion. Wouldn't happen, right? Or are they punching bags? Okay. Don't fuck around there.
One shot. Come on. Why am I getting flashbacks of a different game? What game did this happen in?
This happened in a game, right? I'm not insane. Am I? I remember being like on that exact bridge.
All right. Listen to the message. This turn on. Did I turn the alarm on? No. All right. This
changes this to go this way. Wait, what about down here? Any guns or weapons or hidden secrets or
something? Probably not, but I'm just going to do it. It doesn't look like it. Nope. Wear the shot.
Why not just build two bridges? Yeah. It seems very, very stupid. Why do you need an entire
electronic mechanism to spin this around when you could just have it cross in the middle? Slide
kick. How do you? All right. Let me get the slide kick down. Let's walk. I am running. I missed an
upgrade. What? Back to the boxes. Check the controls. All right. So controls. Configure
controls. Toggle walk. Movement. Step right, turn, lift side, walk, jump, crouch. Toggle walk.
Interaction. Flashlight, slow-mo, aim, reload, throw grenade. Look down, center view, inventory.
Fear one doesn't have a sprint. Yeah. So how do you do the slide kick?
All right. Let me step back to the boxes because I missed something. Did I? It's forward crouch
melee. Holy shit. Oh, nice. Reflex is permanently boosted. So you got to go like that. Okay. Can
you do it in the air? Sort of. Ow. That's a broken ankle. All right. So I moved to the thing, right?
We're going to go this way. Save it. All right. Turn the flashlight off. We don't need it right
now. Okay. Down into the sewer. I don't think fall damage exists. It does not. It's been confirmed.
You can jump anywhere you want. Literally anywhere. God. Okay. Narrow tunnels. Great.
I don't have any grenades. Otherwise I just would have thrown one down this hole.
Fresh blood on the ceiling. Ooh. Health booster. What? What? What? Why is my heart beating? 110.
Nice. All right. Um, caution. I thought that was a person. I go in this building. No admittance. Oh,
well. Peak. All right. There's health over there. There's a guy right there. Okay. Here it comes.
Okay. Slide. Ready? Here it comes. Did you hear that? Oh, what happened out here? Oh, Frank was
practicing back flips again. This time that's, he ain't going to be practicing anymore. Imagine
exploding because you did try to do a back flip and you grazed your head on the ground.
Holy shit. Holy shit. I wonder what that looks like. You know, we always get to see from the
perspective of the person playing the game, what slow motion looks like, but we never get to see
what it looks like on the other side. I want to see what that looks like on the other side.
Are you just really fast? You're just super fast. Okay. Ooh. Grenade. What's that? Nothing.
That's not what that sounds like. Okay. Let's keep going. What about the lockers?
When am I going to move my camera? That's, I know. All right. I'll do it right now. Where should I
put it? Is there a good place for this to go? Top right? That's okay. All right. That's better.
I'm not going to put it in the center of the screen. There you go. Now you can see
there. Put it right in the middle. I'm not going to put it right in the middle.
No. You know how many times I've done that? Doing that. Put webcam in middle, make it three times
bigger. All right. Let's slide. Uh, another person. How would you know I was coming?
We're going to slide tackle the first person that comes down the hall. One, two,
two, three. Shit. Who's left? Ooh. New gun. Slide tackle this guy. Where is he? Isn't he right
there? Oh, no, they're dead. Okay. But is this a new gun? Stuff. Is it stuff? Why is there a
ladder here? Oh, all right. I just, this is just the way to go. Oh, come on. Really free stuff,
secret stuff. No, I didn't get, no, there's nothing there. Go get it. There's something there.
I'm just not trying to make as much noise as possible. How many? One, two. Wait, why am I
going so slow? Oh, got him. No, that hurts more than a bullet. Turn the light off. I don't have
any more grenades left. Bad. Should I switch to the other gun? No. What's the point of switching
to another gun when you have the good one? Slow down. Is there anybody to jump kick? I want to
jump kick somebody through a window. Is that possible? Nothing in any of this shit. Come on.
Really? Am I blind? No. One of these times, one of these days, someone's going to just be standing
around the corner and it's going to be awesome. Well, um, here comes a boss fight or something.
Why would this all be here? Is there, are there bosses in this game? Yeah, this is a boss. Look
at this boss room. What? Oh shit. I froze up there. Holy shit. He got in. I can't see. Okay,
done. That's another person. There's one more. Where is he? Is he dead? He's dead. Okay. Healing.
Good. Anything else? Grenades. Copy machine. I did it. I did it. I did the thing. Guaranteed
fucking comedy points. I did it. I'm going to go up and around. Got it. Okay. Keep going. Save it.
I love quick save. Seriously. It's so useful in every video game. Well, that's convenient.
I wonder what I'm supposed to do with these. Can I pick them up? I can't. But wait a minute,
we got assault rifle, more of this. First aid, seven health packs. Should I? Okay. Should I
restart? Cause I, how much health do I have? I just took, no, I'm good. I didn't mean to do that.
That's fine. All right. I'm ready. Certain laptops contain useful information. Activate the laptop
to retrieve data stored on it. Why are there green tanks on the ground? If someone's not going to
like scream and sprint down this hall. Okay. Good to know. Why are there green tanks on the wall?
I'm not on the wall. Only, you know what I mean? And there's this shit. Okay.
Look at all this prep. 80 armor. How's that? Save it. This is the door. Can I move this out of the
way and make like a shortcut? All right. Here we go. Whatever it is, it is. Turn up the difficulty.
No, no. Absolute zero. No. I have to like, we'll see after like another four hours. I can't,
I can't even turn the, look at it. Where can I do that? Game. Yeah. I know it. difficult HUD.
Okay. I'll put the difficulty to the HUD up at harder. Where's the grenade? Nice. What should,
what should I do? No, this is, this is like playing the division. Now everybody has like 5,000 HP.
It's like I can throw a grenade in here. No, don't you gonna get a shotgun? Too bad. Where's all
their ammo? I think I have full ammo in this gun. Let's use it for a little while. This thing's
pretty sick. So save it. I can't, what the fuck was that? Now get me in here. Grenade. Nope. Just
a can of soda. They so badly want me to be ready. I have eight health packs. Is that what it is?
Is that why the difficulty had to be increased? Cause I have eight health packs and I'm only
supposed to have two or something. And oh yeah, you're so lucky. You can heal whenever you want.
Right. That's what it is. And yeah, I knew it. I knew it. I'm playing the game very, very, very
well. And all of a sudden it's like, you don't, you're playing too well. You have too many health
packs. Turn it up. Fine. How do I turn damage numbers on? Cause I might as well use that too.
Alligator or something. Let's give something in the water. In my opinion, this is just me,
but in my opinion, if there's like somebody waiting for you or stalking you here, there's like the
enemies. This is what I would do in this scenario for real. Instead of where the fuck are they?
Can they see me? I would just start fucking screaming and firing. And then they'd be like,
they'd be like, what the fuck? Wait, is he in here? See it worked. See that fucked him up
because they thought they were with it. When we go in the water and we sneak around and we say,
we'll be careful. No, that ain't me. Hey, when he gets to 10 health packs, we should put it on
extreme difficulty. That is never going to happen. If you want to see a blind play through of extreme
difficulty, you are watching the wrong video game live stream. All right, we're in.
Cool. Did I die? No, I thought that was, all right, good. It's just blood. Hey! That was,
all right, that was kind of scary. It was. That was a little scary. Just a little.
Wait, you think you're having a better journey than me? Think I'm having a cool, oh, I found
some. Oh yeah. Well, I found a, I know I found human remains too. And a fucking monster in the
water was trying to kill me. I killed it though. I mean, but like, tell me more about how awesome
your trip is. Am I underwater? There it is. It's huge though. It's unexpected that I still survived.
Hey, it's all right. I've got a, I got 11 health pack. I can't even pick him up. I'm doing so well.
Extreme, extreme. No, that's not. Okay. We're good. I have to, I need to lure somebody over
here to do this to them. She's afraid of you. Oh, wait. It's, this is like a new checkpoint.
Hold on. What's over here? I've already been here. It's like that game, you know, that game
where you, where you've hit the ice down, the little squares and the penguin falls through the
middle. God, I've loved that game. Here we go. Where's the, where's it? Oh, right here.
Somebody just crashed a car. I want to use this. Can I roll it? This doesn't hurt me, right? Okay.
I think I can do this. Is it on the ground? I don't think I can do it unless I can hit it right
here. Get it out of the, okay. Now, what the, how the fuck does that physics make any sense? I'm
trying to roll this way. Keep going. All right. If you hit it in the front, it rolls backwards.
Fuck it. All right. I did not expect them to be standing right here. They do this thing where
it's almost like they're auto targeted on you and they're strafing around you. So their hand goes
like aiming at like different directions behind them and to the right and left of them.
This is my opportunity. He just kicked me in the face and killed me. How far away am I?
What the fuck? Why did I not save it? No, I did. I did. Okay. I'm, you know, I'm,
I just need to make a macro in this game or just like a script that runs in the background that
presses F5 every 10 minutes. That's not illegal. Oh shit. We both did the same thing. Where is this
person? Don't die again. I'm stuck in the, my DPI just, why? What is happening? I'm using health
potions. He's using this spin bot. Okay. There it is. HP. Was that an arm? Okay.
No, this is not that, this is not that far. Yep. I don't, why do I not remember this?
Anybody else not remember this? The game icebreaker right in the middle. I missed him. It
doesn't matter. I don't remember this at all. Did I go a different way? I think I went a different way.
Shit. I got one. All right. Who's left? Anybody? Still left. Got it. Open the valve. Not yet. All
right. Lots of ammo over here though. Gimme, gimme, gimme. That's all. I have too much of this. It's
all right. I like to use, this thing's better, stronger, faster, less recoil. All right. Let's
go. You're playing, I'm playing daft punk. What do you mean daft punk?
Get him. One grenade. Got it. It's like the, got it. Got reflex booster. Got it. I want to go this
way. Shoot the grenade in midair. Oh, absolutely. We're doing that next. Second, I get an
opportunity to. I'm doing that. I got one chance. What is this? Buoy? Looks like we're going down.
What the fuck did I just do? I'm throwing my, that's a G. Throws your gun on the ground. Okay.
Why would you ever do that? F and G being that close to each other is going to be very, very bad.
I don't think I want those two bound. Throw all your guns on the ground. All melee run.
Oh, sour please. Here we go. What does that do? Raises the water level or I don't know. It does
something to the water. What does it say? Caution. Operate shouldn't buy certified operators only.
Okay. Ooh, it's full now and that can go over that way. All right. I don't trust this. What do
you think? Grenade in there. Okay. That scared the shit out of me. Okay. I don't know. For some
reason, I thought I had to use that. How is it already broken? Impossible. What? Oh, this is
where I came from. Right. Thank God. That's, you guys wonder why I'm doing that. Why does he keep
breaking those? Well, because it's a breadcrumb trip and I know where I've been. Oh baby.
They're all alive. Dead. I thought he dropped the grenade on the ground. I was going to say, dude,
what the hell is the matter with you? Great commentary. Dude, what the hell is the matter
with you? Paying attention and focusing on where I'm going. Words coming out of my mouth to fill
dead air. Dude. Okay. Is this now? That's what I'm talking about. I'm never going to have another
gun ever. I love, I love a shoddy. You know what I mean? Ooh, what are those mines? There's nothing
in there. There's nothing in there. Oh, I don't, I can't. I mean, that was cool, but I thought he
was dead. Why haven't I been, are you serious? It bounced off the ceiling. It bounced off the
ceiling, but it's okay. I still got it. Garlic bacon burger. That's a lot of fun to do, but I can
stop doing that. That's pretty dang fun to do, but not going to do that anymore. Here we go.
Shotgun save the game. Here we go. I'm not messing around anymore. Watch this one. Just going for it.
Mine. Just pick it up. Let's get a couple of these. Proximity. Press five to switch
proximity. Okay. I'm telling you, they're not throwing them right. What's that? Okay.
Through the middle. Oh shit. It spins. No, I thought it was a gray. It wasn't a gray.
What the fuck did you come from the ceiling? What? That guy fell from the ceiling.
Why are you crawling over here? Oh, this game is fucking ridiculous. I love it. Okay. Oh, what?
I hear auto. Oh shit. The wrong button. Ah, let me explain. Let me explain. Let me explain.
This is melee. This is grenade. I got to stop putting these so close to each other.
Grenade. Where is he? Up there. Come on. Fall. That sucks. Okay. Got some stuff. Back to the
shotgun. Move, move, move, move. Get up. What are you doing? What the fuck am I? What? Okay.
That doesn't work. I need explosions. Oh, we really would be great if I had, you know,
a couple of land mines would be fantastic right now, but I don't have them. I don't have any.
Where is he? It didn't do anything. Why did he just turn off? Why was it so loud? What is this
thing? Oh shit. It's like a rail gun. All right. Save it. All right. Hold on. I think I got to go
let auto outside. Give me a second. I'll be right back. I got to go see auto. Okay. He is taken care
of. And while there's a lot of people here, I do want to talk about this because I brought
it up in the beginning of the stream, but there weren't a whole lot of people here at the very
beginning. So this week I'm on a couple of new medications for my stomach and they're kind of
like fucking me up a little. So what we're going to do is instead of streaming like six or seven
hours a few times, we're going to do like four or five hours, like five times. You know what
I mean? So there's going to be more streams, but less time on each stream. So just want to make
sure people are aware of that because there is very specific reason why I will not go into the
details, but more streams, less time instead of the typical, what you used to is like six to eight
hours, like six, seven. I got a little nervous about that comment. Let's go. Oh, there I am.
So that was big guy. Wait, what am I doing? I need two headphones. It's so much better to play
games with headphones in. I've been missing a lot for the last like two straight decades. Damn.
Okay. Do I, I want to keep this going for now. Get the shotgun. I want to try this weird laser
pointer. Yes. Yes. I'm so happy it did that. Pulling out. Are they afraid of me?
Do I have them in a full retreat? What did I just do? I just put, I didn't pick up anything.
Why did it just took a health push? I didn't press anything. I did not press the button to
do that. Ooh, found the secret permanent health boost. I'll take it. 115. Nice. I love upgrades.
How much almond milk do I have in my fridge right now? Zero. Cause it's gone.
Let's go back. I want to see how this gun works. Is it a one hit kill? Is that guy streaming?
Where's he aiming? I want to see how he's aiming this gun. It's important to me.
Nevermind. Oh, this thing is insane. Okay. That's crazy. It's wow. I like this thing.
Is that gas? Yep. No, it's not. What's going on? Is this room filled with gas? I have no idea.
Oh, you can get that open, please. Oh, I don't know. Oh shit. What is going on here? Cool, dude.
How do I get it? Oh, turn the gas off. Yep. Or rise the water. That works too. I got a checkpoint
here. Hammer. Check the room first. Cause I can now go in here. I thought that was a person
crouched. Ooh, all right. Shotgun, but how loud is it going to be? Be careful.
I want this thing. This thing is awesome. One headshot and it just stuck to a wall.
It's beautiful. I love it. Swap the way. Oh, you can just take any three weapons you want.
That is very interesting. I'm glad you told me. Interesting stuff. Okay. I thought that one was
light weapons. Two was medium and three was heavy or something. I don't know. How am I supposed to
know? Save it right here. What is that? I hear something. Turn the flashlight off. This is a
place to hide. I'm going to have to hide back here. I know it. Where is Alma? I don't know what you're
talking about. Some secrets get buried deeper than others. But I know, Mr. Moody, the time for talk
is done. Please. No. All right. This is the guy. That's the guy we got to get rid of.
It's a real bad guy. Okay. But wait a minute. Didn't, wasn't there someone else? No, it wasn't. Okay.
Hey, hey, a crawl, a crawling horror movie trailer girl. Of course. How could I have ever thought it
was going to be something else? Then on all fours here, I'm running at the camera and then I just
have to get sucked. I have to land on my stomach and get sucked backwards and then smash into a
mirror. So, okay. Mission three is pretty much done. No, it's not. Just make it down. Make it
down. Make it down. Deserve to die. They all deserve to die. I wouldn't be scared. I just
didn't expect you to be there. No one can look cool when someone startles them. Guys, when Dwayne
the Rock Johnson is standing there and he's like flexing in a mirror, just like looking huge and
fucking awesome and somebody comes up behind him and like grabs him, he's going to go,
you can't, nobody looks cool that way. I'm trying to take out the cameras. What the fuck am I doing?
All right. Here comes a little scary thing. I'm wasting ammo in this gun. Am I going to stream
with the rock? No, I don't, I don't think that's going to happen. I'm sorry. What this shit, what
is it? All right, we got the info we needed. Get out of here. Wait, keep this room clean.
Something's going to jump out of here. Did I just grab onto it? I can't do anything about it.
There's nothing I can do, right? I don't think so. Maybe I should go down.
Clean it. This is not visceral cleanup detail. Oh shit. Okay. It's mine. Get out of here. How do I
get down there? Got to go like around and down. Okay. I know like, like official, right? People
are writing like, oh, official Dwayne the Rock Johnson, official the rock. If it were you,
would you like my, my name is not official German 985. It's just German 985. Why does everybody
think that that's a way to make it seem like it's legit? No, you would just be the rock.
Official the rock. What? This guy's stunning. Something in the water. Something in the water.
They've been putting, they've been putting chlorine. I'm going to be completely honest
with you guys. Um, I looked over at you guys at chat and, uh, came back and turned my eyes
on the doors in front of me. And it was more startling than if I actually saw what happened.
Holy shit. What the hell was that? What was that? What was that floating person?
What was that? That was fucking weird. All right. I made it. Hey, stop. Why are you getting all scary
now? Where's the guys? Where's the funny slide tackle the enemies and watch their heads hit the
ground. You can't be scared of what you can't see. Told you in person. Where is she? Oh, fuck.
Why did it bounce off of him? What's going on? Do the thing.
Oh, my. That'll find, sir. Origin. Origin. I knew it. Hit the lights. What do you mean hit the
lights? You just turned them off and now they're back on. What? Boom. Right in the head. Still
alive? Right here. Do it. DPI. Fucking DPI. I'm not, I'm underneath you.
What the fuck is happening? No, wrong button. DPI. Why do you do this to me?
Did he just say that we're good? I think so. All right. Investigate time.
Holy fuck. Okay. I don't have any health packs left.
Why are there so many people in here? You didn't have to do that. You did not have to do that.
Oh, yeah. Okay. Save it here. I actually could have just had them burned by running down the
hall. Should I go up here? Save it. Okay. Cool. I got armor. Jesus Christ. Where is this guy?
Fucking hammer. Where? That is a lot of fun. Where the fuck is he?
What the fuck was that? Dude, I don't even know where I'm going right now. What's the mission?
Find packs and fetal. I have no rail gun ammo. Oh, now I do. I'm not going to use it for a little
bit though. Give me a shotgun. Good ammo. I don't know. I don't know. I know. I know. Saving. Okay.
Just save it again. Just double save. Just in case your computer crashes when your hard drive is
broken. That's saving on a different hard drive. You didn't think I thought about that?
How would you explode from that far away?
Dammit. No. No, no, no, no, no. Wait. All right. I was going to go backwards.
Is this guy Canadian? No. I think he's Wisconsin. What the fuck was that? He's putting down mines.
All right. Mines. So the goal is to get him to walk over his own mines. Sounds like plan B.
See you guys 45 or so minutes from now when we actually get that to happen.
Oh, more rail gun to save. Hit the bell. I guess not. Wait, there might be others.
Grenade. Nothing else I need. All right. I can break that. How close can I get to these proximity?
So then, I mean, obviously I cannot go over there. What's the distance though? I just need to see.
Is it one square or is it more than one? All right. That's not bad. I could just shoot it too.
You're out of the way.
Once they've got the fire under control, we can check the rubble.
Not yet. Save it. I've gone. I've been saving. Rats. Can I get through this? No. It's a wall.
All right. Scary guy just jumps in the water. That means I have to jump in the water too. Or do I?
I do not have to jump in the water. I get to bypass that whole segment.
Let's spawn him anyways though. Never mind. Right. Okay. Three shots. One, two, three in the head.
Here we go. He's going to get stuck to the ceiling. You motherfucker. I swear to God.
I think that's it. Give me some more rail gun. Nice. All right. I ain't going to just sprint
over here because if there's one, there's two. If there's two, there's three. And if there's three,
there's 10. Kind of how this game has been working so far. All right. Is this in the
source engine? I don't think so. No, it's not. I don't know what this is in. It's probably like
Unreal or something. One of the old Unreal's. Flashlight off. It's the boomer engine. Health
upgrade. Good. 120 max HP and a new health. All right. Cool. Damn it. I can't open that.
Come on. Got to go down here into the water. Fine. This way. This does remind me of Half-Life.
Even just the sound effects too. That alarm sound. The going through the water sound. It has guns.
Yeah. That's right. I didn't even think about that. Yeah. I didn't even think about that. It
has guns. You're right. It's weird. It's got health glued to the wall. Wait. I ended up.
All right. Fuck it. I don't care. Does that mean I can't go that way?
Why do I feel like this is going to kill me? Shit. How did I go all the way back around?
There is fall damage. What? Just run fast. Run fast.
My body is exploding. It's disintegrating. So no, that's not how this works.
Just use a health kit. Guys, I'm spamming T. It's not going to work. I'm out. I'm going that way.
I will pick this up though. Shit. I went the wrong way.
Back down here. Where did I go wrong? One of these big rooms back here.
I shot the mines. Yeah. Yeah. I did. I didn't know it was going to cause electricity
all over the place. Use a grenade and boost yourself. I don't think that's going to work.
This is where I remember this up. Should I go up here or should I go down there?
I'm going to go up that way. I actually almost just made it. I almost just made it.
Okay. So there's a bottom there that there's no water underneath. It just goes all the way down.
That's good to know. So you don't shortcut jump that just go around and go up. Very good to know.
I'm not going to bunny hop through it. I'm going to go the right way.
There's no bunny hopping in this game anyways. Why am I even trying? I know it doesn't exist.
Why would I try it? See, I thought there was water here. Here we go. Ladder up this way.
I didn't go up here. Maybe I did. Let's try it. Okay. And then is that the? Oh, here it is.
I haven't. Okay. This is the electric. That's the electric. Oh no. The health kit. Oh, here we go.
Solved it. Nice. All right. Let's keep going. 35 armor. Feels pumpkin man.
Feels pumpkin man. What's feels pumpkin man? I can't see it.
Okay. Mine's. Yeah, I do have a BTTV. The thing is though, I'm your chat right now is coming
through Streamlabs. The Streamlabs OBS. So I don't know if I can have BTTV through Streamlabs.
That's a new gun and there's more health. All right. New gun. What is this?
ASP rifle. Oh, that's pretty great. Actually. I love that noise too. Perfect. All right. I don't
need the assault rifle. I want this. How many bullets? 30, 15. Okay. Remote bomb. Remote bombs
stick to almost any surface, including enemies and can be manually detonated, making them ideal
for traps. Oh, don't do this to me. Don't give me this kind of shit. You don't want me to have this.
You sincerely do not want me to have this, but you gave it to me anyways. So
I'm just going to use it immediately. Over here. Wait. I was already over here.
Is there a straight? Straight through here. I came up that way. So, huh. We're just downstairs.
Here comes the blew myself up joke. No, I'm not. I'm it's blow the other guy up joke.
We've lost contact with the search team. How would you even see me?
Is it playing the game that you don't throw with like that? That's just the detonator, but
okay. I get it. I understand. I didn't. I thought you'd be like threw it with that or like,
I get it. It's okay. Nice placement. Can I break this window without them freaking out about this?
I didn't do what? Let me check it out. You heard the wind.
It's not satisfied. I was not satisfying enough. I don't. That's a lot of people in there.
That's pretty cool. Works pretty well. Pretty cool. So we get regular grenades. We have,
okay. Do I have one regular grenade? Okay. Storm troopers. Their aim is sort of as bad as storm
trooper. I want to try the sniper rifle. I'm going to snipe somebody. Who can I snipe? Right
here. Nice. Should I go down? Ooh, there's more of this. Okay. So we need. I mean, I have.
That's what I currently have. More ammo for that thing. Pretty nice. Pretty nice. I wish it was
only a one shot. I don't want the first. I only need is one bullet, not four, because it goes,
did it in, did it in, right? Did it in. What are they? What are they? What are they?
Something like that. Let's see. What are they? That helicopter is huge.
You only dropped two. Why didn't like 10 people come out of there?
No, don't waste them. I'm up. I'm up close now. Get the shotgun hazard. I didn't even use the
hazard really. Nope. Nothing. How do you hear me? Where are they? Where is he?
Are they upstairs in the room? Movement. Who threw that?
Is he dead? I am fucking around. Let's go. I'm no more screwing around. Wait for my signal. Yeah.
It's called. You're dead. It was me. Oh, he fucking missed. Fail.
Who the fuck are you? Oh, I got it. Come on. Did I get him? I couldn't even think about it.
Where is he? It's right there. All right. Those guys are tricky. Those guys are hard.
What else you got? Submachine gun. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. What do I got? 25 shots.
Bad. All right. I got three health packs. It's good. Not terrible. Not great. Not good either,
though. That's where he came from. Very nice. Okay. You missed a health pack. Did I miss a health
pack? Where do you see that? Oh, oh, you got baited. Baited. I don't think I did. I think I'm
doing just fine. All right. Straight through. My point man's current position.
Problem is there's an enemy gunship sitting there at the moment. Oh shit. Thanks. Nice. Okay. Turn
the light off. 70. Ooh. That's exactly what I want. Got 45 in this now. I'm going to use the
shotgun. Yeah. Shotguns. Look at those ammo. That's way too much ammo. Comcast. Yeah. That's right.
Sounds like they're saying. All right. Uh, good. We're good. We're good. Save it. Someone's going
to pop around the corner. I'm not going to shoot him right in the face. Or not. This is going to
alert people. Just don't just walk. You can make it in there. You seriously can. You really can. I
know you can get in there. You can fit inside of that. You are not as big as this. I don't want
that though. No, I like what I have right now. Helicopter battle. Looks like it. I'll put you
can go through that. Right. You can go through that. Uh, nine shots in this. Hey, what? Nice aim.
Idiot. Oh no. Not another one. Okay. I need. Is that a person? No. Run away. NA aim. NA aim.
Explosives. I have one of these. Okay. I'm going to use this one first. Did I not throw it far
enough? Why do you have so much HP? It's just not even fair to us that don't have those suits.
Oh, I just panicked and had to try. Okay. I have to replace something. Maybe not. Did I do it?
This is the, oh, that's the evac point. Interval four.
How do I like the game so far? It's good. It's fun just to shoot and there's some weird stuff going on.
Look at that water. It is pretty beautiful. Drop the scope gun. Ammo forward is too scarce
for it to be viable. Yeah. I guess, you know, that's probably true considering
when you, it's not like it's that big of a difference.
Really guys. Really? What? Okay. That was a little.
That guy has three in his head. He has three in his head. Why are you still alive?
Holy shit. You are a maniac. This is the kind of shit that happens to people in BR,
like in Fortnite and shit. You're just jumping around trying to get that and,
oh, I just got fortnighted. I got like, what? How did I insta fucking die?
Why? That guy's not dead. Can we be clear about that? He was still alive.
I thought it was going to bounce back. I had this, I was just being a cameraman. I'm sorry.
He's got it out. Instantly killing me.
Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Okay. I need to pay. Okay. This is,
I'm going to run. I'm going. Here's the plan. You ready? Watch this.
Oh, this is not the shotgun. Oh shit.
Where is he? Fuck. Where'd he go? Whoa. He fell off the edge. Oh shit. I got him. Okay.
Um, I need to tap a new gun or something. What's this? Oh, that's a nice one. No,
it's one I just threw over here. Okay. I'm going to save it here. I have no health.
Is he going to do it? What do you think? No, he's not. We need 20 more. Oh shit.
I don't think we need more than those. Pre-recorded. What'd it say? Pre-recorded.
Bleach. Oh, no. All right. I don't want to make noise and stay down. Health. Nice. 130.
I feel like you were waiting for me. 200 is max. That makes sense. Watch out for that gas.
What did he just throw? Check it. All right. What, what did you, did you pre-fire me? Okay.
Guys, I, he's, he's pre, just kill me. I'll do it again. Where should I go? I love it. He's just
holding down the trigger on me, screaming, where should I go? I'm so scared. This guy's
fucking terrifying. If the grenade throw, if the grenade pops up here, I'm going to be very mad.
All right. There's no grenade. Oh shit. That's so funny. This bitch jumps at like, like 10%.
Dude, dude pulls out a shotgun. Oh shit. He gets his fucking face blown off. The guy next to him.
Oh shit. Oh, this game's fucking awesome. Oh, that's fucking real. That's just really stupid.
That's really stupid. Oh, okay. Hold on. I have to compose myself here. Let's get this together.
I was hoping he was going to say, oh shit. Oh shit.
I don't know why it's making me laugh so bad right now. What is he aiming at?
I just got, I get stuck on something and I can't, I can't get away from it.
Why wouldn't you do anything? Protect yourself. Okay. He was scared.
Whoa. I held the button for too long. You guys are played, uh, smash TV.
He's not going to use the stairs. It reminds me of the, no way. No way. That game is so good.
I should play that game on stream. I'm starting to kind of lose it. It's too ridiculous sometimes.
You got mortal combated. Yeah. He did like a high punch, mid kick, high punch, mid kick. He was
trying to do a combo. So yeah, it's all right. It's okay. Sometimes you mess up the, mess up the
button combos. He was trying to do like the sub zero freeze. I don't. That's true. You do have that
right. Okay. Let's, oh, save it. All right. I'm good. Two health packs. What's with this?
Here comes the music. What's with the, here comes the music. A lot of people out there.
Good. Can somebody, can I watch that clip? Can somebody cut the, oh shit. Oh shit. It's,
it won't get out of my head. I just, I need to see it again. I don't care about anything
else right now. I just want to see it again. Like you get, you can watch it like on your own time.
I just, I need to see it again. It's funny. Okay. I just want to remind myself if it's funny or not.
All right. I just needed to, sometimes you need to be reminded if it was funny. Okay. So
I'm going to go up this way. Darn it. Darn it. Healing sticks.
Wait a minute. Oh, through the glass. I need to jump through the glass.
I did this already. How did I, I hold up the sign that says, uh-oh. And then I fall. Locate
and reset the network. I'll try. I need healing. I need healing very, very badly.
Oops. Now no one will ever get into the network. Okay. You got to wedge it with something.
Just stick something in there. I got to wedge something in there. First of all,
let's get some refreshments. I don't think there is any refreshments. No, there is not.
Somebody in here watching this. Okay. That's pretty, that's pretty funny. That's pretty great.
It actually moves the projector around too. That's, I love it. That's great.
This is, that's highly detailed for 2004. Hey, open this. No, not, not if I can be open until
the network's back online. Anything in here? Health pack. Nothing. When there are horror
game like this, we walked around in the office. Oh shit. Stay out of my way. What is up above here?
Oh, computer. The data is uploading now. There's a reference of something called Icarus. It says
here that it was a bioengineering program that started in 1973. Something about health issues
related to microgravity, loss of muscle mass, bone density, shit like that.
Well, it's shit. Okay. Oh, I mean, it's the other side. Okay.
Assault rifle. I was, I've talked a lot of shit about how much health I had and how many health
packs I had. And now that I switched over to hard mode, I've not had as many health packs. They,
spawn less. Enemies take more damage. It's a lot harder. Nope. I was going to say it's going to
open up and scream. I knew it. I fucking knew. I told you, I knew that shit was going to happen.
Fucking Venetian blinds. I'm telling you, they're the worst invention in history.
I will never have Venetian blinds in my house. I don't understand why you want these huge,
obnoxious pillars that get in the way of everything you do when you open a door.
Why are they still putting these in houses? Why? Everybody hates them. Every single person hates
these things. Ask anybody that has them. Oh, yeah. They suck ass. Oh, okay. Why are they in your
house? I don't know. Get a curtain. No, I don't want to get a curtain. That means I have to
go to the Home Depot and get a curtain and put it up. I'll just deal with the,
like the swinging pendulums of death every time I open my slider.
How do you leave a voicemail on a public phone? Later. The glossy TV. You should get a matte TV.
Never buy a glossy TV. And if anyone wants to argue with glossy screen versus matte screen,
I'm sorry, but you're going to lose every time. I will win that argument every single time.
Oh, it's a satellite. Okay. How many, what do I have? Three. Okay. I have four. I have three grenades
and let's get the shotgun out. Comes a jumpscare. No, no jumpscare in here. That's strange. I would
have thought it would be. What's that? All right. I thought that was this gun. Hello? I'm walking.
Stop walking. I'm freaking out right now. Okay. Just don't kill me. Kill me. That was bullshit.
I'll do it. That was terrifying. I'll be ready this time. That's like, what?
This is unbelievable. There's no way I'm visible. Well, they're in the game now. That's great. I
can't wait to deal with that. Look for the little wiggly lines. Dead. Place to go up there. Can I
jump up that? No, I can't. Got him. If you only knew how to defeat me. Chuck Hamburger?
So we've got, nice. Good. We've got a, I've got to go up somehow.
I have to go up that shaft over here. How am I going to do that? Is there another way to get up
there? Can I, I guess I could just go through here. All right. Be ready because I'm trying to
put the nail in the guy's head. I see electricity. That's what, I know what that means. There's
electricity. He's running above me. I don't know why that scared me. I don't know. I was ready for
it, but it still did it. I don't know why. Why is this opening? Oh, look, look. It's an, it's office
space. TPS report. Red stapler. What's this say? November. Oh me. That's an office space
reference. That's a pretty good movie too. Never seen office space. Go watch it. Right now. Just
go get it. What? I think grenades. Don't touch that dial. We're just getting started. Thanks.
Appreciate the feedback. What the fuck was that? What's wrong with me? Why is everything all spooky?
Show yourself. That's all it took is right in the stomach. All right.
Shotgun is way better for these guys. You just plant one right in the face. I thought that was a
mine. Computer. Ooh. All right. He's uploading. Looks like the Icarus program got shut down in
favor of something called Perseus, which from what I can tell is funded by DMZ. I'm guessing that's
where Fettel had been sold. Server room. I can't go in server room. Guy live. Hello. That's silent
in here. Why? Oh you piece of shit. Where are you? Bye. Where's he? Don't shoot. It's Norton
Mapes. I'm an engineer. What? Give him a comm link. Hello. This is a human Garfield. I'm having a
hell of a time. He said you're an engineer. Tell you what. You disable the local security system
and I'll see what I can do about the server. I can disable it remotely once I'm locked in.
No, you can't. It's on a separate network. To bring down the security system anyway.
It's happened. You want my help? That's the price. What's going on? He's eating the grenades.
What else does he eat? Will you eat anything else? Whoa. Wait, hold on. Just wait here.
Okay. Back up. That's the price. Okay. That's it. We're good. Just wait here.
He's just an NPC. Whoops. Restart it. Restart it. Restart it. Restart it. Restart it.
Uh oh. Human. I can't believe human Garfield. That's sad. You want my help? That's the price.
Okay. What does he want? Just wait here. What's he eating? Those are Cheetos. He's actually eating
Cheetos. That's fantastic. That's the best character. I wish I could play as that character.
I feel so much more at home. Human Garfield. That's so funny. Scary. Dark hallway. Don't want
to go down there yet. Don't do that. Okay. This is his desk. Oh god. Look at this, like,
gamer chair. Look at this gamer setup. They don't even make Cheetos bags this big.
That's bigger than the monitor. This is like a 24 inch size Cheetos bag. They don't even make
these. Well, let's listen to the message. I just want to shatter his computer so he freaks out.
You know he's had that monitor for like 15 years.
All right. Let's do some sneaking around and actually stealth kill people.
I wish I had a little map with a radar. Okay. So far so good. This is it. Let's try to get a clean...
I mean. I wish I had a silenced gun. Who's down? Am I down here? I mean,
how did you know I was up there in the first place? Holy shit. What was that?
What's that?
You see him?
Yup, yup, yup, yup.
What? Bullshit.
Bullshit.
Alright, that's it.
I've had just about enough of this shit.
I've had just about enough of this.
Wrong button.
Whatever, just die.
Are you really throwing a grenade?
I thought he was
Like, I'm gonna do it.
I'm getting ready.
There, right there.
Right there, right there.
What was that? Did he fall?
Who's fucking tripping around?
Clean. Clean.
Very clean.
Okay, healing.
What else we got? Nothing else here.
I'll take the
I'll take the shotgun and the shells.
We good, we good.
Armor.
Nice.
117 shots in this thing.
That's pretty good.
Oh damn, alright.
Decision time.
Wait, what the? Grenades?
Shotgun.
And then I have
Do I have full ammo with this?
I think so.
Actually, it wasn't really that cool.
Oh well.
I have full ammo for everything.
Good. What's that?
Activate.
Got it.
Locate and reset the network hub.
I will try.
Server room is down here.
Right?
Where was it?
Where was the server room?
Back here?
There's a label. Server room.
Come on in.
Back at the beginning?
Target.
Get that open.
What?
I'm not using this gun.
I'm using a shotgun from down the hall.
Server room. There we go.
Alright, save it. Now...
Wait, hold on.
Let me go in here first.
Alright, that hurt.
Reboot the network.
One, two, three, go!
Did Jerma find the fat guy?
He did it!
He set it!
Okay. I gotta find the status of this person?
I guess.
There's seven shots in this thing.
That's not gonna cut it.
Make that a sub sound.
I can plan under the camera feed, but I don't have any direct access to the system.
Shoot.
Wait.
There's no sub sound?
Yeah, I kind of muted it.
After a while.
Scary!
It's a really fun thing.
It's a really cool thing.
Sometimes if you think about it...
Let's say there's a bunch of subs.
Let's say there's a ton of community subs and a bunch of subs.
It's almost like you constantly have...
every like...
two minutes or every one minute...
just a noise that's just like...
Hey, keep a track of my head!
Boink!
And that shit happens for fucking seven straight hours.
You know how easily distracted I am?
It's very, very easy.
Hold on, this is...
Hold on, this is Laura going around right now.
Full health.
Don't do noise, just the banner?
The banner should be on.
It's not because of this. Hold on.
The banner should actually...
The banner should still be there.
But it's because I had to capture this strangely.
It should be there.
It should be there now.
Unknown origin.
This room's on fire.
I don't...
Why are you running at me?
I'm fine.
Something is right next to me.
I'm here!
Hey, I'm here!
Hey, guys.
There was a lot of anger in this room.
Great. Better to be useful.
I don't see any bullet holes.
There's no brass lying around either.
These guys didn't fire a shot.
Then what killed them?
I don't know.
Figure it out.
Alright, buddy, get moving. Fettel's gotta be close.
I'm not even sure where to start.
Continue the search for Paxton Fettel.
Almost complete liquefaction.
Liquefaction?
Maybe a chemical agent?
Hmm.
It could be a grenade.
This is going to take some time.
Did you take photos of the ground?
What are you doing?
You're going to delete a lot of those.
That's why I don't...
Guys, people ask me.
Dude, you don't take any pictures of your phone.
Why don't you take photos?
I take one photo when I know I want to take a photo.
When I know I need to take a photo.
I do not take
15 or 20 pictures of the same thing.
I get it right the first time.
Because then when you...
If you take like 20 pictures of something you think is interesting.
You end up...
You don't even think about it.
You don't go back and look at those pictures.
Maybe for potentially months and months and months.
You'll go to like...
The Smithsonian.
And you'll take a picture of like a space shuttle.
Oh wow, that's so cool.
The space shuttle, that's awesome.
That's really fucking interesting.
And then two years goes by.
And you have like 16 different
stupid angles of
the same space shuttle in the Smithsonian.
And your phone is at like
99% capacity.
And you go, fuck, let's just go back.
And that's like 1600 photos.
I guess I'm going to go back and delete all these.
Take one.
Just one.
Get a good one.
One that you remember.
You don't have to go like...
Hold on.
I want to also do...
Should I? Oh.
It's not my hand.
Just a bug.
Damn it, my fucking stupid ass thing
didn't work.
Come on. Really?
Do these not break? It would have been fucking funny
if I did it the first time.
It's one of those things. Where is it though?
Full health.
Let's go. Watch out.
They're going to spawn.
They're just throwing...
There's a health pack in every single room.
In this level.
Come on.
Holy shit, that's too many people.
Okay, there's a lot of people in there. We gotta change tactics.
I gotta pick them off one by one.
Sniping style.
You walked in front of them.
And said, oh shit.
Like, seriously.
You've got a guy fight. Imagine there's a guy
right here shooting.
This guy just goes like this.
Like the chair is fighting you.
Oh shit.
How does he know he's
in your crosshairs?
Oh shit. I'm going to get like
right inside of your...
aim down sights.
I know he's looking at me now. I shouldn't have walked
in front of my colleague who's also
shooting. I made so many
mistakes in a row.
Wait, I can't hear.
Say it.
Say it. Say the line.
Say the line.
Alright, it's time to stop fucking around.
Watch this one. Activate.
Okay, we're good.
I'm going to use shitties?
I just frogged that computer.
Alright, I got plenty of ammo. Shotgun?
Is that a different shotgun? I don't think so.
No, you can't apparently.
Hell!
What's up?
I'm trying, man.
Here.
Sauer Tower?
Bye.
Do what? Okay, go to the elevators.
I'm really trying to put on
a good display of video gaming skill.
I had to just blink my eyes a few times.
I'm still in it too.
I'm still in that zone. It's going to happen.
Elevators.
Are they?
Oh, it feels bad for them.
It feels bad for them.
Oh, boy. Your head.
It's no fair.
They didn't get...
No!
We had an opportunity!
We had an oh shit opportunity!
It's over!
I just burped.
Oh, boy.
He just got compressed in the elevator.
I'm not supposed to...
I'm trying to stifle laughter because I'm like...
I'm on like medication right now.
From my stomach.
And it's like making me very, very tender.
And sensitive.
And sore and shit.
And I...
I didn't think this game was going to be...
What?
You guys didn't think I could pick up a free one?
What? Ooh.
Oh, shit!
Where is the hostage?
Oh, right. He's down here.
Where is he? I don't remember. He's over here somewhere.
Can somebody turn this on?
I don't know how to get over there.
Just... There.
Through the wall that we explored.
These guys are both dead, by the way.
This is going to be a...
Scenario.
That's all I need to tell you.
Really?
Get this shit off me!
You just...
You should just...
You shouldn't just pet it for a while.
Whatever you're doing.
Here we go. You and me, let's go!
Forward!
Good call. Let's do it. Emergency.
You and me.
Yeah, that means you have to go too.
Yes, I know.
You're not going to come with me.
You're just telling me whatever.
They were taking hostages.
They were asking about Harlan Wade.
What happened to human Garfields?
Our office is in the...
Oh, nice.
Health permanent at 9135.
Up we go.
Shit just comes back in my head.
I can't stop it from coming back.
I feel like I've been hearing this alarm
for two straight hours.
Hey, I'll be seeing your mail back.
Oh, mega lol.
Shit.
Alright, turn it off.
There's been just a constant
morning alarm going.
This whole time I've been here.
It's like, yes, I know. I need to wake up for work.
Sure.
150 pounds. I was like, wait, what?
That's not a lot.
Alright, get it off. Thank you.
Did I need those?
Is there something behind me here?
I'm just trying to scare... I'm just trying to see if, you know,
if it's flinched or something.
Where's my flashlight?
I don't have a flashlight anymore.
Well, that's not good.
No.
Well, I thought you said...
I thought you said this didn't work.
Uh-oh, this is the part that...
I did it. I made it.
For a second I was very confused why I could not go this way.
Biak.
Head biak. Biak.
Oh, I can't go through.
I actually can't do this. I have to do it another way.
Shit. Really?
Can I climb anything?
Yes, I can.
Why is this...
This looks like it should be right, but it doesn't
look like it is.
Oh, right there.
Get out that way.
Anything else here?
I can stand up right there.
But I don't think it does anything.
This is just the beginning of GoldenEye, the facility level.
Which is the best level.
Can I tell you guys something?
When I used to play GoldenEye,
I actually do not really know
what the last
six or seven GoldenEye levels look like.
Because when I was younger,
I would just go to the facility.
That was one of the first games
where you could kind of just do anything.
You could just do whatever you wanted.
There was a mission, but you could just kind of
go anywhere you really wanted to.
So what I would do,
I'm actually...
Something's fucking wrong with me.
I'm realizing this right now.
So I would just go to the facility level
and find interesting ways to shoot the guy
that was in the bathroom stall.
There was a guy in the bathroom
and you...
I wanted to try to just, okay,
get him and then hide and just watch everybody,
watch the alarms go off and stuff.
Throw a grenade down there
and just wait for the alarm to go off
and then hang out and be like,
I'm just in the vent, nobody knows!
If I have...
Let's say I probably realistically have
200 to 300 hours in GoldenEye.
At least 100 of them were
in the vent in the facility.
It has to be.
Seriously.
Where is it?
Is that Garfield?
Oh, okay.
Looks like somebody already did
the thing that I was about to do.
I'm not going to make that same reference.
They all did it already.
The data's uploading.
Well, this confirms the point of Perseus
was to train telepathic commanders to work with cloned soldiers.
Why would that kill you?
Wouldn't you be cushioned by
all the, like, people?
This is not that far of a fall.
And it's just dead.
Okay. You had some other issues,
I think, besides just falling down.
The data's uploading.
Slide, kick him in.
Well, this confirms the point of Perseus
was to train telepathic commanders to work with cloned soldiers.
Although it looks like Jackson and Fettel
were the only commanders in the program.
The weird thing is, they were further invented
after the drone attack.
I can't think that's funny.
I slide in.
Nope. Okay, we're good.
All right, thanks for whatever I just did.
Okay, let's go.
Open fucking world. You wouldn't do it.
You wouldn't, like, break this.
It's a two window there.
Open fucking world.
Got it!
I saw you!
Here we go!
Kind of messy, but, you know, I'll take it.
Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh!
Sorry, that was fucking sloppy, anyways.
Go, one, two, three.
All right, we're good. One, two, three.
This is a silent fucking gameplay.
You're gonna try
to move the thing that's see-through
in the way so I don't shoot you.
Bring it on. I see light, I see
light, I see light.
Okay, come on, come on, come on, come on. This is the one, this is the one.
This is right in front of me.
It's right in front of me. Why did I do that?
Pick it back up.
He was waiting for me.
He wanted to shoot the barrel.
That's great, I love it.
He was like, I'm gonna shoot that barrel, I'm gonna shoot that barrel.
What?
There's no way you-
Why were they over there?
Not this time.
You idiot. Why are we giving up?
I'm not giving up on anybody,
what are we talking about?
Where?
It's when I activate it.
How do they know-
If I stand still and I activate the slow mo,
they don't- how do they know?
They just go, oh no.
Do I start shaking?
I thought he was alive.
Hold on, I'll see-
Wait.
My-
He was trying to kick me.
This stream is not live. What are you talking about?
No, we had the same idea!
What the fuck is that?
What are you talking about?
What do you guys mean?
Look at the funny image, hold on.
What is it?
I'm looking, I'm looking.
It's a very flattering smile.
Oh my god.
Is that real though?
That's real?
Why do I look like that?
I don't really look like that though.
You're getting old.
Yeah, I know.
Is he still alive? Where is he?
Okay, we're good.
Save it. Bring this up.
Smile and optimism.
Three.
I'm gonna go up ten.
Full health, super save.
Oh, okay.
Shit.
Nice Waluigi impression.
Little too much grit though.
You gotta bring it down a little bit more.
That was a bad quick save spot.
It's okay.
Where is it?
Alright, I'm going in.
Fuck it, here we go.
One, two, three, go!
Oh, I bounced him.
Okay, so far so good.
Flash warning!
Screams.
Fuck, wrong way.
Never mind.
I'm gonna try something.
You pick it up with F.
That was like so...
It had to have been fake, right?
Had to have been.
And I agree with you.
It had to have been.
Is it saved? Yeah.
Get off there!
Who's...
He's throwing a grenade?
What the...
Why would you throw?
Whoa!
I think I shot his gun and it fired and hit me in the face.
Un-fucking-believable.
Wrong button.
Playing with fire, playing with fire!
I'm trying to do fucking cool moves.
Alright, I'm done.
Fuck, that hurt.
We good?
I think so.
Good.
Somebody asked how long I've been streaming tonight.
So, for the next week or so, I'm gonna do a thing where I only stream for four amounts of time.
Beep.
Is that guy on the other side of the building?
Did I drop a grenade in the ground?
What an idiot.
It's never not gonna be funny.
Okay, he's gone.
But anyways,
I'm trying to spread out the streams this week.
To do more streams, but less time on the streams.
If that makes any sense.
It should.
Like five hours?
Yes, it really depends.
Because, for anyone that wasn't here an hour or two ago, or the couple when I started talking about it in the first place,
I'm on a couple of new medications for my stomach that...
Hold on, this is important.
Oh, what the fuck?
I mean, I could be...
Whatever, I could just tell you.
It's not like I'm embarrassed by it.
Who cares?
Oh, hold on.
He hasn't told us.
No, I haven't.
I have not. You're right, I haven't.
What is it?
Well, I'll let you deduce that for yourselves.
What would I be on that would...
Oh, hold on.
I don't know, I want...
Ah, the sniper rifle's fun though.
I'm on a certain medication that requires me to do something.
A few times a day.
And it's a strong medication that has a specific purpose.
And it's just causing me some stomach upset, discomfort, and...
I can't really be in the same place for more than four or five hours, really.
No, I'm not doing cocaine.
But I'm on two new medications.
That's one of them.
And the other one is kind of working together with it.
So, there will be more streams, but not as long.
This week.
Cocaine is one of them.
So you can't clip it.
Whatever, who cares?
Where am I supposed to go? Rejoin?
The Holiday Bishop on the roof.
Isn't that where we are?
I'm on the roof, let's go!
The other roof.
There is no other roof, there's only one roof.
I mean, I guess I have to go through here?
Did I just miss a door?
Yeah, it looks like I did.
I just wrapped around.
Nope.
Fuck.
Okay, I killed it.
I killed it, I'm sorry.
He died instantly.
I really am so sorry.
He's just trying to tell the news.
We're good.
I'm going to pick up, I'm taking the sniper rifle.
I feel like why would they keep showing it to me?
You're leaving without me.
You're leaving without me!
Say it!
Oh, he's gone.
That was quick, alright.
What's going on with this guy's body?
I mean, he was being a little strange.
He was being a little strange.
I thought it was him!
I thought it was the guy flying off the...
They had the same kind of
cadence and tone.
Ugh.
Okay, again.
That's a lot of money though.
Hold on.
Goodbye.
Somebody give a hundred dollars.
Ten thousand bits, hold on.
He didn't feel very friendly to me.
I think that they were deliberately targeting me.
What the fuck are you doing?
He's like
flying in a circle.
Ugh.
One of his colleagues.
What the fuck are we doing?
Who is this? This is the shoulder guy.
Ugh.
This game is really, really fun.
This has been
just very fun.
He's over here!
What the fuck?
How did you get me that quickly?
PumpkinSmasher68
gave ten thousand bits.
That's one hundred bucks in bits. That's a shitload of money.
Thank you, Pumpkin.
I hope this makes your day better.
It's a hundred dollars.
That's a shitload of money.
I mean, thank you.
Why are they not shooting me?
He's over here!
What the fuck is ATC doing?
Thanks a lot, PumpkinSmasher.
Seriously.
You made my day really good.
Thank you.
I'm gonna buy a fucking large
pizza with that. Why would this guy die?
Feels pumpkin, man.
Thank you.
It's quiet. This is my opportunity.
This is my chance. Okay, they come
through this door.
That's as far as you can throw that.
That's unbelievably pathetic.
That's ridiculous. I could
throw that shit over that roof.
Where's the other one?
Wasn't there two?
Wasn't there a second person?
I can't!
Okay, I need to pay attention.
It's too fun to just...
Okay.
No!
Just do it!
You don't have to get close!
I'm getting too close!
I don't know why I'm doing that!
Why am I getting so close to everybody?
I was doing fine!
I wanted to get over there
and I don't know what I was thinking.
Okay, I'm done.
I'm ready.
Out of here!
I wanted to watch him go!
Okay, that wasn't on fucking purpose.
Fuck. Everyone's going to think that I did that on
fucking purpose and I did, but I didn't.
I did, but I didn't.
You understand? I did, but I didn't.
I wanted to do a final look to...
I did, but I didn't. And that was not...
It was, but it wasn't. You understand?
I swear I've not tried to do this
this many times.
Who the fuck are you?
He's here!
How close are you?
He's trying to flank!
What? No, I'm not! I'm trying to...
Where is this person? Oh, right there.
Are they dead? Oh, fuck.
I thought that was a face.
You're not alive!
Has been neutralized. Flashlight!
Good work! He's over here!
These guys...
It's so dangerous. This shit is
so powerful. I have no more healing.
Good. That's what I want.
He's over here!
Close the fucking door!
Alright, give me that. Give me that shit.
Go down. Why can I not go over here?
How the hell do I get out?
Uh oh. I'm good. Okay, let's go.
There's no Half-Life crouch jump?
I know what the fuck is going on there.
One health pack.
This is around the corner here. Alright.
I can go the other way.
Good health. Nice.
They do put it everywhere though, so that's good.
We're up here.
Snipers. That's why, because they had sniper rifles.
Damn. Okay.
I got ammo for it.
Might as well use it.
Watch out! Grenade!
How would you see that?
I don't think they got out. How would you know
that was a grenade? You just, you wouldn't.
Oh, music. What does that mean?
Alright, refilling all the health. That's good.
Flashlight. What?
Get down!
The fuck just happened?
It went like anti-gravity.
What? What happened?
What the fuck?
Okay, I'm fine.
Oh, what the, what the fuck?
What the fuck?
Find a way back up to the main building. Oh, you bastard.
Really?
You gonna do this shit to me right now?
Uh, okay.
I guess I'm going over, oh.
Ooh. Alright.
I'll take it. Thank you.
Now we gotta go, uh,
up there,
somehow.
Or under. Wait, there we go.
Alright, what's, what's going on here?
There's like a giant animal in there.
Shotgun time. Mine's screwing around here.
What is that?
I thought that was a,
it's alright.
Uh, I need to get that health back.
Can I reach the wall?
Let me, let me exploit this.
I can't get up there.
What is going on right now? Why is the,
why is the world shaking?
I knew it was gonna fall.
I knew it.
And there ain't any other way to go, so I have to go around.
Can't make that jump.
So that leaves,
uh, over here.
I guess we're gonna try over here.
No, this is where I came in, so.
If I go this way,
that way is, okay,
over here. No, I, can I get up
that? Huh.
Can I do anything with that?
Just go forward?
I, I guess,
but I can't really go over here.
Wait, can I go?
Alright, I guess I'm going this way.
Oh shit, okay.
No, I can't go that way either.
Let's try over here.
He hates gaming. That may have just ended the stream.
I'm not gonna,
no, he didn't poop.
I'm starting to get, um,
a little queasy.
There's nothing to do with the game. It has to do with what's going on in my life right now.
So, um,
yeah,
on the next stopping point, I think I'll call it.
They left her in darkness.
That'll be just exactly where I wanted to stop anyways.
In about, like, five hours.
Yeah, I just got a good
checkpoint.
I don't wanna push it. Yeah, that's good.
That'll be good. We'll keep going tomorrow.
So again, for the next, like, four or five days,
we're gonna do
more days, but shorter streams.
Uh, plus I actually
have to go take
some of this medicine now.
And it's not gonna be fun.
But, I will see you guys tomorrow.
We'll call it there.
Oh, okay.
This is a lot of fun.
This was a blast. This game's great.
Anybody know how much is left?
What time tomorrow?
It's regular time, around one or two.
It's been about four and a half hours.
Four hours and forty minutes. Keep a couple hours.
Okay. This is about
three hours, four hours.
Forty-six hours. Alright, then that might be
a perfect time tomorrow. There's a lot
to play. We're just gonna spread it out.
So, thanks for coming. I'll see you guys
tomorrow. Let's get to the bits
and everything. We're gonna call it right there.
I'll just manually save it just in case.
And we'll see you tomorrow.
Oh, look. Top subgifter.
I wonder if they fixed this, cause Streamlabs
had an update. Let's check and see if they did.
Uh, let's
save game.
Oh, let me see.
Top subgifter, come on.
Session.
They just had an update.
Tell me they fixed it.
No!
Come on. It's not
me. This is the session.
I didn't do anything this session.
Session.
Let's put on a follower train.
But, see you tomorrow.
Oh, fuck.
I'm getting a little drained.
But I knew that was gonna happen. That's alright.
Anyhow,
let's go back.
About four hours ago.
It's rigged. Well, it's rigged to
reset.
But thank you Sturdy Bread for the 250. Hey, here's
some bits. I don't know what to put in these messages.
Thanks for being the best streamer around.
Thanks a lot. Glad you had fun.
Also, thank you Yes Is Online
for the 250.
They say, I wish I could fully watch the stream
today, but my glasses got absolutely destroyed
at the JPEG
Mafia show last night and I have to spend my
entire day blind.
Inside this Lenscrafters.
They say, good luck.
Thank you.
Thank you Jules for the 250.
Hey, Jerma, have you experienced anything paranormal
in your life? If not, will you be
visiting any haunted places in Vegas
this month? Does paranormal interest you?
Um, not at all.
We had a conversation
like a week or two ago about ghosts
and stuff and I don't really believe in the
term ghost in a
traditional sense.
Talked about how your great great great great great great
grandfather is like watching down and
walking around your house and eating
food out of your fridge.
It was a whole ordeal.
But I don't really believe in ghosts.
In the like,
I'm here
because
I have unfinished business
with you.
You screwed me out of the deal
and they literally won't leave your house like
Beetlejuice style. No, I don't I don't
think that's real.
Say Beetlejuice three times.
I will never do that.
That's what a ghost would say.
Look, but I can't prove that they don't exist
either, right?
I can't tell you guys.
We see a certain
spectrum of colors.
Who knows? There might be a whole other spectrum of light
that we can't see.
That's not like infrared. It might be something completely
different. There might be a whole world underneath
our world. I don't know. You can't see it.
I have no idea. Do I believe in aliens?
Um,
yeah, probably.
If there's 500 billion galaxies,
one of them is going to have a Starbucks
somewhere. There'll be something.
I mean, I don't think we'll ever, ever,
ever, ever talk to them.
We'll never see them, ever.
I don't know. Do you understand how
fucked up this whole world is? Like, the giraffe exists.
Nobody can
tell you anything. Nobody can explain
shit. You have
a series of tubes in your body
that carry a
substance around your whole body
to make sure you stay alive.
Huh? Electricity
is a thing. Like lightning strikes
from the sky. We're just
making our best guesses, guys.
It don't matter who you are.
Can you imagine trying to fucking
explain what the hell that is?
Boom! Lightning!
I have no
fucking idea what that was.
I guess we'll try to think what it
could... We'll figure it out, I guess.
Science can prove how it works, but science
can't prove, like,
why it doesn't... Why?
Why is it lightning?
Why do we have veins? Like, why did this happen?
What the fuck was this for?
It's called electric... I know what
electricity is, I'm just saying.
What? What? What?
You put gasoline in your car and you can drive
down the road. That... Why?
How did we get that far? You have a
flat-screen TV in your house. You're telling me
two to three hundred years ago, people would
fucking ride around in horse and
buggies? And you have an iPhone
in your pocket now? Maybe I do believe
in aliens. They fucking landed and they gave us
all the goddamn technology.
Imagine not knowing what thermodynamics
works. How... Thermodynamics
was a word that was made up to explain
what thermodynamics is.
It's all language.
But an eye-opening
string. Time isn't
real. Yeah, I guess
time is a concept that
we created to try to explain
why the sun goes up and down.
Two hundred IQ?
I tell you, sometimes it's
too easy. Can I tell you,
one of my favorite things
is verbal shitposting at the beginning
and the end of my streams.
It's so fun.
Now I get it. I know why you guys do it.
That's one of my favorite things in the world.
He understands.
You're always doing that. I don't
know. It's fun. It's fun just to
talk about random things.
Dad gets me. Mouth
diarrhea. Yeah.
Who's your favorite?
What's your favorite pantheon?
Norse. Norse. Greek.
Greek. Roman.
Are we going to get a smite stream? I'm
dumb and don't know what you mean.
Gods. Gods. Yeah, you do. They're all cool.
That's how people
explain the world.
Can you imagine if in
a thousand years they're looking back at us
talking about string theory and they're
laughing because it's as ridiculous
as Zeus?
They didn't know.
It's funny now.
All right. Hold on.
I don't want to turn a end of
the stream shitpost into a let's debate
science for real.
Anyways, I don't know how it got there. Somebody
said something. But anyways,
let's go. Let's do it for real.
Lizard Amiibo, thanks
for the 500 bits. Hey, Jerma, I just started my
first year of college and so far it's been pretty
rough. The streams and videos are
one of the things that have been able to make me smile.
The time, effort,
and why is this cut off?
Streamlabs, I'm telling
you. You got, you made
this new update.
But
you're cutting off everything now.
Why are you cutting everything off?
This is this new
mini feed.
Not good. I'm not happy with this.
Huh. Mini feed
cuts off everything. How do I just make it the regular
feed? What have we done?
Hold on. I
think, I think, I think
I think I'm going to dump Streamlabs
OBS. Yeah,
not, not doing
it for me. Not doing
it for me at all actually.
Go here. Good.
It's a bunch of great, interesting
ideas that all of them just kind of don't
work at the same time together.
I'm going to, I'm just going to go back to the regular
Streamlabs. Not Streamlabs, regular OBS.
Apparently it's some really
cool features that they added.
OBS vanilla flavor, yes.
Logitech bought Streamlabs.
That's kind
of interesting I guess, yeah.
That's kind of interesting. That explains
a lot, does it? They're just trying
to load too much in the same place and then
I don't know. I could
talk about how I don't like it but it's
fine. Just don't use it.
It's that simple. Anyways, alright,
let's go back to what we were doing.
We had, we had five community
subs from Snooze and Copter at the very beginning
of the stream. We also had
Cyclops Parker
gave ten community subs
three, four hours ago here. Thanks to the ten community
subs. Also Zake,
this is where we left off here. Zake, thanks for the 250. Hey
man, thanks for providing a nice distraction from student
stress. How are you? Are you enjoying
streaming? Cheers from
5,390 miles away.
I love streaming. Streaming's like one of my
favorite things ever. I would say
streaming is, it's
one of my main focuses of my
whole life. So greetings from
5,400 miles away.
That's really far, I wonder
where is that? I missed two hundred dollars
right now? Oh
earlier, okay, yeah. It was from
Vilemi. Two hundred dollars
twenty thousand bits
from about
five minutes ago or so
we were talking about like
the blood vessels in your body and how that means
that like aliens landed. I don't know.
A bunch of people left and probably thought I was like actually
a fucking weirdo. Oh, whatever.
That's okay. Thanks
for the 200 bucks though. That's a lot of money, Vilemi.
It's a shitload of money.
At the same time, just to dump
two hundred twenty thousand bits.
True.
But Vilemi, fuck yeah, that's a lot of
money. And they say germ
A-W-O-O
Germ-O-Woo
I'm re- I'm reading it!
Tell us when the next carnival's gonna be. There's not gonna be
a carnival with it but you stream on the 31st
or at least on the 30th or 31st.
Doing a Halloween stream
that's gonna have a lot of intricate details to it so
go check out the Discord. There's a couple
channels there. Go read the pin messages
and you'll know what's gonna happen.
But thanks a lot, Vilemi. That brings us back
down. Let's go back down to
right down here. But Lizard Amiibo,
thank you. Sorry to hear that your first
year of college is rough.
It can happen like that though.
The first year or so
is very nerve wracking for everybody.
So you kind of just need to
keep going, try to
make some friends, and try to make
the best of your college experience.
It can be a lot of fun. Just make sure you
are taking care of your work, taking care of your
life. It can be a good time.
But the first year always is
a big kind of
shock for a lot of people.
But you'll shake off the cobwebs.
I wish you the best of luck. Thank you
Snooze for the 250. Hey Germ, I just want to say that your streams
have always cheered me up and made me laugh.
You are genuinely kind and humble.
It inspires me to be the same way.
Anyways, enough being cheesy, I made some
fan art for you recently. I can't wait for the next
Community Content Night so you can
see it. Goodnight. Yeah?
Toss it in there.
The next time we do it, I'm sure it'll be there.
I appreciate the incredibly kind messages
though. Thank you Snooze.
And speaking of Community Content Night, I'm going to be
adding much more
material to pull from for you guys
that make videos. I will say it again,
I've said it the last few streams in a row.
I'm going back in front of the green
screen for a whole stream.
We're going to do a whole other thing where
we pull a ton of suggestions
and we do green screen DLC
for free.
That's the title of the stream. I've got it
already like a month and a half in advance.
I already know that's what the title is.
Hey Lude Sheep, thanks for the 300 bits. Hey
Germ, we just want to say hello from all of us at the Sprio
Discord channel. Hello from
there. Nice to see you.
They say, oh and
Postposs says
hey as well. Postposs
one. Hi guys.
Thank you Lude Sheep. And hello
everybody at that Discord. Whoever you are.
Wherever you are. Thank you.
Sir Canine, thanks for the 250. Louis Anderson
Human Garfield is probably one of the most terrifying
creations in human history.
What happened to that guy? That guy just kind of disappeared.
I wanted more of the
Grenade Eater. But we're not going to
get it. Hey Shiggy, thanks for the
250.
Hey Germ, I wonder if you consider yourself a
what is this? What is this word?
What do you have to say about the fans
proclaiming you are a model
H? What is this?
Yeah, what is that? What does it
mean? It means
stupid but handsome.
Well those people are the ones that stuck around for
the post stream.
There are tubes in your body. Rant.
And then they left.
And that's the only piece of the content they watched. They missed the part
when I talked about the
Well, whatever.
Himbo.
Okay, I don't
What do I have to say about that?
I got a degree. I went to engineering
school. I was a waiter
for three years.
What are the more made up
things around the wiki page?
I wonder. Why don't you look at chat during
the stream? I look at chat
so much during the stream that it makes me step in bear traps.
500 times.
I'm just speaking in reality.
That's a nice excuse.
It is a pretty good excuse.
I mean it's surely, absolutely
an excuse but it's a pretty good one.
Hey Warm Like Biscuits, thanks for the
500 bits.
I've been watching you since your early YouTube days.
Thank you for all the laughs. You've pulled me out of some
dark places. Here's a little bit of gratitude
so thank you. Thank you
Warm Like Biscuits.
I'm glad you can laugh.
I love laughing. It's one of my favorite things in the world.
Hey guess what?
Laughing at shit has
pulled me out of some places that I never
really wanted to be in over the
course of my life. I think it's so
important. I think
laughing and having a good time.
Jokes. I think comedy
is one of the most important things.
If you can pull comedy out of any
situation or situations
and everybody can laugh
I think it's incredibly important.
It's the best medicine. Well it's a good
supplement. It's a good supplement to medicine.
I'd probably say that's more accurate.
We're talking comedy here.
Yeah I think it's
a very important thing so
if anybody gets that out of this stream then that makes me
really happy because that's obviously
I find that to be something that I care so much about
in my life. So I'm
glad it translates to a lot of you.
That makes me really happy.
Thanks a lot. Hey Sad Vega
thanks for the 250.
Question about the slime night.
Okay. That's going to be the 31st
right? Also how are you handling
the slime? Because I'd expect it's going to create a mess
on your gear and your headphones.
Are you saran wrapping your home room?
Doing it in a studio I cannot imagine how
awful getting the slime out of the equipment be.
You'll see.
It's not going to
be in my room.
So don't worry. That's not
going to happen. There is
a whole
the last week and a half
or so since I first started talking about it
has been complete and total planning.
Every day that I'm not on stream essentially.
And it's almost
ready to go completely. So
don't worry. That is completely
and totally taken care of.
He's going to do it on his bed. No that's
not where this is going to be. But
yes it's supposed to be
on Halloween. Halloween
day. I know a lot of people
have things to do on Halloween night usually.
So it's going to be Halloween
afternoon into
Halloween evening.
Should be fun. And it's not just
going to be a slime stream. Let me make that
really clear. There's at least two or three
segments on that stream that are
not sliming. There are other things
that could be Halloween related.
Slime is just the main event.
You know how we do it. Mind my halo
thanks for the ten dollars thousand
bits. There's no message but
just thank you for the ten dollar
drop. Thank you shitty viewbot
for the five hundred bits. Last time you mentioned
Scream Fortress you said ask me again.
Well I'm asking you again. Is there any chance for
a TF2 Scream Fortress stream?
No. I will
probably not stream
Team Fortress 2 ever again.
I don't think so.
Like I said before there would need to
be a
significant major
change to the game for me to get
interested in it again. Because let's be
completely and totally honest here.
Scream Fortress is just
it's the Halloween update.
It's not like a major
change to the game. It's a
few cool maps and some cosmetics
and stuff. It's not
it's not anything that's like a big big
big major change.
And even when sometimes they've done
updates that have brought a couple
of new items and a couple of new scenarios
it's what it kind of
wasn't enough. You have to
remember I put
almost
six seven straight years
into that game.
And I sort of closed the book on it.
There are other things that I'd like to do
that are not that
he hates it.
No but it's kind of it's one of those scenarios
where I like to look back
at how awesome that community was
and how amazing those
five plus straight years of my life were.
I put a lot
I was playing TF2 before
Steam even counted the hours.
And that's when I spent the most time in it.
But I don't think there would be a scenario
where it'd be like hey here's like a
TF2 livestream.
I don't really have any
that's not like doing it for me.
Like it could have maybe
used to years ago.
You want to see TF2 get the love it deserves
from Valve?
Yeah but that would mean Valve would
Valve has not been very game
centric over the last
five years.
They've been more hardware and business centric.
And it's done
really well for them.
Everybody wants Valve to make games
but Valve has done
has changed
they're just incredibly lucrative
when they focused on Steam
and the VR stuff.
If they ever actually
and they're supposed to be
they're supposed to be developing something for VR.
That's what everyone says right?
Half Life 3 VR. I know that's
the thing that everyone says now.
And even if it's not
they're doing something.
But it would take something significant.
Valve would have to really decide
that something like Team Fortress was
alright we're going to go back
to TF2 and we're going to develop
like six new official maps.
We're going to make a new game mode
and it's going to be 12 new items
and we're going to rebalance a bunch more stuff.
But it's almost it's hard for that to
even happen because at what point
is it they've added so
much stuff to TF2.
They've done they've added
so many items
and weapons and game modes
and maps and at what
point do they not have very much
else to do.
They've added whole class
whole new class worth
of items dozens of times.
So it's almost like I know everyone's oh man
I wish Valve would make like 25
new weapons and items
but they've already come up with so many
and in the scheme the grand scheme of what
that game is it's not
that you're limited it's that
they've done probably so much
stuff that they can't really probably come up
with what the hell are we going to give
like the fucking spy.
He's got like 12 15 different
knives and guns and
give him a fire knife a
knife gun yeah
and that's the thing though that when they come up with this many
things they come up with so many items and weapons
he's got like a bunch of revolvers and people only use
one or two of them.
I think the era of TF2
and here's the thing about
TF2 TF2
everybody wants to emulate how
fun that game is and how much
awesome it was and how everybody
cared about it. You see
so many games pop up now that are just
desperately trying to tap that
fun interesting
funny community
game and it's almost impossible.
There was a string
of at least a few years in a row
back in like 2013
14 15 into like 2016
where everyone wanted to be
everyone wanted to make that next awesome
Team Fortress style game that
everyone cared about but
yeah somebody just said it's a timeless
masterpiece it is.
So that's why it's hard to do another
one and I think that's why they're afraid to do
another one maybe not afraid it's the wrong word
but when you make something that's so
good that from its
when it was from release
to all through all these updates
and it is a actual
like first person shooter
solidified in history as
one of the best that has been ever made
so you have to make another one
and you have to make it as good or better than
that one. It's a
lot of pressure and a lot
of work to try to stand on
your own shoulders but we'll
see what they do and people will if
Team Fortress 3 gets announced
can you imagine how
everybody will everyone will be so
excited for it oh this is gonna be
the best game ever made it's a new
engine they're doing source 3 it's gonna
launch source 3 they've got like
two new classes and look
at all these new maps and there's like a whole
MVM new single player it's gonna be so good
if that game is not the
best game you've ever played
if it has to hit that expectation
otherwise it's just ah
fuck it wasn't really
that good I wish they didn't
do it in the first place then you think look at Diablo 3
do you know how long
I've wanted Diablo 3 for
Diablo 3
Diablo 2 is one of my favorite games ever made it's one of
my favorite fucking games I love it
so much and every
day I prayed for a Diablo
3 I thought about all the new
items they would be making a new
engine oh it would be so great
there would be endless content
there would be so much awesome shit you could do
just give us Diablo 3 please
and it's almost like
the monkey's paw right
like you got it
and it really wasn't
what I wanted
Diablo 3 was fun
but it was not the thing that I
wanted at what cost
they made it they tried
to do the whole money auction house thing and
you could look over that for a little while but
items didn't drop the problem with
D3 the very beginning of the game the game was like
a month old
the unique the legendaries the unique items
that's what we call them
they didn't drop and they were just random
stats and shit it was just
dog shit it was dog shit
Reaper's Souls came out and
they actually did a lot of good
they fixed a lot of stuff
what's the
the lead dev of
Reaper's Souls
he tried to do his best
and I don't think that guy works for the company anymore
he like fixed Reaper
he fixed Diablo 3
and I think they got rid
of him did that happen am I remembering
this correctly yeah he left
yes why
why wouldn't you make sure that
that person was
responsible for your next Diablo
iteration that's
it's like almost
he
yeah
his name is Josh Martens
this dude and
obviously some of the other talented people that worked with him
and underneath him right
but this dude at all these
they took that game and they made it
actually like fun
alright well you want to do
Diablo 4 it'd be great
if you did it because from the ground up
you probably would have some better ideas
like what the fuck happened
like what
if they okay if Blizzard announces
forget about like all the other
controversy that Blizzard is seeing
right now if Diablo 4 is announced
I don't what the fuck is this game even going to be
who even made this game
Josh Mascara not
Martens okay yeah I want to make sure I get that right
Josh Mascara and Kevin Martens
were the directors of Reaper's Souls
and after everybody said
all the critics all the fans
were like wow
I mean Diablo 3 still isn't that
good it's still like not what I wanted
but this is actually
really good they like took what they
took all the broken systems
and they made them all work and then they made the game
fun you don't have
those people stick around
it's like it's just counter
productive I bought D3
on release and regret it deeply all my friends accounts
got stolen within the first oh jeez
that's not good
he like Diablo
me click on enemy push number
keys once every hour
right but you're
that you're referencing Diablo
3 Diablo 2
was a dangerous fucking game if you
okay look there's let me be
if you played Diablo 2
and you did like the exploity kind of
ways to just mow through everything
once you play on like when you get to Nightmare in Hell
in Diablo 2 it was a dangerous game
you were at
risk of dying in every
room in Diablo 2
especially when you got past like level 20
Diablo 3
was just a nut it
was an idle game
at it's very very core once you got
once it got to complete late game it was an idle game
and you just waited
until this thing
dropped letters on the ground
that you walked over and did you get
just open it
and what is it okay no it's not better than what I have
we're gonna just watch the numbers again
the ever changing difficulty slider in
Diablo 3 was a bad idea bad design
maybe but
I think there's probably ways to do
that there's ways to do like
a never ending difficulty slider
without it being
well I mean never ending is the wrong
word there really should only be like
five difficulties
the regular game cause there was like even
you would put that slider
on hard
or very hard and it was just
the normal game the issue
with Diablo 3 in the end
was the normal game
was absolutely
just brainless
you couldn't even
lose you could just walk into
rooms and things it wasn't even hard
the game was not even it was so easy
so on it's lowest kind of end
like the first three difficulties were just
why would you even do them there's too easy
and the last three difficulties
were not even possible
it's just such a
scale was just off have
a normal base game that's challenging and fun
have a difficulty after that
that's harder have a difficulty
after that that's really fucking hard
like a normal nightmare
hell you want to have inferno
have it be sure have
inferno have inferno be stupid
and like impossible
but that's like the plus that's like the
game plus mode
you don't have to do that there's like
how many there were like twelve difficulties
in Diablo 3
there's a lot fifteen
that's even more than I thought
there are nineteen now
why even have difficulties then
why not just have prestige
what's the point of having
difficulties why don't you just prestige
give up all your shit and then start at level one
and the game's harder
what's the point of having a slider
and if you don't want to prestige you just don't
just uncheck a box
that's what seasons is
seasons doesn't change the difficulty
seasons is just the
that's not a difficulty thing right
should you play Diablo 2 it really depends
because Diablo 2
is old and a lot of
people can't get over that
old school video game feel
there's a lot of things in Diablo 2
that are stupid
that really suck that you have to get over
it's just an old old
game that never got
the remaster treatment
never got the remake treatment
it's just an old ass game that's really really good
stupid
equals bad
greater than bad yeah
you gonna play the weird minecraft Diablo clone
I don't know
it depends on if it's any good
but we went from scream fortress
to talk about I don't know Diablo somehow
yeah the whole Diablo thing
really it's
that's close to my chest cause
it's literally one of my favorite
things ever and that's why
stuff like Diablo immortal Diablo
4 I
can't I'm not gonna get excited for those games
and there's no I don't
have a reason to because
everybody that ever was really involved in
any of the original stuff just didn't there anymore
it's like they have all these
assets randomly that have been canned over
the years who knows
like the Diablo 4 might have
Titan assets
remember that that a lot of that turned
into Overwatch who knows
there's not a good demand for those games anymore
and that's another thing too yeah
people just top
down ARPGs
at least in the realm of like Diablo and like
loot collecting and stuff people would rather
loot collection is still very much alive
but people would rather
get their loot from
first person shooters or out of a box
they took
that Diablo formula
was transformed into a box you
pay two dollars for
Path of Exile you hit enemies with a rubber sword
yeah Path of Exile is awesome
I just don't like the camera
it's something that's it's kind of
hard for me to get over
uncensored what's the name what
that's an interesting problem what's the problem with
the camera it's I
think it's it's too close
I wish I could pull the camera
out like 20%
more in Path of Exile
and I wish it
was angled a
little bit more
like a few like five degrees
ten degrees more than it is right now
but that's the only reason why
and that's a very
very very just personal thing
as to why I can't play it
there are actually some
I think you can get mods for it or you can
get like window changers for
it but it's really not the same
if you run Path of Exile
in a window and you resize the window in really
strange ways you can kind of get more
viewing angle and but
it's not
ideal and I know that
problem that's not a problem
that anybody really
that's not an
issue to patch the game over
when a
handful of people just don't really like the camera
right like every
there are millions of people that have
played Path of Exile and loved every second of it
that don't care that doesn't bother them at all
so I really I do not
I never expected nor do I ever
expect them to be like oh like one guy
said he didn't like the camera so let's
spend a bunch of development
time making it so you can pull the camera out
by 20%
no I completely understand
but yeah
we can move on. Goad conversation
all interesting stuff
ACDC freak thanks
for the thousand bits I would rather spend
money on you than my Tinder profile
you funny funny man
oh shit
oh shit I forgot
about how funny that is
oh shit
this game is I love this game
how have I not played fear before
ever
monolith like I monolith
is so good I love monolith
they make such great games
how have I never played their original
FPS franchise
I'm gonna be in bed
Kim is gonna think I'm insane
I'm gonna be in bed lying there
just on my iPad just hanging out
after eating some dinner
and I was gonna think of oh shit
and it's gonna make me
laugh and there's gonna be no context
but thank you ACDC freak
thank you for giving
me ten dollars instead
of Tinder I guess
thank you also thank you
to Freudian Weapon for the 250 happy Wednesday
hope you feel better
try not to overdo it on another note
do you plan on dressing up for Halloween this year
I plan on
being in some sort of costume on stream
we'll see what it is I have not figured
it out yet but yeah I
am I'm not overdoing it I mean
this stream is only about I mean we've spent
a little bit more extra time here because we're getting into
some conversations but
I stopped at about five hours
four hours and like 45 minutes that's probably what it'll
be like tomorrow somewhere around like four
four four and a half five
I'm trying just to
be easy but
over the in the long term
it won't be less time on stream
it'll just be spread over more days
so that'll be should be fine
but thank you I appreciate the concern
Siroc thanks for the 250
they say B E E T
L E J U I
I S E C E
I can't say that a third time
or I will get sucked into into hell
thank you thank you the thrill
for the 500 bits I remember playing
this game years ago and my god the sounds
and ragdoll physics is still insanely funny
the game in series really does hold
up well today which is pretty cool
hope your poops aren't spooky
yeah it does
I'm surprised this game is this
old when games are this old
they are not that good
they might be funny but they're not
fun to play this game is actually fun
to play too
the rest of the franchise is really not that good
yeah maybe I'll do
them eventually I know that I just wanted to do this
one because I just heard
so many good things about it and I never put any
time into it but here we are
no uh Freudian thanks for the 250
my last bit message got messed up tried
to put a germa heart emote so have
another thank you
uh Jason thanks for the 250 what was your
most embarrassing moment on stream
uh pick one of these two either
slapping myself in the face or
crying to a
farting and screaming
compilation both pretty
embarrassing I'm not sure
which one is worse one of those
uh thank you
Zeon WASD for the 500
bits bro where the
literal teeny parts of the universe
who invented the idea of things
meaning things so
things just mean whatever they
we say they do where are the
arbiters also I'm sorry for
saying fuck you that one time
so Resident Evil 2 Claire
campaign fuck you
that's what I'm saying yeah that's
what I said I said like we have made
up that idea of giving things
meaning by things that we say
but hey I appreciate the fuck you
thank you Gondrelaine thanks for the
250 since it's been a while since you did some DOS
the archive just added over 2500
hundred new DOS games
I did see that
that seems insane I know you stop
the streams because you were digging too deep into the vault
and the games were getting worse
but the new games should add new stuff
or a new stream also a good
idea would be a horror DOS game stream if you want
I love you Jerma
more DOS games playable yeah we'll go back to it
we'll check them out see if there's any
better ones any new good ones that's
the thing when you have a list of
like 5000 games that are on a
page you just go wow
how are we going to do this
how are we going to do this reliably
but those streams some of the most fun
I've had on stream this last year has been
on some of those DOS streams
so I definitely would like to do it again
but I want it to be the whole stream
because it seems like it's kind of in one of those scenarios
where it's oh we're going to do
this and that's going to be like four or five hours
and I guess we'll do DOS too but you would really
you have to focus a full
day on that
you need to give some of those games the
hour or two plus that they deserve
at least some of them
so yeah I agree we should go back and do it
thank you Jason
for the 250 please watch this I'm crying
my ass off
man what is this this is a
Twitter account
this is a Jerma out
of context yeah
I've been linked to this stuff before
these
this this page gets like a
lot of views
10,000
views on that video on this
Twitter 5,000
71,000
holy shit
50,000 views on this video
what the fuck
is this
what the fuck is this video
something in the water
I'm telling you
it's just this
they linked this
I love him or hate him Jerma spitting straight
facts
sounds like
sounds like a bored
toddler
show it there's nothing to show it's just a bunch of
noises
I'm gonna keep going
I gotta get some food in me and then
take my fucking
gross drink that I have to drink
but thank you Jason that's the
Jerma OOC
Twitter thank you
anything else show official for the
15 dollars
thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you
loved watching the carnival stream
Jerma also wondered what kind of retro
or obscure computers you are a fan of
keep up the cool projects and streams
as always thank you
what kind of retro or obscure
computers are you a fan of I am actually
a big fan of those
old
chunky IMAX
do you remember those things that were in the computer lab
they were different colors
they were red, blue,
green, orange
they were junk but I loved them
they were cool
it was just this
little shell that had everything
right there it was a little computer
this is insane
I remember what that room smells like
I remember what that computer smells like
that room had that IMAX
smell there was an IMAX room
smell it was
it was the computer smell the computer
lab smell so every time I
think of an IMAX
I smell the computer lab
I can never explain what
that smell is I just know that
it exists it was great
but let's get the credits on
throw them up there
get this
to do the thing I would like it to do
why did you get rid of this
streamlabs OBS
why did you do this
how do I I gotta go
into my settings and get this shit out of here
what the fuck is all this
I just wanna go
I just wanna
how do I run
we're switching back
banana cream pie yep
that's good stuff
am I just starting or am I just ending
I'm about to end the stream
we'll be back tomorrow though at the same time
alright let's roll I'm hitting on
thank you everybody
thanks for supporting the stream continuing to sub
new subs old subs
you surprise me every day
thank you we have a few more to get through
in the bits category here
modus pons
says there better be bugleberry on Halloween
don't give in to the haters
thanks for the 250
what makes you think I'm gonna give in to
people that hate that character
don't you think that's more of a reason why they would show up
I'm just saying if they were too
I'm not gonna say anything
I don't I mean I don't know what his schedule
is like it's he's all over the place
thank you zion
WASD for the 500 bits
I'm actually sorry for saying fuck you though
I don't know how to express love dog
real question
are you ever gonna do stand up comedy on stage
and in person you're more funny while improvising
like most netflix comedians are with their super
well prepared specials
and your premeditated skits are even funnier
also any plans on voice acting
and anything you got some cords
uh no
I don't think I'll ever do it
unless it was for a specific
stream
where the point was I was gonna try
to do open mic night
I thought about that before
where I try to come up with
some material
to do a seven minute set
in open mic night
but that's the thing every time
I've come into this oh
should I do that would be fun I think that might be funny
I always hit the same wall
that's a ten minute
stream
that's it
there's nothing else there
I mean maybe if I want to do it one day and just turn it on
and just who cares I'm gonna do like a
fourteen minute stream
we'll see but I don't have really any plans
for it there are plans for other streams
coming up over the next few months
but that is not currently one of them
but thank you so much
I like what's going on here
you know this is where my focus is
completely so I don't think I could
I couldn't spread myself out if I really
wanted to like pursue a stand up comedy career
that's time that's a lot
of dedication it's a lot of work
I wouldn't want to split myself
up it takes a lot
to do that
thanks for the 250 thanks for playing fear Jerma
my big brother bought this game
and I was too young in a wuss to play
single player so I played only multiplayer
so I wouldn't get scared
it's great I love it
that's so cute
thank you though thanks for the 250
lizard and meatball thanks for the 500
bits it's me again
I have some more bits just wanted to make sure you know how much we
appreciate the creativity and effort you put into
your streams cause you really don't see
that every day anyway I hope things
get better with your illness soon have a great night
yeah we're just trying to figure out what's going on
the doctor right now is just kind of throwing
darts and we're gonna see if any
of them land so
good to go but yeah
I can reiterate one more time
as I say a lot
but I have to stay interested
or else I can't do this
if I am not interested if I'm
not having a good time and I'm not
focused and care about each stream
I can't stream
so he hates streaming
end of career
nah that's just the way
it is I can't change
that so as long
as I stay interested then I'm still
interested and I want to keep doing stuff and
keep doing keep streaming keep having fun that's
gonna keep happening but thank you
what's your retirement plan
we're gonna do a retirement party on
this stream
I don't know whenever that happens
could be could be 10
years in the future could be
7 years 6 years I don't know
I'm gonna be 40
in 6 to 7 years
guys I don't know what's gonna happen
tomorrow it's not gonna be tomorrow
no this is not like
an immediate like within the next
few years thing guys maybe
like when I'm 40 I'll just I'll
transition to like eating
sunflower seeds and like
talking about baseball for my streams I don't
know I have no idea what's gonna happen
I don't know what's gonna happen in a year
I have no idea just be a dad
streamer yeah and we'll just talk about
school and stuff
I have no plan
and having no
real plan is what
keeps me able to
care about what's happening now
I don't have a 10 year plan for this stream
I don't have a 5 year plan
for this stream I have a what do I
wanna do this month
what do I wanna do
this year what kind of streams
do I wanna make do I wanna do
a couple of large scale things
maybe not yeah maybe yeah I do
I don't have a plan
but it's a controlled
it's not like I just whatever
who gives a shit I don't fucking
know or do I have no
idea my everyday life is
chaos no
but I need to stay open to everything
that's kind of how I've always lived
am I you gonna stay in Vegas
yes that's at least the immediate
plan is to
stay here stay in Las Vegas
and I don't know
as I get older
there are a few things that may
or may not happen in my life
that I have to start to think about
you know there's a lot of things to think about
as you get a little older
kids
no but you understand
I we have a lot of
fun on this stream
we talk a lot of random shit
we fuck around a lot we have a lot of fun
but you know
that I do have this
I am getting a little older
and you need to start you gotta think about what you
do when you get a little older
I don't know I have no
idea no more poo poo jokes
that's right well actually
just looking at my total unfollowed
for the hour big spike
here 70
80 people
it was 2 over the whole 2 days here
I didn't know that was that important to you guys
no you know what I mean though
I'll be 35 next year
kinda gonna start to think about what I
you know where who
what do I wanna be who do I want what do I wanna do
with my actual like adult
no longer 18 to 34
on the drop down box
what do you know what do I want for my future
you have to think about it
I feel like once you hit 40 it's a whole new
life I just wanna be prepared for it
time's flying I know
that's why I wanna be ready
there are decisions to make there are choices
to make I wanna make sure that I make the right
ones as I continue
to age you grow your
second stomach at 40
but Admiral Breadball thanks for the 5
community subs and then finally
Dr. Clay at the end
for 250 just a random question do you plan
on checking out Meat Fortress
I don't have any plans to do
VR until
after
the Halloween
stream Halloween stream will happen
and then we'll
go back to kind of a normal
stream stuff
we've done a lot of horror games and
creepy scary stuff this month
and I've never done that before
by the way this is the
first time that I've spent significant time
back to back to back
to back doing scary horror
horror games
for October
normal streams like playing with children's toys
drunk yeah
but not until I do VR again
and when I do VR again there'll be another
long list of new stuff that's come out
that I could play like we did last time
but I'll see you guys tomorrow
we're gonna finish
fear tomorrow again
these streams of the next week are gonna be shorter
while I am on this
stint of medicine that I'm trying to get
to I'll see you guys soon
tomorrow same time somewhere around like
between one and two like it always is
we'll finish fear
have a great night
take care of yourselves maybe we'll see you tomorrow
good night guys
see you later