I... I do not trust this guy being the captain of my ship.
In fact, if this guy wasn't the janitor, I would leave the ship. I would get off. I would tell him to pull over.
This shit is like drawn on with crayon.
Well, here's the ship. There's a turret on there to shoot the bad guys.
We got a DirecTV in case we want to watch HBO. Another gun. And there's a... well, I've fallen into space.
I've fallen off my ship. I'm in space now. Can I do anything about this?
No, I don't think there's anything I can do.
Didn't they make a movie about this?
See, right there, that's Orion's belt, right there. And up there, there's the Big Dipper.
See, that's the Big Dipper. One, two, three. That's the spoon part.
Over here we have... that's the planet that we're going to.
In this space exploration, space adventure game. It's gonna be so much fun.
I've always wanted to meet an alien. I've always wanted to handshake an alien and we're gonna be able to do that.
Get excited! This is gonna be the most exciting game!
This bird is not having an easy time in the rain.
This bird... it's a thunderstorm. Watch out!
I seriously don't know what to do with you.
I can't pick you up. I can't really do anything with you.
The only thing I can do is, like, help you by breaking the stone around you.
And maybe you'll get the idea.
And... I killed him.
Very strange things are happening right now.
What the fuck?
Where's the snake come from?
Holy shit. Okay, how do I kill it?
How do I kill it? I'm dead.
Found him, guys. Excuse me, sheep. I need to mine this ore.
Yeah. Yes, Mr. Pig. Yes, Mr. Pig.
Did I just get killed by a sheep?
God, where are these snakes going?
What are you fucking idiots doing?
Leave me alone!
And here's the dipshit that was riding on the top of...
I seriously wonder... I don't even know how many animals are gonna be stuck in here by the end of this.
But it's gonna be probably a shitload.
Good thing I got out of there. I wonder if he's gonna fall into a fucking hole.
Yep.
I gotta jump. I gotta jump out of here.
I can't jump. I gotta...
Oh my god, will you get out of here?
You need to defend yourself. Mortimer, defend yourself!
Turn around and start swinging!
Stop the snakes!
You were created for one purpose!
Here comes the captain's chair.
All this garbage, it took so long.
But I'm finally installing my captain's chair.
And then... I can go.
I think it's time to take off.
I think I'm ready.
There's no like sound. This is such a piece of shit, ship.
Don't cry. I crashed into a tree.
I crashed directly into a tree and nothing happened.
I'm just kind of spinning around.
Well, here we go. I fell off the side of the planet.
Where do I want to go?
Oh, I'm so excited. Why am I this excited?
This has been like a pain in the ass.
I guess it's just slowly gonna drift this way.
I don't even know what that is.
But I seem to not be going towards it for some fucked up reason.
There we go. Okay.
The fuck is happening? What the fuck is going on? What's happening?
What's going on?
What happened?
What the fuck is going on?
I can't... I can't...
I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do. I have to exit the game.
I have to get out of here.
Let's go right over here.
What the fuck was that?
What the fuck is happening right now?
Whoa! What is that?
Hostile environment.
This is a pretty interesting planet.
You've got giraffes
just in the water, walking around drowning and walking on the ground.
And you also have three headed serpents that shoot fireballs out of their mouths.
Pretty interesting collection of animals we have here.
And there's an elephant too.
I don't know if he's upside down or right side up.
I honestly could not tell you.
Okay, looks like he was upside down.
Looks like a monster hunter.
He just shot himself in the face.
Done. Did it.
But I'm going to fall out now.
My guy is just... I didn't want to weld that on the back of the fucking spaceship
and I can't take it off.
I'm gonna fall out.
No, shit.
That's so unsafe. Why would anybody do that?
Why would you ever do something like that?
And now goodbye.
No wait, it might land.
I'm not a scientist.
I don't claim to be an engineer or anything, but
I have to beg the question.
If this 5,000 pound piece of space equipment
is floating this slowly back to the surface,
shouldn't I, as like a 140 pound meat bag,
be able to jump and swim to the next planet?