Hey, what's happening everybody? Jerma here. Welcome to 2016. Let me be the first to welcome you to 2016.
First, before we get started into the top five games of 2015, I want to tell you about my new year's resolution.
Here we go. Here it is. It's to invent a shrink ray so I can hang out with my mice friends that are in the top five games of 2015.
These are the ones that I spent the most time in or the ones that I just had the most fun with.
Warning! This is an automated response. The Witcher 3 has not been detected on this list. Proceed with caution.
No, I haven't even played the game.
Quick little story about Undertale. I played this game for two hours and gave up.
I saw it as a run-of-the-mill RPG with retro-inspired graphics made by a small team.
It took me a good two to three weeks before I came back to it. And not because I really felt like playing Undertale, it's because I just really had nothing else to do.
I ended up streaming the rest of the time in the game and it was a blast. It was a ton of fun.
And I'm so glad that I got bored that day and decided to go back and play it because it turns out to be one of my favorite games from last year.
And I thought about it as to why I didn't care before and why I didn't like it, why I didn't give it a chance.
And it has to do with Inception. How many of you guys remember when Inception came out?
Everybody loved the movie and everybody was talking about it. And if you hadn't had seen Inception, people were like,
Whoa, wait a second. You haven't seen Inception? Oh, you got to see Inception. Just wait for that part in Inception. You ever heard of Inception?
And it gave this predisposed expectation of what you're supposed to expect to get from the movie.
Undertale is the same way. People talk a lot about this game. Even me right now, me making this video, is telling you about it and talking about it.
And the point I'm trying to make is just enjoy the game at your own pace. Don't listen to other people. Just forget everything I've said so far.
Everything. I should not have even talked about it. I didn't plan this through. Didn't think this through at all. Of course not.
Just pay attention to your screen right now. The mind eraser frog is going to come say hello.
So as I was saying, Dying Light is number five because of everything we just talked about.
It's got great melee mechanics. It's got a fun multiplayer mode. You can jump in, jump out with your friends. I highly recommend you check it out.
Number four is Metal Gear Solid V The Phantom Pain.
There's not much I can say about Metal Gear Solid V that hasn't already been said by everybody.
So know that it's a fantastic open world third person shooter with stealth tactics, but also know it's one of the greatest, if not the only, human being collection simulators.
I think the Fulton device might be more fun for me than the actual Metal Gear Solid V campaign.
Something about scoping people out, seeing what they're good at, sending them back to Mother Base, doing staff allocation and moving people around and oh these guys got in a fight, gotta move these guys around.
It was a very, very itchy, itchy, scratchy game.
Now, I have not yet finished this game. I actually didn't start playing this game until 2016, about a week ago.
So technically, it's not even allowed to be on this list because I need to follow my own rules and I had to at least have started playing the game in 2015.
So unfortunately, I'm gonna have to disqualify Metal Gear Solid V fucking up this whole list. Can I get anything right the first time?
Hold on, just take a look at this frog for a second.
Hey, you're on a boat. You're on a boat and it's a nice day.
There's a southeastern wind that comes by, catches right in the cheek. You breathe in the fresh sea air.
You go home, you had a great time when you were there. That was what you just were doing and it reminded you of just how bad Raven's Cry sucked.
And you wanted to disqualify it and that's exactly what we just did.
Currently making our Games of the Year for 2015 list and what a great idea that was that you had. What a fantastic suggestion that you gave me there.
Yeah, I'm feeling a little bit sick too. I'm a little queasy as well. It's probably something that we ate. We probably ate the same thing.
But don't worry about that. It'll probably pass.
Let's move on. We've already talked about this. We can go to number four now on the list.
And it's Victor Vran. Victor Vran is one of those games that I wish the developers had a hundred million more dollars.
Because the base game is so good and there's so many great ideas in this game.
If I won that Powerball, like I'll give you a real scenario here. If I won the 1.6 billion dollar Powerball, whatever the hell it was,
I would have like wrote a blank check to these guys and then like make another one of these games and make it like 50 times bigger.
Here's a fucking billion dollars. But I didn't win the Powerball so I can't do that.
But the point still stands. The genre of action RPGs, especially top-down ones, really needed a breath of fresh air.
Victor Vran is that air. There's a combat role in this game. There's a wall jump.
There's a deck building progression system where you craft cards together and collect different types of cards and put them in the slots down here.
It was a bunch of new ideas. And I just wish I could have seen it more fleshed out.
But what was there was really good. I just hope they made enough money from this game to potentially do another one or a sequel.
Maybe not Victor Vran 2 because we've already seen a handful of Hellsing inspired RPGs.
I'd rather see a different setting or a different story or something. But whatever, who doesn't like slaying monsters?
You know what I mean? Who doesn't like killing monsters?
So that wraps up this one. Here comes number three, Card Crawl.
I was pretty reluctant to put this on the list because it's a mobile game. iPad, Android, iPhone, that type of deal.
So just give me ten seconds, ten seconds, ten seconds of your time. That's all I ask for.
Take all the games that I've talked about so far. Take the amount of playtime I have in them.
I would not be surprised if I had at least half that amount of time in Card Crawl.
The game is fun. You play against a deck of 54 cards and it's three bucks. There's no in-app purchases. The game's really...
Look at this frog. Look at the frog. What? Is that a battery? Does it even take batteries?
No, people are going to remember this. How do I get out of this? How do I get out of this?
Witcher 3 is number two. Yep.
Congratulations. This list has officially been approved for viewing. Please have a nice rest of your day.
Thank you. Thank you. I appreciate it. Witcher 3 is number two. That's it. And Bloodborne is number one.
Not only is Bloodborne my favorite game from last year, it might even be one of my favorite single player games
I've ever played. I seriously cannot remember the last time I put more than 120 to 150 hours into a single player game.
I gotta go back at least two decades, guys. Remember, I'm like 40. But this game sucked me in. Big time.
I was really into this game for a period. I've read an entire 110 page thesis statement about this game.
And I loved every second of it. The game's combat, the story, the atmosphere, the art direction.
Literally everything about this game, I adore. The only issue I have with it is that everybody can't play it.
I so badly want people that don't have PS4s to be able to enjoy this game. But at the time of this recording,
it does not look like it's coming to PC or Xbox One, at least for the foreseeable future.
Besides that, it gets two thumbs up from me. You know when you play a game and you say to yourself,
man, I wish I could just go back and like relive that experience for the first time?
There was some way that I could wipe my memory and play this game again and enjoy it like it was the first time playing it.
Holy shit.
I'm not getting into another argument with somebody from tech support. You're the third person I've been transferred to.
I have a warranty and I need to recalibrate my mind eraser frog. Is it that hard to understand?
Maybe six or seven thousand times over the course of a few years. Not supposed to do it that many times.
Okay, well you work for the company that makes these, so you're like kind of preaching to the choir here.
Underneath? Yeah. I'm looking at it right now. What's the purpose of...
I want to go back, I've said it four times now, I want to go back and play Bloodborne and experience it for the first time.
It's the game of the year.
You think that's a better game than Bloodborne. Well, good to know they transferred me to a fucking idiot.
Okay, no, no, no. It's not better than Bloodborne. Look, we have differing opinions, whatever. I'm sorry, just forget it.
How do I fix it? The button underneath, there's, I see it, yes. Hold it for four seconds.
Now, is there something?
Oh, you piece of shit, that was fucking dastardly!
Hello? Oh, I'm sorry to bother you. Yeah, I did call to tell you that Fallout 4 was the best game of the year.