I am back. How are you? I missed it by one minute. One minute. I'm here. Make an Elden Ring open
and ready. All right, that was nice. I had some food, had a little bit more water, played with
Otto, hung out with Holly for a little bit. Let me just stir my drink because I can't close it
because I have too much ice in it. Just say what you did. I didn't do the thing you're describing,
but you know, I do need to plug this in. I don't know what happened to my GoXLR, but the audio jack
where you plug in a pair of headphones is broken. I didn't really do anything. I don't get it.
Okay, Elden Ring. Let's open it. You guys cannot see anything, can you? No, you cannot yet.
What's in my pocket? All right, so I gotta remember what the hell I was doing because it's been a
few days. I think I want to go north east. I believe that's where I'm heading.
Oh, I gotta change the category because we're in Elden Ring now, not Big Brain Academy. All right,
put a heart rate monitor on. I don't have access to a heart rate monitor at the moment. I'm sorry.
Dude, you should put a heart rate monitor on. Maybe another time? Very cool. I need to change
that. Oh, why is it getting louder? I am fresh. I've returned. I know the audio is not in sync.
Give me one second while I fix it. It'll be good. There we go. There. Hi. Let's go. Elden Ring.
This motherfucker looks like he drinks aloe vera juice. Well, I can assure you I don't.
I don't drink aloe vera juice. Why? Whatever. Okay, so I came over here because it was a few
things I didn't do this way. If you're wondering the character, yeah, baby rattle. I'll give you
just some people that are jumping in that are like, well, what's your gear, bro? What's your
loadout, bro? Imp cat head, godskin noble robe, godskin apostle bracers, godskin trousers,
plus nine bastard stars and a plus four glint stone as your glint stone. Staff,
did you bring your notes? I did. I did bring my notes. They're not showing. I did bring them.
They're there. All right. Door next to spawn is blocked shut. Who cares? Looking for Lanya.
Haven't found them yet. That prawn guy says piss off. I don't know what to do with that person.
The- I did- I did the elevator, didn't I? The sea offer elevator. I think I did that already.
Didn't I put it in? I got this. I remember getting the complete coin. And I think I did that. I did.
So we don't have very much here as of right now, but let's go. Go kill the prawn guy.
Uh, I want to go over here. There's this urn tree that I have not done.
There's a bunch of random shit over here. Like that. Like this. Like that. So we're going to
make our way this way. Why do we still look like this? Oh, we still look like this because
something's wrong with my audio. Get this for a second. Only coming through one ear.
That's better. Okay. I can hear. All right, let's go to five first. Yeah, we're still doing like
the cat baby thing. So this is area I've not been in. I think this is a church, right? Okay,
this trebuchet's launching. Please. Thank you. That was a bird. Okay. I saw a shadow of a bird
and I freaked out. I don't think they can launch over here. Shit mean anything? Why do you have
a toddler on a horse? Just go see the last vaude. I, it's hard to explain.
Hey, I learned this from Reddit. Are you behind me? Holy shit. You're behind me.
That didn't hit him. Oh boy. This is bad. Christ. Oh my God. What's happening? What have I done?
No, don't block that shit. Where is it? I'm trying to get it to kill him. Sucker. Sucker.
That hits. I didn't know that hit that many times in a row.
I got to kill the guy behind that guy. What area is this? This area is. Hold on. I can't really
stop. Give me one sec. Damn. This weapon's actually really, really good. We talked a lot of shit.
Okay. This area is this sort of Northern Lurnia is this church right here.
Is this ever jail? I know, I know how to say it correct now.
I don't want to go this way though. I want to go to my marker over here.
Popium. So many fucking markers. All right. We'll get rid of this guy.
I'm actually destroying people in this zone. I'm annihilating people in this zone. I must be high
for this place. I must be very leveled for this area. At least this exact spot here.
Yeah, I definitely am. Did you avoid most spoilers? Great mace. Um, yes. The only thing that was ever
spoiled for me was the witch quest because I had it on a second monitor over here. And I've,
I apologized for that. I already apologized for it. So we're not doing, I got no more guides.
Okay. Up there. Can I even get up there? That seems far away. There might be a dungeon over
here too. Ooh, cookie bug. He definitely smoked on that 20 minute break. No, I can't. I can't.
I got way too much shit to do over the next like two or three straight days. I can't like,
I can't get like, no, that's not happening. Not right now. Dungeon? Why are they here? How have I
not come up to this kind of Northern Lurnia? Where have I been this whole time? Doing the
witch quest right? That took almost a whole stream. Yellow ember. Nothing over here though.
All right. There we go. I'm watching you. Hey, how are you? What's that sound? What's going on?
What's wrong? What's wrong? What's wrong? What's wrong? What's wrong? What's wrong? What's wrong?
What was that? I need a bonfire. It's the, it's the bloodborne shit. That's bloodborne shit. That's
what they call, they would call like the winter lanterns and they'd walk around and if you saw
them it would fill and you went, you died. Okay. Is it just a line of sight thing? If it's a line of
sight thing, I may be all right. Is it line of sight? Okay. It's character line of sight. Jesus.
I can't see it. All right. Let me get up there and kill whoever's doing that. What the fuck?
Is that a machine? Oh, fuck you. All right. Cool. It's not going to affect me when I'm right here,
right? Five G. Howl of Shiburi. Spell? Shrieks building up madness in nearby foes. 33 faith.
At least it's a maddening shriek that causes madness build up in foes nearby.
And it's a taunt. That's kind of cool. So what happens if I go up here? What's the, am I going
to get madnessed? Oh, your person is so ugly. No, don't say that. Why am I still getting it?
Alleviate's build up of frost. Alleviate's build up of sleep. Scarlet rot, blood loss, frost,
sleep. I don't have any madness ones. Do I? Light, sleep? No. All right. Here's the plan.
I'm going to go up there. If I die, I die. I'm going to start the process right now. Go.
What the fuck is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? Throw a grenade up there.
That it? That's it? All right. I did it. So that means I can walk around here without a problem.
It was just them doing that. Okay. Well, that's weird. No chest or anything.
But that means I can walk around here without hiding. All right. The actual place I want to
go is five. I got the chest. Yeah, that's right. You're right. I got it. That just lets you,
hopefully it doesn't respawn there. This is ruins here too. Remember you look like a Renaissance
painting. Now I do frenzied flame village. There's gonna be another one of those things
here in there. I have not found a bonfire, so I really have to be careful. Even though,
even though I might be a tad overleveled for this exact spot, died from less.
Pretty clean. Clean. What is it? Is this a mask? It's not. What was that?
Isn't it a spell? An item? It's talisman. Constantly attracts enemy aggression.
Okay. Somebody explain this to me, right? In the souls games, they have items like this.
What's the point of this item? Why would you put this on? Why would you ever want to wear this?
Make co-op easier. Co-op. It's tanking in a summon for hard mode farming items.
Co-op to tank. Okay. That makes sense. That makes sense. You're right. What else is in here?
How do I hear something weird? Note the lord of frenzied flame. Boss? Okay. Beneath Lindell,
at the very bottom lies our lord. Lord of the frenzied. The three fingers who holds us in thrall.
Beneath Lindell. Where's Lindell? Lindell? Lindell? Three fingers. What happened to
two fingers? Have I been to Lindell? What are the notes? That's not. Yeah, that's true. What does it
say? Beneath Lindell. The very bottom. At the very bottom of Lindell. Frenzied flame lord. Okay.
Good to know. I don't think I've come across Lindell yet. Is there anything else here? I feel
like there would be, right? A lot of these places have little dungeons to go in, so I'm not fucking
missing it. Maybe not. Maybe it's just a village. I think it's just a village. I think it's a lore
village. Something keeps making, I keep hearing sounds. Like loud sounds. I don't know if it's
just the atmosphere or what. Well, I don't know. That's cool. Closer to my actual goal, which is
no, I'm going the wrong way. But I did want to go to the urtree. Let's go fight the avatar.
I need a bonfire now. Really? That's, that's too many. Challenge though. Let's do it.
Okay. Nevermind. I nevermind. I don't want to do it anymore. I was kidding.
Nevermind. Nevermind. Goodbye. Stop it. You might, I might get something for this. I don't know.
Let me do my stupid fucking move. All right. Is there any reason for me to do that? Grave violet.
Okay. That nothing, nobody dropped anything cool. Nobody had anything. Ooh. What's that way? Market.
What is that? All right. Pay attention. I need, I need a bonfire. It's gotta be one down here,
right? He's going to kill me. Oh, it's a giant. It's one of the fucking bear. Does he care? I
don't think he knows. Get off. Oh, got him. 3000 damage. Yeah. I may be a little, a little,
a little leveled up with this guy. It's very possible that I'm a little leveled up,
although I have not seen anything in this area. So, you know, I'm not going to just not do it,
right? It's definitely a dungeon down here without a doubt. Like a million percent dungeon,
100 million percent. Come on. Hey, how did you miss? You literally saw the entrance. I did.
I did. No, I didn't. Tomically large arrows. Where's the entrance? Oh, it was a liar. Okay.
Oh, it was a liar. Okay. Somebody that's lying. All right. There's somebody with a bone arrow
down there. Whatever. Where the fuck am I? All right. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm biting off way more than I should. Back up to what I wanted to do. I'm getting too distracted.
This is literally the distract yourself video game. You'll see something far away. You'll go,
oh, I'm going to go to that thing. You'll trot like 15 feet in front of you and go,
what's that? And turn left and just you lost. And then you do something else for like four hours.
So focus on the task that is at hand right now. Go to the tree, which I need to get up.
Can I get up from here? Who's that? Who the fuck is this guy? Why do you look so special?
Doesn't he look special? He's, he's a little special. All right. He was a little special.
Oh shit. I found a spark. Cool. Elum highway, black knife catacombs. Somebody said this dungeon
sucks. Beast eye quivers. The beast eye quivers. Beast eye quivers. I have a beast. Is that to
tremble when close to death route? Oh, okay. That just means there's an undead. Okay. Cool.
Maybe I can. Yeah. I'm probably pretty level for this place. So I'm not scared.
This does not scare me. Yeah. That's the guy that eats the, uh, that eats them, right?
Although who knows? I could be just totaled full of shit right now.
I know I could just be full of shit and I lose immediately to this guy. Oh,
there's a stone sword key thingy. Um, why won't they die? What? I want to go in here.
Do they not die? These are like the bones people from Mario and I'm not killed. Okay. You can't
kill them. Those guys don't die dry bones. Yeah. That's the character I'm thinking of.
All right. Just, I, I gotta, I can't kill them. So just, I gotta get my souls. It's going to go
in the stone sword key room because that I want to get in there. All right. So what, what's in here?
Oh, what is that thing? Oh, this is acts. Is there anything else? I need you guys to fuck off for
one second. Nothing else in here. Okay. Oh, that guy's bringing them to life. Okay. So you just
have to kill that guy. Sounds easy enough. I want to see. Why is this guy coming back?
That guy was different. I want to see the acts. This is an int scaling acts.
Roses who shows the path to the catacombs or the lands between is depicted on the virtual acts
summon. Really? Whoa. That's a pretty bad ass move. That's pretty bad ass.
What is it? It scales with strength and int. Oh, only 18 strength. Don't think I want to change it
over the baby rattle at this point in the game. Maybe rattle too good. That's it. That's really
cool. All right. No more stalling. Let's go. I have to go through this bullshit. I thought I
got hit by it. I was like, how the fuck is that possible? I was about to start freaking out and
talking shit about from software. I was going to be like, there's no way it's impossible for that
to happen. Stop, stop it. All right. Now I'm fucking mad at this guy. Sorry. I forgot the buttons for
a second. It's been like a week yet. These guys are connected to a sorcerer.
Why fight them? There's no reason to. Okay. I can go down. Let's go down.
Now you get it. The crab is like dirt crabs. Are they hostile? I don't think they are.
I think that I'm just unnecessary. Kill it before I can do anything. Rune arc.
Ray. Really? The whole point was I didn't want you to come near me, but you did anyways.
So this is obviously not correct. Obviously. I didn't get up there. I can't kill these guys.
Stop for one second. I can't even fucking look. Wait, do you? I don't think I'm supposed to do
that. Is that how you do it? That is how you do it. What a gigabrain. I didn't look at any,
nobody in chat said that. I go back and look at the logs and literally nobody when I looked over,
like the precise moment I looked over, nobody said ride them up. Nobody did.
Oh, like, I mean, that's, you know, well accomplished.
Yeah. All right. There's another. Thank God.
Scimitar. He did it all by himself. No guide. Don't you guys understand? The only way you can
play a From Software game truly by yourself is if you play within the first like two days
the game comes up. That means offline. Okay. Offline. So no blood stains, no messages,
right? The person that gets there first, that puts the message down. Yeah, they did it by themselves.
I didn't do that by myself. See, I looked over and somebody said invis wall. So I just deduced
where the best possible scenario with the best possible place that would be.
And I figured it would be here. Am I going to, I feel like I'm pretty overleveled though,
but this is really far in. I have a lot of souls. I don't have any heels though.
I am going to err on the side of caution, but I need to figure out because there was a lever
I could pull. Is this going to kill me if I go down here? Just do it. No heels. Just do it.
This boss is easy. Just do it. It's easy. Coward. This boss is actually easy. Fine. Black knife
assassin. Oh shit. Okay. Well, if I had a fucking flask, maybe I'm doing a shitload of damage to
him. Attack him. I do it. I'm walking the boss room for the first time. I'm not just going to
start pressing R1. I'm not just, all right, you know what? I guess I walked in the boss door.
Let's just fucking go ahead and start doing this. I mean, I'm going to die in one second. I don't
even know what he does. How do I get back there? There's another boss here. There's a second door.
You fought this guy already. Did I? I don't know. The Elden Ring is like eight games in one game,
so it's hard to remember what I did. Oh shit. Am I going to get hurt? Yeah. I mean, I may have
fought this enemy type 36 or 38 bosses ago, but I don't, I mean, it's been a while. Maybe those
souls don't hurt me. See if I can catch him in this. Ooh. Oh man. That's bad for him. All right.
Don't be a fucking idiot. Okay. He's good. You're way overleveled. I did. I'm just exploring the
areas I didn't do yet. I can miss every fucking swing. What? Yeah. I'm, I'm, I'm overleveled for
this area, but it's, I haven't, I haven't been here yet. And I'm not just going to run by it.
You got, he, that guy got more hits in than the boss did. Yeah. But he was also very surprising.
Okay. That's not it though. Cause this, another not hidden boss. And what was that?
Two things that he dropped. What was it? Black knife print. Mark of the night of the
black knives ritual. On the night of the black knives, someone stole a fragment of death from
Milliketh, the black blade and imbued his power onto the assassin's dagger.
Okay. That's an item. There was another one. There was another item. So it was in one of these
was critical hits, restore FP. It doesn't seem that useful for this particular build. All right.
I can, I'm going to try this. Let's see if I die. Nope. I'm alive. Very cool. But there's a second
boss in here. I wonder if I'm going to one shot that one too. Two shot. Yeah. I was waiting for
somebody to say that. I was waiting for you to say that. It's a fun fact. George R. R. Martin wrote
every single message you see on the ground. Really? That's kind of cool. Don't kill me.
Don't kill me. That's cool. Game fact. All right. So this is this, this is just a boss. All right.
So let me actually level up first in case I embarrass myself and die to a boss. I'm probably
10 to 20 levels higher than and everyone will omega LL and make fun of me. And I'll have to
look over here and freak out and explain exactly why I died. Something about the button, the D pad,
I hit the D pad the wrong way or something. Something about the D pad. It's always about
the D pad. So all right. I can't level up. It's probably not that bad. It's probably fine.
Let's get in there and do it. Cemetery shade. Okay. All right. All right. Have you heard of
jumping R2? Oh my God. What the fuck? I didn't even mean to kill him. Am I like 100 levels too
high for this? What the fuck was that? All right. All right. But wait, but hold on.
I'm only level 89. It's not like I'm that high. And this is all right. So my game progress route,
I went like this way and then this way and then this way and this way. So let me ask you something.
It's doing the rainy witch quest line that took me like, it took me like eight to 10 hours.
Did that? Was I like, was I like under leveled for that stuff, but over leveled for this stuff?
I did Caleb too early. Really? Well, that's interesting. That's really interesting.
This stuff is like during the academy. Really? Holy shit. Well, that's cool. All right. Well,
that's still fun though. It's just a dungeon. Whatever. 100% Radan was very, way, way, way,
way, way too early. Well, that's really cool. That was sick. I like that. Let's kill this guy
in fucking two hits too. Why not? I like being really powerful. Oh, this is actually really good.
No more skin suit. No, I mean, this is fantastic. New armor. Oh no. What about the baby armor?
It's okay. That's not even where I wanted to go. I wanted to go up there. I used to have a bonfire.
Okay. I need to go down this road and bang a right. That's what we're doing because I can't,
I'm not going to be able to figure it out. Dude, you're distracting me from my Mario Kart game.
Dude, don't worry. Just get in last place and hold the blue shell until the last 10 seconds of the
game. I think you'll be all right. All right. Here we go. Is there an bird tree avatar over here?
It's a bear again. I don't want to fight the bear again. I want to get up here.
The hat. Is this thing alive? Is there like a gesture in front of it? Go get the bell, Pog.
All right. Okay. So I mean, I figured you were going to do that.
Um, again, the barnacle. Barnacles. Oh, these things. Oh, really? I feel like this stuff,
are you making that up? I'm really glad you told me that because that would have taken an hour for
me to figure out what the fuck, what the fuck is going on. Okay. So it's a building. With the
remembrance duplication menu, you can duplicate remembrances you've previously acquired. This
includes remembrances from which you've already drawn out power. Duplication can only perform
once per mausoleum. So this is boss soul stuff. So I get to have another boss soul. You can get
both boss soul items. Could I just take one of these and break it? You could do dual baby rattles.
I can just take, does this cost anything? Or you can, I can only just do it once.
So it's only one time. So where are the other ones? I killed way more than these two. Where's, um,
like Godric and Margit and stuff around the map. There are other mausoleums, different mausoleums,
different turtle. Oh, so I mean, is it worth me just breaking this and getting a hundred thousand
souls and leveling up like three times? You can't do two of the same reward. You can only do the
other one that you didn't pick. Okay. I can't do dual baby rattles. If you don't want the other
weapon. Yeah. Which I don't remember what they were in a while. There's only two of like 10
potential bosses that are here. Yeah. I probably, um, I don't think I'm going to do this yet.
That's cool though. It's really cool. What you can do dual rattles. I feel like that would be kind
of funny. And then I would be like, wow, that was 10,000 souls. And I'm going to go back to my
catalyst now, whatever this thing is, staff, whatever. There's another one right there.
All right. I need to, so that's what's in this pond. Let me mark this. I'm going to mark this as,
uh, like a jewel because I don't, I need to go to this tree. Go up to one. I need to get up to
the tree. Where's the road? Okay. I've got to go this way. Jump up the clip. Oh my goodness.
Are we okay? I think I'm okay. Yeah. I'm so paranoid about those jumps. All right. Here we go.
Now we're going to wrap around here and go this way. We're going to go to the tree.
I don't want to fight any of you. We go. I could see, I could open that too,
but bonfire bonfire somewhere. Thank you. And it's not like in a dungeon on the ground somewhere.
Thank God. All right. I need to level up. Oops. Is that a magic flail? That is a magic flail.
I still can't 47. Oh shit. Okay. Well, whatever. All right. Bird tree this way. Oh my, okay. How
do I get over there? I gotta go all the way around. There's probably a dungeon over there.
All right. Do I clean this one of the barnacles too? Not as well. Oh God. Oh God. What just
happened? Somebody threw something at me. Is it that leg? Yeah. Yep. Did I do it? What's happening?
Okay. I did it. So I'm assuming this is the same thing. I'm just going to say it is. It is. Okay.
That's really cool. So I don't need to make that decision now.
All right. Bird tree time. Let's go. Dungeon. I would have put one right here if I was a game
dev. I just want to kill the avatar here. There we go. All right. Let's kill the avatar.
Give me the shit I'm looking for. I want more of those flask things.
It shouldn't be too hard considering it's just an avatar. Spoilers for those that have not seen
one of the avatars yet. They all fall the same exact formula. They are still fun though.
Okay. Let's kill this in three hits. I mistimed that. Okay. I don't want to fuck this up
because considering I'm... I thought I was the body on the ground. I was like, why is this taking
me fucking forever to get up? I thought I was the guy on the ground. That was another body.
I'm getting so greedy. Oh fuck. I'm gonna die. Really? Fuck you. What is this reach?
Your reach is too high. I'm out of heals. Oh my god. What am I doing? I'm dead. I'm just like...
I'm like so leveled for this area that I'm just like, I don't care. Whatever. Just hit me.
Like I have to... I can't just like run into the guy and just swing at him. I'm just like,
yeah, whatever. I'm fucking way higher than you. I'm just gonna fucking walk into you.
Will you get the fuck out of here? Like seriously, like get away from me.
I was... That guy just made... That guy just pissed me off the way he was looking at me.
Good again. Come on. Okay. I didn't like the way the guy was looking at me. What do I get for this?
Magic Shrouding Crack Tear. Lightning Shrouding Crack Tear. Holy Shrouding. All right.
One of those actually might be really good. Where is it? Oh, right here. Okay. What is it?
Boost Magic Attacks? I kind of want to try it. Fire Attack, Lightning Attack, Magic Attack.
Does that work for this? Might be pretty good. How is it? We're good. I'm good on time.
That's the Erd Tree. That's good. Imagine that on a weapon. That would be... I wonder how much
it increases it because that would be good for my L2. All right. So that was the Erd Tree.
I went here. I still want to go here. And now I'm actually... Okay. I can actually get over there
now. Go to five first. Fuck, it's still higher. Wait, this way. The physical effects are strong.
How do I get up here? Over here? Maybe I have to go all the way around?
From the Flame Village, really? It looks like I can go this way. All the way around here or from here?
How high up is this fucking thing? I can see it, but I can't get to it. All the way around?
Fuck. I missed it. I really want to get up there. Maybe it is from the Flame Village. You're right.
You have to go in from the north. Let's try that. Because that's probably a sacred tier.
It's probably a church. All the way around? Oh my lord. Go over the tree? Oh, do you mean
physically go over the tree? Or do you mean like, you know, go over the tree. Like,
examine the tree. I thought you meant go over the tree. Like, you got to examine the tree.
I don't think that's right. You were just being like a weirdo saying to like go on the tree.
Okay, I'm just going to keep going all the way. All right. So dude, how fucking much rock is
around this place? How do I get out of here? Cross examine the tree. I, dude, I don't even know how to
how to physically get up there again. You know what I'm saying? Like, how did I even, what was it?
Go to the village? I think I'm, I came, the village is up here. I can't, I don't think I can even go
there anymore. Unless there's like a specific random way that I have to go. It's all blocked
off by a giant wall. Like this is like, I can't go around this. How do I do it? Maybe I have to go
all the way from here. I go from here. I'm gonna go over here because I think I actually went down
and this, I don't think it's a way to get back up. Now if I wrap around, how do I get, let's see.
How do I approach this? I go up here. So I guess I'm going to go up. What's the number? Is that
three? Okay. So I got, this is a million feet in the air. This is way higher than I thought it
was going to be. That's, that's a million. That's, that's at least a hundred thousand feet in the air.
No. Holy shit. And then I got to bang a right up here. I hope there's a bonfire up there. All right.
There's that. There's Jesus. It's the back of the town lore. It's in the back of the lore town.
I haven't seen this, whatever this is. This is new, whatever it is.
Well, this is, oh no, this is the lore town. Okay. So I'd go this way. I'm trying to just
take a look and see what, do I have to jump on that and walk around and jump off there?
I think that's what, that's what I have to do. I have to go through the town.
Holy shit. There's one fucking specific way to get here. Okay. I'm in the town. I want to go
this way. Like up here. This looks correct. That is okay. All right. Holy my God.
That was a pain in the ass. Lord Vike, it seems that you were no Lord after all. Then where is
he? Our true Lord, our Lord frenzied flame. We beg of you, incinerate all the divides and
distinguishes. May chaos take the world. All right. I'm looking for that guy too.
This is a brainless German woman. Look at the map. There's one way to get here. You
can't get here from any other fucking direction. Not a single other direction, but right here.
That's it. That's it. You drinking piece of shit. Don't you know how leveled I am?
Fingerprint grape and a war spear. This is a faith weapon. So I see it. Ooh.
Can't do the ability, unfortunately. That's a cool weapon though. All right. Give me the church.
For those of you that haven't been watching Elden Ring streams and were tricked by the
Mario tennis stream. German doesn't read chat. He just threatens to put people in meat grinders
every few hours and rubs his eyes because he plays the game for too long. I love how you were
tricked by Mario tennis. Yeah. That's what I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to get,
I'm going to funnel them all in. With Mario, by the way, golf, it wasn't tennis.
I'm going to bait and switch them into Elden Ring where I go like this for the next four hours.
Fuck you. Fuck you. You got fucking baited. Ooh. Nothing special on this. Just looks interesting.
Finger maiden robe. Okay. Yes. Let's get to 40 vigor. All right. That was worth coming all
the way up here. Although I mean, this map doesn't really help to explain that there's only one way
to get here and everywhere else is a gigantic mountain cliff. But I digress. I want to go over
here or do I want to, you know, you know what? No, no, no. I want to go across this bridge.
All right. Use the tier. That's smart. And I'm going to do the flask as well.
I have any more of these? Hey. All right. I think I want to do the magic one and see how good it is
and the heel or the damage negation. Yeah. You can't go wrong with that. I'm very curious how,
how good this is. I don't be that stupid. Okay. So I want to go on the main road. We're going to do
main progress. Main progress. Although I think I went the wrong way. Wait, there's a merchant here.
You got kind of a dog shit inventory. Yeah. Your inventory kind of sucks. All right. Is there a
better way I can go through the church? We're going right through the gate. Okay. I just,
somebody said, Jerma, if I was in school with you, I would be, I would bully you. Oh yeah.
Oh, you think so, huh? Oh, you think so. Did you, you weren't here when you talked about how,
when I told you how fast I was. Oh, give me your lunch money. Dodge. Come here, you little bastard.
Dodge. Get behind you. Wedge. Where's my weapon? This looks cool. Holy shit. I want to take this in.
Don't rush me. Oh, what's this place? Greece. This is a big castle. Have I been here before?
I think I was at the back part of this, right? He's finally here. He finally made it. Uh,
I don't think this is the end of the game considering, um, all this. So no, I, I doubt
this is the very end of the game. I could be wrong. Is there somewhere, another path leading back to
the foot of the urn tree? An ancient tunnel. Huh? I'm about 70%. That's what I figured.
Ran. Boys and girls, I came prepared. I came incredibly prepared. I got both halves of these
medallions. The whole thing's going up. You didn't take the tunnel? Well, I mean, there's two ways to
go, I guess. I collected the two halves of this medallion across the world, so I get to do the
skip. I get my Disney Fastpass. You got to sit in line at Space Mountain for like fucking four hours.
Damn. Where the hell am I? These, those guys are out, out his plateau. All right.
When everyone has a Fastpass, no one will have one. Yeah, I mean, they do times now, right?
Didn't it used to be if you had a Fastpass, you just walked into the line. There was a Fastpass
lane. You just walked in it. That didn't last very long, did it? See, now it's like, when do you want
to ride the Millennium Falcon ride? Uh, how does like 415 sound? And you come back at 415 and you're
getting another line, right? But it's like faster. This is really, really pretty. Sometimes the
Fastpass is just as long. Are I going to kill these guys? Or am I going to get, am I going to get
a shit on here? Let's find out about how much trouble these guys were giving me like 12 hours
ago, 20 hours ago in game. I tried to fight one of these guys. Overleveled Andy. Um, look, I did,
I explored the world of the Elden Ring, okay? Just because I might be a little overleveled.
It was exploring the world of the Lands Between. I got every tourist attraction hat.
I got every mug from every part of Disney World. I would love to get over there.
Overleveled. Giants are not aggressive. I have like four of those. A map fragment would be
Pog right now. Looks like Fall here. Map fragment. Not on this map. Damn, okay, well, just keep on.
Overleveled, underscaled. Actually, I've been doing pretty well in this game so far.
You can go see the VODs. You can read the logs. What's this? Oh my god, an alien! Did he just
shoot himself in the head with his arrow? What did he just do? I think he just shot himself in the
head with his bow and arrow. I didn't hit him. Oh, I did. Am I a bit overleveled? I don't think so.
But I've been exploring the Lands of Elden Ring. I spent two days in Limgrave. It was a lot of fun.
Oh, I want to try this thing. The cheese overpowered Andy. This is the first time I've
ever seen this place. I'll tell you, it was a witch quest. I got so obsessed with it and it
ended up taking like, it took like a full 10-hour day to beat the witch quest. I leveled up like
20 times doing the witch quest. I'm not, you're not, I'm not overleveled. All right. Yeah, I'm
not overleveled. I'm fine. I just have a really strong weapon. I'll take a map fragment, please.
Yeah, I slingshot myself. I did the witch quest way too early and it was really difficult. And I
like went to Radan wicked early and way, way too early. And then I got a shitload of souls from
doing that. Wham. And I launched myself into the stratosphere. This is great though. Is that a map
thingy right there? Yes. There's one here and there's one here. Let's get them both.
You were overleveled for Radan. And now I know that's bait bullshit. Now I know that that's
bait bullshit. Old Fang? Okay. Nobody is overleveled for Radan. That's true.
Oh, urd tree. Great urd tree. The golden order itself unwavering stretched to the sky.
Confer your guidance to our Elden Lord to put this weary world to rights.
We're getting close to this thing. Is Radan still your least favorite boss? Yeah, without a doubt.
One of the game's hardest bosses. Yeah, it's just, I don't know. I, it was a cool idea,
but I don't know. I'd rather just fight the guy instead of just running around like a dickhead
with like a thousand summons. Anyway, I guess you can, but it'd be hard. All right. Urd tree in the
middle. Dungeon here. Thing here. Urd tree. Oh my god, I'm gonna throw up on stream. And then
whatever this is. All right, let's begin. Ooh. Ooh, what's that? Is that one of those tortoise
missions? I don't, I don't want to do a tortoise mission right now. What's going on there?
Do you fucking die? What is this big banner? Ah, hello. Do you take your fingers and go like that?
Like here? What? What? Moons of gold. I don't know. I'm just imagining like, let me read them.
Ah, yes. To the west of that, right? All right. So what you're saying is getting that cast on
slay the goddamn demon. You can do that. All right. We have some things to look at here first.
I hear a merchant. Merchant? I heard like the, ah, there you are.
You got way better stuff. Breezer coat, frosty tower shield, scorpion kite shield.
Damn. Did I get some of this cookbook stuff? Imp shades, unseen assassins, ancient dragon's
apostle cookbook. That sounds important. You got great stuff. What are you talking about?
You got some of the best stuff I've seen so far. All right. Where's this going to take me?
What did that unlock? Anything cool? Not really. Hmm. That's actually a really good tip.
Somebody said I can hit X on it and it'll show me. That's kind of where I wanted to go. East
windmill pastor. Can I dance too? Ah, I didn't even do anything. What the? Why are you mad at me?
I actually didn't do anything. Fuck the whole goddamn group then. Oops. That's not a heal
anymore. Okay, cool. That was weird. What were you playing with? Wind, night swords. What's that?
Wind, night swords, strength scaling. Oh, it's a, it's a Darth Maul dual handed spinning attacks.
Yep. I always wanted to use one of these in these souls games, like the Albert's or like the spinners
things you hold in two hands and spin around like poles. You should respect not this late
into the game. I've got the thing going on here. That was really cool. All right. So what's the
point with the windmill? I've got to jump on it, right? Well, like attack it. I'm going to jump on
it. You definitely get on it. I'll be shocked if you didn't actually get on this somehow. I guess
not. No way in what's the significance of this thing? I don't know. Oh, there's just a ton of
these. Nevermind. Nevermind. I'm going to go, we're going to go to the urd tree and we're going
that way. I got cool clothes. Yeah. I'll take, I'll look at them in a minute. Let me go get this
avatar. It's one of those golden bugs. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, don't go away. Protection of
the urd tree. That's a faith spell. Bro, look at the new clothes. I will just wait. What's this?
What's on the door? Okay. What'd I get? Increase his mind. How many is here? Yeah. That is a mana
hood. Although I don't think, I think having the intellect from the cat helmet is better.
All right, urd tree. Let's go. Did you find the Elden Ring? Uh, I did. It's this. It's just,
this is a big circle and the Elden Ring is going to be the lands that the Elden Lords used to occupy.
And it's going to be a huge thing at the end of the game when there's no thing for you to take.
It's not like, oh, the Elden Ring. No, no, bro. Nothing's, it's not all about material shit.
That's the message they're going to give us. It's the Elden Ring of the lands. It's the land.
Not the, oh, it's a big shiny thing you put on your finger. Nope. It's the land.
Oh, I want to go to the tree. That's cool. Whatever that is. Ooh, ruins. That means there's a dungeon.
It's just an onion ring. That's a fucking person. I thought that was a decoration.
Death blighted? Dude, look, I just want to get this bug, but I'm dead. What, he didn't kill me.
What the fuck is that? That's not an avatar. That's not an urd tree avatar. Is it? Get over here.
What's this laggy glitch shit? Golden Slam. Okay. I guess these guys freak me out. I don't like these
guys. I'm going to, they don't like the sounds they make either. These guys make terrible sounds.
Well, there's definitely a dungeon, so let's find it. I hate that thing. Where is there?
There has to be, right? There's got to be a way down. Are they on top of it? Here. Where's this guy
going? No, dude. Dude, don't go over here. You don't want to go over here. Is he alive? Follow him.
He's walking into a bunch of minions. I don't want to go over this way. They're not happy. Just go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Where are you going? Dude, we've got company behind this. I don't,
you know what? Don't look behind you. I'll handle everything. Just walk like normally. Don't worry.
Nothing's wrong. What? Oh, that's an instant kill. It's an instant kill move. I forgot. I mean,
the bar is gray, so it kind of, it blends into there. He's freaking mad at video games and he
sucks. I don't like him. You know what I mean though? Why am I this far away? Where did this
just put me? Wait, item down here. Oh, golden arrows. That's probably good. Use the teleporter.
I kind of wanted to see what was down here. All right. How scared are these guys should I actually
be? And by the way, I'm going to watch this guy from afar. I'm not going to follow behind him.
I'll watch this guy who's fucking binoculars. Okay. Where was it? Why is it so magical looking
right here? Why is that so magical looking? It's just very magical. Why is it so magical looking?
All right. Where was that? That was back here. Touch that thing and I'm going to literally just
watch him from afar. All right. Go ahead. Go do your thing. Okay. He walks through these people.
Oh, I think this might be the Elden Lord. Now where are you going? This would be actually really
funny. I followed this guy for like five minutes and he goes behind a tree and takes a piss and
then just vanishes. Okay. Well, get where you're going, man. What is this guy doing? Dude,
we're walking to like the edge of the earth. Okay. He turned. We're going right here, aren't we?
We're literally going over there, aren't we? It was already marked on my map. I didn't even need
this guy. He's leading you. It's a dungeon. He's literally going to walk into it and he's going to
point. I was going to come here anyways. Well, we're here. Might as well pay him, not paying him.
Pay him. That's kind of cool though. Can I go down? Altus tunnel. What have we got? Dungeon.
This looks like another smithing stone tunnel.
Overleveled Andy coming through.
I should take a rune arc too, just to add insult to injury.
Just walk around here with a rune arc and just be unbeatable. Unstoppable.
Hey, hey, hey, hey. What is this thing? I think I've seen a version of those.
Crystals, crystals, crystals, crystals, crystals. All right. What about, can I get up here?
It's going to be those shrimp things here, right? I actually do need these. So this is
bad. This is not bad. This is great. Do you get the urge to play Luigi's Mansion from this game?
Not really. Imagine if I still use the katana. I would kill these guys all in one hit.
All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Don't be an idiot. I don't know what that was behind me,
but something happened. What is it making? Is it you? Oh Jesus. It's one of those things.
Walk through the wall for like five straight seconds. Okay. Let me go this way.
He's a smithing stone. Five nerds rope strikes again. Yeah. I don't want to miss anything.
See my problem with games like this, especially like Elden Ring. This one in particular
is I, I want to see all the cool stuff and I know that I can play another character
and just go the ways that I didn't go, but I just, I want everything. I want all the items.
I want all the stuff. I want all the gear. I, even if it's not for me,
I want the strength ring. I want the strength talisman. I just want it. Give it to me.
What about a new game? Yeah. I mean, but I want it now and you've skipped half the stuff already.
Isn't that interesting? It's how you know that there's so much to do in this game
that you could play through this probably five times. These are alive.
All right. Well, let's kill this boss. Make it quick. It is. Oh no, it's one of those
things. I need to parry this. Do I have a shield equipped? I don't. Maybe not. It depends on how
much damage I'm doing. Hmm. I'd still like to pay like this. Not worth it. I need to parry this.
I need a shield equipped. Ooh, excuse me. Holy shit. I killed them. I instantly killed them.
Somber stone miners, bell bearing. They take a ton from crits. Seems like it. Cool. Don't want
the katana? No, I like the baby rattle. I think it's really good. God, I hate one hit moves. Hey,
it's only fair that I get them too. Only on one or two enemies. I think. Was that it? I can imagine
my frustration if I was here 10 levels ago, but just get fucking absolutely stomped. This weapon
is called the bastard's stars. That's a cool dungeon. So now let's go here. So this is pointing
me this way. I wonder if it's this area here. Up here. We're going to go there eventually. All
right. Let's let me check this place out first because I'm right here. There's also these ruins,
but I want to see what this is. Oh, a fucking gigantic brick wall. Never mind. Do the urtree
boss. I am right here. I'll try it. I only have two. I didn't sit down. Shit. I already got it.
Is this the boss or is this the boss? Worm is actually his name's worm face. Oh, I hate this
guy. Oh my God. I did so much fucking damage. I got distracted. I got distracted. I did do
so much damage. You just did more. All right. Kill them before you do a move. I'm going,
I gotta stay away. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Don't grab me. You're almost dead.
Okay. Really nice. Very good. Cool. He used magic. Pogchamp. That was cool. Oh, I can go in here
though. Wait, I could have always gone in there. Yes. All right. I've been here. All right. Let's
keep going. I want to look at those tiers, but I want to go the direction of, I want to go up.
I want to go this way towards five. Why is the stream quality weird? You didn't change it from
1080p from Mario. What do you mean? It was 864. It was always 864. All right. I think I can jump
up this. All right. Okay. That looks, that's where I want to go. That's going to take me to. All
right. That's what this bullshit is from. That's the urn tree. That's the big urn tree. I actually,
I really want to see this. I want to know what that's, what the secret is. I want to know what
it is. I guarantee you, I guarantee you we're going to get down there. I'm going to beat the
game and shit. And you're going to come out the birth canal. I'm telling you. Okay. Don't be a
fucking idiot. You might be overleveled weirdo. What am I kidding? Who cares? These guys can't hurt
me. But if they work together, they can blast. They're working together. Alone, I could destroy
them all, but together they're strong. Villain arc. That's literally a villain's speech. I mean,
I'm just speaking factual information. Ooh, that's good. Where is this on the map? Well,
I'm going the way. I'm, I don't want to go this way. Do I? Yeah, I do. I just want to see it.
Capital outskirts. What's the point of this game? Um, this is one of those ever jails right there.
He's back. Wait, why is he back? I don't want to fight this dickhead again.
Oh, tarnished. I'm back as a regular enemy because you're going to kick the shit out of
me and probably four swings. Nope. No, I'm not going to kill him in four swings. I got to remember
how to fight against Margaret, which it's been like, it's been like two weeks.
No, that was so much. It was so greedy to do that. Let's get funky and get funky. Get funky.
Ooh, 905 damage. That was a lot. See you later, Margaret.
Now what? Viridian Amber Medallion plus one. What's that? Greatly raises maximum stamina.
That's kind of a big deal. 13. Was it 13%? He's probably going to come back again.
Maybe. That was cool though. I want that map fragment before I do anything else.
I think I have enough in the map. I'm going to the. Yes, I am. You missed the guy on the ground.
Jesus, that was a, that was a elaborate move. Open your game facts window. Hit him.
What is this hitbox? Yeah. Dude, his hitbox is so weird. It's like, I feel like I'm like swing,
like just like his body that threw his fucking loincloth. Oh my God. What the fuck did you just
put me? Explain the birth canal comment. The birth canal comment was very simple.
Like you're a baby waking up. One of these days I'm going to be right about the baby waking up
comment and you, I'm going to scream when you know it. It's going to be like, oh, this is,
we have, we, we're alive now. We're the baby waking up. I think I'm in trouble here. Can I
get down here from there? Uh-uh. Maybe I can go backwards. Can I go from here? This is a lip. I
can't operate it yet. I jump on this dragon thing yet. Oh, I'm right here too. Really? Oh,
it even did the, just you die no matter what. Oh my God. This is a fucking disaster.
Can I walk there from here? Turn the fucking camera off. I'm being a
weirdo with camera on the camera. I don't want it on. Wait at the bottom of Len Dell,
frenzied flame Lord. That's where it just was. So this is Len Dell underneath Len Dell.
That's kind of cool. All right, let's start the trek all the fucking way back.
Number two on big wall. Um, I think I have to go all the way around. It doesn't matter. I have
to go from that bonfire. Okay. Down this road, just follow the road. I'm not going off the road. No
matter what, just follow the road. No matter what, I'm not going off the road unless for a grace.
No matter what, only for a grace. If I see one on the road, so far so good. I'm very happy with this
outcome. Okay. Good. Things are going good. Watch out for the, they throw shit at you now. Where
did that come from? I got to go fight that guy. I want to go kill that thing. I do need to find a
bonfire through here though. I want to fight that winged guy. I didn't want to kill it this time.
And I got pretty close. It's just, I got all screwed up. I was a cool fight. I want to fight
that thing again. How did I not touch this? How is it possible that I missed this? Was I just so
just dumbstruck by how cool this world was? How did I miss this? That's impossible. Okay. That makes
this a million times easier. This wants me to go over here, but I'm not doing that yet. I need that
map fragment. I lost 50,000 souls, whatever it is. It's fine. I'm going to fight this thing.
This guy back here. I'm going to get him. You'll see. Let's go. Where is he? Where is he? Only R1s.
Oh, come on. Not this shit again. God, man. Fucking relax.
All right. What'd you drop? What do you got? Gargoyles great axe.
There's only three 2500 souls. That's it. That's it. Is that another seed? Seed, seed, seed, seed,
seed. There's another one right here. Then two. Why they just, they give, they give me these way
like candy right now. Oh shit. I missed one up here, but I missed one touch the grace.
It's all the way back up. Oh, okay. So is this the last area or no, there's more here. There's
something else right here. Oh, there's a lot more. Wow. This is ridiculous. This is ridiculous.
There's a ton more underground too. I had two flasks. I had eight golden seeds. Are you shitting
me? I didn't know that. Ten and two. That sounds good. All right. I'm very curious. Look at this.
Okay. Is this shit down here? All right. I think I want to find the way to connect this just to have
the bonfire and connect it. So I'm going to keep going through here because I, I want to find
the connection here. I'm assuming I'm going to be going this way. Not this way. Um, wait, this way.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Oh, through the doors. I'm already going this way. All right. So if I go
up here, because I already have a bonfire, that's all the way up. Is this what you're saying? I
missed one. I did miss one. That's crazy. Okay. This way. All right. Let's go. What the hell are
you guys even doing here anymore? Damn it. They're just chilling. What? Why they just get out of
here. Okay. Can I open the front door? Lost ashes of war. I definitely cannot go in this way. So
there's two ways I can go down to the lake or up and around by the tree. And we're going to go to
the tree anyways, because I want to get the, I want more of the flash shit we're going to wrap
around here. I'm going to check out what's going on in this little thing here. Oh, I'm fine.
Let's go. How's the radish garden going? Um, it's not, it's going pretty good.
That's holding a box. That guy was holding a 12 golden rune. That guy had just a treasure chest.
Hey, we're trying to stun them. Use the nebula, bro. Be one with the stars.
All right. You too. Do use the nebula, bro. Be one with the stars. That's my favorite part
of what you just said. Okay. Up. Ah, I can go up here. Nebula is only good when I'm very
confident that I can get its utilization down. Can't just do it just nilly nilly.
What the fuck is that? Stop. All right. What's up here? I'm weird. Something interesting.
I'm probably right in the middle.
The skulls are alive. I guarantee if I come back here at midnight,
it's going to be a giant skull boss thing here. This is a, you fight something here.
There's no way you don't guide Andy. Nope. I'm just telling you. That's what I think happens.
It might not happen, but that's what I think. Ooh, that's not even from a nerd tree. Okay.
Let's I got to, I got to investigate that shit. What's going on down there.
It's like a little congregation down there. I'm going, let's go. Is that the urtree boss?
I don't know what that is, but I want to go. Come on, come on, come on. I want to go now.
I want to go now. I don't want to wait. Okay. Here we go. What's going on down here.
It is an urtree boss. What was that? What the fuck? Not too much trouble. What do we got?
That's it? Okay. Easy. Yep. Golden sunflower. Oh, that's not the item.
Twiggy cracked tier. Crimson crystal tier. Dungeon. No, I got to look at what these,
some of these are. This guy's cracked out. I'm getting a little tired, but I wouldn't say I'm,
I think I'm the reverse of cracked out right now. I think I cracked out all my potential crack
during the rain age portion of the stream, which was sapped me of all my brain cells.
Oh, okay. That's giant. Very cool. There's definitely a dungeon down here.
Absolutely a dungeon over here somewhere on the edge somewhere. Come on.
It's gotta be one. Come on. Dungeon finding Daniel. Yeah. It's one of the coolest parts
of the whole game. It is in fact, probably the coolest part of the whole game.
All right. Well, you have to stop that now. Oh, he's shooting now where he is. All of you stop.
Oh, please. 1875 damage. Now let's kill this guy. These legs are blocked. We have to play this
smartly. Free hit. We've already fought one of these guys before. Lots of experience.
I forgot about that one. Get over there and hit his hands, please. Gotta be on his left.
Hands down. Come on. Thank you. Yes. He has a hundred trillion health. I know his legs can break.
Did I try that already? He actually hit me with it. Are you full of shit? Are you full of shit or
what? You throw me off my game. I'm just going to fight him the way I know how to fight him.
All right. Now he's dead. No, I want an item. I wanted the item. What did he drop?
Oh my fucking God. What did he have? He just, you just get the axe. Really? That's it?
I swear those guys have a chance to drop something better. Their helmet or something.
Like their armor. No, don't even say it. Don't tell me. Cause now I'm like realizing like,
that doesn't make any sense. How would I wear that? It would be huge.
I want a bonfire before I go over there. Ooh, there isn't one. Really?
That looked like you could land on that. That looked not that far away.
And he's like, go all, get straight down. You and I just died at the exact same time.
Was that the same place? That would be funny. Okay. Well, I'm going to go fight this thing,
whatever it is. You can drop a crystal. What was it? You can drop rainbow stone to see if you'll die
from a drop. I can't believe I didn't know that. That's such amazing info. I can drop a stone off
and if the stone shatters, then I die. What? Okay. Well, thanks for the tip.
VR Josh tried to share this info before. Fuck. All right. Let's go fight this guy up here.
I should be able to do it. Let's go. You tell me there's not another bonfire like right here
or somewhere sitting right here. Not a bonfire. Has to be one. Has to be. Right? Maybe not.
Ah, okay. I didn't, what? I didn't see it. How did I not see it? I walked right over here.
All right. Tree sentinel version two. Let's go. Draconic tree sentinel actually is.
We got new moves. I'll be foolish. It's not hard. My God. Can I outrun it? If I just keep
running in a direction. Oh, it feels good when you get the fucking fully charged one. Do it again.
Oh, fuck. All right. Run, run, run. Holy fucking moly. That does a lot of damage.
Run, run. Oh, come on. I figured maybe I tried off the horse, but it's way harder off the horse.
It's not that bad. I got it done. I love how colorful the game is. The game is beautiful.
Eternal darkness. Does that do anything? Well, that catches his crazy beam thing.
I have one. Thank God for getting it out of the way. We're going with the other strat.
All the kill him strat. Take them all down. I didn't get away. Why make that a confirmation?
Okay. From software. Listen to me. Listen to me very carefully from software. Very carefully.
If I am going to select, if I'm going to select that item and hit and hit X,
why are you giving me a confirmation where I have to press it on the button to do it?
Why? Why? I have to select it on my inventory menu. Why can I not just do it? Why do I have
to confirm that I want to do it and hit left on the fucking D pad? It's the guy from The Simpsons.
Who's the professor from The Simpsons? Come on, quick. Fucking, it's so huge.
Fuck you, dude. It's too big. That splash damage is fucking outrageous. Three times in a row.
The fucking same boulder. Hold on. Hold on. Wait. I'm not ready to die. I'm not ready to die.
I've walked into the same boulder three fucking times. I've ran into that fucking boulder.
Come on. I'm not ready to die. I'm not ready to die yet.
Oh, he lost his magical juice. All right. I got to kill him. No. You cannot run it. You cannot run
it. I was frozen in fear. Use magic. It takes so long to cast. I'm off my horse. I could have
like switched to the thing, but like I was so afraid to cast because I thought he was going
to do that move where he fucking shoots the lighting at me. Why do I have it? All right.
This is, this is an, okay, listen. This is an int scaling weapon. I'm doing int and dex.
You understand? You understand? This is, this is, this weapon. People, okay, people think that I'm
just like swinging with no stats. I'll get it. I'll get it. I just frozen fucking fear
and hitting, holding Y and pressing R1 and then cycling through my spells to cast and stand still
for two seconds. It's not something I was prepared to do. Falling off the horse with no flasks and
he's got the lightning shit. Okay. I wasn't prepared for it. Okay. You actually can't get
away from that. You have to go forward. You might have to go forward. I wonder maybe to run forward.
Act. Nope. How do you get away from that? Do I just have to fight him off the horse in this phase?
Probably what I have to do. Cause that's like almost seems bad to be on the horse.
Can you jump? I don't know. They come from the sky. Just jump off the horse when it happens
and jump back on. That's going to get me killed though. That's right. Really? That took so fucking
long. Horse has eye frames. Getting back on the horse. Yeah. I'll get off the horse and get on
the horse when he casts it. Right? I feel like I'm, I'm doing the horse dash right when it happens
and it still hits me. Like the horse dash only lasts as long to dodge like the first two because
he goes like one, two, three, four, getting off. Yeah. I'll get off and get on. See if that works.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Oh, this is, I have, did I do it? I think it worked. No shit. It's just
so hard to be able to, that's weird though. It's hard to cycle through that much. It's hard to know
when he's going to do it. Okay. Here we go. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Do the thing. Wait,
there was no eye frame. What? When did the, when did the eye frame start? When did the eye frame
start? Do you honestly think I don't know the horse has a dodge 65 hours into the game? You've
seen me do it like a hundred times. You can't dodge them all. He's turning. Oh shit. He's turning.
He just growled at us. He just turned and growled. Okay. I need to get my bearings.
Okay. We're good. Okay. Okay. I'm going to beat him. I can't laugh too hard. Of course I know
the horse has a dodge. I've, I've pressed it probably 5,000 times in the course of the last
two weeks. I'm going to die. So that was really funny. I would like to continue to play the game.
That would be swell. Why would it just do this? This fucking guy can't even hurt me.
What's happening? Why am I, why can I kill him like this? He didn't hit me once.
All right. Look dodge. He's full of blood. Yeah. Cause I'm laughing my ass off. Don't listen to
what anybody on the internet says. Just stay at his butt and you won't get hit once. Just literally
don't, you know, just stay up with, just stay up his ass the whole game. It's so finicky. Do you see
how finicky it is? From software. I wonder from software. What I want to do is from software. Do
I want to get on the horse? That's fun. What do you say? And I said, please for the love of God.
Please for the love of God use glintstone pebbles. They've been an upbeat dragon that
lands on this bridge from everyone. You growled at us. I need to see it. I have to see it. I need
to see it. Is this it? Hold on. We need to watch this. I need to examine this. Cause I, I don't
know what the fuck. I don't know what the fuck happened. Oh my fucking God. I look like a weirdo.
Oh my God, dude.
What? Why does it sound so weird? What is it sound so weird? What's wrong with this?
Why do I sound like a, is that what I sound like?
Why do I sound like a fucking cave troll? Oh, it haven't. It doesn't sound much better.
He's like, he's turning. Oh shit. He's turning. He just growled at us.
Oh my fucking God, dude. Somebody said Tim the tool man. But honestly, man, when somebody asks
you, when somebody says, Hey dude, do you know there's a dodge in the game? It's like, bro.
Yes. Fundamental part of the whole game. Oh, all right. That was, that was very funny.
That was a very fun time. Let's take a second here. Let's take a second and relax. That was
very fun. That's so fucking funny though. You know, it's funny. Like you pick up, let me give
you some, let me, here's some streamer insight. Okay. When the streamers mad, like very mad and
the streamer looks over and sees just picks out the one comment. That's just like, Hey yo, bro.
Like maybe you should go back to fucking Mario tennis. It's just like, Oh, you fucker. You
motherfucker. Don't say that to me right now. I'm in the middle. I'm getting my ass kicked.
You're the only person that does that. No, no way. That was fucking wild. Okay. That was fun.
I'm glad you all enjoyed that. That was a good time. I want to see what's in this room.
35 Vigor. I'm not the most unhinged Elden Ring streamer, right? Like I'm not. I can't be.
There's like, there's thousands of streamers that are like crazy, right? I'm not crazy. I'm,
it can't, I can't be the craziest guy. Everybody growls at their audience, right? And then like
it turns purple and I turned, I turned purple. Has any streamer played Elden Ring and turns purple?
Uh, maybe I should stop playing. Maybe I should stop playing Elden Ring. Like yo dude, um,
that's probably not healthy to turn like a dark purple while you're sitting in your chair.
You know, they probably got, you're probably right. All right. I'm gonna fucking lose my mind.
Okay. You're turning into Grimace. So was there anything else in this room? I'm in the castle
now, which is cool, bro. Oh, my stomach hurts from laughing. I can't believe I actually growled at
you. I like, I like growled at you. That was like animalistic. Like what was that? Oh my God.
What a fucking weirdo. You growled at like 10 to 12,000 people. Sky Live? I kind of feel,
I feel bad for doing that. How come you're so shiny? Dude, if that's your, if that's your
actual question, if that's your question as to why I'm shiny, maybe it's the beads of sweat
going down the crack of my ass right now. It could have something to do with that.
I'm sure it has something to do with it. Another bonfire. All right. We haven't heard from her in
a while. This is the base of the Erd Tree. Wait, so we had to bring her to the tree?
Why couldn't she just walk here? Why couldn't you just come here? Isn't this,
I'm about to be maidenless. Yeah. Okay. Well, thanks for, thanks for everything. I want to read
this. Okay. Equipment load. What's the utilization on this? Rank that to get temp equipment load.
Why would you, it seems weird. Rank that and then put on a great axe or something. Briefly stop
rune loss on death. What? Really? That seems insane. So if you know you're going to die,
you just chug that and you don't lose your souls. That's like an oh shit button. I wonder how long
it lasts. Enhanced charged attacks for a time. That's pretty good. It's 10 seconds. I wonder what
it would pair with because you don't want to, you really want to do it with, that's like the,
I'm going to die button. I don't know. Maybe just the heal, just in case. It's three minutes. Well,
that changes everything. Okay. So why would, yeah, just drink that right before you get into a boss
room. Yeah. I'm going to keep it like this. Very cool. So she's like, oh, I'm going to leave you
now. Cause now we're at the base of the urn tree. She's over here. Lynn, Lindell, royal capital.
All right. This is cool. Very cool. It's kind of creepy. These guys are terrible. I mean,
you're really cool looking. They're actually, I like these enemies a lot, but what the fuck are
you doing, man? They like crabs, white flesh. Whoa. Oh my God. Good move for here. Good move
for here. Yeah. Oh, check the ax out. Yeah. Where is it? Gargoyle's great ax. No, where is it?
Dragon claw, dragon, great claw. Like a turkey bone. Wreath with lightning. Can I check it out?
It's not faith weapon. It's just a strength weapon. That's pretty cool. Oh, I got a shield too.
You're right. Dragon. This is a lightning shield imbued with lightning. Damn. Very cool.
Exceptionally cool. I don't know what that thing is, but I'm not going close to this guy.
I have a lot of runes. Maybe when you growled at us. I remember, trust me, I love inside of here.
7k is not a lot. No, I mean these are what I'm talking about. I have quite a few of those.
I want to check this out. Invoiced horn. You can actually use one of these horns?
Is this sorcery? No, it's a faith weapon. Oh, you can blow the bubbles too. That's so awesome.
It doesn't work. No, stop. You're getting spit all in it. No, you're doing it wrong.
Give me back. Take over here. Yeah. Really? Don't do it. Don't do it. Please don't do it.
I am begging you. Don't do it. I'm trying. I'm just trying. What's the chest piece? This chest
piece is the mausoleum knight armor. It's pretty cool. It's pretty good. Been very good so far.
I do love these internal areas though. They're awesome. Very pretty. Very cool. I like the kind
of overgrowth. Looks interesting. All right, so that wrapped all the way around. I guess we're
just going to go that way. The growl. The growl incident. It went that way. There we go. Okay.
I'm going to say let's go this way first. Somebody's behind me. Did you block that too?
Yeah, that was greedy. Where's the nearest bonfire? Right here. Okay.
Are you going to do nintendogs? I do like the flail. It's starting to show that it's very good.
I'm going to get it to plus 10. You bet your ass. There's a lever. The weapon art is amazing.
All right, let's try that again. What? Is there something in the front door? These guys are alive
so let's change that. Okay, remind me that there's a ladder in this room, please.
Hmm. I like this area a lot. Let me just check and see what's up here.
Ooh, that was a pretty good hiding spot for this. Fume bottle. I have like two or three of these.
This place looks like a dream for people that like to jump around and parkour in random places.
I can already see a dozen different ways to go. I'm going to get a bubble on them. All right,
I'll get my souls. I'm just going to. There might be something right here.
Shit. Is the ladder in that room? I just went up it. Make me growl. Don't make me growl again.
Upper class robe. Right green robe worn by noble children.
Donning such a robe is traditionally the child's first show of burgeoning independence.
There's a lot of magic details. Why does this fit? I feel like that shouldn't fit.
Ooh, wait a minute. Okay, what's this? Ah, that's this is where I was.
This is where I fought that guy. Down here. Down there. Okay, let's not make the same mistake twice.
Good opener. Oh, what an opener. So fucking good. Who cares about Katana who? Katana who, huh?
Katana who? So what's in here? It's not a door. That looks like a door.
Jesus. Don't get greedy. Look at this space. What the fuck am I doing?
What's the range? What's the range, man? How far can I do that?
He was far. I thought he couldn't go that far with that old bullshit. It's just wherever you are.
All right. Well, let me get back out there. God damn it's a far run.
Like I'm close to a bonfire there. How late am I going? Uh, probably another hour.
And you just distracted me, which is going to cost me all my souls.
I want that person timed out. Yep. I'm fucking screamer again.
I can just jump into there. All right. I just jump. Is it safe for me just to jump to this
and fall? I don't have to wait for the elevator. Stop fucking this up. Beautiful. Okay. There's
nothing else over here. There's a guy right here. Wondering why I killed that guy in case I have to
kite this guy out. I don't want to bump into that guy. Oh shit. Damn. Damn. What the fuck?
Hey, those guys are horrible. Those guys are nuts. Why do people keep saying better gamer
chair? What's that mean? Better gamer chair, better gamer chair. Why are you saying that?
What does it mean? Where is this? This is down in this weird lobby. It's, it's he kills me or I
kill him. Sorry guys. I know it was a beautiful flute song, but the beautiful flute song turns
into a little fucking like shoe knife that he's like and sticks it in my neck.
Not these guys breaking through the wall. Somebody come through the wall.
2500 damage. What burst burst damage. Damn man. How much somebody else alive down here?
Where are they? Yep. So what do you got? What do you hide in here? What's in here?
Forming stone and ruin or the down. There's a, okay. There's a night standing there.
How many little corridors to go in? I don't know which one is the right one. There's somebody to do.
I killed him already. There's so much cool shit over here. Wait, this is just back out here.
Remember, did you eat? I took a 20 minute, 25 minute break or so in the middle of this stream
and I had food. I ate and it was good. I'm good to go till the end of the stream. All right. This
guy's going to be a pain in the ass. Does he see me already or no? Can I get behind him?
Is it open from this side? What? Oh well. All right. We're going right down main street here.
I don't like this without a bonfire. I don't like this without some kind of bonfire to get to.
That one's going to jump down here. Dude, I don't, I don't like this. I need a bonfire.
I'm going back this way. Come on right here. Is this a shortcut? Wait, this is the front door.
I think this is the front door to get in. No, it's not. Why the fuck would I think that? Is
there a bonfire? I just need a bonfire. That's all I need. Turn around, turn around, turn around,
turn around. I will. I will. I'll turn around. Don't worry. I thought that was a tank. I was
like, why is that? This is weird. Why would there be a like a like world war two tank? That was
kind of weird looking. All right. So this is, this is not the right way then. But,
uh, so I got to go this way, but there's no bonfire. This, this dragon is going to come
to life. It's going to break out of the stone and jump down and have two twin blades. And it's going
to be awful. I could try going this way, which is, that's precisely what I'm going to do.
I'm going to go the other way. This goes up, goes down. Uh, um, okay. Oh, can't make that jump.
Fuck. There's a guy up there. I am begging you. I don't know. Uh, I don't know what you're begging
me. I missed it. I didn't see what you said. Begging you. Ooh, nice. What's that? What's that?
Okay. Nothing. Nothing to be concerned with. That linger is such a long time too. That move is so
goddamn good. All right. I can go down. I think this is the boss. Uh, no, no, no, I'm not ready.
I'm not ready. I'm not ready. I'm not ready. I'm not ready. I'm not ready. I'm not ready. I'm not
ready. Come here. In here. In here. I'm not ready. I'm not ready. Oh shit. There's one of these guys.
Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Don't do it. You fuck. The timings. I just was, he, I did not expect him
to be in this room. He goes bang, bang, bang, bang. I didn't think he's going to do more than twice
or three times. He did four times in a row. I have no idea where the fuck that is. Good luck finding
that shit. It's in this labyrinth down here. Uh, I think I just jumped on the roof.
We begged you. Uh, what are you begging me? Please. Oh, did you do that? Fine. Fine. Fine.
Fuck you. What is it? What? What is that? What? He was going to just keep, he was going to chase
me through the whole goddamn labyrinth and I, I just, just, I did, I stopped running because
it was like this guy's not going to stop. He has a lightning move that if he has line of sight,
he can just ping me with it if my back is turned and I'm going to get hit by it and I'm just going
to be fucking infuriating. And then we got this random dickhead over here. Is this death? No.
Okay. That's how you do it. Stop. Okay. So now where am I at now? There's more shit over here.
Okay. This is that kind of just main road. I went over there. That guy scared the shit out of me.
I'm going to go back over there and I'm going to fight him after I get these items.
These are worth getting, man. This is like 10, 20,000 ruins each. Each. Easy. A thousand
damage almost fully charged. All right. So that's that way. I'm going to just gently drop down here.
Just check over here. Yeah, of course. There could be something down here. There is. There's a
mushroom. What's up, boys? No, no, no lightning. Thank God. He's stuck in the tree. What the fuck,
dude? Wow. Are you a leaf? Killed that guy already. I'm just making sure, you know,
lose your area. Well, I should have drank this thing. I keep forgetting. I have it.
Imped faith is too faith for putting it on. That's pretty cool. All right. Now let me go
to where that scary night was. He was down here. Okay. All right. Here we go. Let's see if I can
beat him. Can't backstab him. Holy shit. Damn you. Damn you pile of a damn that. Wait, did I do a
Stewie? Heroes rune five. That was fucking nuts. Okay. I have enough to level up probably three or
four times. Is there anything else down here? What's this? Still going? Uh, yeah. I'm in it
for a little while longer. Or cut please. Oh my God. There's a door here. Oh wow. Thank goodness.
Just like the old days of dark souls. A skip that goes across the whole thing. Thank God. All right.
It's time to do some, uh, rune smashing. Abundance of runes. 35,000 souls. Damn.
We're going to be a level up probably twice. I need like a hundred and something thousand to
level up two times. That should do it. What do we need? Okay. Uh, I think the play is just to get to,
I think it's just to get to 40 vigor, get to the soft cap and a couple into endurance. I think. Uh,
okay. I'll just kill a few things. The off cap is 60. It is. I thought it was 40, 50 something
thousand. Remember it is. Come here. Stop moving around so much. 51, four, seven, eight. I got
enough. Let's go. Thank God I got that door. I didn't even know that existed either. Okay. Let's go
37 vigor. I want to get this to 40 and then I'll cap it. 50 intelligence.
What does soft cap mean? Soft cap means that for every point you put it into,
into it after the soft cap, you get less than you normally did all the way through 40 to 60,
whatever it is. So the soft cap is 60. That means after 60 at 61, you're getting a reduced amount
per point you put in. So they always tell you, you know, guides, Reddit, gamers,
is to try to get to the soft cap and then get something else up and then,
you know, pound out something past the soft cap into the hard cap or gaps in 99. Right. All right.
I'm going straight down here. I want to fight that oratory avatar. It's right here. It just appears
out of nowhere. Oh, my souls. Oh, magic Mario Odyssey build. What used to gain an enormous
abundance of ruins. Is that a hundred thousand? It's probably 50. Oh yeah. 50 K right there.
Hell yeah. I want that item. I'm still, I don't think I don't see you over there.
All right. Okay. What happened here? Spitting stone and then I want to get this.
Holy grease. Please do your best Mario Yahoo. Now I've been streaming for 10 hours, man. I'm,
I ain't going to get a Yahoo out of me right now. I'm sorry. I haven't had my chapstick.
I've been licking my lips all day. Would you please make a sound effect
so we know that you're all right? Yeah. Oh, all right. Don't be greedy here. Just
I can grab it and run, grab it and run, grab it and run. In fact, why not use sorcery?
Ones of ruins here. They really want you to level up. Don't they? Holy shit.
Can you run here from the beginning of the game? Can you, can you just get here? Sort of. What if
you just ran around and just didn't fight anything and just picked up like 300,000 souls worth of
ruins and then leveled up like 30 times and just wet the floor with the whole game. Oh, you have to
beat the horse guy. Yeah. Nevermind. That's not going to happen. That's true. All right. Was that
all that was up here? Yes, it was. Where am I? Where am I? Where am I? Where am I? Where am I?
Where am I? What happened? Where'd I go? Where did I just go? I went back to like the beginning.
Oh, don't do it. Oh, oh. Oh, he de-aggroed. Hell yeah. Fuck you. That's a bad, that's bad.
That's very bad. Let me get it off. Oh, stop it. Ah, somebody's shooting a bow and arrow like a dick.
Look at you in there. You're so fucking good. Weasley coward. I see. All right. We're doing
like the sewer. Kick the ladder down. Oh, dear God. Uh, fuck it. Still hurts. Wasn't as scary as he
looked. Omen smirk mask? What was that? Whoa. Mask with long hideously twisted horns worn by the
Omen killers increases strength. That is pretty ugly. I don't need strength. All right. So what
was that for? Oh, nice. All right. I can level up again. Lionel's helm. Lionel's armor.
Who's Lionel? Death bed dress. Who's Lionel? Worn by Lionel the Lionhearted. Wait, he was part,
he was at the Redan fight. But heavy load. Still heavy. I don't think I can, I don't have enough
endurance to put any of this on. It's cool though. I could put the gloves on. Sure, why not? I cannot
put the gloves on. Never mind. Too heavy. Still fat rolling. What? What did I put on? Oh, it was
the Godric soldier grooves. Okay, there we go. Did you go to sleep? Uh, I have a feeling there's
probably something right down here. I'll give it a 10th or two and then we'll probably call it.
Let's crush this. Damn. So many. I'm telling you a figure to 40. I think I can get there.
Let's be 20, 30, 30,000. Almost there. All right. Whatever. Okay. I rested here. That was pretty
cool. Sewer. This guy's back. He's just a regular enemy. He's not scary. You're done. Dude, you're
put on the dress. Um, I could look at it. I didn't even see what it did. That was a missed click.
Are you in here? Really? Get out of here. You couldn't even fit through the fucking door.
Don't even aggro him. Just go. What are you hiding in here? I think you just cashed out
all the ruins. I know it was stupid. Okay, here we go. Whatever it is. Wait, we're already, we're
Oh, it's this thing. It's this thing. Right. Okay. Let's go. This is the rot one. Oh,
oh, he's in the fucking wall. No, that's a different move. Oh, he got me. He got me in his mouth.
No, survive it. Survive it. Prove me wrong. Jesus. Fuck you with this weird bendy neck.
Hey, yes. Okay. Golden seed. That boss looks like beyond meat. Did you say that or did he make that
up? Somebody actually say that? All right. So he dropped a golden seed. They're just throwing.
This is just like the boss. Enemies are enemies that are regular enemies here. What's that?
Pulsarated worm. Yeah. I have fought that thing a couple of times before. All right. So that's all
that's over here. Listen, missing something, right? Anything else that he was guarding? Well,
I'm going to level up. Put the dress on. What do you want? Where is it? Slowly replenishes
the HP of nearby allies. It heals. That's pretty cool. All right. Now, now where? Can't level up
yet. Should I keep going down the street? Go down the main street. Okay. Uh, where the hell was that?
I went down to the sewer. My Lord. Not over fucking here. How did I get there? What's this?
Oh, right. There's a bonfire. Let me just go sit at the bonfire and then come out and walk down the
street. Do you feel okay? I feel all right. I'm definitely, it's definitely getting close to,
I'm probably going to call it soon here. It looks so red. Yeah, I know. Let me just go back.
Why am I running? Do I have aggro? Why do I have aggro? Okay. So what bonfire is the best one?
This one here. Yeah, I'm, I'm very red, very sweaty, a little tired and a half hours. That's not,
it's not too, I mean, that's long. Okay. I'm going to go right down the main street.
I would imagine that within the next 20 minutes, we're probably going to stop.
Look dead. Yeah, I'll stop soon. Don't worry. I'm fine. Trust me. I'm fine. I would tell you if I
wasn't, it's just an intense gamer session. Plus I have a light here. This is like an orange light.
So it's making me look a little more red. Okay. So you're saying go all the way down here,
straight through into the store. Yeah, I remember this. Okay. See what we can do. I can go in there.
Wait, I was going to say, is that a bonfire? It is. This would be handy if I knew what this was.
So is there something down here? It's a dick move. Oh, that's a dick move. And they got a guy back
there shooting arrows. Of course they do. Both of you. I don't care. Ash of War Thunderbolt.
Okay, this is a new place. This is a new zone almost. Is he looking this way? I think he is.
Yeah, he's not. Get the items. And if there's anything else down here, I'll take it.
Oh my. Whoops. All right, we're going down here. All right, I'm almost close to a level.
And daggers. Birdsteel dagger. That's new. What does this go into? Broken colossal weapon damage
on that? Oh, I just snuck behind everything. Whoa. Whoa. Jesus. I guess I'm going to do this.
This is massive material. Gravelstone? Somebody's shooting at me and I know from where
I make that. I can land here. Yeah. Lunark. Shit. Okay. Okay. Be careful. I don't want to lose.
I don't want to lose these, so I'm going to drink this. Take them off the edge.
Gravelstone? Lindell Knight armor. Wow. Jeez. Whoa. This place is massive. This is huge. Wow.
I'll take that. I can go down that way. But let's take it. All right. There's another bonfire.
Perfect. Exactly what I wanted. I need to literally sneeze on one thing. Do I have any?
I don't want to use that. All right. Well, that guy's scary, so we're going to go over here first.
Cane sword. Love sword of an aged knight whose last quest was long behind him.
Repurposed into a walking stick. Cool. Looks like... I'm curious. How does it swing? It looks like a
Minecraft sword. This looks like it wouldn't hurt very much. Like a fire poker. This doesn't really
look that dangerous. It's cool though. All right. This looks interesting. Whatever it is. Okay. This
is actually perfect. I'm going to level up. I'm going to see if there's a boss right here.
If there is no boss right here within 30 seconds of this bonfire, I'm going to call it.
Is this a lever? Did that open this door? Did that open the gate underneath me? Oh,
shit. That's definitely a boss. Yeah. Without a doubt. Let's go see who it is.
I'm going to level up first. Let's just see if it is. I'm going to check right now.
I'm going to hopefully don't kill me. All right. So what's down here?
Dude, this is a boss. This is a boss, dude. Who the hell am I?
Ooh. Al. Albarich's pointed hat. How do these people die? Strengthens thorn sorcery.
The robe looks awesome. Where is it? Yeah. Look at this. That looks cool. That looks cool,
but not for me. At least not right now. This is the guy from the round table,
the basement of the round table. Oh, is this the round table?
This looks like the round table. Wait, but if this is the round table, then
where the hell have we been teleporting to? Painting table of lost grace. I don't get it.
Like the hunter's dream. Interesting. It's the real one. All right. I'm out of gas.
This is a whole nother. There's a whole nother like ton of explanation.
Explanation exploration is what I meant to say, but I will get the items because they're right here.
The two fingers prayer book. I scared the shit out of myself. I heard something skittering around.
Oh yeah, this is the round table. That's cool. All right. As much as I want to keep going,
after turning purple at that upgraded tree sentinel, I think it's time to stop.
That was really cool. Is there a boss that's like right here that I can see?
Like right here? I feel like I'm really close. I just want to see it. I just want to see it.
Right here is a dog. Keep going. And this is fucking crazy. I'll explore this better next time.
All the way. How am I? Stupid. All right. I'm going to explore this later. I just want to see
the boss. There's a bonfire like right here. It probably is odd free. The first Elden Lord.
Why is he a shade? You got some fucking moves. Don't you? God. Oh my God. He's so susceptible
to that move. Wow. That's an 1100 fucking damage. Jesus Christ. I'm burning through all my shit.
I got it. I got it. I got it. I'm going to beat him. I'm going to beat him. I'm going to beat him.
He's not, his timing's not that hard. I got it. I got it. I got it right here.
I got it. I got it. Don't worry. I got it. I got it. I'm going to get him. What? Oh, okay. Right.
All right. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. I got it. I got it. I got it. Just dodge. That's it. Just
dodge him. Blocked it. Fuck you. I'll do it and I'll do it again. That was a mistake.
The baby rattles the best weapon in the game. 80 fucking thousand ruins. Holy shit.
Do the next boss. This one right here. Are you serious? New talisman slot, dude. Oh my God.
That's actually, this is going to take me a while to figure that out. All right. I got,
I'll just see what the, I'll just look at the boss. I'm just going to look at the boss.
I don't know what you want to do. Maybe just like the FP. I'll put it on for now. All right. So you're
saying that there's another boss on the HP one. I, I don't want to lose these ruins though.
This is a lot of ruins to lose. Do I need to level up these six? Hold on. Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I'm almost there. Just, oh, I can use the flask. That's right. Okay.
I forgot about the flask. All right. So just wait, just check out the boss.
We rest here and you're saying there's just another one right here. This is actually it
though. Like I'm just going to literally walk in and just fight it for five seconds.
Just up the branch, up those stairs. Wait, let go up that branch. Wait, there's an item over here.
All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. So you're saying there's a boss up here.
That's pretty crazy that this back to back boss is, where's he at? Just here. Okay. Yeah,
this definitely is boss. All right. I'm going to drink the thing. Oh, we both have the same idea.
Is that it? More? That's a pre-boss. What about my flask? Is my flask still active?
How was the, that was a pre-boss. Is it, is it actually a boss? Are you guys fucking with me?
I was thinking of the urn tree. Damn. Oh, that actually is. Okay. All right. So that was a
pre-boss. All right. Drink the flask. What's in here? This is the base of the fucking urn tree.
Is it Margit again? Margit for a third time. This is, he's like Kael'thas at this point.
All right. It clones.
We haven't seen half of these people yet.
Is my drink running out by the way in this cutscene? I hope not. Margit.
Oh, now it's actually. What's this guy's problem?
What's his name? Morgoth? No, fuck you. It's going to hurt. Oh man. Oh fuck. I thought I had it.
I'm just too tired. Oh, I'm just too tired. When we got down to like the last 40%, I just was like,
fuck man. It was like colors. Oh, damn it. Oh, if I had 11 more matcha powder in my vape.
One more try. One more try. I thought I had it too. Damn it. Oh, oh, I'm too tired.
Why can't it be like hour number three instead of hour number 11? Oh, thought I dodged it.
Oh, sloppy, sloppy, sloppy, sloppy, sloppy. Damn. Oh, I was so close on the first try.
I almost did it. I was going to be such a fucking gamer. I was going to be such a gamer.
I was going to be best gamer moment 2022. All right. Actual final try. I promise. If I don't,
it doesn't matter. Actual final try. I promise. Use your summons. Oh, I don't have anything.
I was so close. I thought I did it. I didn't do it, mom. Sorry. All right. Let's get him. Oh,
double. Oh my God. We're kicking the shit out of him. Oh my God. Beat his ass. What the fuck? Oh
my God. Why wouldn't I do this the first time? Get him. Get him. Get him. Get him. Jump him. Not
yet. Not yet. Not yet. Get him. Oh my God. That was so easy. That was so easy with the summon.
What? That was so fucking simple with the summon. We just beat the shit out of him. We just comboed
him. The mimic got the last hit. What the fuck? That was so intense and so hard and so ridiculous.
I just rang a bell and a guy came and fucking kicked the shit out of him.
Okay. All right. That was really cool. Mimic is fucking unbelievable. Are you fucking kidding me?
That was insane. All right. Well, I almost beat him first try. Oh, and then I rang the bell and
somebody else came in and beat him for me. All right. That's actually the end of the fucking
scream. I'm done. That was nuts. All right. So you tried to be Elden Lord and didn't work.
Oh, he's dead. All right. So you tried to be Elden Lord. That didn't do anything.
There's another boss behind the door. Check it out. No, I don't know. I'm out of here. I can't
leave. Why can't I leave? This is not okay. This is not a boss back behind you, right?
Impenetrable thorns refuse all. None may enter the urd tree.
Can't go on the urd tree. Why not? I'll level up. All right. That was crazy. I'm so glad I had a
mirror of myself to come in and fucking help. What are you doing here?
Converse with you. You were unable to enter the tree prevented by the mantle of the thorns
are impenetrable a husk of the trees being that spurns all that exists without the only way to
stand before the Elden ring. I'm telling you right now, the Elden Lord is having trouble with this
game. I'll get the mimic. So I'd like you to undertake a new journey with me to the flame of
ruin far above the cloud upon the snowy mountain tops of the giants. Then I can set the tree a
flame. Burn the urd tree down the path. I don't trust a word. I don't trust anything this lady's
saying. A red mark was made on the map. Okay. So now we're going to do 50 intelligence.
That's what I want. Oh, where is it on the map? I'm curious. So it is another area. All right.
That's it. That's it. I'm going to bed. But honest to God, if you're having a lot of trouble with
this game and you're like, dude, I can't fucking do it. I just can't do it. If you're been,
if you've been hitting your head against a wall, just going, I keep losing this guy 100 times. I
actually can't play the game. I actually can't do it. That mimic really made that fight very,
very manageable and not, I wouldn't say the word is like the words, not easy, but like manageable.
I am going to try to beat most of the encounters in this game without that because I feel like that
was, uh, I did not think it was going to do that much damage. I really did not think that was going
to be that ridiculous. That's the first time I've used that item. I leveled it up like five or six
times or seven times. Maybe I, that's the first time I've used it as a boss and just watched him
kill the boss. That was ridiculous. Mimic is really OP. It makes every single boss that easy. Really
damn. But I mean, but seriously though, like if you, if you're having like a lot of trouble
and you just kind of, you really want to be able to progress and you really want to go level up,
go get the mimic, that'll help you. They will. Um, I probably won't be using it for the remainder
of the time that I play the game. Not that I, not that I'm looking down on it or anything. I just,
I, I thought I, I almost beat that guy first try. Uh, so I'm only going to use it if I really need
it. Really, really, really need it. Not every boss. Some are fucking insane. Yeah. Again,
I'm not looking down on using the item. I, uh, if I can do it without it, I'm going to try to do it
without it. You'll be using it on commander Neil. Okay. Well, good to know. Uh, all right. Same with
the Katana. No, I mean, like everything is viable. You don't, you don't, don't let anybody tell you,
you can't use a certain item. If you, if you haven't fun and you're playing through the game,
then use it. There's no reason not to, right? Uh, I think the most fun I've had in the game so far,
I think I can give this an assessment, a real review, like of sorts. The most fun I've had in
the game has not been at the boss fights, like the main story fights. It's been exploring the world.
It's been finding a dungeon. It's been getting killed somewhere in a spot that you're like,
holy shit, where even am I? I love the areas. I love the actual huge open world as hard as it is
and as crazy as it's been, right? Um, I actually liked that more than the actual boss fights.
So, but yeah, I'm going to try to beat step on my own. I'm going to try to beat it without
using too many of the, uh, powerful summons or anything. We'll see if I can do it. But yeah,
that was ridiculous. I'm glad I at least got to kill it and I will see you guys. The next stream
is going to be, well, interestingly enough, uh, it will be Saturday, although I will not be
streaming. I am going to be at the streamer awards. So you're probably going to see me.
I'm going to be presenting one of the awards. Hopefully I look okay in a suit. Hopefully I
look all right. Uh, uh, it's going to be fun. Looking forward to it. Jano's nominated for two
awards. We'll see what happens. I mean, I, that'd be cool, but there's tons of great nominees. So
it's, it's very, very competitive from what I would, uh, what I would assume.
Very good nominees. You're handsome. Hey, yeah, I'm going to do all the side stuff too,
or at least a lot of it. So I will be back on my channel on the 14th or the 15th. Even I and the
sus either that Monday or Tuesday trying to figure out when I will actually be around the stream.
Sorry for turning out purple, although that was probably very funny. I hope you got a laugh.
Don't growl again. I won't. I promise. All right. I, uh, I'm going to let the credits play out.
Oh, that's right. I put that in there. I'm going to save the game. I'm going to be right here.
Thanks so much for watching guys. This was a long one. I planned for it to be long cause I knew that
I wasn't going to be around for like six days probably. And I've been trying to stream this
game a lot cause I think it's great. I think it's amazing, but I will see you guys later.
If you're going to watch streamer awards, go ahead and watch it. It'll be on cutie Cinderella's
channel. I have a fantastic evening, of course, rest of your night. I'm going to get some sleep.
I got a lot to do tomorrow. Yeah. And I'm going to let this play out.
I didn't mean for that to play us out, but it did. Is this the longest stream? No,
my longest stream. I think was 14 hours is Lord of the rings. Uh, the two towers
mauled of the rings.
Simpsons was close. Simpsons. I think was 12, 12 and a half, 13. All right. I'll see you guys later.
Thanks for all the subs everybody. I haven't really been paying too much attention to anything
that's coming through a brain's been focused pretty much the whole time. So what is,
let me ask you this. Those of you that has to finish the game, what remains if, okay,
let's say I were to walk down the main story campaign hallway and you just go down the main
story campaign, how much is left? What'd you say? I'll be around somewhere on 80% done. Okay.
Maybe like two or three streams. There's a, there's another map. There's another. Yeah.
God, this game is so big. I'll be about 15 to 20 hours. Okay. So I'll do it. I'll come. I'll
finish it on stream. At least I'll try to still about the still four main bosses remaining.
Really? I was thinking two. All right. Good night guys. I'll see you later. Catch me on
the streamer awards. Have a great evening. Have a great weekend. Take care of yourselves. Good night.