Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
This is gonna be a demo man with the demo night setup. This is just a quick little prelude.
I got a bunch of multi-kills in a row. Just wanted to briefly show them before we got into the actual
gameplay. The actual gameplay is like three and a half minutes or something, and you guys all know
me. I do not like having less than three or four five minute gameplays, which is why this is here.
And I gotta ask, how was your Christmas? Hope you got what you wanted, hope you gave some things
to your friends and family as well, because it's not just about getting, it's about giving guys.
And the only real holiday that's left in the year is New Year's Eve. And New Year's Eve, if you're
over 21, New Year's Eve potentially is the best holiday of the year. Only because there is so
much stuff going on, so many parties, so many bars are open really late, it's just awesome.
And even if you're under 21, even if you're not old enough to drink and go to a bar, it's still
just as fun. You get to stay up wicked late, hang out with your friends, watch the ball drop, it is
magical. So anyways, I want to talk about a couple of things in this gameplay. I'm not going to really
talk about what's going on, because as a demo night, you can't really talk about a whole lot.
You just bullet train people in the face, smash them with your sword, and rinse and repeat. There's
not really a whole lot to it. I top frag in this gameplay, but you know, that's, you can pay
attention if you want. I want to talk about a new series I want to try and do. A lot of people are
familiar with indie showcases, where, oh, here's an indie game, here's how you play it, there's
little things about it. Indie showcase. I kind of want to take that another step. I want to do a,
not really an indie showcase, an unknown showcase. Take a game that not very many people know about,
not very many people play, and it doesn't necessarily have to be an indie game. It can be
an older game that maybe everyone has forgotten at this point, or maybe a game that came out
recently that nobody really cared about. But it's probably good. So that's my plan, sort of. I want
to do this unknown series, or unknown showcase, or something. I'm not sure what the title will be yet.
Probably won't be more than once or twice a month. Maybe not even more than once a month. I'm not
sure. I haven't figured it out yet. But we could probably turn it into a community project. That's
kind of the future of the series. I see it as, you know some cool games that maybe not all your
friends know about. Maybe you just found it the other day, but I would like to know about it.
So we could start this community project where we share all these games with each other,
and it'll be great for everybody. Because we can all, oh I heard of this game. I heard of that game.
You should really do the video on it. Try and get as many people involved as possible. Because a lot
of these older games guys, especially for PC, if you're going back to like 1995 or something,
they can be pretty difficult to find. Like vaporware. That's what they call it. And also speaking
of PC, some of the older titles that had servers that were multiplayer, I'm sure nobody plays them
anymore. So how cool would it be if we got everybody in one of these servers and made an
entire game out of it? I just wanted to throw this out there. Wanted to see what you guys had
to think about it. Probably going to start this with the Neverhood. If any of you know what the
Neverhood is, I love you to death. And if you don't know what the Neverhood is, you are going
to find out in the next couple of days. Because that's what I'm going to do the first one. So look
for that on Friday. I'm assuming I'll have it done by Friday. Going to do a small showcase,
probably a five to six minute video. I'm not sure it'll take much longer than that. And the first
one, like I said, is going to be the Neverhood. The Neverhood is an adventure game for the PC.
Came out in 1995. It is made entirely out of claymation. It's one of the best games I've ever
played in my life. It's my childhood and it's great. So you can either wait for the showcase
this weekend or you can go do some research yourself. But let's talk about the gameplay now
for just a minute so I can give you one or two tips before the video is over. This is on King
of the Hill Lakeside, arguably the best demo night map in the game. Pretty much any King of the Hill
map, you'll have success with the demo night. Because there's so many places you can run around,
so many hiding spots. Not to mention people are literally all over the place because there's only
one point right in the middle. And really the only thing you have to worry about as a demo night on
a King of the Hill map is an engineer. Because most engineers are going to be running with the
mini sentry, which can really be horrible if you're playing demo night. If you charge somebody and
there's a mini sentry right near where you charged, you're in a lot of trouble because you can't
really get away and you're just sitting there taking hits over and over again and it'll eventually
kill you. A good way to go against that is to equip one of the grenade launchers and not have
the wee booties on. But in my opinion, I like to play demo night straight up full demo night,
which it actually does get me killed quite often. But I love the theory behind it. I love the
aesthetics. Like you have one item, you can only swing at people, that's all you can do.
And of course you can charge too, but it's just funny when you scroll through your weapons.
Nope, just got a melee item. It just makes me laugh every time. The only other real enemy you need to
be careful of is a pyro with a compression blast because they will just bounce you around and get
away from you. Other than that though, you can pretty much take anyone else. You get the jump on
somebody, doesn't matter who it is, you'll probably kill them. That's going to be the end of the video
guys. Thank you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it. Keep on the lookout for this new
unknown showcase I'm going to start doing and I'll see you guys all next time. Take care everybody.