Somebody said, Jerma, please only stream for four hours today.
Why? That's not enough time to beat the third boss, Wendelinda Gargantuan.
Rerecorded. What do you mean I have to leave? I have to leave? Well, when you come back, we'll probably still be live.
Anything less than 12 hours today is quitting.
Uh, I can't- I can't agree with that. Unfortunately.
I've got one of those voices today. That's a radio voice.
Because I talked a lot yesterday for about nine and a half straight hours.
And I woke up today with what I would call something that would be a guaranteed gig.
For an early morning commute, uh, talk show host.
Joe, what's your eyebrows? Maybe I will eventually show you my eyebrows, but not right now.
Right now we're going to talk about, um, Elden Ring.
Hi Joe. Does he want to come in here? Hold on. You want to come in here?
I opened the door and he just ran. He was like, let me in!
And then I opened the door and he went, and just sprinted.
Does- uh, maybe he wants something. I don't know.
He doesn't want- he doesn't seem like he wants anything.
Bring him back. I think he wants somebody to like, chase him around the house.
Dogs are so weird. Hey, come chase me around the- come chase me around the living room!
I do. And we play, I run after him, and then he runs after me.
One of our oldest, oldest games.
What's with the pickle thing? Okay, are people really trying-
are people trying to make a meme in Elden Ring? Right?
That's- that's what's going on, right? Like, pickles, like,
pickled relish and shit, right? This is like an Elden Ring meme thing that's happening, I think.
You should take CBDTHC to play on extra hard mode.
If I were to be high, I would not be able to play this game.
Do you understand how horrible that would be?
The stream would be an embarrassment. It would be embarrassing.
I would be walking around and forgetting where I was,
and I wouldn't even be able to fight enemies and shit. It would be impossible.
What did you call last night? Okay.
Like, yesterday was an embarrassment? No, was it? I pre- I killed like four bosses!
And I explored the world, and I immersed myself in the world,
and I walked around and did stuff. I got four boss progression.
Your eyebrows were embarrassing. All right.
Let's just- are you guys ready? Because I'm ready to play.
About the same boss for four hours? No, I fought the same boss for like an hour and ten minutes.
You can't- don't- don't gaslight me here.
I played that boss for about an hour and ten minutes, and you know how I know.
I went back, and I just checked on my VOD to see the exact time it took for me to beat that boss.
And it was about an hour and 12 minutes.
Just to make sure that I could defend myself if somebody ever said,
oh yeah, dude, just like you spent five and a half hours on the first boss,
I can go, no, it was an hour and 12 minutes. Go back and look at the data.
Did you eat another salad? No, I actually did not.
So I might be playing at a little bit less power today.
I did have a little bit of a snack, and I'm- and actually,
because I know I'm going to be going long today,
I'm ready to take a food break somewhere in the middle, which will be a salad.
I do have my- I've got my green tea powder here.
It's the thing that gives me my gaming powers.
Oh, it's ready. I think I'm ready to go.
Can you burp on stream? Maybe.
Okay. Hello. How are you? Previously on Elden Ring.
Do you have a Caesar salad? No, I don't really- I don't know.
Ever since I found out that anchovies were in Caesar salad dressing,
I kind of just, like, don't want it anymore.
That sucks, and I know. It's, like, stupid.
Okay, I like anchovies. I like sardines. I like fish and stuff, right?
But the fact that there's anchovies in a lot of, like, Caesar salad dressing,
it's- the combination of it kind of freaks me out for some reason, even if I know it's good.
Like, if you put Caesar salad dressing without the anchovies here,
and you put an anchovy here, I would be okay with dipping the anchovy
in the Caesar dressing and eating it.
But the combination to me is like, oh, I don't know about that.
I don't know. Maybe I should bring that up to the doctor next time I see him.
All right, ready? Why does it matter?
It doesn't. And I still eat it. Look, okay.
I gotta- I gotta clarify some things with some people here.
I think there's people here that think that because I- like, ovens freak me out,
that, like, I've never cooked in an oven in my entire life,
and all my food, like, comes out of the fucking, like, of a bag in the refrigerator.
No, I still- I use the oven.
When I- when I talk about, like, the microwave being something that freaks me out,
I- it's not like I hear the microwave turn on and, like, put up, like-
like, run into, like, a room and, like, hide in the corner and go, like,
Turn it off! Turn off the microwave!
I still use it. It's just kind of a weird device. It's easy.
He's an admitted oven user.
Why does it freak you out?
It's weird. It's like radio waves making your food hot.
It's weird. I- I use it- I used it literally, like, 12 hours ago.
But it's a weird device.
All right, what was I doing in my, uh, game of the year 20- what year is it? 2022.
It's not a radio wave, it's a microwave. Whatever the- I don't- it doesn't matter.
Still the same weirdness.
I'm not gonna get into this again because people will just leave.
All right, so what was I doing? Oh, yeah, I forgot. I was going this way.
I was exploring a little.
The magical world of, uh, Lindgrave.
I did see that they made a post about all the PC problems.
I saw how they were saying,
Oh, hey, yeah, we're aware that, like, the frame drops kind of fuck everything up.
And, like, especially the big and bold, bright, bright green text.
We are very aware of, uh, of Dodge not registering on some German 985 PC computers.
We're gonna address this immediately.
So I'm really, truly- I'm glad that they actually, you know, addressed it.
But actually, they are talking about it.
So, um, all right, I forgot that guy was even there.
I gotta get back in the swing of things.
So what's down here?
A bunch of explosive shit.
This is gonna be such a pain in the ass.
They're all gonna throw shit at me and it's gonna be annoying.
My hands are already sweating.
I didn't even do anything.
You know, no, I think this is sweat that's been here since last night.
As disgusting as that is.
I actually think I- because I just picked up, like, a-
Like, it's like the controller had olive oil on it.
I think this has just been here because I didn't, like, I didn't clean it.
Watch out for the dive.
What the fuck? Clean it.
It's- I- it's fine.
Actually, it's- it's really not fine.
I'm actually probably gonna have to wipe it down with this.
We're good.
Danger clothes.
I'm wearing completely different clothes than yesterday.
Controller Andy.
How do you- how do you play these games?
What's going on?
Playing with controller is how- like, the way you play these games.
Playing with the keyboard and mouse is- is hard mode.
That's hard mode.
Keyboard, mouse, with- what?
That's what- actually, I would call that way too hard mode.
That's not even hard mode.
Okay, so we're keeping going here.
Make sure I check for items.
Remember, you're epic and you make me LOL.
All right, so I'm just gonna throw, like, a grenade down here, right?
Wait, that was a pretty view.
Let me look at it.
Nice.
Really nice.
That looks like- I thought that was a Statue of Liberty.
I was like, that's kind of weird.
You should jump off.
I'm not gonna jump off.
Same joke?
Elden Ring takes place in New York.
Can you imagine just walking around and it's like,
oh, look at this beautiful castle.
It's so nice.
And you just- you just hear, like, ambient audio of, like-
That'd actually be kind of funny.
Oh, thank you.
Good try, though.
And- not just the cars, but for, like, every- hold on.
Let me- let me- let me just, like-
Quintessential city background audio is not even cars.
It's- with a little bit of an echo in the distance, like, every eight minutes.
It's just, like, the truck backing up sound.
Just that, like,
It wakes me up every morning.
Yeah.
This truck- A truck is backing up and you wonder,
man, that- wow, that truck's doing a lot of work.
No, bro.
That's, like, a hundred different trucks in different places.
It's like, oh, that- that's- that's the same truck.
They're doing a lot of work today.
Nope, that's, like, 5,000 trucks.
All in- scattered around the entire city.
And jackhammers?
Yeah.
Wait, did I miss anything here?
No, it's just one truck.
I always thought it was one truck, but it goes on all day
and it'd be like, why is the same truck backing up
over and over and over again in the same spot?
No, it's a different truck.
All right.
Why does it keep leaning in?
I'm a weirdo.
I don't know, like, somebody was saying yesterday,
and I looked at the VOD.
They were like, dude, you would probably be playing this game
five times better if you stopped dodging with the guy on screen.
And it's just like, you know, that's just what- I can't help it.
I actually can't help doing that.
It's going to happen.
I can't stop that from happening.
In fact, I don't know how people play these games just, like,
with a huge monster on the screen
and a bunch of crazy shit is happening.
And they're just like, like, I'm under attack.
You're- I'm under attack in- when this happens.
It's- I don't know how you stay so calm.
They're actual gamers.
Okay, I'm going to get killed out here.
Oh, well, all right, I can go down there.
Wait, let's go this way.
This is probably my favorite area of the game so far.
I could just fall- I could just go and go for it.
You know what I mean?
I could go for it right now.
Oh.
What's down here?
I don't know what to do.
I think I'm going to go with hole.
Yep, I'm going hole.
It's not going to hurt me, right?
Oh, shit, okay.
All right, so what's in here?
All right, I think it's an NPC right there.
Yeah, my voice is going to be like this for like a 15 minutes.
Is that an enemy or an NPC?
An NPC.
All right, what do you got to say?
Nice to meet you.
The pleasure's mine.
Roger is the name.
A sorcerer.
That's like a mushroom hat.
You might have guessed.
Sorcerer!
I'm looking for a little something here in the castle.
I'm not hot-footing it from the troops, that is.
But enough about me.
What are you doing here in Stormvale Castle?
Sorcerer's Sue.
Oh, boy.
That's bad.
They sacrifice our kind for grafting.
Not exactly a place I'd stroll into without a purpose in mind.
Does he got, um...
I'm here to defeat Godric.
Did I say?
What if he's a friend?
What if he's friends with Godric?
I'm here to defeat Godric.
I see.
Here to challenge Godric and lay your hands upon a grave.
You can see it then.
I take it.
The guidance of grace.
Well...
You're the only person that's doing a magic build, and I love it.
I'm tarnished, like you.
But...
I think there's other people doing it.
I've seen neither...
I'm not a pure caster, though.
... this guidance for the longest time.
Still, won't forget how it felt when I first came here, to the Lands Between.
I'm privy to a few magical battle arts.
Would you care to learn one?
As a fellow tarnished, once guided by grace, I'd love to...
Magical battle art?
Oh my god, this could change everything.
Yeah.
Grants affinities and skills to an...
Wait, what does this do?
The ash of war grants an armament of the magic affinity and the following skill.
Spinning weapon.
Defensive skill employed by carrion princesses.
Lifts armament into the midair that makes it spin violently.
Those it touches will suffer a successive attack.
Useful on small...
Okay, so this is like a magical spinning blade?
Ahem.
Carrion royal prestige embodying a skill.
Transform blade into a magical greatsword.
Oh, it's the swing.
The magic swing.
Ooh.
Linestone pebble.
I already have this, though.
Wait, what?
Wait.
This is a weapon art version of the one I already have.
I think I want this.
Yeah, I want this one.
All right, I gotta remember where this guy is.
I will forget.
You fucking bet your ass I will.
I gotta get rid of the other ones.
Look at all these.
Yeah.
I got so much shit on the map.
Because they're the markers.
Is that one there?
Okay, yeah.
I gotta remember where he is.
For me, you're gonna mold hard in about 30 minutes.
You know, you could probably say that at any timestamp in this whole stream,
and you'd probably...
You'd be right.
You'd be close enough, probably, I would assume.
Put it on the notepad?
Oh, yeah.
That's actually true.
Very true.
Okay.
At...
At one.
At waypoint one has new spells.
All right, that's good.
I have to be careful.
I don't want to hit him.
Okay, good.
All right.
So that's where he is.
I gotta remember...
Wait, where's the marker?
Oh, the marker go away.
All right.
Sorcerer in there.
Can you imagine if this was the game facts for this?
This is my game facts for Elden Ring.
Full walkthrough.
Door next to spawn is blocked shut.
Two stone sword key gargoyle statue at tutorial zone bonfire.
Looking for Lanius sent back to main character of anime.
Winstone key for sorcerer guy and to open CL2 academy.
Buster pat sorcerer at waypoint one has new spells.
I'm just starting to do auto.
These are dog notes.
If auto knew how to read and write, this is how he would do it.
What about in here?
Would the guy in front of him hear this?
Gorsh, I hope not.
You got bombs, dude.
Okay, run.
Trying to hit them both.
What did I just hit?
I hit something else?
Were there two people sitting in the corner?
Oh, I didn't get...
This is bad.
This is really bad.
Yeah, okay.
I hit left.
This is why, like, okay.
Hitting left on the D-pad to get the sorcerer stick in order to do the parry.
I would have hit it.
It's like I have four fucking items.
I feel like...
Not gonna get it.
It's been 10 minutes, so you were wrong, by 20 minutes.
Just two guys sleeping in the corner.
What?
Did they increase the hitboxes in these games by, like, 500,000%?
I feel like an action happens here and in, like, a four-mile radius it actually hits.
Like, that beaked motherfucker right there threw a bomb at me
and it hit two other people in other games that are not even here.
Just kill me.
Alright, I'm shooting this guy from far away.
Somebody got punched in the face in that top tower and my neck started to hurt.
Okay, give me my sorcerer's abilities.
Oh, hi.
I can do it too, you know.
Really utilizing, like, the exploding barrels.
The barrels.
Barrels everywhere.
There's barrels everywhere.
I lost the souls that I had.
Thanks a lot, Donkey Kong.
Watch out.
This is so far away.
I was probably so close to a bonfire too.
That's so annoying.
Oh.
Alright.
He's my favorite Sonic character.
Who cares?
Stop asking questions like that.
Who gives a shit?
It's fucking...
It's Tails, I guess.
I don't know.
You know why it's Tails?
Here's why it's Tails.
You don't have any responsibility as Tails.
Zero.
Your friend gets to be the one that makes all the fucking wrong decisions
while you just float around.
So it was awesome when somebody wanted to play Sonic.
Because I would always pick Tails.
Because I knew that that idiot that missed the jump,
I was just kind of hanging out.
Always player two.
Yeah, Tails was the equivalent of what they did in Mario Galaxy.
Where you could give somebody else the controller
and they could just be a little pink star on the screen
and collect items for you.
That's Tails.
That's what Tails was.
You're at 100 deaths?
Okay, I need to pay attention.
No more...
I'm not speaking ever again.
Okay.
So there you go.
But the answer is that actually he's probably big the cat
because he's the one with the fishing pole, right?
So that's kind of cool.
Alright, keep going.
I do, okay?
I didn't even need to go up there.
That was such a waste of time.
Alright, no more fucking around.
It wasn't really worth coming here,
but this looks like it can break.
Oh, nothing.
Okay, this is just the same place that I was.
This horse first guy is right there.
Why stop getting rid of my shit?
Um, this looks...
Okay, this is like a hand with like a magical spell on it.
So that's what I'm going to say.
Have you tried the McPlant?
Is it in America yet?
I don't think so.
By the way, you're a McPlant.
Is there no way you don't work for that company?
I don't know.
Oh, man.
I fucking love McDonald's.
I'm kidding.
I haven't tried it yet.
No, no.
I'm really spicy this morning.
Yeah, it's four o'clock in the afternoon.
I know.
Okay, these two...
I got to...
It's going to come down to catching them off guard
and just doing cast, cast, cast, cast, cast, cast,
and get them in like a bowling pin.
Let's play bowling.
What?
No way.
Third time's the charm.
Huh?
What?
Where were we?
Did I fall through the map?
I fell through the fucking map?
What?
Where were we?
What happened?
All right, fuck this.
Okay, I could probably make it.
I just wanted to skip it.
I can definitely make it.
I know backing up in From Software Games
is like digging straight up in Minecraft.
I know, but like sometimes you have to do it.
Otherwise, what am I going to do?
Dude, I can absolutely make that.
There's no way I can.
I just have to get a little...
I've got to go to the corner.
Use the horse?
I can't use the horse here.
The horse is banned in Stormvale Castle.
Let me just make sure.
Let me take a look.
I actually think this is possible.
Right there.
See what I mean?
I think it is.
All right, it's not possible.
Fucking whatever.
It might be, but I'm not going to...
You need to run jump.
It's hard to do, though, because you have to hold B.
And if you touch B too early, you just dodge.
So it's like you don't...
There might not be enough time.
It's my last try.
Oh, it's possible.
Oh, yeah. Okay.
All right, it's possible.
I just had to go a little bit more to the right.
That skips that whole area too, so that's perfect.
Okay, but counting these deaths as deaths is like...
I'm experimenting with what I can do in the world.
So I need to go like here.
Like right to the left of the pillar there.
Got it.
Okay.
Now, what is that?
Okay, so I can drop down there and just kind of go that way with these guys are going.
I can skip those guys entirely too, which I don't need to fight everything.
What's down there?
Whoa.
I mean, I kind of want to see what that is.
What is that?
Holy shit.
All right.
I'm going to go see what that is.
Oh, what?
I don't think I have one.
What's it called?
Storm...
Stone sword, not storm sword.
I'm going to abbreviate this.
SS key.
How many keys does it need?
Good question.
I don't want to spend them, but how much does it need?
No, it doesn't say.
Okay.
Well, here we are.
I mean, there's obviously something's going to happen here.
There's no way...
Okay, just be ready.
Be prepared because there's no way that like five people don't jump down after I touch this.
It's too perfect of a spot.
In fact, smothering stone?
No, really?
What the fuck is that?
I can't go anywhere.
I'm stuck down here.
Is that his back or his front?
I don't know.
Is he looking away from me or is he facing this way?
Oh shit.
Oh, that's his front.
That's his front.
Okay.
I don't think I'm supposed to be here, but give me all the stuff in your house.
I don't know what that was, but it's mine now.
Oh.
Oh, no.
Don't call me.
Don't call me a Cheez-It.
I mean, you can, but you don't.
I can't Cheez-It.
He's too quick and I can't shoot him through the door.
Oh, yeah, I can.
Oh, that's some...
That is some pure Gruyere cheese, if I don't say so myself.
Absolute pure delicious Gruyere.
Come on.
You're dealing with a casual right now.
Huh?
Do not say that.
Casual.
He almost took my fucking hand clean off my shoulders.
All right, just come over here so I can fucking...
Oh, that's...
No, that's a really good Brie.
No more.
Why am I losing walk-on?
I'm so good at fucking video games, man.
That's it?
Be careful, that guy killed me through a wall.
Yeah.
Look, I am a battle mage.
I have this claw, which attacks, but I also have the staff, which attacks.
You're a bimbo.
I'm playing the bimbo build.
Is that what you're telling me?
Is this bimbo build?
Wait, what?
Like, I get to hang back and cast spells and only need to use my weapon if I absolutely need to?
Oh, okay.
I said this last night and I'll say it again.
Sorcery works really well until it doesn't.
And we might find out really soon enough here the places where it doesn't.
Oh, it's getting auto-modded.
Sorcery works great until it don't.
Sorcery is going to fall off real hard in the next probably couple of hours,
from what I've been told.
This is a cringe build.
Can we bring back the guy that said that, like,
I'm one of the only people playing a sorcery build?
Where is that person?
Can you come back and can you, like, say what you said, like, five more times?
I'm building decks and I'm building sorcery as it stands right now.
As it stands right now.
My sorcery does more damage than my dexterity attacks.
Therefore, I'm going to continue to use it until the dexterity takes it over.
The very simple equation.
Very easy.
Simple.
Can I talk?
It doesn't open from this side.
I'm in trouble here.
I think I have to sneak by this person and try to find a bonfire,
which I'm going to think is probably over there.
All right.
Two schools of thought here.
Run straight through there and just sprint into that build.
Sprint in there and just run until I find a fire or sneak around.
You think it's run?
I think it's sneak.
I'm going to wait till his back turns, but I can't run sneak because people hear it.
When he goes this way, we're going to go that way.
One, two, three.
Let's kill him.
Excuse me?
What?
You got to be kidding me.
How did he fucking hear me?
Just give me whatever's in your house quick.
Oh, fire.
Is there fire in here?
I need a fire.
Thank God he de-aggroed.
Come on.
I'm so far down here.
Fire, fire, fire, fire, fire.
Fire in here?
Damn it.
Fireplace?
No, that's not what I'm saying.
I swear to God, if one of these birds drops a fucking grenade on me, I'm going to be so mad.
Where the hell am I?
Wait, what?
I went around.
Wait, where am I in a circle?
Wait, hold on a second.
I had to have missed one.
Maybe this one down over here?
I don't have enough to...
I'm scared to attack that guy.
There's a chest over there, too.
Teleport?
Yeah, but I swear there's probably one right here somewhere.
Like, right...
Okay, look at this.
Like, where...
This spot, this one, probably right here.
Shit.
All right, well, at least I know it's not safe.
Okay, so let me...
If I go from this fire that's up here, I can just kind of...
I'll do skip.
I'll do castle skip, right?
Which will put me right here.
Yeah, and then I can level up once or twice as well.
Yeah, because castle skip puts me right here.
Wait a minute.
Where am I?
Yeah.
Why do I not heal?
I don't have any flasks left.
Okay, let me level up.
I have a lot of those crunchies, so...
I got plenty of crunchies.
I have a lot of crunchies.
Wait, that's wrong.
Here they are.
Yeah, let's use it.
I have not been using the crunchies.
What do I need?
3,600.
I think I have a big one.
Gain ruins.
All right, let's take this one.
All right, that'll get me to 3,900.
What do I need after that?
Either intelligence or endurance.
How are you liking Soulcalibur?
It's pretty good.
What is, in your opinion, the most clusterfuck of a stream you've ever done?
The family dinner stream, without a doubt.
Strength.
I don't really want to do strength until I need it,
but I probably will soon here, right?
I imagine that very soon, even a deck scaling weapon,
I'm gonna have to have at least probably 12 to 15 strength.
And it's cheap now.
But I think I want some more endurance.
I'll get intelligence to 18.
And then...
Actually, I might be able to do it right now.
Yeah, I definitely will.
Yeah, this is gonna get me to at least probably 3 or 4,000.
Shit.
Okay, it's all right.
All right, so now from here, I gotta do...
Wait, how much is this one?
None.
All right, so here we are.
So right there, I just do castle skip.
Right here, and I'm back to where I was.
Holy shit, that was almost a disaster.
Okay, so now we go this way.
And this is exactly where I just was.
So now I'm in a better position.
Let's do some exploration.
But first, I want to go down here because there's an item down here.
Where was it?
It was...
I asked a question.
You don't even have 5 seconds to respond.
Okay, here we go.
I'm gonna go in here and kill this guy,
because I have to be a video game player.
And these guys are hard to play against.
I need to play...
Here it is, right here.
I gotta kill this guy.
There's no...
Are we gonna cheese him?
Ah!
Dude, fuck.
God.
I hate these like long-winded swings.
When somebody swings a weapon at you,
and normally, it's just like, here it comes, right?
Well, when they do these little like crow hop moves,
where they're like, here it comes.
And then I'm doing it.
Oh, and by the way, it's gonna be a 360 degree tornado spin too.
Don't miss this jump, please.
Okay.
That was 3,000 souls I would have lost.
I'm fine.
Everybody relax.
You're calling this guy the fuck out, man.
He's like a streamer?
Yeah, I mean, it's like fucking bullshit.
The guy like does these dumb shitty tactics
when he plays PvP, and it's annoying.
Like, what do you mean, calling him out?
He definitely saw that.
I need to get a backstab on him.
And I should have had it the first time,
but I apparently didn't for some reason.
He turns back around this way.
Yeah, he walks back this way.
Okay, here we go.
I'm gonna get the backstab, and I'm gonna kick his ass.
You see how long that move was?
What the fuck has happened?
That was crazy.
Where did my souls go?
Hey, wait.
Didn't I have like 3,000?
What happened to them?
You picked them up.
Yeah, but I thought I had like already had 2,900.
And you have 3k.
Why are some of them gone?
It's the cheese tax.
I think you still lose some when you die, do you?
That's new.
Wait, I swear to God, I thought I had like 2,800 or something.
After killing that guy, I don't know.
That's weird.
Oh, you map.
It was the cheese tax.
Okay, so there's got to be a way to go from here over there.
Yeah.
I mean, it's not that way because that's where the...
I don't want to fight this guy.
I don't care.
Where was that door?
Really?
Cheese tax.
That's actually really funny.
All right, this is where I wanted to go.
Pretty sick.
Cheese stacks?
Cheese tax.
Okay, got to be ready for anything.
Lump of flesh.
Wrist Lids Memento.
It's a key.
And a golden rune.
Okay.
I actually picked up a bunch of items.
I need to look what they do.
That's up there.
This is just the other room.
What?
Really?
Elevator.
I'm not going to get away with the cheese for long.
No, I know.
I know.
All right, so that...
This is...
Goes up here.
Okay, so now I'm...
This is like a weird skip.
What though?
This is the tower.
Tower's right here.
Where is this in regards to where I am right now?
Oh, nice.
Still need a little bit more.
I did get a rune.
This is a golden rune.
Still need more.
Let's just kill this guy and get his...
So I know I keep saying souls, but whatever.
All right, so that's actually really helpful.
Wait, I got a key item.
When I have a second to pause,
I'm going to take a look at it.
What is that for?
Roach wrapped in red velvet.
Cementa left by the chrysalid sacrifice for grafting.
A brooch wrapped in red velvet.
Traces of blood are visible.
faintly visible spirits try to convey something,
but their voices cannot be heard.
Key item.
Small withered bag knitted by hand.
Oh, okay.
Where does that go?
Okay.
Oh, progress I think is out this way, right?
No.
Progress is...
Where is progress?
Not over here.
I gotta go back up.
Yeah, I haven't gone up this way.
All right, progress is this way.
Did I go up this?
Did I go over here?
He's senile.
Yeah, it's this way, okay.
All right, there's that scary guy with the axe again.
I think I just...
Wait, is this openable with that thing?
Oh, this guy sucks.
I'm just running.
Fuck it.
Actually, I could probably get by him.
I don't want to fight this guy again.
He's annoying.
He BMs.
He's a BMer.
I don't like him.
All right, then...
Whoa, I can jump over this.
Okay.
You should play Elden Ring.
Stop.
What are you doing?
Don't blow the horn.
Okay.
Sound of progress, my friend.
Hey, hey, remember me?
Yeah, can he hit you through a wall?
Or should I hope not?
Oh, but there's something down there.
There's a lot of stuff down here.
This is the front door to the castle,
but I was never able to get up there.
Yeah, I see the ladder here, but...
I mean, look, there's items.
There's stuff on the ground.
One, two...
Maybe I can go through...
Let me see if there's...
Okay, there's a ladder there.
Ah, just stuff I missed.
Ah, fuck it.
Whatever.
Guy, I see the ladder.
I see the ladder.
Don't worry.
Tree's going to be a boss.
Just calling it now.
Okay.
A weird spot.
Let me see what's over here.
A lot of nothing.
I can go that way.
Let me drop down there.
See what the heck's going on over there.
Yeah, let me see what the heck's going on here.
So...
Ah, this is the door.
Wait.
What a terrible guard.
Are you looking into the wall?
Like, if you're aiming this way?
What are you doing?
He was AFK.
Pickled turtleneck?
Why do I feel like that's like a TikTok
or like an Instagram trend?
Pickling your clothing.
Yeah, we see.
I pickled it for about six months
and it came out and it actually looks a lot better.
I like the design that came out with it.
Nice.
Boomer moment.
Why, because I said TikTok.
So I said TikTok.
I like that I said TikTok.
You should, you should, you should.
Yeah, you should do the orangutan.
Okay, so that got me the key,
which now I just got to run around,
which there's the door that led to here.
That guy, that guy was just resting.
Yep.
I think I have to go back up though.
This is no way to go the other way
unless I can go this way.
Which I don't think I can.
Um, anything on the chandeliers?
No.
No, we just got to go back.
Back up, dude.
Dude, just go full magic build.
No, I don't, I'm not going to go full magic.
Okay, well, I just need to go.
Where am I going here?
Over here, right?
Whatever, I'm just going this way.
Where's the, where the hell am I?
I need to get back up to where I was.
Wait, what?
Getting confused.
Uh, I should actually start putting markers
down or just kind of traveling around
and walking around because
kind of go around in circles sometimes
and you're just like, wait, where the fuck am I?
Okay, yeah.
And then over this way.
Yep.
What about your notes?
Um, I think notes are for like important things
that I have to remember.
Not necessarily about direction.
So this is going up here.
So now just climb back up.
Climb up here.
I almost have enough to do the...
I feel like I'm going to find another fire though.
Like almost immediately, like very soon here.
That's what's getting me down there.
All right, I am convinced
that there is going to be a fire here soon.
So I'm just going to keep going.
I just, just jump down here.
I just go down here.
I think I'm just going to go down here.
Use the key.
I think I need to.
I think I'm just going down here.
Like what, like whatever, right?
Like should I, I can go from here to there?
No, I just jump from here to there.
I feel like I'm going to die.
Don't break your hip.
Don't do it.
It could be fall damage.
Use the ladder instead.
Um, what's over here?
Can I not go over there?
It looks like I can jump over there
and go that way.
Use the ladder.
I'll go back down.
Maybe that's actually death.
But from here, I'm trying to think of where that guy can go.
I could go this way, jump down here,
and then go over there.
I do that?
I'm just going to do it.
I think, I think I'm doing it.
I'm just going to go that way.
Okay. Um, I'm here.
I might as well get the items.
There are a couple.
Ooh, that's good.
All right, I'm going to go that way
and jump over now.
Did you get the cat item?
I don't, I don't think so.
Arrows.
All right.
This is where it gets weird.
I think that's the, that's where I got to go.
Or down there.
Please tell me there's a fire here.
I feel like I've gone a pretty long ways without one.
Wait, shit.
I can go down here.
I can also.
Now that's just kind of where I was before the main gate, right?
Festering bloody finger.
Okay, I can't.
This is going to be very tricky.
I have to just be a gamer here.
If I can just pull one, that would be great
because I don't want to fight them both at the same time.
I hope they don't aggro at the same time.
So we're just going to go for it.
The slow fucking attacks kill me every time.
They're so slow.
I just, they're like, oh, two seconds.
I just think it's going to happen way sooner than it does.
Everybody's so slow in this game.
Everybody takes forever to swing.
Fuck.
At least I have the skill.
That's copium.
Yeah, it is copium.
And I'm going to suck it and smell it.
Whatever that, you know what I mean?
Copium, you like, you like, you suck it.
You like an hit, right?
Again, like, like I fought that last boss in Elden Ring.
Wait a full, another full second before you dodge
with every single enemy in the entire game.
Everybody's weapons are apparently so heavy in this game
that it gives them five full seconds to fucking swing them.
Uly noted.
Back over here, right?
Yeah.
You lost a bunch of souls.
I didn't lose them yet.
Go get them.
So I, well, just stay down there.
I don't care.
Deep slurping copium?
What does that mean?
Turn it on high.
Sir, I don't think you should turn it on high.
Turn it, turn it on as high as it goes.
I don't know.
I think that's kind of dangerous.
I said to do something that means you do it.
I'm king.
King.
Too much.
Raid song.
Oh, here we go.
We got a raid.
Too much copium.
I feel the need to defend every single Marvel movie
and Marvel TV show ever made.
Even dating back to the fucking 90s.
Thanks, RT.
Appreciate the raid.
We're doing Elden Ring.
Are you playing Elden Ring too?
Oh man, people just came in inhaling copium.
You don't understand.
I think X-Men Wolverine Origins
actually was a pretty good movie.
It was actually very well made
and the cinematography was actually pretty good.
King German, what the fuck are you talking about?
It's like 1400.
Why are you saying these things?
2006 was four years ago.
Well, thanks for the raid, dude.
Welcome.
Hope you're doing good.
I currently just was very upset at this game
because I found it to be not cool and not fun
and very not hog champ.
All right, I gotta pay attention.
I gotta figure out where I'm going.
Where am I going?
The idea is back to...
This is why I need the fucking marker.
It was down the ladder and then where?
It was like right here somewhere, right?
I thought I dropped down, right?
I went right here.
Maybe I can hit something
so I don't get to take damage,
but I don't think I can.
Did that work?
No.
All right, no more copium.
No more bullshit.
Just go get this guy.
The slow swings.
Just get ready.
I know it's going to make me very mad
and you're all going to laugh.
Everyone's going to laugh at me when I lose again.
Oh, that's bad.
That's fucking bad.
Wait, it's climbing the ladder.
Guys, what?
Come on.
Get away from me.
You don't climb ladders.
Shit.
I was fully prepared to do that again.
Where is he?
Oh, it's a fucking thing, the drape.
I thought like a tentacle came down and grabbed me.
Dude, why?
Now I'm like I'm all cracked out now.
Holy shit.
I am cracked up right now after that.
Are you kidding me?
That's so violent.
That moved around so weirdly and violently.
I think I can get him before he comes over here.
All right.
I'm definitely losing souls because I had like 4,000.
Copium.
He's coping in advance.
Yeah, I was because if I died,
you were about to hear a lot of bullshit.
Okay, I was going to talk a bunch of shit.
You wouldn't be able to escape it unless you of course hit the X and left
because you didn't want to listen to it.
All right, but I'm still not out of this yet.
I'm kind of fucked right now because unless I...
Okay, that guy's going to shoot me.
Oh, no, he's going to shoot me with that.
It's going to hit me.
No, don't get up.
Don't get up.
This fucking horse shit.
There's always a guy sitting down somewhere
who slowly gets up after you attack the one guy that you see.
Oh, I'm insane.
I got to run by it.
I'm just running by all these fucking turds.
Here comes the cheese tax.
There is no cheese tax, but it's called
I'm running by everybody and hopefully I don't die in the process and lose four thousands.
Whatever they are.
If you were in a souls game, what kind of creature would you be?
Definitely one of the ones that goes like this.
You know what I mean?
I didn't want to do it.
I really didn't want to do it because I didn't want to like hurt everybody's ears.
And my move set would definitely be the one of the ones that goes like making that sound
and then going and then falling down.
And then you just you kill me in three hits back up.
I'm going to just try to get over there and run and just pick up my souls at least.
And this if I die here.
Oh, I'm going to be upset, but let me just be not stupid about this.
Selectively kill people that need to just knock him down.
Okay, just go.
Where is he at?
Pretty bad.
Okay, we're safe.
It looks like Burger King's.
It looks like Burger King.
Sneak King.
You mean I look like the Burger King from Burger King.
They didn't make him up for Sneak King, although that would be really funny if they did.
Already out of potions.
Okay, so I got to just get over there.
Ignore everybody and just get the souls and just run.
It's okay.
That's what you can do that in these games.
It's a decent strategy.
It really is.
So they're around the corner.
I see him right there.
See ya.
Where do I go from here?
There's a lot of.
Oh, a lot of.
Oh, thank God.
He hit me with that.
The hitbox.
Somebody fucking 10 miles down the road swung an axe and I got hit by it.
Oh, yeah.
They're climbing.
They're climbing up right now.
They're right behind me.
They're right behind me, I think.
I got a cookbook.
I escaped.
Where am I?
Almost fell down that hole.
That would have been horrible.
Do I need to go there?
Yeah, they're taking souls away.
That's new.
That's not in any of the other games.
They're literally it's a tax.
It's a death tax.
It's like 30 percent.
Yeah, that's new.
All right.
Did I miss anything over here?
I'm afraid to try to make this jump, actually, if I'm honest.
Otherwise, I'm fucking dead meat.
So do I drop down here and just spam at this guy?
Yeah, right.
Un-fucking-believable, dude.
That was almost a disaster.
You got to be kidding me.
It's going to hit me through the floor.
Please don't have anybody in this room.
Wooden great shield.
I could go that on my end.
That's a big person.
I could go that way.
I could try to go that way.
Let me see what's over here.
I need a better weapon.
I need to upgrade a weapon.
I actually did pick up a weapon.
I forget what it was, but hold on.
Let me see.
Or anything here that I need to look at.
All right.
I'm going over there.
There's also that wolf with the sword enemy thing that I could probably go kill.
Did they get a new axe?
Yeah.
Um, I don't know.
I'm not sure where to go.
Need to call the boys?
That's actually not a bad idea.
If I don't need to aggro this...
There's a dog right there.
Oh my god.
All right.
In that door or up in that door?
I don't know.
I think before I do this, I think I have to consult with the boys.
All right.
Here's the plan.
We have an opportunity to go up
or we have to...
I hear somebody moving.
Okay.
No, I don't.
We have an opportunity, boys.
Let's go.
What's that?
I don't know.
Boys, no.
No.
Don't attack people.
Um, bonfire.
Bonfire.
Nice job, boys.
We did it.
We attacked like a boss.
All right.
Let's go.
Hell yeah.
The boys are the fucking worst.
They're so awful.
Okay.
So what are we doing here?
Probably another point into...
Do I want more endurance?
I think so.
Either endurance or intelligence.
No, get intelligence to 18.
So, very important.
Let's go kill this fucking guy.
Why not?
I'm trying to go up the goddamn stairs.
You just hit your own dog.
I didn't get the backstab.
Shit.
Fuck you.
Oh, there's an animal up here.
He's trying to kick me down the stairs.
Oh, there's no juice in this thing.
What are you worrying about in your head?
Is that a pumpkin?
All right.
Well, that guy's gone.
He was...
There's something where he was standing.
What is this?
What is that?
Can I break this or something?
It's like a weird thing to have here.
What is this?
Start using one-liners when you get kills.
Nope.
I'm not going to do that because...
Um, what is this?
Prophecy painting.
Reminisce of the painting prophecy.
Examine it using square.
I'm afraid to touch this.
Square X whatever.
I actually don't think I want to do that.
I'm kind of scared to press that button.
What if it like sucks me into a new world or something?
We're watching you in a bar, German.
Do something wacky.
Hey.
Hey, this one goes out to all y'all in the bar.
Three.
Two.
One.
Let's go.
Mmm.
Green tea.
Hey, what are you drinking?
Hey, dude, what are you drinking?
Oh, it's a vodka pineapple with a little bit of cranberry.
What are you drinking?
Hey.
Hey, what are you drinking?
What do you got?
What are you drinking?
A beer?
Oh, cool.
What kind of beer?
Oh, what are you drinking?
Welcome to every conversation you have in a fucking bar.
Oh, can I try that?
Yeah, let me try.
Oh, that's like spicy.
What do you got?
What's that one?
Oh, that's called the Dr. Manhattan.
Let me try that.
It's blue and it smells.
I don't know.
That's not for me.
I don't like gin.
What do you got?
Let me see.
I don't like beer, dude.
I'm not a beer guy.
Anyone want to try mine?
It's fucking sludge.
I got it from the fucking toilet.
Try it.
Minus two, play the game.
They said I was on TV in their bar.
What, you want me to not like say hello?
There's a door back here.
This is a shortcut, maybe.
This looks like it's probably a shortcut to find out.
How much to have you sing at my wedding?
Three or four million dollars.
So, okay.
I'm not going down there yet.
Is this the front door?
It's not.
But this, I have not been over here.
That's not the front gate.
The front gate's down here.
So, I should probably take a look over here for a minute.
Did I even rest at that stupid bonfire?
I'm also going to do some allocation here.
I want to, I need more health.
How do I like Breath of the Wild so far?
I never played Breath of the Wild.
I haven't played it.
Sorry.
The bar is real.
Bar video.
What am I doing up here?
They can't even hear me.
Should I try to communicate?
Like, hey, hey, wait, wait, look, look.
Look over here.
Hey, everybody, everybody, look over here.
Hey, you, wait, look.
Hey, everybody, hey.
One, two, three.
Yeah.
I'm probably, I probably just look like a fucking psycho.
Nobody's probably watching this TV.
Nobody's watching this TV.
I don't think anyone is.
It's going to be so weird looking over there
and being like, what's going on on the TV over there?
In a lot of bars, TVs are just on.
Like, I'll be honest.
They're kind of like, they'll be like a basketball game
or like a baseball game or like some talk show.
Nobody's really paying attention.
Use the notepad to say hi.
Okay, I'm trying to communicate.
Okay, I'm going to play the game now.
Somebody was just really mad that I wasn't playing the game.
The funniest part is that nobody is probably looking.
I just look like a fucking weirdo.
Wait, hold on.
Is there another one?
Is it, wait, you took another video?
We have an update.
Play the fucking game.
Hold on, I'm communicating.
I'm going to be streaming for like 10 hours today.
Don't worry.
Oh, what's your, hold on.
Here it is.
Update.
People aren't even paying.
I look like such a fucking weirdo.
Oh my God.
Okay, hold on a second.
This looks so stupid.
Okay, let's watch the, oh, you got to, hold on.
So stupid.
Play the game.
Hold on a second.
Oh my God, hold on.
I want to be able to show it.
That's so ridiculous.
Pretend you're stuck in the TV.
No, guys, you're killing me.
You're killing me.
I need to be able to like see, where is this?
Why did it just disappear?
I'm like.
Where is it?
Why did it just like broke?
Why can't I show it?
I'm like.
Why is it upside down?
All right, all right, all right.
I got to move on.
I'm moving on.
That's funny.
That's cool.
Hey, I'm cool.
Hey, that's cool.
You got me on your, in your bar.
That's pretty cool.
It's a video of the text.
All right.
That's fucking funny.
But I want to play the game.
You just showed the bar a video of the bar.
All right, I'm moving on.
It's funny.
It's cool.
I'm happy that I'm on your TV.
But that's it.
Let's go.
It's not just a TV, Jerma.
It is.
You've infiltrated their reality.
Okay.
Back to the video game.
You're stuck.
No, no, no, no.
It's funny for a minute.
But no, let's, let's, let's, let's move on.
Oh, we hate the video game.
What is all over my mouth?
Oh.
You need to put baby sensorys on.
No, no, no.
They just got me on their TV and it's fun.
And it's funny.
I don't want, I don't want to like fuck with them, right?
Like that's, I'd rather just like kind of end it there.
It's cool that I'm on the TV though.
It is.
I find that really, really, that's really sweet.
Did you ever beat Hollow Knight off stream?
That's a really interesting question, actually.
No, I didn't.
I really wanted to, but I just didn't find the opportunity to.
All right, let's go this way.
No, I did not.
What the fuck?
Okay.
How is magic?
Magic is actually...
Really fun.
I like it a lot.
I like the combo magic.
Kind of magic plus.
Oh my gosh.
That's not what I wanted to do.
Okay.
You want to fight with me?
Is this a summon?
As fellow tarnished, we must each follow our own guidance.
Down whatever road takes us to the throne of Elden Lord.
Apologies, as fellow tarnished...
Okay, so I can summon you for the fight.
Whatever that fight is.
That was burp.
Okay.
I'm imagining that's probably happening very, very soon here.
Very soon.
Nice.
Another charge.
I haven't been able to use my horse in like six hours of gameplay.
Damn.
Okay.
This looks...
This is gonna be actually pretty bad.
I think I'm gonna go...
I think I'm gonna upgrade some weapons.
At least a couple times.
Or at least...
Because I don't...
My weapons are all plus one or plus zero.
I gotta kill the ad.
Shit.
Can I backstab?
I wonder.
Can I get like on his like leg or something?
This is bad.
Can't like break his leg?
Really?
Ooh, there it is.
Pain in the ass.
All right.
Do I have mana?
No.
I don't.
This guy sounds like a Scooby-Doo villain.
Ooh, I forgot about that.
The weapon art is actually incredible.
Uh-oh.
Okay, well that's the boss right there.
Item?
Well, let me level up one more time.
I have enough souls almost.
Give me a minute.
Is a bonfire...
Wait, is a bonfire in there?
Is there really?
Oh, okay.
Get over here.
What are these things?
Where am I going?
Ooh, okay.
Nice.
I think it's gonna get up.
So I'm just gonna take this thing away.
Where's this bonfire?
Oh, there it is.
Okay.
Sweet.
How many hours until you're gonna jump attack?
I'm saying at least probably two or three.
Shit.
4,200.
How many, uh, so how many rune, uh, crunchy things do I have?
One.
All right, let me, uh, let me just get to...
I'm gonna kill some of these guys.
Because I definitely want to get to enough.
So I don't...
I'm gonna die probably 500 times in this boss.
Hey, hey!
Settle down.
Wait, he's jumped up?
You are so slow like everybody else in this fucking whole universe!
I'm the developer of this indie game.
I just want to let you know that you really should...
I...
Okay, I'll try.
Sorcery is so good.
Although, I think actually using like a two-handed weapon would be...
You're still alive.
I just, let me get a few more souls and we'll be good.
Two-handed is pretty good.
Ooh, what do we have here?
And I'm gonna put it into, uh, stamina or vitality.
When are you gonna let us have a turn?
Just get it!
All right, fine.
I will P...
I will PS4 screen share play with you guys.
But you have to share.
Where am I going?
Okay, so this is just right here.
Although, I don't really want to do this right now.
Just get it, forehead.
I know.
It's 60 fucking bucks.
It's not like two dollars, I feel you.
All right, this is another skip back here.
So, what's the point of that skip?
It like doesn't really have a...
And does it really have that much of a purpose?
Because there's a bonfire literally right there.
It's kind of a weird place for that.
Hmm, okay.
I still need a few more souls.
Let's fight the boss, the loser.
I don't...
I'm gonna die to the boss.
So, I need to get to the souls required to fight this boss and not...
And not lose all the stuff that I have.
I think that's enough.
What is it?
4,600?
4,500?
And yeah, I have to go upgrade my stuff too.
All right, I'm doing endurance.
And we're traveling.
I'm going out of here.
I'm going to the blacksmith, which is...
Where is the...
This place, right?
Yeah, because I have to upgrade something.
I can't just...
Plus one.
It's awful.
It's very bad.
Where is he?
I got a few new weapons as well.
So, I need to examine what I want to do here.
Because I actually...
The claws are pretty good.
The claws are fast.
Let's take a look.
Yeah, I have...
Why not have?
There are...
I'm speaking of runes.
Well, back to what we were doing.
I'm going to just go farm for like five seconds.
Just get...
Wherever.
It doesn't matter.
I could sell something, but I don't want to.
I really only need like a few hundred.
How much do these guys give?
All right.
Yeah, I'm just going to kill like a few things.
Oh my god.
This guy has to farm.
He's so bad.
He can't just play the game as it shows up and progress as it happens.
Get away from me.
Okay, that should be enough to upgrade a couple things.
If I need to sell something, I will.
Well, thank you for those good meter day subs.
Artemis.
Of the blue.
I haven't like shouted any subs out in like two weeks.
I'm very focused on Elden Ring.
Okay, back to here.
Because he hates us.
No, I don't.
Wrong way.
Rodrik is cool as fuck.
I'm hyped for you to see him.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm very much looking forward to it.
Okay.
So I've got this dagger, which I don't want to play with daggers.
It's too hard.
It literally takes forever to kill anything unless you stab things in the back.
Yes, doc, which is another one of those.
I don't want to do it.
Island Axe.
This is D in both and requires 12 strength.
It's probably the claws.
I have to pick something and I think it's going to be claws.
You're fast.
Bloodloss is pretty good.
Either that or I need to...
I mean, what does this look like with 12 strength?
I don't know.
Does this okay?
Once I upgrade this, does this scale with strength?
Probably.
Well, as it stands right now, I have to pick something and I'm going to pick the claws.
I'm going for it.
Claws have been upgraded and I'm gonna just put one into this.
I think because I haven't found another staff yet and like what the sorcery scaling like
needs to be better.
Right?
Like it just does.
So it's going to be doing a little bit more damage.
Okay.
I actually have like a plus two weapon now and not walking around like a dickhead.
And then we need to go back here and I am ready to attempt whatever this is.
Which was here, right?
Happy birthday to the guy in chat.
Happy birthday.
Hey, laugh.
Get the counter ready.
I'm going to stick with three and two.
I got the boys on standby.
If I need them, it's time to just let's all right.
Let's open the door.
Let's see it.
Got a big fucking accident.
It's going to be slow as shit.
Okay.
I thought this was four people riding the horse.
Oh man.
He's got, he's got, he's going to be swinging with like eight different arms.
I'll drink the grafted.
All right.
What do you got?
Show me your moves.
It's a lot of AOE.
Big AOE, big AOE.
And he goes through a ball.
Got a lot of health.
Whoa.
The AOE, right?
Got to be careful.
The AOE does a double AOE.
Holy shit.
All right, dude.
Come on one.
And then it's okay.
So you got to get the fuck away from that.
Hey, after he does that role, you're going to get the fuck out of here.
Is that what's he doing?
What is he doing?
Did he miss and hit himself?
Phase two.
Yep.
Of course.
Oh, it's got his head.
He has a flame thrower now.
I think it's time to jump over it.
Nope.
That's insane.
He looks like a resident evil villain.
Yeah, he does.
All right.
So it's very clear here.
So phase one is a lot of just...
I don't want to...
Here's what I have to do.
I have to get good.
And I have to get him all the way to phase two without casting a spell.
Because that's where it's going to be really important.
Let's see what I can do.
One.
Two.
Oh no.
The tornado.
What the fuck am I?
Trouble here.
How do I get that fucking bleed?
Shit.
It's faster than the other moves.
Oh, that's right.
I did get another seed.
Yep.
Thanks for reminding me.
Seriously.
I would have forgot.
I wouldn't know.
I would have absolutely forgot.
Blasks.
There we go.
Okay.
That's a big deal.
That's a huge deal.
I'm thinking four and two is fine for now.
We'll see if I...
I'm...
What?
We'll see.
We're going to call...
Yeah.
I got to get him to phase two without calling on the boys
and without casting a spell at him.
That's definitely doable.
And then I can hang back.
The boys can do what they need to do and I'll kill him.
That fucking pro hop, man.
Why does everybody have to do that?
I think I'm fighting the little brother of the guy that I fought fucking four hours ago.
What about that lady?
I think I can get it.
I got to get back.
I got to get to phase two again.
If I can get to phase two, then I bring out the boys and then I just...
And then I coward him.
I'm not doing a lot of damage to him though.
I'm only doing what?
Like 60 or 70.
It's going to take a little longer.
All right.
Really happy little tantrum.
That's fine.
He's just like just amorphous blob.
I don't even know when he's attacking.
He's just like moving his body around.
Parry?
Can you parry bosses in this game?
I feel like I tried.
Should I try parrying?
I think parrying has the same problem though.
That was as...
That was perfect.
Like that was actually a perfect parry and it didn't do anything.
I don't think so.
Yeah, you can't.
Guard counter works?
Oh, should I put it on?
Does that even lift lowly tarnished?
No, I got the right idea.
I got the right idea.
I just got to be patient, be good.
Go get it.
That is so slow.
Everybody's in slow motion.
All right.
But okay.
So he goes huge slow swing.
Dodge attack again.
You get hit by it again?
If I dodge that one, he swings immediately after you land
with the iframe.
Fuck this guy.
He attacks three times in one session.
Don't stop rolling.
But how do you...
What am I supposed to do?
Just run away?
Two.
That was a one, two.
That was three.
I have a better idea.
I got a better idea.
I'm going to use the weapon marker.
I got it.
Protect yourself.
Try this strat.
Boom, boom.
He only does two swings.
Okay.
So he goes boom, boom.
I think I can get behind him.
Build up stamina for a second here.
No.
It's so hard to tell if he's going to actually swing
or if he's going to do the fucking tornado.
It's the same animation.
Is that not...
Wait, does the dodge not have iframes?
Does the weapon art dodge have iframes?
It doesn't.
No, it doesn't.
Fuck.
I thought it did.
Damn slow ass goddamn boss.
Fuckers.
You have range?
I know.
I'm trying to get him to phase two without using it
because I'll burn through it all.
And then he's going to do the flamethrower
and he's going to kill me.
Should you do jump R2?
Quick jump.
Quick step and quick jump.
Have iframes?
What the hell are you guys doing?
Summon the boys?
All right.
I'm going to...
Let me try this one or two more times.
This is a good strategy as long as I can actually do it.
That extra second that he sits there
and you think he's going to swing
and he just fucking doesn't.
I hate it.
Just kill me already.
I'm going to try...
All right.
New strategy.
No.
Okay.
All right.
He holds it in the air
and just like his dickhead brother,
he goes like this.
So it's on the...
You wait for the two pumps
and then he'll do it.
So he puts his arm up.
Okay.
There and there he does.
All right.
Yeah.
He's a two pump.
What does that mean?
I don't think I want to say that out loud.
I don't want to say what you just...
I'm not saying that out loud.
Yeah.
Okay.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What the fuck?
They're all slow.
He's so fucking slow.
it's so fucking slow they're so fucking slow oh you're scaring people all right let's go
i gotta at least get him back down to 50 like i dude what the fuck man what what why an elder
ring do they want you just to turn and just run the other direction to the other side of the map
like oh he's doing that move just run all the way to the back and like we're playing it's like
fucking recess playing like fucking tag the boys suck they're actually doing pretty good
i just got lucky there oh my god it was like homing missile get this shit out of there
run run run run run run what is he doing what is he doing what is he doing what is he doing what
is he doing oh wait i can just smash on him there okay i can just smash on him i don't know why i
thought he was gonna explode i could get in there and just like wail on him all right
right okay so when he does that just absolutely beat that lever every little shit out
all right let's go at least i get to see it again here's another attack with the arm
round up in the air okay fire breathing just goes oh fuck bad how do i get away from him
i just can't get away from him why is it taking me so long to do that dude
i'm gonna unbind the left stick by the way it's just such a hindrance it just fucks you every
single time get me out what huh what happened a fire hot fire all right i got the strategy here
here's the strategy probably is when he all right when he goes down wham wham wham wham wham wham
when he's breathing the fire you can usually get a few good hits in all right let's get this
going here honestly you know what phase one i think is is magic because i can get them
down reliably hopefully let's see what i can do should i maybe just walk the magic just get
in there and beat this shit up let's see i got of course like i had to walk right into that like
because who the fuck even tells me an idiot just want to do a single fucking move unbind it i have
to unbind it it's such a bad place to put that i would rather have no ability to crouch than
have to crouch in the middle of fucking boss fight let's go get in there oh is it close enough
come on fucking what what's happening it's a new move i haven't seen that shit too greedy
is it actually a homing missile that's stupid it is it actually is
here comes shit homing missile attacks you and it goes 100 miles per hour i'm burning through
all right i gotta like i feel like i'm not doing enough damage like even when i hit them it just
feels like it's i'm doing like nothing let me see if i can actually handle this forget about the
boys for now let me practice for a minute because like seriously if it's just about
magic actually is probably gonna be a bad idea in the second phase because of how
fuck that he turned around it's fuck dude you reach across the whole game
my fucking god it's over let's put gravestones fucking scan it around the whole area and they'll
run into him he's in the air and he just goes like like i would rather just be like final
destination like there's nothing here it's just me and you and like a black screen behind us i
don't want i don't want to run into this shit let's go i keep thinking he's gonna jump in the
air and do the big two-handed swing but he doesn't just so hard to tell sometimes what he's actually
gonna do he has the same telegraph with like two three different moves or he does that shit and
like what are you gonna do to get stuck in it and that shit is like driving in a blizzard it takes
up the whole fucking screen you can't see where you're going i'm angry i keep being like a tenth
of a second late on that all right we're going we're gonna go combo andy here okay don't combo
andy let's see what i mean in a minute stop doing fucking moves like do you have a fucking
stamina bar trying to avoid the fucking huge tombstones they got these like giant like
10 commandment slabs that are scattered around the whole fucking area all right we're going
combo combo this video game seriously like it was under the ground it was under the goddamn ground
it was like fucking tornado one of the blacks oh that can hurt you dude i can't fucking see
through these stupid gravestones man come on i'm so fucking dead let's just come on
he says so many different moves and he has 500 fucking million health like even when i get him
like down to like i only have joe biden wouldn't die to this boss i'm not sure joe biden would know
where x was on the xbox controller i don't think most people over the age of 60 would know where
the x on the xbox controller is so i don't think so i think i got an advantage time to angry flight
and i'll show you what i mean by that shit dude you have to seriously go across the whole fucking
game take dude left stick being crouched what were they thinking what were they thinking
what were they thinking i have to unbind it it's like fucking awful what can i change it to
there's nothing the amount of times that like i'm moving around and the left stick just actually
clicks in and he crouches it's just like what the fuck dude you're down on the d-pad that's
actually not a bad idea no but that potions though find it to the xbox button what can i make it
what is up on the d-pad switch sorcery what is uh no i don't know what i can even make it
i'm just gonna leave it without any okay yeah it's not happening now i'm just gonna i'm gonna
unbind it put it on right stick that's actually not a bad idea no right stick is um is lock on
that's a huge deal i'm just gonna unbind it dude that's so irritating you really have to put it
in the ground like the second one sometimes goes underground i'm in trouble actually you know what
i need i need more flasks i think i have to go adventure before i continue to do this
because as a caster losing a few flasks is like horrible horrible horrible i'm at like a
disadvantage every fight because i just have like three healing yeah i mean i'm doing like 25 percent
of his bar that's awesome oh man a little bit longer it's actually a little better i could
probably try just not using magic at all and just having five uh those flasks might actually be
better the bleed stacks i think are way better casting i think i just have to actually hit him
run not again right after it come on no i thought i got under it i didn't get under it
oh man you just get so caught holy shit i didn't think i was gonna go that far
oh
how long does he do it for how fucking long do you do it for
i should have gone forward but i just like he was just at an angle on me oh my god all right
i've made a decision there's the decision i'm not doing magic magic i think it just takes up
too much i'd rather have like six heals get up there actually hit this motherfucker lead him
and i think that's gonna be better let's go dude he didn't do the jump how did he not do
my damn rock next to me this little fucking ledge it had to be the stupid fucking ledge
i like bumping into the ledge it's like somebody came in and played like fucking
roller coaster tycoon and just didn't understand the terrain tool just fucking moved it all over
the place just die just die that move is like a full three seconds just go like one two three
calm down honey let's get you some tea you know i just i want to take that tool in roller coaster
tycoon that like you just drag it over and like smooth out these fucking bumps all right settle
down over an opening no you don't oh my god i'm not doing enough damage how many times did i hit him
i did like fucking big 10 of his bar why do i dodge to the left because it's burned into my brain
dodging right like it's hard to do for me get in there blood-borne style my problem with getting
in their blood-borne style is the guy is so fucking slow that like it's not like a dodge here we go
fight fight dodge it's just it's it's this slow ass encounter i just get i get myself killed
that's another reason why i can't do that the guy has like a fight me counter
this boss has a fight me counter where you're not supposed to fight it
even to go like this to his head use the quick step yeah but the quick step it's i don't know
sometimes it's hard to gauge sometimes like when you can and can't do it because if you use quick
step when you're locked on sometimes you'll just spin around it could be kind of jarring
i don't even know what direction i was just trying to go there he said your build is awful
i mean it's great for fighting like regular enemies but it's sorcery man like if you sometimes if you
don't go full sorcery you're you're in for some shit i would adopt all right hold on let me let
me get this right all right i'm gonna give him like one or two more attempts so then i'm gonna
go to something else is this why all the battle mages died out just do six magic flasks and
fucking run away it's so but i'll i will run out i will run out of flasks i can definitely do it
it's just here's the problem splitting between intelligence and dexterity is making both my
magic and my actual swings not as good as they could be right eventually it'll even out eventually
it should be fine but for now now i have to rely on both i could do it all right no more no more
i'm doing both headphones don't nobody talk to me i fucking hate that it's so dumb it doesn't
even give you a chance to fucking attack him he just hits you you have another move with that
fucking combo oh fuck off just swing it dude come on it's so stupid it's like his game is
lagging and he's not falling down i'm so dead god are you supposed to close the gap with this
fucking guy hitting the second phase consistently with magic at least it's not the trees the tree
center was had like a tactic you use the horse which by the way where's the fucking horse
why can i play with it where's the horse i was the where the fuck is the horse
where's the horse try this what the fuck boys don't help here they die in one aoe
on where where where where where i'm a little baby i don't like hard games dude i can't even
fucking see what he's doing dude god i tried to wait too what the fuck he does that stupid
shit man it's so hard to it's so hard to not get juked when he has 50 other moves he does
no stop doing this move what the fuck man dude he's done this like so many times in a row
i can't get a position on him he's talking strategy by the way oh my god i
i know i was doing so good god last one get in there boom boom get it my god can you seriously
the fucking aoe moves how many are you going to do in a row what the fuck oh my god what
he got agreed for the bleed i know it's just he has so he has so many different kind okay here's
the thing about elden ring listen to me they all have so many different kinds of moves so like
on a scale of one to ten like area attacks like short attacks quick attacks long attacks from a
scale of one to ten they got them all they have from one to ten it's so difficult to like predict
what they're going to do because they have so many different kinds of moves this is not like the
dancer that just like spins in a circle five times well i wasn't ready for that
can i just say can i go can i jump over that just jump but jump where jump over a lot of things
i feel like i've tried to jump over aoe moves and i just get killed the ground pound can be
jumped over can it i feel like i've tried that a few times i'll try it let's see what happens
but that okay not that one that's not a ground pound yeah that one when he goes
ah i would actually save a lot of time if it actually works i have to go around his right side
you have to dodge roll the second one so you have to go like bang bang i feel like he swings
too fast to dodge the second one after you get the eye cramp you're doing good at the beginning i
actually that last one was not bad just trying to like figure out should i do our right trigger
should i do a heavy attack maybe a heavy attack is better than just one or two i wonder how much
bleed how come is there a bleed counter that i can see i think that's better can't get away from that
one it also doesn't have this body goes off the screen too what the fuck i have no stamina
fucking can't see when he goes behind a fucking tree dude come on when he's like you can't see
what he's doing i can't fucking see him he does like the roll and it gets stuck somewhere and
then it's like all right what the fuck are you gonna do next fuck you fuck you oh be careful
he might get like stuck behind like the fucking giant blockade dragon and then uh good luck
finally he did he shot a projectile at you behind there by the way good luck oh dude really again
with this fucking bullshit like i if you're not at like the exact precise place you need to be
when he's randomly will do that that was such a good start too it's just like the dude remember
can you look at my bumble profile i can't get any matches um i don't know he's incredibly mad
this guy's fucking hard i meet his fucking fingers you're not as mad as last night i feel
like i'm playing the same boss as last night i feel like these are the same people okay i think
beginning as a fourth attack there it takes a fucking so long to do it how do you even remember
i keep i'm just so i can't get the slow attacks it's always been a problem
in every from software game i've ever played and this game is full of them
summon the lady i don't i don't want to summon i want to beat it on my own
i don't want to summon i want to beat it on my own without any help
any outside sources i got him down to like 10 like three or four times now i can do it
got stuck in the fucking gravestones they don't even need to fucking be here why are they even in
here what like if the enemies can get stuck on that stuff delete it why is it here so here's the
problem building bleed stacks on this guy's heart because by the time you almost have enough he
might just do the whirlwind move and then you just get fucking hit by it all right this is the last
one before i go do something else because obviously i need like another point in this weapon
or i need another point sorcery or something it's in the air my i can't dodge that second attack
yeah you can't dodge the second attack there's not enough time
once you by the time you land he's already swinging his right hand or his left hand
your armor is at zero percent durability all right last one for real actually last one last
one for real see what i mean like you just can't you can't stay near him fucking gravestones
yeah see he fucking hates him too he's pissed too he's sitting there going like all of why is
this here who put this here why the fuck is this light post here he's as mad as i am don't call me
mad he's bad too i'm getting hit by the axe it's hard to get that second dodge it's gonna be perfect
no dude it's give me the other blade give me the other blade dude come on i'm a mad i wonder like
i don't know if you just dodged through it i feel like you can still get hit by it
when he does the big fire thing like you have to run around him right you have to get around him
but you can't run to the left because he'll just hit you with it did you dodge through it like can
i go through that fire i feel like you can't i tried jumping over before and you still get
hit by like the residual hitbox like you can jump over the fire can i actually jump it
just hit last attempt i'm a liar i'm a liar god fucking get the shit out of the god damn place
come on where's the blade
get rid of the fucking stupid scenery why is it here what what is that ending what
do you understand why now i what the fuck is the point of some of this scenery bullshit i'm sitting
like in a fucking tree i had to burn through like three or four flasks that's so stupid
it's not worth dying over no he went the way with it i was going he went the i was jerry he went my
way run away far away we cannot harm you wowie wowie wowie wowie he had to do that right there
he had to do that right there i tried to get up and like jump but it was just too late i was too
i was on the ground already oh man i was right there that's just so unfortunate like the fire
thing i can't jump over it i can't dodging through it is hard too i i if i had mana or something
fuck man come on sprint i gotta dodge through it like that way oh i'm so fucking far away it's
a different way i'm good god damn it i still don't get it i gotta get away from that shit
dude fuck you are a huge ass arm fuck off oh my fucking god dude i can't i just it's so much for
my brain to handle just choking on those fucking moves just so annoying i have to dodge right
through the middle what the fuck it's just like okay so here's my problem when he does the flame
thing right it's like he this too that's why there's like you have so many different random
fucking ass moves one of them is like a big cone in front of them and the other one is like a big
slow wave but it's like it's hard to tell which one of those fucking two stupid moves it's gonna
be because you can't dodge through the one that's in the front no bleed where's the bleed bro where's
the bleed seriously where's the bleed i had so many fucking times one two
it's even fucking longer than that fuck this goddamn game one dude no that was i dodged right
through it and i got hit by a piece of fire that i'm gonna i would like the referees to go back
and fucking take a look and see if that actually happened it's like the fire was gone and i like
touched it with like my heel too late too late fuck you i should have my steam in the bar was
a little too low friend dude it's the stupid fucking gravestones that was probably the one
just getting like trapped behind fucking objects you can't walk through and like the fact that
everything has fucking collision and the collision is like a full square around the goddamn thing
it's like you just get stuck and they're everywhere they're fucking everyone it's like how are you
supposed to fight this guy in a a like fucking two-lane highway right here that was absolutely
the one this guy's area just sucks like asshole fuck this area fighting this guy here different
elevations the gravestones the gigantic dragon ass tree that's here you gotta fight this guy
in like a 10 meter radius like here i'll i'm got i got it i got it this guy's fucking dead
this guy's fucking dead mad yeah because that's like the fourth or fifth time that a run gets
blown because there's a gravestone behind my body that i can't like i'm just dead put them like up
in the fucking vistas and shit like they don't have to be so many down here how many people have
died here this is like this how many gravestones are there in fucking elven ring all right let's
go i don't understand bleed i really don't that was like three auto attacks and it and it did
bleed i have done like 40 auto attacks and it doesn't happen is it a cooldown what bad place to
be i'm just being a fucking clumsy i'm alive i'm fine i'm fine i'm alive god damn it man
oh god fucking damn it like the one move that he couldn't do in the one spot that he couldn't do
it in the one move that would have hit me if i when i get up the instantly i fucking get up
stay close to him but dodging some of those aoe attacks that he has he's gonna get trapped
i need stamina i need stamina all right fuck you see that's why like and you get trapped in there
like what the fuck is hitting me behind you can't go near him is it happening behind him too
such bullshit god it's so much longer even when you think even when you think you're holding it for
long enough it's still not enough fuck now so much variance in speed one two wait it's so hard to
tell i'm not going near him man no not again
fuck you no you can't i thought no he stops and he does the two fireballs come on he stops and
he goes fireball fireball and the one time he fucking does it there's just too much variance
it's like how am i supposed to tell am i too far away am i too close the fucking goddamn
variables on these fights yeah i know i have full mana but man i've got a thing going on here and
i'm doing well changing changing it up is bad so all over the place when it comes to speed and
shit but he was not gonna do another move i would try to fuck you all right all right all right
fuck you piece of fucking dog shit i you know what i need to figure out what the actual strategy is
there because i keep fucking it up i just keep getting hit by it every time
get away from the fucking tree i'm not having this happen again
dude come the fuck on i don't care who you are that's a stupid fucking move i don't care who you
are i don't care what your complaint is wowie blade hot hot too hot hit him what
oh
that guy sucks that i sucked that guy sucked this game's not even fucking me it's a great i love it
what a what an experience really trying to get going and fight him and get him and kill him
it was uh that was a very very interesting thing to do we got him it took a lot it took a little
bit of perseverance i got a little heated there but you know it's okay we got him fuck that guy
and fuck that area those stones fuck the tree fuck the dragon on the tree and it looks beautiful
but it's no place to fight this is no place to fight a human or an animal or a beast or a legend
or a fighter it doesn't matter i don't care what we're fighting this and pick another place
like i would walk in here and be like dude all right you and i can fight but like can we just
like go like out in the open like let's do like a fair fight let's go do like a duel man
and dr seuss lyrics that sucked i just missed everything about that what did that say
reverence of garfield i missed that literally that whole thing i said would it say great ruin
can somebody explain it i literally skipped it i can't fucking dude i almost died at the very end
i would have fucking eaten my controller dude i really would have eaten my controller when i
was just casting and it's just nothing was hitting him did you notice i want you to rewind for a
second if you can for a moment it was hitting like a gravestone it was like hitting this thing
it wasn't though it was just a little too far away like i was out of range but i thought it
was hitting that thing and i was sitting here just going gravestone andy you know what i mean
i was about to fucking flip out i was gonna fucking freak out i thought it was actually
hitting that these these two main bosses so far have been fucking hell god all the tutorials
there okay they both have this like i know i've done this routine like 10 times already let's go
take a short break yeah i will i'm gonna get some more water what do you think hey so for those of
you that were saying sorcery hey casual you're a casual i beat that guy pretty much without it at
the very end i may have thrown out a a little a little dingy at him but i did that without
sorcery i need a break after watching strength 12 just to be able to use items what do you mean
that doesn't count um let's do 2020 16 i must have an i can actually do it again take the power of
its namesake be a finger reader yeah we're gonna take a break in a second i just want to get
situated oh where is that thing of course how many of you guys watch the stream muted you don't have
to listen to the guy complain for like an hour like is it at what at what point do i do this is
the streamer die like three four five six times ten times fifteen times in a row and then like
when they die this is how i would do it this is this is stress so when the streamer dies for like
the 15th time and his mouth goes that's what you just mute and he's gonna sit there and be like
and then when you when he goes into when they go into the boss door you unmute it so it just
it's if you get to watch the stream normally that's like that's actually a good idea that's
what i would be doing just every okay if i die 10 times in a row to boss just mute me after i die
you're always muted on my stream okay where is this item it's like this prime evil stone
or something whatever it was use this fp to mimic nearby objects where's this thing
what where is it you got godric's great rune you need to take it to the tower
i got two things though wasn't it i got two different things didn't i
or was that just explaining what that thing was all right let's take a break you got the
rune and his soul all right let's uh i'll be right back i'm gonna get some water i'm gonna
get a refill of maybe some green tea and i'll be back we'll keep going i took a break what happened
uh i gave up on the game i uh i just like a little too hard i think it's just like too much like i
if they patch out i got i haven't beat the guy uh if they patch out like 10 to 20 of the gravestones
then maybe i'll come back and try it again it's unfortunate but i'm gonna skip break when i come
back we'll play pit cross oh i didn't loop it i'm not even kidding they guys i had to go change my
clothes i was wet i was soaking wet like but that that shirt was as if somebody put it into the
washing machine sorry that took a little bit longer than it should have but i actually just
had to change my clothes i'm in like a different shirt now i'm in like a star wars shirt okay
so what's the last thing that just happened a spot but godric the gravestone um and that was an
intense fight i had to believe i was cooking up that one while i was taking a piss um okay i need
to my lips are dry chatters are saying you smell like cream corn um i think i smell like kind of
coconutty um with a hint of like a lavender and like sewer gas okay i can just i can go that way
or i can go back and start looking around let me see what's this way because wait i have his rune
and after all that
felt the same way i mean like me and this guy would be the same person
this weasel was godric was always looking down on me bloody deserve thanks to you
you're gonna give me anything
okay i guess you can now okay well yeah he was uh he was a dick
sure was all right what's anything over here that i need to see i mean that looks beautiful but
what do i need to see here i can get those new sorceries right i'm looking over at my notes
read the great rune to see where to go next i mean i could just walk through here i just want to
make sure i didn't miss any items over here which i don't think i did because this is just the boss
area all right let's just go in the front door four hours to beat a boss andy that's not the
only thing i did i explored around the castle a lot i can't attack in here rewind that i don't
know i guess i'm in is this the place where i was before with the the council we see your character's
face yeah pretty much all you need to know is he's uh it got a long chin and a big nose and that's
pretty much every character i've ever made captain hook it does cut it does look like captain hook
holy shit where were you yesterday we really could have used you yesterday it actually is
captain hook and i have the claw oh my god i didn't even think about that it's warrant this
warrants an erin moment why shabiri shabiri shabiri grape maiden dear maiden where are you
please take my grapes all right i have a few key items i really need to look at uh this was not
the only way i could go so let me go the other way there's a joke here um you know what i really
messed up i i should have i should have made earnest what was i thinking i could have made
earnest so that i have captain hook there's really nothing else down here i feel like something is
going to be down here because why can i not swing okay well let's go oops okay when i get out here
i'm gonna finally get the use of my horse again i feel like it's been ages since i've been able
to get on my horse where am i okay where was the sorcerer okay sorcery guy is here what's the
fastest way to get to him wait what about after castle skip look at the menu oh that's the green
herb thing poison build up at hp this is a weapon coating hello worthless rubbish okay i gotta find
the finger reader great rune of the shard bearer godric devoid of any benediction seek the divine
tower of limb grave which stands beyond the great bridge from stormvale castle the great bridge from
stormville castle which is this way right like i'm just i just keep going this way imagine it's
just this way or should i go to the bridge it's the huge bridge of this bridge over here okay i
think the easiest place is probably to go here go to the tower i'm gonna go down i'm gonna buy some
spells and i have a few spells i want to buy let's get this on the map down here i forget exactly
where he is i got two of these on the map i don't want to i just want one where's the other one how
do i clear all my stuff but i remove my beacons because i don't i want okay that's one was two
okay he's down there i'm just gonna go that way trying to remember where he is where is this guy
a little bit of tree i'm gonna die here if i'm not fucking careful easy easy easy all right i can't
just like stare at a map jeez this fucking dumbass camera oh my god a little bit of me
where is he he's like under here all right you motherfuckers are really starting to piss me off
enough okay so he's down here this doesn't hurt me it doesn't kill me all right dude where are you
i need you to teach me spells where is he where is he is he not here anymore does he go
back here after you meet him not you not you not you he just left where did he go not you
oh okay there's there she is you again i thought you'd receive a summons to the round table the
felly loop we met at stormvale i'm glad to see you here i have something for you i found it in
godric's grafting grounds you defeated him you should have it make good use of it i don't intend
to make a habit of scavenging corpses arsenal charm oh yes i wonder if you've met my foster
father he's in his study the room entrance garden just over there if you haven't already
i'll introduce yourself at the round table i'm sure talking to him will be
raises maximum equipment load you might as well just use it
it's not you doors closed oh i'm gonna look at the painting
who's this isn't this place impressive the round table hall over quarters of the two fingers
and gathering place of champions who vie to become elder lord i never knew the guidance
bestowed upon us tarnished had such fantastic root although it's all a bit much for me in truth
i'm still looking for my own purpose your spells it's all a bit much for me in truth i'm still
looking for how many spells who has spells for captain hook oh it's this person oh it's the
finger reader
why is there a hand here
has taken its toll across the realm life lies in ruin pieces
foul curses and misery spread unabating but the greater will has not abandoned the realm
life that inhabits it so it is that the tarnished are guided by grace oops i'm sorry
are you that new tarnished until it was the tragical across the realm foul but the great
so it is brave to seek another of its kind to become the elder lord and restore the golden
seek another of its kind
i don't like this i don't like this this is weird touch the two fingers rapture what the hell that's
so weird
i feel like that's like attacking the world stone
so this is probably boss um boss shards boss weapons
who and you the strength of strength of the fingers
the fingers guide us all and you tarnished you are here to take our hand is this though
oh great rooms great children of the goddess queen marika
queen marika she who is vessel of the elden ring tainted by the strengths of their ruins
her children ward but none become and so grace was extended to your kind listen the fingers speak
the grito will has long renounced the demigods tarnished show no mercy
have their heads take all they have left indeed but remember what are you talking through
the demigods are each and all the direct offspring marika
gudrik the glove that's the only thing i can say in like the 10 minutes we've been walking around
with the power of remembrance menu you can draw out the power of remembrance namesake each
remember is can provide one power once the power is claimed the remembrance will be lost
axe of gudrik or whatever that thing is and i see what it looks like okay rafted dragon
faith scaling what is that it's faith it's not intelligence unfortunately it's the fist
only i knew that you're doing a faith strength build well i i believe i believe you've just
seen something that you should be using what if i don't want these can i just break it or
do i have to use that is it like the other games like can i just smack shit and eat it i can just
eat it for money right you can turn it into ruins just yeah just like all the other games
yeah i i can't i can't use either one of those things i use it yeah that's it of course
20 000 runes are you serious i mean it would have been cool uh that that dragon arm thing
is probably awesome all right is there anything else you need me to do so this is the boss soul
person all right fingers are here i'm gonna level up again i hope somebody has a staff do that gesture
in front of the fingers really what do you do gesture was rapture this is it looking this is
like what everybody's cat does it's like you look down the cat's just there like pick me up so you
look down the catches on your leg like i'm coming up here okay that was cool don't hurt that that
was very strange it's all right up ease up ease rest oh i can rest here i knew i could i'm not
sure what to do because there's a theory of dumping it into endurance and vitality
i feel like it's been a while but i feel like i'm falling behind a lot on damage right now
fighting godric i feel like i was not doing enough damage i i think i need to start i really need to
find that sorcerer because he had that that weapon and that move maybe some more mana
all right we're gonna do two and endurance get endurance to 15 and we'll get mined up to 14
and then i i saved those souls because i need to find that guy because i gotta get some of these
new abilities because that magic sword is essentially what i'll be using for the most
of the game i would assume i don't want to hug i know where the sorcerer is but i won't tell you
that's all right i wonder if he's not here why aren't you upset um i mean do i if you want to
watch me upset just rewind the vaude by like 15 to 20 minutes and watch me just absolutely call
out every single thing i don't like about this game it's the hardest game at walmart yeah it is
we were okay we talked there was a lot of back and forth about what i said during dark souls
3 i believe i talked about how fucking impossible the game was the game is so hard it's too hard
and i said it was the hardest game i was like it's the hardest game ever made it's like the hardest
game you can buy whatever and people are like oh dude what about like boshi and i was like okay
fine so it's like the heart it we came to the conclusion that it's the hardest fucking game
at walmart okay it's the hardest game at target okay it's not like some crazy like impossible
game that was made it's but it's what do you want me to say it was sakiro yeah it was sakiro
not dark souls 3 it was sakiro and sakiro was fucking brutal this is open now you've received
the wisdom of the two fingers have you oh this guy will talk to me now you like this more than
sakiro
i like okay
i need to see a few more of the bosses like some of the main story bosses
because as it stands right now the first two like main story bosses i feel like we're very
similar i want to see more before i have an opinion of like the bosses in this game
there's a story yeah okay so what are you after more great ruins then as your fellow allow me to
dive all your little knowledge the inheritors of the heroes boss fights were crazy and the
thing about sakiro was like you like the revive feature was very interesting even though the game
was really difficult and it was really brutal like in fact you come back to life like two
three times sometimes was really that was really forgiving
gorilla yeah that's crazy queen of the full moon you'll still be after more great ruins
but those are all the people that have the great ruins but this is where i need to ask
where they are i heard about the academy understand you've been speaking to me wait no
she's my daughter when she lost the guidance of grace youthful curricular purposes so i put her
to work do not hesitate to employ her despite her looks she is more than capable in the press
of battle godric the grafted lord of stormvale despite being the blood of godfrey first elven
lord he's a grotesque old fool his castle lies upon the cliff to limb graves northwest okay
but i suspect you know that well enough already because he's dead all right where i want to hear
about the academy because that's where i want to go that's the sorcerer academy general radars he
fought millennia to a stand house to lim gray hailed wilds lindgrave east has been engulfed by
the scarlet rot even approaching the region is no mean feat i've heard survivors of radon's army
are still in the wilds okay east and if it's true i said oh i doubt he much resembles his former
self then i want to know where are this person is the grace given his lord of laindale it lies
at the foot of the earth what are their retreat nope east of the altus plateau but the two fingers
forbid us from venturing there why until we've acquired enough great runes to repair the elven
ring set your sights elsewhere for the time being so that's like a hard boss where's this person
no no no not you the academy okay that's where i want to go
herself is no demigod her beloved to become queen marika's second husband
all right so we're gonna go north king consort also within the amber egg that was it's an egg
all right that's where i want to go we're gonna go north i believe i was already accidentally
kind of going that way here but where's the where's the sorceress where's this where's the
sorcery guy he's in a different spot somewhere else be sure to tell me if you meet a young woman
name line yeah she's reserved into my house she's been like i've lost count of the number
honestly oh you're not we probably fight this person again i would actually have like moves
did i kill this person oh okay this is bm that's bm i'm seeing if i can call the boys down here
you can't even swing that many times in a row in this game you can't swing that many times
in a row you just can't swing that many times in a row we have to all play by the same rules
and and we don't see you motherfucker let's go what is this fucking double frost bite i'll get
okay if i kill you do i get that frost move because i will do whatever it takes to get you
oh my god i forgot that those weren't spent oh my fucking god are you kidding me i thought
that they i why is that sorcerer not in this fucking building
i can't fuck it we were like talking about something and i just whatever i'm killing this
guy come on that sucks i can't believe i did that what's with the bm he actually drank a potion
oh god damn it how dare he do that i'll get him we got to bury him a couple times
i'm i can't believe i actually just dumped seven thousand souls into the ground
we meet again after all i apologize for any offense given by my bearing but able to move
you see so what do you need you defeated godric and claimed yourself a great rune
looks like we both got what we wanted out of stormvale didn't we well done friend something
to mark the occasion go on oh what are you giving me what are you gonna be a plus eight item
as you might have i still can't fighting days are behind you need to be polite holy shit
what is that dude why does this have to happen to me you were sitting in the one spot that he's like
hiding in this place like okay i thought it was just a balcony i don't think there was a guy
sitting against the wall dressed dressed as the guy in the painting and he's wearing the clothes
the blades wearing the same color scheme what is that plus eight c scaling oh it's a thrusting
sword that was some walter white panic moment it's actually one of these things but it's all
it's the best thing i have right now get away from tried to parry a jumping attack i can't
fucking believe it obviously just like have them stand up like that just have them all stand in a
line next to each other shoulder to shoulder yeah like why can't they all just be sitting at the
round table like oh i'm godric i'm uh i'm bodrick i'm codrick you're just oh yes we're here
strategizing i don't have to go look for him i can't believe he's just sitting over here i thought
actually like indicate some of the souls games the npcs move around and sometimes they're in one
spot then they're in another area entirely saves come your souls it's too late now
in the name of god is that whoa that's kind of cool actually cool the only problem is it's
it's a thrust weapon mad tongue has died hunter's tongue i this thing actually is kind of good
i'll hold on to it wow 1500 ruins hey always good to son thanks for the sword
uh i would like the it's 2500 i can't there's there's more down there is there more stuff down
here i don't see anything i can sell some stuff yeah i will what else is down here these doors
can't open bro i'm gonna sell some stuff to get 2500 to buy that at least the great sword one
because that is a really good move who can i sell to uh you right i like this guy this is my
favorite mpc the reason why this guy's my favorite mpc is because he stays fucking put
and he sits out in the open where i can see him is that guy who who do you sell stuff to oh the
blacksmith are they be careful now lay out all right i'm gonna sell maybe some of these weapons
that i know i'm not going to use only 100 that's it i mean i'm absolutely not going to use this
or this so it's a really cool weapon but it's going to leave i i'm not going to use it i need
what do i need 2500 i want to keep that never sell gear because it could come in handy
what about some of this shit temps invasion of other players worlds i'm not going to do that
24 god damn it okay it's 2400
uh i mean i don't i'm not going to use this meat dumpling it's it gives you poison it hurts
let me buy the great sword mr room somebody said i missed a room the room i believe i just
walked down there just died always good son all right this is what i want i want this thing
grants affinities yeah yeah thank you that thing is amazing from what i remember it's sort of like
a melee weapon i'm gonna remove this to put on this where is it wait is that the same thing
wait what's going on it's a weapon skill oh an ash of war where is it where is it that's not
okay ash of war or ashes so there's different ash of war and ashes so how do i put that on again
you can change it right how do i change my ash of war actually there's so many random fucking
things in this game i have to go to the blacksmith can't do it just on my menu oh wait i need to
blacksmith it needs to be a great sword what what what it needs to be a great sword
i thought it was a magical great sword what the fuck no it doesn't okay so this is
magic there it is you guys gave me a heart attack okay let me see how it works i wish i could just
swing the weapon here so let me put the spell back okay it's time to go miss the room go down
go down then up from where down then up what do i go mean like down like over the balcony
what are you talking go down then up are you guys are you trolling this is this dead person in here
cipher potter what is that it's a holy faith thing there's so much cool shit that's dropping
that has nothing to do with sorcery can i get a cool sorcery item i want like a staff or something
all right i'm going back time to progress he's finding out that no one likes magic
that's not true all right so it's time i want to go over here this big lake it's a huge thing to
explore i'm going that way if anybody has it if anybody has a problem with that you're gonna get
banned okay anybody has an issue with that you're gonna get banned i'm not gonna listen to that
i'm not gonna listen to people um kind of say don't fucking do that
go play like the main campaign get banned see you later sayonara you know what i mean
bye bye oh where'd you go bye bye all right let's go to the water let's make this our site to rest
we're getting toxic oh my god guys the horse is back a little camp all right haven't been to this
camp let's go for it this is my favorite part of the game so far 539 damage on a backstab oh my god
he swings so slow it's such bullshit stop swinging so slow dude it's so impossible to decipher
this thing does a lot of damage it's actually pretty good but it's kind of hard to use
okay quick look i gotta look at those hey fuck you cheating all right so can i get on the horse
oh he's getting away what i'm sorry oh all right that was a little cool little camp
anything else here ready be careful frozen raisins this just seems like kind of delicious
okay all right so this is telescope thing over here i want to see what that is too
uh there's nothing else here i don't think let's head towards that telescope is it to the right
is this thing here i don't know what it is it's like telescope looking thing
what is that i don't what is it nothing not really maybe a night time maybe it's night time
all right here's the lake i wanted to explore this because look at that there's a bunch of
cool shit over here i don't know what's that it's right there it's not a telescope dude
oh this is this is like a it's like a campfire shut up
where the fuck is my horse i'm trying i like camera just spun around just to go back here
and get on the horse there's no i can't see this is the fucking telescope like i'm spamming because
there's a there's people in every direction and there's a guy on a fucking horse just running
around just ramping just running around the circle around me i'm just going to the fucking
the lake where i wanted to go in the first place and not get distracted by the thing that's that's
i don't there's not even here i'm telling you this is nothing fucking here this is it why is so huge
i thought it was a huge thing all right relax this is cool though why am i so high in the air oh
i want to go there after the lake i'm going to the fucking lake nothing's going to stop me now
i'm just i'm driving right into it i'm not going to do anything else i'm just literally
going to drive into the lake and nothing's going to distract me okay here we are hit the fucking
thing ah come on hey boys let's go looks like we got ourselves a fight don't get stuck gone
oh somebody's still dead does that mean fucking hit him with something
where are the boys it says they're all still alive where do they go one of them died oh shit
oh
i'm good man we're cool oh shit oh shit you fucking can't be serious
i'm stabbing down with this stupid thrusting weapon hey instead of going like this go like this
what is this turtle get the fuck away from me
who's the dragon
oh you're playing dark souls hey son what a game you're playing
oh i wonder oh no no get on the horse what's happening get away from these gravestones
get me with these glorified gravestones oh my god did he just go excuse me video game
excuse me game of the of video degrees excuse me the video game you can't just disappear
that's what we call cheating in this industry that's what we call cheating
die fuck away from me what was that a new draconic power is available
a draconic power is available you've got a new draconic power where are the where are the boys
this whole time where are they ellas they have a hundred percent hp that was insane
the d's bomb that was so fucking dumb that was so stupid why they went they went away from the
dragon this game's gonna make me lose my fucking mind i swear to god they went to the bar i really
want to know where they are they all have full health i'm like all right boys let's get the
dragon they all turn and run get your souls yeah where are they where are my soul well that
actually is a turtle i'm not gonna kill it i'm sorry like we're up there
oh
that despawn seriously was such a good that was kind of lame i'll be honest i'm assuming he
probably has like a timer or a i i don't know like maybe you can't he can't go out of the area
everybody over here it's an area thing i mean that was really funny but i've that almost cost me the
whole encounter well okay all right let me keep looking over there if you didn't have a range
you'd be able to terrify the whole map that'd be kind of crazy though if you're just flying around
something else that i noticed too that i didn't really have to worry about before
so if the horse is dead you have to confirm that you want to use it on the horse it was kind of
weird because i just got shot with a gun like that was a bullet i got something new what is it
aiden armor oh it looks kind of cool same thing uh greaves okay i look cool let's explore the lake
these guys get pretty good souls in there oh they don't what okay i just lied to you okay i just
crab gets his own music i need my sorcerer's thing i need my sorcerer's thing and it's i can't
use it because it's on two hands oh my god oh my god joker's voice in the last few years
has started to sound like this crab eggs i don't know the older i got like the more of a mickey
mouse voice i have like when i yell i don't know what happened i used to be like go whoa now i'm
like whoa oh i'm like paul bearer like why do i have a paul bearer voice now what happened
oh look out i can't believe it the dragon's breathing fire the undertaker like what happened
to my voice what fucking happened oh tunnels started you started sounding like a gingerbread
man in trek bring it back up bring it back up because did you see that did you see it at the
left side of your screen an orb all right we're doing health no we're gonna buy new spells
inside was it on all right hold on here this is dangerous is there something on the ceiling
i think there's something on the ceiling just a rune that's too where's the elevator
is the elevator is it did it go up i went up me with my souls how do we get the elevator to
come back down is there a lever how do i can't get the elevator back bring the fuck up fuck up
all right i'm very mad and i'm gonna pretend to be very angry and like actually like not like fun
or like funny angry like messing around like really actually angry okay what the
it's it's that far of a drop it's not though why did that i went through like a wind tunnel
dude why is this so far is this gonna kill me if i land right here i'm just trying to die
to a place where they spawn i need my souls back now bro bro somebody said bro fall joke central
no i'm not trying to do fall joke central i'm trying to simply just get the souls and just
come back down here no it's fucking there give it to me okay so i can't do this i have to go up
here i can't do anything i can't do anything how am i supposed to get down is there something i
could jump on from here what can i jump on from here there it is okay we're okay now sorry about
that just a little problem let's continue to find out the heck is down here although i do
now that i'm not fighting a boss let's get this situated i am a magician no no we call it
magician here mage oh you're a mage no you're a magician what the hell is going on down here
oh these a lot of smithing stones that's what they're getting oh you were way more dangerous
looking than i thought you're all way more this is awesome this is where i can finally get some
materials okay another tunnel which way should i go i'm thinking this way
stone i'm really happy the game actually gave me an upgraded weapon so many people that aren't
doing this exact stupid thing that i'm doing well it's not that stupid but like the intelligence
and decks is that's what this weapon is for so a ton of people are getting this and see plus eight
they do a pog face and they go wait no dude that's not i can't use that and i'm sitting here
giggling i'm sitting just laughing my ass off does this go down or up because if it goes up
then there's an opportunity to go down there which i think wait oh this just goes down okay
wait look for secrets got one where is it what side is it on this side on that side what are
these statues for this guy has zero object permanence but i'm real fun at parties my
weapon is bouncing off of these guys these guys made out of this material that's kind of cool
lintstone scrap oh i thought it was a glintstone key another interesting another tunnel to go
through another elevator all right i'm actually starting to get confused because this is like
the third elevator i think i may have missed something oh my god that was just streamer
syndrome i didn't want to have to go back down because i was going to look over and people are
going to be like dude this guy's got zero object permanence like this guy sucks like really dude
you have to do you have to go up and down the elevator three times to know where to go
and i was like oh shit like people are gonna think i'm stupid so i have to i don't even know
where that is um where the fuck do i go marika you fool what i wouldn't is marika what is it
marika is the statue what marika is the statue i don't remember how to get there
it was like i jumped through here i went down i went down twice i think right it's not wait
it's not there i went down here and then it's down i jumped in the middle went down again
no i'm not this is wrong where the hell am i the elevator you just used but i have to jump in the
middle but hold on i didn't let me see what's down here though i'm not gonna die large glintstone
scrap what is this for oh wait there could be a hole right here you know what i'm saying
somebody's gonna attack me right they would have done something like that okay so that was worth
coming down here a few things did you kill the horse guy yeah you can charge up the greatsword
can i okay i'm a little more interested in this weapon now the only problem is good luck doing
that at any boss encounter in any game ever all right zero object permanence uh i believe
it's on this side i want to see the range critical miss i just want to see what the
item does okay finally finally finally finally let me get this let me jump over here
it's this ledge right there i'm ready here we go zero awareness this is not the right ledge it's
that it's that one okay it's that one great am i dead if i jump off this golden rune and then
the whatever that is i want it somber smithing stone excellent okay well are we ready uh if you're
if you're low on smithing stones i recommend going to this stage of the map right here
right here the limb grave tunnels there's plenty of materials for you to gather to be able to
upgrade at least two or three times there's a guy in there this guy's fucked are you ready for this
i'm gonna aggro this guy and then i'm gonna run back here and go up the elevator and he's gonna
drop down and die i'm getting ready preparing to escape oh i can't fuck i can't i can't boys
i have no mana left what an idiot what a fucking idiotic thing to do what is that
it's so hard to tell what he's doing one more time okay easy game is not even a hard game
rare medallion raw medallion that was cool what a cool little dungeon
anyone that's smithing stones i'm just i really am i need to like settle down i'm burnt okay i'm
burning like 30 extra energy by like being loud and weird i need to like i gotta settle down
i'm being too like loud i'm burning extra energy okay there's nothing else here is that a
is that a i a war thing one of those war things not what is it roars and breath attacks
oh man man i feel like i'm burning calories is watching you but you are it's like for an hour
but you are that was really cool all right i love the little random dungeons man that's the best
part of the whole game i know the bosses in these souls games from software games are the best part
everyone's like oh i love the bosses uh-uh not on this one i think the main story bosses are like
all the way down to the bottom versus like exploring the open world and finding a cool
little dungeon that is way way cooler to me now bought that the huge main story campaign bosses
so far i've been all right they've been cool but that's having little dungeons like that
that take like 30 40 minutes and there's like a little mini boss at the end
i find that way more interesting to me right now like going and exploring the
the like go okay first coming to the lake right there's like oh shit i'm at the lake
oh here's a good here's a guy here right it's cool there's a dungeon go find the thing at the end
there's a few more places i want to see but i really probably should get out of here
and go explore something else collect these don't wait our flies or those bats the bats
ruin you probably like breath of the wild and probably so we did this wait dragon burnt
ruins no he didn't i did this what's the wait that's where the dragon came from
hold on a sec new area a little dungeon or something dragon burnt ruins bye nobody move
nobody move nobody move nobody move the safety at the door this safety at the door this safety
at the door there always is this eye frames the whole time you open a door okay should i do the
steak of marika because it's right there is that the statue that i hit in the head that looks i
feel so bad for jeremy he looks trapped trapped like i can't leave all right so what let me get
this straight steak of marika so you can have a choice sometimes to spawn but how what's the
criteria for spawning here do i have to have seen it just like walk by it because i don't activate
it this is supposed to be my line of sight we're gonna have to get the boys involved in this one
here you just have to see it okay ding dong sorry uh let's see crash the party
me and the boys just figured we'd come and see what you guys got here
oh jewels trinkets help help me that's like a terrier what's this like don't die why is there
a terrier in this game this just like that's just like a fucking scottish terrier get him a big wave
i think we clean it up god boys okay i'm here i'm gonna go back down here i'm gonna drink a potion
and i'm going to get rid of these watch this i'm gonna just bowling ball them check it out ready
i'm gonna scoop them all up and run back why did they not aggro this you know you guys just get
in there and just help me by the way master looter is on i get what it's in there if you have enough
dkt maybe we'll figure it out but do all the work got hit by the encounter not good okay
okay mike mike nice it was all right but i can't come from the fucking guild like that you know
honestly this was honestly i get guys we can come clean this whole thing was a fucking test for you
see if you can handle it and you can't you pronounce that you can't handle it i'm really
sorry dude maybe you'll find a better guild somewhere but like that this whole thing was
to see if you could kill a fucking grab you can't rune arc oh my god i can't wait to open
up the treasure what happens it's kind of like gassed silly a crystal tunnel where are the boys
oh yes gravity stone fan gravity stone chunk oh wow this is cool oh boy watch out watch out
watch out watch out don't go in there don't go over there either these guys have made it the
same chunky bullshit what the fuck was that what's happening what the hell was that you got to
change guild the boys are not cutting it anymore this place is horrible by the way those are
shrimps they really are like giant shrimps what where's my respawn here is it just back at the
statue am i stuck here holy shit i'm all the way over here this is weird all right
all right all right all right don't fuck around we're playing this super safe i'm not messing
around there's a weird huge skeleton bug shrimp people where is he is he next to me
oh he's up there oh sorry um can i backstab i let me try to backstab got these spikes that
just go out of you and this excuse me where did you come from there's enough who threw that one
everybody behind me it's where they go i don't want the stupid claw go for it by the power of
the great sword i think sucks i'm i'm literally uninstalling that i'm literally uninstalling that
i'm equipping that right now i dodged it accidentally get the fuck away from me
don't forget these you jackass okay okay i have nothing i'm in trouble here
there's so much shit down here there's so many materials what if i just avoid the big bug guy
i don't get shit on it's so much goddamn noise hide hide hide quick where's that other bug
up there right look at all these things that are here oh my god look at all these materials
i think he saw me those crystals crystals everywhere okay all right let's go anything
else down here are there any salads in this game why did i read that slowly when i slow me i you
know i mean that joke i mean fucking slow there's an animal down here i just heard it i'm gonna
climb down this ass bait the game is waiting for me to go down to a certain place to have the guy
run at me jesus of course i'm gonna be paranoid are you serious rock grease it's another little
dungeon what's down here whoa oh coral what is that i think alive what is that is that a big
turtle oh i thought it was a big turtle going like this i mean the thing has to die well that's a
boss area if i've ever seen one i don't know what that is but i don't want to be near it all right
settle down settle down what the fuck like general grievous enemies all right fine i'm just gonna
that's very upsetting to me i can do i can swing three or four times with the crust
and not even have to worry about this but you know what let's just go ahead and do this because
who cares at this point what does this guy work if we drop something 500 souls and strip of white
flesh well now i'm gonna okay they're just everywhere what's the point i'm gonna go back
and i guess this is boss right this has to be a boss and they listened you notice that this is
a big open area just final destination it's not like a hundred gravestones nice and flat
let me just see if what i can do here because i'm gonna i don't want to lose any souls i already
lost seven goddamn thousand like a dingus i got a lot okay i can i can break these i think i will
do it yeah there's also a couple of spells i can still buy too right which i will did you get to
godric i beat godric and i was very very unhappy for a majority of that hour or plus that it took
me to do it let's go back to i can just port here so that's fine let's go here wait what
what do you mean can't leave go out here i can't tp indoors oh okay he's about to be very scared
all right there we go so i'm gonna go buy the other spells is this one that he has that i
know i wanted there was a defensive one and then there was a regular attack one forget it fun to
see you play a game that you actually enjoy instead of fart simulator it's time to chap stick
it up just for a minute my hands are so sweaty that like i couldn't even open this okay what
do you have that i want always good to see son i want okay glintstone pebble it's an ash of war
these are all ashes of war what about that guy didn't that guy have other stuff the other sorcery
guy dude that's up here this guy right where was that other guy there was a guy sitting down
at a ledge i think it was here he was sitting at like the ruins where were they no it was here
it was here right i think it was up here yeah he had a couple other moves that i wanted it's the
church yeah yeah yep yeah how come this guy doesn't go back to town well i need to like remember to
blink okay bud of course this one here starlight okay let's get it just to have it so what am i
supposed to do with the scroll that i have this thing what do i do with it what am i supposed to
give it to academy scroll give to a learned sorcerer to acquire new sorceries what do i do
with it great glintstone shard swift glintstone shard i do have to get access to the academy
well at least i got that i'm actually not gonna use it but i i'm gonna have it just for when i
need it now i hate having souls like this though i have a lot of shards maybe it's time to upgrade
something you know i'm saying you talked to the finger lady i did i wonder if i can upgrade
this sword is pretty good though i like it did talk a lot of shit about frost weapons but
already upgraded so i can't complain about it the dragon stuff that's right
where have you are took you for dead no matter it's lay out your own
that's your war lint blade phalanx that's what the one that i had before determination is the
new one right this is do i get an ad description of what it does nightly skill hold the flat of
the arm into your face and pledge your resolve powering up your next attack i don't think so
i think i'm actually gonna put this on because this thing kind of sucks
and i can at least move around with that on
and scarcely swing a blade but she has a gift spirit tuning i saw another one like a
sheva same view like a spirit tune okay uh this i need six smithing stones three i mean i could
just this is probably what i'm gonna do well i find another goddamn staff one more time i don't
want to use the bigger smithing stones like that's not a good thing claws are cool they are but i
this thing has actually been working pretty well it the claws were great for bleed if i need to
use it my will all right let me go talk to that person where were they not you i don't want to
hug who is it you thank goodness i'm still looking for it's not even no it's whoa it's all of it
much for me in truth i'm still looking hello what the blacksmith said there's some kind of
gift i don't believe you if i do have this talent i suppose i should try to hone it shouldn't i what
is it i'll ask master hugue to teach me certainly he does appear intimidating and holds no love for
us too i know he's trapped here at the round table hole just like jerma he's trapped here he can't
leave so if i do have a talent for spirit tuning and goodness knows that would i suppose i should
try to hope i'll ask master okay we'll do it hurry up i got stuff to hone ready all right well that's
cool uh i'm gonna buy some stuff what can i do now 2400 souls is enough for me to not want to
fight this boss because i'm just gonna lose those souls i'm never gonna get them back
so i need to buy something with those wizard lady it's like the old lady right there's a vendor
over here somewhere down here yeah okay finger seal what's that rune arc that's what i picked up
so this is a permanent hp increase if i use it i don't get it i have a stone key that i can use
yeah but i think i need two rune arcs like humanities but they're more rare just buy the
rings i guess i could just buy the rings just to make sure i have them either that or another
shield well how is this any different heater shield it's for multiplayer yeah um rings or shield
more spell spaces metal shields negate physical damage when guarding i guess it's not it's not a
terrible thing to have i get it okay this is a parry shield yeah i mean this is just better
bunch more physical i could i could guard start guarding the only issue is i can't cast with that
but it's okay get all these off i'm not using them okay let's go let's go try it let's go get
our ass kicked might as well all the dragon stuff that's right i'll look at it what would
that be under is it an item lords and invaders that's one of the other thing that i got
who would it be dragon thingy dragon heart gain power of the dragon at the dragon communion
altar okay dragon communion altar well i gotta find that well let's just walk out here here we go
this time i've got my stuff equipped ready all right what do you got let's see it i can use the
horse swamp of ionia another rune arc interesting run away
shit settle down who who coo coo coo glintstone oh marionette soldier armor focus bites all right
resistance to focus problems holy damage reduction magic damage reduction put it on i don't like it
bro thrust is op all right so what do we got what's here a lot of nothing there's nothing
up here though what's that i don't know knock it up by the shack beyond the southern gate
stop by the shack beyond the southern gate must be go this way what else is over here though
i'm just checking each little nook and cranny whoa got a new dog that's got a lot of health
will you die just stab him in the face already i didn't even oh this fucking thing all right
watch out watch out watch out beast blood what's up there wow okay this is getting weird
holy shit i'm out of mana jesus man these guys are crazy okay i can go up here or i can go this way
let's see it's the bloodborne realm it actually looks pretty cool glintstone check over here
that's a big boy he's huge he's massive what am i doing get put a weapon put a weapon on
put a fucking weapon on that him right there shit i gotta respawn and just start stabbing him
hope i have enough damage to kill it where is he okay let's go here we go and what'd you get
there's nothing in that that's kind of bullshit bullshit well god more bugs
he has to explode you have to explode new spell though let's check it out i think that's a holy
spell i don't think that's a uh that is a holy spell sacred ring of light used by the commanders
of the clean rot knights gather a sacred ring of light in the armament pirate fords can be fired in
rapid succession these belong pole arms i think this is holy i don't think that's for me let's go
get our souls back summon your new squad i i will in a minute you know i need something like this
arm rest sucks i need my arm rest to be made out of like putty or something like clay all right
what's down here can't open the map i gotta get out of here get away get away get away get away get
away get away what's that flag okay oh smithing stone an anion whatever that was something beauty
hello okay who the fuck are you wow you're gonna play this game fine i'll get off the horse
you want to play this game fine scarlet what what is that poison or something oh that hurts
oh all right so be here i think these guys are hard i think these guys are hard i think this is
like a heart area you're under leveled for here yeah it's i kind of want to okay let me get my
souls and i'm gonna run this way of course there's a swamp right water's poisonous i think it was him
attacking me that was hurting me right giving me poison yeah there's definitely stuff back in uh
limb grave that i have been saying but let me just give me give me a second i might be able to find
something cool here let's fuck all the bullshit right let me just take a look killed my horse
okay what is over here tons of items here something's gonna come out of the ground
right this is two purple items halid moon arc sacramental bud and the spitting stone okay
i do like this area though this is not like the typical swamps that they put in their games this
is actually kind of this is actually cool it's more spores than it is swamp that's all right
that's kind of cool now the real question is what's here
it's a point of interest right here it's a trader
lion pot he champion pauldron flaming bolt or gravity's advantage okay maybe should i buy um
buy pot crack pot do i have one i wonder if there's a crocodile and it could be
i guess i'm just gonna buy pot i already have one oh i'm finished yet
i give you the can i sell you that back wasted activate the campfire well that's just random
vendor all right um do i go i think i'll go back to the limb grave here i think i'm way out of my
league there's one i'm gonna turn i'm gonna go turn around i'm gonna go over here i feel like
there's something cool right here i'm going this way for a minute just keep your eyes out got
something hey don't look at me it's in parry excuse me what's up with that
i kind of just panicked there for i don't know why kind of for no reason
i was just panicking just kind of bizarre i just was just freaking out because i thought i dodged
the first one the second one but i didn't know why i needed to dodge two more times that was stupid
the jewel of dragon this is it i actually found it i have the so i can do the dragon spell does the
dragon spell is it intelligence base because that would be pretty huge if it was agent dragon
cookbook well i'm glad i'm getting these for later so all these places i can travel to that's
gonna help out when i know i need to go here demon altar ritual of dragon communion where's all this
cool shit for sorcery flames dragon breath scarlet rot breath it's faith where it's at did i did i
pick like the there's got to be some more cool sorcery stuff right i want you to go that way
you know what let's go see what it is it's like the edge of the earth wants me to go over here
i'm very curious what this is i this is probably high level bullshit but whatever i'm going for it
i just want to see what it is what i tried to double jump to time it i yeah i tried to do that
correctly i guess that was still too high that dog is huge do you think i can kill the dog on
the horseback this is cool this game is so cool this open world dark souls is so cool
all right let's try that again these dogs are huge i didn't even hit the ground yet
what why did i hit the ground preemptively i was like five ten feet off the ground
i hit the ground preemptively that was not right here it's not right here it doesn't work
wait i can't do like the scout from team fortress why not well i'm guess i'm just gonna go the
regular way then and it's not yoshi yeah but i mean the one that makes sense that you'd be able
to do that all right it's down here right over here look at that weirdo what a weirdo that's a
weirdo okay that's a human with a gigantic bird head that's not hurting him really at all
shit i can hurt these guys all right i'm not even i don't even want to be here i'm not supposed to
be here i'm just checking it out because it's pointing this direction i'm i'm exploring the
world this is crazy look at how cool this is this is how dinosaurs really looked what the what's
that wait what are these dogs on my whose team are they on are they on different teams
is holy shit oh just kill each other just kill each other and by the way
why don't we get the boys involved yes yes hey hey hey hey you're out of bounds
hey buddy you're out of bounds get them they're killing each other this is just like
hold on i'm gonna get my staff out all right i'm gonna go for the uh what do i go for i'm
gonna wait till all the guys have been killed and then i'm gonna walk around pick up all the
items all right they're about to kill the dog let's thin them out a little bit this guy right
here sorry you were picked to be the first person to die okay just making it interesting
dogs nice that was a parry all right you're way too strong so you have to die next this guy this
knight right here stay away from me though okay we're gonna thin this guy out here that one you're
dead you right there the knights are actually starting to become a problem kill one of those
knights please hey hey hey excuse me out of bounds i'm trying to aim at you and it keeps
changing my target like aim at the fucking sir come over here please come over here over here
are we doing look at all these souls i'm just all right the knight has to die
how do you miss a guy that you can't even see you hey oh he's still alive item collection time
one of the dogs is dead nope okay all right all right i'm gonna be ready to kill the dog in one
hit why are you so strong actually come over here come over here i changed my mind come this way
there's still two dogs over here and you guys need to follow me because you have to fight these
things because i'm not fucking doing it who cares follow me come on all right go on shit no you're
supposed to kill him oh my god i wasn't paying any attention dude what's going on now he's
blood all right i think we're good tuber transformation i got some gloves there's
one more enemy here all right successful lot of souls that's awesome all right that was pretty
cool that was actually really cool how much health do you have is it enough for me to spam and kill
you might be let's go for it very good so what the hell is even down here a lot of nothing don't be
greedy what else is over here i'm about to leave oh hell yeah perfect oh i can upgrade my flask yeah
i did that now do a pee break i will in about five minutes we're doing uh dexterity after this
a ton of golden seeds all right i already used it i think i i already used it i guess okay what's in
this building i'm just gonna examine what's in the building and then we can go from there i think i
can probably go up i can all right there's something over here okay well fine goodbye
heavy crossbow so what do you got stored up here three stooges the chest there's somebody else all
the way up that's the question sorry about that okay back down back down back back down back down
go on go on go on go on go on go on go on go on go on go on go on all right so you just pick
your head up and go back down whatever they're all just sleeping up there no one's there's
whatever i got this i got this uh-huh okay yep come on not gonna follow me down
all the way down get on the ladder what am i doing go up why am i doing this
i do that for i could have just climbed up and i just lost two thousand souls i could have just
gone up i don't know what have i like rage took over i had to like slide down and get hit them
and like hurt them i could have just climbed up without even a single problem what was i
doing i need to know what's up there there's probably something up there like a chest or
something put your shield down howard put your shield down put your shields down
put your shields down stop moving just stand still i freaked out because i thought my health
was at zero it was the it was the exact same color as the sky for a second and i was like why is my
health bar zero i kind of freaked out both of you just cheeses the whole game what are you talking
about the last like the last like three or four bosses i've bought without sorcery i'm a battle
major you just don't want to you don't want me to use sorcery like i have 22 points in intelligence
come on get down here holy shit is that the only guy that encounter was yeah tell them to stop
cheesing me i'm sitting there i can't even climb the ladder yeah that guy's asleep over there he
comes ready all right nice hey you guys they call freddy fencing because of your elden ring fencing
gameplay um i've been called a few different things yeah all right so what was the point
is another ladder it's actually another ladder right there come on something good something
worth coming up here for arrows sting talisman that seems probably like extra damage on range
but let's see what's up here uh is it what is it yeah okay whiz raises attack power of sorcery
spells still cool coming up here all right it's time to go back to limb grave it's time to take
a break and i'm gonna i want to go this way i think either here or here this is like the spawn
and i need to wait a minute hold on wait wait wait is it time to i actually go back and do
this how many um it's two stones to go in the one at spawn right so if it's two stones to go back to
the it's four thousand to buy one i have one i could go like here and go like down this way
essentially right let me try that first though let me let me farm just i will take a break after
this i'm gonna farm a fight here get enough to buy one go open the one at spawn see what's in there
i just need i need four thousand good luck everybody don't be a dickhead really you know
i'll just fight okay i need four thousand come on go for it weirdly enough they're not the dogs
are not doing that much damage to these guys like at all kind of getting destroyed harry i'm just
waiting for one of you to die i don't care who this is gonna be worth like a thousand you gotta
get the boys out all right sure why not let's get the boys out here and then we come in and
we claim victory that's such bullshit like i'm such a piece of shit for what i'm doing right now
hey don't blame me blame the game that lets me get uh experience points when i don't do anything
work smarter not harder i got way too complacent okay 3d 30 35 000 out of mana we're almost there
one all right let me just switch to this get a couple of stabs in i am on no one's team
such a dude i'm such a dick i have like all the cheat codes i'm not supposed to be here
so bad okay let's go i've got enough souls i can buy it we're gonna see some cool content here you
ready anybody drop anything who sells this shit something this guy does right somebody does
who sells them you do right you're the person in team fortress too when everybody on both teams
is trying to chill and hang out and you the one guy that come in and ruin everything yeah i just
like i just boom boom drop an entire magazine or entire clip of stickies in the room and then sit
there and go and just watch the kill feed have like five names on it fucking dick who's this
should be left well should you spy a mariner unless you wish to lay down your life in vain
those who live in death should be left or more should you buy a mariner whatever that means
okay i'm gonna buy one of those things and then we are gonna go from there to
the spawn of the game i'm gonna put both keys in and we're gonna see what happens
actually pretty excited this actually seems pretty cool very excited let's do it uh it's
like right here right first step right is it two it's three no it's not it's it i thought it was
two it's actually three it's three yeah people no no i'll get down here we'll i'll get down
here and we'll figure it out where is it bro i gotta go pee i know i know man i know one moment
i'm gonna get the bonfire there it is okay i'm gonna open it rest here open it see what the
hell is down here actually no this will be when we come back because i want this thing to be a
big reveal all right let's go pee i'll be right back um how long have i been streaming for because
i'm streaming tomorrow too how long has it been six hours all right we're gonna go for like another
hour or two and then i'll be live again tomorrow with more elden ring make sure you loop the music
i will play uh we'll play a different one when you guys are recognized right back don't be time
to see what's over here great beginning of the game very excited i feel really bad if there's
frostbolt bolts down here i'm gonna be incredibly upset about it
okay very cool that song is absolutely but what's the word i'm looking for dope
seriously that song is dope okay let's do it use the keys
what we got that poisonous it is poison oh shit it's poison
oh scope looks like we are a little bit of a poison shaggy is just morty for freaking morty
what was that you see that that was just like a car driving god um did i miss anything back here
this poison is going to stay on the whole time but what can i do i'm not saying character wise
they're the same i'm saying that vocally they are pretty similar now what can i slide down here
when does it stop what the fuck turned and bumped into me and they killed me okay piece of shit
so there's probably a rhyme or reason for me to be able to actually just go like this and run really
fast and not have the poison build up fast enough maybe jumping will slow it down it does not
just run before it fills up all the way and i should be okay and i am okay what do i do about
this i think you just follow it down what exactly what i'm gonna do i thought there was gonna be a
slide i thought i was gonna just like start sliding down anything over here there's a way down all
the way they guys have to keep going well there's gonna be an item in one of these what a bad time
to leave i gotta check every one of these holes because you know there's gonna be an item in one
of them it has to be hello okay hello why was that guy so magical i don't have enough
am i safe here or it's not i thought there was going to be a second one on the other side going
up and down i didn't think that one changed tracks oh well
ah you gotta love those dungeons right you gotta love those dungeons i will eventually okay i just
have to be patient just be patient and stop doing that stuff i know there's no items on any of the
ledges or anything so i can just run through there's a guy in this one no there's a bow and arrow
yep this guy here guy comes over here yep i think i remember that okay so now
i just gotta keep going just run turn the corner run go this thing does not stop i need to find
another little uh place to go right here let me get a good look first i'm not just running down
there how far does it go does it go all the way around no it stays here that doesn't seem like
very far is there another safe zone what the fuck are you what i'm trying to spell the sprint button
what the guy just fucking killed himself he just fucking jumped onto the tracks
i thought it hit me what did it was a foul ball what was that weird foul ball was it did it bump
into my sword and i think my sword hit me in the head oh man is so there's more dude okay uh
where's the next place to go i don't see another place to go it's right there
do i follow it down i think i have to follow this down because i'm not gonna have enough time to
run down that whole way i gotta follow it down run run run run run run run run run run run run
run i gotta follow it down pretending is exhausting okay but i had the right idea
just i didn't i caught the lip you piece of shit i probably could run all the way to the second
thing i can just facing in and out of reality horseshit all right turn just go down i know
where to go from here and then just follow it down wham hurry up hurry up just keep going
you had it keep going am i gonna die here the fucking camera sucks okay so you have to go
you gotta just keep going okay so when you turn you just have to run all the way to the bottom
i get it okay this is the one i'm gonna get to the bottom just keep going after that corner yeah i'm
just literally just gonna run just run run run run run after that corner just keep going all the
way down run past the bridge and i'll be out of there it's the last one i promise i'm gonna get
it here this is it this is the one this is the last one no don't push me into it don't push me
into it all right this is the one here we go this is it ready when it goes up okay when it goes up
i'm running for my life all the way don't stop don't stop don't stop don't stop go go go go go
go go go go go go go go go go go no stopping run run run run run run run run go go go go
safe zone safe zone no keep going keep going keep going it's not here yet
uh um what where am i where do i go hey where is it where is it oh shit it's still following me
should i go i don't know what to do oh it's hard to tell it goes all the way down there's a little
thing on the right i think i can just sneak into the thing on the right and let's see that little
like uh nudge sticking out i think i just would go down there i think so is there a bonfire down
here this is a boss down here are you kidding me there's no bonfire or anything i can respawn
here let's go who's down here what the fuck holy shit holy shit this thing's crazy all right
so let me see put the headphones in let me see if he does he has like these like i'm thinking stay
in his back stay in his hind legs he's just so big he takes up the whole room yeah it's definitely
right it's definitely his back damn so i don't know this is such a tiny little area you still
have the shitty default shield from the tutorial i don't know i don't i don't what can i block
maybe this is a block fight i think you honestly i think you just stay right behind him stay right
at his ass i'm thinking try to stay behind him his tail kind of swings around not look that
effective i had the right idea i think is just try to stay and i'm i'm not doing there's no time
for spells here this really sucks because i cannot change the allocation i have to beat him with four
blasts boys don't work down here i can't even summon the boys even if i wanted to what am i
talking about here they come jesus dude this guy is just a fucking slob he's one of those bosses
that you don't know what he's attacking when he's just moving his body it's the fucking tail the
tail is sensitive you know what i mean like which one of those is attacked and which one is this guy
just moving around the room i think it's the tail someone's rotten stray spirit let's try that
here is rotten spirit versus rotten spirit might be about the flask it yeah well let's let's see i
mean this guy's insane so there's no distance really let me see maybe the belly this guy's
fucking ridiculous it's not the face dude what come on i mean how do you even how do you even
decide when he's gonna attack how are you supposed to even know he this this this dude is just
crazy are the flaws they're so under leveled though and what about maybe distance maybe this
is better i can at least see what he's doing right i think that's the play i really do
i think this uh boss is uh like 10 bosses try sorcery i don't think i'm ready for this dude
he's crazy let's let me try sorcery and just like run away can i two hand the staff can i two hand
the staff and that's how you charge i wonder if i can do something weird here hold on let me two
hand stuff and i actually doesn't work doesn't seem particularly weak to it either well now i
don't have a weapon i will block your attacks best bet but spam heavy attacks with the uh with the
rip here are you you're just punching the dude that's worth it i think it's worth it let's try
it i'm there's no way i beat this boss what about fire i don't even know if it hurts him i mean it
does oh there's no way i'm supposed to be here hey you want to fight the boss all right here you
go let's you want to fight this game this this game's boss this sounds fun all right here's your
screen it's time for you to fight the boss good one uh this ain't happening it's not happening i
know i know where they are though i know i know i know what's on spirit what happened to my sound
but i want to fucking beat him you know what i mean like i know i it's like this is just game
just gets you get obsessed with something and you can't leave even though i'm like 30 levels
under leveled for this dude i use fire but i'm gonna waste so many materials that's no i'm not
gonna be able to do it he's too spammy i i need to be able to eat hits and at this stage of the game
i cannot damn he still hit me with it no fucking way no way that's not happening
i need a i need a health bar three times as big as this twitter omega l all right i know but like
it's so hard to leave don't you know you know okay it's so hard to leave because if i beat this guy
oh my god it'd be a huge deal like oh but just what the streamer did the streamer like beat this
fucking gawdrick the tree ulcer he actually beat him and he's not supposed to be here and
holy shit wow like what a gamer i want that i need that what the hell are you doing
were you guys there a turbo 985 beat the ulcerated tree spirit at like level 31
were you there it's dumb it's dumb too like that was dumb this guy even have blood
fuck you you weren't even moving attack moves no i'm serious were you there when i did this
because i'm gonna do it especially with this uh with this build all in health potions i could
go get health potions only and then but i have to make the whole trek back down here
i ain't coming back down to this piece of shit he's dead now fuck that up sorry no fuck all right
when does he do this like 50 i got an unbind crouch worst fucking thing in the whole game
seriously like honest to god that's such a bad place for that like that happened to like unbind
left stick and rebind it like stop squeezing the controller do you see the game this is not
like mario party this is not mario party 2 the what how are you not supposed to what i'm not
sitting here like oh wow watch out watch out for the mushroom i'm gripping this thing like
it's fucking about to strangle me i'll get this i'm fucking beating this boss you bet your ass i am
i don't need full estus i don't need it i think i broke my audio cable audio is only coming out
of one ear it's weird okay i got it i got this motherfucker right now i forgot to unbind it
just kill me you know okay you know how they make it not awful is if you have to hold it for like a
full second like if it was like hold left stick for like one crouch it's like who's crouching in
any of these fights i'm gonna give the fucking boys a call on this one you better believe it
you better believe that i'm giving them a ring a ding ding not be fuck what i just do
fuck settle down stop swearing all right let's go boys bring him up it takes too long to cast it
it's not worth it it takes way too long to cast it's just guaranteed to get hit
yeah it's a waste of time you have to literally go like this ding he's literally got you in his
mouth already do it on the second phase it's not a bad time to do it but like if i just focus and
just fucking go hit him in his gut all right quiet quiet i knew he was gonna do it fuck you i
wasn't even there fuck that you don't have any time to fucking do that at all you get there's
no time to run at least i know what time he does it don't do it again man oh it's so slow
wait he blows up more than once i thought that was just like a i'm going to phase two now
walking on sucks because like it locks onto one central point and you might you can't get close
enough sometimes between each phase doesn't he only have two and settle down too you know
what's really killing me is the stamina i just don't have enough just like if i had like 10
plus more points in stamina maybe this would be like much much easier to do we see your heart rate
um start like 280 i don't like walking on i got him pretty close a few times ago but i
i'm just i'm just not supposed to be here and what's five out of ten decide to do you
burn all your cooldowns all right here comes phase one phase one incoming phase one outgoing
phase one outgoing not yet when phase one outgoing where is it he should have done it by now
why isn't he doing it what the fuck's happening fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you he does it twice
yes god damn it if i just had a little bit more attack power just a little bit more
the fucking flasks are killing me i got this i really do i've got this it's the four fucking
flasks i'm about to go back and just put the two in and just run back down here like i have this
stupid goddamn mage shit class i have four heels oh my god it's so frustrating
i wish there was a fucking bonfire down here just give me my two other flask and this guy is
dead all right three more attempts if i can't beat them then i'm gonna go bonfire get two more
flasks no this one doesn't count this this this piece of shit i'm literally talking and he has the
balls to fucking attack me while i'm talking how come you guys are counting to 10 why because you
know what even upgrading the 2020 hindsight man is he gonna do it dude and i was ready for it too
what i didn't dodge through him i'm fucked i'm fucked here tail swipe sucks
that tail swipe is like holy shit man he likes spins but you think he's gonna go up but he
just doesn't and he'll just swipe you with the tail all right this is the last try before i get
more heels and i'm i what i was gonna say is 2020 hindsight claws were the thing to upgrade
unfortunately even if you try to dodge through it like sometimes this one's okay this one doesn't
count like i i have to try to beat him now because there's no way i'm gonna come back here later and
like remember all this bullshit this idiot does it's just it's just like just way too hard for the
level a and it sucks because i don't want to come all the fucking way back down here
were you here were you in the room were you in the fucking room
oh it feels good to beat that motherfucker coming in dance roof 2020 hindsight these gloves i should
have i should have upgraded them oh oh my god it feels good so what was that is that a new
thing summoned spirit of the banished knight oleg oh dude we've got a new best friend here
we've got a new bro here really what does it do holy shit i have like a dual welding
oh man is he gonna be sick he's a hundred fp i'll be honest i thought i was dead i thought i
he did that did you see that bullshit he did the exploding thing that wasn't a phase change that's
just a thing that he can do that bastard just does that move normally i don't think that's
a phase change he did it like three more times you've got your gamer license renewed you missed
the last tail thing you didn't dodge it i think i was too close to his stomach so the tail just
didn't i just got lucky at the end all right i'm probably gonna have to say that's probably where
i'm gonna call it for today because i need to go eat food and go take like a cold shower because
that was seriously like it was i i'm like a lightning bolt right now oh i you know what i
have to stop doing i have to stop doing like emperor palpatine you guys know what i'm saying
like yeah should i have probably been here no but like every three or four deaths like i can't
i can't do it no i'm too weak i'm too weak no i'm too weak i can't do it no i just i can't
i can i just did get the item is there i'm gonna make sure i don't want to miss anything here
is there actually an item that i missed yeah i already got the item i got the item up the slope
didn't i okay let me upgrade that i'm so glad that i didn't give up damn okay let's do health
no x there were two ways oh wait maybe the maybe it's just off the boss is dead let me just see if
it's like turned off there's there was another way to go hold on let me go check that out it's
definitely worth going up never go back down here ever again just that last moment when i
hold on this was stupid the last moment when i okay i i'm trying to do like a motivational speech
okay and again again no sorcery i want all the doubters to remember that uh you said that i was
a casual sorcerer and i only do sorcery and i'm a loser well what what do you think about that
all the way don't stop don't stop don't stop don't stop don't stop don't stop i'm out of stamina
that's not good i'll stop i went up and i'm gonna chill okay so now doesn't even come up here
am i certain what the fuck dude are you you see how many fucking swings how did i beat that boss
with this like level two weapon how is that possible that i just beat that guy i just got
possessed by a gamer demon there's no way like i just had to hit that guy like six times
what excuse me i'm in the same zone what the fuck it just it just cut my nose off that was horse
shit oh i gotta get these souls back oh that's dirty i don't know how that's been it's been in
my ear but you know what i mean i really want to be able to hear the music feel the music
that's right now it's gonna be a good night okay i'm fucking done don't make me laugh don't make me
laugh because i said okay put on the other weapon because how the fuck did i beat that
i i seriously have no idea how that happened i can't die here though and please give me a break
all the shit talkers uh goodbye i'm too tired i'm fucking gone i'm like gone i'm actually gone
i don't know what are you fucking talking about i don't know i have no idea i'm just like it's
equal parts excitement equal parts like relief and equal parts hungry i don't remember is this
the one where you know it's not here we go you're still shooting the arrows at me don't stop going
don't stop going just go go go go go go go go go don't stop don't stop don't stop don't stop
don't stop for anything and you're gonna bang a right bang a right don't stop the edibles are
kicking in i stop here no i don't this way holy shit it's right behind where's it going do i
follow it i kind of think i should follow it i think i follow it no it's too fast forget your
souls they're up here i actually don't know if i should wait or should i follow it going forward
fucking who cares hey hey hey hey not fair it's not fair to push people out of the way
whoa it's fucking so easy like what people think this is hard this is like
boring i am bored out of my fucking mind right now who's this guy now excuse me when i say where
does the thing end let's do teleports around give me the item fucking moly i killed him
there go get him gotta go get that item i thought it was gonna stop at the ledge i didn't think it's
gonna go all the way up i didn't forget i just figured it hadn't come look it hadn't come up in
a long ass time it didn't come up it took like that was like a minute or two it didn't come up
that actually is such a shitty place to die though because like i freaked out and almost
i just i gotta get what on earth am i doing i think i don't think i can use this
honest to god i don't think i can because those two people i gotta have you are pissing me off and
it's really starting to show you don't stop right why do i hear it why do i hear it behind me
why do i hear it behind me why do i hear it what it's over i lose i thought you didn't stop i
thought you just kept going i timed it wrong well i want the fucking item i want the items to train
bullshit minus 7k whatever i had plus 15 so who cares such a stressful piece of shit area
you stop one more time before because it turns around i forgot i thought it just kept going
the fact that it one hit kills you is your patch it that's not fair can i mario 64 this
wait a minute can i actually like mario 64 slide level this guy every time i seriously
fucking hate that guy do i die if i jump down here i didn't get hurt at all i'll take it i don't
care how come i'm not using you kidding me well there goes 7000 souls it's actually what actually
works i don't know what the hell i did to make it so i he's back why is he back i killed his ass
i want the thing to come up here because i'm gonna get him killed by it three five six seven eight
nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen
follow me follow me shit i didn't count one two three four five six seven eight nine ten
eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen how did you come in
here with me two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen
sixteen so that's what you get for fucking teleporting around you dick i'll take the dragon
command to seal give me the fuck out of here what an asshole all right give me up nothing else here
right why did he do that okay i will i'll see you guys tomorrow that's it uh that was pretty
intense day of gaming i was very upset i was very happy excited i was annoyed i was awestruck it was
everything that was awesome it was fun i really wish i knew what this guy was because i've wasted
like 15 000 souls being an idiot how do i rate the game so far uh 9.4 oh summon oleg let's see
what he looks like yeah uh i'm gonna have to reduce points i would okay when i first opened up
okay after the first like four or five hours of the game i would say it was probably like holy
shit this is a 9.8 i point seven uh i need to see some of the most the story bosses
because the first two story bosses really kind of looked kind of like the same guy
and they had similar really similar moves um all the other side boss stuff has been incredible
but i want to see some more of the main story bosses um because they kind of the first two were
very very similar uh but this game apparently has a shitload of bosses in a ton of places to go and
see i mean i i mean it's i think it's phenomenal i think it's absolutely phenomenal game i think
it's really good uh i also some of the controls are a little weird if i'm honest and the more that
like i get frustrated by controls the more the more that i might you know like the left stick
thing has really kind of been annoying if i'm completely blunt it really i mean i know it's
like well just don't press it as hard but i mean it's still like it kind of happens all the time
uh just by simply moving too far to the left or right of your controller and sometimes just
have it hit if you guys pick up a like an xbox controller or a ps4 ps5 controller hold it hold
in your hands and like move all the way to the right and if you're like trying to move and dodge
it's way easier to push the stick in when you're all the way to the right or all the way to the
left on the stick you know what i mean like i'm talking like this like you hold the button like
this and you click like accidentally you don't really want to like just standing still like
yeah you don't like click it it's the pushing and like running and oops i clicked it happens a lot
but to be fair i don't know where else it could even go i really don't i don't know what that
would how else you map this if it's not on like a keyboard because they put a bunch of other stuff
in the game to have to use right so i don't know like how you make that better it's an xbox one
controller i wonder if maybe the xbox controller might be is it a little bit easier to accidentally
push it in if you put if you're pulling too hard i'm trying to think of how hard you have to push
in to actually with the ps5 controller addles would help yeah yeah that's actually a good point
all right oh like yeah before everybody leaves right i'll see you guys tomorrow though we're
gonna start uh we're gonna start at four tomorrow it's a 4 p.m pacific we're gonna continue elden
ring and then i probably i don't know if i'm gonna do four days in a row
because these streams have been really like beefy but we'll do we'll be tomorrow
i'll be live tomorrow pretty much all day and all night again and let's uh go attack something so
you can see oleg but to answer your question in a very long-winded uh way yes i think the
game is absolutely fucking phenomenal it's really really difficult though and that's a good thing
and it's a bad thing right like it's an amazing thing to like accomplish something but in the
moment sometimes it's just like it's i can't do it like palpatine right and it's still so much
more to see and so much more hard shit to do but the very final opinion you can really have
is like okay the game's too hard but eventually it isn't like eventually it isn't like once you
actually figure out what you're doing and you like study bosses and you stop making the same
mistakes you keep making and i still make them all the time um it's actually awesome how hard it is
but sometimes you kind of look at it and go like man did i really it took me like four hours to
beat that guy um something it's just like holy shit i feel i feel like i'm an incredibly
accomplished person um so it's great as much as you can feel sometimes like it's too much
i can't do it it's too fucking hard eventually it's not all souls games ever yes there you go
this is my take i need more fp i can't even cast this really how much fp do i have dude i need way
i need a i need to level up my mind i can't even cast it okay what's your take on frozen pizzas
well frozen pizzas are way way too hard um until they're not when you put it in the oven and you
spend some time uh seeing it and watching it cook and letting it do its thing for like 15 20
minutes and you understand that you need to cook it first um it comes out and it's very edible and
it's delicious i would say the same exact thing okay goodbye i'll see you guys tomorrow goodbye
i'll see you tomorrow take care of yourselves see you soon good night goodbye take care actually
i'll play you uh the final song from blordow that i have uh i feel like it's gonna be a a big hit
so this is what will play us out tonight see you tomorrow