I want anybody to see my armpits, so I'm not lifting my arms up.
See my armpits, so I'm not lifting my arms up.
Can't breathe without these.
Just a little too big.
Oh, a mailbox! Yay! Whose house is this? This is my house? Let me give it a check.
Are you in there? Hello? Can you hear me? Why don't we give it one more check?
The door, I'm here! That was a voice crack in the first 10 seconds.
All right, it's not bad. It's not bad at all. I mean, I kind of feel like a dickhead.
Just by the way that I'm dressed, but you know, whatever.
Refrigerator. Oh, refrigerator! Stove! Oh yes, I love stoves! Sink! Oh my god, I can't believe it.
How many rooms do I have? Just one, or do I have two? How many do I have?
Oh, is this a nice bathroom? Spacious, comfortable. I could utilize this. Toilet,
shower, and sink. Does this sink work too? What do you think? Should we try it? It does.
A workable sink. I feel pretty good, but that could change really, really quickly. I'll look
into this one here. Take care of me. Don't fuck around. You've got three streams to do this.
I'm just gonna go, I'm gonna go in the kitchen. Whatever. Why not? Is there anything even in the
fridge? I don't even know if there's anything in here. I see something I like in there.
Wash my hands really quickly. Welcome to the dollhouse though. Got a few things you might
need to take care of. Got a few needs. I just saw somebody said starve him. I want that person
timed out for an hour. So what I want to do is I, I want to go, what I want to do is I want to
use the bathroom. It took me a while to be, how am I using my hands?
You know what? I don't even, I don't even need to hold it.
I want to give the toilet a flush, why don't we?
That was a long one, I think. That took a little while. Hey, Jerry. Get this thing out of the way.
Do I have to wear, oh, this shit the whole time, by the way. Do I have to wear this the whole time?
I'm like on fire right now. This helmet, this helmet is making me sweat. I like the shower.
It's beautiful. That's really what it is. And I'm taking this off because I, I, I don't want it on
anymore. I just don't, it's too hot. That's just the way it is. So I'm, I'm looking, what I'm looking
for for you to do is I'm looking for you to take care of me. Take good care of me. Don't, I want
to be, I want to sleep well eight hours a night. I feel like I'm presenting like a, I feel like I'm
presenting a, like an infomercial. Hey, does your toilet, does your toilet do this? Does your
toilet do this? Well it does because that means it's working. What do I want to do? This is what
happens when you, when you're just in this world. What happens is it's got a really bad migraine
that's making, I don't want to go that way though. I want to go back in the bathroom. What am I doing?
I want to take a jog. For what? I don't, I don't jog. Okay, I'm gonna, I didn't even lock the door.
I gotta lock the door. Somebody lock the door. Why am I doing this? I don't want to fucking go here.
There are cars on this road. There are cars on the street. All right, I, when can I stop doing this?
I'm starting to stink. All right, I'm going back in. I'm going back in. I'm going back in. I'm not
wearing that helmet either. Oh wait, anybody in here? Hold on. I'm gonna have to get, I'm gonna
have to get an electrician to look at that. Oh, I smell awful. I gotta like feel awful too.
Let me wash my hands. That was a fucking big run. All right, we can just chill. I don't have to do
anything. I don't have to go anywhere. God, this is awful. Can I go? Why can I not, that one, I can't,
I don't know what, that one doesn't do anything. Why? I, I, why am I going outside? Why am I going
outside? What are you doing? Hey, I don't, wait a fucking second, all right? I'm not going out there
yet. I don't want to go out. This is a beautiful day out here. Wow. Look at those birds. This is
pretty nice. I like this. Look at these flowers. They're beautiful. I smell so bad. Take care of
me for God's sake. What about, how about another one? Going back in. That was beautiful though.
I have sweating through my clothes and I mean that in like, in real life and in fake life.
So it makes sense that I would be like this. You'll have a series of choices. I hope you
choose wisely and when you have these choices to make, I really hope that, I feel like shit.
I hope that when you make these choices that you do them in a way that it can succeed all of us.
I think I need to fucking lie down. Um, what was I saying? I wanted to go for a hot jog or something.
I feel awful. I'm getting like a bad headache and shit. I'm like really tired. I really just kind of
want to like, that's probably, there's, over here, I think that's a good spot I sure went.
Oh, that was fucking hell. I feel like somebody just punched me in the face like three times.
I feel like I just, I had this weird vision, this weird dream with this
like sleep paralysis demon just surrounding me. Oh, ow, my knees. What's that? What is this?
Is this a, what was a stool? I don't like that there. That's not what that should be. I don't
like that. I don't like it. But I'll tell you what I do like. I like sassy sunglasses.
How am I supposed to go to the bathroom in this? I am disgusting. Someone please help me. Can I,
please just put me into a bathing scenario. I am here washing my hands desperately. Let,
please let me bathe. Put me into a scenario where I can clean my body. Trash. Sink.
I need to clean myself. You can't just let me fucking be like this. Give me a break.
Ah, I better, I hope that nobody comes over because this is absolutely revolting.
What if my mother shows up? Huh? What if, what if my mother decides to come in here?
You know what she'd say? She'd be disgusted. She would put her face in the air and she would run
away. What if my mother shows up? What if my mother shows up? All right. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, not with the stool there. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
okay, okay. I guess I have to go to the bathroom now. On the stool. Now I'm peeing on the stool.
We gotta poop the stool. I don't want to pee on the stool. Very good. Very good. Very good. Very
good. I can't even use that. That's supposed to be a place to sit down. That's a place for me to sit
and relax. Can I take a shower? Can I just take one? I want to. I want to. Right now.
I would love to take a shower right at this moment. I want to take a shower. Put me in the shower.
I'm waiting. I'm waiting to go in the shower. I don't want to go to work. I want to go in the
shower. You know, I can't go in front of people like this. Shut up, dog. I like mailboxes. I love
them. Thank God. Am I going where I think you are? Am I going where I think you're going?
Please tell me you're going this way. Are you going this way? Please say yes.
Don't make me like take a shit in the toilet for like a second. I haven't even taken shit yet.
Whatever. You know what I'm saying? Thank God. Am I going there? I am going there. Thank God.
Oh my God. They picked it. Thank goodness. Thank you. Thank you. Oh, this feels so much better.
Hey, look at me. Look at me.
Well, maybe you do, right? Maybe I do sometimes. Sometimes you just got to let the water hit you
right in the face, right in the face. There it is. That feels so much better. Oh my goodness.
I'm not naked anymore. All right, we're good. We're good. We're fine. We're fine.
Oh, I feel so much better. I'm fucking hungry though. If I'm not going to go to work and I'm
not going to make money, then you got to make me food. Stupid. I should have called you stupid.
That was mean. I just want to sit over here, put the hat on. I want food and I want it.
I don't need to go to the fucking bathroom again. Something's going on with this toilet.
Something's going on with this toilet. Okay. All right. The toilet's like pissing at me.
The toilet is effectively peeing at me and I didn't even sit on it. It's just broken.
The toilet's broken. What the fuck? I didn't even have a chance to sit on it. Oh my God.
I don't know how to turn it off. What the fuck? I didn't even sit on it. Okay. I think it's clean.
I think it's good. No, it's not. No, it's not. It's fucking still pissing out.
I've used this toilet twice. I don't know what to do about that. All right, I'm going over here.
It's just like peed all over me. I was going to use the bathroom. All right, all right. I'll
put the clothes on. Okay. Here, let's put them on. Can I just take the stupid thing out? I hate this
thing. What am I going to do about that? I can't go to the bathroom. I need to eat. Make some
decisions. How am I going to call repairman when I don't have a phone? I'm going to have to like
scream out the window. I need a repairman, but I don't have a telephone. If anybody in this
neighborhood is a repairman or a repair woman, I could really use your help right now.
Fuck you, dog. What'd he say? I have a telephone, but if you could show up, that would be fantastic.
I'm starving. I haven't eaten in two days. I haven't eaten in two days. What the, who the
zoo's at? I'm feeling like faint. I haven't eaten in two days. I feel fucking terrible. Who's at the
door? Hello? Got a clogged shitter? Yeah, I guess. Not really. I haven't taken a shit in it since I've
moved here. So that's, I guess, technically, how much is this going to cost? I haven't taken, I
haven't gone to the bathroom. By the way, I'm sorry I look like this. It was chosen for me. The
toilet's in here, by the way. Yeah. I don't know what's going on. It just started leaking and,
yeah. I'm really, I'm really happy, in fact, that you live in the neighborhood. In fact,
you heard me and you were ready to work and you had your work clothes on and you had to
buckle with you. That's really, really helpful. Yeah, it's just going. I don't know what to do.
Yeah, it's just spraying water. Yes, it is. I haven't used it, so I don't know what to do about it.
I have no idea what you want. This is what I'm supposed to do.
Oh, it just cost money. How much money does this cost? There's so much water over here.
What am I doing? What, you, I, oh my, look over there. Don't look. Look over there.
Don't look, don't look over here. Don't look over here. In fact, get out of the room.
No, don't. The toilet's fixed. I don't know. I didn't want to go in the shower.
Okay. I'm fine. I'm back. I'm back. Ready to go. You motherfuckers. I swear to God.
I'm fucking starving too. Where did, where did they go? Where is she? I didn't. I'm fucking
starving right now and I need food and I need it now. Make it happen. Thank God. Finally,
some mac and cheese. Mac and cheese. Thank God. Finally get to eat some damn food. I guess I'm
out of my finger. Just get some. Okay. Shit. Give it a minute. I'm not having a good time right now.
I didn't want to fucking, I wanted to pay the person for the love of God. I just want to
fucking have some food and shit. And like, I would, I'm like, feel fucking terrible.
I don't fucking care. I'm fucking not having a good time. This is good though.
I need something to do. Give me something to do. Get this hat off too. It's, it's
constricting. I don't like it. I don't care. I'm not happy. I can't do that. I'm, I'm so stressed.
I'm not do. I can't. It's on me. What's on me? What is that? Does it break into my fucking
apartment? Break into my house? Okay. Um, I don't hate it. I think it's kind of ugly and it smells.
Uh, okay. It's kind of comfy. I like it, but I, but I don't like it.
I don't want to sit on a dirty bed in a dirty fucking place. Okay. I am nothing is I'm not
having a good time at all at all. And I blame you guys. I blame it's your fault that I don't feel
good because you have so many opportunities to make me feel better. And you put, there's a mattress
and like a stool that I piss on. That's fantastic. I, whatever. I don't even fucking care.
I don't fucking care at all actually. And you guys fucked it up. Does the toilet even work?
I don't even know. I didn't want to fucking do that stupid shit that you guys did.
Well, it works and it works so good. It works twice. I don't have anything to make them
do. Fuck off. I don't care. There, I made the bed for you. Any fucking way for me to live?
Who? What? Um, who the, who are they? Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, get off. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no. Off the bed. I don't want a cookie. Get, get that cookie away from me. I don't want a
cookie. Fucking weirdos. That's hilarious. Hilarious. Get away from me. I don't want it.
Ah, I'm in here. Don't come in. Give me your weapon. Okay. It's a little funny. It's okay.
It's a little bit funny. It's kind of funny. This is actually kind of cool. You're, you're crazy.
Ah, I didn't, that's okay. Oh man. What, uh, what are you doing? What are you doing?
What are you doing? What the fuck are you doing? Uh, um, that's, no, no, no, no, you can't, you can't
just take whatever you want out of there. You can't just take everything you want. You can't
just take whatever you want. Get me something I can just swing at him. I'm going outside. I'm
going outside. I'm not fucking doing this. I mean, you're funny. It was pretty funny, but please
leave me alone. Please leave me alone. What did you do to my front door? I gotta go to work?
What did you, you motherfuckers broke my front door. I can't even fix this.
Why am I still holding the balloon? Why am I holding the balloon still? I don't want this.
That to go to work? I don't have to go to work, right? How much money do I have left?
This is my, no, no, no, no, no, no, excuse me. This is my house. I'm like, why am I hiding
outside of my own house? I'm hiding. I need to eat out of that peanut butter later. Now I'm not
going to. I'm not eating out of that peanut butter. I'm not going to work. I don't want to
go to work. I'm not eating out of that peanut butter. I know I'm supposed to, but I'm not going
to. I'm fucking telling you right now, I'm not eating that peanut butter. All right. I'm going
to work. Fine. Goodbye. Take this and fucking leave, whatever. They're fucking taking over. I
wait for me. I'm going to work.
Thank you. Thanks for the ride. I know it was a little weird. I'm sorry. I know I just had a
lot of shit going on and I'm sorry that I may have smelled up your entire car.
It just, they're gone already, but whatever. Thank you. I'll see you again. Whenever I go to work again.
Mess. Somebody's going to have to clean that up. I just want to let everybody make sure everybody's
wear this. There's peanut butter all over the door handles and it's actually like actually
gross. So I'm going to have to figure out what to do about that. And this is, this is a disaster.
Great. Cookies everywhere. The peanut butter. What did he drink? This is his drink. He drank a whole
beer in like five seconds. I'm fucking tired. I'm disgusting and I need food. Okay. They're still
here. What's going on in there? That's funny. There's just clowns drinking beer in my house.
Yeah. That's, that's hilarious. All right. Don't now get, move, move, move out, out, out.
Why are they still here? I'm too tired for this shit. Get out. Move. What was that?
Somebody got like shot. This is a mess in here. It's a mess. Am I taking a shower? Am I going to
get in there? I'm getting in. What are the, what'd they say? Am I getting in? Oh, I'm going to get
naked. Okay. I'm getting naked. I'm in the shower. There we are. All right. This is feeling much
better. Please don't get the clouds out of here. I think I can like sense them. I can actually sense
the clowns inside and somebody's in here. Don't come in. Somebody's in here. Somebody's in the
bathroom. Don't come in. That's very universal. I know it. So I, okay. Okay. We're good. Ah,
fresh, but very tired. Very, very tired. Why is it fucking wet peanut butter on every handle?
You're not going to drink milk out of the jug. You're not going to drink milk out of the jug.
Like that's just fucking gross. And I don't even know which one of us farted,
but somebody did. Somebody farted. All right. Please. I'm starving. Just leave me alone.
Take all. Okay. This is fantastic. All right. Get out of the house. Out. You're out. You're out.
You're out. Out. Out. Get out of the house. Now. Go. Go. Go. You. Help him, please. I won't even
touch him. Just get him out. Next time, I want to stick big enough to swing. That's, yeah. But I
feel good, by the way. Thanks for the help. I appreciate it. I think somebody just said,
red Andy. It's hot up here. All right. I need to actual like wipe these down. There's fucking
peanut butter everywhere. I'm exhausted and I'm starving. You're going to have to pick one
because I don't know what to do. Let me just wipe the handles. He, he like got his hands on
the peanut butter and it was just disgusting. I'm so tired. Give me something to fucking play
with or something, please. For the love of God. It is filthy in this bathroom. There's water. There's
dirt. No, I'm not. No, I'm not going to do that. I'm not going to make a peanut. I'm not making
peanut butter and jelly. I'm not. He put his hand in that. I'm not going to eat out of that.
He actually put his hands inside the peanut butter and like he ate his with his fingers
and put his hands back in. So I have to eat it. They want me to eat a peanut butter and jelly
sandwich. Let me at least get the peanut butter off the handles. It's a disaster. I got to take
the trash out too. Eventually. I got a lot of shit. Hold on. I look at all this. This is ridiculous.
I'm going to fucking pass out too. I don't want any of this. Drinking my beer.
Can I find it? That's his finger. That's his thumb. That's a, that's a literal thumb print in here.
I literally, a sitcom audience just laughed over here. I just heard it. That was revolting.
Damn clowns. I'm so tired, but you have no idea. I need a utensil to do this with at least.
Oh shit, plastic, plastic, plastic, plastic. I don't want to cook this. Get this out of the way.
Why would you cook a peanut butter sandwich? I'm not cooking. I'm not cooking anything.
Who does like a peanut butter sandwich on the stove? I need this bad, but let's go around the
fingerprint. Oh, I can see it. I'm just going to have a little. I need to, I got to put this
somewhere where I can actually use it here. What a sad peanut butter and jelly sandwich, but there's
no jelly and a clown put his hand in it. This is good. Like that. It's really hot in my house. I
don't even have air conditioning. I know there's milk in the fridge, but the clown drank that too
directly out of the job. He ruined everything. He ruined my entire fridge. That motherfucker did
what? This is good. I'm fucking tired. That's bringing me back to life. Thank you. I have to
pee bad though, or I don't know. I have to do one or the other. It feels much better. I need to pee.
I need to use the bathroom. I didn't even sit down. Why is there already something in here?
I'm not doing that, but I'm not doing that again. I'll pee in it. Okay. I'm not going to do the
other thing. That feels better. So tired. I'm so fucking tired. Um, nothing in here. I keep waking
up to new shit in my house. Apparently not today. Everything here that was supposed to be here,
those weirdos were here, but great. That's where that goes.
Oh, popcorn. I love popcorn maker. What? Oh, this is awesome. Popcorn. It's a popcorn maker.
It creates popcorn out of thin air. Oh, the mail too. Why is there food in here?
Is everybody like left something? Um, okay. This is from the neighbors, I guess. Well, thank you.
Thank you, whoever you are. I really appreciate it. Thanks for coming and fixing the toilet too.
I know you can hear me because everyone has their windows open and everyone's ready for work
at all times apparently. How much money do I have? I need money. What are you guys buying?
You're buying all this shit. What am I going to do with the popcorn maker? I mean, I like it. I love
it. I mean, I love popcorn maker, but, um, I mean, what am I going to do with this? Did you buy me
popcorn kernels too? Cause I mean, this is cool. Let me plug it in. I don't, I, this is a disaster
in here. It's a fucking mess. I can't do anything. I don't even have popcorn kernels. I'll put it up
here. Maybe I'll use it. Maybe I'll use it later. I can't even go anywhere. I don't, I don't like
this living situation at all. I don't like the bed being here. I don't like the, you know what?
This is disgusting. I don't know where this is. I don't know where this is from. I don't know where
this, what this has been, but I don't want it in my house. I'm sorry. I'm just going to be honest.
Time for work. I'm coming. Hold on a second. I got to test my doorbell.
All right. All right. All right. I'm going to be late. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Tough day at work.
See you at the party on Saturday. Did I really want to invite everybody in that car? Probably not.
Are they still out? Why are they still here? Did I leave, did I leave my phone in the car?
What if I did though? What if I never get to make a phone call for the rest of my life?
What if I can't make a phone call for the rest of my entire life? Right? Like I have to go to the
fucking phone store. I got to get a new phone. I have to like call and redo everybody's numbers
and stuff. I just, I don't want to do that. Give me this. You won't fucking.
Okay. Can you guys buy a lock for the door? I'm not answering the door. I'm literally not.
I just, I don't have to answer the door. I'm not answering the door. They can stay out there.
I'm not going to let them into the house because like I saw, I don't want another
finger in my peanut bar. These are good. I'm not letting them in. I'm not sure what happened last
time. Come on. It's really. Oh, God damn it. Hold on. Wait a minute. You can't come in here.
You can't come in here. You can't come in here. I don't know how they got in. Why are they allowed
in the house? Why are they allowed in the house? What happened? What happened? What happened? What
happened? Somebody's touching my face. Somebody's on me. Somebody's on me. I'm not gonna eat a piece
of pizza with whipped cream on it. Okay. Get the fuck out of here. I'm not going to eat that.
I'm not going to eat it. I'm not going to eat this. I don't know what this is. I don't know
what this is. It's like a kid's school project. No, get away from me. I don't even know what they're
doing here. I don't even know why they're even in here. Why don't I have permanent clowns? Take
this back. Okay. I don't know what you have, but I can't see. I can't see. I need help with something.
Please. No, no, no. I'm not taking a shower. I'm hiding. Are they gone? Oh, no. What gave it away?
I gotta find the fuse box. I gotta find the fuse box. Oh, my face. The fuse box is back here.
Close the door. Close the door. It's over here somewhere. I think I found it. God damn it.
Where is it? It's back here in this little cubby hole. Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow. My fingers.
Ow, shit. That hurt. Oh, my hand. All right. How do I get back into the house?
My hands. All right. Out, out, out. Power's back on. Get out. Out, out of the house. Out of the house.
Out of the house. Out of the house now. Out of the house right now.
Now. Now, don't come back. And you're not invited to the party. Oh, God. Don't come back.
I burnt the shit out of my hand going back there. I'm so tired. I'm exhausted. I can't. I'm not
going to. You want to play outside? Great. It is soaking wet out here. Disgusting. I'm playing
outside, apparently. Why do I think that's playing? Christmas time. I love Christmas.
This is, you got to choose sleep sometimes, guys, because this is how you fuck me up for the rest of
the week. Oh, pee. Oh, this is ridiculous. I've only lived here for like fucking four days.
It's like a throw a party. Oh, hey. Ha ha. Make sure the doorbell works. I'm not even going to do it.
So what happened? The popcorn machine. What's new? Oh, phone. Telephone. Finally. I can make
telephone calls. I don't have to scream out my window. I messed up something over here.
I ripped up some tiles. How does it work? Hello? I don't know. How's the phone? Hello. Yes, this is
control speaking. Hello. Yes, this is control speaking. How is the spaceship doing?
I don't know. I don't know how to use that. Wait, call. Oh, I'm going to piss. See how mom's doing.
Hey, mom. Hey. It's just, it's, it's Jerma. Well, you know me as Jeremy, mom. Well, you know me
as Jeremy. Of course, mom. Yeah, I'm doing okay. I'm doing fine. Yeah. I just, um, I just moved in.
Been here for four or five days or so. It's been great. It's really good to hear your voice too.
I'm sorry. I kind of like disappeared. Yeah. I have had no way to communicate with me at all.
Now it's very, yeah, that's funny. Wait, what did dad do? Are you kidding me? No, it's good. I just
wish there was more electricity. I have one outlet. Yeah. I've never heard of a house before that had
one outlet, but you know, this plumbing, it works. It's comfy. It's cozy. Mom, I, uh, it's been really
good to hear your voice, but I definitely have to go. Uh, I've got to go. I've got to get off the
phone and yes, yes, I've got to go. I've got to go. I've got to get off the phone. I've got to get
off the phone. If we're going, I'm, I'm going to go pee with you on the phone and I'm going to
hang up after goodbye. Mom, it's not just gonna see you. I'm not gonna, I'm not going to piss or
like shit on the phone with my mother. I'm sorry. Like you picked it too late. There you are. Not
going to happen. Ah, it feels pretty good. That was a good call though. Good. It's good to talk
to my mom. Ah, it feels good now. Life is good. I feel good. I feel like I look good.
Too much stuff though. I just, I wish I could just get rid of this stuff.
Do you see what happened over here? This is, this is a slice of pizza here with like whipped cream
on it. I don't want that. I want to get rid of it. I don't want that. I'm in my house anymore.
Time to go to work. Let's go. Be there in a sec. Time to make some money.
Bye. Bye. Thank you for the ride again.
Tired, hungry, all the above, all of the above. Ridiculous. That was a rough day at work too,
but I made some money, you know, and that's the good thing. That feels better. Oh my goodness.
I feel like a thousand dollars more than I did earlier. Oh, thank God. I'll have some of this.
If I can even get it in, it doesn't do anything. You know what? I'm going to have some cereal.
Cereal sounds good to me. Am I peeing? What? Am I peeing? What happened? Why was I just peeing?
Oh, it was a sizzle. I was like, why am I pissing? All right. I think, wait, shower. I'm not done.
I can't take a shower with the food. All right. Maybe I can. Oh, it's getting all in there. It's
getting all soggy. It's all getting soggy. That was like Peter Griffin. I just realized that.
It's getting soggy. Oh, but killing two birds with one stone though. This is good.
Starting to feel better. Life's coming back. Life is coming back into me.
Oh, I'm just tired. Unhappy. What? What's in the mail? What? I got a piece of mail. What's it say?
$500. An inheritance. $750. I misread it in my glasses. $750 from Dear Uncle Ted. No way. What an
inheritance. What did he leave me? His weight set? Was that rain? That's a huge deal. All right.
That's money. That's big money. I was sad before, but that's another $750. How much money do I have
in my bank now? How much money have I got? Do I have more than $500? Like $1,200? Holy shit.
This floor is filthy. Hello? Mom? Yeah. I know. I heard about Uncle Ted. Yeah. Yeah, I know. He
sent me some. Did he send you anything? No. Yeah. I got $750 in an envelope. It was a check, but
still. How are you doing? Yeah. Yeah. No, I mean, it's really nice of him. What did he give you?
You got $10,000. That's awesome. Hell yeah. That's awesome. Well, that's sad, but I got money.
When did he send it? Why would he send it? Oh, his inheritance. That's right. That's right. That's
right. So it was split up across the whole family. Oh, there's a house too. Wow. That's very
interesting. Yeah. Yeah. I know. That's sad. Well, I mean, he left some stuff for everybody.
It's really cool. It's really nice of him. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'll talk to you soon. Yeah. All
right, ma. All right, ma. Yeah. Yeah. We'll figure it out. Yeah. Love you too. That's right. That's
what you say. You love you to your mother. You haven't talked to your mother lately?
Say call her and say, I love you. Do it. You do it. Do it tonight. Don't wait. Mother's important.
She's very important. Right in the bed. Finally. The first night I've actually been able to sleep
in the bed. It's been a very long, that was the mattress that I, that was the mattress. That wasn't
me. That was the mattress. It's like the fart stream. It's the fart stream. I got to get comfy.
Hold on. That was pretty, that was not bad for the first time ever being able to sleep on this bed.
Uh, I feel a little groggy, but it's okay. I didn't have one of those weird sleep paralysis
dreams. Not last night. Filthy. I hate it in here. I can't even be in here. I literally cannot even
be in this room. What? I don't know. What happened? Can I at least get rid of some of this stuff?
It's ridiculous. It's, that's just, no. I'm cleaning up a little just to be able to walk around again.
What? It looks very broken from what I can tell. Am I gonna, can I even go to work? I don't think
I can even go to work if you wanted me to. I'm going, I'm going out the window. I'm going out
the window. I can't, you didn't close the window. I'm going out the window. Yeah, I'm going out.
Seeing fucking Ace Ventura when he's coming out the rhino's ass. Oh, oh, oh, oh. Hey, yay, bed.
Bed. I love, I love what you've done with the bed. Why does everything have to go in the yard?
You have to put everything in the yard? Any mail today? No. Well, at least I can, I'm not climbing
back in, so send me to fucking work, okay? I'm not gonna, I'm not climbing, I'm not gonna climb back
in the window. I'm going to work. I'm not climbing back in. I could sit on it though. I could hang out
on it. The side just sunk. Oh, that's what this is for. That's what fell out. That was the very
loud noise that I heard. I heard an incredibly loud sound. This bed is fucked. I wouldn't, I'd rather
lie on the dirty one. I'll be honest. What, I got mail? What's the mail? I got a hundred dollars
from Dolls R Us for the thing I left at the shop. I had a consignment. Well,
cool. All right, more free money. I'll take free money. Should I go to work too? Send me to work.
I can't, I, I'm not, I literally, nothing else I'm gonna do out here. I'm not, I'm gonna have to use
the bathroom too. Feeding, feeding you money so you can make the right decision. I don't think I
could even put this together if I wanted to. That's the last part of the day. If I hear the
fire, I'm coming over there. I swear to God. Oh, it's just the bottom. All right. Now I can,
no, this is a fucking, this is a train wreck under, but wait, this is an air mattress.
This is not even a bed. Look at what happened under here. What happened under, look at this.
Do you see what I have to deal with right now? This is, I can't put this together.
I'm going to sleep on it like that. It's just absolutely destroyed. I don't know if you guys
can hear it, but it was seriously, it was like, it was like an explosion back here. Like it just
fell apart in their hands. Work. Oh, is it time for work? I see the car pulling up. Hey, pick up this
guy. You know what I'm saying? Car. Are they on the road? I don't even hear them. Oh, there you are.
Don't worry about what you see over here, by the way. Just don't,
don't drive far enough to see by my driveway.
Let's go. Yeah, it was a dick move. No, that was a dick move. What you did. Not everybody,
not everybody thinks that's funny. So I just want to let you know,
but we'll see you at the party on Saturday. He's still going to go.
I can't, I got to pee bad. You know, it's funny, even if I wanted to move this,
I wouldn't be able to. I'm not going through the window. That hurt. Even if I wanted to move this,
it would be hard for one person. I don't know what to do. I need to get in there.
What do I do? Help. Hey, excuse me. Excuse me. Help me. Excuse me. Help. Right. There's a water
fountain over there that I hear. I heard a water fountain. Hey, I wonder if it flushes.
That's so stupid. Oh, I'm not having a good time though. Give me something to play with. It's so
much fun. I wouldn't go back in there, but I just don't want to go in the window. Will this fit over
me? No, I don't think so. I could go like this. No, this is kind of fun what I'm doing, but not
really. This actually could be a hat, but somebody just said it could be a toilet seat. It's not
going to be that. I'm not going to use this as a toilet seat. Oh, this is kind of a funny hat.
This is a funny hat. I like it. This is a funny hat. I can't even block the door. I could very
easily just get in there. I could, but make food. I can't. Can I eat these flowers edible?
I don't think I can even. Can I eat one of these? What happens to my hunger level if I eat one of
these? Hold on. Let me see. Ow. It's like stung me. All right. What if I take like a bite? I'll take
a big bite. It's not good. I can't go. All right. I'm climbing the window again. No, I don't want to
climb in the window because then I won't get the comfortable bed. No, I don't want to get hurt.
This is day one. Oh, shit. But these have been out here for like five days.
Haven't these been out here for like at least five days, right? Can I actually eat these or is that
going to be bad for like, what if I just pretend to? I don't know how long these actually have been
here for. Now I've had another bite. Ooh, that was really good. I want to just like jump in.
What? What are you doing? You want me to run? Run? Run away. Like now. You want me to run away?
That, that's like run down the street. I can't get back inside. That's very obvious.
This is a nice house. How am I going to get back in here? Run away? I've been walking around the
neighborhood for the last like six hours. You know, people have come out and just looked at
me and been like, what the hell is this guy doing out here? Seems you have chosen to upgrade the
house. And what does that mean? That means that that is the end of the tutorial. So thank you for
playing in our tutorial version of this game. Hopefully it worked out pretty well. I think it
did. And in two days, that is where the real game starts. So I, this was a ton of fun. Let me look
at the right camera right here. There we are. I had a ton of fun. Thanks for watching everybody.
Special huge, huge, huge scam. Well, I want to say thanks everybody for watching. We have two more
streams of this and it's going to get even more wild. We're literally going to dial it even higher
and higher every day. So I keep talking to the wrong cameras. I don't know what's wrong with me.
We're going to dial it up every day. Every single day it's going to get more ridiculous.
So we want to make sure that everything worked as intended before we got started.
So I cannot actually get into this house. So I'm not going to even try. Trial version of
full game unlocked. Special huge thank you to Twitch for partnering with us and to Coinbase.
Without them, this would never have happened. And there's way more to see over the next two
or three days. So what that means you'll see in the next few days, but we got everything.
What was that? You paid to end the stream. You paid to end the tutorial is what you did.
But yeah, I'm really, really happy. I really think that everything worked out pretty well in
this kind of tutorial version of the game. So I'm very, very excited. I hope you had fun.
We got a lot of data. So we got a lot of things that we might have to work on and check out and
see how they played out. But for the most part, I think it was pretty fun. So we'll see. So we'll
see with the upgraded house in a couple of days with even more wacky, wild stuff. Thank you,
everybody. We'll see in a couple of days. Thanks for playing the tutorial. I can't go back in there.
Huge shout out to Twitch. Huge shout out to Coinbase for letting us do this shit.
Huge thanks. Without them, it's impossible. We'll see in a couple of days.