Stream's bopping. Stream will be bopping. Stream is currently bopping. Hey, welcome back. Hope you
had a good Monday. I had a good Monday. I had a great Monday. Tuesday is now. Hopefully we have a
good Tuesday too. Every day of the week is hopefully a good day. Today we're gonna do something I've
been looking forward to for a while since it was announced. We're gonna play Ancestors the
Humankind Odyssey. It's a game where you play as an ape and you have to evolve in this permadeath.
I don't know much else. I have, I'll be honest, I have read the reviews. They're very bad.
But who cares about reviews? You think I give a shit about a review? They're not great. Let's
just put it that way. You think I care? I'll review the game when I'm done. And you can trust my review
because it's from, it's from the heart and it's from the brain connected. Equal parts brain and
equal parts heart. You get the true review. But you're not gonna get that. You're gonna get me
playing the game for as long as it takes. There's also something I want to talk about real quick.
I want to talk about the activity book stream. Some of you know what this is. Some of you don't
know what this is. I have not really gone into detail on it and I'm gonna do it right now
because I've been pushing it off and pushing it off and I don't want to do that anymore.
So what is the activity? The activity book stream is going to be a stream
where some community content is made and is put into a highlights style activity book.
We're talking dot to dots. All community themed by the way. Dot to dots. Where's Waldo? Me? Well,
it's gonna be where's Jerma? You know, you gotta get that point across. And other random brain
teasers and activities and coloring books and shit. This is all supposed to be next week.
The deadline for submissions for this is currently the 31st. But I'm gonna move that forward because
I don't think that's enough time because I haven't really talked about it. It's been in the discord
for a little while. It's only in the discord. Please, if you want to submit something, which
it is a full submission for anybody in the community that wants to do this. There are a
few things that I'm going to commission out on my own. But stuff like dot to dot and if you don't
know what a dot to dot image is, it's when there's the template of dots and they're numbered and you
have to connect, you know, 123 to 100 200 whatever it is, then it makes an image. But I want to do
this thing. It seemed like a fun idea. Read the rules in the discord if you want to participate.
The new deadline for submissions for those activities is going to be, are you listening?
Are you listening? September 3rd is the last day that you can submit something. Not everything
will be chosen. We're going to choose some of the ones we think are obviously a little bit better
or more interesting or fun. There'll be some shitposts. Don't worry. I probably should have
just given the blanket statement there that you can do shitposts because I shouldn't, I don't
think I should have said that. And then the actual stream will be the 7th of September. This is not
some huge deal, right? This is not, oh my god, this is a fucking huge stream. It's just a fun
thing I want to do. Probably take a few hours. To give more detail on some of the things,
we can do it a little bit later. I think more people are here. But I want, where's Waldo?
So you can make an image of, if you don't know what a where's Waldo, you kind of need to like
know what all these things are before making them, I guess. But there's going to be like 10 to 12
where's Waldo's, but it's me, 10 to 12, maybe 15 dot to dots, 10 to 12 brain teasers written by
somebody in the community, 10 to 12 jokes, 10 to 12 coloring pages. There's a whole thing in the
discord. Read those rules, take a look for yourself. And if you want to participate, go for it. If you
don't, then enjoy it when it happens. Now let's turn into a monkey. That sounds good to me.
Game sucks next already. No. Ancestors. This game is going to be wild. It's going to be intense.
You're probably going to see a couple of like, I'm probably going to be like, fuck. At one point,
I just want to warn everybody for the bad language coming up here. Because there is permadeath.
I want, do you think I can get through this whole thing without dying? Absolutely not.
Here we go. You're going to see a couple of fails. Lineage name. This is the name of all
through history. So we've got to think back like 60 million years ago, like a hundred million years
ago. Were there any Elbertsons back then? No, guys, they were no Elbertsons. Elbertson is a
European name. It means guy who makes shoes. I was like, my family is like the shoe blacksmith.
So I, there's no way. Write it. Why can I not write this? Lineage name. Can I not type a name?
Why can I not name this? Lineage name. Why can't I type in here? No, there's something going on.
Something weird. There we go. Right? Yes. I can't. I'm just going to be the Elbertsons.
This is where it started. My family's been making shoes for millions of years.
Choose your game experience first time. What do you mean? How could you do a second time? Explore,
expand, and evolve by experimenting what our oldest ancestors had to face.
Player help. Choose the level of assistance. Full HUD, full tutorial.
Full HUD, no tutorial. Minimal HUD, full tutorial. No HUD, no tutorial.
How am I supposed to play the game? I'm not doing that. Full HUD, full tutorial. How about,
how about minimal HUD, full, I'm, no, I have to do this like minimal HUD, full tutorial. Okay,
that sounds okay. You guys are going to have to help me here. No balls. That's fine.
Minimal HUD, full tutorial. We're just going to go random. Got it. Here we go. Lineage Elbertsons,
game mode, first time, settlement, hidden waterfall oasis, female, clan size, medium.
I didn't get to pick my clan. Here we go. Mama Elbertson is going to take us home here.
Here it is. The first ever human to ever be recorded. Inspired by true events. All right.
You can't, you can't say that. I don't think that's... The world and characters you will
encounter are meant to represent archetypes of a place and of a moment, not the exact depiction.
This adventure was made by Panache Digital Games, which is composed of all these people
based on a true story. Yeah, but we don't know. They didn't write this stuff down.
You can't say based on a true story, based on a bone. With the help of... They did.
In the following hours, you will relive the challenges of the dawn of humanity.
Based on a true bone, embark into the never-ending odyssey of human progression on this planet.
Use your body, senses, mind, and voice to guide your voyages. Gain strength in numbers and advance
the species. Survive the elements. Teach your family. Build a home. Make sure to watch your
food and thirst meters. We won't help you very much. And remember, evolution is not set in stone.
It is your path to forge. This is very loud. Yes. Where am I? Do I land on like a comet?
This is how it started. We crash landed on fucking comets. Let's be... Got it. First try. Ah,
fuck, I dropped it. It's all right. There's probably more of those. That's probably the currency.
Watch out! Look at all these animals. They have every animal. Wait, was this... weren't they dinosaurs?
This is supposed to be like 500 million years ago. All right, well then that guy's got like...
Uh-oh, watch out. Here comes the... It's the Jaguar thing. Jaguars attacked alligators? They did?
No, they didn't. Based on one true bone. They dug up a bone and now they can tell me that
that panther attacked that alligator. I don't think so. Where do we start? Ancestors with
human kind arms. Eventually, you'll be working in a fucking office. Volume one, before us.
Okay. Is this us? This is us. All right. We got the fish. We got to eat it. Watch out for the bird!
Holy shit. Okay. Regain safety in a hiding spot or in your clan's... What the fuck is
going on? Why are they like specters? Tap Y to use your intelligence. Use to identify a hiding spot,
your clan settlement, or other practical items. What? I'm a baby. Okay, so this is intelligence.
Don't move to stay in intelligence. Look around. Right stick to highlight point of interest,
then follow the steps displayed on the contextual UI. So, okay, over there.
Right? Go towards the square. All right, let's go towards the square. Why are these all these
like nightmare images? What do you mean? I can't like drown. Now what do you want me to do? Yeah,
I know a hiding spot. Latibolum. Oh, all right. How do I sprint? How do you punch? Dude, why do
they keep doing this? I don't want to see anymore of these weird like 3D animations. There it is.
All right, I found it. Sense of hearing. Don't move to stay in the senses. This is the representation
of the sounds within range. Look around to target a sound. What? Minimal fucking tutorial,
minimal HUD. I found the hiding spot. It's right here. It said look around for the sound and then
what did it want me to do? What is that? Another... another person? What is that? Food? Current clan
settlement. Okay, well, let's... let me go into the hiding spot. Am I hiding? Is this a hiding spot?
Grabbing foliage and creepers. Jump and hold A to grab the foliage or the creepers when press
passing through it. Trunks, branches, and rock walls are... what the hell is that next to me?
That's me. Okay, well, I fucking didn't even see what it was. Is it up here? Should I get up here?
No, look, this is right there. Hiding spot. How do I get in this hiding spot? How do I get in this?
Okay, that was... I clearly was... I did it. Find the lost child of your clan. What do you mean?
Sprint L... L to move. Hold A to sprint. Release A to jump. All right. What do you mean find the
lost baby? To cancel jump. Stop moving before releasing A. Okay, well, I... I just grabbed
something. I just grabbed like a stick. All right, I got a stick in my hands. I'm ready to fight.
Growing Neuron. Who are these people? Are these friends? All right, it said we won't tell you
anything, so I just have flowers in my hands. What am I supposed to be doing? Look at all these
things. Okay, what about over here? Don't know what this is. My intelligence is gaining
because I looked over here at like the briar patch. I know what that is now, apparently. Hold on.
Is that the baby crying? Tap X to use your senses to help you locate any member of your clan.
Okay. Down there. All right, I gotta be careful. Can I... I'm coming to save you.
That was scary. I'm not gonna lie. All right, how do I get down from here?
What? I couldn't even read that. What did it say? Spring... Got you. Okay. Tap B, then wait for the
answers to progressively comfort the kid. Lower the temperature. Take the time to listen. What the
fuck are you talking about? Why are we doing this? It's me! Oh, thank goodness. So that's...
Is this me? Which one is me? Join your clan in the settlement. All right. So here's the thing. How
do you swing and how do you climb? The tutorial was on the screen for five seconds. Can I look
at tutorials? Adult, female, single, fertile. Okay, hold on. Options, controls, intelligence,
emotions, concentrations, emotions. It didn't tell me anything. All right. I don't know how
to grab a vine. All right. Let's listen. Let's see. Where was the settlement again? Let me zoom in.
Let me just take a look at some stuff over here. What is this? You don't know. Right. Okay. I don't
know what's over there. Where was my settlement? It's up here, right? There it is. All right. So
get up there. Up that way. Up this tree. Here we go. Is this like... Can I jump higher and grab?
No. I have to just hold. Motricity? Motricity? How can I go? I wish I knew how to actually hold
on to stuff. Do you even need to? Maybe you don't even need to. All right. I made it. Back in the
settlement. I could do this pretty well. Which one's me and which one's the game? That was the game.
What's going on here? What's going on? Why are we... Can your lineage evolve faster than our
ancestors did? I don't know. Can they? Avatar's vitality. Energy is limited by stamina, is limited
by life expectancy. Eat well, drink well, and sleep well to maintain a great stamina. Avoid injuries
and stay on the screen for more than 10 seconds. Stop moving to see all the contextual actions
offered. They vary according to your situation. Contextual actions. All right. Well, now what do
I do? Can I drink out of the stream? How do you drink? Okay. No, that's like... That's the taunt
button. Wait. Hold on. What? There's so many things to look at. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What? Okay. When already discovered, dropped items can be stockpiled with identical items.
What are you talking about? I hit right bumper. Fucking minimal HUD. All right. So we can... You
grab with A. Hold X to inspect any item you have in the right hand. That's good to know. What is it?
How do I know what this is? I don't know what it is. This is just a green thing to me.
New food. Horsetail. How do I eat it? Just like corn on the cob.
Adaptable metabolism. Assimilated nutrients from the vegeta- vegetal kind of food.
How much do I have to eat? How much green corn do we have to eat? Oh, I'm teaching them. I get it.
See? Everyone, this is how you eat food. You pick it up and you eat it.
Okay. I learned communication. I'm going to learn how to talk. What else is there? Oh, can I eat this
too? Is this food? Examine. What could this be used for? What do you think? New tool. Grass sci-cad. New
tool. What can I use this with though? How do I use this? There's something over there. Take a shit
in the river. I'm glad- I'm glad that's what you want me to do. Oh, what's happening?
What is that? Why does he have lasers coming out of his mouth? Hold on. Wait. Come here.
What's this? Something over here. New species of fruit. What is it? Pick it up. What am I doing?
What's in here? Why can this be examined? Oh, am I drinking? How do I drink? How do you drink water?
Examine the water. I have to examine it. Oh, yes. I can drink this.
Aqua dulcis orego. Isn't it just- that's not it. It's H2O. It's hydrogen and oxygen. Twice.
All right. Let's go. How do I feed the kid? What's this stuff? Oh, berries. Are they poisonous?
Will I know? Poisonous berries? New food. This is going to poison me. No, I did. Okay. I guess we
can't eat these. We can eat these. Guys, we can eat these. Come over here. We can eat these berries.
Although, they might be poisonous. Should I not have taught them how to do this?
Wait. Wait. Don't eat them. Don't eat them. Stop eating those. I can't be for certain. I have to
wait until I have diarrhea. Okay. Something's wrong with me. I think I'm cold. I'm sorry.
I think we have to test it somehow. Okay. Don't eat those. Well, whoever that is,
we might not last very long. What's this? I'm gonna make a shelter. All right. Can I hold it
over his head? I just gave that to him? No. Having children nearby allows the accumulation of
neuronal energy. More children means increased accumulation. Turn the HUD on. I don't think I can.
Oh, fuck. All right. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Vitality,
injuring, and poisoning. Poisoning comes from venom or by eating rotten or green food,
or by ingesting of toxic elements. When poisoned, find something with medicinal properties. Okay.
So I've been poisoned. Your organism can't assimilate nutrients from all kinds of food
right away. Some may cause a temporary poisoning. You can become omnivorous through neuronal
development. Okay. Attack. Hold A to prime dodging. Move to dodge.
Release A at the right time. Hold A to prime the counter attack. What the fuck do you mean? All
right. Let's just let's go look around. Everybody get over here. Don't be out there. A sleeping
spot. When built, a sleep spot is at the basis of every settlement. Tap A to lie down on a sleep
spot. Let me examine that as a sleep spot. There it is. All right. So I got it on the UI now.
I got it examined. Let's see what it does. And let's sleep. Can I go to bed? How long does it
take to go to sleep? Go to bed. Baby. Baby with spontaneous genetic mutation metabolism.
How do I turn the fucking HUD on? Yeah, I'm sorry. That ain't gonna happen. This is staying on.
I'm not gonna play. Let me learn the game first. Jesus. All right. Let's see. So I got
changed. So it's like Path of Exile. Okay, so here I am. Neuronal growth is complete.
Assign neuronal energy to initiate a new communication skill. Assign neuronal
energy to initiate a new motor skill. All right. I think I want some motor skills. The ability to
switch hands with an item is acquired. Tap LB to switch hands with an item. Nice. That has opened
up so many more things. All right. I can switch hands. Wow. What a development. What about down
here? Let's do some more communication. Okay. The ability to gather all clan members is acquired.
Hold B to gather all clan members and have them follow you. Okay. This looks huge. To launch an
evolution, you must be in your clan's active settlement. You've passed at least one generation
and succeeded in evolutionary feat. Okay. So I haven't done that yet. All right. So let's go to
That's it. We slept. We now can hold something in our other hand. Analyze. Baby. Love. This
spontaneous genetic. All right. Rename. New name. Yeah. Change name. Change name. No. I want to
baby you. All right. Let's go. Let's try it. Everybody get over here. Who are you? All right.
I'm going to rename you as well. Tweet. Sounds good. Thank you. Thank you. New
Kaiser for the 10 community subs. Thank you. Appreciate it. How do I pick you up? Isn't this
my baby? Sleep. Sleep. Why is the time going so fast? What is that? Am I having a dream?
Oh yeah. Yesterday I looked at my hand. I have something outside of my arm that looks weird.
It's got five things on it. Dawn. All right. Let's get up at eight o'clock in the morning.
Here we go. Food. Water. Daily regimen update. I need some water. All right. Let's go. Everybody
come over here. Let's all drink water please. Everybody come over into the pond. Let's drink
some water. All of you. Come on. Together. Over here. All of you. See? How much is too much water?
We don't want to get over hydrated. All right. That's good. What about food? How am I doing on
food? Handling. Tap to switch hand. It will free the right hand to pick up something else.
All right. Here we go. Alter. What do you mean alter? Oh right. Some items may be altered with
bare hands or crafted. What? What am I doing? Oh picking the leaves off. All right. Dexterity.
Okay. Let's try it again. Should I do that again? How many times should I do this? Is there
anymore leaves to pull? This has to do something eventually, right? What? I don't know what this
is even for. What's this for? I don't understand. I don't know. I need. We need food. Food. Food.
Follow me. Everybody follow me. We gotta get food. Where's the food? Over here. What's that? Cold?
Okay. Wait. Hold on. Food. Is this food? Can I eat this? No. I can't eat this. Back to the
poison berries. Food. Found it. It's all mine. It's all mine. I'm the clan leader. Okay. Let's
analyze. Let's go. I want to go. Let's go somewhere. How about what's that? Identify. Memorize. The
location of anything you have identified can be memorized. There we go. Intelligence can also be
used to discover practical items and to visualize the things you have identified. Nice. All right.
That's so much better. So what's in here? I memorized this. I don't understand. All right.
I'm going. I gotta. I'm gonna go find. Wait. Food. Over here. Grain on the cob. Over here.
So what's wrong with me? What's my. I'm still like having problems. Where are the kids?
You. Come here. Okay. A rock. A stick. New tool. Dead branch. All right. Let's analyze it.
What am I doing? I'm just cutting my hand. Build a computer. I don't think I can. Well,
I want to pick up the rock. Rock. No. Rock. I saw the rock right on the ground. Right here.
Got it. All right. Rock. You can smash stuff with this. Okay. Granite rock. Can I do anything else
with this? Eat the rock. I think. I think the rock is funny. We learned comedy. All right. Can I like.
Uh. It makes a scratching noise. That's all this does. I'm trying to break a rock and
my hands. All right. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Stick. Okay. Wait. I have two rocks. I've got
two rocks. If I hit rocks together. That makes a fire. Eventually. Fuck. Wait. Give me. Wait.
Give me the branch. Okay. Rock. No. Get rid of the rock. I don't want two rocks. Branch. Okay. I've
got rock and branch. No. Pick the fucking rock up. You idiot. Okay. Here we go. Rock and branch.
Rock to branch doesn't do anything. I don't think. Shit. Branch and. There. Take this rock.
Hold and wait for the audio cue. Oh, we like each other. Okay. Copy paste. Tell them. Somebody
tell them. Wait. All right. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
Oh. All right. Okay. So you said hold. So let's get it in the right hand. Alter. Wait for the
audio cue. Here we go. Ready? No. Stop. Stop. Give me this. Give me the other rock. Okay. I'm. Here
we go. Do I have things in my hands? Okay. Switch hands. Alter. Let's go. Listen for the cue.
Okay. It's like a camera sound. Okay. Am I making like a spear or a knife or a weapon?
Okay. I've got it. I've got something. Now what do I do with this? Switch hands. Can I just
hit somebody with this? Is it not? It's a sword now. Okay. Inspect it. Okay. It's a sword. Here.
You can have this. Let's trade. I'll trade you a stick for a rock. Thank you. I've got two rocks.
Discovered new alteration. Hitting. A granite rock can alter a granite rock. Wow. That's real
scientific. No. Look at the other ones. Switch hands. Stare at that. Take that in. Yeah. It's
new. It's a new experience. New tool. Granite grinder. Okay. I've got a grinder. So let me drop
the... No. Where's the grinder? Okay. I've got the grinder in my hand. Now let's grind.
Something over here. Should I grind this? All right. I'm gonna grind this. It's not burning.
Oh, wait. Okay. What if I put it over here? Construction. Some items can lead to construction
possibilities when in a stockpile. All right. Hold on. No. No. No. Let's get some more leaves.
Everybody. Grab a leaf. Grab one of these. Okay. Let's put it down. All right. We're starting to
build a house. Should I grind this? No. That's not gonna work. Give me that rock. I need that rock
back. Here. I'm gonna put this over here. This is our... Give me another rock. This is a bigger rock.
Okay. Give me a stick again. What's going on here? What's going on? Why are they holding their
throats? Okay. This is scent. Okay. Let's go. This is a new rock. Okay. This is obsidian. Wait.
Obsidian and... This is flammable, isn't it? This is my grinder. I've got obsidian. Here we go.
Is this gonna explode in my hands? Shit. Wait. Can I take... Where's my obsidian? Okay. Give me
the obsidian. Remember, that's my grinding stone. All right. Give me the stick. I'm gonna put the...
I'm gonna put the obsidian on the stick. I think. Obsidian is volcanic glass. Yeah. I'm gonna
attach it to the front and I'm gonna throw it through the jungle at somebody. Why did I
just do that? Oh shit. It's getting late. All I've done is hit stuff with rocks. Hitting. An obsidian
can alter a dead branch. Shit. We gotta go to bed. Wait. Let me look at this. Was it... I don't
understand 2100. Stick. Okay. Just leave that there for tomorrow. You just hang out. All right.
Let's go to bed. All right. Good night. I learned some new stuff. Assign to initiate how dexterity
will improve. Ooh. EU has an increased capacity to metabolize food. Let's get it. Item manipulation.
The ability to switch an item from one hand to the other while moving is acquired. So I can...
That's... Who cares? I can switch hands while moving. That's... Who gives a shit? Well,
we can keep going. Now what? Once connected, it would be possible to drop an item while moving.
All right. Well, connect it. What are you doing? Why? You can't go that far? Why can't... I don't
have enough brain power. Okay. Well, I can do things while moving now. I think that's all I
can do. All right. Let's sleep. Everybody go to bed. Good night. We have to... We gotta move to a new
settlement, right? There's only day three. Oh. We're learning how to stand... How to rest.
How to... We're doing charades. Okay. Sleeping. Tired. I need... Especially... I need... Wait,
wait, wait. Okay. Here, here, here. Stuff, stuff, stuff. Water. Really? There's water right here.
Why is everybody so fucking thirsty? Everybody over here. He's holding a stick. Have you figured
out what to do with the stick yet? I don't know what to do. You need to drink the water. This is
not drinking water, is it? He's gonna become the alpha. No, he's not. I'll do some diabolical
villain shit where if it looks like he's starting to pass me, I'll just fucking put... I'll just,
I'll just like cut his vineys on when he's swinging around. Yeah, so that's fucking diabolical.
Let me go. I'm gonna go explore. Are we well fed? I think we are. He's figuring... Uh-oh. I think I...
No, no, no. I think here's what happened. I handed him that stick yesterday and he still doesn't know
what to do with it. Let me show him. Look. Ready? Look at me. Look, look, look, look at me. Look at
my eyes. Look at me. Get a rock. You got a stick too? They're all, they're all holding sticks. All
right. We need rocks. What's this? Just hold on. I know, I know what I'm doing. I'm the fucking alpha.
We need a rock. Where's the rock? Did you guys hoard the rocks? All right. I'm going for it.
Let's go. What do we got? We have some points of interest. Nothing too... No, no, no. You know what?
I'm gonna do this first. It's focusing on this. What is that? Okay. That's just grass. I don't
even know that. What about over here? It's just grass. Don't need to memorize it. That's the same
shit we had already. Anything else? There's water? What about down here? What's that? I don't know
what that is. We're gonna find out. What is it? Look at it. Scoop. No, no, no. Look. I want you
to look at the patches. Phylactery Lich just gave 50 dollars. Thank you for the 50 bucks Phylactery.
I can't wait for Jerma to extinct the human rice by shoving every food he finds directly in his
mouth. I'm not gonna do that. Don't worry. How do I look at this? How do I examine it? But thanks
to the 50 fucking dollars dude, seriously. On top of the insane amount of money we've already given.
Don't fall. What's that? What was that? Do I need, I need to like hit this with something? All right.
Don't fall down the waterfall. To like, you know, laugh out loud he fell down the waterfall. I'm
not gonna do that. Let's look at this one more time. They throw, they throw any branches. Yeah,
well they're on the mini map. Okay. I'm going over here. Memorize it. Remember it. Pay attention to
it. How do you climb? It's probably, it's important for me to know how to climb. Because it was on
the screen for five seconds and it was off. All right, so movement. Swinging and jumping. Stop
moving left stick before releasing A to cancel a jump. Left stick to swing. Hold A to prime a jump.
Release A to jump. Jump then hold A to grab foliage or the creepers when passing through it.
So you just hold A and then you let go of the left stick and you let go of A. I, yes. I'm not
gonna go this way. Everyone expects me to do the thing where oh the streamer fucking fell down the
waterfall and I laughed and it was not funny. Not today. Today we're going exploring. This is
sound. No, this is smell. Something stinks over there. Let me take a look. Oh my god. Okay. Oh my
god. Okay, we're fine. He fell down. All right, I gotta be careful. Let me see if there's anything
out here. Hold on. Be careful. There's some smelly things over here. We're hearing something going
on on the right side. I hear something over there. There are some sounds. Rock. New rock or the same?
Okay, should I carry the rock in my hand? Okay, I'm gonna smash somebody's head with a rock if I see
anybody. Gotta head that way. What's going on? What's wrong with me? What is that? Oh, those are,
those are my, those are my plants. Something can see me? I don't know what can see me right now.
This is freaking me out. Smell. What do I smell? There ain't nothing here. That's a rival? Is that
a rival monkey? I don't think it is. I think that's one of my friends, isn't it? He does have a stick
in his hand. This is my friend, right? There's a snake. Where? Where is there a snake? I don't see
a snake. All right, communication upgraded. I don't, there's no snake. We're fine. All right,
everybody come with me. Follow me, guys. We need to get over there. And there's berries over here.
I'm a professional. Don't fuck around. All right, there it is. Berries. Is it, is it berries?
That was fucking close. All right, we're almost there.
I need to get some vantage so I can take a look around. There's a new tree up here or something.
This is new. All right, guys. New. Everybody up. Take it. Smell it. Get it in your hands.
Alert. Alert. Alert. Alert. Why is there an alert? It's a pig. Oh shit. Somebody get a rock.
Does anybody have a rock? I do. No, give me the rock. Do I have the rock?
Okay, I got a rock. Where'd he go? Here. I think we're okay. I need to examine
this shit though. This is something new. Is it edible? New food. Caught. Eat it. Wait,
no, no, no. No, you got, don't eat it yet. Let me test it. Is it good? All right, we've all eaten.
Should I chop the tree down? Oh, no, you guys don't eat it all. Okay, analyze. I now know what that
looks like. Let's stand still. Let's smell. No, we got, that's where I want to go. Let's smell,
though. Let's just make sure. Not missing anything. Listening for something too.
Oh, I can hear you guys. Stop screaming. All right, we're good. Maybe one more for the road.
Kill the pig. We don't know how to use weapons. I can barely teach these guys how to throw a rock.
I don't know anything else. No, the mission is still the same. Get to this question mark. Identify
it. Memorize it. Get over there. There's something over there we need to investigate on. All right,
easy. Here we go. Hello? Is that guy on my team? I don't get it. All right, this is where the baby
was. Anything else we need to see over here? Oh, wait. Might as well take a look at it. Get
it in your brain. This is a hiding place. What? Hello? Is it above us? Where is it? Is it over
there? Where is this thing? Whatever it is, it's that way. What is it? Is it a snake?
Oh, it's a snake. Oh, shoot. Kill it. Kill the snake.
Fight it. Uh-oh. Hold A to prime dodging. Move left stick to choose direction. Release at the
right time. Okay. I'm poisoned. Drink water. Intimidate. Why did I chase it? I don't know
because I figured we were all gonna fucking stop them. Drink it. Drink the water. Drink the water.
Please. Drink the water. Oh, God. I need a healing plant. Somebody help, please. Medicinal? What's
that? Hiding spot. No. I need a medicinal plant. I don't know what's over there, but let's find out.
Hurry up. All right. What's this? Is this wheat? It's wheat. New gathering spot. Fishing spot.
No, I'm still poisoned. What like heals poison? What? What? Huh? Fear of the unknown. Use your
senses and intelligence to identify what's around you. Fear and dopamine is needed to...
Dopamine is needed to avoid hysteria when in fear. Oh, fuck. It's another snake. Is that the same
snake? Everybody get over here. Strength in numbers. Give me that thing. All right. I need...
Snake still here? All right. I'm out. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up. Climb. Climb. Climb. Climb.
Don't. Just don't. No, no, no, no. Get it. Just get... What the fuck is that?
What? I thought it was a snake. Oh, my God. It's a lion. Get out of the way. Get up on the tree.
Climb. Oh, he's looking at me. Why is he looking at me? Why is he looking at me? Why is he looking
at me? Why is he looking at me? Get up here. He can't climb. Okay. What am I supposed to do?
He can't get up there. It's like the three stooges. He can't get up. He can't get up. He
can't get up. Come on. All the way up. What's wrong with me? Why? Where am I going?
I'm not in control. I'm not in control.
Did I just knock myself out? I have no idea. Am I still poisoned? What happened?
I put my head so hard that I cured the poison. What is in my hand? New food? A giant African snail.
When did I pick up a snail? Nutrients from the mollusk kind of food. I'm still poisoned.
Dammit. All right. I need to fight. I need to learn how to fight. I need to lie down first,
I think. How did I even get back here? I need to lie down. I'm gonna sleep off the poison.
I'm good. You died? This is a different monkey. Why is this one? Wait, did we all get bit by the
snake or something? Wait, this is a different... This is different. Wait a minute. Hold on. Is
this still you? Who's on me? Wait, this is not me? Partnered with Book. Oh, okay. I can't even,
man. I need to learn some new abilities. There we are. All right. You're supposed to just die
because there's no way you can survive. All right. Handling. What about what just opened up down
here? More communication. Self-empowerment. Once connected, clan members will have the capacity
to automatically mimic an intimidation or the action of conquering fear. Get down there.
I need you guys to be independent. Good. All right. What about this generation? The past
generation was being an adult, being your clan's active settlement, and the clan must have at
least one kid. Okay, so we need... We got more shit here to do. So this is generational. Switch
an item from... So this means that new... Wait, does this person not know how to do anything?
Shit. Okay. Generational. Item manipulation. So what about... This is reinforce. So the new
monkeys will know that. So this is ensuring that the next generation will know. Okay.
This... I mean, that's fairly important, I think. All right. Let's go. I need to go... We need to
go to sleep. This time, I ain't gonna do anything till I fucking learn how to make like a weapon.
Why am I having a dream of the hyenas? All right. It's 8 a.m. Let's go.
We're good. Sleep, food, water. Everyone's healthy. Let's get this going. I was on an
expedition. We're not gonna do... It's too dangerous. Where is my stuff? I have like a rock over here.
This is... It was my grinding rock. Let me... I'm gonna build a little thing first. Here's a rock.
Give me a stick. Stick of some sort. Something like that. Here we go. Drop the babies. I get
extra points if I have a baby with me. Let's alter it. What the hell? Shit. I missed the
opportunity. Hold on. Alter it. New stripping. Okay. Now a grass can be modified. All right.
Now let's take a look at that. What do you think about this? Is it... Can I hit somebody with this
thing maybe? Okay. Stem. Stem and... I don't know. Just eat it. Enchant it. Now can I do something
with the rock? No. You made a butt scratcher. That's not gonna do anything. I need the... I need
like leaves. I need... Give me... I need a... Come here. Put my stuff over here. I need one of those
sticks. Give me the rock. I'm gonna make a stick and then I'm gonna take the stone and I'm gonna
make something else with it. Smash it up. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Don't throw it. Don't. I had to
let go and it's gone. That was obsidian. I don't know where it is now. Okay. So there we go. I don't
even need the rock anymore. Well, I do now. Okay. So you can just strip it. Now what happens if I
take an obsidian rock and I smash them together? I'm sharpening the end. Just learned how to make
a weapon and I'm gonna make like... What happened? Who died? Okay. Well, I don't know. It just
happened. Come on. Come on. Keep it going. New alteration. An obsidian can alter a stick.
And now this stick can be used. Use the obsidian as a tool at least twice. Switch up the hands.
Take a look at the weapon and learn. Pointy means pain. Ow. Sharp. Blood. Sharpened stick. Good.
I now have a weapon. I am ready. I am gonna actually give this to you.
Come here. I want you to take this. Learn. Take that. Why is everybody choking?
Here. Take this item. Good. Now you have the pointy stick and we're gonna make like three of these.
He's dying. He's not dying. Oh, I'm eating bugs. What happens when I get this to level two?
All right. Couple. Couple? Should we make some more children? Wow. I have two kids. There's two kids
on me. Okay. Ig. Coupled with Ku. All right. Good. Make sure you take that stick with you.
You're gonna be fine. Stop like... What are you choking on? Analyze. Yeah, you're fine. All right.
We're gonna make babies. You and I. Here. Eat this. Eat it.
Well, never mind. Here. Somebody else eat this. All right. Now it's time. I'm gonna make a couple
more sticks. We need to have some... some form of defense. I'm not gonna walk around the jungle
without anything. It's that. Grab the rock. Let's make another sharp stick. Do the rock and obsidian
next. You don't know how to use them. Can I just like stab somebody with this so we know what happens?
Like I can't just walk into somebody with this and just stab them through like the chest.
And everyone would be like... and they'll know that it's... that it does that. Oh my god. I'm a
fucking idiot. I'm gonna put this down. Water. Why am I afraid of the water? Does phobia get passed
down from generation to generation in this game? I'm good. Got a stick. Put this down. Now put the
stick down because I need to drink water. All right. Everybody get over here. Water, guys.
Everybody in. Look what I'm doing. Do what I'm doing. Why you have to... food, water,
didn't we learn this already? Everybody in the water. Follow me in here. In the water.
In the water. You can do it. Very good. All of you now. I know I'm gonna move because you're
not gonna do it. In here. Get in the water. Why won't he come in the water? Look. Okay.
Do I need to teach you everything? Yes, apparently I do. Do we even have any more food?
Stab him. No. I need to... okay. I need... where's my food? Where's food? Hold on. He's like...
is food over here, right? Right here. Come here. Everybody over here right now. I'm going blind?
What? Eat it. Good job. Finally. Can we drink in here now? Good. I can't... I cannot have...
I can't have sex right now, guys. All right. You got a stick. I got a stick. That should be good.
Everyone's eaten. Everyone's drank. Let's go. Where's my stick? There it is. Give me my stick.
I don't know how to use it, but I might be able to like accidentally hit something with this. All
right. Let's try this again. I want to go somewhere close. I don't know what... I don't know what this
is, but I... wait a minute. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Can I hit it? I think I
can hit this with a stick. Let me try. Use the stick on here. Come on. Come on. You know you want
to do it. Swing on... swing the stick. Ow. Damn it. I thought I could just whack it. I can't hit.
Damn it. All right. We need to go to bed. Try to hit a tree. Let me see if I have any more evolution
points. I do want to do this. See if I can reach it. Is there enough points? Yes, there is. Thank
God. You can drop an item while moving as acquired. Good. Now that opened up something over here.
Need more dexterity. Motor skills. Growth potential for reflexes. More training is needed.
Motor skills. Potential ability to build. I have to like just bring trees and branches and
shit over there. All right. Lie down. Sleep. I'm getting up at 5 a.m. and we're going out.
Put down the children. The children give me bonus points.
The ability to breathe while walking has been unlocked.
Oh yeah. Something like that. Somebody else is dead. How are there people dying?
Are those people that are still out in the wild? Okay. I've got my... we got two spears.
It's you. How did you die? Why are we just dropping like flies? I don't understand.
Analyzing the corpse of a friend generates energy as for other actions. Use it for evolution while
resting on it. Okay. I just got points for looking at it. Dead for zero years. How do I
like get rid of them? This is gonna attract predators. All right. I'm doing something else.
Everybody over here. Eat. Come here. Everybody eat. Everybody drink. Use corpses of training.
Tell me that's not gonna work. You need to survive. We need to eat. We need meat to survive. We don't
need to eat meat to survive. The real question I have is why can I not break this stuff? We've
eaten all the stuff over here. We need more food. This settlement is done. We've eaten everything
here. Follow my lead. I need building points. Hold on. Do what I do. Pick. Do what I do. Drop.
Right over here. You can do it. No, no, no. Hold on. And then I'm gonna burn this. Okay. Start
construction. Oh. I just figured it out. Various construction can improve your settlement.
There you go. I just did it. All right. I deserve some water for that one. I got my weapon.
I am going to go. We need to find some more food or something.
What is that? Let's go take a look. Can I? I can't hit this. No. I can't break it.
Even with a stick. I don't. My butt. Ow. My like brain doesn't understand. I'm gonna climb up here.
What have we got up here? Anything new? Yeah. Looks like it. All right. I'm gonna get this.
No snakes and shit, right? What is this? New stuff? What is that? What is this? Food. Found
the food tree. Eat up. No. I need to get. What the hell do I need? Nothing there. Are you eating?
Smell. Anything smell? That's something down there smells.
I'm going that way. Can I inspect it? I think I've already inspected this I think.
Where's the other clan members? Especially where's the one with the spear?
No. You're down there. Okay. Let's go. I'm gonna be careful this time.
I don't. I really don't want to fuck this up. I need to discover something.
Smell. Up top. Any apples? What's over there? I get something that way.
In there. There's something smells. I'm staying in the up up in the trees.
I ain't gonna get fucking killed up there. I learned new intimidation techniques.
Got a pit stop right here. Easy. You got a stick? All right. We both got sticks.
You gotta be fucking kidding me. I'm fine. That was just barely not enough to get hurt.
What is that? Oh, a new thing. No, that's I know what that is. A hiding spot. Okay. I know what
that is. Another hiding spot. Don't know what that is. Let's check that out first. Memorize that.
Remember it. Burn it in your brain. Let's go. Okay, let's make our way down here. I'm gonna go up.
Can I climb this? Climb the moss over here, right? You can do that. How can you not do that?
Got it. This way. Have you seen this before? Is this new? I don't think this is new.
No, it's not. Just want to make sure this is not something new.
Nope, but it smells good. Eat it. Get over here. Get over here. Come on.
Well, I'm trying. I can't. Whatever. Let's go. Where was the thing that I wanted to inspect over
here? Oh, it was down here. Okay, right there. Granite rock. Granite rock. Don't need that.
What is that? Unknown. It looks like there's predator faces over there, though.
Is that a snake or something? More food. Are those mine? Are those my monkey friends?
Yeah, they are. Okay. I'm going over there. Is it a beehive?
Somebody's choking. What's that? Do you hear that? Who's choking?
I don't know who's choking. That is a beehive. I'm gonna get the honey. I gotta go. I gotta go.
Gotta go. Gotta go. Found it. It's right here. Why is somebody choking? I got it. What is it?
How do I take it? Okay, I gotta let go of this. Somebody is still choking. I don't know why. I
died. Donut. Okay, I got my right hand is free. Here we go. Grab. Should I grab the beehive?
It's bees? Kapok fiber. What do I do with this? All right. Who is that? What do I do with this?
All right, easy. Smash it. Apply. It's like soap. Okay, I learned how to bathe with like a
fucking beehive. What's next? Find a new spot that we haven't seen. There is a snake over there.
I am fucking around. This is what I wanted to look at. What's over here?
Okay, we know what those do. Let's get some drink while we have a minute.
Food. There's a snake over here. There's a snake over here somewhere. Wait, where's the snake?
I'm not gonna fucking die again. Where is it? Giant warthog. Where is there a giant warthog?
We work together. Got it. Intimidated the warthog. We have sticks and shit. I would be scared too,
wouldn't you? I don't even know where they were. He saw the stick. All right, now let's go back
down here. Let's make sure there's nothing here. I don't see anything. What about here? I'm gonna
know. Let's eat. All right, good. Let's eat. Let's drink some water on our voyage.
I need to put the stick down. I don't like that though. Maybe I should give the stick
to somebody else. Come on in and drink. He's drinking mud water. Give that person the stick.
I'm using my two children. No, I'm not. Then I'm not using like the kids' armor.
I'm getting extra points for being here. What? What is it? What is it? What is it? Snake, snake,
snake, snake, snake. Intimidate. Together. Should I go to stab the snake? Nope. Intimidate. Let's go.
Together. That's right. Fuck off. All right, now throw javelin style into the snake. That's right.
We got two sticks and our crew. You don't want to fuck with us. All right, what we got? We got some
new stuff over here. This is different. I don't think I know what this is. This is a new item.
Let's check it out. Is it? What's going on? Why can I not inspect? Fishing spot. Huh? Oh shit.
Did I get one? I got one. Spear fishing. You found a way to get food in a fishing spot.
Is it? What is it? It's a lobster. Nice. All right. Do we need to cook food? Did our ancestors
cook food? I think they just ate anything they found on the ground. What the hell? Oh god. What
do I do? Why is it? Are we just watching like a match? Where did that happen? He just kind of ran
over. Wait, wait, wait, wait. I got to put down my like crawfish weapon. Somebody just puked.
Who just puked? How do I eat this? No, how do I eat the crawfish? How do I eat it?
I want to eat the fish. Oh, whatever. Okay, let's go. I think that was over here.
Yeah, there's all kinds of fucked up shit going on over here. Relax, everybody. Hold on.
Don't get too crazy up here. Okay, there he is. There he is. There he is. There he is. There he is.
What do we do? What do we do? I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do
about this. Should we scream at him? Should we run? I think we've run. No, no, no, don't fight.
Intimidate. Yeah, we got sticks. It's fine. Good. The sticks really do help. He's right there.
Get out of here. Run away. I want to get over there. He's going to try to wrap around.
Inspect the stick. I can't take it off. All right, watch out. Away from the pig.
Can we sleep up in a tree? Up here, follow me. Where are you going? Where are you going? Where
are you going? Come on. Don't be the one that's left behind. Where's the number three? Number
four. All right, we got four, right? I'm too stupid to grab with the other hand. What's wrong?
Am I getting gas? Am I getting gas for andrological problems? That just gave me a stomach ache.
Should I not have eaten that? I need a place to sleep. We need to go over there. All right,
we need to go over there. All right, let's go. What is it? There's something over there.
Question mark. I got to get up top. We need to find a place to hang out before it gets too late.
I need to sleep. Holy shit. That would have been so fucking horrible. Okay, I'm almost at the
unmemorized item has been forgotten. It's been forgotten. How does that make any sense?
All right. I found the thing that I'm... Why is there a ticking like,
bomb sound? No. All right, let's make camp over here. No, we don't. No, we don't. Don't make camp
over here. Don't make camp. Don't make camp over here. Don't make camp. All right, we can get up
here. I don't know what it is. I don't know where I'm looking at. I hear something. This is
alligators. Alligators. Jesus Christ. Get up. I don't know what to do. Hurry up and get up here.
He's trying to surprise. Let's help. What do we do? Should I stab? Go. He was trying to hold
his mouth closed. Where's the thing I need to get? It's over... Where is it? Over here?
This is not the appropriate music for what's happening right now. This is like Dora the
Explorer music. I lost my stick. Why did they want me to come over here? I need to get up high,
and then what's the thing I need to examine for my future generations to know what it is?
Where is it? Is it up there? I don't even fucking understand what the hell this wants me to do.
All right. I'm dying. How do I stop bleeding? How do I fix my bone? How do I fix my bones?
I don't know how to fix them. I don't have no idea. I think you're alive still. Okay, you need
to take... You're gonna take... You're gonna take everybody. Here, take... Take the kids. Take the
kids. Take the kids. Take the kids. How do I put the kids down? Take the kids. No, take the kids.
Forget about this stuff. Take the kids. I need to eat something and just sit. Good luck. There's a
hiding spot over there. There's a crocodile right below me. Oh, he's dead. I couldn't even hand off
the kids. Here we go again. Okay, what are you gonna do now? He's just... He's following me up.
He's like, slow down. Wait, wait, wait. It's not worth it. You don't have to be great.
Just hold on a minute here. I think... I think we're still alive. We got to the top of the tree and
then we somehow made it home. I don't know how. Okay, well, let's lie down. We've unlocked some
new things, apparently. A cognitive enhancement. Once connected, it would be possible to detect
more distant elements through the intelligence. Okay. The ability to detect more distant elements
through intelligence is acquired. Tap Y to use your intelligence and follow the steps proposed
by the contextual actions. Did I unlock anything over here? EU has an increased capacity to
metabolize food, but is EU even still alive? All right, let's lock in a couple more of these.
Lock that one in and let's lock this one in too. All right, the kids are gonna stay.
It feels like this game was made without any real premise. Just a bunch of ideas.
Kind of. I'm good. Water, sleep, food. I don't have any sticks. Who's even left in the plan?
I've got a couple people here. All right, let me try. Give me rock and give me... What about two
rocks? Do two of these do anything? Two obsidian rocks. I mean, I just... I think there's something
here. There's something here to explore. No. Pick it up. Give me the... Pick up the rock.
Pick up the fucking rock. Give me the rock. Memorize where the rock is and look at it and
pick it up. No. Is there another one over here? I can do something with this too.
Pick up the rock. I could have just picked it up. Why can't I pick it up? Give me the rock.
I just saw it. I just hit A. Fine. Take the other one. This person is so dead. Can I at
least move this person out of the way? No, I can't pick up the rock because this game suffers from
so many games that do this. They tie every action to the same button. I'm just gonna make it fun.
Come here. I did it. Give me a stick. Give me this damn thing. I need another obsidian rock.
I ain't gonna find one. I have to go looking for a rock. I mean, hold on. Can I do anything
with these two? I don't think I can. No. Make a gun. I don't think I have the necessary items.
Can I not look at this yet? I feel like I should be able to examine the briar patch.
Touch it and go, oh! Anyways, what's over here? What's happening over there? A snake of some sort,
maybe? Is it a snake? What is going on here? Bugs? Can you eat bugs? Liftable rock. Okay.
I'm doing it with the stick. Come on. Use your strength. Oh, you idiot. I need a better stick,
a bigger one, a stronger stick. What do we got over here? More stuff to look at. He's trying his best.
Well, get up there and look. Look at it. It was just like, oh, what's this thing over here?
No, he doesn't care. No, you don't care. He still hasn't figured out that you can touch that.
Anything else over here that I can do? All this shit over there.
He's learning. I want to lift a rock up so bad. Come on. Liftable rock. I can do it. I just need
something stronger. Get everybody over here. Everybody, come here. We all might need sticks.
Let me make a few sticks. I need like a stick tree. That one right there?
No. Can we use this, though, for something? Are you guys coming? Here. I don't know. We're not
going to be able to use this for anything, but I'm going to put it over here. Give me a stick,
a big one. I wasn't doing the rock thing right. I didn't have a prop to do anything. It was his
whole day. And let go when it makes that sound. I didn't hear a sound. All right, there's a stick.
That's for you. Come here. Here. You take that stick. We're all going to do this together.
Come here. You. You take this one. This one's mine. Follow me. We're going to go get the buried
treasure that's underneath that rock. With me. Let's go. Wait. First, drink on your own because
you're stupid. Get over here. Drink. Just do what I do. Get in here. You're staring at it. You're
so thirsty, but you won't drink the water you're standing in. If only there was something cool and
refreshing. Why are you covered in blood? Get it. Why do they not understand this? How do you not
understand? Let's go. Follow me. Follow. Let's go. Bring your sticks. You gave them sticks to hold.
Well, is that my fault that they're that stupid? Everybody together. Let's get this thing up. You
got your sticks? Good. Together. Over here. Here we go. Help me lift. Bingo. I found mushrooms.
There it is. Take a look at that. New food. African agaric fungus. Here, you eat this
because you know who's the one that needs the most food? You. Just watch me eat it.
I think that means that I have a stomach problem. Here, come try it. We have to get our stomach
stronger. Try the mushrooms. They're delightful. Anybody else gonna eat one of these? Okay,
so I know that those are mushrooms. Very cool. There is another spot right there. More mushrooms.
Here, somebody take one of these. Take this. Here, try it. Look, see? Try it.
Finally, he's eating it. Do you like it? It's good, huh? I think I think it's drugs. Okay,
I think. Can we have some children? This is chio adult male coupled with clue.
Well, let's keep going. I think there's another rock. Yep, there's more stuff over here to inspect.
What's this? What do we got? Grab. This is a new rock. Oh, this one's marble. Tool. The salt.
What's that? What's that? What's that? What's that? What's that? Is it just the drugs?
It might just be drugs. What about the smells over here? I think we're good.
No, I don't see anything. All right, let me get this in memory. Why are too many drugs to figure
this out? There's salt. Salt over here. I need to just record this. Evolution points for that.
All right, keep going. I thought I freaked out first. I thought that was a giant snake.
I thought that was the head of a gigantic fucking like pterodactyl snake monster alien
with big spread out wings. I was about to shit my pants. What's over here? That anything up top?
I think I want to go to the one back there. This is too dangerous. I'm not high enough level for
this. Oh, there's that fiber. I probably should grab some of that. Yeah, let's get some of this
fiber. I'm going to try to combine it with something right hangs on a tree down here.
Can I do this? Can I? Maybe I can do something with these two things.
Yep, let's make a spear. Am I hungry or thirsty? I can get the salt can alter a stick. Okay, got it.
Spin that around. I need to grab the it is a couple over here. Where is it? There's one hanging
from that tree right there. I need to throw this rock. I don't need it anymore. Just get rid of it.
And I'm going for right there. I want to use this because I don't want to just rub this on my body.
I want to put this somewhere else. You know what I mean? I need to craft this into something.
Maybe I can grind it on the spear. Use it on the bloody clan member. That's actually not a bad idea.
That's not a bad idea at all. Where are they? Let me see if it's a problem.
Can I burn it? Maybe I can light it. All right, follow me back to the campsite.
We are good. What's the dead? What's the dead thing? I know I knew that you were dead.
Okay, there's the kid. Is there another person dead? I don't think so. All right,
so let me see. What can I do with this? I have a stick. Let me get a rock. Give me a rock. I'm
going to hit the rock and fiber together. I want a rock. I would love to pick that obsidian up.
That's right here. But I can't. This is not possible. So we're going to go over here.
Here's a rock. All right. Can I smash these two together? So I smashed them. That's not going to
do anything. Okay, I can stop it. Okay. What about this one? This other rock? This is obsidian,
right? Can I just eat this? Just crafted by itself? Okay. I can't. I'm missing something.
Maybe the rock? No, something else. Smash it. Smash it. Smash with rock. Smash with rock.
No, I need an obsidian rock. Not this one. This rock sucks. I need the obsidian rock.
And there was two in my bed, but I can no longer get to them. So we're gonna have to find another
one. I already know what that is. Let's just identify all this shit. This gives me points,
right? Might as well do it. Sleep spot. Oh, another sleep spot. Dead branch. That's for sticks.
Another sleep spot. Okay. Hello, baby. Fishing. Oh, there's a fishing spot right here. Obsidian
rock. I think I found an obsidian rock. Yes. Give me. Here we go. Will this do anything?
No, it won't. Well, I have an obsidian rock. I wanted this before. Try to sharpen this rock
with the other rock and then try to hit the sharpening rock on this thing. All right,
let's try that. Give me a rock. Put this down. God, fucking evolution sucks. Why did it take
this long? Just learn to read already. Try to pick up this rock. Where's the rock that I just
threw on the ground? Now I have to go to bed. It's just a regular rock. Oh, full of love of God.
Full of love of fucking God. Where is that rock that I had in my hand? And why can I pick it up?
Jesus. Okay, let's go. Come on. I need another obsidian rock now. Fuck. Why? I did it.
I let it go when I heard the sound. What do you mean wrong hands? It doesn't make any sense.
Do I really have to go on an expedition for a fucking obsidian rock? Because I can't get
this dumb thing out of here. Somebody's dead. I don't know. They wouldn't drink water while
they were standing. I can't help you if you're going to do that. How am I supposed to help you?
You won't even drink water while you're standing in the water. I didn't heal him. What do you mean
heal? And how do I tear this bed in half so I can pick up the fucking rock in here?
Oh my God. I have to go get a fucking rock. An obsidian rock to hit the... I need to sleep first
because there's no way I'm going to be able to do this without sleep. Go to bed. Okay.
Environmental analysis has been unlocked. I can detect rocks better. That's all I... That's it.
All right. Give me... Just keep this... Keep these ones around. These ones down here.
That's fine. And let's do item manipulation while moving. That's fine, too.
Okay. Go to bed. Rock hunt. Oh, found a rock. Good. Except it's not an obsidian rock,
so that's worthless to me. All right. Granite rock. Dead guy. Higher intelligence.
Branch. I don't think there are any... I would... I really want to get in there and get that rock,
but I fucking can't get in there and get that rock. I'm gonna eat and then go get a rock.
Yeah, I know I could have cured the bleeding, but I wanted to try... I wanted to try to combine
the fiber with something else. I could have like wiped him off, but I would rather try to combine
it. What's wrong with me? All right. I'm just going for it. No kids are with me. Give me a rock.
Invention's more important than lives. I'm just gonna have to go down here.
Branch. Fishing spot. Ran... Fuck. Just give me a... What are you doing here?
Why are you here? Get out of here. It's... Ew! How did you survive out here for so long? Holy shit.
I can't believe you're still alive. Is this... Is there a grip in this game? Okay. Good. Rest up
here. Look who I found, guys. Any rocks? No. No. Can I make obsidian? That'd be great.
You... You and I have to find a rock. And that's the only rock that I'm gonna have for the whole
clan. And we can't find one. So I'm just gonna bring you back. That's so bad. That looks so awful.
All right. Sit down. Hang out here for a little bit of you. I'm gonna sleep till tomorrow.
Hippopotamus? Oh, wait. It's noon. Never mind. All right. Who is left? I don't understand. I don't
know. I don't get it. I don't... What? I need some water or something, please.
I have to take the stick from you. Come here. Give me the stick. That's a rock. No, it's not.
That's that thing. Give me this. Stop paying attention to this and get over here. He's fucking
useless. No, now you go. Now you figure it out. I'm gonna take your stick, then. That's fine. All
right. Give me some... Let me eat. I can't believe I'm still on this fucking quest for a dumb rock.
There's an obsidian rock in my bed and I can't take it out. I can't, like, cover it up. I need
to make more children. Hit obsidian with normal rock. Are you kidding me? It's not gonna... It doesn't
work. Combine rock with head. Throw the rock at the obsidian? That's not gonna do anything.
Why is it so hard to find a one that's the most, like, prevalent rock on Earth? Just give me the
obsidian. It's right here. Just give it to me. Let's just have sex. Come here. We're a couple,
right? We gotta have some children. Come here. No, we're not. I thought we... I thought we were
together. I thought this was... Apparently not. Is it female elder?
It's okay. We still... It's still possible. We're good. That's it. We're good.
Okay, do we have to wait, like, till next year? We're going to bed till tomorrow. Wait,
are we both... We're both female? Is that true?
We gotta go extinct.
The male was the one that was bleeding.
Oh, is it it? Is that over? Range detection for non-edible resources has increased.
That's great. We're branching out, though. Hold on. Genetic mutation will be needed.
Okay, who's left? Spatial perception. Let's get this one down here as well.
There are wild males. I have to find them. Well, that's not gonna fucking work out.
Where's my mate? That's not right. No. Is it? No, that can't be right. No, that's not it.
Right there. There we go. We're good. There we are. We have a job to do. We have to... I gotta go.
All right, it's time to go. I'm not sitting around looking at a rock screen anymore. I
gotta get... I'm going. Give me a stick. I need to find new things. There's a new thing.
I'm going that way. It's right here. Let's go. Find a male. What do you think I'm trying to do
right now? I gotta try to find somebody. No, why are you here? You shouldn't be here. Both of you
shouldn't be here. Why are you both here? All right, I got them full on everything. It's time
to move this way. I need to get something. Something. I have to get something going.
There's that. We got something this way. There's nobody left at camp to watch them.
Right. That's... I guess that's true. We're gonna find it. We're gonna find a new camp,
a new settlement. Hopefully, it's right here. No, don't forget that. Memorize that.
All right, I gotta be careful. Don't do anything stupid. That was stupid. I'm fine. Okay, we're
good. We're there. Almost there. Whatever this is, whatever that is, I guess I'm gonna go look at it.
How's everybody doing? Okay, you're with me still? You have any sticks or anything?
No, you don't. Okay, let's get on the tree. I'm gonna go down over here. Now, what does it want
me to do over there? There's some big point of interest over there. What? Why didn't it not grab?
Okay, new stuff. It should have grabbed. Why did it not grab? What do you want me to do?
What just happened? The Sister Arches. New landmark. New camp. Discover the Sister Arches
as a memorable location. Good. So, what does that mean? Does that do anything for us? Not really?
All right. Well, okay. What's next? Stuff over here to look at. More of that fiber.
Hiding spot. It's a fucking obsidian. No, it's a granite rock. Wait. Hey. Hello. No, it's a pig.
What's that? Somebody else over here? Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. How are you? Nice to meet you.
You all right? Something's wrong. Do you have any gypsum? Just get the food. Here.
Take this. Eat this. How you doing? You good? Okay. And let's get another one. Let's get some more.
Here. Try this. This will help. All right. Couple formed. All right. So, male. Okay.
All right. Stay right there. Stay. Don't move. Don't move. Don't move. Everyone chill.
Where's the beehive? Okay. I'll be right back. I'm going to get one of these beehives
and I'm going to heal you. Stay there. Don't move. Where's one? Right here. There's one right
at the top of this tree. I will be right back. It's a long fall. I think I can make the jump
from here to there. Give me it. Okay. I got it. Don't fall from that height. I want to climb down.
Can I make it from here? Yes, I can. All right. Come here. I got something for you over here.
Intimidate who? Who am I intimidating? Who am I intimidating? What the fuck is going on over
here? Is it a bird? Over here. Oh, hi. Okay. You. You are... Here you go. I got something for you.
Take that and rub it all over your body. You all right? What the fuck? I gave it to him.
I handed it to him. I think he's fine. He's not injured anymore. No, he's fine.
You have a broken bone. He... What? Did it take too long? All right. Let's go. New stuff.
Okay. We need to get back to... I can't go any further. This is literally the last of the entire
clan. Right? We're going to head back. Let's make a bed over here. Can I just make a bed with these?
I think I can. Get out of the way. I'm trying to make us a bed. Is that enough? We got to get
this going. All right. Come here. No, no, no, no. I need to settle. What do you mean settle? Settle?
Oh, I made this my news. On the edge of a mount on a cliff. We did it. We bought a new home.
You and me. And the old lady. We did it. All right. Let's go.
Hooray. Give birth. Let's go. New member. My child. 15 months later. Hey, Granny's still there.
I was probably supposed to do this in the first like 30 minutes. Ran right into the screen.
New baby. All right. Oh, there's another one. And she's so beautiful. Congrats on twins. I wonder if
you'll learn anything. Go for another. Can you? I don't think you can. Maybe you can. Where's the
other baby? Okay. What's this? New communication skill. That's a long way to go. I don't think it's
gonna make it. It's not gonna make it. Oh, it made it. It's not possible to ask from a distance some
clan members to come closer and follow. Hold B and release B to have the visible clan members
follow you. Okay. Body language. I need to do some more like punching and kicking.
Evolution. Explore. Expand. Feared rival. Feared species. What is this shit? Advanced problem
solver? To launch an evolution, you must be at your clan settlement and have passed at
least one generation and succeeded in evolutionary feat. Leading tool user rocks. Use the tool ready.
Ready one. Ready three. Are these just achievements? Evolve. Birth of a cartographer.
Okay. Now. I'm not mating again. No. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Item manipulation. Drop
while moving. Body language. And this one. Okay. Change generation? Is that what I'm gonna do?
When passing a generation, the neurons that have not been reinforced will lose their energy and
will have to be refilled. All unborn babies will also be lost. Do you want to still pass
a generation? Am I doing this? So we, we, these are the kids that are grown up now.
15 years later. Is that grandma? 15 years later? 15 years. 15 years. Reinforce your
lineage's neural development. Early phase one. What do you mean 15 years? Metabolism is now
effective. Where is everybody? Oh, okay. This is you. Where is everybody? Who am I? Who are you?
Oh, that's you. Okay. That's you. Okay. You and who am I? Okay. No, there's a lot of people here.
All right. So this is you. I'm going to play as you. All right. We're good. Anybody have any kids?
You have any kids? Okay. So we have to, we have to do some, somebody has to have a kid. Oh,
shit. Look at that. You and the members of this, of the lineage will have the capacity to better
metabolize nutrients. This spontaneous genetic mutation will become effective after the lineage's
next evolution. Okay. This is right. All right. I need to, we need to, we need to go out there.
Okay. There's a lot of people. We got to fit this big amount of people here. So let's do,
I want, wait, let's get some rocks. First things first. Let's eat. Okay. How's everybody doing on
thirst? Have some sticks and some rocks and some spirits. Let's take a look at the new destination
we've got. Oh, somebody is over there. I think there's children. There's like 30 people in this
clan. Tribe or whatever this is. What is like a bunch of, what, what, what is it called? Is it a,
is it a clan? A gaggle? I got a gaggle. Okay. What is that? I found the big stick in the middle of
the forest. Let's go look at it. What did you want to do here? Is that not what you wanted me to do?
Oh, it's not actually anything. Okay. Grass, fishing spot. Still, by the way, just want to
make sure everyone's aware. I haven't seen a single obsidian rock on the rock. It's been 17 years.
I, this is just danger. I don't want to do this. This is bad crocodiles and shit everywhere.
This is a stupid idea. Where are you going? Where are you going? Where are you all going?
Where are you all going? Don't don't. Why are you running? Why are you running? Why are you all
running the random directions? Excuse me. See you in rock though. We got to get some sticks.
Something right there that I don't know what it is. Oh, hold on. New tool. New tool. New
gathering spot. It is a hole to poke. Dammit. All right. I need to give me this. Can I take a
branch off this or something? I got some more senses. I want to poke that hole. Is it a note?
Run. Run. Oh my God. Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up the tree, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up,
up the tree, up the tree. Everybody. Oh, my whole fucking body hurts. Up, up, up, up, everybody.
Okay. Random fucking tiger. Obsidian. Is it obsidian? It's probably the loudest sound I've
ever done. You still around? No, there's alligators and shit. How are you ever supposed to do this?
This is not even possible. How did anybody, how did humans survive? I can't even find a fucking rock
on the ground. And you tell me that we've, no way. We were dropped off by aliens. Up the tree,
everybody. I'm like bleeding. I need one of those fucking beehives. Here we go. Up here.
There might just be one up here. There it is. Give me it. Okay. Use it. Anybody else hurt?
I got another one of these. Nobody bleeding. I just want a rock. I don't want to come this far
out on an expedition. I just want a rock. I want an obsidian rock. Can't get it. I need a stick.
I want to poke these rock. Let's go back to camp. I need to fly. Seriously. Have everybody
else stay home while you get a rock so nobody dies. That's not a bad idea. That statement that
is made is stupid. What the hell is going on now? Everybody stay home till I so I can find a rock.
Okay. Let's go. What is over? It's a snake, I think. Snake maybe somewhere. Back to camp. Let's go.
Down there. I need to, is anybody else bleeding? Just eat. Seven out of ten. Seven out of ten.
What are you talking about? Can I combine these two? I wonder if I can combine.
Maybe I can. Don't try this at home. All right. Here we are. Back at our camp. It's currently
15 o'clock. I'm gonna combine these. No I'm not. Let me take a good look at all of you.
Anybody bleeding? What does end expedition even mean? I'm gonna leave this here. Who would have
thought finding sticks would have been the hardest fucking thing in this whole game?
There was one tree that had sticks. I don't fucking want to do this thing, man.
Here. You take this. I don't know. Whatever. Can I use this? Maybe combine these two?
No. Can I poke at the hole? All right. Everybody stay here. Wait. All of you. Nobody come with me.
I don't want to see one person here. Stay. You too. All of you. Stay. Okay. I'm gonna go poke that
hole. See what happens. It's down here, right? There was another one. I can't believe it's just
granite. Where the hell am I gonna find them? Just mix lava and water. It's easier said than done.
Oh, finally. Okay. I'm actually kind of glad you came with me because we need to make some sticks.
Take this. Now get the fuck out of here. Can I combine both the two sticks together for any
reason? No. Just dual welding. Okay. That's fine. All right. Now, this is a stick I can poke with
these. Fucking granite. Where was the hole? I really don't even know where the hole was. I
thought they were right here. There it is. All right. Here we go. Poking. Food can be poked out
of holes. Okay. So how do I learn stabbing if you know you can poke? Why can't you know you can
stab? I haven't learned that yet, apparently. I hear something. There's something coming.
Right there. Shake? Oh, it's dropping coconuts.
Coconuts have fallen. This is awesome. Okay. Hold on. I think it's a pig. Yeah, it's a pig.
He's just chilled. I'm trying to spear this motherfucker.
I'm walking bait. Wait, can I stick it? Wait, hold on. I think I can do this.
No, I want to stick a straw in there and drink it. I swear to fucking God, man. What?
Oh, why does this have to fucking happen? God damn it. That's two in a row. Twice in a row.
All right. Why can't the boar come over here? Shake coconuts off his head. Get away from me.
No, get... No, no, no. Don't call anybody.
Get away from... Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait. I need one of those things. No!
Ew. Is that you? Ew. Come here. Ew. You all right? Oh, no, that's not... No, I'm all right.
I'm you. Right. I know. Fucking rock. I want a fucking obsidian rock.
Why is that such a rare resource in this game? Okay. I can use granite? Well, why... Don't I need
obsidian to scrape the granite to make it so it's a scrappy rock? I thought that was the whole deal.
Otherwise, what the hell have I been doing for the last, like, 45 minutes?
I can just use two rocks. My caramba. What is... No, give me that. No, give that back to me.
Yeah, you can't be trusted with this. This is mine. I need to sleep. Back to bed. Let's go.
I did end an expedition. I don't know what that does. All right. We got some new stuff to do.
What's over here? How motor skills will improve. The neuron can't be initiated because you don't
have the neurological energy. Carrying kids will perform... So I have to carry it on the kids.
Do you want to sleep? I also need a water source. Yeah. Am I lying in with a skeleton?
There's bones in here. I'm sleeping in a grave. All right. Now give me a rock. Give me two rocks.
I need to drink water. And then... I don't even remember what the fuck I was going to do with
those rocks. I have no clue. I was going to do something with the fiber, with the rock,
that could be grinding. Right? I want to eat, not pick up an item on the ground.
This is not very nutritious. How much do I have to drink of this shit? Is there anybody to even
tell? There's just a big green circle on my screen. Just drink it all. All right. I'm going to make
this a... Give me... Here we go. There we... Oh, you found two rocks. He found two fucking rocks.
I'm unbelievable. All right. Now get out of here. Give me this. Give me a fiber. No, give me this
thing. Can I like grind it with the sharpening thing? Let's see what happens. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. I need to... Give me one of those hives. There's always one there on top of the
trees. Go. What's that? I heard something over here. What? Somebody just hit bro. Mother fucker.
Where are these things? I swear to God, every time I'm looking for something, it's not on the
screen. There were just like 300 of these and now they just don't... They don't exist. What?
Where are all the honeycombs? It's been hours and I'm still a monkey. Yeah. Sorry. I'm a little...
I'm getting a little slow to the renaissance period. Sorry, guys. There they are. And I'm
hungry too. I'm very hungry. Like too hungry to even grab anything. Is there birds in this stuff
here? What is this? This is like a huge nest. New discovery eggs. New discovery egg. Who cares
about this thing? I want... Give me the egg. Inspect it. Cook egg. Quick. Take one. Take it.
Take an egg. Quick. Take a couple of them. Drop it. Okay. I'm fine. All right. I got two eggs.
Yeah. The spoils of war. Let's go get another one. I also have to get the rock.
I left a rock up here. I need that thing. Where was it? Over here? Where was it? Where's my rock?
All right. Let's do... Let's Spider-Man this. Let's get a good view. What the fuck are you doing?
Remember, every action is the same button. Oh my god. What? Did you press A? Press A again. A.
Hold A. Let go of A. Press A. Hold A. Let go of A. Press A twice. I'm bleeding. I need one of those
things. I gotta find one. I know. I know I'm bleeding. I just need one of those things,
but I got so disoriented. Let's... All right. Down there. Let go. Let go. Let go. Let go.
Give me another one. Give me my rock. I got my rock, motherfucker. See you later. Okay. So far,
so good. Now I just gotta get to... Over here. There it is. Go. Okay. Use it. I gotta stand on top.
What's this? It's a golden egg up here. There's a golden egg. There's a golden egg here.
I'm gonna pick up the golden egg. It's a golden egg. I'm gonna say the same thing five times.
Ten times. What's this golden egg? No. I know what this is. You fucking idiot.
I know what you're fucking rock. All right. Stop. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What is this? New food? Oh. These things are very nutritious.
They're similar to nutrients from this dope food. Okay. I got it. I have my rock. I just need...
I wish I had a... I wish I had a backpack. Can I make, like, soup? Never mind. Thank God.
Okay. Seriously, I don't want to, like, let go of A, but I have to.
I'm finally gonna do it. Here's the funny music, the good music, the you did it music. Here we go.
It's time. I have in my hands right now, I have a grinding stone and fiber. I'm about to do something
that will... it's taking four hours to do. You lied to me. Keep doing it. Keep doing it. Keep
doing it. Keep going. Not long enough. I can't do it in the tree. I have to do it on the ground.
Another jump scare tiger down here. Let me make sure. Hold on.
Do it on the ground. Do I need to do it on top of sticks or something?
I need an obsidian grinding stone. If that's the case, if that's true,
I'm going to be very angry because that's what I've been looking for.
Everyone told me no. I don't need that. All right, let's try it. Here we go.
Every button is the same button. Don't you understand? I fucking hate that so much.
Where is it? It doesn't matter. I can just... just give me... it's right here somewhere. It's
right here, right? Just give me this one. Just fucking bang the rocks together again. They're
right here. Give me the fucking rock. Give me two of them, please. Thank you. Give me another one.
Sorry. Jump is also grab is also hold is also laugh is also grind is also fucking eat is also
groom. It's also run. Where? All right. So should I fucking just do both of them? No.
Don't throw it. Keep it in your hand. All right. Screw this. Here's what I'm doing.
I'm fucking gonna turn this guy. I'm gonna turn this into a panini press.
No, I want to do both rocks. Whatever. Can I only have which one is the which one's the griddle?
Okay, good. Got it. Okay. Should I maybe try to grab at least they do try this thing. Maybe
I should try doing this. I'm going home. He's furious. I'm not furious. I'm fine. I'm fine.
Don't worry. I'm gonna be fine. But I will. I will put this down. I want to have. Yes,
I got a grinder. I have a grinder in my hand. But what the hell do I do with a grinder grind up
berries, seeds, berries? What? I don't understand. What do you? Why do I have this? That's so bad.
There's only mushrooms. All right. So let's think about a scenario here where I don't get killed by
the boar that's near me. Make a stick and kill the boar that there ain't even any combat in
this game. I don't know what's going on. He's even killing other players. He's killing other
players that aren't even me. What is there? Is there a cop? Why is this flashlight in my eyes?
Help! Help! Where is he? I want to go to the boar and like pick up the boar meat.
When am I going to discover fire? I don't think I'm going to discover fire. I'm having trouble
discovering rocks on the ground. You think I'm going to be able to do fire? What is it? Why?
Why? What's here? What's here? Okay, just get rid of one of these fucking rocks. Which one of them
is the grill? Which one of the rocks is like the griddle? Why is this? Am I being stalked? I can't
tell which one is the grill on it. I don't know. Can anyone see? Okay, it's mounted in my left hand.
That means right hand I can just throw it. I don't care. Okay, now what is this? What is this? Why is
it telling me to like look at this or be aware of this? Inspect. No. Go to the light. Should I?
What? Should I do that? Why is it doing some Truman Show shit? What did I just do? I just picked that
up and waterfall. All right, there's the tiger and there's the boar. I'm gonna be patient here.
I'll just sleep. Look at that. I want it. I want it. I'm gonna wait till he's gone. Should I throw
the panini at him? Should I? I'm gonna throw my fucking panini at him and see if he leaves.
Don't don't do that. Wait, hold on. There's probably something I can throw over there,
right? Like a stick or a branch or something. I want that so bad. All right, here we go. All
right. I've got it. I'm just gonna throw this over there because I want to build. I want to go like
sniff. I want to go smell the corpse. That's what they do. Is that the panini? I can't tell.
I don't even know what's in my hands. Okay, what's in my right hand? Okay, here we go. Ready? See if
I can get him to move over here. Dude, I would love to do a jumping R1 on this fucking tiger right now.
Why did it just put me like all the way down here? There's another combat scenario coming up here.
There's a snake. Snake is going to the tiger right now. Look it. See? That's gonna be huge.
This could be huge for me. I just have to observe and the snake might kill.
Snake is right there. The snake might kill the tiger from behind.
This is great. I love climbing. Apparently didn't learn that. Okay, sit right there. Is that not a
snake? How do I get you to leave? Any rock plus stick equals weapon. I did. I tried that before.
Can I sneak up and grab a stick? The only stick I can see is literally right here.
There's a stick there. That's the only thing I can get it. I'm gonna try.
This is scary. I made it. Okay, this is my chance. This is my opportunity to intimidate. I got my
rock. What's wrong with me? Oh, I'm about to lose my mind. I'm about to lose my mind, right?
Sniping with the rock. Okay, I gotta go for it right now. This is the time.
Nope. Quick for other generations.
Do we get to meet a tiger? We're fine. No more fucking around. I am pissed.
Give me a rock. Give me a stick. I wonder if it's gonna take me like another 40 minutes to find a
rock. Assemble a crew and avenge. Liftable rock. Got it. Oh, it actually means I can just
pick it up. Okay, here we go. Ready? I'm making a deadly fucking weapon. A granite rock and
altar stick. I already knew that. I now have my weapon in my hand. What's that thing? What's that?
There's frogs. Hold on. Wait, wait, there's frogs. Can I pick them up? No. What was that? What is
wrong with me? What the fuck was that? Does it mean I'm tired? All right, well, I got a stick.
I need to hit something. The only combat that the game told me for a tutorial was
A is dodge. I wonder if A is swing too. I mean, everything in this whole fucking game is A,
so I would be shocked if it wasn't A to swing. All right, I'm going to bed. A is counter-attack.
A is dodge. A is jump. A is learn. A. A for ape. Of course. I want to make another couple of sticks.
When can I evolve to literally use my other hand for anything?
I'm not just lefty. I don't have access to my left arm. I mean, I'm not just a righty. I don't
have any access to my left hand. Where is my stick? Where's the stick that actually has a
sharp end to it? I'm killing this motherfucker right now. I just wanted to go to sleep. I just
wanted to go to bed. I just wanted to get a rock and go to sleep. And now I'm gonna die.
And I'm underwater now, so I can't even... There it is. Where's the bed?
Where's the bed? The whole... This is... I'm looking... It's like cell-shaded graphics now.
Is somebody pissed in my cell-shaded graphics space? Okay. Like, what... Where is the bed? Sleep
it off. All you gotta do... Okay, food and water is bad. Very bad. Not good at all. I need to... Hold
on. Do I have enough for this yet? No, I don't have any, like, children. Oh, no. My birth and
death rate is terrible. I can't do any of these. Well, I know that there is water down here,
but there's food as well. There is. Everybody come over here and eat. You've died every time
somebody's been born. Well, come on. My only goals in this game are to eat food and dodge tigers.
Failed both of them? Yeah, one of those is a lot easier than the other one.
You're gonna over-hydrate and die. Hey, anybody else? Fucking idiot and doesn't want to drink?
Come on down here. You need me to shut you out of the way. You can lead a man to water,
but you can't make him fish or whatever it is. You can teach a man to fish, but you can't
give him water. I don't know. Whatever that saying is. You know what it is.
What's wrong with the one on the left? They all have, like, stomach aches. What is wrong with you?
Are you hungry? He's holding food in his hand. Or is that a ring? Give me that,
you idiot. He wouldn't eat it. He was holding his stomach on. Oh, man. I wish I had something to
eat in my... I wish I had a ring pop like what's in my right hand. Okay, now it's time. The hot
today is gone. All right, give me a fucking spear. Shake the tree. No, give me a... It's time for a
smoke break. It might be. Smoke break. I'm gonna start drinking. Am I dead? Oh well. Better. Let me
grind up a rock on this. Have a weapon. Go take a smoke break. I don't smoke. Don't worry.
Add to pile? What does that do? Can I just have, like, a few of them here? I guess. Weird. Okay.
All right. Let me just hang... I'm gonna have a sharpened spear. I gotta... You know what? I wish
they would just pick it up. Why am I the only person that ever grabs anything? It's been 17
years and nobody's picking up any sticks? Well, you didn't hand it to me. Okay. Here. Can you do
something with this? I have to, like, equip all of my people with stuff. Why don't they learn?
I'm the only one that learns here. Nobody else does. In fact, they're so fucking stupid.
If they're holding an item, they will starve to death. Why? You didn't tell me to eat!
Now it's time to just relax. Get over here. I'm gonna get my rock. I'm gonna make a couple
of spears and I'm gonna go on an expedition. Here's food over here. I'm just gonna hang...
Here's food over here. I'm just gonna hang... No, don't end the expedition.
Where's there a fucking... This is... Okay, there's already one made here. This is the plan.
Now I just need a rock and then the three of us are gonna go. Species is evolved. Yeah, we already
did evolve. This is 17 years have gone by. There's already been another generation.
You need to have babies. What is going on? Yeah, what? Evolution, guys. You don't... We grew, like,
extra hands and fingers from our grandparents. It takes, like, 10 years, right? All right,
give me my sticks. I'm gonna mate. We're gonna have some babies. We're gonna go out with our
three spears and I'm ready. God. I'll be right back. I... I'll be right back. I... Fuck it. I'll be back.
I... I didn't even care what happened to me. Do I still have the rock in my hand?
Don't cry. I'm gonna be fine.
Get kids and carry them around. Do you guys remember, like, a couple hours ago when I was
doing that and everybody told me not to do that anymore because I was endangering the children?
Turns out it was what I was supposed to be doing the whole time. All right, I've got... Give me the
third stick. Your ancestors were fucking stupid. Hey, well, guess what? They were your fucking
ancestors, too. You think that's gonna offend me? This is your great-great-great-great-great
grandparents, too. So, I have weapons. Three spears are made. Maybe I should do a fourth just
to make sure we're all ready. Do I... Is that it? One more? Sometimes it's hard to tell. Okay,
another one. One... One more? Okay. Three spears. There are one... Here comes the deep freeze. Here
comes the ice age. All right. One, two, three. There are four of us. Four spears. We're gonna have,
like, three kids make a fire. I have no idea how to do that. Every time I've tried to, it doesn't...
I bang two rocks together, scrape two rocks, grab a leaf, scrape a leaf, rub two sticks together
on top of leaves. I don't think I can do fire. Didn't somebody say I couldn't do that yet?
Okay, I got four spears. Let's put them down. I'm gonna... This is my community rock.
Just let it sit there. Who wants to come lie down with me? What have we got? I... Am I female?
I'm not sure. All right, come here. You. I think you and I should be hanging out,
maybe. All right, come to bed. We need two kids, and they have evolved. Four spears for the four of
us. We're gonna go out. We're gonna douche. We're gonna... We're gonna make it happen. I have to
watch this every time. It wouldn't be bad if it was not the same cutscene. Like, do like three
different potential cutscenes. Here we go. Doing it again. Baby with the spontaneity's genetic
mutation. Here comes another one. We're gonna wear both the babies. Gonna go out, dig up some
mushrooms. Hopefully, down a taiga while we're at it. You know what I mean? Down a taiga. Get a...
Eat, drink, be equipped. I wonder if he's gonna run into the camera. Cool. All right, two babies.
Let's go. Have we slept? Have we... We've slept, I think, right? All right, let's go, kids.
Everybody gather up. What are they doing? You slept for two years. Okay, everybody,
listen up. What I want you to do is I want you to grab a stick. Mannequins. All of you. Here,
this one's for you. All right, we are now armed. I want to pick up the kids. How do I pick up these
kids? No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Let's head to the stream. I would like everybody to eat something
before we move out. Follow my lead. Pick up a berry. Eat it. Watch me. You know what? No,
let's go fishing. Let's go fishing and just eat raw fish and shit. Whatever. With me, let's go.
Where's that fishing spot? I know there's one over here. All right, learn through me. Do as I do.
I mean, somebody's gonna make a reference here about something seeing and something doing,
but I'm not gonna make that. Just follow me and do what I do. And got one. Oh, this is a fish.
This is a bass. This will feed us for days. Okay, who's gonna eat this? Should you eat this?
All right, I'm gonna show you how to eat this. See? I took a bite out of it. It's good, huh? Hey,
kid, try this. Don't try this, actually. You probably shouldn't try this. Okay, now you try.
See? It's pretty good. Try it. Don't eat it all. Don't eat the whole thing. Greedy.
Very greedy. You shouldn't be doing that. See? You pissed up Dave behind you. Take your stick back.
Let's do it again. Look at me. Follow me. These kids are gonna learn this too. This is an invaluable
skill. Here we go. Ready? Is it gone? Fucking Chad walk. Oh, hey, we should have given you that
fish. All right, stay there. That's what I was talking about. This is why you don't eat the whole
thing. What happened? Where did my stick go? Oh, give me a fucking break. Isn't this a fishing spot?
No, you can have this back.
So, why can't I not? Somebody, we gotta help this guy. This haha, I keep losing stuff. It's
not funny anymore. Here, take a crab. Haha, I keep losing stuff. Here. Actually, no, no, no.
Take this. Eat. Delicious, huh? How do you feel? You feel better? Good. Pop. All right, let's go.
Everybody. Pa, you don't have a weapon, but that's all right. Look at. Are you gonna fish?
You're gonna fish? She's gonna do it. All right, let's keep moving. We are going to examine
that. Get it into your memory and then forget it.
No crocodiles. Let's go. This game is really cool. Haters be gone. I think this game is really cool.
I think this is a really, really awesome game underneath a layer of unintuitive control.
Like this is, this is, we talk about fossils. This is a fossil that's underneath
a layer of fucking sand. There's gold under there, but you've got to dig down like 25 feet to get it.
And right here, there it is. I found the giant waterfall. I'm gonna get a cut scene, right?
But this is like, oh, this is an Irish spring. It must be an Irish spring.
I just turn the fucking stream off and I never stream again. I make one tweet a year that says
it's an Irish spring. You never see me again. Something going on here. Something going on here.
All right. Did he pick somebody up? What happened? We good? Why are you all hiding?
We're supposed to work together as a team. God damn it. Fucking useless. Useless. Useless.
Useless. What? Something in the water. Don't go in the water. Stay out of the water. Everyone
out of the water. Don't go in the water. What is in the water? Hiding spot. All right. We got to
make it. This is the new shelter. We're making camp here and then we're going to evolve. I'm
pressing the button. No, don't make noise. Where is it? What is it? What is it? What's the noise
here? What are we supposed to be looking for? I don't know what's wrong. I'm starting to get
a little scared here. How do I fix a broken leg? I gotta sleep. All right. Fuck it. Make camp.
I need some sticks. I need some twigs. I need some yarn. Where's our newest recruit? He needs to
get away. Take my stick. Take this. No. Take it. Take this. What are you holding? You have a stick.
Who doesn't have a stick? You. Come here. You're gonna fucking hurt too. All right. It's time to
set up shop. Okay. Where is this thing? It's spawned. Get in the water. Everybody get in the
water. We all lions hate water. Use your sticks. Do something. Somebody do something. He's spawned
in. Somebody scare him. He won't come in the water. What was that? Why do we all get sucked down?
Okay. We got like pulled in like the undertow. What is in here? It is the undertow, isn't it?
What is this? I don't understand what the problem is. All right. Get me the fuck over here. I need
food. He's still here somewhere. Is there a cave behind the waterfall? Follow me. Pick up the orb.
Quick. Quick. Quick. Quick. Quick. Quick. Quick. Quick. Pick it up. What the fuck are you doing?
Pick up the orb. Why can't I get the orb? You've got to be fucking kidding me.
Please. It's in the background. So was I being lied to about the orb?
Why is it in my face? It's like eclipsing me. Okay. You explain to me what happened here.
Eat this. Eat this. Eat it. What is this? Eat it. I can't eat it. Where are my friends?
Where's food? I need food right now. Like I need to eat something right now.
Fucking tiger spawned in next to the lake. I can't eat this. All right. What is that? Food.
I'm fucking believing. Okay. I need to change. I need to switch to you or something.
My bone is healed, but I'm still I need to go. I need the that thing up there. I can't believe
that I got like a server admin spawned a fucking tiger in on the lake. I need to like find
one of those things, but I can't carry anything. So you get a tiger spawned up your ass and then
the tiger kills everybody. And then you have to run around like an asshole trying to find like
the fruit hanging from the tree to peel your broken bones and shit. I'm going out. I'm going out. I'm
going out. I'm going out. I'm going out. Okay. I'm alive. What are you doing? Give it to me.
We even brought stuff with us. This game. Seriously. Is anybody else hurt? We need to go to
bed now. I would love to put a shut up shop next to the waterfall. Come here. Who else is injured?
I can't really tell from here. Can everybody get up here? Is it just the two of us? I'm just
going to bring two of them with me because there's one more here, right? Where did I get them both?
I literally as if there's a tiger here, I'm going to uninstall the game. Go get the orb. I'm not
going to get the fucking orb. There is a tiger here like hiding in that bush. Is it in the rock?
That's how you regain your sanity. Well, I chased one around for 30 seconds and it just
glitched into my screen. If you don't get the orb, you go insane. Well, why did it not work last time?
Reach conquer zone. Didn't I already do this though? What the fuck are you? What the fuck are you
talking about? Like it's like inside. Where is this? Every fucking time. Every time. Every single
fucking time. Come on. Who's hurt? And then I'm going to, we're going to have to put a,
we're going to make a little camp back here. So if you go outside of the waterfall, all of a sudden,
you've lost your mind again. No, don't go out of there. It's, it's not safe out there.
What the fuck is this talking about? I don't understand this. I have to conquer my fear
of, of over there now. The water is scary. How far away is this? I don't. Okay. Is this it?
I got it. Conquer your fear. Conquer your fear. Please eat something. Who's hurt?
Anybody with blood on them? How are you doing? You all right? I think you got blood on you.
Come here. We need to eat. This is the worst game I've ever played in my whole life.
This is the worst game ever. This game, this, this is probably, this is like up there,
like top five worst games I've ever played. He wasn't even here. He's not even here.
He just spawned. This is like the fucking slender man. How do I attack? I swear to God.
It's not fair. I was just, he's, somebody has fucking cheats.
I've conquered my fear of water. Let's drink some.
Is he drinking too fast? Okay. Where are the babies? Thank God. The babies are safe
or at least one of them is. Okay. Let me, I need to, I need to sleep. I need to, I need to. Hey,
look, now guess what I have to fucking do. I think the tiger's here again. Did you hear that shit?
I have, I have to go get one of those sky fruits because I'm bleeding now.
And when I go to get a sky fruit, I'm going to get attacked again. And then it's going to eat
three people. And then I'm going to have to get another sky fruit and then just leave the area.
That's what I tried to do. And then tiger spawn. I was very clearly, I looked at every direction
and the tiger wasn't there. And then all of a sudden, I, sorry, I picked up the fourth notebook
page. So he comes faster and there's no, none of those things around. I might as well just die.
Just somebody, all right, I'm going to turn around and just hit me in the back of the fucking head
as hard as you can with that thing. And then eat me. Some, just eat me. All of you. Sometimes
you have to make sacrifices. Give this to me. Let's make a camp. Who cares where it is? No,
get out of the fucking way. Oh, Jeff, those gators. All right, can I stomp on this yet? Hey,
oh, I wonder what it is. Is it a tiger? Hey, was I just looking in that direction and there was no
fucking tiger. Does anybody have a spear? Give me that thing. Give me that spear.
Give me that fucking thing right now. Come here. Give me the spear. No, stop running. Give me the
spear. You give me that spear. I need that. Give it to me quickly. Oh, he's dead. So I'm going to
get the spear anyways. Spear. Okay, here we go. How do you counter attack? What happened to my
hands anymore? Where the fuck is it? It's on my hands. I just picked it up. Was he smashing?
He was just hitting something on the ground. I don't know what he was hitting. He was smashing
somethings at it. Was he killing another monkey? I don't know. Oh, hey guys. I was
fancy seeing you all here. He made it back. Hold A. Okay, I held A but the problem was I
dropped the spear. Hold A. That's what I did. No, you pressed A. They've made it X or like
right trigger or any other button besides A. They couldn't have done it like B.
Everybody's bleeding. So let's go across the map to find another one of those healing scrubs
and the cycle repeats itself. Do I have any spears or anything? Reaction time for attacks
will be increased. Oh, sure. Hold A to prime dodging or attack. Move left stick to choose
direction. Release A at the right time to dodge or attack. Okay, so dodge towards them to attack
but that's been dodging. I've been dodging like towards these motherfuckers. I just got
$50 from Phylacter Lich. Thank you. I'm glad you have a Wendy's nearby or you'd be fucking dead.
No, give me a break though. Could be like hold A and then tap forward and let go of A.
Why can't I just have like an animation where I fucking bash the motherfucker with like X?
What is this like QTE thing? Thank you for the $50. Is there a sound cue? I don't know.
But I can take care of my own food. Trust me on that. I know how to cook two things. I know how
to make a hamburger all the way to well done because I'm too scared to take it off any other
point because I think I'll get sick and I know how to make a delicious salmon in the oven.
You just put a piece of salmon in the oven with some with some fucking spices and seasoning and
some some you put the water sauce and shit all over it and you put it in the oven for like 10-12
minutes you know you can't fuck it up you just take it out and eat it. I also know how to make
spaghetti al dente. It's four minutes although I do have to be careful because one time I did make
my famous crunchy al dente spaghetti for a family get-together and four people chipped their teeth.
And I'm still dealing with that family lawsuit to this day so I gotta be careful. I gotta be
more aware. Anyways thanks for the 50 bucks and thank you Great Canadian FK Club for the 10 subs.
Appreciate it. Hold A to prime to dodge or attack. Move left stick to choose a direction. Let go at
A at the right time to dodge or counter attack. I am just gonna go kill something. I'm ready.
Next step and more just yeah. This is what happened. This is what happened to me.
Everybody thought I was lying. Everybody thought I was a liar. I dodged and I dropped my fucking axe.
Once connected the chance of dropping an item when a dodge happens it will decrease. I dodged and it
dropped the fucking axe on the ground. Like what was I supposed to do? I don't have enough power
yet. All right I want that. I want that to follow in future generations. There's an audio cue for
counter-attacking. You have to do it towards the enemy. What's with the fucking audio cues?
Phylactery Lich gave another 50 dollars. What am I doing? Everybody go home. I have four holes in
my body. They didn't make it. They didn't make it. I sent them all home. They fucking died in front
of me. I think they're standing on top of me. All right it's just you and me and you. I need a
spear or something. Give me that. I need to heal. Is this thing sharpened? It is not. Thank God
there's somebody still alive. All right give me the rock. Here we go. I'm not I am not fucking
around now. I'm gonna do this restart. What do you mean restart?
We're going and we're killing us. A lion and the expedition. I just did. I just didn't. They all
died. I already did the expedition. Yeah there are too many bodies lying around in bones.
Okay now I have to go get one of those things. Let's go. Hurry up. Eat the other bodies. I can't
do that. Why do these things have to be so far away from where I am? Evolve. Evolve. All right
I'm evolving. Fuck it. I got two kids here. Evolve. I'm done. Keep that acute response and I think
that's all I can do right now. Evolve. Change generation. Let's go. I got nothing else I can
put it in. Let's go. Yeah go. I got two kids but file actor thank you for the hundred bucks.
Thank you for real. That's a shitload of money and a great Canadian FK club. Thanks both of you.
Another 15 years. Okay we're in year 35. How are we doing? Okay we're good. We need to have some
more kids. Everybody with bones? No. Okay give me my I need a spear. I'm gonna go try to kill
something. This is gonna take a while. I hope I'm not the only one alive. No there are at least a
couple other here. All right here we go. I'm going to get one of these. There's one. Just I'm gonna
just have them at the base. I'm gonna go pick them up. Just go get them. Nobody follow me. I'm just
gonna do it by myself. How come you're not taking the spear that you made 15 years ago?
It's dull. All right where am I going to keep going up? Where the hell were those?
There's eggs up there. Maybe we should get those too. No it's just a branch.
What about this? Is this like a new species of plant or something? Bird? Can I like identify
the bird? Let's go up here. These have to be so high up. You can't just put these like I'm like
around. I hate me. Consume the bird? I don't think I can do that.
You just like sometimes you just have to like take a leap of faith to and I'm gonna die. I'm
gonna fall off and die probably. I just was trying to get this shit and sometimes it's hard to tell
what's even grabbable and what's not grabbable. Like I can't grab those. I can't I can only grab
the vines. I can grab the trunks. I can grab the branches.
I don't even like fucking remember where like just I'm gonna just go all the way to the top
of the damn tree. This is an Assassin's Creed. It was made by the same guy that made Assassin's
Creed. It may as well be. Give me that. How can I stand? Do I have to sleep to cure a broken bone?
Fuck you bird. I almost got him.
Give me the other one. I have two of these things now. That's all I wanted.
The red or green plant will heal bones.
Where can I find one of those? I guess I'm just gonna have to. I want just to bring these back to
have at the camp. I'm sorry guys. I'm sorry. There's one over there. This game we go with
multiplayer. I've been playing for about five hours. I still don't understand what the fuck the
point of the game is. What am I supposed to what do you mean that you just you just exist?
Just live? To evolve? Into what? Become a caveman? Is that even in the game?
No. What do you mean no? Are you just a monkey the whole time?
Yes. No. No. Yeah. No. We're getting some 50-50 responses here.
All right. Here's the red thing that I wanted.
Is this working? What's wrong with me?
My phone is re-broken. I'm just trying to fix myself and and I'm poisoned from the berries.
What happened? To evolve? I don't have any children guys. Who even is this and where are they?
That was kind of sad. Yeah it was. Restart the game with your knowledge of how to play.
Should I just do that? But I'm not sure I have that much knowledge on how to play the game.
I didn't understand. I don't think I have the knowledge you're you're referring to.
Read the no I I know like the basic understanding but should I just restart?
Read the help section? No I I know all we mean we did this already.
Yeah like I understand this stuff. Yeah yeah yeah yeah. Okay when you access the
Neural Engineering development you use the Neural Engineering by surviving to grow the neurons.
Okay it will increase your capacities. When you access your neural network ready for reinforcement
it means you can pass generations right? Okay but I already knew that. The problem has not been
about progressing in the game. The problem has been running into tigers that spawn on top of me.
The combat page? The combat page is two sentences. Hold A to prime dodging. Release A. What do you
mean? I just read them. I know I already knew that shit. What's that?
What's your enemy? A boar? I ain't giving up. Not yet. Nope. I ain't giving up. Who died over there?
Okay there's somebody died there. I can already read the patch notes for version 1.1.
Reduce the spawn rate of the tiger by like 30 fucking thousand percent.
This is the last one. This is the only monkey I have left.
Hold and release. I'm gonna ban the word. I'm gonna ban the word hold and release.
I didn't have a spirit in my hand and by the way even I'm banning the word. I'm banning hold and
release. Hold and release does not stop the fact that I'm surrounded by there are more tigers than
people. There's another monkey over there I think. Found him. Hey you. Follow me. You and me are
friends now. You understand? Let's go. People are donating to say that. Don't even do that. That's
that's a waste of money. Don't do that. Okay follow me. Uh there's two of us. Wait what are
you? Are you female? Male? Am I male? Are you female? What is it? Let me know. I'm doing this.
I'm starting over in mid-game. Come here. What are you? Male. What am I? Who am I? What am I?
Shit. No wait. That's good. Right? Yes. It's good. Come here. Yes. Come here.
Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here.
We can start over. We can do this. You and I. Come on. No. I'm trying to turn off the emote only mode.
How do I turn? I don't. I know how to turn it on. I don't turn it off. Got it. Okay. Now I need a bed.
Okay. We already got some stuff here. There's a stick. There's sticks here.
I see a couple of rocks. I just want to make a bed. Or no. Just follow me back. We're already
here. There's one, two, three, four dead up there. So many dead people up here. This doesn't feel
right. I don't think I can. I don't think we can like have kids up here. This doesn't feel right.
Okay. Evolve first. Didn't I already do that? Like I'm talking like an hour like 45 minutes ago now.
Didn't I do that already? Because I don't have any points. I can't reach here. No. I have nothing
else to do. I need to like survive out there with kids around me. But surviving out there
has deemed to be very, very, very difficult. Evolution leap. What? What is this? When evolving
through ages, all spontaneous mutation neurons are not carried by adults or elves but vanish.
But then matter may reappear in future babies. Do you still want to evolve?
Just what the fuck even is this? What? What? What? What? There was nothing told me about that.
Zero. Did not tell me to do this. 24,000 fucking years. 24,000 more years. Obsidian is a tool.
I used it twice. I intimidated a warthog. We gained 50,000 years. Is there a reason why the game
would not tell you that this existed? It's going too fast. Oh shit. I'm gonna be sick.
I would... I even looked at this screen and I thought these were just like achievements. Dude,
I don't... This is happening. There's too much happening on the screen right now. I don't know
what's going on. It's almost a million years. The game doesn't tell you mechanics so you learn?
I don't think this is a game mechanic. I think this is a menu option. Game mechanic would be
like finding herbs and spices and shit. I think this is a very important screen to know
what it does. This is five hours of stuff.
You've 102,000 evolved faster than science. I went 819,000 years. What? Hey, wait, that's not fair.
Evolving slow. Okay, more deaths than births. So that means you don't exist.
You have moved forward through time to nine to four million, whatever, years before now,
and will be brought back to the world to catch up with your lineage. That is an insanely important
fucking core game that not... Well, you didn't know it existed either. Neither did I. Why is
it year 36? Did anything change? Who am I? Anybody here? Is it just... Am I the only one that made it?
Where's my bed? Okay, who are you? Adult female. All right, I...
I'm going out on my own. New thing. I can't fucking believe I was there for five hours
and didn't know. I can't believe it. I am fucking... I'm shocked right now.
All right, get the honey. Get it. How do I get honey? Oh, okay. I got some more senses. Can you
grab it? I don't think you can grab honey. You need to do a couple more feats to evolve as a
species, okay? So let's just grab a few sticks and do the thing I did already. Strip the weeds.
I know how to... No, I don't know how to do that apparently. All right, what do I want to do?
I need to go over here, find one of these other things. Let's go this way. Okay, I'm going to
find the evolved tiger. Yeah, that shit was un-fucking-believable. Oh, you okay? I need to
help you. I got a headache. What can I do for a headache? Something for a headache? That's not
food. You're looking for war or something. I need to...
I can't. What do I do? Why is he still alive? Get off of him. Run away, you idiot. Stupid dumb
tiger. Is he all right? What the fuck am I supposed to do about that, guys? I'm just going to remember.
Can I not climb up any of this? All right, I did my... Did it work? It worked from this far away.
Okay, let me... Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Okay, this is fruits and shit. I need to heal.
I think I need a rock to break these open. I don't think I can just eat these. I'm pretty
sure I can't. Where did they even go? No, I can't. Okay, I'm going to bring these. We're
going to smash it with a rock. I'm going to give them to him because the tiger's gone. Where are
the other two that fell? Right here? These things. Okay, I got one, apparently. Where?
I'm bleeding out. I know, but I have to go get one of these fucking things.
It's a story of my life. No fall joke? No. You healed yourself from bleeding. That's a feat.
I need like a couple more feats. Can I break this open? Metabolism. What exactly am I doing
with this? Oh, this is the nut. It's a big nut. Let's break this open and eat it. It's a coconut.
Okay, can I do anything else with this? Can I? I think I do have to smash this with a rock,
I think. Yeah, okay, I can smash it with a rock. Is he still alive? Tiger's gone, right?
Give me a rock so I can break this open. Any rock will do. Any rock will do. I'll take any rock in
the whole world and on earth. Any rock will do. I wish I could pick you up. I need a rock
so I can give this to you. I wish I could put like something. I wish I had like a monkey inventory
because now I gotta find a rock. Give me, please. He's really hungry. Right here. No, those are
mushrooms. Just eat them. No, don't eat those. Oh, hold on. Berries. Are these poisonous? Hey,
I learned self-control. I would have loved to give you a berry, but that guy said I'm gonna
have to leave him. Just put everything down and fucking get out of here. I can't even get up the
fucking tree. Climb the tree. I'm learning dodge. Well, that's good. I'm just farming points.
Whatever, we got a stream drop? We're good. Guess what I need now? I need another one of those
things to rub on my fucking body. And he's just guarding this fucking tiger. This is always around
no matter what you do or where you go. There's always a tiger. There's always a fucking tiger.
And tigers come out like for five minutes a day, guys. They don't fucking do this.
And then they go to stay asleep. I have no like depth here. What am I looking at? What are you
looking at? What are you looking at? What are you looking at? What are you looking at? What are you
looking at? What? Oh, it's been a whole day. Okay. Is he still just down? Of course he's down there.
Just always expect that there's always a tiger everywhere no matter what. This whole game is
tigers. Ancestors. Monkeys ran away from tigers based on four bones we found. Okay, can I heal
this guy? That's not gonna hurt me, right? Thank God. Okay, come here, please. What the fuck was
that? What just happened? What happened? How did my character die? I wasn't bleeding. I just healed
myself. I just healed myself. I'm just trying. All right, no more rescuing other people.
The tiger shot me. God damn it. Well, I... Shit. Your circle was so minuscule that the act of walking
killed you. Oh, that sucks. Is this water? Let me just drink some of this fucking water.
You get zero xp unless you have a baby on your back. Am I scared of the water too? What is it?
What am I looking at here? Lily pads? Are you scared of lily pads? No, it's a fishing spot.
So what's the problem? Relax. All right, where... Let me go over here. I'm just gonna sleep.
Do I have a thing here? This is where he spawned. Is there a bed?
All right, am I gonna have to make one?
Stay in the trees? Well, I would love to stay in the trees, but half the stuff I have to do,
I have to be on the ground. Dig in this hole. Pick up this rock. Grab a stick off the plant.
Okay, I can dig. I can dig. I need a stick. I also need to go to sleep somewhere.
I don't even know where the hell that even is. I guess I have a camp somewhere.
I'm here. Might as well put it on the... Whatever. Just sleep on the floor? Let me go.
There's like other people. There's like apes over here. Where is this other person on the map?
Who the fuck is this? Where are you? Are you just lying? Oh, you're like camouflaged. It's a baby.
Come here. All right, baby. Time to learn. What do I want to do now? I'm teaching the baby about
the world. Okay, so this is... I don't know. I don't think I have anybody left. I need to find
somebody. So here's how the course of action is going to be. Find somebody that's in need of a
new clan. Start the process of getting to know them, and then we both die by a tiger in 10
seconds. So let's just continue the same cycle we've been doing for the last two and a half hours.
Sounds good to me. Let's get a rock and make this a spear, and then we have to go find something.
I need to sleep too. Get off the tree. Sharp. I need a rock. Teach the baby about taxes.
I think we're just going to sleep somewhere. Can I sleep in a tree? I didn't want to do that.
We can't just sleep all the way up there. Yeah, I know. I'm trying to find a place to sleep.
I have to sleep in the bird's nest. Now I gotta find sticks, make a bed, or go up and sleep. And
let me try to sleep in a tree. Can I like just find a spot where we can lie down? I don't think so.
I have to make a bed. Make the bed on the tree. That's gonna be pain in the ass because I have
to bring individual... two individual sticks up here. Like five of them, and then stomp on it.
But I'll try. Well, there's a rock. I need that.
While I do this, don't pass out. All right, I got a weapon. I need some sticks.
Rocks. No sticks. No, like, leaves. I need to eat something too. I got... let's go find it.
Go tiger hunting. It's revenge time. I'm not going to kill that tiger. There's not a chance
in hell. Okay, right here. Put down a branch. Give me another one. Is there any more? That's
the only thing that was here? Come on. Tiger joke waiting room. Yeah, don't worry. You'll see it
again. Give me fish. Switching hands every time. It's just... what the hell? Why would you? Why do
I have to switch fucking hands for everything? I can't do this with my other hand? If I could do
it with my right hand, why would I not be smart enough to know I could do the same thing with my
other hand? Because it's dumb. All right. Okay, where is my right-handed? Yeah, I mean, like,
ultra right-handed. I want this. Is this ready? Keep that in the pile. It's not ready. I need,
like, one more. I can get that. Sorry, sorry, sorry. Wrong hand. Baby's hungry. Doesn't the baby eat
when you eat? Oh, I got rock. Here we go. A, up, and then let go of A.
Wait a minute. This is the final baby. I need to live. Climb something. Climb a tree.
Where is he? Why is it still doing this? Why are you doing this? The tiger cannot climb trees.
Speaking of trees, I need food. I need to eat something. I still hear the tiger screaming.
Find a hiding spot. I mean, I think this looks like a hiding spot to me.
Fucking orb is up here. Okay, so try and tell me that the orb is in the fucking sky. No,
I'm not jumping. No, I gotta find the monkey. He's pretty good. He's pretty good. He's pretty
strong. I heard the tiger. Just like in Dark Souls. Dark Souls 1. The tree. What are you doing? Let
go. Turn this way. I'm not even holding on to anything. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got
it. Tiger's still waiting for me down here. I'm looking for, like, a hiding spot or something.
I'm good. Okay, get up. That tiger is doing great. Yes, he is. Dead. Fish. Rock. Can I pick stuff up
as a baby? Holy shit, I can. Why can I do this? I can't strip it, though. Where's the... I can't.
I need somebody to do this for me. I gotta make a bed? No, I can't be on the ground for more than
fucking 30 seconds, otherwise... The bed was over here. Can I sleep into an adult? Why did I go back
here? If I die, the game ends. Yeah, I think I'm all right with that. No, wrong item. I can't pick
up the fucking spear. I'm trying to pick the spear up. I got it. I got the spear. No, this... No.
Every button is fucking A. Pick up, jump, run, fall down. No way. I don't even know where it went.
I want to just grab the spear and see if I can stab him. This is like... No, this is like...
You can't fight a tiger as a baby. What with my options? Where does this start? I just seen that
on Planet Earth. Yeah, I've never seen a... Never mind. No, I'm just a fucking baby again.
This ain't happening. Come on, motherfucker. Let's go. What you got? This is my last stand. Okay,
so hold A, towards him, audio cue, let go of A. I probably should know what this does first.
As a baby. No, I know what this is. I saw dad do this. There he is. Damn it. First time?
Custom game? Region? The jungle? Settlement? Rockslide? Oasis? Clan size? Medium? Okay.
Delete tigers. What is easy mode? I don't even know what that means. Find yourself alone somewhere
in Africa 10 million years ago. Let's try this one. No, no, not this one. One guy told me to pick
this. This is hardcore. Okay. Well, no, I ain't fucking doing that. I just quit the whole game,
actually. For the best. We're going to play something else. Rage quit? No, my entire lineage
was killed. That's not a rage quit. That's like a, I was wiped out. Go play WoW Classic. Oh no,
no way. I'm going to play that right now. Let me go, let me go get a drink. Let me pee and we'll
do something else for a little while. I'll be back.