Hi. Hi. Hi. I got, I got, we get bunched up underwear.
Is it weird that I wanted to go get bicycle shorts for these VR streams? Just wear them?
Not, no, no, no, not just, but I'm talking underneath my pants. Is that not weird? Okay, good.
All right, for a second I thought this pair of underwear had pockets.
And I'm sitting here thinking, wait a minute, holy shit, what a brilliant idea.
Imagine underwear with pockets. It would be sick. You'd never have to wear a pair of pants in your
house ever again. You just put on underwear and have like, you know, there's the right pockets,
got your chapstick in it, your left, got your keys in your left pocket. I think there's something
there. Why would you want, why would you want, what? What about your hair? You just take your
pants off to access them. No, you don't. You just reach down in there and like go in your underwear
pocket and pull it out. It's like a secret chapstick. How's the hair? You'll see it in just
about two seconds. You tell me. Looks okay, right? It looks all right. Doesn't it? You know what I
did? I'll tell you. This camera's not in a good place. It's hard for me to show you. Uh, hey,
by the way, if you didn't know, Twitch partner, I have so many of these. There's no other time
to wear them. This t-shirt I think has been in a closet since the last time it was on there,
on video. I have, don't tell them what. It's that, no, it's not the same shirt because this
one says Gerber985 on it. It's number 17. You know, I picked 17 because that was the,
that was the age when I knew I wanted to be a Twitch streamer. Yeah, that's where it all,
that's where it all started. Except every person with this jersey has the number 17 on it. Every
single one of these made. They did, that was all too, that was way too much work. They're all 17.
Anyways, give me one second. I want to grab a water and we'll get started.
No, no, no. Why am I doing this? Back to the intro, back to the intro. Okay. I'm,
let me grab a water and we'll get started. Just what, it's VR, man. You know how fucking hard it
is to VR? Why did somebody just say cringe? Don't call me a cringe. I'll be right back. I was going
to get a water. You want me to die? See, we, we hadn't even started. Oh, I didn't, I forgot to
even tell you. No, it's not a late stream. We were supposed to start it too. I, this, I had,
the suss was wrong. So my hands look like a bony. How do I feel like I have like these big bony
hands? Anyways, so here's what I did to my hair for all you wondered. This is quarter cup of olive
oil. You know, okay. I, I have to go down here. I have no chair. Standing and leaning down like
that is killing me. It's a, it's a quarter cup of olive oil and like eight drops of tea tree oil.
And you just go like this with your finger and then you don't do that by the way. And then you
put it in your hair. You get it in there. You get it in the problem areas. And it, my hair feels so
good right now. I can't wait to do that later. Look at the link. Don't forget the link. Salad
dressing hair. This is what your diet does to you. Hold on. I'm going to put this on camera.
Uh, this is, this is per, hold on. Let me get it on here first. Uh, this is, this is not a person.
This is an ant. This is an ant sized ant. No, this is a human sized ant that has, they're,
they're hiding. What the fuck? I don't know. You know what I was trying to say.
It does, it kind of looks like that. All right. It's, it is a human sized ant that's hiding in
society. This, that's an ant belly shoplifting a beach ball. You know, I was going to get,
I was actually going to get for like today or tomorrow, one of those, uh, like,
like pregnancy bumps. You know how you can get those pregnancy bumps at like, like 12 weeks or
something, just so you could see what your clothes look like. I was going to get one of those and
just wear it and just not say anything about it. And people think I'm just getting, it's getting
worse. This really is porn week. No, I'm talking about like to make it look like my stomach is
bigger, not to pretend that I'm pregnant. Like, yeah. There he is. Why? I'm not pretending to be,
I'm pretending to be a fat guy because I'm getting fatter. And it's because I've been
eating a lot of food. I've been feeling all right. I gained like 20 pounds. It's the green screen
stream. MPEG. You got Olive Garden hair. That's good. Because when you're here, you're family.
You're my family. None of you are my family. Not one of you. Am I really getting upside down colon
faces? None of you are my family. I'm not related to anybody in this chat. Maybe my mother.
Isn't that what that means? I don't think I'm related to anybody here. That's what I like to
see in the mirror. But anyways, all right, let's go. We're going to play Half Life Alex. We're
going to continue. My hair is going to be bad. It's going to be awful, but it's okay. I've got
my tea tree olive oil treatment in the bathtub waiting for me in about five hours. It's right
here. Five hour stream. I don't know. You missed the link. No, I didn't. That is, that was the
link. All right. You got to get your links out of the way now because there ain't no chance in
hell I'm stopping to do this. What the fuck, dude? That's shaving cream. Okay. Weed, Tovleft, Coke,
Ecstasy, Shrooms, Alcohol, Meth, PCP, and Xanax. I don't know. All right. The weed one is kind of
funny. I don't understand the PCP one. Why am I so red? Why did you make me wicked red? Do you get
wicked red when you get on PCP? I don't know. I've never done it before. I don't do any of these
drugs, but hold on a second. Is that actually true? I don't do that though. I don't. All right. We're
going to move on. All right. Let's go. You drink so much. The last time I drank alcohol was like
six months ago. You drink so much. Oh, by the way, I put the new, uh, yes, Stalin, Stalin. Yes,
I am. I am Stalin. I put a new face mask on here. This is new. This is a new face mask. This is not
the old one. The other one was the wide peepo happy and this one is the narrow peepo happy.
This is for the narrow face. Hopefully this doesn't hurt. No more coal miner. I don't know.
This is new and I might get the, uh, I might get the coal ring. Enable peepo happy. You say it. I
just said it. Just because I say it doesn't mean I have to enable it. This is actually really
comfortable. All right. Let me, hold on. Give me a minute. Why wouldn't there be like a hair
place for your hair to go? You know what I mean? Why not just have like a big hole here that this
hair can slide through? I mean, I would look like fucking Abe from Abe's Odyssey, but do I care? My
hair won't get all damaged. Can you guys hear this? Now you can hear this. Just shave your head. I'm
not shaving my head. I like my hair. My hair's fine. You can't gauge how somebody's hair looks
after a VR helmet. That's not, that's not fair. Although sometimes I think about being bald and
I'm like, damn, like it must be so easy just to not have to worry about it. Do you even wash your
head? Okay. Bald guys in the chat. Do you use shampoo on your bald head or do you use body wash?
Which one? Do you use both? Oh, okay. Left ear. All right. I'm going in. I'm going in. Mr. Ant
stomach. All right. So I got a shotgun. I got a pistol. I got some resin. Oh yeah. I just got
the laser sight, didn't I? All right. Let's go. Half Life Alex part two. Getting really hyped up
for this one. All right. I'm in. I'm in and I'm immersed and I'm ready to experience the virtual
world. It's hard to say words when you have ears and blocking ears. It's hard for me to talk when
there's things in my ears because I can't hear myself talk. So therefore I can't really talk that
well. You guys get that, right? It's hard for me to talk unless I can hear myself and I can't hear
myself really at all. So that's why I'm talking louder. Yeah. It's hard for me to talk when I have
ears. All right. Let's go. It's going to be scary. It's going to be fun. Oh, remember the piano. I
forget. How do you move? Oh yeah. That's right. Oh shit. I forgot about this. I forgot this game
is good. Oh, I forgot. I forgot we're playing a good game. I see it already. Okay. I have a,
I have a, I've got a little homework for you guys. Go find a channel, a stream. Doesn't matter if
it's a YouTuber, a streamer, a Twitter guy. Find somebody that's played through this game and didn't
come up here and do this. You find me a channel that ignored the piano. I don't think it's possible.
All right. Let's go. Oh wait. You found somebody that actually ignored the piano.
I'm getting resistance back here. What, what's going on? What's going on here? What is this?
I'm putting on like another person's skeleton every time I get into VR. All right. Let's go.
I still got it. I still got it. I still got it. Let's try the other hand. All right. Let's go.
Oh shit. How do I, how do I do the thing? I've been awake. Please only. Yeah. Breaker boxes.
Let's go back to the elevator plan. Breaker boxes. Bingo. Oh, they move now. That's annoying.
He's on goal. The CBD is kicking it. I would never be high in this thing. Are you fucking
kidding me? You got to be shitting me, dude. I on VR. No, there's no way. Well, I have, this is,
I have a grenade. What do I do with this grenade? I do with it. It didn't reset.
It really wants me to take this. What does it want me to do with it? Reset in there.
What was that? Game's a little quiet. Hold on. Fix that. Where are you?
There's a game a little bit quiet. I'll take care of it. Got you. Where's the mouse? Come on.
Come on. Where's the mouse? Got you. Okay. What happened to my grenade? All right. I need that
thing. The power supply. A lot of resonant here. Jesus. Power supply. I got it. Why is this? This
is the most lazy here. They just put like 10 residents in this room. You don't have to look
for it. Cool. Thank you. Okay. It's something I wanted to play with this. I knew you could play
with this. This is a better bartender simulator than the bartender game we were playing last night.
Never mind. Really? Oh. Take it. Come on here. Do it. Here we go. Elevator main power is not...
Ooh. Now I can see. I can see what the hell we're doing. Take this room. Look at the actual bottles
of liquid. Come on. Not touch this. You wouldn't want to put your hand in here. Okay. To the
elevator. What's going on here? What's going on here? Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Going. Okay. Where? Where's that going? Hey. Nothing even in these boxes. What are they doing here?
I hear somebody moving behind me. Why? Ah. Ah, damn it. Is that... Hey, nice cable management,
dickhead. This is a big one. Dude, this is a fucking huge one. What the hell?
This hotel's engine. The wiring's going to be a real rat sniffed.
Oh. Let's check the elevator. Let's check the elevator. I forget how you activate a grenade.
I don't remember. I don't remember how to do that.
Look at the bottle. Look at the bottle. Top button. Okay. Oh, look at the bottles in a second.
All right. We don't need the lamp. Where the fuck is this? I'm not tall enough for this.
This is like trying to reach the top cupboard in your house. If you're under six feet tall,
you know what I'm talking about. Just all of your top cabinets have nothing in them.
They just don't have anything in them because why would you put it there? You need steps to
be able to get them. Anyone under six feet gets it. Just leave that thing on the ground.
Where is this going? Get over here. Right there. I can see it. I can't turn it. Why not?
Why is this right there? Move this painting. Oh. Okay. Actual like hidden electricity safe. Okay.
I wasn't... Power back on. It looks like we're taking the ladder. Bottles. Bottles. Somebody
said look at the... Don't let me forget that. What do the bottles say? Three eighths. NBB.
Why do I have to read these? Is that the wrong language selected?
Liquid physics. I feel like I'm going to hit something. All right. So why do you want me
to read that? I don't understand. They're all in like Russian. I can't read these.
I don't get it. Is there a joke I'm missing or something? What am I hitting?
Don't read them. Liquid physics and refractions. Oh. Okay. Okay. What is this? 2008?
Why do I care about liquid moving liquid like water in a water level and like the light
bouncing off the door? Enter your... What the fuck happened? Did it... Why is everything crashing?
Stream VR desktop game theater? What is this? What? Did that save it?
Got VAC banned. I did not get VAC banned. I think my SteamVR just crashed. Fucking motorcycle game.
That motorcycle game has cursed. It's not even the... All right. It's not even the motorcycle
game. I gave that game a lot of shit for no reason. Okay. But you guys can't even see anything.
Let's just go back in and see what happens. Is my Steam even... I don't even have Steam anymore.
God damn it. All right. Hold on. I might actually have to restart my computer.
It's supposed to be a triple A, triple H Steam game. No. Not again. We were just playing, man.
Hold on. Let me see if I have to do this or not. Okay. Open it up.
Half-life Alex. All right. Please tell me I don't have to redo this.
What the fuck is this doing? Why is it opening up a game theater for this toolkit now?
It's just showing like everything on my desktop. This is fucking bizarre.
All this shit is so fucked up. All right. Let me open this. Did that take it over or is that good?
Stupid motor... Say you like the liquid physics. I mean, they're cool. What do you want me to say?
Dude, I have no picture at all. There we go. Hold on. All right. They're cool. Fine. Is that what
you want? All right. I got the game back, but what the fuck happened to my like actual my toolkit,
my OVR toolkit? It just exploded and I can't even open it anymore. I need a break. Hold on. Sorry.
This is like just a bizarre issue that I've never seen before. We're getting just bizarre problems
that just didn't... For no reason, they happened two days in a row. Okay. So anytime I open up
OVR toolkit, it takes over everything, deletes the game I'm playing, and goes into like this
desktop game theater. This is something that's... I have no... I'm gonna have to play the game without
chat. This is fucking nuts. Like why is SteamVR desktop game theater opening when I put on like
the chat window thing? Try killing the task for it. The fucking stream is going to turn off,
guarantee it. No, there's nothing there. Hold on. God damn it. Why? It's two days in a row.
Why can't this shit just work? Sit down at your pilot station and get rid of this
play VR with chat. I'm gonna restart SteamVR. I got a fresh install of windows.
It's been cleaned and wiped. Let's try this. Get a better computer. Yeah, I would,
but there's no computer parts exist. I'm gonna get a brand new computer. There are no 3080s,
no 3090s, no 3070s, no new CPUs. Everything's gone. There's no RAM.
Yeah, I could get like reliably a fucking case and just put paper in it and pretend there's a
computer in there. Get a 2080. No, that's old technology. Okay, let me try this again. If not,
I'm just gonna have to play without chat. That sucks, but whatever. Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on. Oh baby, I think we're good to go. Finally,
computers. Please tell me this is fine after I just rebooted Steam like three times.
It's so stupid. I didn't do anything. I just, yeah, sorry, guys. I have a 1080.
Roast me. Wait, you have a 1080? You're not allowed to play video games. Go buy another
$4,000 computer. Don't you want to play VR, dickhead? I don't even have hands. Okay,
crisis averted. Let's hope it doesn't do that shit again.
Let's go. Imagine 1080. Okay, nobody move. Nobody breathe. Resident on shelf. Oh,
right. That's right. All right. God damn it, man. That was a nose scratch. That wasn't inside. You
didn't get you. It looked like I went in my nose, but I didn't. There you are. Okay, let's continue.
So I'm choking. I'm dying. I'm dying. Breathe. You can breathe. Breathe, breathe, breathe, breathe,
breathe. You guys can breathe. All right. So, all right. Ow. I don't even know what I did to
trigger that happening. That's weird. All right. Resin on shelf. You mentioned it. Resin on shelf.
5K people watching. It may solve technical problems. Welcome to 90% of all VR. Ignored?
Ignored? What do you mean? Who did I ignore? Oh, right, right, right. Reddit on shelf or
something. Whatever it was. Where is it? Where is it? Where's the resin? Where is it? You said
it was on the shelf. Where is it? There it is. Thank you. Did I get it? I don't know if I even
got it. 19 resin. I got it. Okay. Let's move. Pat. Yup. I'm to climb. Oh, I climb with one hand.
I'm fucking Spider-Man now. Oh, shit. What happened? Okay. What? There you go. Oh, shit.
It's one of those things. Okay. Can I get through there? Wait, should I let him suck me up and then
I jump off? Suck me up. Up. Did I say up or did I say off? Which one? It's hard to hear.
Which one did I say? I said up, right? Okay. I can't even hear myself talk. This place is
overgrown. How dangerous do we think this stuff really is? Well, it is spores from another
dimension, so probably, yeah, extremely. But a rare opportunity to examine alien flora up close.
Okay, I got 20 resin. What should I do with it? A lot of resin in here. Is there any other guns
in the game? Canyon Cube. Bomb. Derma, derma, derma. Attach the grenades to your pocket.
I can't. See? I got full shit. Box. One shotgun shell in there. What a joke.
Okay, can I go through this door? Take a little bro. Just chuck it over your shoulder. Bro,
you have two pockets. Oh, what? No, no, no. What? Bro, bro, come on. Bro, bro, bro. I don't know
what you want me to do. What do you mean bro? Why is everybody saying bro? Hey, bro. Just chuck it
over your shoulder, somebody said. Okay, I'll try that. It didn't work. I'm not afraid to use this.
You better take it off the closer you get. Okay, they put creepers in the game.
They put Minecraft creepers in Half-Life. That's great. They're looking forward to that.
Gotta get the water from somewhere. Why is this glowing? Hey, hey, remember this? Classic Jim
Carey. What the fuck am I holding this? Oh, it's soap. Oh, secret, secret, a secret, a secret,
a secret, a secret, a secret, a secret. Just keep moving. Secret, it's a secret. Maybe breeze-less.
Oh, I didn't get it. Okay, so now, what the hell do I do now? Did I? I go down. Down? Wait,
something in here probably. Huge wardrobe for nothing. Hates us for punching. Fuck you. Bro,
look board in a row. Reddit spotted. Reddit spotted. Fuck you. What is happening? It's like,
I would imagine, oh yeah, Half-Life out. Let's talk about Half-Life. Alex, what does it feel like?
Kind of slimy, a little tingly. I feel like I don't want to do that. We're not even talking
about like, hey man, I'm speaking to you in Half-Life, Alex. No, you're talking about like,
dick and punch guy and larks. Should I drop? I'm gonna drop down. Okay, I made it.
I don't like that. It's like something's in my ear. This is a reeks. Oh, really? What does a reek
like? Be specific. Like a rotting animal mixed with ammonia. Oh, what cool vegetation. Penis dip.
Streamer has a small dick. The streamer has a small dick. Oh, Half-Life Alex, cool. Oh,
I wonder if the Vortigaunt is going to show up next. The streamer's penis is tiny.
Like, what are you guys even talking about? Oh, these things explode.
Come on, pop. Pop already. Pop. Oh, that's a big one.
Come on, pop. Pop. Oh, dude, that was the best fucking 90s commercial for any fruit snack
that you've ever eaten. What was over here? Going down? Oh, shit, let's keep going. All right,
hold on. Let me just, one, two, three, four. Oh, dick. You're still on that. You're still on that.
You're still on that, guys. You're still on it. Does that mean I have a tiny face? What's this
thing doing? What is that, and why is it doing that? Why is it doing that? What is that? I don't
know what that is, but I don't know why it's doing this. What is that? Should I take it? Oh,
sorry. I just want the thing that's in your hand. Give it to me. Got it. What? Press to arm
send grenade? What the fuck is happening? Give me it. Give it to me.
No, give it to me. Hey. Okay, we're good. Shit. What is that? Oh, man. A blast of berry flavor.
Y'all think you can handle it? I'll try doing two at the same time.
Oh, sick. Oh, this is like 700. Bye bye. Who else wants this shit? Oh, man. And introducing Green
Apple. Oh, that would hurt. That would hurt my teeth. Mom, I think I have to go to the hospital.
Oh, that's so good. It looks like he's just moving. I'm ready. Wait. Ah, okay. Let's make
sure we're loaded. Guys, load it up and ready to rock and roll. One of those doors that only
one side opens. Okay. Hey, no, I'm in the right spot. Kind of. Oh, it's rambling. Don't come
near me, man. How should you? Who's the sorry bastard that's going to take this one right
between the eyes? I need this. I don't have electricity. That thing doesn't have electricity
to it. What the fuck? Come on. No, I'm doing this wrong. I'll get it. I got to get a power
source. The laundry room. Where did that thing go? What's that thing vulnerable to? Fire.
Okay. It's vulnerable to earth. Like a leaf spell. Hey, no pictures,
no photos. You got to pay for that. Oh, come on in. Yeah. Okay. 10 bucks.
Cool. Say Twitch. TV slash Jeremy. Thanks, man. Hey, teleport around. That's what's going on.
Wow. Stop doing that. Stop doing that. Hey, no pictures. This guy sucks. Am I going to have to
creep up on him? No. Get over here. All right. Go to the chamber. That looks good. I would eat
that. That looks like a cool, it looks like ice cream. That's like blueberry cream ice cream.
I would just like shawarma style, man. I would just carve some of this off. Just like into a cone.
Where is this weird little stingray guy? He's toying with me. You know ceiling? Back here.
Get over here. He's still alive. What? What's going on? What happened to him? Alex, Alex, what
happened? There was like a dog looking lightning thing. Oh, sorry. I missed that. Oh, that was the
boss. Killed it and it crapped out this thing. Put it on top of an ice cream cup. It's blue cream,
Alex. Ah, how's it go? Ah, is it hurting me? Put it in a health thing. Oh, shit. That could be used
in place of a, you know. All right. I don't want to look at it. If I don't look at it,
it doesn't hurt as much. Done. Well done, Jeremy. Ow. He's a lollipop. Oh, thank you. Good. Health.
Shots. Shots. Oh, fair point. Have I ever rushed Jeremy? I'm jittery because of the game. He's
jittery because he went old turkey. Please don't wave. What? Why don't you get the shirt that says
Jerma? That was given to me from a gift. Gift. This is spectator capture right now. This is not
the, where are you? This is not mirror capture. This is actually like in game capture. And I have
the spectator view on smoothing and everything. Am I just like a jittery fucking mess? Is that what
the problem is? Wait, we can't hear you. Why not? Is it bad? Should I turn the volume down?
And when I turn away from the microphone, yeah, that's definitely going to happen.
Four shots left. I'm out of shells. I was at 10 minutes left in the game. It's like the end,
right? Oh shit. It's one of these, okay. Red. Red. Blue. Blue. I got it already. Why is there a shield?
Fuck. Oh no. I didn't notice. I don't remember where they were.
Red. Where's red? That's an orange. This is red. This is red. Red. Red.
That was weird. I don't know. That was weird. I don't know why I just did it.
All right. And now that's yellow. This is green. No, that's orange. Orange is
up here. Fuck. Okay. Okay. This green is right there. Okay. Orange is over here.
Purple. Yellow. Shit. It's going to restart. Okay. Now I get it. I get it. I get it. It's color
blind. I'm not color blind. I didn't understand the middle portion. All right. Yellow. Yellow.
Bang. Bang. We got red. Red. Red. Red. Orange. Orange. Red. Green. Green. Green. Green. Green.
Yellow. Yellow. Go. Go. Go. Go. One. Two. Did they make it easier for me? All right. Okay.
A shit talker. There it is. That elevator will take me up to the sub station.
Boom. Did I do it? Wait. Did I actually just do it? What the fuck? There's a person over here.
There's a guy there. Oh, no, no, no, no, no. I think so. Punk. Let's give it to me. Give it to me.
Give me another one. All right. There's explosive in there. Give me another one. Just give it to me.
Give me that. You know. I got something in my pocket. Shit. Sorry, dude.
Wait, wait, wait. I got to do a video game. I got to do every single video game ever developed.
All right. I forgot. Oh, yeah. Fun. Cool. Let's, let's use that mechanic a thousand times.
They've been here, right? What was the point of doing it? What was that? Why did I? What was that door?
Something in here? Reddit shelf. Germa resin. Reddit. Reddit shelf. Reddit shelf.
And explode. Why? Hey, what's what do you want? What's what do you want to do?
Resin on the shelf somewhere. Do you see resin? Oh, there is. Oh, I mean, is that a shelf or
is that a duct? That's not a shelf. That's a duct. Grab. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, we're supposed to go down here anyways. Who cares? I have no shock enamel.
Waste, waste, waste. I got plenty. I don't care. Nice little puppet show going on over there.
Let's see. Hey, guys. Hey, fellas. Hey, it's an eagle. All right. Now go to fucking bed.
What's going on down here though? Health station, station. There's a station of health station.
Station, station. Hey, come on out. Well, this is the part of the movie. This is the part of the
movie where the main character is in here right now. And they just know that I'm right underneath
and they go any second. I could just shoot where the you are. Couldn't I? Oh, thank God. He missed
us. Did I use this? What health down here? Why are there pockets? I don't have a pocket.
There's something in there. It's hard. Again. All right. Again. Swipe the David Buster's card
again. For God sakes. I'll get it. I'm getting those 500 tickets. And I didn't panic. You panicked.
All right. I need a power source. There's a shit load of health down here. Why is there so much
health down here? Secret. I'm going to put all the health in one spot. All the health is going
over here on this barrel. This is my healing station. It's my like healing shell. Wait,
can I put it in a box and just take it with me? Yeah, I can. Get your ass. That's what I'm
fucking doing. We're going trick or treating guys. This is my fucking health bucket. It's coming with
us everywhere. And this is the fourth one somewhere. I saw it. Fourth healing thing over here.
I know I saw it. Oh, trick or treating. Oh, nice. What'd you get? Oh, whoa. Dude. The Albertson house
is giving full size Snickers. Oh, you get three each? That's right, kids. Those are full size
candy bars. I'm an asshole. Remember, remember, rob this house. Here you go. Catch that. Line up.
Here's a full size three seats for everybody. I'm the house to rob. Thank you, kids. Have a
great day. What happened to them? Raid song? We got a raid. Who raided? Raid? Who raided? Raid song.
Raid song. Raid song. Who, but who is the, I can't sing the song because I know who raided.
Astergear. Astergear, thanks for the raid.
That was kind of, I don't know, a thank you. Why I did that? I don't know what that doesn't,
that doesn't mean anything, apparently. I don't know. I was so nervous that you raided me.
I go, well, that's when they all leave. It's, no, they're here. Okay, this is where we're going.
I keep losing my, gimme that. My trick or treat basket. I'm gonna fill this thing with trick
or treat items. It's a Halloween string now. Hey, oh, there's only two slots in your inventory.
No, there's 60. You just gotta fucking bring it with you. Oh, it's one of the electricity guys.
I hate you. Oh, crap. Lightning dog. Don't forget my trick or treat basket.
Hey, don't go near my trick or treats. Come here. Oh, he's in the vent somewhere.
Hmm. Okay, where's that fucking main character? He's in there going right now. He's like,
that went right by his ear and he went to the secondary main character that was right next to
him, behind him. If I'm in that movie, I'm just gonna fucking go like this.
All right, fuck it, he's gone. Actual villain. My trick or treat. Oh,
more fucking throw up jokes. If I do another throw up joke, I will end the stream, I promise.
That's like such low, that's so easy. Oh, shit. Awesome. Oh, dude, what do they got here?
Oh, man, I'm in take five? What's the last time you had a take five, dude? Cool. Okay,
those of you guys that are playing Diablo 3, this is just the bounty boxes. When this hits full,
I'm gonna just sit there and open bounty cubes for like 10 minutes. Okay, let's go. Am I supposed
to turn on something? Oh, no, that guy, I gotta kill that thing and get the electricity thing.
I'll just leave you a pillowcase full of Halloween candy down around.
Oh, that was close. Oh, dude, that went right by my face.
Where is it? Come on up. All right, come on up, you little bastard. Come on.
Get back here. Come here. Oh, do not. Do not.
Development? It went into a dead guy. No. Yes, I had to shoot both of them. It was
nuts, Russell. It sounds nice. Oh, it was. I think they're starting to fall out of the bottom.
How did it explode? Why would it explode? Okay, okay, you can't go in there. You can't go in there.
Oh, man, it's time. Oh, I'm so happy. It's so exciting. It's Halloween night. What'd you get,
dude? Oh, man. Oh, what's this? Oh, nice. Whoppers. Oh, what? Those are so good. I
haven't had those in so long. What's this one? Oh, it's a hundred grand. Thanks, Mr. Stevenson.
Oh, really? Looks like the Gregory household is giving out little shitty stuff here.
One little bullet, huh? I don't have any room for these. I don't have any room for these. What
am I supposed to do with these? Drop the grub. Did I? Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Okay, I'm ready. Oh, do not. Oh, man. Do not drink an orange juice right after you brush your teeth,
dude. What are you crazy? I was gonna say don't ever mix Reese's and fucking like a Hershey bars,
but that was going to be like, of course people do that all the time. I had to think of on the fly,
improvise. All right, where's the? Oh, right here. Hey, dude, have you tried the green slide flavor?
Oh, I can't carry it around anymore, guys.
Vent, you blind fuck. Vent, you're a blind fuck. Vent, vent, vent, vent. Go to the vent. You're
blind. There's a vent. What are you doing, dude? Go to the vent. You started right and pulled the
orange one. The one get in the vent or I'll have you bent. Holy shit. He's going to miss the vent.
What are you talking about? It's in the vent. This vent? Oh, no, on the floor. Floor? Vent, vent,
vent. Doesn't matter. ADHD vent. Where is it? And I think I know what you're talking about.
The one that I pulled off, but I didn't go in. I don't remember where it is. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I remember that. Thanks, folks. Pretty good. There's isn't another fucking strange scatter
gun in here. I'm going to be real fucking mad. I can't go in. Let's go. Hey, thanks for the tip,
guys. Last two shows. Hey, you know, I appreciate you. Move. Oh, I just need to power the elevator
here. I gotta close the bus door. All right. I got, I got help.
Just think about it, Alex. Three miles an hour. Plus, he's a fugitive. He's only got one leg.
There's obstacles. No direct path. You know what? I'm not going to lie to you. He should be back by
now. Yeah. So I should be working. Normally, yes, but you're the one headed towards the danger. So
we should be the ones worried about you. Oh, it's one of these hard ones. Hello. We're going to do
yellow right here. That is right here. I don't, I don't know what these are. Not a good yes. Open.
Oh, upgrade station. What should I do? Right. How much resin do I have?
Second. Oh, true. Quick. I'm going for the pistol. You pulled my scottish.
All right. What should I do? 33 resins. Bullet reservoir and additional bullets. That's a big
deal, man. That's a huge deal. I'm going with the bullet. I want more ammo. Yeah. Oh yeah.
That's what that's already. Wait, any more upgrade? That's it.
Oh, wow. Check it out. That looks really cool. You know, Russ, technically I don't think there's a
whole lot of your gun left anymore. Thanks for telling me how infinity war ends. Can I get a
grenade launcher? I'm going to scoff. Hello. Twitch TV admin. Yes. I'd like for you to ban
that fucking guy for at least two days. Thank you. Minus two, minus two, minus two, minus two, minus
two, minus two, minus two, minus two, minus two, minus two, minus two, minus two, minus two. Oh,
wow. Actually not bad. All right. I got pistols. This lamp is huge. This lamp is too big, right?
Hey, hey, look, it's me. There's the monitor. That's what I'm looking at. That's me after every VR
stream. Hey, guys, I just want to let you know that, yeah, I think it's been about four hours.
I can't do it anymore. I never like take a bath and do a hair treatment. Yeah, it's fun though.
Relax. Go lie down, Jeremy. That's not a good bed. This bed sucks. Holy shit. Dude,
are you living like this? Are you making like a bed out of wood? This is Minecraft?
That's the same way. See that? Oh, what's that? What happened? Why did the room just explode?
Oh, it's you. Oh, shit. Read the bottle. Read the bottle. Read the bottle. Read the bottle.
Hot car. Hold on. It's adjustment. I need a pants adjustment. We're on in a sec, guys.
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen. Just do a little pants adjustment. There we go. Hey, just make sure
the old pants adjustment happens. Every door opens this way. I hate that. I want doors to open in.
Oh, there he is. Irma? Irma, you all right? Yeah, I just, I was going to take a bath and put oil in
my hair. I just really crawled over here. Yeah, I'm going to be okay. There's oil, oil all over my
hair and shit. There's olive oil and tea tree. Yeah, I haven't really turned on the water yet,
though. All right, man. Just, just relax. Take a bath. Let that oil get a seep in over here,
over your hair. Boots and jeans. That's not my look. Need to reload twice. That was a lie?
Little lie? I think that was a lie. Oh, shit. All right, nice. Definitely putting on the new
face mask has helped a lot. Check the mag. What? Need to drop the mag. I'll test it out.
Wait, about a toy, about a guy. Okay. Well, mag has been ejected. Empty inserted magazine.
Press to eject magazine. Yes, what do you want me to do? Put a new one in. This is empty. Oh,
oh, shit. I thought it was empty. Oh, all right. So you have to drop two empty magazines out.
That's too much. That's stupid. Oh, yeah. Game of the year, right? Don't say anything bad about
game of the decade. Oh, boomer. Oh, I hate those things.
Boomer over there. Oh, that's pog room. I thought that was resin. Hey, all right. You want me to
want to give me a grenade? I guess I got take it. I guess I mean, I guess I'll take one.
I guess. Thank you. Thank you. I guess. Thank you. Oh, I guess. Oh, dude, it's fog flavored.
Oh, good flavor. What does that even mean? All right. Well, if they were Twitch TV. Hey,
if they were Twitch TV, popsicles and stuff, would you get like the germa pog flavor?
That's I, if I had a popsicle, if it was like a germa 985,
it would be sour. It would be a sour popsicle. Probably like a raspberry of raspberry sour flavor.
No, I'm fine. Give me that. I can't make this jump. What happened? Why? I just died instantly.
Is this the one? 336. I just took a step off. Got eaten by the stairs. It wouldn't give a star
flavor like that to you. I'm not. You don't think I'm a star? I don't want to. How many stars do I
have? I'm not a Twitch star enough to get a raspberry. So what flavor would I get? Wait,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'm sorry. No, you are not going to designate the banana flavored popsicle
to me. No, I'm blue raspberry or green apple or grape. You're not going to designate like gross
banana flavored popsicle to me. No, I'm not going to be that. How dare you? Did it even kill?
Now I got to shoot him. I did it. Follow me. Follow me in this room. Follow me in this room.
Follow me in this room. Look, I'm in this room. Just kill me. Kill me so I can do it again.
Kill me so I can do it again. Just kill me so I can do it again. How do I die?
Just kill me. I want to do it again. Don't. I'm trying to just die. I can't die.
I want to do it again. Kill me. How do I? Do I have any grenades? Wait, there's a grenade in there.
Give me this thing. Just let me. Are you aware? Was that a monitor? I think that might have
been a monitor. I think that was my monitor. Goodbye. Goodbye. Where's that microphone?
I'm sorry, guys. I smashed into this. I just crushed it. You were dropping.
Better not me. Oh, shit, dude. That guy had to restock viewers. Fucking plummeting. I'm going
to go watch a real stream. A guy that deserves like a blue raspberry flavor. That's me. Better
not get banana. Okay, here we go. Banana streamer. Reload again. Oh, my God. Reload again. Oh,
my God. Reload again. Oh, my God. Reload again. Oh, my God. Am I not doing this right?
Hey, what are you two talking about? Hey, dude. V.O. That is instant death. We made it. Viewers,
minding.
Broken window. Okay, let's see what happened here.
Past tray. Still hot. Smell. Oh, just the bed was a little disheveled. Down in a hurry, it seems.
Two beds. Effort beds. It looks like the escape route. What do we have here? What do we have here?
Throw some water in there. Thirsty. What a mess.
I wonder, uh, maybe, uh, I wonder what happened. No, don't do that.
I'm sorry. I was going to start going into like Rorschach.
And the thing is, I wonder what happened in here. It's really possible that, you know,
somebody would have carried in here.
All those people. All those idiots. Those that look like they've been recently used.
A smell of shit. Just like the outside world. Just how I feel about the outside world.
False shit. That detected. Marge Simpson. It's pretty much Rorschach.
Just do, okay, go into your favorite pitch shifting software.
Take Marge Simpson and drop the pitch by about 10%. You got Rorschach.
Oh, I have to actually go out the window. As I got outside, I felt the urge to do a fall joke.
I didn't do it. Society. I actually fell off.
I'm not trapped in here with you. I'm not trapped in here with you.
Yeah. I mean, that's true. I am trapped in VR, but it being like, I'm not trapped in here with you.
You're trapped in here with me. That's you guys.
Next window. I've got a delivery of milk.
Okay. Hey. Special delivery, dickhead. Ah, that was fun.
Why am I opening that? Why was he using the bathroom?
German. German. He finally got in. He got in the bathtub.
Can I tell you about my big long bony fingers too? Wait, he was just in here.
What is this thing doing in here? Wait, this is the thing that flushed the toilet.
Fuck on there. All right. Whatever. German after VR. Oh, that's so stupid. It's so true though.
I think I did that exact pose and made that exact face last night in the bathtub. All right. Come
on. Come on. We're going to home alone this guy. Come on. You're never going to be able to catch
me. I'm getting your stupid little bread. Hey, come on barf. Be careful.
Come on, you big stupid idiots. Oh, he got him. Oh shit. It ripped his head off. Oh man. He's dead.
It just tore his fucking head off. Turn, turn, turn. Turn, turn, turn.
Okay, that's dead. That instantly killed me. That probably weighs like 30 pounds. That would have
just caved in my fucking face. You've never seen Home Alone. Home Alone 1 and Home Alone 2 are some
of the best movies ever. This is such a good movie. Open up. Hey, I'll give him a courtesy knock.
Okay. Anybody in there? You're about to be dead. Wrong building. Sorry.
P.T. hallway. 424. Devil's number. 5. Devil's number. I was going to crush him with the TV.
I tried. I was trying to crush him with the TV. Didn't work out so well though. Oh well.
I just announced my presence. I just called this alien. TV redemption. Something under there,
isn't there? Is that resin? All right, let's deliver this TV into an alien's skull. Oh shit.
Fuck, I wanted to turn it. Any more TVs? Are there any more TVs? Whoa, it's big.
You burst already? Oh, wait. Fuck. A one. Elevator. Hey, I just want to say, those of you that are in
broadcasting school, some of you might be into audio. It's a fun one to say. That's also a good
one to say. Elevator. The elevator. Elevator. Elevator. Elevator. Elevator. Elevator. Elevator.
That's a good broadcast word to say. Psycho. Oh, he went to broadcasting school. He's a
classically trained broadcaster. I can say, sorry for the audio problems. Sorry for the audio
problems. I don't have a shock about it. I'm a professional. Sorry. I gotta back the fuck away.
Back away. Oh, you guys are all dead if I can do something.
Disgusting rancid. I'm jumping me. Fit in there. He'll get grabbed by this guy. Oh shit,
it's just a thing at Best Buy to fucking demonstrate the ring doorbell. Hey.
Hey. That's a long way to go. Eat him. Eat him. Get grabbed by this thing. Oh shit, nice.
What is that? Oh shit, it's a Roomba. I got it. I shot his eyeball up. That's like an evil Roomba.
We might as well just do this again. I feel like they think that's fun.
Let's keep, I'm gonna have to go down there. I know it. Two more. Damn it. Okay, I think we're good.
It's a big power source. It's a big power cable. I've had enough already. They keep
running. Rough grenade, monster's belly. What the fuck is that? Did I just?
Did that make the grenades more powerful? Thumbs up. Let's go down here. No. Arsehole destroyed.
I don't even need the grenades. I'll take another one though. I'll take another one. Sure. Let's go.
Upstairs. You go anymore? Go. Hey. Oh shit, there it is. There's the, oh that's a table.
Okay. Um, whatever. Oh shit, all right. Oh, that's what I, I have no room for this and I must scream.
Here. You take it. Hey, that was expensive. That was expensive.
Oh, there's a force field. Look at that. There's a combined shield blocking your path.
I'll figure out how to shut it down. Uh, where's the things? Power things over there?
Yup, behind the painting. Always behind the painting. What? I have to go down? Follow the
giant cable. Oh, and really? Oh, come on. Just kill me? Hey, oh, hey, hey, oh. I can't see anything.
That was a Homer Simpson scream. What the fuck? Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Turn on the flashlight? I can't. Oh, what a lightsaber.
How are you sure? What? It's still in the case. They never leave them in the case.
Nice. New weapon. I didn't even need to edit your genetic code. I know. I would've loved that.
Oh, that's okay. There'll be a next time. Insert power cell.
What? How do I use? How do I store this? Can I store it? Erty, how do I store it?
Oh, it didn't do it that time. All right. Cool. How does it work? Get.
Can't get in here. That's what the grenade was for. That's what the grenade was for.
They can't open doors, right? They can't open doors. It's locked. You can't open a door. I
know you can't. I've played this series before. Can't open doors. You're stupid.
I have to go in there though. Okay. Load this twice. Fucking done twice. Get it. I know. I
figured it out. I get it. Dead. Dead. Dead. Dead. Hello, boys. Oh, shit. A lot of ammo.
This is an insane amount of ammo for this gun. 240 rounds in it. Holy shit. Switch on.
Oh, man. Oh. Oh, no. Oh, I hate the fucking dark. Okay. Let's go. They can't get in here.
They can't get in here. I'm good. Get. Okay. Any more grenades? I think grenades. There's so
many of them. Oh. What the fuck? This is an infestation. It's infested.
I'm just going to run. I'm just going to run.
Okay. Here we go. I don't want to waste ammo. Move your mouth. Move your mouth.
You jump right here. Jump at me. Right here. Jump. Jump. Jump. Jump. Jump. I need you to jump right
here. Stop doing an AI path and jump. Jump over here. Jump at me and get me. Jump at me and get
me. Jump at me and get me. He's too high up. He's too high up. Okay. I think he had work.
He jumped over my head. Okay. One of those opportunities for being a little bit shorter
and out. The worst Elvis I've ever heard. It's not supposed to be good. I'm just scared.
Don't fall off the edge. Geez. What are you doing? What are you people doing?
Where am I? Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God. I have no health.
I have no health. Give me this thing. Give me this thing. Give me it. Give me it. Give me it. Give me
it. Give me it. Give me it. Give me it. Ah. You're all dead.
Fuck. Oh my goodness. He's going to... Hey. This is where it gets a little weird. Good. Where are you?
Come on, come on, come on, come on, right here, right here, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
this is the upgraded weapon of course i'm gonna be a handgun hang this is the
upgraded pistol i don't have an upgraded laser cannon minus two ham
handgun i'm locked in here with you you're locked in here with me
those combined shield doors are effective
all right dude could you get like verizon or something
this dude's on at&t okay most coverage across all of america
most bars you'll ever have sky's on sprint
oh that's okay that's it's okay coverage not the kind of quality coverage you'll
get from verizon and baubles well have to do it there the other
balls hey no no no no no racket man
racket hey this is this is a drunk rack
hey man can you rack it yeah yeah i got it
where are the other balls i don't know man let's play
okay i'm trying to move this fucking thing
all right nice rack man hey this is how every
five-year-old plays this game do you know that i
where are you do you know that i would actually like pool
if you could play it like this if there was no
stupid pull if you could just like bull it
everybody used to do that we used i remember the dude that i had that i knew
that i knew that i had a pool table we would sit there and play like like
ice hockey with each other what was it like what's what's that stupid thing
called the what's it called ice air hockey not ice hockey
we would have a ball and it'd be like oh i didn't get it i gotta get it in
that corner watch out man oh nice nice almost
oh it'd be like dude fucking what the hell my hand was there
get the fuck off my field man by the way
nailed it you're a man child i didn't do this last i didn't do this yesterday to
this like 20 years ago but when i tell you guys a story about
a thing that i did it wasn't like you know
after breakfast this morning i was throwing pool balls at one of my fucking
12 year old friends hitting his hands
oh that's what i was like that's what i was like 14
that would be to reply what all right let me pay attention stop
distracting do one puzzle at a time oh it's hard
okay make quick work of that open thick and gun harry that's me
another one of these oh pistol pete oh handgun harry no single shot steve
no reload randy so angry no what all right let's take let's get
inventory here that's why and how about this guy
looks good all of our guns look good pistol peter
he's power source looking good this needs a power source
boss ow my eyes all right that's what's one of those weird guys
i'm just gonna unload a machine gun into his body
you guys know how many zits i'm gonna have on my face because of this
i'm gonna be covered in since oh wait that
wasn't that i wasn't for this door
zack harry i'm gonna be covered in zits all right powered up
and i powered powered something i'm missing something here
it's fisto i'm gonna go down oh no not no not i want a grenade
i want a grenade is that a grenade um i'm going down
i knew he was gonna get off too that's getting the shit out of me
fuck make that noise what's going on why am i attached to him
oh my god oh no no no no no no no no no no no no no oh shit throw a testicle
shit nothing has ammo this one was
you're all right though right yeah russian we've got to get you out of
here and i'm working on it
kermie let me take some a minute here how are you liking the game so far
it's good it's very fun it is very very fun so far
i like it got a few complaints though like number one i i really don't really
have any complaints what a sellout
oh all right let's start in this room hey ben
do you like this hey man hey man yes i yes i like the game
all right i gotta bring this power source so hold on turn this one on
two okay health is over on a second everybody relax press that button
all right there it is we're powered why is this one red
one that's still red why is that still red
you're ass gay ben i'm not gave newel but
all right i think i got everything out of here i got the shortcut
about that shortcut
oh wait i need to bring you up here ah
hmm open that door give me this shit
now that door is open all right let's get out of here
um right i can't leave without the right um all right so i gotta pull that
from down here i get it i know stop yelling at me
stop yelling at me don't yell at me stop yelling at me
okay we're gonna go like this odd watchers skip 30 minutes
yo you just have to skip five minutes oh
four shells left how are we doing on a mo
nice
got it what are we what chapter am i
hey what are you doing i'm actually still comfortable i don't think that we
had that a single i'll see the bear impression
uh waka waka no kermit we can't go there because
we we can't get in there filler words waka waka
can't go there because we can't get in we can't go we can't get in there
i don't even know what i'm starting to think that was just filler words kermit doing a fawzi impression
that was kermit being like mean and satirical
talking shit about fawzi yeah you know i'm really fawzi he's just
he's starting to get on my nerves you know like oh waka waka
he only has two catchphrases he's got to get more catchphrases than that right
piggy
this is like a fucking impression hour if omega low saved no it wasn't the same
thing i said 20 minutes ago oh yeah great i can do
miss piggy going hi ya i need a new material
all right give me another character let's go give me another character i want
another one another character animal
ah ah ah yes play drums play drums play drums ah
ah it's close it's close i i if i didn't have the vr headset i could do it
come on just a bean um all right just all right oh all this
okay next kiwi well i mean cherry i just want to say
that we have lots of fun today with all the kids
next one i mean all of them seinfeld no peter griffin i see the long con you're
playing here that's the long con i'm not going to
fall for it hey hey guys get him to a bunch of
impressions so he does the wicked shitty awful peter griffin and we all
laugh at him what happened today sorry guys
i'm gonna have to find another streamer that's no don't leave but i'm gonna have
to find another streamer that's gonna do those voices don't leave this stream
you're leaving i don't know data okay data data uh captain we're not
sure what the disturbance is what minus three horrible whatever
ah no these must be on your wrists they're on my
forearms that feels so weird it's cutting off the
circulation of my brain okay they better be like a bunch of
shit in here finally i have full health you know what
just stick it in there i'm not going to use it but i will later
i need it all right here it is now just snap those cables and off we go
reload the gun happy happy this is so loud i can't hear anything
this isn't going to be as easy as it looks from the ground
no one tell him i don't i just cut the wires but
i russ i can't figure out how to disconnect these cables
maybe try opening the cable shielding and shooting them
that's what i was doing that's what i did
oh that's what i tried
inside and deactivate the power source
all of a sudden we just start falling down what the hell is that
good grief that's a full account all right
we have been trapped in the dark you're free now it's okay your friend sent me
the alex band that's me you are our friend what are they doing to you
here what they do to us wait they just they
put them in these machines that's where they get their power the
combine drain from us the power they use to protect their weapon
there there there we are ripped from ourselves
we have to stop them from killing your friends we're gonna go do this three more times
we'll extract ourselves and exact our own vengeance
you must go to the weapon what i can't get into the vault if the
substations are still online do not worry alex fans they will not be
we will not allow it clear the path
the verge there is no distance between us we are
thanks good luck here you might need this
okay cat look i like cheese slice my head off
trust in that vortigaunt to shut down all the substations i
i trust him yes me too he doesn't well that vault isn't going anywhere
i'm standing there with no vault to break into surrounded by combine
russ trusting him is our only plan here he'll do this we can do this
yes you're right he'll be fine we're all going to be
fine good i'm taking this one oh uh we're too i gotta go towards the
weapon all right oh shit
everything's okay
what's that grenade oh no it's reinhardt what alex
i'm just saying this is like shitty one word impressions it's like what i've
been doing for the last 30 fucking minutes
shoot the guy shoot the guy reload from raisin all right i'm
ready this time no f u c k i n g around
i'm gonna go make this guy eat this ready we're gonna sit on the bench
check this out this is my little battle station
jesus who's left hey
you had a good run
this is the smallest soda i've ever seen nice all right i got three tape
measure bombs now i just want the big guy died over
here somewhere we just get here that's what i want
okay uh the big guy died go over the light it's already in here i already
did this bye wait hey that hurts you
trying to see where it goes i'll stop it how much resin do i have
well that's not
i don't have i don't have a present uh i don't have it
i have a resident having a president going up
um like that's the wrong way oh fuck oh shit i'm sorry
really don't want us to happen now i just want it more now that's the spirit
oh take one of these all right what do i have for uh
i need good good good good let's keep going
resin i need some resin viewers here thank you for the
yeah more viewers i can tell me what the resin is
now okay let's go right here no no no no i almost just had to delete my
twitch channel almost almost had to delete my twitch
channel what was the thing i said if i didn't know the puke thing
mines now of course there is that's okay is that a head
a head and an arm that has their arm like this
like ready to shoot me with a gun right a little brim for the hat
that's a person aiming a gun got him moving thank you i want that bad
oh resin buzzing buzzing i hear a pig i hear a pig that means
combo is wrong oh who is it who is it where are they
shit okay put this back
trying to shoot them through his legs getting a little rusty
fresh is this fresh tv oh not a fresh tv
making my head yeah shaking my god damn head
you are they saying my name yeah that's not good
open up everything anything else in here they're doing an impression
wait i know what i could do we're gonna move a chair out there
we're gonna whip a chair out there and we're gonna close the door
worked perfectly exactly what was planned exactly what i intended
oh my god i don't want to go that's every single time i ever play an
online shooter seriously battlefield call of duty
fortnight whatever it doesn't matter i get into a firefight one two three one
five six they don't die and then i freak out and i run behind
they i run away and i die they kill me every encounter i've ever had
online let's let's do this right
what's my shit i'll bet okay i'm ready now show yourself you call of duty camper
another guy in the head like seven times hold it up
p max left okay that wasn't so bad and it wasn't
hey you guys have ammo you guys have nothing on you that's
disappointing oh you did eat that now let's save it
the uh the vortigaunt's in there maybe fresh tv don't fuck this up this time
he held it with one hand all right let's go
really oh man oh look who it is you see it's omega lol andy
omega lol andy hey dude long time fan here yeah i've been watching
i wonder if you've been hyping up that urethra reveal stream for a couple
months now all a date all day for that um i have no idea
back here oh dude okay why not don't fall i'm getting tangled i can
already feel it i've got a bottle or something i can throw
over there that box fuck i'll take it
good work oh mega lol
fuck what happened
hello omega lol copy pasting omega lol know what i will tell you about
half-life alex uh the movement in the game is the best of any vr title
that has released that's a fact it's just the best movement in a vr game
very very easy to control shut up nobody talk you can't i can't do it it's
not possible you just can't do it it's it's way too awkward to think just
into falling down and not carry it around oh your dad's back
oh thank god
honestly i picked your survival at about four percent
you can think that's vortiga he got me back here in one piece
rus russell but dad on dad dad we just took down a substation
good because when they move this thing that
weapon's gone we need to get it tonight we will you
still got that data pod right i do this thing's biocoded i'm gonna need
the tlr yep are we gonna get boarded sport okay
great have you got your good honey for sure
you go ahead i'll be fine dad i promise oh my
keep that promise i'll get the work on the data pod
image why did i take so much damage didn't work on a mannequin sorry man
all right dude it was alive just in case you come back and try to kill me
how do i go yes oh how are we doing how long have we been screaming for three
hours holy shit i haven't come out of this once in three
hours arms race his pants all right anybody
huh let me ask you this how far am i into half life alex now
this point right here like the halfway point
okay probably like 60 percent 60 70 percent
at over half okay all right it looks like we're right on schedule then
play this for a little while longer and then we'll finish it tomorrow
probably right on schedule i thought i had 50 resonance
18 resin this guy's annoying get off comms man all right can i upgrade
this at all i i'd like to spend a lot
reflex site lazy site
turn on push to talk dude i can do reflex site but i don't know that
sucks i think it's worth doing
i'm not gonna spend anything you get extended bag that that's exactly all the
only extended bag only bye oh again huh
where i heard that guy where where is he to bring up jump
i know how to jump hey but it's blocked oh fuck off
i go down here i gotta kill me if i fall i gotta go down
hey does this kill me i kill me if i fall isn't it
jesus what do i do enter something i missed
yes why can i why can i look over here cut out
f-force oh almost fucked it up pipes
you guys said i was gonna die okay we need to power that
is that the code no it's not what was it well shit
but on earth is that where oh it's you it's you
come on apparently a dark vader over here oh he was shooting at the alien
i'm getting so sweaty all right yeah yeah yeah yeah time for the first break
break number one oh oh yeah oh what it feels like to be a human
he cleans break oh the hair it's actually not horrible
the headband really caused so many problems skipped a bunch you weren't
supposed to fall down wait what you skipped a lot reload the
save you missed stuff you skipped a whole sequence you skipped
25 minutes of content what hold on i glow let me just get some water
i'll be right back dude i don't think he i don't think he's
ever coming back tugging water slamming water
base station error there may be something blocking the line of sight
between your base station and the what why is it saying that mike peeked
we could hear you regurgitate why am i puking into the toilet
go back in the hole this is getting let me untangle the cord for a second
i have to do the thing where you have to hold the thing upside down and raise
your hand as high as it goes this board is like he's going out
uh huh who's so annoying what i am annoying you think i'm annoying you
what the hell are you doing here he's so annoying
you're gonna stop reading chat oh i want to be one of the best streamers on
twitch and that means you read everything i'm getting that blue raspberry
popsicle oh shit that's gonna be ninja he's got
the blue hair what color is my hair what what color is
my hair my hair is brown that means i can have
uh it's like blonde i have blonde hair that's banana of the banana popsicle
uh let me update this video thingy there we go
oh it's a little that's a little bright is that
what's that is that all right why can this is uh the fps so bad on this
bullshit all right there we go that's better okay let's go
uh so i definitely gonna be playing this tomorrow because i don't think i'll be
able to do this for another maybe a couple of hours but we'll be
finishing half-life alex tomorrow even if it's only like a two or three
hours left it's my end of stream voice no not yet
it's like six hours i think no i i know i know this at least like another
probably seven hours left in the game six or something yeah i know
reload the last save no hold on when are you doing chubby bunny i i have no
idea dude how is that with the most anticipated
stream of 2020 it's the chubby bunny stream
oh my god i thought that was a monster how's my health
oh now why is that there why is this here
fuck you
why why what was that for oh we were both shocked at what just happened
okay uh fucking vr jokes i've done those already
and we here at five guys we got piles of bags of potatoes
that's how you know it's fucking fresh and real we stack them up all over the
restaurant just so you know that it's a real bag of
fucking potatoes unlike those other guys that use real
potatoes but we prove it man we got the bags all
over the restaurant those are peanuts did i just like did i
just totally like fake news everybody i think i just did
let's take some drugs and forget about that wait those are peanuts i thought
they were potatoes well okay an even better question why
the fuck do you have peanuts everywhere why do you have peanuts everywhere that
if somebody who has a peanut allergy you're like putting land mines all over
the place for them why are there bags with peanuts everywhere
he's okay his eyes turned red he's dead he's not safe
keep peanuts lord chad is gaslighting you those are potatoes
okay thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you
thanks okay there's no direct path from where you are to the vault
so you're gonna have to snake your way there well it's huge so it shouldn't be
hard to know which way i'm going i don't understand what they're doing
with it here if this weapon is so powerful
my guess is they're trying to find a way to shut it off earth back to their home
or some other planet why not use it here they already won this war alex
they already won the war okay so let's head up boy
oh they made them stronger i'm so glad that there's no like big event coming up
here in the next few weeks so glad like twitchcon isn't next
weekend or something i would i would have radiation burn marks
on my face and zits all over my forehead like jesus and like the top part of my
hair is gone dude it's like let me do this let me do
this little mission i just pulled the muscle in my arm
oh anybody want some spare ribs get the fuck out of here with this
bullshit oh shit for a grenade it'd been better but
whatever i'll take the resume yep i'm here oh we ain't had nothing but
maggot eat bread for three stinking days
all right let's play real funny man i forgot all of you aren't 11
there's a room full of 11 year olds you all laughing your asses off that
strap's not secure i'm right on the fucking edge
that's the wrong hand we just took a screenshot
we just took a screenshot this thing is vibrating
okay they go in they went in that one didn't
the war for gamer of the year you're up on nine eight five
hello i'm home don't let him up you're gonna have that
i got him are you live where you go how am i doing that like just why am i
what do i like kill like and go i wish you could actually use these
i have an itchy face in the part where i cannot scratch it
oh man thank god better that check i already know i have a bunch on my face
really don't need to do a check one of the five
guys bags i guess i knew i told you one of them was
gonna be alive at some point i knew it oh hello honey it's mom we're coming to
see your place oh we tip right now like like now yeah
yeah we're on the road there we'll be there in five minutes
oh yeah yeah sure okay see you soon i love you
fucking wrist ah old man wrists oh you don't want to i smashed it
oh yeah try to be fucking sneaky it doesn't do anything apparently
i'm doing that a pistol ammo lock it lock it up all right has to be a reason
for why i could come back here of course there is
i can climb climb line line thank you chap for the education
fuck that one guy he knows who he is okay wherever you are i guess this is
like a big battle zone so i'm a little weary about going out of here
how we doing on ammo everything good everything's good
how we doing anybody anybody anybody like anybody aim like this
i feel like this is like more secure like right against the hip
you've got company damn it that's really close
now my eyes my eyelids back pulled my eyelids off that shit just
my eyes were open and it took my eye lashes and eyelids and just like
pulled them backwards don't die in the game where you die in real life
first the hair now the eyes reload the 25 minutes you skipped
it's i thought you think it's a little too late for that i think it's a little
too late to go back like 14 minutes to go get the two
resins i missed oh load it up load it up
activating jex mode jex mode engaged check this shit out
was it isn't there ammo in there too where are they
you've got company wasn't very good wasn't very bad
i'll take a mediocre c plus what else we got i gotta eat i love the
shotgun's my favorite weapon in any video game and i'm not using it ever
good pocket here this is this i'll take this
build right here i'm just coming something else in here
more i am gonna do it like this actually i'll put it in here
yeah like this dude guys this is the way this is the way right here in the
i can't get that that's in a really shitty place
okay whatever
he just rocked my head back with one bullet right in the forehead
i'm fucking crying those of you that know he missed about
a few minutes of dialogue in about two or three corridors
go watch vinnie play to go see it
i'm just like the i'm like the fucking like
secondary like oh yeah i didn't mean to go go watch like somebody else if you
want to see it like i would really should happen
this guy drops grenades and like stubs his toe and hits his head on the wall and
stuff if you want to see a gamer play this
you know i heard i heard my like grandma played this part she did pretty good too
that's so funny like to see it done correctly
go go check out somebody else i'm gonna do it
why is it why don't you dare watch another streamer
don't you dare watch another streamer actually i mean vinnie's awesome vinnie's
very very good oh when when vinnie's not live you stay
here oh my fucking god this is the reason
this is the reason why they all say this this is the reason why they're saying
this this is the reason why they all say this put the gun down
and he's live right now no no no wait wait
wait
hey uh can vinnie do this i lost the bullet again i lost it again
what about this oh dude how to be better than this i'm sure we're pretty
out of work watching boom what's that how's that oh this one
what's that one huh what's that sound what's about this one hey
part two are you ready ready for part two
i don't think you are say you are i doubt it
doubt it what do you do finally stopped pretending
well you know yeah sometimes you gotta pretend
dirty i need to fuck clean up a little bit here
unplayed big fight over here oh that's flashlight
walked into it whatever i'm trying to get one to do this
oh my god you're alive you're alive are you dead
see oh nice nice that would fucking hurt
oh wow i appreciate that i appreciate that
it's just covered in blood oh shit that counts that actually counts
right oh i guess that makes sense right what i thought so little to save the
game you just shit the bed i'm right here i guess how do i get
it was multi-tool what serious i have to do steady i do
i don't get it oh superman 64 okay i get it and take them off the wall
like rearm them same thing here right i mean that takes a
long time just throw a bucket of the fucking thing
but that you know what i mean i don't i don't want to do the puzzle just just
blow them up so much easier why do the puzzle when you
just blow up the room yeah what do you want me not to flinch
it's scary okay um
no no no no no give me this okay that didn't work
that didn't work i had a theory that maybe if i could close the door it would
i'd be fine all right again they want you to do it
you do it quicker this guy's shitty let's watch
finny
that was marge too all right give me this without any problem
nice root force vivus
it wasn't even aiming for that aim sucks
this game sucks this game sucks game fuck it sucks think it with me now
game sucks this game fuck it sucks this game
sucks you stop pretending to be bad at video games
that's the best way to like trigger any streamer i told you guys that a long time
ago okay that's the one i want thank you
okay just um what why did i even need it i didn't need it
oh slow slow slow oh i'm getting close i almost just went over it hey germa like
shoot the barrel for a funny joke do not do that yep
fuck how am i supposed to get this
fuck room is clear room is clear scientist that's how i'm gonna shot the
barrel i almost percent that's right boom
give me uh then doesn't i thought i was gonna hit and explode
this double resin over there boys oh my god oh oh oh my goodness oh
fuck it's a lot get it i don't know how to juggle
i don't hit right but nice continue that's a dangerous game that's a
dangerous game that's a dangerous game all right sign
are a shitty room it's oh am i already here in the beginning
of the game i swear to god i was already here
something in that car all right just be careful said what is it resin
oh it's 11 okay we're out into the open house how wet are my underarms it's
probably a joke
oh he wasn't he wasn't seeing me
just sitting there just vibing man with a beer what the fuck
he didn't care at first oh we gotta go back there quick
because we didn't get that resin i'm i'm gonna get up there guys
hit me it works
oh that's it i'm leaving only he had two healing syringes
yeah but they're like okay on your screen it's really clear on my screen i
gotta look like under my underarms i gotta what do i have for a healing
item oh it stinks under there it actually
doesn't though relax it cost like 1.5k viewers in the last
hour what what would you cry about it where you at let's go
fucker you're right there you fucking oh shit
ow ow ow ow you give me the all right he's up here i gotta move i gotta move
to that storage unit done i can't i don't know i'm
gonna smash into a thing in my room this stupid thing get open open up
but let's go
it's full health i tried unloading like 30 rounds of that fucking guy
uh close and use the shotgun the guy is unloading a
gatling gun into me and i can i can only go like
two miles per hour no i don't i can go much faster than that
i just have to do the dumb diablo 2 charge move
okay i figured it out go jesus teleport around the whole fucking
map all right i'm ready i'm done with this bullshit they're all dead
oh shit what i got it i got that motherfucker he's dead
i told you that's why i was so concerned that's why i didn't want to
throw it that hard i was still alive such a coward way to
play this i feel like i feel like when you when you
go paintballing for the first time and you're terrified of getting hit so
you just kind of go like this to make it look like you're
participating just stay down here and i yes i was one of the guys that wore the
fucking big vest so it didn't hurt when it hit you
we are good we're good we're good we're good we're good we're good we're good
we can take a shortcut through that building okay
i don't see a way into this building ah i'm gonna look around
we have a problem we got a real problem
problem like that this control is broken vodka good oh no oh god no
rustle doesn't like vodka got it well i i never said that but it's not good it's
poison but i love it everyone everyone loves it
okay that's all very confusing i gotta push really really hard
i'll find you some wonderful if you could actually yes
yeah this is fucked up okay the the plastics coming off
oh shit hold on is that better it's not great
it's not great it's not great but it'll do
not great but it'll do i don't know what happened
oh boy that sucks okay left on the uh on the track pad is done so
well i'm actually surprised it took this long
like wouldn't you have figured that was gonna happen like six months ago or like
a year ago when i first started doing vr
this has been this long i don't i i need a power source here cool
all right we need power power that's um he's dead up here nothing else but soap
and shit good all right the power is over here
but hold on so uh there's a fight stick in there
i'm gonna see what it does force field it's a baby toy how much
resin do i have i got enough to do the uh the upgrade
oh nice oh nice nice nice
hell yeah uh doors open i don't know what that for but it's open
don't break shit it it worked i mean i can go in here now i have a
grenade oh nice all right here we go this is
where i gotta put the power in here i don't care
little mario chomp guys those little uh little black
things that build cheese to meet you and they said
locked in the corner
oh jeez what am i eating all right what am i eating
i got food i'm trying to shoot him like ten times
i'm trying to shoot him like five times we'll meet you outside
it looks as if there are combined barricades up ahead they're stopping
anyone from getting any closer to the vault
okay so what do you think make your way into the distillery and see where it
takes you with my drive back online we've finally
got the upper arm no you're kidding me oh my god i have all
these things shit shit shit
that shit shit
oh shit oh oh no don't come in why do you have a shield i can block
everything it's a fair
oh
god who's my healer
where is he where is he
out of cells he's fucked up already okay i've got a whole lot of ammo where's the
power cell there it is okay now i gotta plug this thing in where
what do i plug it in nice to plug this in in here isn't it
where is it i actually don't remember where's that
power cell thing down here i thought that was a bad guy
oh i need this let's go give it to me do the whole thing
ah oh it feels so good great great oh no
oh no shit in my fucking pants good i'll take that shit
one left one
have anything that's fun uh i don't have any bullets in almost any gun
kind of a deep shit just looking for ammo no ammo
i'm not jumping from here are you nuts how do you climb back down a ladder
are you crazy i'm gonna do whatever the hell this is
didn't i turn it on that's something oh it's powering this fucking thing
this beam right here extended mag 37 extended mag let's go
hi to eduardo hey this is eduardo hi welcome to the stream
oh ammo yeah but i'll find him looks like i'm not gonna see ammo ever again
you can put that to good use sick out of cells
oh i'm in a lot of trouble then huh i need to take that cell and put it
cell somewhere else how is this thing red cable the red cable goes
i can't watch this i'm at the exact same spot in the game
not fun man good game i wish you the best luck in your video game adventure
red cord got the box i can't let me go over here for a second i've
got to so where's this cord it's a red cable that if the
plug something in put this up and go up there
get all this shit out of the way going under here shut up
there why i watched the bar shoot it please
it doesn't do anything i just shot a shotgun in there guys okay i can't
bingo all right so how do i get this power on
how do i turn this on like a lever in this multi tool multi
doesn't do anything in the upgrade room is this
that's a red cable not going at anything ding ding
ding ding thing what does that do it is that was it at the console
ding ding ding ding that ding ding is all right the clapper boys oh my god it's
at the shield door thingy what no it's not he's donation fading
no i just like where the fuck is this the power to the red table is like i
need to go to here to there i but the power connected but then
where the fuck does the power go is it like just stop
dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb
okay get you switch the stupid power he did it hooray
all right don't move this shit what happened that's the monitor monitor's
going back good alex still there
guys how far back is that please don't tell me if it's that far back
that's not that far back right it's gonna be after the fight please be after
the fight please be after the fight please be after the fight
please be after the fight don't have it be load up and there's like
10 people have to fight hey please be after the fight like when they turn the
power on thank god that we can hear the clappers
okay thank god thank god thank god thank god
it's not even extended back but it's okay all right
i forget this one already i already forget how this one works
okay come here pod watchers unskip you know what pisses me off more than
anything is that was true like the the vod
pod watchers should have just skipped 15 minutes
it's pissing me off because it's accurate
hi pod watchers we made it you can put that to good use
i'm targeting this one video games aren't even any good anymore
they used to be better when they were eight pixels each i remember when i
played et it was better than this one game could be
games are the best they've probably ever been ever don't let anybody ever tell
you that unless it's me and we're talking about the golden years of the
super nintendo entertainment system or the nintendo 64 entertainment system
that was the golden age no game is compared
and bloodborne pod watchers pod watchers my god pod watchers
pod watchers pod watchers that's that's a good height
right that i'll take it to the top please thank you
i did it i did it we can keep going we can move on
one bullet seven bullets i need the shotgun the only damn thing i have that
has any bullets in it borden borden freeman never it's me
thermos sucks at everything i hate that it was too low thank you
warning yes there's definitely a bunch of old bottles in here
does alcohol go bad it only improves it's all good alex
wrestle your
i was gonna take off the lid whatever your ouds oh shit
it's the it's the mario things things i was talking about
this is them all right settle down
shut up they hungry should i be like puking with their mouths
all right here you go baby birds
oh looks looks like it sucks okay literally covered in news
it's gonna hurt oh my god thanks uh how am i gonna get by this
insert three power cells all that shit drop it i can open that right
here get in all right i'm out yeah oh fuck that's right i did pick it up
this is creepy what am i supposed to be doing
rozz hi everybody i know i'm not purple
else else else what um all right what's the matter why is it
referring to her please love you no what's going on
how's everybody doing this is beautiful alex come in alex
alex oh there you are there you are beautiful sunset there's no straight
shot to the vault i'm gonna head inside and find a way out
gorgeous i love this beautiful it's it's so pretty
okay you tell me yourself and i don't shoot you in it
yes alex you're never gonna believe
russ i'm here i don't know i guess i might hey hey
you with the uh with the blood on you you with the blood
i uh got a little situation here yeah you sure do you have a gun on you do
you got a gun yeah look at that
it's a nice one too it's nicer than mine which is up inside
this guy i saved you thanks
i alerted the horde sorry what the hell was that
wow that's jeff jeff don't worry you can't see
here's just fine though got him here like Mozart
who all right now let me help you out all right see you on the other side
don't worry yeah keep your voice down
that's a character named jeff where is he
it's like an angry hungry baby yes right watch this
oh see he's totally predictable but he will rip your arms off if he finds
you we do oh get out of here
this is gonna be like the run from the scary monster park right
of course it is i wouldn't think what is scary
i'm assuming i should probably take a few of these
jeff ready go yeah
hey hey those things are nasty you gotta cover your mouth
got it thanks hey i i almost forgot what's your name
Alex hey alex i'm larry nice to meet you hi larry try not to get killed
okay i've got wait do this give me the resin give me the resin
okay i have no bullets i guess bullets don't matter
armed with noise
see right here all right oh there's a thing
you can open it open your mouth what i just told her
oh fuck you see down here my god god fuck where's
oh fuck well there's shit in here he can't it's blocked he can't get in here
i'm just gonna clean their locker okay jeff i brought you a treat
it's over there go over here man go over this way
he's stepping on the bottles
no open the window okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay fuck me fuck me it's over there look look it's over there
you can't get in here you can't get in here i'm safe in here
i'm safe in here fuck you i'm trying to place it down
oh that just made him angry made him angry
am i alive yeah okay i get it i get it i get it i understand i understand it i
get it i just gotta figure out this is kind
i gotta figure out a way to get around him
that's a great checkpoint by the way thanks for that
good okay can he is he gonna come in here oh my god
jeff jeff jeff jeff fuck does he leave eventually does he leave
oh i grabbed something i grabbed something i grabbed something i grabbed
something smashing my desk i don't know what that was but how the fuck am i
gonna do this thank god thank that heavens thank
susan fucking thor that that didn't break
fuck you wow how do i get rid of you oh shit it was worth a shot it was worth
a shot just try once just to see if i could like misdirect him
and he would like fall down on his knee i theory was like i shoot him in like the
face when it opens up and he like goes down on one knee for one
two three four i'm alive but i'm gonna get you i don't know hey thank you
five subs don't fall okay so like this gotta be some way i could like fuck him
up oh hey jeff i hear outside
hear that jeff hey jeff i think i heard something down the hall
what is he not going what go why is he not going
um excuse me jeff
why does he keep coming back in here oh shit hit him in the head
br sucks fucking virtual reality it was not ready it was never ready it's another
10 years before this shit it's gotta work
it's emote only mode this is some fucking dumb little secret to beat this guy
let's not go like this and then have the wiimote get disconnected for a second
because you went a little too fast what's the little is it's gonna be like a sound
secret okay it's gonna be like a shelf with a hundred bottles on it i'm just
gonna drop a ball where is he i gotta lock him in the freezer oh you had it
goodbye jeff let's see you again
you suck you're gonna get out of there you can't get out of there right
can he get out of there i think he can he get out of there give me a little hand no let's not
what am i doing here what am i doing here am i in here what am i doing in here what's
the point of coming in here i'm gonna have my face on the corner of the table i know it
i have to go in this room
um oh that's not good okay hold on a minute here stay there jeff just relax relax jeff
okay jeff i'm gonna let you out i gotta need you to cooperate
okay
at least we're in the dark in this one still okay muscle man voice
hey colonel dingleberry thanks with five community subs all right so i gotta get in there i gotta
turn that shit on and i gotta go through the elevators you have to put me right here though
all right i gotta be ready for this don't turn on the car alarm rips out we'll just take our time here
car alarm rips out we'll just take our time here
it doesn't matter he can't get out okay right when this door opens i'm throwing this
shit down the damn hallway no bell no bell what is he what's he coming over here for
why do i hear him why the fuck do i hear him why do i hear him fucking ceiling right here
did i get it did i get it did i get it did i guys did i get it did i get it
cough glass bottles in here you can't get it hey let's go go go my god how do i go go go
here have lots of tissues
oh my god the door is gonna open holy shit oh i'm not stuck in here with you
you're stuck in here with me right you're stuck in here with me
didn't cover your mouth
oh no that's why i can't really broke my controller all right well so now he's gonna be right here
other hand other hand playing music what's he doing what the fuck is he doing what's he doing
what's wrong with
he knew i was in there the whole time dude he just wanted to be in the camera
i was covering one night i was covering my mouth that was the home stretch
that door's locked oh the motherloat what was that what why am i doing this what oh my god
oh it's just a little dog it's just a dog it's just a dog don't drop that what why is this why is this like this
wait eat a stick i don't know no get out of the way get out of the way get out of the way
can you hear that he's got the ears of steel where is he oh here what is he where is he
oh yeah i can jump over there
treasures treasures aren't worth it what okay i don't even know where he is
out of cells earth is this
god is stabbing me they're stabbing me i think
alex coming in hey alex oh there you are can you hear me more or less you're breaking up
i think you're still in the distillery i made a friend named jeff well that's great we can take
all the help we can get yeah we're not really close listen there should be a big tunnel-sized
plug in the floor there somewhere that's gonna be the tunnel out of here correct
you get it open i'll figure out where it leads
three power cells that's gonna be the last jeff you and me have all kinds of fun
oh my god
oh shit that's a big eye he's bugging out at me nice try power cell
one power cell okay oh my god slow down slow down slow down slow down
okay two more you can hear this shit why did i just do that why did i just do that
breaks twice power source power source power power power power don't touch that that's a
fucking bad play
get this fucking thing open gas basket here give me this and give it thank god
it's gone gas mask on
oh my god i know what to do i need a bottle right now right now right now oh my god that works too
that works together works shit thank you very much okay we gotta get the fuck out of here give
you that bottle i'll throw it over there that would be great cool cool cool cool cool don't call don't
call don't call don't call don't call fuck you what did i hit i don't know oh shit i'm i'm gonna be
in here how do i get the fuck out of here letter two of these things man i got two i got two you jeff
oh no three where's the third one that's the third one down right all right am i gonna save point here
i do right i better get a safe point here and you'll say i don't know how to do that
okay where was that last guy last guy was not i got the one in here i did i have the one in there
one right there that's only one there okay got the one oh that way yo
oh
thank god i have one of those on me
run from run from run from put this in your
it's gonna melt
three that's three i can i'm done i'm done after this i'm done i'll pick it up tomorrow
this is fucking killing me this is insanity oh yeah let's go i'm so glad to be over with this
oh man hi jeff it was a lot of fun but you are you are terrifying
is he gonna break it
what i can't i can't turn these fucking things
oh i can't turn turn turn it won't turn oh oh oh turn turn i can't turn oh get in there get
in the trash can pack the trash can pack the trash can pack the trash can pack
holy shit that was that was wild now he doesn't stand up oh my god jack are you okay
that wasn't funny
he's dead holy shit thank god it's over
oh my god it's over it's over and i got it i killed him that was intense
whoa what did you do to jack yeah i trapped jeff in the trash compactor and then i crushed him
god damn well i uh i hope you came across some of the good stuff see you around all right and
that's okay the coast is clear time to get that's the end of the stream get through those tunnels
okay go go engage what was the minute for a second that tunnel hits to the vault great also
little heads up i think the tunnel is full of antlions just in case i cut out permanently
antlions antlions antlions yeah you know aliens with stabby legs oh yes i will see you guys tomorrow
camp no i like tiny little lions no that's not them these ones are pretty dangerous
yep on i go all right tunnels we will pick up tomorrow with the tunnels
get a chapter change yes we are all right guys it's nuts this is where it gets
chill uh when i hear screaming antlions i don't think chill we'll pick it up tomorrow
and then i'm assuming that we'll finish it tomorrow yeah fan chill all right so from here how many
hours are left in the game which day three three ish three to four yeah that's perfect
we're around four three four three four all right yeah that's perfect we'll just finish tomorrow
he'll beat it tomorrow all right cool i'll see you guys tomorrow thanks for watching i believe we
haven't saved but before i turn off my computer i'll make sure it's safe let's take it let's do a
hair check oh man this is only the second time i've come out of the headset it's not good but
it's okay grateful for a normal human doing another hair treatment tonight oh my assessment of half
life alex so far is it's uh it's pretty solid it's pretty solid i'm a big fan oh and wow uh
actual actual perfect timing because this thing just ran out of battery this is the one that
broke though so i don't know if that's is that a bad sign is that low battery or is that a bad sign
all right let's uh do the subs let's chill for a minute and then i'm gonna get some food and
i'm gonna relax and lie down take a bath do a hair treatment thanks again everybody for watching
and thanks to all these subs appreciate it they were i'm gonna go through some of them actually
five community subs from ink cat five for marlin brando marlin brandio and then we got the five
and five from colonel dingleberry and just be i love it so far typically you can't see yourself
sitting in a vr game for more than three hours but it flows together very well the jeff sequence
okay you know when something seems so horrible and so terrifying that oh no i can never do it
it wasn't that bad considering it's just scary so valve definitely decided they were gonna make
you think of every vr game you've ever played it's the lookout here comes the scary monster
right and it's coming to get you in the headset hey how about a shooter where you gotta shoot
headshot duck duck use cover hey we've got like weird little puzzles where you gotta look through
the wall with a little device they kind of just took every vr game that was an hour long and
made it a 12 hour long game so i think it's pretty good i'm very surprised that it's this long
you know when they first announced this i really thought this is going to be some kind of
demo because the index was coming out and i thought this is gonna oh look half life alex
it's like an hour and a half and it's just kind of fun and you play around with alex vance and
that's it i did not know that it was going to be a full experience like this so it's very very good
we will finish it tomorrow it's a full triple a game oh yeah it absolutely is
and i don't want to give you a rating because i don't want to blow it but i mean it's it's up
there and i'll see you tomorrow we're gonna start 2 p.m pacific tomorrow two o'clock pacific thanks
for watching get some sleep get some food get some rest i'm gonna get up right now and i'm going to
let me turn that off whatever that is show the streamer
good night guys i'll see you tomorrow have a great night