And I have to... This beautiful kafamari. Can you see it? No, you can't. But why? Oh, there we go.
I think it's working. Ears are be noticed. That's really loud, sorry. Hold on. Almost ready!
Make my audio delayed. Just watch the video.
My flash? No? You guys are gonna tell me it's in sync though. But I'm not gonna really tell.
It should be pretty close.
Be updated. All right, let's start.
I'm sorry, I just skipped. I do have the DLC for this game too. Why? Because I just did. Painfully
low on data. There we go. The ball flew open away into the depths of the great cosmos,
leaving a great hole in the sky. Oh dear. King made a black hole playing tennis. Consumed the
whole planet. All suffered the same fate. They all got sucked in. That's not good. Have I played this
one before? Maybe. I don't remember. I've just... I don't remember. I never played this game enough
to remember anything about it. Well, this is a pickle. Daikon, dill, and cabbage. Sorry.
Most of the stars in the cosmos are gone. This is where we come in. We always save the day.
Side by side, we'll save the cosmos. But you're the sidekick. Just so that's clear. Do you want to
cape bunny ears and wings? Anyhow, we want you to assist us with this one. By a stroke of luck,
Earth is still there. So go roll lots and lots of ginormous katamaris. We'll do the hard work
of turning them into stars. We'll take care of that pesky black hole too. Ready to turn out some
colossal katamaris? Okay, time to get going. The cosmos needs our help. Yeah, this is not the
remake. This is... This is like katamari three or four, isn't it? Maybe even five. What does this
sit in release? Three? Four? Four. Okay. Rolling practice. You know the basics. Yes, I actually do.
That's all right. We can teach you Wii moon brain. Roll! Katamari 101. Presenting the
astonishing katamari. Sleek! Roll it. Pick it up stuff. Grow bigger. Repeat. If you do well,
this katamari will become a moon. Profound, yes. We have that effect on everyone. Give it a spin
and pop it on top of that platform. You ready? Roll. Roll. Roll. Roll backwards. Roll sideways.
Roll up and over object. There we are. All right. Not hideous at all. Enjoy yourself.
And now there's a big mess of stuff all around. Such odd shapes they have downright disturbing.
Anywho, roll them up with the katamari, please. The katamari will start to get bigger and bigger.
It's all very strangely satisfying. Who knew? Yes, I remember. It feels so wonderful.
This is as satisfying as pulling up chest hairs with a tweezer. Did I just say that out loud?
Holy hornbeam! That box you rolled up is a present. From us to you with love. We know you need a
treat. Thanks for the present. Picking up the puzzles now. Now we can start taking over this.
What 10 centimeters you say? Getting bigger. Do a dash. Quick turn is the middle portion of
the buttons. This is you can go really, really, really fast. There we are. Look. I can move around
with the royal look. Let's see what you look like. Cool. And then there's looking from the prince's
perspective. Apparently out the door. Got it. I want to get all the pink puzzles. All useful and
necessary. So practice, practice, practice. Oh, nice and big. That'll make a nice moon.
And now the finishing touch. Roll up Marcy. What have you seen? That's weird or not.
Marcy is just hiding somewhere as usual. My money is on that big ball thing. Difficult word.
Once you roll up Marcy, you're done with practice. Let's get Marcy. Marcy. Did I get you?
Got you. You're done with practice. Marcy is rolled up. Remember how to roll now,
come and practice anytime. Back to the prince-dom now. Royal rainbow. These games are so fun.
Welcome home. So we got you to roll this moon for practice. Was it crazy hard? Not so much. Ah,
hubris. Hey, this Katamari is regular size. It's the wrong one too. Boo. We ordered a large.
Envelope, please. Points total time. Let's see. 63 points. Such an ordinary score. Was that
Kalasari? It's okay. Normal is back in vogue. It's the new black. Inside sources reveal.
Prince has a penchant for weird things. Back up, we see. A present. An ambiguous accessory for you
to make your own. We'll keep it safe in the cake in the prince-dom. There should be lots more
accoutrements, so enjoy. A dazzle of color Marcy and none other. Lost again. The Pantone party is
in the prince-dom. Yay for a star. Uhuru. That one piece sticking out the top is annoying me.
That was barely worth it. Here's an idea you can do better. Are you the chat? That's a chat saying.
Okay, so I can walk around. Are we good?
Alrighty, here we are. This is the prince-dom. Your not-so-secret base. Are you thrilled? Dizzy?
It's okay to throw up. We made it just for you, a custom tailored star. It's small and precious,
just like you are to us. We'll keep adding to it more places to play. When your cousins come over,
they can live here. We made you houses too, so go inside each one, yes? Explore and play our little
prince. The prince-dom is where wishes come true. This just in. The prince-dom is now bigger. Check
out the new places. There's a photo album, presents, and other things. We also added a totally
fab place for you to play. We gave it the best name, the big tripper. Takes you on a voyage of
light and sound. See? Now you can make new stars again. Twinkle twinkle. Extra extra. A new area
has opened up in the prince-dom. A place of icy beauty called Sub-Zero. Watch your step, it's very
slippery. You can make new Katamaris there, so roll away. Attention shoppers! There's a new area
in the prince-dom. It's called the Tropic Quasar. So pretty and warm, just stuffed with flowers.
There's fun new things to play with too. It's the prince-dom 2.0. Go have a launch party.
Excuse us. Seems to be more colonies. Oh, did you go shopping Xbox Live Marketplace, yes?
Fabulous! Now you can make new stars again. Go pop into a colony and get a star maker.
Remember the present you rolled up just now? Those gifts you find are all in the presents.
It's that house shaped like a yummy cake. We'll pop all the presents in there from now on.
But right now you should try on your new gift. Let me try it on. How do I try it on? Does it
have to be like on a certain run? It says I have it, maybe it's just on. Is it on me? I got scammed.
Oh. All right, Xbox Live Marketplace. I already bought everything you can buy,
except for all the stupid shitty things. All right, save and load. Let's save it.
No, I'm not going to buy the cousins. They're like a dollar fifty each and they don't do anything.
Sound and vibration. Actually, turn off vibration. I hate vibration.
Collection. Oh man. Well, that's a lot of data. And then here is a photo album.
I don't have any photos. Wait, is that the camera? No. Unable to edit photo data. No great new photo
data. This music is freaking me out. I don't have any photos though. How do I take a photo? Pick up.
Maybe I have to take pictures. I love the giraffes. Okay, let's go. That's multiplayer.
And then this is online battle. I don't, that don't exist no more. What's this?
This is Fancy and Schmancies. Create a space station within the budget. This is DLC.
Egg School. Learn the basic controls. No. Munchies Manor. Roll up food to make
Cetus. All right, so this is this is DLC. No. All right, so where's like the regular just game?
One of these little huts over here. Just go to the cosmos. Oh, okay.
Fly to the cosmos. Welcome to the cosmos is an existence delish. Here you can look at all the
stars you made. Use a left stick then a A button to look closer. You can look at all the leaderboards
The queen wrote us a note about it. So here we go.
Hello, darling king. Hello, sweet Marcy. Here's a quick sketch of the leaderboards for you. I don't
want to see the leaderboards. For each star you make, Katamarius gets the data. But only if you
have an online connection. Data from all over the world comes to Katamarius. So who made the
loveliest star of them all? The leaderboards will tell you. Close look at each star shows its score too.
Simple. Sure. She sends us kisses. Great. Play around with it. It's the best way to learn. Sure.
Oh, and press the B button to go back to Princeton. Sure. Okay. Moon. Everyone's Katamari.
What is this? Everyone's Katamari. Okay. What's that? That's like a password hash. I got like
scared for a second. I was like, does that make my personal identifier? Um, I don't think I have to
be here. Oh, right here. Dangerous colony. Roll up dangerous objects. No, that's DLC.
Is this not DLC? Lovers loom. Roll up fabric to make Vega. DLC? I don't know. I'm just gonna
go on this one. This is also DLC. Um, how do I play just the regular game? Go to the first island.
Hubble horoscope? Does it matter? Well, I think it's meant to be played after, right? This is
DLC? What is this? Mechanical colony. That's DLC. Am I gonna ever find this? The green island? This
one here. It's all DLC. Delightful dribble next to egg skull is not DLC. Okay. All right, all right,
all right, all right, all right. Munchies manor. Here it is. Delightful dribble. Go. That's all
DLC, man. This is DLC. Oh, who cares? Welcome to the thrilling delightful dirigible. Roll a great
Katamari here and you get a satellite. We require lots of stuff that has to do with play, like toys
and dolls and games and balls. May as well make it a fun satellite. You have to go to Cosmos?
This is fucking DLC. He's doing it out of order. That's why I didn't want to do the DLC.
This is not DLC. This one isn't DLC. I'm just gonna do this one. All right, roll time. Candy store
full of sweets and toys and everything. Delish. Maybe we'll get a treat. Yeah, this is the first
level. Okay, this, yeah, yeah. Oh, the Katamari. If you roll up this big in this much time in
20 centimeters in three minutes, then it's a lolly good job. Roll up playfully. Today's challenge is
to make a playful satellite. We'll be back if you need us. Be good and play nice. Let's go. 20
centimeters. All right, get off the screen. One yen coin. Hmm, very encouraging. Yes.
I'm gonna try with the rats. I can pick up the crayons. Oh, I can't climb that yet. Oh, shit.
Come on, get me in this. I can't climb all the way in? Ooh, red crayon. Your inaugural crash
from E20. I have like one minute to do this. Shit. Pick it all up. 10 centimeters. All the way up.
Come on, there's gotta be something up here. All right, here we go. Into the fridge. All right,
just get off. Get off this and just start rolling on the ground. Under one minute remaining.
Get all the rats. Come on. Over to the toys. There we go. Hurry, hurry, hurry. I'm going.
I'm going. I only have like another one centimeter. Go. Oh, shit. I'm stuck. Oh, 18, 19. Come on.
No. No. I'm gonna lose. Go in there. Yes. Kind of fast. There's still time. Plump it up now.
This is like your first real achievement, yeah? The first time you met our size time request.
We are so proud. Maybe we'll bronze this one. You can return to the Princeton
by pressing start. From there, we'll make the Katamari into a slug.
You can also continue rolling to make even bigger Katamari. The choice is yours.
We're going back anyway. It's really soon here. Dang it, chat. What is this dang it, chat? Oh,
whatever. Hello again. Sputter Nick. Feeling orbital. Is the satellite a go? Did you get a
lot of play things like we asked? Space toys, you know. Got a Katamari to show us? Bring it out.
This is 20 centimeters and eight millimeters. Here's what's in there.
Playtime, snacks, and rich. The top ingredients are play things. Yes, looks like you managed to
get some stuff. So we asked you to roll a playful sort of stuff. Hello. There's no play in there.
All work. Playtime is number one and snacks is number two. Let me see with dull boy, doesn't it?
Were you even listening? Such a killjoy. Now for a bonus bean count. Well, let's see.
14 points. Is this on purpose? Like for a documentary? If you don't shape up,
we'll ask Prince for help instead. Is this for a documentary? What a dick.
Doesn't take up that much space. You're a party pooper. Learn to roll better. All right, that one's
done. What about over here? Nothing else over here?
The tea kettle? Oasis Cafe. All right, roll up drinks to make mercury. Welcome to Oasis Cafe,
a rest for the wicked. For you, more work. Help us make mercury. We need lots and lots of things to
drink. Like water, juice, tea, milk. Mercury should be plump and juicy.
Like peeled grapes. Mmm. What skin tastes weird. Off to Earth. See you later. Now connecting to
Seoul, Beijing. I didn't even see the last one. They did surgery on a grape. Time to roll. We're
in a candy store. Love mom and pop places. They're yummy and cheap. Are you going to eat that because
if you aren't? Oh yeah, right. The Katamari. If you're old to be this big, 50 centimeters
in five minutes. A little juice. Lots of drinks. Water, tea, juice. Don't drink too much. There's
no bathroom. All right, let's get every piece up here. Or at least 50, 60 percent of them.
It's a really good early game. Turn the music up. I don't know. Nobody even said that, but I assume
they did. All right, I need drinks. Okay, what about over here? That's a good start. Except
there's weird, there's like animals up here. What the hell is this thing? Frogs?
Present. Let's make our way down. It's a present. So what's in it? Do we know? I gotta get all those
drinks. 15 plus. All right, there we go. Can I get in there? That's a chunk.
I got like four minutes. You can relax. Bigger Katamari means you can leave the shop.
Does, but not yet. Not big enough to get that. Of course not. I need drinks. I gotta pick up
every pallet of drink. All right, let's get up. We asked you to bake. All right, King, can you like
fucking come through like the PlayStation 4 controller speaker? Not big enough. Loading eggs
give you. I need more drinks. Back in the store. Or at least over here. Does that really even matter?
I don't think it does. Water. Nope. All right, back in the store. Wait, there's like a grocery store
right here. Holy shit, that's a lot. Up on the shelf. Get it. I'm almost there. Am I on the grill?
Yeah, I'm rolling over the grill. Back outside. I'm gonna go back in here. No.
50. All right, all right. Back in the store. I want to get back in here. Can I get in there anymore?
I'm not sure I can even go in here. Ah, whatever. Not a strike. Reset the whole thing.
Eat the kid. You can't. I'm not big enough. All the candy apples. Check this out. Come on, I need those.
Yeah. 65. Your Katamari is as big as 6,000 squids. Let me do you a favor here. Turn the volume up.
You need that mercury. You managed to get lots of things to drink.
Mercury fluid. A quick silver planet. Got a Katamari to show us.
Oh, bring it out. This is the Katamari. A mere 65 centimeters. Snacks, drinks, food.
Top ingredients are snacks. Looks like you managed to get some stuff. Hardly any drinks.
I'm gonna do this on purpose. 10 minutes.
A trace of earnestness. Aha, master of puni hero. All packed and labeled for a trip to the
prince. Yay for a star. Uhuru. I think that's kind of cool, isn't it?
Your party pooper learned to roll better. Two for ten gold.
All right, where's that other, where's the weirdo? I know they're called cousins,
but I just, I'm going to reference some of the weirdos. That's bad. New place?
Okay, so that's on. Looks pretty cool.
Game is so loud. Sorry. All right, where's the next, what's progression?
Is it that? Oh, this is Cafe. It's this one. This is DLC.
Ain't nothing over here. Maybe the outside? Oops, noob.
Lady Luck Casino. There we go. This is DLC. I don't think it is. Doesn't it have a planet if it's DLC?
Roll a winning catamari and planet Venus arises. For that we need a lot of expensive stuff.
Metals, jewels, money. Are we right or are we not?
Yeah, the Saturn icon is DLC. Yeah, that's true. These games are just so relaxing.
Dead Rising 2 end game to this is like, there's one extreme to another. I'm just chilling right
now. It has a glam vibe. It's totally simpatico with us. Oh yes, the catamari. If you roll this
big 60 and 50. Let's go. Five minutes. Going straight for the cards, what do you think? Yeah.
Hmm, almost there. I felt that one in my chest.
Can I get the scraperies? Yeah.
Wait, ship. Yep, I can get them.
When you run to something and you go, can I get that, can I get that, can I get that,
the answer is yes. It takes a whole day and a day.
Wait, the game's allowed? Did he say something? There, I got you.
Is this guy talking? I can't hear him. He's kind of behind.
A bigger catamari means you go outside now. I don't think I want to do that yet. Maybe I have to.
Yeah, I'm gonna go outside.
Is this technically outside? No, this is just a weirder wind inside.
Shit.
Uh oh, I gotta make something happen really, really, really soon here.
Oh, crap.
This is so itchy. I can't pick up the bearded dragon.
One minute. I'm almost, actually, that's just...
Going back in the house.
Right here. Holy shit. Wow. Well, uh, I found a way to make that happen immediately.
Oh, go up the stairs quick. Go up the stairs. Look at that thing. I can't get it.
Oh, get upstairs. Look at all the stuff.
Yes!
And this shit just run in the direction and you'll get something. Oh, stuck.
Nice. Now you know why the game is so satisfying? Yeah, because you can go from
40 centimeters to like 100 in 12 seconds. Well, there's the expensive thing you wanted.
Gold bars, right? All right, this is from Venus. 90 centimeters. What do you got?
Games, rich, and snacks. Games. Yes, looks like you made it to get some stuff.
Hardly any expensive stuff. I just, that's like 50 million dollars worth of gold in there, man.
43 points. Stop pretending.
That's nothing to a king. Doesn't take up much space. First cheat code Venus. Cheat code.
All right. Sunrise Castle. I'm making a comet now. If you roll the right, the cosmos gets a comet.
But you need a lots of Japanese things. Ninja, sushi, sukiyaki, bullet trains, and kimonos.
They have a fancy for a classic kind of comet. Give us Katamari to write home about, please.
After the Rugrats. Yeah, there is a Rugrats vibe from that music.
Hold on. I need to hear it. Rugrats bop music. Rugrats. What are they called?
Rugrats weird music. Rugrats theme. No, no, no, no, no. It's, it's like, it's not just the theme.
The theme doesn't do it. No, that's not, that happens during episodes when they're walking
around. What you're referring to is that like happens way more often like this in the episodes.
Like Tommy will get up and start walking and it'll be like bop bop bop bop bop bop bop. Here we go.
And we need that chocolate.
I know I'm going slow, but sometimes you have to. I gotta get all the chocolates.
Got the tops and I can move back this way. Let's clear this whole rack. What do you say?
Am I already big enough to pick this up?
These things? Yep. I got a decent amount of time too.
Cookie dough. I can't feel like this is just gonna get to the grocery store.
He's like, I want that. I give me that too. I want that. I want all that. Let's get four cookie doughs.
We don't really, I think we need one cookie dough. No, we should get four.
Why? Because we're gonna, we'll make like, we'll make like 80 cookies.
I did the same shit when I ordered pizza. How many of you guys have ever ordered pizza before?
And you're sitting there going, all right, pizza. Anybody want pizza? No, I don't want one.
Do you want any pizza? You other person that's here? No. Okay, well I'm going to get two large
pizzas and eat like four or five slices and that's it. And then it goes in the fridge.
You can reheat pizza? Yeah, but it's never the same. I know some people love it, but
did I miss a present? Was I talking? Cold pizza? Yeah, but the grease like solidifies
and it turns into this weird blanket. I mean, I'm not saying I won't heat it up and eat it.
I also feel the same way about, for instance, like a steak and cheese sub.
It does not matter what the circumstances. I've tried a million times. There's no way.
And I think I brought this up like maybe a week or two ago. Someone brought up like eating and
eating one meal a day or whatever. If there's a steak and cheese in front of me, it's going to
be gone. I'm not going to have any leftovers. This thing could be like 16 inches long and it's,
I'm going to eat the whole thing. I never have a leftover when I have a
hero or like a grinder. Ever. It's never happened. Come on, get up there. Come on,
get the stuff on the top. Come on, look at how much stuff there is up here.
Come on, climb it. Don't look here as you go. I'm going outside.
Didn't you eat a grinder from your car a while back?
All right. You're making that sound like I opened up the hood and cooked it on the engine.
Technically, no. It was, I bought it and left it in the car and it was a turkey sandwich.
And I, it wasn't very good. I did not eat it.
Hey, don't do that. Disgusting. Yes, it was. That's why I didn't want to eat it.
You did it. You're a liar. You're fucking with my image, right?
It's been one minute. How big is it going to be? Back in the house. Is it going to be 100?
It's got to be 200. No, it does not. 200. Oh, this ain't happening. I'm going to do it again.
Nope. Wasted too much time inside. I messed around too much in the shop. Can someone please
explain this to us? Why do we always get our heart broken? What is with Kunihiro? Two little
self-esteem too much. We hear that common entitlement. Wait, we get it. It's a slacker
thing. What next? Video store clerk? Screenwriter? Whatever it is, we are not paying for it. Poor
Poro stuck with a loser. But if you make it big, we want the swag. This game is fucking crazy.
All right. Let's do it again. Yeah, I didn't, I spent too much time dicking around in the shop.
All right. Uh-huh. Two meters. I'm just going right down. Started me in a different spot.
Can't climb over that? I guess I can. Let's go. A wall up against a wall. Get them all. Can I pick
up those things? They're killing me right now. Milk bottles. Can't get a cookie dough. I still
can't. Go this way. I gotta get outside ASAP. Get to two meters. That's not gonna happen
unless I get the hell out of here. That was a good grab, but not enough. Let's get out there.
Wait. Not yet. I know. Stop dicking around the shop. I know. I know. But look at all this.
I don't even need to do that. I can't get the flowers. I can't get that. I can't get that either.
I can't get any of this shit. I gotta grow now.
There we go. Can I actually pick up these? Oh, this stuff takes so spread out.
Cars.
Move, pro. Please. Not stuck in a wall.
Get it. Go around the city. Yes. I know, but I want the cake. Ugh. Okay, city, city, city, city, city.
Two meters. I gotta, I got two, three minutes to do it. Faster, faster, faster, faster. I'm trying.
I don't wanna go in the water. Okay. Here we go. It's so slow. Move. Ah. I'm not gonna make it.
Guess I hit the people. I'm too small. I need to be a little bit, like, even for the kids.
All right, I'm at one meter. This is where, this is where it's steam rolls.
All right, big enough for people. Get it. 40 seconds. Come here. 1.5. What am I running into?
Consume. I'm not big enough. I'm gonna fail it again, I think. It's gonna be tough. No, it's not.
I can steam roll right now. Just go pick up everything. Get all these TVs. 1.8. No! People!
1.8, 1.8, 1.8, 1.8, 1.8, 1.8. All these kids. Oh. That was close. Off to Princeton.
I want Derma to be my sleep paralysis demon. You don't want any sleep paralysis demon.
It's scary. Do we get a little Japanese stuff? Two meters. Hey, Japan.
Ingredients are Japanese things. Yes, looks like you managed to get it.
What about our big Japanese wish list? I think he just is mean to you every time. That's bad.
Comet. All right, Japan unlocked two for 10G. That pasta sucks. I can't even read it.
Okay, where to? How about? Do I want to do presents? What about this train?
Hey, look at a new place.
Cloud nine forest. Roll up plants to make Jupiter. Let's see it.
This is your chance at a majestic Jupiter. King has never been more right in his life.
It's all Jupiter's bottoms. Yeah, what's going on here? I've seen like one.
This is unbelievable. Can you guys get one? Almost. No. No. Oh, it's not going to happen.
Some of you guys have usernames that are way too long that you're pushing them. I've seen some
sloppy Jupiters. I've not seen a complete true Jupiter though. Can't do it because of slow mode.
That means you have to work together harder. There we go. It pretty much happens. Yeah.
All right, we may be the glitziest star in the sky, but this is so yes. Five meters
in six minutes. This is a big one. I got to pay attention for this one.
Can I get cheating? Get them all. What are we? Candy corn? We are not speaking to you.
What? I don't even know what's happening. Why do you guys get so angry? Look out. Ayaya. Ayaya.
Why are we doing ayaya? Get that shit out of here. I'm just kidding. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm kidding. It was a joke. You can say ayaya if you want. He was serious.
All right, I got to pay attention. I think it was six meters. I'm not even close.
The whole, like, rabbit seance.
All right, I gotta go. Six meters. That's not gonna happen.
All those crabs. Ooh, Ashley. You got the cat? I did.
Ooh.
I can't break the glass and get the angel hair pasta with a sprinkle of olive oil and salt?
That's right. That's what's in there. Who sung this? I don't know. I think it says it in the beginning.
Rewind. This person just destroyed me. I got roped over five times by that same person. All
right, three minutes. Get rid of all the radishes. Strawberry plant, actually. Cool.
My favorite Ed Sheeran song. That's not even how you say it. Okay.
Can I get the bikes? Not yet. Get all the fruit. I think it was inside of this person's restaurant.
Two meters. I just ruined somebody's party. Can I get the little frogs? Yep, I can get those now.
All right, I need to steamroll this now. Here we go.
Almost in one minute. Banger right. I got the... Is it a clown?
I can get to the roof. I'm going to the roof. Get up there!
No! I'm not big enough. I'm not big enough.
Yes, restarted. Oh, four. I need six. Well, can someone please explain this to us?
Why do we always get our heart broken? What's with this guy? Too much is titled slacker,
loser, idiot, stupid. Is this more or less stressful than Dead Rising?
They may as well just be the same game. You're right. I know. More clocks to worry about.
Crap? No. That kind of started me out in a weird spot here. Oh no, here's this song again.
One in chat if you hate this song. Two in chat if you love it. I gotta hurry up. Go!
All right, end. Oh, oh, shit. The bunnies. They keep forever to turn on.
He passed. I passed? What do you mean I passed? What's with those bricks?
All right, I gotta pay attention. Good, good, good, good. I got a cousin!
I gotta get out of here. Please, just get me out of here. Congratulations.
I'm trying to get the pitch right. I'm stuck in a fucking wall.
All right, I have... Oh, this is hard. All the shocks. All right, get all these in a row.
Better than last time. Let me in, let me in, let me in. Oh, come on, I'm mostly free!
Turn around. Up. No, no, no! Oh, I'm so... In the water. I'm so fucking angry right now.
We're gonna lose again. We're gonna lose again. How do I get to the fucking city center?
I lose. This again. There's not enough time. I feel like I need like extra time. What? It's like
too long. It's possible. Hold on. It's possible. Fucking giraffe. Stop. I don't care. I have to
get out of this world. Old face to itch. Oh, all right. Just go outside already. I'm not going to
sing it again. If there's anyone that's curious. Move out of my fucking way. Those trophies.
Watching you do this actually aggravates me. You literally go pick up the smallest stuff where you,
German, NA5. Watching you do this actually aggravates me. You literally go pick up the
smallest stuff to where you could be getting larger. Try harder, German, the Cosmos, Daddy,
plus Spanky. Good thing I read that whole thing. Stop distracting me! All right, I'm distracted.
That's not good. All right, it's already, you've already fucked it all up. Oh, you've fucked it
all up already. There's lots of gold back there. All right, out. Two centimeters. I need to get,
just not much more. I've got three minutes. Get out of there. All the stuff with the water.
I'm going up.
Yes, I know. All right, three minutes. Two minutes. Bye. All right, now I gotta go up here.
What do I keep hitting? The umbrellas? Fuck off. You're gonna make me mad. Watch out for the
umbrellas. I swear. I thought that was a breakdown for the song. I was about to start singing.
Go! Get up. Pog. Pog. Pog. Pog. Pog. Pog to the chat. Pog to the chat. Pog to the chat.
Down the road. Pick up everybody. Every car. Every truck. Ducks. Might as well. Q.
Oh yeah. Game's pretty sick. You guys are so mean. Let me do this. Daddy's gonna be mad at you.
I want to hear this song again. I can't. I'm not gonna do it. Plants, flowers, aquarium. That's
what you wanted. There are hardly any plants in here. It's all of them. But there is a present
accessory. A little flower. Never good enough daddy. All right, that's enough. That's enough.
Spaghetti, aglio e olio. It's the essence of Italy. In case anyone was wondering.
Oh, fuck. Oh, my chest. Okay, that hurt. Okay.
Were you here like an hour ago? Oh, fire. Looks like fireman.
Welcome to the red hot roller coaster. Out of this crystal will rise the new planet Mars.
You can guess what you need. Hot, hot, hot stuff. Heaters. Kotatsu. Campfires. Cork buns.
The red planet should be piping hot. Freshly baked. Be warm. Be generous. And roll a big
Katamari up. This thing's probably going to be like 10 meters. We've come to roll in this store.
Kind of hot. Yes. Ew. Someone remind us why exactly we're here. Oh, yes. Katamari. We need
a nice hot Katamari. For that, you need to roll up the piping hot stuff.
We'll time you until the Katamari is 10,000 degrees Celsius.
What? It's not about size. Cold things will lower your temperature.
All right. Sausage. Bowl of soup. This one is the Katamari song with dogs and cats. All right,
this is all hot. We'll get the sodas. Baby milk. Why is baby milk so hot? I mean, maybe warm. Oh,
shit. I think 10,000 degrees. Hot soup. Oh, slow down. Hot buns. Hot coffee.
Hot tea. I can't see what the hell I'm getting. Okay. Bags of hot. I don't even know what they are.
Salmon. Does it hold? There's like steak dinner and shit over there. Something warm. It's miso.
We asked you to go feed the star ponies. The king is hungry. Every day. Let's go outside.
What's with the screen? Is it a roast pig? No, that's cold. Of course, they put the pig right here
next to all the freezer shit. Pizzas, cheeses, pizzas. Watch out. Is it dervishes? Yep.
Pairns. Fire extinguisher. Don't touch. Let me get the pig now. Forget about the pig.
Those are sodas. Don't go in the water. What are you thinking? Don't go in the fucking water.
5,000. Halfway there. What that is. This shit is absolutely real fire coming out. All right,
present. Slow down. That's ice cream. Don't touch it. Is that snowmen? This
sheep in the background is fucking with my head. Pick up the flames. All right, 10,000.
Nobody can listen to that. All right, I'm gonna go across the water just for a second.
I'm gonna pick up. Shit, it's so hard to see what I'm picking up. I just dropped.
Dropping fucking viewers, man. Dropping viewers like crazy. Dude, turkeys and shit. Oh, look at
this. It's done. It's over. 9,000 degrees. 97, 98, 99. Viewers increasing. Oh, shit. Viewers
decreasing. I won. I won. Imagine a viewer count was that volatile. I mean, maybe if it was
ants or something. The amount of ants that tuned in. He sees this as ants. No, I'm talking about
like just ants. I don't know, man. I have to stop laughing at my fucking side.
You don't just roll, Mars. You broil and braise it.
It's big from far away. Let's see. Food, cooking drinks. Lollipop. Nice. And a new, is it just the
same person I am with clothes on? 57 is not a passing grade. That's enough. Anything under 60
is a failing grade. Unless they've changed schools in the last 20 years, which they may have.
Have they? I'm gonna save. Should I get the lollipop? No, I don't want to get on the fucking train.
Get out of here. Oh, it's just in my mouth. That's sort of strange.
Under 65 unless it's a purge. What? No way. Anything new down here? DLC. What is dentist in my mouth?
Oh, I miss someone. Maybe to the right.
Go, go, go, go. Yes, there is.
Seadome. This is to make Neptune. The Tide Palace. Roll with distinction and the cosmos gets a new
Neptune. What you need are things from the big blue sea. Yachts, boats, fishies, maelstroms.
Neptune should be briny and wild and free. Yes, make a big catamaran and surf with the tribe.
For classes in your discipline you need to have usually 80 or higher or in an equal of credits to
offset a grade under 70. You usually can do that for like eight credits. What have they done to
our schools? What have they done to us? I don't know. Whoever is in charge. What do they do? In
my college everybody would, there would be no grades. There'd be no attendance record and there'd
be no grading. Everybody gets a B. People just show up and there's zero students in class.
All right, how big is it after 25 meters? No, but once a week I would have like a weird like
minute to win a contest for grading. I'm just describing. There's like a TV show on ABC that
is that right now. It's AP Bio with Glenn Howard. Yeah, like that's like what I'm describing.
Oh my god. It's a TV show. The guy that, Dennis from Always Sunny. Do I have to explain this or
am I about to get livid that you guys don't know who that is? This thing's gonna be huge.
Watches TV. Oh megalal. Well you don't think you watch TV? That's interesting. Everybody
has said they do not watch TV. I can get you with a got you right now. Would you like to hear it?
Where do you consume the Olympics? You know, the Olympics.
That's the Star Wars theme, but it's it's almost exactly the same.
The Olympics theme is almost the exact same as that Star Wars song. See, I just had to think
about it for a second. It's just the same song for a long time. The Olympics app is free.
They have like a table subscription. Here's about sports. I don't know. We'll see. It's
gonna be interesting because the the younger crowd, with me included, I'm the one. We're
not watching as much sports I don't think as our older relatives are.
Am I making this up? No, I don't think I am. Having like sports attendance
like the last five years or something. I can't be making this up. There's no way this is wrong.
My sources, there's just some drunk guy at a bar one time. NFL viewership is rising. Okay, I've
been hit by every car that came down the road. Am I going to be clear about that? I'm just gonna
get some houses here. You only put one in the road. If you hit one more car, I'm gonna leave.
Does it count if I crush it? That's what happened. Oh, look at this.
Almost there. That last one was so much harder. The islands. Go to the circus.
Pick it up. No, this is where it gets crazy here. All the cars. Yep. Out of the way.
Something round. You got Marnie. Yes. Am I big enough for the boats? We'll find out.
Not quite the boats, but big ducks. These ducks are huge.
And yes, they're boats. I know. Oh, almost. One more and I can pick up all the buildings.
13. I don't want 13.
Biggest one yet. The RVs up there. You can't get up there. I can get some of the houses.
Not all of them. I go back around. Come on and get the dog. It's stuck and over. But wait,
there's more over there. Stop picking up small things. Don't pick up small things. Stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop. You want to know how I read that coffee pasta? Watching you do this is so
aggravating. You continue to pick up small items and it's not. What's the king doing?
Resignation? Put that silly ball down and come over here. Oh, I failed? What did I need? It was 25.
I thought it was, oh, I thought it was 20. That's why. I was picking up the small items.
It was 25? Oh, that's not good. Well, I thought it was 20. Shit. I would have taken that a lot more
seriously. Damn it. Eight minutes. All right. No fucking around. Let's go.
Anyone notice this? I really like when Jerma like starts to understand like he has to really try
and go get through to the game. I always think it's so like inspiring when he just like starts
to do so well because he knows he has to win. First comment. Me too. I love that when he really
needs to get to the end of that. I actually have beaten Dead Rising 2 a bunch of times
and I can't believe he didn't restart. He played through just one and done. That's pretty,
that's pretty remarkable, if I would say so. New thread. Anyone just fucking loves him?
Okay, that's a wide, I thought he was like, is that a urinal? What is he riding?
All right. Okay. Let's put the image of him pissing himself.
Fuck. Bad timing here. I'm just doing so poorly.
Hello? Over here. I can't pick him up. Now I gotta actually really pay attention.
Now that I can get pretty much all this stuff in one time.
Greasy. Not there yet.
Holy moly. What? What happened? I gotta turn?
Let's get all the people sitting over here and then I'm gonna go over the ledge.
What am I listening to? That's pretty big Katamari. I know, I just said Katamari. I know.
Stay here. No. Now I gotta really string it together. Every road. Every car.
Traffic right here. I gotta go one more up. Up one more. Up one more. Oh, maybe do it again.
25, right? All this shit over here. Yes.
We're turning around. We're going back the same way. Ready? Buses. Can I not get the buses?
No, not yet.
That's really possible, actually. It's very possible.
Freeze. Help. I don't have to leave here.
18. Come on. Give me the big ones. Give me the big red ones. I'm stuck. Fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
Give me the whales. I got them all.
There's a lot of concentrated shit over here.
No, not choking. No choke this time. That's for another time.
Move steady. Oh, save. Jerma, you're huge. I don't know. Ocean. Plants. Yay.
I would love to see King of Cosmos and Smash Brothers. That'd be pretty great, actually.
He's too big. He's too big. Too big. That's the, that's the Ridley argument. Yay for a star.
Neptune. He's planet size. Something of a stage. There's a rainbow. Oh, it goes nowhere. What's the next level?
Egg school. I see one. I see two, actually. Interesting. Cool house. Maybe I have to go here.
Well, this one is just like the hot one is the cold one. Pluto. Honey, there are lots of cold, cold things like snow, ice, icebergs, fridges, and a cold Pluto for what we need to cool off. A wet washcloth planet, a dark room of a star. Anywho, slip, shy, can, can. Look at all those Xbox controllers. Oh, this place again.
Kunihiro. Remember this place. Yes, we have been here many times before. That's right. It's the money dimension. We understand that money can't buy everything, but it's nice to have a lot. Yes. So, anywho. One meter in three minutes. That seems hard.
One of the best controllers ever made. Picking it up right now. Can I get the ice creams that are on the...
What's going on? Hey, give me those. You dick. What?
Look at all these Xboxes. Oh, so this is where they keep all the ones at red rank.
I mean, that's an average household amount of Xboxes that you had to send back.
Alright. No, here's the sponsoring stage. I get to roll up cool things. The Xbox. That's really cool, huh? Can I get the Xboxes? Not yet.
I'm going to have to punch into this, because... I'm going to get to one meter. Here. Kunihiro.
Xbox, for death. Got an Xbox. I got multiple Xboxes. Did it! Lost. I got to get most of these.
Should I go back to the red ring room? It's too late. The Xbox 360. I mean, the hardware was dog shit.
But it was a good console. You must be freezing from rolling all the icy bits.
And I just got the Xboxes. It was cold? Weird. I wonder what I would actually say is the worst console
of the last three generations to count this one. You know, so like Xbox One, Xbox 360, Xbox.
It's probably the Wii U. Yeah. The Wii U was terrible. It's funny because
immediately after that, they have one of the best consoles they've ever made. The Switch is awesome.
Saturn. I don't even know the Ouya. The Ouya does not even count.
I don't. It doesn't. No, that's not. I think you only count as a console in a generation
if more than 200 people owned you. Because I could probably make a box that played like one shitty
game and it would probably have more people that owned it than the Ouya. I remember seeing them on
shelves and it was like dust was on top of them because none of them had been taken. You could
run your finger across the top of the 25 they had stacked. This is a stylish city. Lots of
pretty people here. Lots to see and do. This Katamari has a special rule. Go collect lots of
ring-shaped stuff. You have this much time to collect lots of rings. Bicycle wheels, car wheels.
Okay. How many do I need? It's not about size, but don't be tiny.
Are you mad at me? Pires, skateboards, before rings.
Power place. You guys like this one? Donut, score. Oh, it's Van Van.
We asked you to put the cozy on. Oh, that's a new character. I like that one. Get the bike.
Get people around. Cars. Yes.
I'm vibing with this one. How does that pick up all those people?
That counts. Dropping carts. What does that mean? Vibing. I see it all the time. At least day
of the day. Fun fact, this track is written by Avril Lavigne. What are these strange things and
why? You know what I want to do? Does the thing exist to keep your vocabulary up? You know those
things? Brain games. Brain age. Is there one where I can do vocabulary? I need to have my
vocabulary checked out. I'm talking about a little game I can play in bed. It has to be a game I can
play on my iPad or I refuse to download. No, no, no. Not a book. I don't want a story. I want a game
that I can play that gives me a word. For instance, let's say the word is fast and it has like five
other words that mean fast and you have to say which one is the right one and it tells you if
you're correct. Were it a crossword? No, no, a crossword is a thesaurus. A thesaurus game.
How do we gamify this? I need a thousand rings or I'm going to quit live streaming.
I'll go on camera and I'll say, ladies and gentlemen, this is the last one.
Thanks for everything. We're all the rings. We're just a bunch of like dead animals.
Like, no, no. Okay. I got to do this. These circles? These aren't rings.
Guys, guys, this is bad. How will anybody ever trust a single thing I say ever again?
I know his career is over. His career is over. His career is actually over.
What did I say? 800? Hold on. Hold on. What did I say? 800?
It's okay. Within five. If you're within five, that means you did it.
If you're within five miles per hour for the speed limit, you know, if you give the speed
limits 30 and you go like 31 or 28, 32, you're fine. You rounded up. Guys, I say that like,
I say that like five times a month. No, I don't. Not that much. I say that like three times a year.
I say that a lot. I believe in you from the beginning. Hey, it's been really good.
You've done that four times this stream. You know, you're right. I can't keep getting away
with that. How could I ever trust him again? I know. Seriously, you can't trust me anymore.
I'm definitely going to be the donut person. Make a montage of every time I've lied. I've actually
asked for that. That would take a long time though. Not because I lie all the time, but because
just think about the amount of time you need to go through and find every time that I lied
in at least the last five years. That's probably hundreds of times.
This is not possible. The video would be hours long. Oh, I would just, that video would be so
long that I would have to just play that video and mute my microphone and just sit there silently.
All right, I want to be the donut. Come here. All right, I'm going to be Ban Ban.
And I want to try the new clothes. With the camera on, yep. Just shaking my head.
Is the game audio too loud? I'm sorry. Yep, the horn and a backpack.
All right, we'll do, we'll do one more and we'll finish it up tomorrow.
See, we're on this trend the last couple streams of beating a game, getting halfway through another
one and you need to start at the next stream, beating that game, starting something else.
Always half a game behind, yeah. Is there a new one? I don't see anything new. Did I miss one?
When am I going to do NGU Idol? You're going to have to fight through a sea of people
who will do anything it takes to not see that on stream again.
So I don't have, I, what am I going to do about that? Roll up energy to make the sun.
Actually, this is a good one to stop on, I think. Dinaville. No, I can't do NGU anymore.
The game is cool. I love those little games like that. They're not stressful. They're just,
they're just there. Oh, also, I know that the feature sucks and it's a stupid shitty feature
right now, but I was thinking about just putting on a random TV show to watch with the Amazon
watch party when it comes out. Those of you that don't know, you can't talk and I just have to
type in chat. This thing, it has to be huge, by the way. That's enormous. I have 10 minutes to do
this. Why don't I do my own Amazon watch party where I go get royalty-free old movies and we
just watch one. Stuff that's just in public domain. That doesn't even matter.
Can you do that? Can I just watch like a shitty public domain movie from like the 30s?
That would either be a really funny fun stream or a terrible stream.
We both. Maybe we'll try it. What do you guys, all right, what do you guys,
the problem is, here's my problem. You gotta commit to that because if halfway, if like,
after like 20 minutes of that movie, I'm just like, I, this sucks. I don't want to do this anymore.
You can't, I can't leave. What am I gonna pause, cut the movie off after like 45 minutes? If it
sucks, just play Fortnite on your phone or something. Something about watching a kind of
current TV show though, it actually might be kind of fun to just sit in chat and just be one of you,
you know what I mean? Just experience it with you guys. We'll have to see. How does it work?
I don't think I even have access to it. It's like a beta right now, right?
Just recreate a public domain movie. That would take a lot of work. Can we do that right now? I
don't think I have access to it. Like a beta right now. I could probably request access to it.
But I would, I really wish I could at least talk over the movie.
I, okay, I understand that. I understand that that, oh, it's like a thing with copyright and
they don't want to have like the movie be shown or replicated again with it. What, what, how,
why does that matter? You guys ever watched a movie with your mother? My mother talks over every movie.
Why is that bad? What, I think people don't talk during movies? When you go to the movie
in the movie theater, there's somebody talking. They're like having a full-on conversation.
What's the difference? I mean, the face cam thing, maybe. All right. Okay. So because you're,
you're like not in the movie. You're not, you're not supposed to be part of the movie.
It's licensed out. It's the movie. You're not in it, but just talking.
You can't even talk over the movie. No, from my understanding, you cannot talk.
Like there's no microphone and you can't be on camera and ever whoever is viewing needs
to have Amazon Prime. Yeah, that's true. Broadcast the show to your channel or the movie. I mean,
that, that isn't that the quickest way for me to get like my channels suspended.
Now what do we need? Like 500 meters. Can I get houses yet? I get it. If they ban you,
just ban them back. Uh, that didn't work. All right. I only have like four more minutes to do this.
I'm not going up there yet. Let me get all this shit first. You're going to get banned
and then imagine that. Oh, why'd you get banned? Uh, well, I streamed the nutty professor
to my chat and we hung out and watched it and now I can't stream ever again.
That's too bad. It was fun though. All right, we're getting there straight ahead. Super fast
motion. Hit the plane. Copyrights only last 75 years. Yeah. Ain't Mickey Mouse going to be
up for a copyright soon. That's going to be really, really crazy. Imagine your local car
dealership having Mickey Mouse in the commercial and the guy that owns the dealership is doing
the voice. You're going to have to deal with that. Oh, come on down to Paul's, Paul's uh,
employee of all of land vehicles. Oh yes, it's me, Mickey Mouse. Come on down and just save
20% on the neck on your first purchase. That's going to be horrendous. Oh, welcome to Michael's
furniture store. Oh, it's me, Mickey Mouse. Thanks for joining us and I have you come in
by a sectional. You guys ready for that? I don't think you are. Oh jeez Rick. And some of them
aren't even going to give a shit. They're not even going to try. Mickey Mouse will be on screen
animated. That's right. With two purchases, you get the third one for free. Tell them Bob sent you.
All right. I need to, I need to get to 500 meters. I'm going to lose. It's going to be a
15 second pause. There might be. This is some cool shit though. Too bad we're never, too bad
we're not going to be able to see very much of it. It's still kind of possible. Maelstrom.
Not big enough for the maelstrom. What the fuck is going on in my chest?
Come on. I spent too much time talking about Mickey Mouse. 230, 220, 230. Halfway there.
I fucking lost. I swear. Didn't even make it halfway. Yeah. How the fuck did I do that?
This is Matthew from the other streaming platform team. We're reaching out to you for a rat pack.
We're reaching out to your rat pack. We're fans. I can't even read this. We're prepared to offer you
$5,000 a sleeve full of Oreos in a backpack. Free present. Am I not big enough to get this?
This is terrible. Bad RNG. What a bad place to start.
Backpack. Imagine changing platforms for a backpack.
I'll tell you, that thing better be made out of gold. Imagine selling backpacks.
What a bad idea. Did you guys buy a backpack? No, by the way, there's $79.99. Dude is right.
Sell a briefcase? Dude, you know what I would, you know what I should sell? Fucking not. Hey,
luggage. Everybody needs luggage. Yes, other cities. I know.
Let's go get the stuff that I didn't get over here. We're out. Which way is it? Straight left?
Like a lug? Yeah, like just like luggage. Luggage. Suitcase. Stuck. Where the hell am I going? I gotta
go this way. You don't get it. Just suitcase. You know what you can take on an airplane or on a bus?
Nice spot where I can probably do this.
Why is he not talking? I mean, I am. I'm just trying to focus. I think I have to get
500 beaters in seven and a half minutes. Six and a half minutes.
I'm still not big enough to get these. Mike is not muted.
Don't be cool. My girlfriend is watching. I got you. Does anybody know when, um, I think
as long as I go up this, I can't fake a voice crack. So I'm fucking cool, man. So I'm gonna tell you.
All right. 48, five minutes remain. Holy, holy, a present.
Okay. Better spot than I was the last time. Let's go get this city. Okay. Now where?
Really? I can't get any of those? What? 100. All right. Start picking up everything.
You listen carefully. You can hear him scream. Or you can hear the dust scream.
What was that? Am I big enough to start picking up islands? I'll be there in a second.
All right. Islands. To the mountain. Oh, this way. Dinosaurs. Here. 250. I'm fucking close.
Okay. What are you doing?
Maybe at 300. This will stop to. All right. Now the islands.
I can start picking up most things now. Just move. Flag. It's so hard to turn it. I can't even
control it. Oh, no. I don't want to be this way. Why would you move? I'm just moving. Get to a
thousand. Get the giant dragon. Dragon. No. If I don't get to a thousand, I will quit screaming.
Here's your new thousand. Career saved yet again. C-A-R-E-O-M-E-G-A-L-L. No, there's no O.
It's not career or. You want fries with that? Career. I'm kidding. I know how to spell career.
I'm not like from the fourth grade. Energy. Present. Pancakes. Sandwiches. Another cousin.
Another cousin. Peso. The sun. That's a new one, though, for a lot of people is,
are you pretending to be bad for a documentary? Cool. All right. I think it's a good time to call
it. Just under the seven hour mark. We will. I'll ride the train. We'll see you tomorrow.
I'll finish this tomorrow. We'll do the DLC levels and then, I don't know,
fucking mystery stream. We'll find out tomorrow. The Nutty Professor. We're not going to be watching
The Nutty Professor, unfortunately. Thanks for coming out, guys. See you tomorrow. Let us go
to bits and hopefully the sub credits thing is fixed. It was screwed up before. Remember the
credits from last time? They just didn't get pulled through. Maybe they fixed it. We'll find
out. Let's go over here. Might as well check it. It was worth a check. Dermavurb noun. Immortalized
in the bits and the insane gifted subs. Yeah, pretty much. But special thanks to Dark Soul.
Thanks to the 250, they say. I hope you're getting to the bottom of your doctor stuff and feel top
soon. You haven't even said your famous catchphrase. Have a Jerma 985 day in a while.
Get well soon. Yeah, I'm going to have, I'm going to know, I think, what's going on soon here. It's
been a real pain in the ass, but, you know, do what you got to do. We'll see. But thank you,
Dark Soul. Appreciate that. For real, though, thanks to the 250, Jerma, have you ever considered
to do a one-off stream of a Paradox game like Stellaris? I know they can be hard to fully
grasp, but I think they'd be some good RP and bit opportunities. Probably not. Games like that,
they sort of, they require, correct me if I'm wrong, don't they require a pretty large time
commitment before you can really get into the game and care about it? And you all know me when it
comes to reading. I get distracted and I lose interest really quickly with stuff like that.
Not just on stream, just in general, too. No books. I'm more of a run zombie over with car.
Kind of guy, you know? He's our illiterate streamer. That was a pretty good time rumor. Yeah.
But no, probably not. The last time I played, I mean, I don't, Mountain Blade is one of those
games that you have to kind of sit down and actually care about and play and learn and
there's a learning curve to it. And that kind of didn't turn out. That was all right. It was fun
for a while. It gets good $500 in. I'm sure it is. Just not really for me.
But thanks. Thank you, Doc, for the, whoa, almost just read one under the threshold. That's my bad.
If you don't know, we have, there's a threshold on the channel. Anything above 250 bits
is the ones that are read. And I fucked it up right there. I'm going to let this one slide,
though. This is from we ran or why ran. Thanks for the 249 bits. But hold on. I'm a dummy and
I used one bit to talk in sub mode chat. So that's okay. Whatever. That's like funny to me. So I'm
going to read this. Anyways, any plans of playing the MCC halo games or any other rhythm games?
I have Buster group. That's kind of waiting in the wings for some random day. But halo,
we're going to have to, we will enjoy the halo games together. I have never played a halo game.
I have only played halo to multiplayer, just sitting in a room with some friends.
I have never played halo ones campaign, never played halo to never played halo. I don't,
I've never played them. So I have the string of that series. Whenever I feel like doing it,
we'll see. I'm looking forward to it. Thank you. MGS fan for the $30 3000 bits. No message.
There's a lot of money. Thank you. MGS fan. Appreciate it. Hydra. Thanks for the 500 bits.
Please watch Joel's 3d movie maker movie. No link. You don't have a link here. How long is it?
It's 26 minutes long. There's a full episode of TV. We're going to set like a whole day to
watch this one. It's like 30 minutes. Well, there's your TV show. Maybe we'll watch that.
Not right now. I thought you many made like a little bar that I have to check. I wonder how
those are you that will anybody watch? Anybody watch his 3d movie maker streams? Did he have
fun playing in a 800 by 600 window in the middle of his desktop? It took him 60 hours to make it.
Yeah, my game takes time. Halfway through his files. Yeah, you have to mod it. Otherwise,
it's unbearable. I'm not even sure you can play it without the new tools. It's been a long time
since I've really gone in there and played with it. Talk about 3d movie maker.
Well, maybe we'll watch it one day. We'll have to watch it in chunks. It's legendary. Yeah,
rat movie two took like three weeks to make. And it was like nine minutes. There's like at least
two or three weeks to like it sit down and do it for a few hours didn't to get away from it. Sit
down for like three, four hours to long fucking time. That program is not meant to make stuff
like that. So I can imagine a 30 minute short movie. It had it had to have taken like months
of actually sitting down and like sitting working on it. But that's really cool.
I knew that they were I knew he was he was doing it. I know he was doing 3d movie maker at one
point. But I'm glad other people know that that exists and use it. Because it's a untapped gold
mine. It's good to see people playing with it. But that was from that was the
that was just a chat. That wasn't even a bit message. No, it was it was Hydra. Hydra 500
bits. Thank you Hydra 725. Dino pulse thanks for the 500 bits. Just the thought I'd ask what's
your experience been with Street Fighter accidentally putting 50 cents into the machine in the arcade
losing so badly that I've never played ever again. I don't I don't do fighting games.
You know when I just get really angry when a zombie grabs me in Dead Rising. That's the feeling
that I feel every time somebody gets a combo off on me. It's like God fucking damn it. No,
stupid. No games fucking not even that happens every match. Stupid fucking idiot fucking down
fucking idiot. Those games can be kind of fun. When you just have a few drinks and you just act
like a dickhead with some of your friends. But you always end up with the one friend that actually
knows how to do everything. And nobody wants to play against them. Because you gotta you gotta
room for four or five people. Four of you have no idea what you're doing. You've learned one move
and trying one small combo. And this this other this other dude can do like a 40 hit combo with
smoke. By the way I'm talking about me. That was me. Mortal Kombat 3. I decimated with smoke.
Cyborg smoke. That's the one. I love being the guy that knows the stuff. That's actually kind of fun
because you can tell everybody what to do. And then they look at their controller and they look
at their hands. And they slowly do the move you just told them to do. And they did it so wrong
that you're just mad in the chat. Because the streamer didn't go the way that you told them to.
And you just can't believe that they would miss the thing that they missed.
And then you do you watch as they crumble.
We struck a nerve. I'm sorry what were we talking about Street Fighter?
I respect those games but I can't play them. You played you played Divekick. Yeah but that's
it was just me and Star just dicking around. I respect them I can't play them. They're fun to
watch. VictionIshius thanks for the 300 bits. After this can you do a Simpsons hit and run
speed run? I would probably never play that game again. It's in the vault. I've closed the door.
I put Simpsons hit and run in the bank vault. I closed it spun the thing and then when it said
please create a password I just smushed my fucking hand all over the keypad. I don't even know what
the password is. Don't ever let me open that door. But thank you for the 300 bits. Hole of one zombie
thanks for the 500 bits. I think you mentioned some of your comedy influences before or perhaps
it was a voice actor. Did growing up in Boston shape that at all? From what I heard there was
a large stand-up comedy scene back in the day. Also what's up with Providence? Why if I ever
watch a film set in Boston is there a scene where some guy's brother coming down from Providence?
Like it's Mickey he's coming down from Providence. Maybe I'm just a lunatic thanks for the streams.
Because Providence is in Rhode Island and it's really close. It's just a state away. It's just
like another state for them to say you know you know when you go and watch a movie and they say
the name of your city it's for that's why. And you sit in the chair and you're like oh and you look
back up back to the people that are with you and you're like that's they said the name of the city
that we live in. Did you hear you guys heard that all of us heard that. Cool cool they said the name
of a town. I guys I do that now even with Vegas. Anytime I oh yeah yo uh give him a call yeah he's
down in Vegas. Oh I that's me that's where I live. I just watched the hangover movie and I'm
constantly going oh fuck I know what that is. Hold on where's that camera pin I yep yep I've been
there I've been there I stood there. Cool oh you guys see this I do it with my city yeah everybody
does. I don't know why I guess it's just cool to see it in like 35 millimeter film. It's all digital
now. German lied about 35 millimeter being films. It's still cool though. But um I'm not sure if
being around Boston is what shaped. I just watched a lot of cartoons and a lot of tv.
I was just a huge fan of just weird cartoons. I was a huge Jim Carrey fan. They're just animated
fun interesting people. But with the weird cartoons running stimpy pretty much anything on
Nickelodeon from 1992 to 1996. Thoughts on Jim Carrey in the Sonic movie? Um I don't I don't know
I've just seen like the trailer. He's getting older too. You know you see he's like he's something
he's like almost what he's 60. He's old. He's getting older. Yeah he's pretty old. Let's see
how old is Jim Carrey. Jim Carrey is he's 57. I mean he's still doing what he's still able to do
right. But yeah I just a lot of Saturday morning cartoon stuff. A lot of Nicktoon stuff. There are
others that I could definitely think of that have just shaped the way that I think things are funny
or interesting. There's probably I could probably go rifle off a bunch if I sat here and thought
about it. But yeah there you go. Thanks for the message. Thank you uh Lights Noton for the 250.
Hey Jerma love the Dead Rising streams. I really commend you on the all-in-one-go approach. Keep up
the great work. You're a treasure. Turn cam on. Turn the streams over. Turn cam on. Don't work.
Yeah I told you I get I get the the the Boy Scout badge that says I did it in one go.
You may have restarted. I didn't. I get that the stapler comes over and just
onto my chest. It says you did Dead Rising and Dead Rising 2 true endings in one go without
restarting the game. And it hurts a lot. And then I turned it and you're sitting there behind me.
You're about to get your badge but your badge is not that. I turned you and I just go
I stick my tongue out. Quick enough where the adults don't see me do it.
And I turn back. Oh yeah thank you. There's that Nicktoons influence. Dexter's lab. Yeah that was
the same kind of era. Early 2000s, late 90s. I know it's so easy to be like ooh 90s.
I'm a 90s kid. Oh 90s. But there were some really great great
cartoons and pieces of media and actors and comedians. It was awesome. So many incredible
shows and and were just airing during that period. I know everybody looks fondly down
on when they grew up when they were a kid and everything and I don't know some of you guys that
might be a decade younger than me right now in this chat probably have those same fond memories
of something. I'm trying to think of something that was like Minecraft. Think about that for
a second right. Imagine if you imagine if you were like 12, 13, 14 when Minecraft released.
Dad it's kind of a that's a huge thing. That was a really really cool thing. If you were younger
imagine 10 years go by and you look back on everything that's me talking about running
Stimpy. So everybody looks fondly back on the cool shit that they had. I was in my 20s in my
late 20s and I thought that Minecraft was one of that first alpha. I remember specifically saying
holy shit if I was a kid right now if I was 10, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12 years old
that would have been with me. This multiplayer you can build your own communities and houses and go
on adventures with your friends. I cannot even possibly imagine what it was like for some of
you guys to be able to do that when it came out and you tried to cash in with grandpa.
I used to carry a copy of Minecraft on a USB stick so I could play it at school.
That's so ridiculous. But then you think about what's the what's the new thing? What's everybody
going to get into now? If you look back fondly on how awesome Minecraft was for the years that
you played it when you were a kid. What is that now? Is it Fortnite? Is it? I don't think it is.
You know why? Because Fortnite is a battle royale game. Fortnite is not Minecraft. It's really,
really popular. But if the Fortnite if Fortnite is the Minecraft for the kids right now
and is the Ren and Stimpy for me. I don't I'm not so sure I like that. It's just a BR is not
need to wait a few more years. I wonder what the next big thing will be. Once BRs are done and gone
it was mobis for a little while. What's it gonna be next? Maybe the next iteration of VR
might actually do it. Because imagine you picking up a VR headset that's like a Vive 3 or whatever
the hell it would be. And you put it on you're like holy shit this is insane. This is this is
way better than the original vibe. This is like genre defining. And there's like a 12 to 13 year
old that's putting it on for the first time. We'll see. Just wait for Minecraft 2. Didn't
it already come out? It's Minecraft in real life right? I actually was gonna download it. I couldn't
all of my devices aren't good enough. I tried. Yeah Minecraft Earth. My iPad's not good enough
and my iPhone. They're both not good enough to run the game. I can't even download it. It
won't let me. I was a little disappointed. Yeah I have an iPhone 6. I want. You ready for me to
explode right now? Have I ever talked about this? It's the end of the stream. Who cares?
Have I talked about the iPhone SE? You ever heard me go off on that before? I don't think so. No.
This is fresh. Why is the only phone that's not a gigantic brick not only discontinued
but they're never gonna make one ever again. That iPhone 4 case, the iPhone SE was this iPhone
special edition. It was small. It was that iPhone 4 chassis. Small enough to fit in your hand.
Easy to go in your pocket. And they deleted them. They discontinued the SE. Why? And apparently the
rumors that the SE 2 is gonna be as big as a regular iPhone. Nobody make, they're all huge.
Nobody makes a phone anymore that's a 4 to 6 inch screen. That iPhone 4 size, everyone's just
making huge ass phones. Nobody, nobody is making a fucking phone that is a, I'm gonna say it,
but you know, I'm gonna say it. Compact. It's compact phone. I don't want a huge phone. I want
a small phone that I can easily get in my pocket and get out and put, I don't like this big phones.
And the SE was perfect. I am not kidding. Kim can literally corroborate this story.
I was going to get an SE and they discontinued it two days before I went in to go buy one.
We actually went into the iPhone store. I was like, oh, let's get an SE. Oh, we don't have those
anymore. And it was because I was like, I got on stage once every fucking seven months and goes,
hey, we're putting out new phones now that are all 1500 bucks each. And we're deleting
the last generation. Why do they have to delete, what is this, Hearthstone? Why do I have to go
back like two generations and delete them? Well, that's not in our standard decks anymore. The
SE was so different that I don't know why they didn't keep them around and everybody loves them.
It's not like I'm some weirdo that's making a big stink about the SE. If you type in like SE,
new SE, please God new, you get threads. People fucking want it so bad, but no, please scan my
face with the fucking 17 inch screen on my phone. I want my camera to be as good as like a film
camera. I don't give a shit. I want to be able to take my phone out of my pocket and it's so huge
and heavy and it makes a loud noise and I drop it on my desk. So everybody has to hear it and look
over here and they see my cool case. If you could kill somebody with your phone, it's too big. Just
saying. I don't know why they don't make him anymore. And I looked up other companies too.
There's a, uh, there's the, the, the, the razor, right? The Motorola, Motorola razor,
but there's a new razor coming out. It's a, it folds. It's a foldable phone. Well, that's really
cool. What's his, what is, what, what did you say? What did you say about that? You said that it was,
it was more than 15, $1,600 for that phone. Oh, okay. The iPhone SE was like 300 bucks.
I don't want a like $1,700 phone, but it folds. Is that worth 1,500 bucks? Sooner or later,
they're going to, you're going to have to start financing your phone like a car.
Now I got, yeah, I got a great interest rate on my phone. How much was it? It was 8,100 bucks,
but I found financing it over 40 years. Yeah. I have a 12% annual interest rate on it. It's,
it's pretty good. Pretty good. It would have been 15. Good thing my credit's so good.
I just want a goddamn telephone that can text and can play Minecraft Earth. You could buy a
trash phone to say, but I don't want a trash phone. I don't want a trash phone. I want a small
screen that has like apps, like small, doesn't have a big process, a long battery. I don't want
to go into Walmart and buy the $39 like poo poo wireless, whatever the hell the things are,
like prepaid, like $30 phone that is made. It's like a toy. It's like a baby phone.
I know it sucks even worse. Rip the whole, rip the covers off this conversation.
Rip the covers off. You know that they still make the SE, but it's for prepaid phones. So if you
want a SE, you got to go to get one of these prepaid fucking poo poo wireless phones and you
can't unlock them. They don't, you can't use them on another carrier. Just give me the phone and
just unlock it. Stop doing my best buys filing for bankruptcy. Well, give me my phone and maybe
we'll see. But like I'm going to help them. And then it has to be off of the right carrier.
Well, that, if you, that would, if you unlock that one, well, hold on a second here. That one only
works on the, uh, the Verizon and AT&T networks. That's not going to work on T-Mobile. Why? Uh,
because this is the way that I don't know. I can't tell you either, sir. And then you got the people
that bought a bunch of SEs. They went to, I just wanted to, I just wanted an SE. They went to the
Apple store when they heard about the discontinuation and they bought 10 of them and they keep them in
the seal. And then they sell them for like 500, 600 bucks, 700 bucks. It's sealed. I just want the
SE. It should be one per customer in the store. But then they buy them all. I don't even, where
do they even get these? Okay. Welcome to the, welcome to Apple store. How can I help you, sir?
I'd like to buy 15 iPhone SEs. Sure. Right this way. The 200 bucks new on eBay. That's a lie.
Those, those have like tracking devices in them. The person opened it up and like put a bunch of
viruses on them and they closed it back up. You wouldn't complain if they were buying 15 of your
shirts. You don't need my shirt to make a phone call. And my shirts also aren't $300. My carrier
is glue. All right, let's get out of here. Just so you know, where the fuck is the SE2? If the SE2
comes out and it's not a compact phone, I will leave Apple. Oh, wait, I don't care. I don't give
a shit what phone I have. I know that's like a way to pull. I'm going to take that seriously.
Jeremy, your phone is a tracking device. Yeah, I know my phone is a tracking device, but it's not,
it doesn't have a direct bug to like Larry's apartment. The guy that put it on there. It's
constantly recording. How do you think voice activation works? I don't have any of that stuff
turned on. Siri off, tracking off. They don't know where I am. All right. I just,
I'm just thinking of somebody turning off Siri and then being like, all right,
now I can go to Pornhub. Siri's off. It's the greatest surveillance device that the police
state could have wished for. Not if you turn off Siri. Don't you have to actively go into
like Windows 10? I remember doing this when I first go Windows 10. Don't you have to go into
Windows 10's settings and just click like, like, please leave me the fuck alone. It's crazy
because as much as this is a joke, I don't like being in a room that has an Alexa in it.
It's almost like I want to talk in a different room. It's like, Hey man, what'd you do yesterday?
Well, you know what? Well, you have an Alexa. I mean, nothing I say is going to be bad.
You're like, can we go, like, can we go in the other room? Like I just come up here,
like when I whisper into your ear, you should choose your words more carefully.
That's the freaks me out. I don't like Alexa. I don't like Siri. I don't like the Google
Assistant. I don't like them. I don't want them. I don't want them. I'll tell you the convenience
factor for being like, Hey, Alexa. Yes. Order 10 more cases of ocean spray pineapple juice.
Okay. It'll be here tomorrow. Thank you. But I don't, I don't like them. They freak me out.
Stop, Jerma. You just ordered that. Why are you scared to talk around Alexa when you tell us so
much about, too much about your life on stream anyways? Yeah. But that's me choosing to tell you
if I shit my pants, like I did three days ago and I was in my bed and I was like,
I just shit my pants. I don't want Alexa to know that. I tell my Alexa everything you tell me.
Anybody playing telephone? Oh, I shit my pants yesterday. Hey, Alexa. Yes, Roger.
Jerma shit his pants yesterday.
What is it? I don't get it. All right, we gotta get through this. No, it's different. When I like,
when I'm in a conversation with somebody, here's the difference. I am broadcasting to you right
now. I'm choosing to broadcast to you. If I go to dinner with Kim, that I'm not broadcasting the
dinner to you guys. I'm not broadcasting the dinner to my mother. If I'm sitting at the dinner table
and we're having a dinner conversation, that's not me doing a live stream. That's me and Kim
eating dinner. I don't want Alexa to just fucking lean in and listen to me. But why not? I don't want
somebody just like listening to me. If somebody opened my front door while I was eating dinner
and just sat in a chair and just that's what they did. They just sat there. Hey, who the fuck are
you? My name is Alex. Oh, hi, Alex. Can I help you? No, I'm just listening to everything you say.
Okay. And like Kim comes home from work and we just start to, you know, I don't want to have Kim,
can we go another? This guy is sitting in the corner and he just has his hand put up cupped
around his ear leaning forward. That's freaking me out. Can we go upstairs and talk? He hates Joel's
movie. What? He's writing everything down. That's what I'm saying. I don't want anyone just to
listen to me. People have like private conversations. I don't want like some random
Alexa sitting there hounding me. And you can always tell because if you talk too loud around one of
those things or if you like you're in the middle... Okay, let's say I was talking to the doctor. I'm
on the phone with the doctor and we're going over some very sensitive information. Yeah, okay,
that sounds good. So we're going to come in next week. I'll come in next week. We'll do that other
test. Yeah, thanks for all the information. Thanks for all my medical records that we just talked
about over the phone. Next week, adding to your calendar. What the fuck did you just do? No, no,
what? Or, or... I'm sorry, I didn't catch that. What did you say? I wasn't talking to you. I'm
plugging it from the wall. I'm not having one. Joke's on you. We're all Alexa. All right, how
do we even get on Alexa? I don't know. I'm going to tell Google Home you're scared of them. Sooner
or later, there's gonna be a service in the dystopian future where it is a it is a phone
booth that is padded and you go in and it's called the monologue box and it's just a spot for you to
go in and talk without anybody fucking being able to hear you. You go in there and vent,
but then it comes out that the boxes were bugged and they were being sold to Facebook and that's
how you're getting your targeted ads. Monologue box. That's my bathroom. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. You're right. Thank you. I go off on full like theatrical monologues in front
of my bathroom mirror or the shower. It sucks when you get caught doing that though. Well,
this happened recently. A week ago, I was I was on like a full-on just like just like theatrical
monologue just talking into the mirror in like a towel and I and Kim walked in the room and when
you have that scenario with you're just monologuing somebody comes in the room you have you you have
that one second panic ability where you either pretend you were talking to them pretend you were
singing a song or pretend that you are on the phone pick one and it better be quick. I didn't
have it. I just simply said you caught me just monologuing. Yeah, I got nothing and she's laughing
so that I was she says like that you're a weirdo or pretend it just didn't know you can't pretend
it didn't happen. I'm a talker though. I will tell you I am a monologuer. I even like go over like
just just scenarios into the mirror that aren't even real. I have to constantly be in communication.
Why do they got live live streaming so much? I just love just being in constant stream of
conscious communication even when it's with a fake person that's just me in the mirror.
Also fun tip if you if you want to get even weirder before you monologue into a mirror
lean forward put your fingernail up and make sure that your fingernails aren't touching
because if they're touching that's a two-way mirror and you're monologuing to somebody behind
there. Fun tip that's not true it is if you put your fingernail up to a mirror and your fingernails
are touching each other touching no space in between it is a two-way mirror. Why do I know
that? Because I don't know it wasn't like a book of fun facts. I don't know where I don't know.
I don't know it wasn't like a book I read. It was a book I read called avoiding the government.
It was from a reddit post probably. I don't know where do you do you guys remember every small
little random tidbit of information you've ever been told in your life? You just you just know
never monologue when there's a bird on your windowsill. That's a government surveillance drone.
Birds are government surveillance drones now? That actually wouldn't surprise me.
Birds are weird. Maybe they're just constantly just bugged out. It's just old technology that
we don't even know about. Birds are not real. Birds are dinosaurs. Speaking of dinosaurs I
can't wait to get my monitor lizard. I'm not getting a monitor they're huge they're too big.
I can't no I can't. Although I have been doing a lot of research and it does seem like
for a large lizard the the Argentine tegu is probably the best large lizard you could get
in regards to how social and and just chill they are. If you're in the market for a very large
lizard. What do you guys don't think what do you guys think I do when I lie in bed? I've watched
like probably 50 reptile related videos just I'm looking at snakes and shit but I don't
I don't want a snake. They're cool but I don't think I could do it. Clint's reptiles that's yeah
yep I've seen some Clint's reptiles videos. I'm cultured. I'm gonna do it one day one day soon.
I don't think I'm gonna get like a tegu. I'd probably get something small.
I would never I would want to make sure I was prepared for that. What if your reptile doesn't
vibe with Otto? Then they just they would be separated. They're not gonna be together.
Anyways we got a little bit more to go. Let's go. Thank you to where are we? Crispin3day thanks for
the 400 bits. Jerma lied about not streaming for two months. Thank you daddy. How do you still have
this username? This this feels like a username that would get automatically declined when you
make your warcraft character. How is this still here? Uh thanks for the 1500 bits. Dad they say
wubba lubba dub dub. Excellent excellent contribution. Daddy again thanks for the
thank you dad for the 1500 bits. 30 dollars total here. I really like the cough and puke mechanics.
Super epic that's talking about dead rising. We've got a video here. We have a video of ducks.
This is from anonymous. Thanks for the 500 bits anonymous. Hey it's the animal rescue guy here.
The duck you named and the duck italics named had some babies.
Here's a short 30 second video of it. Feel free to share it with chat if you want.
Oh yeah let's take a look. Baby ducks. Let's see. Uh they say also go back to
Resident Evil 2. It was top in your discord poll of games people want you to revisit.
What do the Claire storyline? Let me get this on screen. How am I going to get this on screen?
Well we're going to move to here because we're almost done. Oh that's how. Okay can I get this
on here? Let's go browser source. Nah fuck I have to do it in chrome. That's why I forgot.
I have to do it in chromegalelome. Actually no I don't. Uh what the fuck is going on?
Can you guys see this? I hate computers. You know I like toasted marshmallow jelly beans.
Why can't this be more like a toasted marshmallow jelly bean? You know what I mean?
Can just open please. Open. Is it this? Let me try this. Oh finally. It only took you like three
years. It only took you three years. There we go. All right let's watch a baby duck hatch. What are
you gonna say? Oh here we go. Oh my god that's what's happening right now. Oh there we go. It
just got its fold job. Yeah. There we go. Hi. I did it. He's trying to keep his head up.
The miracle of life. This is just like Jurassic Park. Did that fit you? Oh here we go. Oh my god
that's what's happening right now. Oh there we go. It just got its fold job. Wow. That was awesome.
Cool duck. Duck's name. The duck's name. What's the doctor's name from um
Jurassic Park? Doctor what? Doctor starts with an H. Come on give it to me. I need it. That's the name
of the duck. No not Dr. Schmikeson. It starts with an H. Uh the doctor from Jurassic Park. Dr. Ham.
What's it called? Not Dr. Henry. Dr. Hammond. There you go. That duck's name is Hammond. Hammond?
Little baby Hammond. Took you guys a long time to tell me that. You guys are usually quick.
Hammond's the old guy. Yep sounds good. All right good. Yeah little Hammond. That's good
shit though. Thanks for sharing that. Hey Kai. Thank you Kai for the 500 bits. A few months late
but still glad the birthday card brightened your birthday. It was incredible to see the pages
filled with art and messages from discord, reddit and chat in a week. It was insane. But I agree
with your thoughts on birthdays. Becomes a number in another day. Spent yesterday just hanging out
with friends and family but cheers to being 28. Hoping to continue drawing more stuff from this
community. That makes me ask what the heck am I doing? Take it easy. Much love. Hell yeah. Anybody
that contributed to that card. Thank you. It was overwhelming. And yeah yeah once you cross the
you can rent a car and you can be in a hotel room. They just sort of keep happening every year. That
doesn't mean you shouldn't celebrate it. At least in a nominal sense right? But thank you.
Man boy thanks for the thousand bits. Hey Jerma just wanted to share that after a pretty long
time of trying I finally found my first job in a theater. Theater? Like a movie theater or a
theater? Like a theater production. The pay isn't the best but everyone here is nice and I couldn't
ask for a better first job. It was pretty hard and my mental health wasn't the best for most of the
time but your streams always gave me a reason to be happy and laugh thank you.
That's awesome. He's on the screen right now. What do you mean? Oh there he is.
That's great though. First job. That's a pretty good first job to have. Nice work. Hope you make
some cash. And thanks for the 10 bucks. Take care of yourself. My first job was at a bowling alley.
That's a good first job. It sucked. Still though, it's still experience. Thank you Vilemi for the
2000 bits. Jerma I still don't see Jerma Psycho. I'm beginning to suspect you have lied to us about
it. I may have lied about it but it's gonna happen. I gotta find the right image. All right let's test
the credits. Do they work? Please? They do finally. It got reconfigured. Thanks to all the subs,
community subs, old subs, new subs, all of you. Thanks for being the oil and moves the stream
forward. Thanks guys. And thank you Vilemi for the 2000 bits. And again with for 300 here. I can't
believe Jerma is a weeb now. That was when I was singing the song. I wasn't singing the song. I was
just getting the pitch right. I don't even know how the song goes. He's grinding us into oil.
Hey Al Stora H2O thanks for the 250. Hey Jerma my birthday was last week but I finally have the
cash to send a message. Could I possibly get a QRS for the occasion? Yep. Yep. Oh I can't.
I can't do it. I have to be like shit faced. I got I gave you three Qs. I can only do that when I have
had like four glasses of wine. You got you got Q Q Q. Why do you back away from the mic so it doesn't
hurt your ears? If I went like yeah it would be so harsh. I only unintentionally hurt your ears.
Not intentionally. He backs away from the mic to breathe. Yep. But happy birthday Al Stora. Hope
you had a good one. Enjoy those Qs. Stinky Beaver thanks for the 250. Unfortunately I had to work
all night tonight and missed all of Dead Rising. I was feeling kind of bummed out until I saw you
alive. Thanks for making my night better. Yeah we finished Dead Rising. It was great. I got a little
angry at the end but that's how it happens in video games. You just sometimes you just get
frustrated and it's all good. That's what I tell myself in the mirror when I monologue tomorrow
morning. Thanks for sticking around. Avery dropped dead thanks to the 500 bits. Hi Jeremy
I just got off from work and I'm happy to see you playing Katamari again. It's one of my favorites.
It's very good. I don't know what to say in this message but I love you and your content spreading
good vibes and much love to you and everyone in chat. Also can you say hi to my discord server
who also watches you. They're called poop shitters. That better be real. Thank you. Thank you Keith
King Crimson for the 250. Really happy that you're playing more Katamari. It's my favorite game
series. Also if you do a public domain movie night you should set up a green screen face cam
and a movie see graphic so it looks like mystery science theater.
At the back of my head that would be so dumb. Or just I'm at the movie theater.
Make it a whole bit about it. Like throw shit at the screen. Get angry. Stand up. Like cause like
a problem. Yeah that sounds like fun. Maybe I'll do that. But thank you Keith. Hey hoops thanks for
the 500 bits. Have you considered playing bombastic the dice puzzle game. Keep up the fun content by
the way. Love watching you. I don't know what that is. Bombastic. I'm not sure. Mostly lost.
Thanks for testing the bits. I'm not going to read your message but thanks for the test.
Test works. Apple shift thanks for the 250. Hey have you had any wild dreams lately? I have wild
dreams all the time. I just don't remember them and I always tell myself I'm going to make a
dream journal where I get up and just turn over and write. But the one or two times I've tried
to do that I've woken up from a dream and then immediately want. All right do you guys do this
too? Some of you have to. Right when a dream is over you go holy shit that was fucking crazy.
That was so weird and interesting. I'm gonna go back to sleep and rewind and go over everything
that happened. And then you fall back asleep. And then you get up and forget everything. Yeah
okay. So I do every time I do that I don't turn over and write. I want to I want to re-watch it.
So my first thought is not to pick up like a notebook or a iPhone or something and write
something. I have some really weird dreams too. It's too bad. But yeah I do. Hey Zeg heart thanks
for the 250. I recently discovered that my 14 year old cat is seriously ill and I'll probably
have to say goodbye to him soon. I've been feeling completely heartbroken so thank you for cheering
me up a bit with your streams. Sorry to hear that. 14 is a nice long life though. Always remember
that. Hopefully you still have a good amount of time left. I'm really sorry to hear that. Thanks
for hanging out. Remember the time that you did have. More than a decade is such a long time.
The memories don't matter. Thank you for sharing. Thanks for the 250. Gnarly thanks for the 250.
As much as I'd love to watch you revisit Dead Rising 3 after playing the first two,
what if you went back to that Rome game you abandoned that was the sort of inspiration
for Dead Rising with the green blood enabled because my mommy won't let me watch without it?
Probably not. It's good to see the inspirations but sometimes the inevitable end product is just
way better than the prototype I guess beforehand. This is kind of one of those scenarios where
I play Dead Rising and Dead Rising 2. I wouldn't want to go super super backwards
to play their original game there. Interesting thought though. The shadows of Rome is by the
same people that made Dead Rising. I think it's by the same group of big directors or something.
Something like that. But yeah. Thank you Gia Norv for the 500 bits. German my first stream here.
What's up? Been watching your stream highlights on YouTube more so. Glad I subscribed. Seen a
couple people ask but if you haven't answered are you gonna play Code Vein? I wanted to. It just ended
up being one of those things that I got it, I bought it, and then it just ran out of gas before
I even left the parking lot. I want to get in that car but I have to walk gas from the gas station
to that car. There's just so much stuff, so many games, so many things I would want to stream.
But there's going to be a lull in stuff that I don't ever think that a game will never show
up on this stream because once we hit those times where two, three, four months go by and
there's nothing new to do, stuff like this would make an appearance. I play everything on this
stream. There's not very many things that I would not do. Maybe like a full game of Civilization,
something you would never see on this stream. Or strategy games. But even still, I don't think
that's even true though. Joel's movie is another one that comes to mind. Yeah. But welcome to your
first stream. I hope you liked it. Heroes of Might and Magic 3. I know, but that's a little
different. Heroes of Might and Magic 3 is like different than like FTL. It is. Or like Civilization.
Salty? He's fucking salty. What the fuck are you talking about? Fucking goddamn fucking thing. No,
I can't do that. Half of the people here right now may not have been here like eight hours ago.
I can't do like the stupid fucking dumb fucking dumb fucking stupid. I can't do that right now.
There's a huge amount of context to that. Not really though, but still. But thank you Geonov.
Geornov. Welcome to the stream. Hope you enjoyed it. Modest Narcissist, thanks for the 500 bits. Hey
Jerm, I'm trying to lose weight for my first attempt at cosplay in May for a convention.
I've already made some small progress, but I was wondering if you had any fitness or diet advice
that you could impart on to me? Thanks in advance and have a good night. First of all,
it's a great first step to try to lose a little bit of weight. Hopefully your cosplay in May
turns out great. In regards to losing weight, I unfortunately cannot give you much advice
because I've been the opposite. My whole life has been I need to try to gain as much as I can
and keep and maintain weight, not lose it. So I don't really have very much advice to give you
on the losing weight front. Do not eat tahini if you're trying to lose weight. Do not listen to
anybody in this chat. Tahini, if you weren't here, tahini paste is the most high dense caloric food
in the world. Do not eat that. But the real easy shit is just don't drink. It's just liquids take
up so many calories people don't even understand. Even shit like drinking orange juice, juices,
sodas. If you just cut out sugary drinks, somebody already said it, but I'm going to
parrot it because this is the way it is. If you start replacing all your high sugar drinks with
water or tea or even coffee, if you drink coffee, that's fine. Just don't put a bunch of junk in it.
You know, you can get a coffee from like a Dunkin Donuts or even a brew to the house.
You can put a sugar in there. You can put like a flavor pump in there, but just don't overdo it.
Don't go like six pumps. Cutting out soda and only drinking something like water.
There are, that is hundreds and hundreds of calories a day that you're not taking in. Diet
soda. No, I don't drink diet soda. Diet soda may not have sugar, but it still causes an insulin
response. It's just as bad as normal soda. I don't, I don't, I don't know the science on all that,
but I just know that diet soda is, you know, you're not really doing anything for yourself.
If you're drinking diet soda because you want to lose weight or because you want to drop calories,
you're still drinking soda though. You're not like solving that problem. Diet soda
fucks up your system. Yeah, but, but more so you're still drinking soda and it's so easy to
just go back to drinking a regular soda because you still drink soda. It's like snorting coke,
but it's healthy. Coffee's terrible for dieting because the caffeine messes with your dietary
instincts and appetite and it triggers insulin. Yeah, drink tea, but that's, it's rough to say
that to somebody though, because coffee is so, I love coffee. I love coffee. And if somebody told
me, dude, you can't drink coffee anymore, I'd be like, you can fuck off. I'd be like, nope,
but sometimes you have to do what you have to do. I just love coffee. And eventually here,
probably soon I'm going to have, I'm going to probably have to change my diet a lot
because I'm getting older. You can't just like pound coffees and fucking creamers. I don't drink
cream, but you know what I mean? It's like not good for you. If you drink a bunch of coffee,
it's just, I don't want to have like hypertension or something later on in life,
but unfortunately I can't give you that much besides general stuff like drink more water.
And that's so basic. You could find that on any blog post. I unfortunately can't help you with
weight loss. And I don't want to tell somebody, well, here's what you do to lose weight when I
have no idea. I can't do that, but I wish you luck. There's tons of great literature out there
for losing weight healthy. Good luck in your, for your convention cosplay. Hope it's a good one.
Thank you, modest narcissist. Reaper, thanks for the 250, Jerma. I have an old S E. Do you want
to buy it? Now you've bugged it. Nope. It doesn't matter. You could have that. I could have that
cleared by like a tech that it's not bugged. It's still bugged. You bugged it. Thanks for the offer
though. And then finally we have anonymous. Thanks for the 300 bits. Hey Jerma meant to mention that
those baby ducks will be combating an invasive bug species that's arrived on the East coast.
The duck you named will have thousands of offspring to help the environment.
Also, if you ever want to know a good reptile, ask me. I've owned everything and I have over
7,000 gallons in reptile enclosures alone. Holy shit. That's a pretty crazy couple of sentences.
Prepare the ducks for battle. Also, when's metal gear revengeance DLC?
Well, to be fair though, did I ever say I was going to play? Yeah, I probably did,
but I don't know. Like, Hey, I just finished the game. Will you play DLC? Maybe. Yeah, maybe.
No, you can be floaty and aloof with DLC in my opinion. He promises too many things.
You don't have to complete DLC because it's added content. You can be floaty with it. You can.
He just hates video games. I think I did say that like three times during the Dead Rising stream.
Oh well. Just like Dead Rising 2. What's the plan for tomorrow? We're going to finish Katamari
Beautiful. And then after that, Mystery stream. We'll see. Got a few things we can do.
And I'll see you tomorrow. Same time, same place. Take care guys. Thanks for watching as always.
Thanks for sticking around. For someone who makes a lot of wild references, he sure doesn't want to
make the classic guild he promised us. Yeah, but I opened up Warcraft and I got to like level seven
and I said, fuck this game. I'm not doing this again. I just didn't want to do it and it was
like a lot and it takes a lot of time. It takes a huge amount of time. It's a fun idea. I tried and
then I said no. So that was a lie. No, that was an attempt. I downloaded WoW Classic. I paid for a
subscription. I opened the game and I had the intention to make a guild and I got to level
seven and I said, I'm not doing this. I didn't lie. I gave up. There's a difference.
Bring back the polygraph. Polygraph stream two. Giving up is worse than lying.
Well, whatever. So what do you want me to do? You want me to force myself to play WoW Classic
to get to level 60? So I can open a guild bank and we can what? So we can just
put like 500 stacks of thorium in there? I'll get to 60 and I probably won't play the game anymore.
You know what would happen? I would have put a bunch of time in and got to level 60 in WoW.
All right, level 60. Let's go guild. And then I would have just fucking flaked and never
played the game anymore. I would have just quit. Is that worse than giving up at level seven?
I think so. You would have 5,000 people carry you through it on a golden carriage.
I don't want to do that. I don't want to do that. That sounds like so not fun.
What do I do? Watch people kill mobs and like hand me items? I don't want to do that.
I would just be like, all right, guys, I got to go. I'm going to go. I'm going to log off.
Just carry him around. I wouldn't even want to stream that. Oh, that would be so.
What would I even do? What would I even talk about? We could just fan you with giant leaves
and feed you grapes. The highest bit donator gets to be the one you slash follow.
That would be the dumbest stream ever. It wouldn't even work because if I,
if there was a quest I was doing and there was like 100 people, 200 people around me,
I would never complete a quest. All the mobs would be dead and people would just be like
trolling and killing mobs. I would never complete a quest. Please just do a carry me around stream.
Are there any other games where I could just be like carried around and just do nothing and
just get stuff? What other games exist that could do that? I just don't have to do anything.
The MMO streams. Yeah, they were a mess. They were fucking hilarious.
Rust. All right. Get in the Discord. Let's wrap our brains around this. If you can find me a game
where I can just be the sultan that just sits on a throne and just doesn't do anything and has the
game played for him and everything is given to me, everything, the title of that stream would
just be called the sultan. The title of the stream should just be called Lazy Fuck.
The Lazy Fuck. Does anyone really want to watch that stream? I know I'm sitting here laughing,
but I don't think very many people want to watch the Lazy Fuck stream.
And by the way, if I die, the stream ends. No bullshit. I will turn the stream off if I die.
If I have to even exert any fucking force. All right. Let's look into it. That sounds like fun.
We need a game where people could assassinate you. Okay. Somebody mentioned rust. If I buy
like a 500 person rust server, is that possible? No, this is so stupid. All right. Let me look into
this. Floats of my ideas in the discord. It could be Minecraft, Roblox. Yeah, I'm actually
going to look into it. Just do Dark Souls 3 with phantoms. No, I would want there to be at least
a hundred people on screen. All like just doing everything for me. I want people whose sole job
is to like chop wood and bring it to me. Even if they don't even need it. The Lazy, the fucking
Lazy Sultan stream. How many people can you have on Minecraft server? Can you have like
a thousand people on a Minecraft server? Okay. How much is a 1,000 slot Minecraft server?
It's like 300 bucks a month. It would be for one day. Oh my God. I need to
think about this a little more. This sounds really funny.
Multiple rounds. We could even do multiple games. Planet side too. No, I ain't doing that again.
If you die in the first 10 minutes, that would be such a waste.
And I'm not even saying bye. The second I die, the streams off. Like you killed me and like I'm dead
in real life. You guys need to work together to make sure that does not happen. The second that
my HP is zero. Oh, off. See you next time. He's going to jump in the lava for fuck's sake.
All right. I'll see you guys tomorrow. Sleep on this idea. It's fun.
Yeah, no bits or no just the stream will be offline if I go to zero.
See you guys tomorrow. Have a nice sleep. Good night.