Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here again with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary like you know it.
Using the Soldier in this gameplay with the default rocket launcher, the equalizer, and the strange shotgun.
And I think for the remainder of this gameplay, I'm going to speak like this.
Casey Casem. If any of you know who Casey Casem is, that's kind of how we used to talk.
I'm Casey Casem. He was real weirdo.
But anyways, yeah, this is a gameplay commentary on Nucleus. King of the Hill Nucleus, even though there is not another type of Nucleus.
I wish there was though. Imagine if there was like five control point Nucleus.
Alright, let's get right into this here.
Rocket jump over to the middle point here. What was I doing? Can anybody tell me why I did that?
I'm one of those people that when they rocket jump, they do it at completely inappropriate times.
And when you really shouldn't be doing it at all. I never rocket jump when I'm supposed to.
I only rocket jump when I'm just being like an idiot.
Oh hey, I can just like jump over to the middle point.
Yahoo! Woohoo! Yeah!
I'll never do that again, I promise.
So I'm spamming over at the middle point here. No one's even gotten onto the point. Three minutes, three minutes.
This was also on a 32-person server.
And if you're aware, 32-player servers and Nucleus, or any King of the Hill map for that matter,
is pretty much complete and total insanity.
It's just crazy. 16 on 16, especially when they're full, it gets out of hand so quickly,
where you'll be walking out of the spawn and just... everything just kills you.
Ridiculous. I hate playing on King of the Hill maps with 16 on 16.
But you know, you're given a take. It can be fun sometimes, especially if you're playing a spam class.
Because once like 15 people get on the point, you can just lob four stickies over and kill a million people.
So we now have the point captured. 2.35 minutes left to go.
And I gotta commend this engineer that's behind us.
You'll see where the dispenser is. Absolutely fantastic.
I've never done this, but this is a great idea. It's level three.
And it's just healing everyone that comes over here. It's awesome.
This is one of the reasons why we're continuing to win, because this engineer has a fantastic dispenser.
Really guys, try that out. I'm excited to do that the next time I'm on this map.
You should be too, because it looks really fun.
And engineer's the best class in the entire game. Let's keep going, huh?
So as you know, some of you don't, but a lot of you do, this month is breast cancer awareness month.
And I really want to do something besides getting pain trained in the face, like just happened right there.
I want to do something interesting. I want to do something to kind of support the cause.
And it's not going to cost anybody any money. Just something really interesting I wanted to try and do.
So what I want to do, guys, is at some point in the next, probably the next few days or the next week or something,
I want to get a full server in my server, line up everybody, both blue team and red team,
somewhere maybe in bad water, a big, big open map, and have 32, actually I have a 24 person server,
so 24 people standing kind of in a group, all with a painted pink hat on.
And I want to just take a picture, put it somewhere, post it online somewhere just to say,
hey, look at Team Fortress 2, the community, we're all for this.
And I think it would be really interesting, because pink is in the game, you can paint your hat.
So if you don't have a pink hat or if you don't have pink paint,
maybe we could set up some type of donation system where if you have pink paint, you can send it over my way.
Or, guys, I'm willing just to buy 24 pink paints from the store.
It really doesn't matter to me. I think it just would be something really fun and interesting.
So yeah, we'll figure that out as time goes, but that's just something I wanted to throw out there,
something I wanted to do. We'll see how that goes.
And also, I'm going to be upping my upload schedule. It used to be about three or four times a week.
Now, guys, I'm going to try and really, really push for four or five uploads a week.
I know you guys want me to do more content. You guys ask me.
I get PMs all the time saying, hey, Germa, you should really upload more than three times a week.
And I can totally understand that, guys. I completely understand.
I'm going to try my best to keep this channel inspired, to keep the quality bar, the content bar,
as high as it can be and pump out five videos a week.
Maybe I'll take a break here and there one day or something like that,
but I want to do at least one video every other day.
I never wanted to get to a point where the channel is just me pumping out videos just to make them.
When I sit down, guys, to make a video, I want to make sure I'm really inspired to do it,
because this is a whole lot of fun to me.
And I would never want this fun to get dragged down into hell.
So don't expect any quality degradation.
This is just me telling you, be on the lookout for more content, baby.
Go watch the 4,000 subscriber video.
It's probably not in your sub box anymore, because I'm an idiot,
and I uploaded it at like one in the morning.
So it'll probably be knocked out of your sub box by now,
especially if you like Burger Boy, because Burger Boy makes his triumphant return as the egg.
So what are you guys doing for Halloween?
That video was kind of made in the spirit of Halloween.
What is your costume going to be, and do you have any ideas?
Because me, Burger Boy, an exoskeleton bug body who you've never seen or met before,
we're trying to figure out our costumes.
It's getting kind of late, so let me know what you're doing and your ideas.
That is going to be the end of this video, guys.
Thank you so much for watching. I really appreciate it.
I will see you all next time, and take care, everybody.