Hey, what's up? Yeah, um, uh, yeah, why are you acting like I delayed the stream two days ago?
Delayed it again yesterday and then came in today and reverse delayed back to today.
I think I didn't do that. This is outrageous. Yeah, I figured. All right, so I got some stuff done
that I wanted to get done. And I did say, wait, well, maybe we'll do an Omega gaming weekend.
No, no, let's just go now. I'm ready to hang out now for a little bit. Sometimes I, you know,
you just get the urge. You want to go. So that's exactly what we're going to do. Welcome back.
We're going to play Xbox games, original Xbox. The plan is still on Saturday to play Elden Ring
with Ster. So that's still the plan. You smell what you don't have. You have no idea what I
smell like. You have no idea. It's called old piss. Anyways, you need to change your pin tweet.
I don't think it's ever going to happen. You know what? I, my pin tweet will change once.
Uh, honestly, probably when grotto beasts is like ready and here and ready to go,
that will be the pin tweet very soon. A lot of things in 2023 that I just, they're very exciting
and I don't know how to tell you them, but I've seen a lot of copiums.
Uh, just wait, just wait. It's, I, I'm not talking. I'm not saying anything.
I'm not going to say anything. All I'm telling you is that grotto beasts is imminent,
very imminent to a point that I think a lot of people might not understand. I think a lot of
people like, Oh yeah, he keeps saying it. Oh, it'd be a few months. It'll be a few months.
Grotto piece is imminent, imminent, but I want to give you a real date when I have it, but it's
imminent. No, I didn't just learn that word today. I've said imminent a few months ago when I talked
about this as well. I didn't just find that word out. I know words guys. I know words.
I have at least a higher functioning caveman intelligence. I know words. I have a vocabulary.
Media, imminent. Oh, what, what? That word, imminent media, imminent.
Ooh, I say that word now too. You should play dark and darker. I'm, I'm going to,
I just have to find the opportunity when I want to do that. Cause that game has gone into alpha
for like a weekend, come out of the alpha weekend, go back into an alpha weekend. Right.
When it's in beta, when the game, when I can just play the game whenever I want,
that's when I'll do it. I, is it a closed beta? I really do not have been really paying that much
attention. I will be honest. Why do you hate the last of us? I've never played the last of us.
No, that's a lie. I believe I'm in a long time. So let me see if my memory can piece together.
I think I did the PlayStation now stream feature connected to a friend and like played the game
through their game. Am I making that up? It's been a while. And I think I played like the first 40
minutes that way. PlayStation had this feature where you could like stream the game to somebody
and they could take control of it. It was very weird, very weird system. Read this, read this,
read this relax. Will you relax? It's share play. Yeah. So yeah. Okay. So I got like a,
I got like a fucking 1500 bit rate share play version of the first 40 minutes of the last of
us. I don't know. I just didn't play it. I didn't play it. So what? Oh, well, I didn't play God of
War either. Well, I played the first hour of that. It's phenomenal by the way. That's the worst way
you could have played it. Yeah. But what, who cares? But hope you're doing well. What a fake fan.
I had never told you I was a fan of the last of us. When have I ever talked about that?
Has there been a stream where I've sat here and gone, oh, last of us. Let me just, let me just
tell you all about it. Oh, I could take, I could talk for hours about last of us. That's never
happened. Hurry up. You relax, settle down. You, I, you did. I remember it. That was actually kind
of funny. That actually would be really funny. If somebody has like a clip from like a few years
ago or something of me being like, Oh my God, it's so good. I just never played it. That's funny.
I will accept that if that, if that's the case. But anyways, yeah, we're gonna play more Xbox.
We're going to start kind of right where we left off with Obi-Wan. We're not going to play Obi-Wan,
but the one that's coming up in the list was the DaVinci code. DaVinci code. Are you guys ready?
Are you ready to play a little bit of Xbox? And then again, next time I'll see you after this,
the weekend stir randomizer Elden Ring co-op stream is still happening on Saturday and Sunday.
Well, Saturday. And then if we, you know, we're giving ourselves the option to do it Sunday as
well. Cause what if we're just not having any fun at all? That's the plan. And let's go. I think
we're ready to get rolling here. Just make sure this is plugged in correctly. Let's see. Can you
see it? By the way, haven't seen this movie either. I've never seen this movie. I've never, I've never,
it's a book, right? Is it a book or a movie? I don't know. This is the DaVinci code video game
based on the movie, based on the book. Okay. All right. I'm ready. You guys ready? The DaVinci code.
Whoa. New game. Okay. I would like to create a save game. Anybody played this? Is this any good?
Tom Hanks is in this. I, I, okay. Here's the only way that I would say I think Tom Hanks is in this
game. It's stuff like, Oh, what are you talking about? Huh? We have to get over there. And it's
just stuff from the movie that they just kind of sentence mix together, right? There's option one.
Option two is it's an impersonator. So I, I don't think this is, if it's Tom Hanks, actually like
Tom Hanks as, um, DaVinci detective, whatever he was, I would be surprised if it wasn't just like
sentence kind of mixing from stuff he set up previously on the movie. Let's find out. Let's
go. Start game. Let's go. That's not Tom Hanks. Kind of reminds me of Bale. Paris by my lecture
at the American university and followed by an unexpected invitation. That's Tom Hanks.
Professor Langdon, thank you for coming. I am captain Bezoufash. Do you know this man?
Chauxinier, a curator of the Louvre. I was supposed to meet him tonight after my speech.
Is it? Follow me. It kind of sounds like him. Is that actually? No, but it's from the movie.
Yes. But it's not original dialogue. It's from the movie. That's a huge, heavy ass painting.
You should not have run. Now tell me please. I beg you. Is it? All right. All right.
This is like shot.
What? So it's so intense. Where did he shoot him? All right. What kind of game even is this?
So this should be of no surprise. Feel free to examine the body, Mr. Langdon.
It's like a detective game. Search the body for clues relating to his death.
Why is this in a window like this? This is in a window inside of a window. What did that say?
What the hell is going on here? All right. The position of his feet reinforces the reference
to the Pinnacle and the sacred feminine. Replication. Repeating a symbol is the
simplest way to strengthen its meaning. Chauxinier positioned himself in the shape of a five-pointed
star. That's not Tom Hanks. That's not Tom Hanks. Interesting analysis. That sounds like Ross from
Friends. Is it? It's a Pinnacle. One of the oldest symbols on earth.
Used over 4,000 years before Christ. Devil worship. It's an actor. No. The Pinnacle is
a pre-Christian symbol that relates to nature worship. The ancients envisioned their world in
two halves. Masculine and feminine. It's the ancient alien's narrator? What? Oh my god.
What? Ancient aliens?
Wow. Okay. So yeah. Yep. All right. We saw that. What is this?
That's a great Tom Hanks.
Wait. It's a marker. It's not blood?
As you know. You know, as you know, us detectives, we do these things.
What does this mean? That, monsieur, is precisely the question you are here to answer.
Part of it looks like a numeric cipher. Yes, our cryptographers are already working on it.
What is this game? These numbers may be the key to who killed him. This is like a CSI game, but it's
Tom Hanks and it's the movie. Does this happen in the movie?
An accusation against his murder makes sense, I suppose. Sonnier was a Frenchman. He lived in
Paris. This happens in the movie just like this. I have seen a lot of death in my work and let me
tell you something. When a man is murdered by another man, I do not believe his final
thoughts are to write an obscure spiritual statement that no one will understand. I believe
he is thinking of one thing only. La vengeance. I believe Sonnier wrote this note to tell us
Oh, but that makes no sense whatsoever. You told me Sonnier was attacked by someone
he had apparently invited in. Considering the circumstances, I would assume that if
Sonnier wanted to tell you who killed him, he would have written down somebody's name.
Precisement, précisement.
One moment please.
No, I'm not skipping it.
Unacceptable. I made it very clear. Captain, please excuse the interruption, but
I have deciphered the numeric code.
We already got the code deciphered. Hey, Resident Sleepers, we already got the code
deciphered. It took us 15 seconds in the cutscene. The US Embassy asked that you phone in as soon as
possible. While I explained the code to Captain Fash, you need to make this call.
Thank you. Where can I find a phone? This line is secure. You may use it.
What that actually means is that phone is bugged. It's the most bugged phone we've ever had.
I'm sorry, Miss Nouveau. I think you may have given me the wrong.
No, that is the right number. It's the three digit code on the paper I gave you.
What? The embassy has an automated message. It kind of looks like he's like,
it looks like it's a little too tight. Okay, so examine an item. I should look at that.
Select the item. Okay. What does it want me to do? Is that it is some kind of.
Well, I missed everything. This isn't important.
Examine the item. In his final hours of life. Oh, shit. Okay. Clues.
Okay. What game is this? No, we're not skipping. You got, we have to follow the rules.
Ooh. Who do I, who do I, I wasn't looking. Who do I talk to? Is it you?
Who is that? Who's captain? Who's the, what is, where's the captain?
I don't think this is relevant. Who's the captain? Wait, I need a phone number to call.
What? There's only like two people in the room. That's what, dude, I can't talk to either of these
people. So you mean to tell me that in his final hours of life. Dark souls music. I certainly hope
you have. Oh, look at that. Okay. Use the phone to call the three digit number.
A progression sum of the two preceding towers. What was it? Never heard of it.
Mathematician Leonardo Fibonacci created the succession of numbers in the 13th century.
Obviously there can be no coincidence that all of the numbers Sonia wrote on the floor belonged
to Fibonacci. Stop talking. This isn't working. Three digit four, five, four. I was going to say
that nobody has a three digit phone number. What is it? Like fucking 1400. I know that's a family
guy joke. That's a family guy joke. I know. Oh, what is this? Is this three? Yeah. I, I, look,
I get it. I know everyone's going to spam that in a second, but a three digit telephone number,
four, five, four. This isn't what I'm looking for. What is he saying? What does this mean?
There's not a fucking phone number. I'm pissed.
I got a minus two that says be original. The person that made this comment is the real
Peter Griffin is their name. That's the name of the chatter. You love that show. You should
have been happy about that. The restrooms are at the end of the grand gallery.
You should have been very happy. I had to go to the bathroom.
I'd like a little bit of privacy. No more than 45 minutes. At that point, it's a little too weird.
Do you agree? I agree. I think that is correct.
Hey, hit the fucking hand thing. The fan.
Hit the hand dryer so nobody hears us.
Weird. It was stuck out of your neck. I don't know how you did not notice.
In case you decide to run. In fact, they hope you do run because it would make their case much
stronger. Why would I run? I'm innocent. Do you recall the three lines of text that Sonia
wrote on the floor? What you saw was not the entire message. This is a photo of the complete
message. Why would Sonia write this? Was he trying to frame me? No, he wrote it for me. The number of
code is meaningless. Sonia wrote it to make sure the investigation included cryptography, ensuring
that I would know as soon as possible what had happened to him. Why you specifically? How do
you know it wasn't for some other cryptographer? P.S. is the nickname he called me when I lived
with him. All of a sudden, we're just going to hear a flush from the stall. It's like,
he was my grandfather. Where's Langdon? Still in the man's room, sir. We are seeing small movements,
so the GPS dot is obviously still on him. Perhaps he feels ill. If he had found the
dot, he would have removed it and tried to run. Hm, fine. Start screaming for no reason.
Fash will be taking you into custody any minute. You gotta just, just breathe in and out of each
other. We need to act now. You want me to run? It's the smartest thing you could do. If you stay,
you will spend weeks in a French jail. But if you get to your embassy, then your government
can protect you while I prove you had nothing to do with this murder. Forget it. You need to
tell Fash that the message on the floor was for you and that my name is not there as an accusation.
Fash is convinced you are guilty. The only way to get you out is with a distraction. The GPS tracking
dot? We need them to think you are running. If we can throw it out the window onto one of the cows
going by, I bet a lot of the police would clear out. Wait, throw it out? Wouldn't that be moving
really fast all of a sudden? See if you can find something to attach it to that would make it
heavier. Like, oh wow, we picked up, um, Tom Hanks is now going 70 miles per hour right now.
And in weird, it looks like he was going like 100, 200 miles per hour out of a window,
like really fast, losing elevation quickly and then drove very fast. I hope he's okay. Okay,
so I have to find something that's going to weigh this down. I'm not leaving yet. No,
I need to weigh it down. Is it like an examine button? There's a sneak button too. All right,
cool. You can pick up items like the soap. I can use this soap that will work.
Come help me open this window. Open to every stall. Oh, he's trying. He's trying to get away.
He's trying to, he's trying to sneak out the window. Where's Langdon? Stealing the men's room.
I knew it. He is trying to escape. Go down the toilet. Hurry Robert. Hurry Robert.
Hey, it was like minus 15 last night. It was frozen. Combine items. Hold on. They heard the
wit. What? Hold on a second. These are the dumbest detectives I've ever seen. There's no way. If
you're going to open up all of them, he's going to get a call on his phone at the last one.
Oh wait, you have a new location? Of course. Of course. You pre-watched. No, that's just
welcome to every single. We're trying to hide from someone. Wait, we're here. We're literally
in the place.
Oh, lame saint. Wait, what am I doing? What do I have to do? It's a puzzle. Do all Lang sign?
Uh, how about uh, let, let, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, let home. Let, let him not let him cook.
I might. Oh, you have it in emote only. I see what you're doing. This game takes around five
hours to complete. Two of them are cutscenes. Are you serious? Okay. Um, I think what about a hint?
An anagram is when the letters of a word or words are mixed up to form other words.
Uh, captain, I think I see a couple of people here. They look like the perpetrators.
No, no, it's definitely the way all the rats hang out in the alley where the ping is going off.
Uh, okay. I guess I will just go back to what I was doing. It's going to be like the, the,
the, the, the song, the same, the same, the same time they were killed at the same time.
I don't, I have no idea. I've ran out of hints. The, this all the main, like the main main street,
the main sale, the main, the main lasso. I don't think that's correct. Oh, lame saint. Wait,
what do you mean? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. What? That was correct. Do you think that was right?
How do I check it? The main, did I actually have it? Main lasso. I had it right. I'm pretty good
at this then. Is that it? No, that's not. It's the main something then the main,
wait, it is the main something. Stop posting a delicious meal. Like I've seen it a few times
and it's making me hungry and I don't want to see it anymore. It's delicious, nutritious,
and it isn't weird. It's not a strange thing to eat sometimes. Okay. The, oh, sorry. I had a bunch
of vegetables, like a ton of like really good for you, like high in a bunch of different vitamins.
Incredibly good for you. Good for your brain and shit. Oh no, I ate food that's really good
for your brain. I don't know how to do this. All right. It's the, the, the, the ale, old,
the old, the slow, oh, lame saint. Is this in the movie? Did they figure this out in the movie
really early on? Does Tom Hanks go, oh, lame saint, the main silo, right? Does this actually
happen in the movie? Is the answer in the movie? Is it really? It's in the movie. All right. Give
me five more minutes and I'll get it. The, the most, the lost, wait a minute, the lost, the lost,
the loser. Maybe it's not the, how, the, how she should, give me the first, give me the first
letter. Give me the first letter. This is, I look, I'm sorry. I don't, I don't, these are cool for
like a Sunday newspaper. I, give me the first letter. Just give me the first letter and I,
give me the first letter or I'm not moving on. I'll sit here all day. Give me the first letter.
T. All right. So I had it right. It's definitely the, not like this. All right. The, so the what?
The, the late, the most, the most, the most, the nice, the, the what? All right. What's,
all right. Second word, first letter, second word, first letter, second word, first letter.
No, no, no, no. The moon? The question mark. Hold on. The, the salt. I see a lot of salt
shakers. The salt. No nuts. What? What's, why can I do two A's? Wait, wait, wait, wait. Go back.
How do I go back? What just happened? Oh, there are two ways. The salt. Okay. The, there's no T.
The salt, sugar, the spice, the spicy, the spice, the sugar, the ice cream, the malted,
the sugary, the M, the main silo, the main lasso, the main, did I have it right? The main, the main
lasso, the main solo, the main solo, the main losa, the main as also, the main also, the main also,
the main also. The, the, the mom, the mom. Why are you spamming Bob Ross? Why are you spamming
Bob Ross? The Bob, the painter. The, the mist. No, the mist. Bob Ross. Painting? Painting. Education.
Follow along video series. Paint. Bob Ross. What does that mean though? Give me the next letter.
I was just staring at the chat with like my mouth open. The mole, the main, the ma, ah, the ma,
mo, me, mom. You're an expert at charades. You got this. Bob Ross. Picture. Bob Ross. Snap, snap.
Paint. Picture. Picture. Picture. Painting. Picture. It's not, that's not what it is.
That can't be what it is. That can't be. No, no, no, no, no, no. That can't be what it is.
No, that can't be what it is. The shit that's on the fucking cover of the box.
I did not know. I did not know that's what this game was about. I didn't know. I, I didn't know.
I didn't know what it was. I thought it was Mona. I, that's the shit. That's literally the front.
That's on the box. The Mona Lisa's on the cover. But like I, and it burnt into the screen. I was
on it for so long. All right, relax. I didn't. I've never seen the movie.
This screen burning is so bad. I was on that for so long. That was painful. I didn't think
it was going to be. Dude, give me a break. I did not know what this movie was about.
Lena Da Vinci. I didn't think they were going to give us spoilers in the first five minutes.
No, we don't know how long the grand gallery will stay empty. You have to go now.
I will see you at the embassy, Ms. Yolanda. That's that person that, okay. Wait, new character.
Okay. So what's the objective? Find a UV light. Isn't that, isn't that in the case over here?
The main, the main, what was it? The main lasso. I forgot this whole game was about a painting.
Look, I know. Listen to me. I did, I forgot this. I'd never seen this movie. I haven't thought of
the Da Vinci code in, I don't know, at least, at least fucking 10 years. I don't know. I never
even care where the movie came out. I forgot like Da Vinci made the Mona Lisa and the whole thing
is about like stealing the Mona Lisa because there's a secret in it. I don't know. I don't
know what it was. I just looked at the cover. I need a UV light. You didn't know the Mona Lisa,
what? You didn't know the Mona Lisa was painted by Da Vinci. No, but I didn't, I guess I just
didn't realize like that this movie in this game. Well, I don't, I don't know. I was just kind of,
I was lost there for a second. I didn't, I know Da Vinci painted the Mona Lisa, but in my brain,
they weren't going to start with that. Like the Mona Lisa was going to be like the big reveal at
the end of the game. Not the first puzzle. You know what I mean? I, but I didn't, you're an iPad
kid. I can't defend it. I can't defend it. I, I take the L. I can't defend it. This is the first
thing they do in the movie is they go over that. I didn't see the movie. Guys, I don't even, I didn't
care. For a second, I was blending two movies together. What's the one where Nick Cage? It's
like American treasures or something. It's like he, and he's like the constitution or what they
both are the same movie. All right. Sneak. I don't know, dude. It's like this relic that has all these
secrets in it. It's like the constitution had a bunch of secrets in it. The Mona Lisa has a bunch
of secrets in it. Like Leonardo Da Vinci was a like an alien and he landed and taught everybody
fucking technology, whatever the hell it is. I don't know. Oh, I thought there was a person
behind a desk. I was like, why can't they not see me? What are you? What's happening?
Why is it fighting right now? Holy shit. Stop, stop, fight, fight.
That was an extraordinary reaction. I did not, I did not fucking think that was going to happen.
Knocked on the floor and then they just punched me in the face over and over again.
I didn't even know there was a combat in this game. What the hell was that?
Dude, knock, knock. Who's that? You wouldn't even like, oh, who is that? Let me, I can't even
identify myself first. That was, I would have, that was fucking crazy. If the officer sees me,
he will not let me pass. I must sneak by him. Okay. This game just, you all wanted me to skip.
We have melee combat in this game. It was one of the most ridiculous things I think I've ever
seen in a game. Like what was the point of any of that? So far, so good. Items you can use be on
the lookout. Okay. Can I just like take everything? Like you can pick up weapons. What do you mean?
Where's a weapon? You need to initiate a throw during a throw. Okay. Why is this a wrestling
game now? This is like turning into like Arkham. Defend begins when the enemy gets the upper hand
counter the attack. When you start an attack, buttons appear at the bottom. Okay. Okay.
Leave him alone. What? I can and will defend myself.
Get off him. What? Stop. It's not fair. Why do I have to do a QTE every time I want to fight?
Give me the weapon. Where's the weapon? There's supposed to be a weapon here somewhere. Where is
it? Oh, shit. Get me the fuck out of here. Is there, how do I get a weapon? Where is this weapon that
apparently exists? Do not make me help you. You keep walking past it. Guys, it looks like somebody
threw up on my monitor. I can't see anything. Where do you see? Oh, shit. Where is it?
What do you see? Is it on the ground? It's on the floor. Actually, guys, this shit burnt into the
screen. It's hard for me to see what's going on. What was that? What's with the weird? Okay. All
right. This time don't aggro everybody. Get the weapon. It says get the whip on and equip it.
It wasn't in French. It was just text on the screen. If the officer sees me, he will not let
me pass. I must sneak by him. Okay. Okay. Let's go. Very nice. Keep going. Keep sneaking.
Be looking for items you can use as weapons. Be on the lookout for items you can use as weapons.
I don't see anything I can use as a weapon. Have to knock out that officer to get to the evidence
count. No, I don't want to see this whole fucking tutorial again. Oh, my God. Okay. All right. I
think I see it on the ground. Yep. Okay. Let's go. How do I pick it up? How do I pick this thing up
off the ground? Oh, my goodness. How do I? This should be useful. Okay. This could be useful to
Knox. This just won't end. Would you really hit a lady? Get out of here. This thing sucks.
Have you had enough? Oh, my God, dude. I hit him in the face. Everybody relax. Oh,
what? This fight is going on way too long, man. I will use force if necessary. We have been.
I hope he will be all right. This looks useful. Wait, drag his body? To where? Why would I want
to drag him anywhere? There's nowhere I can put him. All right. Let's go. I got a weapon.
And now I need to look at the evidence area, right? Examine, please. I'd like to examine
that evidence. Hey, not working. Maybe I can't have a weapon in my hand. What are you doing?
Get out of there. I cannot satiate my bloodlust. Wait, why did I drop it?
That's so unfair. Can I just go into the evidence cabinet now, please? Nope. You can't be in
anything. Oh, shit. All right. I'm going to beat the shit out of these guys now. I am pissed off.
I am done. I am pissed off. I'm ready to. This is it. I thought I heard something.
Are they both right here? How do I knock? Got it. First try. First try. There you are. Robert,
I told you to get out of here. If I. Where were you? I had to get the black light. If my
grandfather left me a message. I can't believe I fucked with that. I thought I told you to leave.
Why did Senor write my name on the floor? Oh, my God. I'm never going to live that down.
The letters PS may mean Princess Sophie, but do they mean anything else to you?
Anything at all? Yes. I saw the initials PS once when I was very young. Sophie,
this one hasn't been out in over 10 years. The initials appeared with a symbol,
a fleur-de-lis. How could you possibly know that? I'm fairly certain your grandfather was a member
of a secret society. The fleur-de-lis combined with the initials PS, that is the Brotherhood's
official coat of arms. They call themselves the Priory of Scion. The Priory's membership has
included some of history's most cultured individuals. Men like Botticelli, Sir Isaac
Newton, Victor Hugo, and more importantly, Leonardo da Vinci. The identities of living
My jaw hurts. That was like snapping. But the PS and fleur-de-lis that you saw as a child
would make sense if tonight were Priory related. There is a lot we need to discuss,
but I cannot afford to let them capture you, Robert.
Sonier obviously brought us together for a reason. I'm staying until we figure this out.
Fine, then help me. My grandfather wanted us to see this painting for a reason.
There must be a message hidden here. It smells like alcohol. Where have I smelled that before?
I thought he was implying that I was like drunk. No, not it. What is this?
Pfft. Why can I see this? What do you see? Random symbols in my face. You see random symbols?
Yes, yes, lots of them. This one looks like a P. This one looks like an E.
Nice phlegm. Okay, it's going to be like of...
They obviously are not random symbols. They're arranged. Yes, it does. This is somebody...
Okay, so now what am I supposed to do about this? How do I solve this? Do I have to like highlight
ones that match or something? Do I have to highlight the whole thing? All right,
maybe I have to just light up everything. Like just highlight it. Highlighting, highlighting,
highlighting. Highlighting every word. Highlighting every word. Oh shit.
Guys, I've done my fair share of the back of the Cocoa Puffs box. You don't think I know
how to do this flawlessly? Do you know how many Captain Crunch boxes I've been through in my day?
E. B? We? That's definitely E's. That's definitely a P. I'm gonna say we. We was A, right? There's
gonna be a lot of As. This could be A. That could be A. This is probably A. One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten. Okay. One, two, three, four, five, six, A, B, C, D, E. That's F.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck. What did it mean? It's like he wrote this
when they were like bashing the door down to come get him. What's the code though? What's
the Da Vinci code? I'm gonna solve it right now. Well, I was wondering if you had anything specific
to tell me about this encrypted message. As you can see, this symbol is the most common one.
As a result, I believe it is the letter E. That's what I said. Wait, what's? It's this one. This is E.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten. Anything come up more than 10 times?
That's what I was saying. I had the formula, right? We just gotta find where A is, right?
How am I supposed to? How would you ever do this? Okay, this is E. This is maybe like of
or like two of. This is probably T. Whoa, the, that, that, that, these, that, and, the, the, what?
Painting, painted, I, there's something painted those, the, those, these are probably those.
I've painted those that lies, lies and lies painted those that be tween, between, between
those that knew, knew between. This is wrong. It's not D. Maybe it is. Do. Wait, what? Oh,
it's Da Vinci. Miss Da Vinci. I'm thinking like, I don't know. It's just relax. Relax, relax, relax.
Da Vinci painted those that knew. All right. Listen, I'm reading it like the painted to
something like the. Oh my God. What's wrong with my brain today? I must be tired or something. I am
probably tired. Da Vinci painted those that knew between Bacchus, Bacchus,
between Bacchus and lies the clue. But what's this? You Da Vinci painted those that knew between
Bacchus and you're, you're Yu-Gi-Oh. Oh, I got it. Hey, you want to look behind the painting.
Nice. Bacchus is the God of wine and Uriel is an angel. If I'm not mistaken, there is a painting
of Bacchus. He forgot it was the Da Vinci game again. I keep forgetting Madonna of the rocks,
which should be in there too. Let's go. I keep forgetting. This is a Da Vinci game. Wait,
Robert is innocent. He did not murder Sonia. Asian Navoo. Innocent or not. I have direct orders to
arrest Robert Langdon on site. I'm sorry, but I can't go to jail until I helped Sophie find
the real murderer. You are working together. Robert, look out. What the? It would be best if
you would let me go. Ow. Was it this much fighting in the movie? All right. Take him.
You take him. Told me boxing wouldn't be useful in a teaching career. Where do we put him? Who
cares? All right. We got what we needed. Oh my God. Now, now let's go. Search the Bacchus,
Uriel and John. Where the hell is this painting? It's actually, it's pretty dark. I can't really
see. That means you guys can't see. I need to turn this up. I need to make this a little brighter.
Hold on. Give me one sec. It's dark. How many of this helps? Does that make this better or worse?
Actually, kind of worse. And the game's just supposed to be like this. Yeah, the game's
just supposed to be like this. Okay, so where is this painting? I gotta find like three things.
Oh, wait a minute. Saturn's sphere. And okay, so I have one of the planets. I have no idea which
one of these is the right painting considering that they're all so hard to even decipher what
they are. Is it just not even in this room? Oh, I thought it wanted me to do it in here.
Well, I don't see anything special. Everyone seems to be pointing at something now. Bacchus
points to the right and Uriel points to the left. In between them we have John the Baptist and he's
pointing up. What does that mean? There's something up there. What? On the painting above John the
Baptist. Give me a boost. Maybe I can reach it. I was seeing if she was gonna fall. Back in the day
when they were just QTEs for no reason. Zero. You gotta make it harder than that.
I thought one of the paintings is ringing. It's like wait, inside the painting is like a painting
of a phone but it's a real phone. Hello. That would have been fucking cool. Imagine like one
of these there was a phone and you could reach it and it was actually it was a real phone.
Why would you not do that? And it was like embedded in the paint and it was flush with the paint and
painting. So it was just like what the fuck am I looking at? Hey, wait a minute. You reach it and
it's like a phone. I would be so much better at this. Where somebody's office was ringing.
Where's this person's office? I wasn't even looking. Like an office telephone is ringing
and it was like oh look it's this way but I wasn't even I wasn't even looking. Down here?
You didn't pay any attention? No, zero. Like absolutely just as close to zero as you can get.
Down here?
What? This is my grandfather's office. Maybe we can find a clue here.
I'm just standing here.
Wait what? That's you talking here but you're standing here. How could you be in there and out
here? Wait that's not her talking?
I thought that was I thought she left a message and that's how they found out that
I got the bug. How high are you? I'm not. Just relax. I'm not. I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine right
now. I'm not high. I haven't had any marijuana cigarettes in like at all. I'm not. I'm kidding
around. It might be another clue to Sonier's involvement with the Priory of Scion
or perhaps the Priory's involvement with the Louvre. Okay so let's take a look. Take a look
at this. It's research on where all the Fleurs de Lis are in the Louvre. It might be another clue
to Sonier's involvement with the Priory of Scion or perhaps the Priory's involvement with the Louvre.
Interesting. Okay. Nothing else. Take a look at this. Okay. What about what's on the
computer? A special laptop used by police for crime scene investigation. Okay. Oh wait a minute.
This night has been moved recently. The dust has disturbed around the edges. I think grandfather
moved it so the lance would point us towards something. So excited. This map of the Louvre.
It smells. It smells like alcohol. It smells. Map of the Louvre. This map of the Louvre.
It smells like alcohol. Okay. But it. So what? There's a phone on the map.
This map of the Louvre. This map has been drinking. Okay. But so boring as fuck just like the book.
Come on. What do you mean all these trues? True, true, true. It's a novel.
Boring as fuck. Book sucks. It's probably good, isn't it? All right. So what's a good book?
What's a good book? Can chat agree on some nominees for what a good book is? Okay. Well,
I don't know what else to do here. It smells like alcohol. Search the office. I did. Can we get some
Apollo up here? Okay. I see the Bible, Green Eggs and Ham, Dante's Inferno, and Dune. All right.
Pick between those four. What? What? What? What's your favorite book? What's your favorite? Well,
not with the Bible. Put the Bible in there. No, those three. Those returning the Bible.
Large bookshelf containing many books. It's probably like a right. No event seems to connect
to the adjacent room. Can we get up there? How do we get up there? This map of the Louvre.
How do we get up to the vent? Can we move a chair? Do I need a ladder? Bring a ladder back in here?
How much of a point and click adventure game does this game want to be versus how much is
it actually? Right? Like, do I need to go get a ladder and bring it back into this room?
UV light. Okay. All right. All right. So, so it's, it's okay. So it's a, I just didn't know. I didn't
know if it was like a go to your inventory. Like point and click. Okay. What's this?
What do we need to know? Okay. Wait. He circled his office. No, look closer. It is the room next
door. The restoration room. There is a vent up above. If you boost me up to it, maybe I can get
to the other side. Oh, wait. Yeah. We're doing a poll. What was the poll again? It was, what's your
favorite book? What's a book that you consider to read? I have to tap every time. What were the
options? Um, uh, green eggs and ham. Do you need to search around some more? Dune. Maybe we can find
a clue here. The Bible and what was the other one? I said there was a fourth one. What was it? Oh,
Dante's Inferno. Yeah. Okay. There you go. What do you, do you like any of those? Chemistry isn't
my strong suit. Me neither. What do you think this table is used for? Oh God. I can't even read this.
There must be instructions for this somewhere. I'm making a, we just just chug it.
Lactose. Okay. Well, I don't know. We'll figure that out. What's this?
Best book of all time. What do we got? Green eggs and ham. Dude, it's so funny how Dune is the lowest
of all of these. So green eggs and ham is just absolutely sweeping right now. Okay. The Bible
is in second. Best book of all time. Green eggs and ham more, more important than the Bible.
Bible way more important than Dune. Also Bible more important than Dante's Inferno. Two religious
books up here. Well, one of them is a religious book. The other one is a take on the religious
text, right? How is Dante's Inferno not higher? Those books are terrible. Dante's Inferno. I
remember, I remember reading Dante's Inferno and just being like, what's going on here?
What the fuck? How many of you guys just haven't even read Dante's Inferno? Green eggs and ham.
Okay. All right. Dante's Inferno. What was it? Dante's Inferno is a... I haven't read any of these.
What? You've never read green eggs and ham? You had to have. You've never read green eggs.
I think this might be the only one of the four that a lot of you have read. That's the one I know.
Can I get a towel? All right. We are way over, over our time limit on this one.
I did, this was very fun, but I'm going to do one or two more puzzles and then I'm moving on.
I cannot make out what the painting is supposed to depict. Maybe we can remove the dirt.
Finish it. Dirty painting with the towel. I cannot make out what the painting is supposed to depict.
Maybe we can remove the dirt. Use the, use it. Rinse it in the sink. I don't actually have to do
that, do I? Anything else in here? This one's cool. I like this one. I like this one. Box is empty.
There's nothing out of the ordinary about these books. What book? Nothing there. What's your
favorite? What's your favorite book? What's your favorite Xbox game of all time? I never had one.
I've never had an Xbox before. Original. New game, please. I will. Let me just get past this.
Enzyme that functions in the defense against fungal and insect pathogens.
Commonly used as a counter enzyme that neutralizes supercharged oxygen molecules.
It neutralizes supercharged oxygen molecules called superoxide radicals.
You don't want those on your counter. I mean, pretty good cleaning.
Involved in the hydrolysis of lactose to constitute galactose and glucose.
Its functions include catalyzing the decomposition of hydrogen peroxide to water and oxygen.
An enzyme that catalyzes the hydrolysis of urea into carbon dioxide and ammonia.
I'm just going to pick two until I get it right.
A speaker of enzyme should clean the painting. I cannot make out what the painting is.
Toilet sounds. It kind of was toilet sounds.
It seems to be working, but I think we need to spread the enzymes around.
You ruined it! That was a weird look.
What is that?
The winged victory of Samothrace. That's here in the Louvre.
But why would Sarnier want us to go there?
How many books have you read in the last year?
This is actually interesting. Yeah, right. Yeah, right.
10 plus books in the last year. Yeah, right. I could believe between zero and five.
10, 10 plus. Some of you mean that. Some of you are talking about like 20.
My goal is always 100. 10 is easy.
Some people read a lot. That's a lot.
How many books are you reading? 10? More than 10 books a year?
Yeah, those are 10 Dr. Seuss books.
All right. 32% say zero. 30% say between one and two.
Wow, we have to read more, don't we?
A majority of people in this chat right now, I'm included in this.
62% of us, at least out of the sample size that I chose to answer,
have only read under two books in the whole year. Sometimes less than one.
The last time I've read a book was Game of Thrones.
It was the Game of Thrones book. It has to be the last Game of Thrones book.
What about audiobooks? I think those count.
It's the only book you've read. Name 10 books.
That's not fair, though.
That's actually not fair because I don't pay attention to that world really at all.
Name 10 books. Dr. Seuss.
Rain, Eggs, and Ham. The Great Gatsby.
Um, The Shining. The Catcher in the Rye.
The Twilight series.
Okay, Twilight. I don't want to look at chat. I don't want any help.
A Song of Ice and Fire. Book one.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. How about this?
Book five. A Dance of Dragons.
Okay, that's five. That's six.
Tempest. Let me do it. Let me do it.
Let me do it. He's thinking so.
I was thinking of a relevant book that I may have even read or heard of.
The Tempest. Um, I mean, everything is a book.
I could just name anything. Lord of the Rings.
I mean, The Hobbit. Lord of the Rings.
And that's like 15. What do you mean not a book?
Eight? That's four. That's not four.
That's not four. Uh, you know what?
I'm just going to name a random movie.
And my Big Fat Greek Wedding. Is that a book?
That's a book, right? That's a book, right?
That's a book. Was that a book first?
Like, I kind of feel like it was. Is it not?
I'm thinking of like, okay, movies that like were books.
Dune. Titanic. A screenplay is not a book.
Technically, it was.
James and the Giant Peach. How's that?
That's been at least 10.
The Titanic. No, somebody said that in chat
and I said it out loud. I didn't say that.
I was laughing. No, the Titanic.
Okay, I need to defend myself here.
Somebody said the Titanic. Like, 10 of you said it.
And I was reading the chat room.
Going, the Titanic? Like, what the fuck?
The Titanic was not a book first.
Oh my god. You guys are, you guys are, I'm being, I'm,
you guys are, you guys are attacking me.
Play the game? How many of you guys actually care
about me playing the game? I thought it was like,
don't play the game, play the other one.
You cannot honestly believe that I thought the Titanic
was a book before it was a horrific thing
that happened in the world.
You can and will defend myself.
What's going on?
This isn't necessary.
The book is actually what was based on the,
okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We need to make sure that we get this clear here.
The movie, The Titanic was, was it based off of a book
of the telling of that story?
Move them out of sight.
So they just made that up.
Okay, I just, I'm just, we're just checking.
It could be the movie that's, this isn't important.
A lot of you know what I mean.
Like, Titanic, the movie, was it like a retelling
of like a book version of the Titanic
where those characters were in it?
I don't think this is relevant.
It's historical fiction.
That's what I'm saying.
Was there like a Titanic book?
All right, I'm playing a different game.
I think that great wedding.
I don't know.
I figured like maybe that's a, maybe it was a book.
No, the Titanic is a real thing.
Oh my God.
How do I get out of this?
How do I like, how do I get, how do I take the car
and like slowly get off the exit
and like get us off this highway?
You know what I mean?
All right, the next one coming up
is going to be in the same world, I think.
And I, wait, there is, there are Titanic books.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We have a paragraph, Andy here.
The film based on the book and with advice from the Lord
was released in 1958.
Lord also served as a consultant
to Canadian film director James Cameron
while he was making the film Titanic.
That is precisely what I'm talking about.
That is precisely what I was talking about.
I'm so glad we get to turn off the exit now.
Yes, it was, somebody wrote a book.
You just got back on the highway.
Somebody wrote a book based on this
and that's what the movie was based on.
I, you know, I might say things
completely fucked up sometimes, but you know what I mean.
Coming up next is Stolen.
The film based on the book with advice from Lord
was released in 1958.
Lord also served as consultant to, so somebody wrote a book
and then they consulted on the movie about Titanic,
about like that happening.
Okay, like the story that he wrote.
All right, sounds good.
Um, I think the Xbox is wrong with it.
No, not the Lord, Lord?
Did somebody write something named Lord?
There we go.
Okay, I thought the disc was broken or something.
Everyone else disagrees with you and that guy.
At least I got one, one person here that can help me.
This game is called Stolen.
No, I agree.
I exist.
I'm here.
Oh, the goofy movie was the book before it was the movie.
There was a, wait, what's happening?
I feel like we're getting the whole movie spoiled by the trailer.
They're doing it.
I get to, they're doing it.
I need to calm down because they're doing it.
Okay, I'm going to relax.
I didn't want to do that.
I don't, what did I just do?
Why am I doing this right now?
What's that?
What am I doing?
Silent.
This could be a scorn like.
Good evening.
I'm Jacqueline Meadows.
Tonight's top news story.
The heat is rising in the run-up to the city's elections.
Earlier today, Mayor Thomas Morgan made a public appearance
at the Metropolitan Art Museum's Japanese Treasures opening.
And once I'm re-elected, we'll bring more international
treasures like this one to Ford City.
While the mayor's main rival, candidate Richard Killian,
unveiled his anti-crime platform in a televised address.
For years, crime thrived under Morgan's reign, but no more.
I don't know about you, but I hate this city.
It's cold, it's dirty, it's home to far more sinners than saints.
Myself among them, truth be told.
Yeah, they say things are about to change.
20 years now, I've been hearing the same thing again and again.
But nothing ever changes.
Same old victims, same old crimes.
That's an endless problem.
Unless that is, you happen to be the problem.
Wait, is this that guy's apartment?
Good of you to drop in.
So what kept you?
Just a little pest problem.
What can I say?
I'm a popular girl.
All done.
I thought those were all screens.
It's gonna work this time?
It's just a window?
It'll work fine until you break it.
Wish me luck.
All right, let's do it.
Whoa!
Okay, there's that.
There's a crouch.
There's a punch.
Press A to go across gaps.
Run at the...
Stop that, okay?
Swing and jump off a pole to the opposite roof.
My god, this is crazy.
All right.
Press...
Oh, I didn't see that.
What did it say?
Press and hold R to run up the wall.
Oh, press...
It's kind of hard to read.
Press A after jumping at the pole to swing off it immediately.
Nice.
This seems pretty sick.
This seems pretty good.
I start to view the objectives screen.
Left thumb stick to scroll the GPS map.
Okay.
Okay, now what?
Pretty cool.
Okay.
20 FPS?
Yeah, it's an old game.
First person mode.
How do I get out?
Okay.
Well, who cares?
The game is quiet.
Not anymore.
I like those glasses.
Use Up or Down to bring your inventory.
Press the first person mode.
Dude, wait a minute.
This really is Metal Gear.
What do I do now?
Is he asleep?
He's asleep standing up.
This guy is not doing good.
Can I take his gun?
Okay.
Sonic emitter.
Press once placed to...
Okay, how do I...
It's very confusing to use items.
I have to go into first person mode.
And then I can't walk anymore.
And then I have the sonic emitter now.
Which there's a person over here.
Which activate the emitter.
Is he going to open the door?
And it's inverted.
He just shined the light at me.
How did he not see me?
Steel?
Hey.
Oh my god, he's just done that.
Wait, he doesn't remember?
Just gonna say how is he missing?
Your AI is not smart enough to hit me moving.
Guarantee it.
Okay.
Oh, the framerate just got to 60.
That's a good change.
All this stuff must be worth a fortune.
One of the technicians said that Jade's statue alone
is worth more than my house.
So what?
I seen your house.
All I'm saying is they should put that on display
instead of hiding it away in the research lab.
Yeah, but it's like really old.
Those museum boys want to prod it
and poke it a bit while they have the chance.
Remember the time we were in the museum?
Let's lock up here and get a coffee.
And you and I got to fight.
Are you concerned about this?
Or is this supposed to happen?
Oh, that's...
Stolen.
Lockpicking.
Oh, that like hurts.
Oh, I have to very lightly hold it.
We need a new emote.
There's like 10, 20 new emotes.
What do you mean?
Let's go!
Hold to whistle.
You might need to make the whistle.
How do I look?
Wait, I can scan through the...
It's not working.
Where's my sonar?
Use the scan?
Eliminate the sonic visor view.
Or illuminate the sonic visor?
I don't have...
Where's my sonic visor?
Where's the sonic visor?
Wow.
D-pad left?
D-pad right is that.
D-pad down is this.
D-pad left doesn't seem to do anything.
This is like zoom mode.
This is whistle mode.
This is punch.
This is jump.
I actually think that kind of helped.
Sneak up behind this guard
and while standing press X to put him in choke hold.
Why am I moving so slow?
What are you doing?
Hurry up!
I snuck up and pressed X.
Oh, while standing.
Right, right.
Whatever.
Stole that.
Anything else in here?
What's this?
They get up really quick.
What is happening?
Your fucking aim is so annoying.
How do I get out of here?
There's a vent, vent, vent, vent, vent, vent, vent.
Vent!
Get in the vent!
God.
Make them shoot each other.
Now don't get up.
I thought he was going to get up.
They got up before in like 15 seconds.
Nice.
Anything else?
Ooh, I can steal in here.
Doesn't come back on, does it?
Really?
Ooh, an MP3 player.
Oh, okay.
My guards.
Night vision.
I don't, I don't want to use night vision.
No, I don't want to use it.
It looks worse.
I get it.
I get it now.
I'm using sonar through the walls.
Pretty sick.
Is anybody there?
I'm like chewing on wet concrete trying to use the inverted controls.
It's just like, I'm just like.
I don't know what it means.
What the fuck does that mean?
I don't do this.
It's, I'm just using a phrase.
Stop moaning.
I'm going to do whatever I want.
Right.
Where is this guy?
Press A to select the hacking target.
Use the left dump stick to copy the computer sequence.
Right dump stick.
L and R control the camera.
Jerma, you're a brat.
What's going on?
What was, what happened?
How did I fail the hack?
Do I even need the key anymore?
I don't need the key.
We're good.
Everything's fine.
What?
Dude, this guy's fucking final boss.
All right.
Steal.
Oh my God.
The analog just fucked me up, guys.
The analog went like.
Oh, come on.
Get away from me.
Give me a break.
Turn around.
Don't point the flashlight on me.
Fuck.
The buttons are so fucked up.
I promise.
It's such a weird game to play.
Shoot him.
Shoot.
Okay.
Now what?
Get out.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes.
I'm good.
I kind of like this game.
It's fun.
The night vision mode looks like you're inside of a Mountain Dew bottle.
True.
I like those glasses though.
Those glasses are awesome.
The door uses a swipe card system.
If you kill the power, it'll release the light.
I missed that.
What did they, what did he say?
He said that uses something.
We'll lose something about a lock.
Kill the power.
What does it want me to do?
I wasn't paying attention either.
See, I'm not the only one.
Okay, hold on.
Should I go in the middle here?
He said it out loud.
But I didn't comprehend it.
It was like something about using the light to see where I can go or something.
Something to do with my, maybe an emitter.
Turn power off.
I don't know how to do that though.
Destroy the electricity?
I'm picking up some.
How am I supposed to do this?
Louie, you're full of surprises.
I just walk through this like who cares?
It is not an alarm.
It's a Tesla coil.
I thought it was an alarm system.
It's not an alarm.
This shit zaps you.
Okay, so now I need a different solution than this.
So I need to shoot something that's emitting this.
And I should have listened to the guy talking.
No, this is going to suck.
I'm so dead.
Get up.
I can't get up from here.
Oh my god.
Okay, I get it.
What are you?
What?
What was that?
Why did that?
I didn't press.
I did not press A.
I didn't even press A.
I didn't even jump.
That was weird.
Got it.
It's a lot of trouble just for one door.
Can we use the Xbox now?
Remember, you should put matching shades on.
I can't just jump over the fence.
That seems kind of...
There's no way, right?
Look at this.
It wants me to go like boink up.
This is not a chance.
It does not want me to do that.
Is something funny?
No, I don't feel like it.
There are more than two people here?
There are.
Okay, there's one down there and one over here.
Get out of fucking fr-
I'm done with this fucking game.
I'm done with it.
I'm done.
I don't play this one anymore.
I'm done playing this one.
This one was fun for a few minutes.
I'm going to put on this one.
Death Row Underground Team Combat.
That was fun for a minute.
Seeing some pogs on this one.
This is a good one.
Can you do a piss break?
Do you guys need a piss break?
You guys good?
Piss break?
What do you think?
Yeah?
Maybe?
You guys need a piss break?
Yeah?
No?
All right, fine.
We'll do it.
It's been a few hours.
It's been like two and a half hours, right?
Yeah.
All right.
We'll take a quick break.
I'll be right back.
I'll see you guys in a minute.
We'll come back with Death Row fighting game or something.
I'll be right back.
I have returned back.
Hello.
How's it going?
Okay, here it is.
Uh, here you go.
See it, right?
Can you hear it?
Good.
Okay.
Uh, this is not what I thought it was going to be.
Not even close.
I thought this was going to be a game where you fight.
It's like a big brawl of underground fighting.
I think it's a sport.
It's some kind of sport.
It's like basketball.
But with a disc or something.
Should we do sports view?
Or it's probably sports view, right?
The droids versus the blitzards.
How do you play?
This is my lineup.
Oh, definitely Blitz Andy versus the training droids.
What?
Did I get a point?
Okay.
Where's the disc?
I just injured the droid.
Pass it, pass it, pass it, pass it, pass it.
Pass it over here.
Pass it.
Okay.
Oh, this is actually kind of cool.
All right.
Where's the disc?
Let's go.
R to locate the disc.
Isn't that what I'm pressing?
We're running by three points.
All right.
We win.
Replay the round.
That counts as two points?
I threw it behind.
Oh, that's when I was just injuring people.
Okay.
All right.
I get it.
We don't even do it again.
Game stinks.
I don't think it does.
Crowd sounds like a vacuum.
All right.
Single match.
Conquest.
Okay.
The Blitzers.
No rules.
Oh, these are the teams.
The Seacats.
The Protectors.
Convicts.
There are four teams in this league.
Who has the highest punch percentage?
It's convicts.
Convicts are the worst scum of the galaxy.
The most hardened criminals.
Senses to death for the most abominable acts.
Penitentiary governors lured them on with the promise that victory would lead to freedom.
It was mostly out of sheer bloodlust that they entered the arena.
For these guys, it's victory or death.
Okay.
We've got Alvarez, Zeke, Becker, and Toro.
I don't think this really matters.
I'm going to challenge the Blitzers.
Is somebody behind you?
Where is he?
Oh, there you are.
Hey, Tacho.
Do you want to leave?
He's lying down over here.
Do you want to get out of here?
All right.
Let's go.
I don't see him.
Give me one sec.
Show Otto?
Oh, okay.
Um, he's got to get in the right spot.
Otto, go over here.
Come over here.
Let's go.
Go over that way.
Go over so they can see you.
Otto?
Hey, look up here.
Oh, you can kind of see his butt.
What's up?
Do you want to get out of here?
Okay.
All right.
We're back.
Let's go.
Excited dog.
Cartoon.
Let's go.
Okay.
He's good.
I took that one out.
I think we saw all we needed to see.
I mean, what did I do?
Court is down.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know.
All right.
We're putting in.
I feel like we're going to be in this one for at least half hour.
Maybe not, though.
This is Eragon?
That movie with the dragons?
Eragon?
Eragon.
Yo, this game.
People are excited about this one.
Okay.
Let's see it.
Why can I not hear this?
I don't hear anything.
Why can you?
That's weird.
Okay.
Now I can.
There's a cord loose.
All right.
Eragon.
Never saw this movie.
I haven't seen this movie.
It was a book?
That was weird.
A time without tyranny or fear
does fill this sky.
Thorix now rules.
Wicked shade enforces Galvatrix's iron rule.
The reach of despots is limited.
And even Galvatrix couldn't touch one unsuspecting farm boy.
A boy whose heart burned with hope.
Like old film?
What is this old film?
Okay.
Oh my god.
That was loud.
Those combos.
That was all my left ear.
This game is awesome.
Is it?
I thought that was her screaming.
It feels like we're watching a mobile game ad.
Jump and grab the rock ledge then use L to move across.
Got it.
Just make my way home.
Enough's enough.
Hold and hold R to draw your bow.
That just makes perfect.
It targets by moving R and fire.
It's so cool that he's using his camcorder to record this.
Dude this is what video games looked like back in like 2005, 2003.
The stone, Ardya.
Be the stone.
The stone.
And that you will live.
Yes.
No the game looked like shit back then too.
Did it?
Fate destined to change our world.
Oh yeah there's dragons in this.
Cool.
Okay.
Power orbs.
I didn't find the secret egg.
I feel like I need to shake and then pop off at the end.
Eventually discovered that what he found in the spine was not a simple stone.
But a small blue.
The dragon quickly grew as out speaking.
He was furious that the egg was lost.
And he commanded Dosa to finally feed a new rider which strengthened the resistance.
Led by a group called the Varden.
Why is this pacing so cracked?
I think it's just it's hard to make a cutscene.
Especially back here in the day.
It's like hard.
You know how many hoops and strings that they had to pull through to just
to make any of this look like anything you care about?
There's so many tricks to make it even look like this.
Do I get to fly a dragon?
Am I cutting their heads off?
Use grapple combo grab stun for a few.
I'm just my body might want to sneeze so bad but I just can't.
Okay this game is pretty cool.
Oh my god.
How do I aim?
He's doing it too.
You figured out the strategy.
This is a tower defense game now.
I think I'm probably going to need some cannon towers in a minute.
After next round.
Probably two cannon towers in the front.
Fury mode?
L and R.
L and R sticks.
Pressure chest contain items break them.
What's in it?
Health orb?
No you have to put money or items weapons jewels something like that.
It better not be a health orb.
Okay it's loud.
That was it.
That was the start of it.
That was that was actually the start of it.
It's just slowed down.
Block.
Right now there's somebody that was like oh dude Aragorn the game this is my childhood.
And they're watching this right now.
They're going no it gets no it gets better.
I can't wait till the dragon shows up.
Wait till the dragon shows up.
Move the smithy.
That is a bloody sword.
I should wait shooting at them.
Keep steady.
That was awful.
Okay get close and then use your kill move.
Oh my god.
Who are these people that were doing this?
Why are we attacking these?
What's the point here?
Should we do fury?
Fury mode.
Play Rats too?
I already did.
Yeah it's called Aragorn.
What happened?
I just skipped wait we just what happened?
I missed the cutscene.
Stop getting so close.
Oh my god.
I'm just trying to get out of here.
All right let's go.
Let's go.
Play Stuart Little.
No we have to get to the dragon part.
I'm not stopping this till the dragon's here.
Saving game.
All right good.
Rom has been given Aragorn an old sword.
Your attacks are now stronger.
Do your best Stuart Little impression.
Well I I think that it's going to be a really fun day today.
I have no idea.
I've never seen it.
I've never heard him talk once.
That was the Joker.
Can we start reading fire at people?
I do appreciate we're getting there quickly.
Quickly.
Everything is the Joker, Alex Jones, or Mr. Satan.
Or Trump.
How are there too many?
Headbutting this guy?
What do you want?
What are we doing here?
No!
Jump to the ledge.
Where am I going?
That was far.
Yo.
He said not to fight.
I think they're supposed to be spawning over here
but the game is really confused about what's happening.
You jump.
Get up.
This was released on the 360 and PC.
I just missed an incredibly important thing.
You used magic.
A gift all dragon riders possess.
Concentrate.
Quickly.
The archers.
Stay sharp son.
Use your magic again.
I didn't even look.
Who gives a shit about magic?
I want to see the dragon.
Okay.
How did you miss that?
Did he just get knocked off the edge?
No wait what?
Oh no he just did.
Wait what?
I'm so confused what just happened.
Why is it going up?
Oh my god stop.
Let's go!
This camera.
I can't tell what's happening.
Let's move.
What's what's happening here?
What's the problem here?
Stuart Little 2 impression.
That's when they introduced the sidekick.
It was like a little dog right?
Stuart Little and Dougie Doo.
It was a bird.
Oh that's right.
Shit sorry.
I just made it up because I've never seen or heard of it.
The only time I knew what Stuart Little was
is because I saw like a TV commercial for it once.
And Dr House is in it.
Watch it right now.
Dude what are we doing?
How do I keep going?
Oh my god.
What do I?
But I mean.
I mean.
He's game sucks.
He sucks.
Dude he sucks.
All right aim at the right thing please.
All right roll off.
Do I have to you have to kill everybody.
I just want to fly around in a dragon.
Is the dragon talking this?
Is it like Aragorn you and I?
Is it like or is it deep?
It's like you and I must.
Dragon's a girl?
Oh okay so it but is it a deep?
Is it like or is it uh hold on.
Damn this game is blurry.
No no no no no no no no no no.
Spin it back around.
I want to spin it back around.
Does that help our cause?
Yes it does.
Nice okay.
All right let's go.
Aragorn police helicopter angle.
I just want to ride the dragon.
The Battle of Home Depot.
The dragon's probably 50 hours in dude.
I doubt that.
All right jump on this.
All right we need to hang on this.
What the hell is going on?
Oh my god they just get replaced.
Okay what I don't get this.
Like climb it.
I pressed up and he didn't even move.
I pressed up.
Let let it go.
Let it let go.
Let go.
I used the potty all by myself.
Time the person up for five minutes.
Can you fucking help?
Still in blight town.
Now what?
What?
What am I looking at here?
You'll play this but you won't play Spyro.
You don't know that.
Oh my god stop dodging.
I want to do the magic.
You have to stand completely still or it doesn't work.
Because that's the same button as hold on.
Get off.
Oh my goodness.
I just want to I just want to.
I'm gonna put it on easy.
I just want to ride the dragon.
Oh this sucks.
Does anybody know when it when I actually get to play the dragon?
It's the only reason why I'm still here.
Triangle is jump.
X is dodge.
A is attack.
It's just all wrong.
Holding left trigger activates magic mode.
Which sometimes it's or if it's not magic mode it's a dodge.
It's just it's just all over the place.
It's just it's not what you think.
Triangle you know why whatever is also magic attack.
I'm just fucking sprinting I don't care.
Ah this is bad.
Oh shit oh no it's over I'm so screwed.
I can't get out of here.
Oh no okay okay okay.
All right everybody relax.
I have to beat this I don't care make fun of me.
Please veto this I I am only stopping when I get to the dragon.
I want to fly around in a dragon.
And I want to hear the dragon say.
Aragorn use my fire.
No come on I have to hear it.
Please that's all I care about.
What why are we so far away?
Oh my god oh my god.
Oh if we get a checkpoint yes.
You are at least 30 minutes of gameplay if you do exceptionally.
What if I do exceptionally well I have 30 at least 30 minutes of gameplay.
Before we get to the dragon that can't be right I refuse to believe it.
Why won't you lift up you know get over here and jump up and just grab it.
That guy is hopeless right now who cares.
All right we're getting there we're getting there we're getting there.
Just watch the dragon part on YouTube.
Why not just watch every single one of these games on YouTube.
And why play any of them for more than one second.
Why even own an Xbox if we're just going to open up a gameplay of every.
Oh what's this next one coming up.
Oh brute force brute force gameplay with no commentary.
We're not doing that.
All right look it we're almost there.
Pause the game hold L T R T L B R B press X four times and B two times.
You see this is an original Xbox I don't have those buttons.
The dragon is in about an hour.
What's the level select cheat.
How do I cheat to get level select speed run it's a 10 minute speed run.
Yeah but how do you even speed run.
There's no dragon in the game seven minutes.
All right how how do what's the how do I skip a level.
Well how do I do it in the menu.
Pause the game and hold hold L one L.
I don't have L one guys this is original Xbox.
There is a dragon so I want to play it so how do I do it.
There's no L one R one on an original Xbox.
Furry mode pause and hold you just play the game.
You can't there's no cheats but level skip.
Is there can somebody help me.
Is there actually a level skip so I can just skip like five.
I just want to fly around on the dragon.
There's only one cheat you need to earn it.
I definitely don't think I'm going to play this game for another hour.
All triggers X X BB.
I got lightsaber mode permanently activated.
Is there any more.
Give me everything whatever it is.
First we have to retract those eight blocks.
The lock Aragon use your magic to the second block.
That got sniped immediately.
That got just sniped.
It was in all capitals that dude be careful it might crash your Xbox.
Oh nightbot took him out.
Okay oh dude there's another one.
Press this hold down the triggers BB X X Y Y.
It's hentai mode.
Be careful dude it's going to crash the Xbox.
What is that even supposed to mean.
Let's just imagine being like wait what like BB.
It's like fuck oh I'm going to take the disc out.
Auto mod just like sniped him.
I wouldn't even be laughing at this if it wasn't.
Oh dude be careful it's it'll like crash your Xbox.
Why do I cheat.
How do I cheat.
I need to collect all the dragon eggs.
Love us like pause game hold both triggers.
BB X A Y Y.
BB X A Y.
Turn the Xbox off turn on PS2.
Insert the Spyro game disc and then do this in real life.
Got it.
Thanks for the tip.
No I'm gonna get to see the dragon.
Sorry all right I have a choice for you.
Where are they gonna go to gladiator sword of vengeance or circus maximus.
Chariot wars both sound pretty enticing.
But which one which one are we going to do.
I don't think we even need to pull.
I'm seeing a lot of circus circus.
Yeah I'm seeing a lot of circus circus circus circus circus circus.
I don't think it would even be a contest.
Okay what's that what's that scary like robot's voice.
Did you hear that it was weird.
All right circus maximus.
Okay circus maximus please good.
Oh don't break it please.
Okay circus maximus.
Ready your Xbox can't recognize this disc.
Wait what.
This thing is fucking dirty.
Oh man this is so dirty.
This is so dirty.
It's a little better.
This is an Xbox game doesn't like it's not a real disc.
And it's gonna be really loud turn it down quick.
Circus maximus empire circus tournament academy.
So we're gonna go to we're just doing circus.
Let's see what should I play.
Aurora wait what's going on.
What is it I can pick different horses.
Somebody said holy shit this looks real stanky.
I don't know what to pick.
Is this I mean what should I do.
Fantasy.
All right we're gonna go with the fantasy.
Laps how many wait 10 laps.
I said fuck you Jerma.
Hey come on taunt duck power attack accelerate.
Wait this might be really good.
Elwynn forest I said it first.
Wait am I the back character.
Oh shit hold on.
I don't think that's very safe.
Why.
Oh no I got lightheaded.
I got lightheaded I was about to scream.
That was like I just like got started to laugh really hard.
But then I had to stop for a second because I just got really fucking lightheaded.
Okay relax we can get this back.
Hope I don't get passed but okay.
We'll get the controls down.
What happened.
Wait you dog.
He just shut up.
I'm gonna get laughed.
How do I go faster.
I'm actually I'm making ground on somebody.
There they are.
I'm making I'm making ground.
I got him got him.
Oh shit.
Oh god damn it bro there are 10 laps I don't want to do this.
Why did I do that.
Did they crash.
Fuck you.
I'm gonna restart this.
What is going on.
Oh okay I'm not doing that for 10 rounds.
Speed I want speed high.
All right just two laps and we'll go to I don't know whatever this is.
Cyprus I want speed.
Block hard turn right hard turn left.
All right let's go.
I can change the camera too.
Wait I was trying to get a funny angle.
Okay now we just have to keep pacing we're good.
What why am I so slow.
Why am I so slow.
I have the fastest zebra in the.
Why am I going so slow.
Your stamina is too low.
What friend we're so slow.
Holy shit they went flying.
Oh my god okay okay okay okay.
We're still going we're still all right.
We're still fine.
It's the it's the horses that are doing all the work.
Oh look at that pace.
What that was blended into the environment.
That was blending into the environment.
That blended into the space.
This is still the first lap.
Wait they get the super speed boost.
First place let's go.
Fuck out of here.
It was nowhere to go.
What happened.
I'm so pissed.
I'm so irrationally angry right now you've no idea.
Stop blocking.
I'm so fucking mad.
We're going outside shortcut.
More dangerous but it's a shortcut for sure.
Look at that.
What are you talking about.
What no I wanted to go down that one.
I didn't want to go this way.
Boost I you saw me duck.
You saw me duck.
You saw me.
I ducked why did you still hit him in the head.
What's the brake.
What's brake.
I was sandwiched.
There was somebody on the left.
There was somebody on the right.
There was somebody behind me.
They were all sandwiching stabbing me.
No what did I just throw.
I just threw lightning.
That's it.
I think I just did it.
It's over not yet.
All right I have a lightning bolt.
I don't know what it does but I'm going to hold it to the very end.
Okay all right.
Okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay.
Where is it.
This car sucks so bad.
Okay why when does the race end.
I feel like I'm on like lap six.
Arcade race.
Wait oh no that's that's what it's called career.
I mean no I'm not doing a career.
That was fun.
That was worth for sure that was worth playing.
All right it's time for you guys to take a vote here.
Are we going to play Indiana Jones and the Emperor's Tomb or Driver Parallel Lines.
What do you think.
I've seen a lot of both though.
Let's see.
Indiana Jones or Driver Parallel Lines.
Oh this actually is a lot of people that want both.
You've played the driver game already on stream.
Jerma plays Driver Parallel Lines.
No I didn't.
I didn't.
Maybe a different driver game.
I think this one's only on the original Xbox.
I don't think this one's backwards compatible.
All right what are we doing.
Pretty close but we're doing Driver Parallel Lines.
We'll do Indiana Jones after that.
Well we'll see.
Let's see.
All right driver coming up.
No burning.
Driver 4 is Parallel Lines.
Driver is Parallel Lines.
You played Driver already.
I played Driver 1.
I didn't play the other ones.
We'll see whatever it is.
I don't know.
Tell me I've played this before.
I don't believe you.
What did you say?
You googled yourself.
I'm googling to see if there's a video of it.
Guys I've played thousands of video games
and I've made thousands of videos
over the course of 13 years.
12, 13 years.
I've streamed millions of different pieces of frames
have gone into my brain.
I don't remember.
Maybe I mean yeah.
There's like seven of these games.
Maybe I played one of them.
I don't know.
Do you know how many frames have gone in here?
How many actual animation frames have gone into my head?
Driver.
So the way Driver Parallel Lines.
Driver Parallel 4 is what I just said.
Driver Parallel Lines is just Driver 4.
How come it didn't say that on the box?
I don't think it is.
Right.
I remember this.
Okay I remember this now.
Drop me in Harlem.
One way or enough.
Liquor stores huh?
That mean you're on your way up or your way down.
I've already played this.
We're gonna do Indiana Jones.
I've already played it.
So wait so Driver 4.
I just maybe I thought oh I played Driver 4
because the name of the video was Driver 4.
So when I was like oh Driver Parallel Lines.
That's a different spin-off Driver game
that I've never played before.
Just put up a gameplay video and react to it.
All right.
Indiana Jones for the Xbox.
Adventure has a name.
Let me ask in the mod chat is he okay?
I drive.
Guys I've seen hundreds of billions of frames.
The amount of data that's been from this screen
put into here and me streaming it.
I've played.
Does anyone want to count the amount of games
I've played on stream or on YouTube?
It has to be at least like two or three thousand.
It has to be thousands of them.
At least two or three thousand.
Is it gonna get DMCA too?
Just say you forgot like a normal person.
I did.
That's and I'm just explaining.
All right we're good.
You are obliterated right now.
All right is it Harrison Ford?
Oh it should be that same guy that did Tom Hanks.
That'd be great.
I played this growing up.
It kind of sucks.
Pretty good.
You gotta check.
This guy has three acting credits.
They're all Harrison Ford.
Great doing a pretty damn good job.
So many of these games would just ledge grab Andes.
You know what I mean?
Like I said oh grab the ledge and pull yourself up the ledge.
Okay let me see.
He's so tired already.
No I'm I'm not tired right now.
What do you mean he's so tired?
Can I press something?
This water to fill up my canteen.
Can you drink it?
Why does it smell bad?
Why is he he's like uh there's gonna be an awesome cat puke here.
Be ready to clip it.
Be ready to clip this cat puke because you know it's coming.
How do I use that?
How do I use this machete?
You don't have one.
But didn't he say I'm gonna use my machete?
He didn't he say I'm gonna use my machete?
Or did he say I need to use a machete?
Oh let me do the yeah yeah every game had this shit.
Even Super Mario.
That's punch not jump.
B is jump.
Thank god machete.
Okay that's actually really good to know.
Mm-hmm that looked dangerous.
This is so boring now because I'm now aware of how long the ledge climbing is.
Thanks.
This game looks incredibly boring.
Not really.
It's just a game.
It's just a video game.
There's a jump.
There's a run.
There's a there's a slash.
We want driver.
We want driver parallel lines.
These guys are no boy scouts.
According to the German video ran 4,800 hours of video.
Okay so 4,809 hours of video with the assumption that he's running at
60 hertz.
German has personally viewed over one million.
Is it billion?
That's one billion individual frames.
If it was 144 hertz it would be 2.4 billion individual frames.
Damn.
And that's what just makes it into videos.
Right.
And he can't remember the last 100.
Wait till you get older.
You'll see.
So wait till you get older.
Wait till you get a little older.
You'll see.
You're not gonna remember.
Yeah guys sorry.
I I mean I don't I remember kind of playing Spelunky when it came out.
But like I forgot that until I just thought about it.
I already have.
Yeah my memory is already bad.
Can I sneak?
How do I beat am I just gonna get it?
Get out of the menu dude.
All right sounds good.
Who made this game?
Hey it's me the American.
Everything you heard is true.
The fire killed me.
What the fuck is this garbage?
All right one last try.
One last try.
Guys they made the DaVinci code.
Same company.
Have I played all their games today?
They made Men in Black the game.
Star Trek Deep Space Nine.
Buffy the Vampire Slayer.
Indiana Jones.
Wrath Unleashed.
Star Wars Episode 3.
Mark Echoes Getting Up.
The DaVinci code.
And then a cancelled game called Dirty Harry.
Interesting.
Interesting okay.
Very cool.
How do I reload the gun?
All right the game just got way better.
Because I can I get a chair.
Uh what is this?
Can I dig?
Let's try to do that.
It's doing that music.
It's doing the Star Wars type music.
The one that goes
And it is the best.
Press Y.
I'm pressing Y.
I get to it didn't do that last time.
We're good.
I remember this game on PS2.
It sucks balls.
That's such like a ridiculous term.
Like oh I played this before too.
This thing sucks balls.
Okay uh from here.
Where am I going?
Oh this thing sucks ass.
It's like what?
It's just uncomfortable.
Like how weird this is.
And dog shit.
It wasn't even good.
That wasn't even good.
All right so what the what am I what am I doing here?
What happened to my hat?
What's going on here?
Up there?
I don't.
Wait and where am I going?
You just that guy fucking ruined everything out of here.
All right I just I'm gonna rip the disc out.
I'm just gonna pull the disc out.
I'm gonna pull out the disc.
I'm gonna I'm just taking I'm just gonna take out the disc.
You know what I'm gonna do something else.
I'm gonna move on to another game.
I think I'm gonna take out the disc.
One more second.
I'm gonna give it 10 seconds.
Nine eight seven six five four three two come on.
Where's the water?
One and a half one and three quarters two two and a half two and three quarters three three
and a half four and a half all right let's try it again all right we're good done this
ought to even up the odd gun what do I do with this down there I don't know here please put it
down I I will in a second all right let's get a new pull up.
Do you want to see Brute Force or Blood Omen 2.
That's it Brute Force or Blood Omen 2.
What about the Fellowship of the Ring?
I beat the first level of that.
I don't play it ever again.
Tell us what those are.
I don't know.
I don't know what they are.
This one says dangerous alone deadly together and the other one says the other one says
the legacy of Kane which one that was fun it just wasn't very good it was all right if I
was a huge fan of Indiana Jones I would make sure I had that like just round out my whole collection.
All right Brute Force or uh Blood Omen 2.
Why do I feel like I've played one of these before somehow legacy of Kane I feel like
I probably played a long time ago I like the Xbox pause screen yeah I do too I just want to
make sure it's not here for that long because it burns into my screen legacy of Kane is real
shit okay well I think that's what you're voting for so we're gonna play legacy of Kane Blood Omen
2.
All right let's try it.
Soul Reaver on PS1 was really cool.
I feel like I remember that game is this stuff still burned in from the first day
no thankfully it turning the monitor off for a day or two helps it fixes it
yikes okay sorry so glad I turned that down because that was awful for me
Crystal Dynamics look at all these game studios that we all know Crystal Dynamics made this
this is Blood Omen 2 so we're we're jumping in like the third or fourth sequel of the game at
this point sorry we don't know what's going on they made the Avengers game this is on Steam
is it really cool you shouldn't be playing it I can't I'm being speech jammed I can't even
hear myself thinking somebody said you shouldn't you shouldn't be playing it if it's on PC yeah
but I mean I already put the disk in oh all right very cool let's go am I gonna get like obsessed
with this game yeah vibration on let's go am I hold and hold left trigger to block attacks
tap left trigger as each enemy attack starts I mean I feel like okay um it's a cat puke menu
maybe a little what's more fun I'll try the fun one yeah PC ports of old console games usually
are awful and the developer has not updated this for anything past like Windows 7 or something
so it's still a huge pain in the ass to actually get in that big problem this might be bugs
original hardware chapter one slums welcome to
Riddian it looks kind of crunchy it looks kind of crunchy
I could do it really good but I need the headphones out you want to do a good one
should I do a good one yes can I get a poll to see if I should do a good one yes or no
do you want me to go do an all-in all-bearer yes or no it's a checkpoint
we are in the oldest and most decrepit part of the city where few people dare to come
place to train train me you take me for a dog your memory has been shattered and your body
has lain dormant for 200 years what skills you had must be recovered before you can be of any
use to the cabal you must learn to fight and to survive I thought you were taking me to feed
patience vampire first knew that you are stronger and faster than mortal men oh there we go to jump
higher and farther than any human that ever lived wait what is this all bearer or all barely seek
for a place to jump all right 85 percent right now here we go I'm gonna go away from the mic
it's probably gonna be really really really annoying I go like this yeah I don't want to
be super awful I'm not gonna be on camera either oh oh my god I can't do it
chain chain he's your brother kane you destroy him pretty good pretty good I even doubt at the
end there actually even doubt pretty well at the end it was kind of rough at the beginning
dude you're scaring my dog yeah I told you I was I had to get away from the mic
I told you I did it back here on purpose you woke me up my cat my cat just ran away
what what do you mean you just woke up my entire family I was falling asleep at my desk
you got you you voted for it you voted for it 76 well there's only 1300 votes how many people are
sleeping in this channel 1300 votes there are 18 000 people here how many of you are sleeping
you're evil I don't know how many people are asleep watching my stream when I say hey guys
all right you want me to do an all-in pallbearer and I even have you vote for it everybody's like
all right here we go I'm gonna do it I'm gonna it's here comes an all-in pallbearer scream
I'm gonna go for it I'm sorry but that that I'm sorry but that's the way things are
can you imagine sitting asleep and just like when you're killing it's just like what the
fuck and you don't even care what it is you don't care what you're listening to it's just fuck
whoever is doing this fuck you turn it off and you just I think we lost a thousand people right
there like it doesn't matter what it is it's just like I don't care what this is shut it the fuck up
and turn it off I hate whatever it is I think that just happened I said destroy him yes I did
okay let's play I can't believe 1300 people just are you sleeping do a full send destroy him no
no I'm not gonna do that again I'm I set up the microphone away so it wouldn't be so awful
I did it for like five seconds or so and we move on I missed it
hold on let me see how bad it really was people are like hurry up move on move on
we're good we're good let me just I just need to see how bad was it really was it really that bad
somebody linked it and listen that wasn't even that bad what was wrong with that what was wrong
with that I mean those two like stepping on a fucking squeaky toy too hard that's not even that
loud that's not even that bad you guys are all making it up it wasn't loud it was just bad
let's play the game stop making us relive that what is going on right now you don't even know
who that is 75 percent of you don't know who paul bear is so I was just I just sounded like an
absolute what oh okay now that makes a lot more sense as to why everyone's like what's wrong with
you what movie is he from oh no oh no it's this it's this guy you tell me if I came close not bad
yeah so I didn't wait how many you guys really don't know that you don't know the reference
okay all right I'm not fucking around anymore I know like like 5 000 people just left they're
probably never coming back because thanks a lot thanks a lot guys thanks a lot now they're never
coming back okay x is pull the lever I thought it was from Star Trek when he goes no no it's
Kane one sec mod chat just linked this and I have to watch it I'm sorry if you're expecting a video
game to be played right now I do apologize but we need to watch this watch party I wish I could
apologize to those people that's not even close you could win a freak I'm already playing the
xbox right now all right that was I thought that was gonna be like a deep fake fan that person that
linked that okay all right let's play the game no more I'm not gonna have to scream anymore the
person that came in here like four hours ago hey dude scream as loud as you can hey I don't want
to do that I just did it because like I thought I think I thought like 15 000 people voted for it
but only a thousand people did and 17 000 people were sleeping and I just screamed and made them
wake up and now they hate me great he sought to move this victim but he met me instead
that was a good video actually loved and direct me to his throat drink then I will be waiting
no there's definitely not guys 90 percent of the audience does not sleep in a dead sleep
during the stream it's probably like five percent it's not that many if you are wounded seek out
blood to restore your vital must know too that by drinking the blood of others you will gradually
become stronger and harder to kill we call this a vampire's lore
you will need their blood to survive let us continue wait I thought that was like funny all
right remember your fly is done
while we are superior to humans in many ways we also have certain weaknesses that they do not
possess though it is life-giving to humans water is deadly to vampires its touch burns our skin
immersion in water can kill us avoid it at all costs also know that scattered throughout meridian
our relics of our ancestors useless to humans only vampires can access these coffins and use
the power within seek these out on your journey cool okay so don't just water if I could I if
I could go back and just delete the cane scream I would interested to go like shit I wish I could
I wish I could just go into the vod and just like just snip that part out and even if a jump cut
like people would be like what happened what why did that happen because I don't know must
make a glitch with the game or something he's so fixated on this Jesus am I supposed to be
drinking blood I think so thank god I wish I could go back in the vod and delete that part
just snip that part like just that right when I fell I have such a stupid idea okay I'm doing
it soon I'm gonna do it like within the next couple weeks I'm going to pre-record an entire
stream no I'm not even gonna tell you but you know what I'm gonna do I'm just gonna pre-record
a whole stream I just have to like cut all the shitty stuff that I do see how long see
what you what you guys do I spoke before that's called a YouTube video yeah but not the way you
think to destroy this they have developed special defenses you see here precisely does it do should
you so much as touch it you will be burned as by fire the seraphim have raised these wards
throughout meridian we can go no farther this way follow me into the sewer somebody's got it
yeah we're talking about as if I played through the game in one try like what kind of egomaniac
would you have to be what kind of megalomania of making it so I'm trying to make you guys think I
beat the game I did everything perfectly or something your first line of you have to be
kidding me give me a really hard game too using your inhuman speed you can also defend yourself
by blocking attacks I shall now strike at you this is what I said did I say megalomania
yeah you guys don't know what that is and we can proceed to the next lesson
press L to block oh this is the the perfect timing one okay cool hey it's not that bad
we are all armed with a natural weapon our claws use them to kill your enemies
you can practice by attacking me if you see an enemy become tired use this opportunity
to grab him once grabbed you can throw him a great distance hold and hold press Y to grab
and press wait are you doing like a choke oh okay excellent your lesson is over for the moment
continue through the sewer and I shall meet you again shortly that is unforgivable tonight
I think that everyone's been having fun I think everywhere chat's been all right
can you play conqueror's bad fur day oh when I do N64 I'm gonna do N64 eventually we'll play a
bunch of those yeah I'll do a full N64 collection kind of like this let's play a ton of it
here you are at last conqueror's on xbox yeah it is your first true test a gang of
are in camp number stands guard his fate approaches you must kill him kane you have
the skill to block and dodge his attacks first thing I see in chat is what I'm gonna eat tonight
once you have felled him drink his blood to restore yourself from any wounds you may receive
bagel I will be watching bagel look look look it was like chunks on this
fury okay did I miss it do pizza bagel you know there's a lot of stuff that is so good on a bagel
but people just don't ever think to do it bagel sandwiches and I'm not just talking about egg
I'm talking about tuna like a tuna melt on a bagel ham sandwich on a bagel
especially if it's warmed up and toasted oh yeah ham and cheese on a bagel is perfect
these are our supernatural abilities bagel french dip I've never had that sounds good though
giving us unique powers much of your former power cane has been weakened during your long
hibernation mist you see here can be used to your advantage rubin on a bagel you have the
ability to assume a missed form and become nearly invisible you can move silently to bring down our
prey from behind cream cheese and locks at times when you are outnumbered look for mist from which
to kill your enemies I really have to be in the mood for that though if you are pursued you can
hide in mist to escape now use this gift to kill those before you in the cemetery
corned beef is so nasty what oh it's not you just never had it made well maybe you have
okay missed it's like a stealth mode how useful how did you see me
me
should I go why does it keep telling me to do this I just did it legacy of
cane did I not yeah I got it what's the next step here up this way didn't I come what do you want
me to do I mean I did that already why I already stealth killed that person where do I go am I
missing something here oh I can go this way oh I actually can use weapons activate the weapon box
while holding a weapon doesn't hold to activate the weapon box while holding a weapon it's just
pretty good you should do a joke where you pretend that owls are in your room but you're the only one
that can hear them glyph energy eyes of the seraphim it supplies power to all of meridian
the gate you see can be opened using this energy activate the glyph box this will bring power to
the gates lever and allow you to open it it's fun it's fun oh 45 minutes without chapstick
what will you do if I do okay a secret society existing what do I get if I do that you may see
them working on glyphs from time to time they rarely talk with the townsfolk and very little
is known about their origins ahead is the market with a common dregs of meridian engage in their
filthy commerce beyond the market is the bridge that leads to the lower city make your way east
to the bridge I shall meet you there and where are you going I shall scout ahead to ensure that
you don't meet any seraphim patrols you aren't ready for them yet how trusting of you to leave
me to my own devices consider it an act of good will how many tubes of chapstick do you go through
um actually quite a few not because I use it too much but because I actually just lose them
they just disappear I'll use the same one for a week and then it's gone it does not exist
what's that try drink everybody's blood should I what was that powering stop this is why I
fucking hate streaming outside it's so annoying having just like an open roof screaming an open
roof germa streaming an open roof like you told you complain about your room being so hot just
take the roof off because I figured that'd be like still privacy and shit never listening to
you fucking idiots ever again I can't go in this what is it powering up here I'm bored um
I'm just kind of chilling out now I think we hit the peak with the pallbearer scream and now I'm
just like kind of you know I'm just chill I got all that out of me you know what I mean
just relax it now how much longer um at least until the chapstick wears off because I can't
leave for at least 45 minutes there are animals here all right this is fun but I am I'll do
something else it's a cool game I could see myself just sitting on the couch just playing this
it's very cool but I think I need to play it it's almost like jumping through a glass window
you've never loathed a game more in your life that's not true
hear this so-called leader's plans and learn what he thought his plans might be for me
cain this way I'm gonna play this game called maximum chase here close the gate
cain way to reach the lower city the smuggler's tunnel will take you there
pestilent vampire the grand hotel in the slums a contact will meet you there
he will tell you where to go stinking verminous bloodsucking fiend do you want your death now
come and you shall have it come back I was alone at last in a city changed beyond all recognition
in a lab like links should I flinks is available on the newer platform isn't it
I think you can play it on the game pass but answers were promised me in sanctuary
after that I would know what to do that's a good one that's pretty good keep going
I'm gonna put maximum chase yeah it's on game pass that was literally sick hair flick you guys
fumbled voting for that vampire game no that game is actually a classic video game it's actually
really good but I feel like it I don't know if I want to play um legacy of cain for like
20 hours takes a bit to ramp up all right what about this one
this based off a book well it's based off a movie clearly wait view film wait play the film
let's watch this it is fmv stop stop that stop it I'm gonna skip get those fucking flashlights
out of my face stop doing that oh my god you can't shoot this from the other angle for at
least a few of these they have to be facing the camera for all of them every single shot
oh my god stop put them down even this one it doesn't you don't need to have this guy doing this
stop aiming this shit in our faces why are they doing this make sure to take out the big case
that's just luggage that's luggage look at can I go back do you see that was this just luggage
this isn't like a big cool briefcase that was like a look at this light in your eyes
you're gonna get a copyright strike dude I don't like this is this is the no I'm not don't worry
boss I'm shining a different light in their fucking face the cg okay very cool so that was
some type of did we just see everything that wasn't the whole movie was it oh we only have
the first cutscene unlocked well that's just not gonna do that's not gonna do at all
for a traffic cop forever the whiner huh urban take it like a man this time man some of us spent
all of last month crushing the drug cartel and haven't had a day off this is dubbed you take your
day off I'll take the ticket whatever next time I'll be getting your Camaro man oh what did the
last thing we watched have to do with this hey we get hit okay we're playing this whole game
wrapping we're not leaving until I beat this whole thing I refuse to stop the stream until
this game is done three two one how do I drive how do we drive the car like dude what is happening
we would be liquidated right now we would be liquefied right now
what I don't get it there's no indicator I'm not going anywhere is this the what we just did
all right this is gonna go on for a long time without any it's already said dude this is like
a disney stunt show wall what was the objective no this is just what happens when you let the dvd
sub menu just loop over and over and over again of your favorite action movie this just doesn't end
does anybody know what we're supposed to be doing do something let me lose these guys
okay let me lose these guys lose them whoa now what I don't understand what's supposed to happen
here get out of the way did I finally make it to that part this game is fucking terrible
this game is so bad okay so what do I there's no map there's no indicators there's no nothing
it's just go find that alleyway dude I don't know where it's trying to get me to go
drive just drive till you see arrows
my god like I got it oh thank god wait what
what
all right movie time wait do we watch this whole thing I don't think we watch this
at the same time okay it hurts my head I can't look at this anymore
I can't I can't skip it we're here okay no it's too much stimulation
why is it just on the hood of the car right here they just kind of got lazy at the end of this movie
single angle what did I do that oh I did it okay I I'm done we have it's almost over
whoa you see that slow motion dude all right here comes the big finish right here this is it
I almost didn't make it all right I kind of feel like shit right now I'm Rick what's your name
Katherine Katherine Stanfield what the hell happened all I know is I got home and they were there
there god damn it no not another chase sequence not another chase sequence
why do I have my hand on the wheel still I'm not firing out the window what was the point of me
changing seats I'm helping her drive the car still I just made this way harder for both of us
for no reason I haven't shot the gun one time I have not fired the gun once that just was annoying
what I did okay here we go what how what's happening why is this a light gun game how
many bullets do I have in this car what I don't I get am I shooting at the right people what are
we cautioning why can I charge the gun up that's gonna be like 200 million dollars
I don't know I wouldn't say that this isn't like oh don't worry I'll get the check I don't you
don't say that here okay now there's a is that us no why are we fighting a tractor what this
who drove this shit into the parking garage I got it all right all right all right settle down settle
down settle down somebody just said it and I have to take a second somebody said this is making me
sick let's take a minute just one second okay but just chill for a second take a sip of water
I got some right here I feel like I'm playing every light gun game ever made at the same time
in a room full of I don't like screaming bats or something okay we ready oh all right this is it
all right come on this is it thank god oh my goodness thank goodness
whoo oh this is the we're not watching this I mean how do I get out of here
go are you okay yeah crude but effective wait this is yeah this is dubbed over
this is dubbed over I thought there was okay I touch your beard yeah so what now
off to the LAPD we'll see what they have to say about this AI generated that whole game even the
thing they're walking on his green screen they're not gonna let us off that easy but wait why did
we get out of the car emergency police business I gotta commandeer your vehicle so you're a cop
yeah and off duty one I can't I can't react this is very that was just weird
all right I'm not doing another one of these that's it this is just the same map but a different car
this time it's just a truck replacing the other car I'm gonna give this one attempt only we are
going one attempt only the rest of the game how smooth no I feel like the game is generating the
level 15 feet in front of me I don't know where I'm going but if the levels just here I please do
an ASMR video with this game okay so what we're gonna do here is some very quick mouth noises for
you to help you sleep I know you're listening to this because it helps you sleep at night
some stuff in the background don't pay attention to me talking so pop pop did I do a full circle
that was a meditation just what I want you to do is I want you to breathe in through your nose
and out through your mouth we'll do it at the same time you and me ready so here we go it's in
the first second here and then now very very nice excellent breathing so now what I want you to do
is I want you to breathe in again that's right pay attention to what I have I haven't known the
direction I'm supposed to be driving for the last five straight minutes I'm telling you the game
is being created in front of me I somehow made it but we're not watching this hey we get to keep
going home sweet home I'll just take a quick look around stay in the car and be ready to roll
that window amically huge is it well it's a big truck never mind officially hit 45 minutes without
a chapstick why are these cars like weird bugs this camera shake is so it doesn't need to be
that much they were so afraid of you seeing the outline of the green screen they were terrified
of it are we still going it's a shooting mission first try if I don't get it first try I'm done
I'm not playing this I'm done after this holy shit what oh oh god let's go the only film we
are watching is the one that's live action Rockford Institute it's what Irvin was going on about
in connection to this development James Stanfield lost his life
this music does not make any sense in here either what's wrong
my brother your brother he died three days ago
who is this yeah they are going they're gonna kill that guy
oh my who are these people who are these people please turn it down fine whoa why is this even
here why can you even do this what's the point of that Vegas I like that place what was that
not why did I why can I come in here I don't know where to go you're lost yeah other side
wrong way go around it I see what you mean it's hard to see I just suppressed a yawn
and then fucked everything up it's ah I kind of like want to lose but I can't I'm playing too good
but right before he died he sent me this show me what is that is it like a big um keepsake from
my mother is it don't touch that and this oh my god oh my god oh my god
if that's it my brother's friend where have I seen that before can you get in touch with the guy
that exact look what is that it's it's yep it's TMNT TMNT ooze that's exact that is just TMNT ooze
I love how he has a revolver like that that has six bullets but yet I shoot four or five thousand
times I really don't want to do this I'm gonna turn way down here I'll make this more tolerable
for everybody watch the bumps what a tropical beach in the background I don't I don't have
access to that right now I don't have a tropical beach I gotta fight this boss wait die no put
family guy moments in the top right corner I can't do that I can't do that that actually will get me
in trouble dude I can't I can't do that you don't understand I can't do that as fucking funny as
that would be what a germa compilation in the top right corner what what do you mean germa
compilation how do you fit shit in here what do you want what do you what video do you want me to
put on put temple run gameplay at the bottom put on germa craft no how about a bird cam I think
that works all right like just bird cam like birds bird cam germa's worst face and worst
moment you're laughing at vehicle accidents okay hold on I'll put this one on to see if it we're
gonna see if it matches okay wait I'm interested in this so keep in mind I I cannot hear it so I
don't know how much it matches up I cannot hear it this is apparently me laughing at vehicle accidents
how loud is this though this is gonna be so stupid okay fine okay how's the audio good
all right let's go let's go let's go let's go
so if you don't mind how about we mind besides they'll only come after you next
I don't want to put it louder you're trying to turn this off everybody so you're a singer huh
yeah I haven't released my CD yet but when I sing I use the name Malvina we need to wait
okay here we go let's go I'm going to get ADHD is it too loud I know it doesn't look like it
I think it's okay this is a great stream germa yeah you meant that as an insult I think but I
think it's fun all right let's go let's go let's go let's go I'm putting a stop to this right now
I'm putting a stop to this right now I somebody said to put slime videos like the people who
they play with this you know what I'm gonna tell you guys something because I think have I
talked about this before I don't care about leaking shit because who cares I'm definitely
not gonna do it at this point but maybe maybe somebody will maybe someone will did I talk about
spending like years straight making children's videos for YouTube and don't tell anyone and just
see how long it takes for people to figure it out I did I've talked about that right
a long time ago I wanted to do like double time streaming this is the part with maybe like four
or five years ago I wanted to stream and have a different YouTube channel where I just made
children's videos as a different person and still stream the same amount of time that I do
but have this like kids kind of content where I was doing like all kinds of like wacky stuff
it's like oh mr goofball and make hundreds of videos hundreds of them hundreds of them
and see how long it took before people figured it out because you know that if I did this for
like two or three years and eventually everybody found it it would be like what what are you doing
you mean to tell me that there is it there are there are years worth of children's videos that
you've made high production value by the way not dog shit not just like five seconds we're talking
like 10 to 15 minute long real educational shit and there would be like five or six hundred videos
over the course of five years I wanted to do it so bad but it was just too much work it's okay don't
worry yeah why children's videos I don't know because like I had this thing in my brain where
like I was gonna see if I could hit a billion views on that channel before before like germa
985 hit like I don't know like a certain amount of subs or something I was gonna play this internal
game with myself see if I could hit like a billion views that with like children's videos
see if I could like overtake the other channel why not elderly videos what what do you mean yeah
why well that's a good question to ask yourself a bill yeah I was thinking I could get like a
billion views a billion of them a billion views a billion of those views how many views are on the
regular channel how many views are on the regular channel like just like the germa 95 youtube
channel 500 million 300 million I could have gotten to a billion views a billion
let's say this two or three forms 250 million I could have done it dude you've gone completely
off the deep end I would you know what I would have real no wouldn't have been slime videos
it wouldn't have been slime videos it would have been like high quality children's entertainment
I would have made sure that it was like the best videos I was gonna make like characters and
and like puppets and shit like it was gonna be awesome it was gonna be truly fun
dinosaur videos you oh yeah animated stuff I was gonna really go all into it I was gonna go all
up the channel has 224 million views the auto show that's exactly what I mean auto show would
have been perfect I would have done the voice and everything too aren't you already making
videos for children no no no that's not true actually second germa has 245 million
so I got about half a billion views across the two youtube channels what just happened why is
this helicopter in such a weird spot I lost all right that's it I'm done I think it would have
been fun yeah I think it's a good place to call it I'm hungry I'm getting hungry well I apologize
to the 2000 people that left when I screamed the pallbearer thing hopefully you don't hate me
forever do a children's show stream I mean there's yeah I trust me I've thought about it where the
stream just turns on and it's just a it's just like a sesame street show and it's not I don't
we don't talk about just like yeah of course of course I'm gonna do like a children's entertainment
stream and it wouldn't be funny it's not gonna be funny like oh is what a funny no no no no
excuse me this is gonna be quality a quality children's entertainment stream I'm gonna I'm
writing it down I'm writing it down all right then you're so weird man well you should kind of like
the muppets I wonder okay what what if it's really fun though hey can you talk in the background for
a little while while I play some shit yeah sure five minutes that would be cool if it's not terrible
god damn it I see a bunch of like puppets and stuff me interacting with them and like don't
eat that many cookies when's the next breath of the wild stream I'm begging you um I don't probably
soon and there's gonna be a lot of chill streams this year too I think I told we I talked about it
already but maybe there'll be some maybe there'll be some children's entertainment streams along
with like just chilling out playing games I'm gonna play breath of the wild I promise but
I can do some chill streams all right uh I'll see you guys later I'll see you guys actually
there's a big thing coming up here uh this weekend Elden Ring co-op mod with stir with
randomizer turned on uh it's gonna be probably pretty cool I'm looking forward to it seems like
a pretty simple thing we're gonna test it a little bit so that's Saturday we'll see you Saturday uh
I think we're starting at two so 2 p.m pacific what is randomizer it is every single enemy and
every single item could be wrong but it's every enemy in the game is completely randomized it
could be a boss or it could just be like a rat you can walk out the front door and one of the
dragons just might be there just out out the front door good luck yeah that was some more xbox there
is a lot more ps1 ps2 and xbox but I don't want to sensory overload I feel a little sensory
overloaded right now uh I'm gonna get some food I'm gonna relax and I'll see you guys on Saturday
for Elden Ring we'll put it away for a little bit hope you guys had fun with these streams they're
always really fun for me to do hopefully they're fun for you to watch so maybe we'll see you again
let's uh say our goodbyes oh okay there were some really good ones I feel like the xbox has had some
real quality stuff I mean Indiana Jones was Aragon was well that one was cool what else was there
Maximum Chase remember that one that was pretty fun Circus Maximus might be my favorite game of
the night you're allergic to jet set radio I played it for Dreamcast a couple of years ago
now I'm not against going back to old games that I played that I've already done but I mean if we've
done it already it exists already I actually remember playing it and I didn't like it I
remember being like the controls are stupid it's too hard remember that was a complaining stream
it was yeah I was a complainer music's great though the main lasso though god I know I know
that might be one of the worst things that's ever been recorded of me doing it was so bad
all right I'll take uh I'll take my wait hold on a lot of subs today damn thanks guys I'll eat
at least one serving of vegetables today please uh drink a glass of water if you haven't drink one
glass of water if you haven't already listen to your mother you know eat some vegetables if you
haven't do carrots and ranch count yeah moisturize your face with a face moisturizer don't skimp on
that do that when you come out of the shower just put a little you know moisturize your face
no all right take it easy guys see you later see you Saturday Elden Ring I'm excited the first
time I've actually played Elden Ring or streamed it or touched it in since the game came out like
a month or two after the game came out so I'm excited see you later take care have a good night