Hello. I don't know what the emote is. What is it? Pepe face? Pepe laugh? Laughing face?
You know the one I'm talking about. Everybody knows about it. Do I have to explain what I mean
by Pepe face in the title? What is it called? I don't even have it activated. It's like Pepe
laugh or something. I don't know. The one where it's like Pepe the frog and his teeth are showing
like this and he's leaning back in his chair. Why is my mic quality so bad? Am I in the wrong mic?
No I'm not. Why is my mic quality so bad? I don't know.
I don't know. I think I have a nice mic. Who knows? It's not even been one minute
and Phylactery Lich just gave $50. 5000. But that didn't mean life at 30 seconds.
Watching your old videos reminds me of how old I am. Anyways, here's some casino money. Thank you.
Really appreciate that. Watching old videos of mine reminds me of how old I am too. Because
I get to watch myself degrade over time. I get a 10-year mirror. Don't you understand?
I can watch. Guys, I used to make a video like every other day. You know that thing? Oh,
take a picture of myself once every day for 10 years. I did that. I can go back and just see
me aging over a decade. You're aging like fine wine. Hey, thanks. I think I'm doing okay.
Oh, but anyways, let's talk about some stuff before we get started. I know, I always do.
All right, here we go. He's gonna talk about stuff. This one's important. Nobody say it.
Nobody say it because I didn't get a chance to tell anybody yet. Don't say it. Don't say it.
Ah, somebody said it. Ah, shit. What do I do now? Turn the stream off.
The carnival stream is set for September 21st, 2019. Of this year. Of this year. So I'm fucking
excited. A lot of work and a lot of time went into this. And I hadn't even gotten started.
I actually have to get on a plane next week and fly across the country to the facility
and go back and forth. We're gonna do a site visit. We're gonna walk around. We're gonna
talk about everything that's gonna happen. It is not Boston. No, somewhere else. It is somewhere
else in the United States of America. But the facility seems pretty great. The person that's
helping me and the team that's helping me work on that end of things. Area 51. No, it's not in
Nevada. It's in another state in the United States. No, it's not Florida. Wait, we don't have to guess
what state it is. You're gonna find out soon enough. He's going to Canada. No, but that's a
reality now. And a bunch of resources going into this. I can finally tell you that it's really
actually September 21st. There's like two teams involved with this. So it's not like, oh September
23rd, maybe maybe October. No, it's a contract. So I hope it's fun. You'll get more details as we go.
Let's hope it's I think it's gonna be fucking awesome. Get a lawyer. I am a lawyer. I just
looked. It's a big contract. It's like 25 pages long. And I just like skimmed it. And I was like,
yeah. And I flipped it over. I signed it. The best kind of lawyer there is one's one that skims
contracts. Click agree. Yeah. It's an it's the end user license agreement on anything you play
or do. I don't want to sound out of the loop here, but or sound mean. But why are you doing this?
I don't know. I because I because I want to. This is real. Do I have I don't really have a
reason for anything I do here. Mainly, I think it's because I think it'll be fun.
And I think the community over the years has been involved in so many things. And we've done so
many things that it's just it's fun to do shit. It's fun to make stuff. I don't really have a
reason. And they open it up at like win or lose. I don't care. I want to try. I want to try to do
something fun. I think that you guys know that over the years like that's something. Hey,
Super Mario Maker 2. Is it going to be a film crew? Yes. This is me playing by the way. Oops,
never mind. Now that was the computer. All right. So I'm going to play just random levels. What do
you guys know we can tell? All right. Give me fun levels. I don't want to do I and I know everybody
I know what people are writing over here. I don't want to do to start the stream. Central British
time. You understand? No. New notifications? No, I want to disable notifications. All right,
so let's go to courses and then new courses search. No, no, no. You go to ID, right?
That's not going to show if I like ID to everybody, right? No. Okay. What do we do? What
are we going to start with? Well, I like your lich. Thanks for the $50 and the five community
subs and core monster for the community subs too. All right. This person said I hate German,
so we're going to do that one. D6267 searching for course. Reach towards the end to get through the
portal. Find the hidden key for for what? How many people have tried this? 20%? That's not many.
All right. By the way, I'm doing strict vetoes this stream. If I don't if I'm not this is not
to say that anybody's levels are not good. I need to warm up first. I know I quit.
What was this one again? I don't know. I got a lot. I'm not ready. I haven't played in like two
weeks. Okay, no, I'm fine. I haven't played Mario in like two and a half weeks. Last time I played
was last time you saw me streaming. I'm not ready. I don't know the controls to Mario.
Do I have to find the hidden key? This is a trick. This is a trick. Well, it's too quiet. I don't
like how quiet this one is. It's silent. Oh no. No, you can't just run and jump. You have to like
walk turn 180. Jump. Twist. They added a twist. Oh, fuck. Wait, did the dog just? No, I can't. How
do I get over there? Why am I toad? I don't know. I didn't pick this. Did I pick this?
I did pick this, didn't I? I think it's gonna pick it up. Does that make the door up here?
Holy shit. What happened? It's a P door. Oh, okay. How do I get up there? Oh, I kind of like this one.
It's kind of scary, but it's fun. This is more of a walker than a runner.
Anything over here? What is that? I don't know. I don't know. I'm gone. Oh, that's a checkpoint.
Whoa. Whoa. By the way, this is going to be a not angry one. I know that if you're watching
these streams and you've watched me play Mario Maker like twice before, right now you're just
like, oh man, I can't wait to literally like start to say like mean things about video games. No,
I'm in too good of a mood. I got a locked in date of September 21st
for that carnival stream. Nothing can anger me today.
It's not going to make me. I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm doing fine. I feel great.
Nothing's going to like bring me down. I should have seen that. I thought it was just spikes on
the wall. You're the best around. Thanks. Appreciate that. Now what? Ooh, I didn't even.
I have to read this.
Thank you door cube for the 250. We usually don't read bits like this early here, but they said,
how did you get the carnival stream off the ground this quick? But it's been years since you promised
a Noah's Ark toothbrush merch. Well, that's easy because it's impossible to find a company that's
going to manufacture custom toothbrushes for you. That doesn't exist. We're going to call Colgate.
Dear Colgate, can you make like 1200 toothbrushes for me? Or am I going to buy a bunch of blue
toothbrushes over a year from like CVS, the ones that have no brand on them, stockpile,
like 5,000 of them, and then just resell them. Isn't that as illegal? Isn't that against the law?
Oh shit. I'm dead. What? Oh, this is going to be hard. Hey, you're the lawyer here.
I skimmed it. I think that's like, no, no, no, you can. But isn't that like mean?
Let's say I buy a CVS blue toothbrush for a dollar and then I sell that CVS blue toothbrush
for $10. There's no like government agency that's going to get involved and go like,
hey, these are a dollar. What happened? All right. I got to be ready for this.
Drop it. Oh shit. I'm dead. It's guaranteed to lose here. Guaranteed.
I got to stand up on the slow down. Don't go too fast. Oh my God. I went too fast.
All right. So I got to bait the first one and then jump over the second one or just jump from,
give these livid right now. Yeah. So I got to get this one to drop before it gets over here.
Same thing. Get it to drop, drop, drop, drop. Holy shit. Now what, now what do I do? Oh fuck.
Give me a checkpoint. Oh, I hate this. No checkpoint or anything. I don't, is it safe
to fall down here? I'm going to get trolled. This is going to be, oh, now go over here.
There's going to be something on the ceiling. I just know there is. This is going to be something
in that, in that thing's arm. Does not. Okay. I just needed to know. If I jumped into that,
it would have been horrible. Slow down. If I was a Mario maker level maker, I would put just
something to kill me right there. Just, just for me to walk into. I'm this far. I don't want to
blow it for a second. I thought I was making that music. All right. This is too deliberate to have
there not be something wrong here. Ah, I told you. I fucking told, what did I tell you? Look.
Oh shit. I probably shouldn't have done that. Where are they coming from? Where are they coming
from? Where are the football helmets coming from? Oops. Should I not have done that? Oh no. Okay.
Should I hit this one too? I feel like I should hit this one. I can get it. No, there's one right
here. Hit this one, I think. I don't know. I don't know. I don't like this one. This one's too,
it's, it's very deliberate and I like just running straight really fast.
Okay. Is that it? Don't blow it. That needs, oh, that needs a key. That needs a key to the key.
Where's the key? Oh, please respawn over here. Thank God. Wait, what? I did it. I did it. Okay.
Key to the true ending. I don't need, I don't get true endings. That was fun.
That was a little scary. Why? Wasn't it? All right, we'll grab this one. This level,
this level was made for fun and not to be mean to you. All right. Well, what is the over-under
that this is mean to me? I wonder. Hey, I promised this level was not made to be mean to you.
Why do I have to say that? Why can't you just, you know, hey, here's a level, man. Check it out.
Oh, maybe he doesn't know my face. All right. Four minutes. Fire Flower Skies one one.
Okay. Let's try it. It's going to be a German short spelled in blocks.
It's too hard. All right. Well, I got it. I got it. That's good. I got over the guy with the stereo.
Turn this way. Right. Got it. Bingo. Shit. Okay. Oh, I can get up there and get that 50.
I got to get two. Come on. They weren't lying. This is a fun one. You got, you're playing to my like
addicting shit that I do. Okay. No, it's not worth it. I might die if this goes down all the way.
I thought that was gonna just kill me. All right. Give me, I need to knock this guy out.
Ooh, how do I get the key? Uh-oh. Is it gonna be tough? Uh, what? Feels good when you get a nice
string. You can lay a nice volley back and forth. Well, can I bring one of you? It's all right.
Too much weight. That's not it, is it? Is there weight in Mario? That's definitely not weight.
Oh my god. You got me. You fucked me up with the whole weight comment. I'm trying to like jump
lighter because like maybe I weigh more. This, they don't have like weight classes in this. Toad
is like shorter and fatter. How did I get over there the first time? Toad has good acceleration
but bad turning? Is he a fucking car? What are you talking about? Wait, what? That's not real.
Yeah, Mario's got really good handling, but his brakes are always like kind of shitty.
All right, get me up there. He's automatic. I'm just gonna carry this. Get out. Okay. All right.
Excuse me. What happened there? Did he escape from my grasp? I have to go like this. No, I don't.
Okay. Um, uh-oh. Why did I do that? Do I have to go down? Okay, I gotta go down.
Holy shit. Okay, I got it. Give me that spring. I thought that was a hole.
I thought that was a hole. I thought that was a hole. I thought it was a hole. Like I'm explaining
the funny fucking, hold on. Oh, nothing has got that handling. Fuck. It's all right. I know how
to get down there. I almost missed it. You think everything is a hole. I have to think everything
is a hole. I'm playing Super Mario. Wait a minute. Is there a secret? Maybe I can jump up there?
Why am I, why am I storing them? This is bad. Why did I do that?
Uh-oh. My thumb got cold. Oh my god. Why is my thumb so cold? Okay, I might have to do like a few
push-ups. I'm not kidding. I guess I have blood in my hands. I'm telling you. I have to get blood
in my hand. I'm freezing. My hands are turning into ice. Oh, I'm gonna fall. Stop laughing.
Well, okay. I know that's there. Oh my god. No. My hands are freezing. They're turning like stone.
Every time I move my fingers like I hear like crack and my fans crack. This happens to me
sometimes. Does this happen to anybody else? I get like bad circulation in my hands. Oh my god. I'm
gonna fucking not get angry because today nothing's gonna make me angry today. Nothing's gonna make me
mad today. You know what today is? September 21st. Well today's not, that's not what today's
date is. Oh my goodness gracious. It's okay. I'm gonna go, I'm gonna go put like my hands in the
microwave. Just for like two seconds. Oh, I gotta go get that stupid thing. All right, I'm good.
Let me just do this. All right, I just did a person microwave right here. That's a little
bit better. Turn down my AC. All right, I'm not gonna, I'm not gonna even go that way. What's the
point? To get the secret true ending? We don't get true endings on this screen. A lot of you know
that by now. Hold on, this is interesting. I'm gonna, I guess I'm gonna go this way.
Ooh, all right, hold on. What's over here? You know, I only get bad endings? That's not true.
I'm gonna wait for another one. I even said it out loud. You heard me say it out loud. I said it out
fucking loud. I said it out loud. Slow down, Jeremy. I said it out loud. Why did I not do it?
I got impatient in three seconds. How is that possible? Oh god. Yeah, I know, right?
Don't worry, it's been salvaged. It's okay. I can dark souls them. Wait, that doesn't happen in
dark souls. That's all that was over here? What? That has to be more. Oh my god. I didn't know
that fire coming out of that shit. What do I do? Over to the right? I'm not stuck in here, am I?
No. What? There has to be a way. No, there has to be a way. There's got to be like a secret block or
there's got to be something hidden. Damn it. Oh, that was tricky too. Damn it. That was...
It's all right. I can... I know... This one's tricky. I'll tell you, this one... I wouldn't
put this one... This one's not hard. It's tricky. God damn it. Give me another one.
He's balding so hard. All right, you guys gotta tell me. Am I missing something on Twitch?
That's like a... Oh, he's like bald. He's like mad. You're not bald because you're mad. You're mad
because you're bald. Don't you understand? That's not... You guys got it in the reverse.
He's scalding. Easy. All right, the last... There's a hard jump over here. Once you get across,
you get to jump and then hit... Hold on. That would explain my internet rant? I don't do
internet rants. What? That's what I was talking about. That's the jump I was talking about.
I have to get it. What is it? Bang, bang, bang. Oh man. Oh man. Oh man. Oh man. I can't see from
here. Did I just almost get fucking hit by that thing? What do I do? Okay. Huh? I can't go
underneath this. I can't go this way. The way? I'm not gonna go down to the right. I don't...
He's faking it. What are you... Wait, wait, wait. What are you talking about?
How... The vine. What do you mean the vine? Oh shit. Okay. Watch out. Like I said, that guy's
good stuff. What does it throw at? Is it gonna hit me? No, it's not. Oh shit. This is gonna be
terrible. I gotta get up. Oh no. I have time. What's my time? No, this should be unlimited time in
Mario Maker. What happened? They hit the skybox? What happened? Oh, he... All right. I gotta go
quick. I can't just dick around. Let's go. I know where I need to go. Over to the right is just
getting baited. Go to acceleration. Bad balding. You're all gonna be fucking bald, all right?
I got news for all you young kids here. You're all gonna be bald. All of you. And it happens to
everybody. So you can just stare down that highway knowing that you're gonna drive down that road
eventually. You're all gonna be bald. All of you. Do you hear my voice? I've been talking a lot
recently. I've got a lot of... I can't, man. All right. Ravraw just gave 10 community subs. Thank you.
Thanks for the 10 subs. That really was an old man yell. I need to like work on that.
You're all gonna be bald. I can't wait like 30 years from now. How old am I gonna be? Like 75?
I'm gonna be like 96. Lying in my deathbed. And like Twitch 2 will be out by then. And fucking
super DX, Degeneration X 49222. You're gonna be streaming right there. You in the chat.
Gotta set bald like 10 times. I'm gonna be watching your channel while you're spreading
fingers through your hair. Going, I don't understand. Like I'm... This wasn't like this
like a few years ago. And people get in the chat gonna be like, haha bald! Bald! And I'm gonna be
lying on my bed just going like... You fucker. I told you. At least I'll get to see it. I'll at
least get to see it. Finally, I can die in peace. One of my Twitch chatters is bald now.
What about the... Grandpa, what about your will? You didn't sign that yet.
Make sure you skim the will first. I'm not gonna hold on to this thing for that one.
Why do I hold on to these guys? What did I just... I just like set that guy up to kill me later.
What was over here? Oh shit. I don't know. I'm going this way. Ooh, fire. Wait, can Toad do fire
in canon? He's not like worthy to eat the fire flower, right? Only like Mario and Luigi can eat
these. It's like the hammer. All right, I gotta get down here. I'm not sure what that did. Do I
actually have to carry that all the way over here? Uh oh, I think I do. Don't do that to me.
I gotta jump. Jump off the... Oh god. No, come on. No. No. Come here.
Do you remember the door? I'm okay. I'm fine. What do you mean the door? No, I don't have the key.
I don't have the key. I don't have the key. Pause it. I don't have the key. What are you talking
about? Low door. Go right. The bottom... What? Oh god. Key! Uh oh. I have 38 seconds to get down
this. It's a fucking maze. What is that? I freaked out. It's all right. I'm starting right here.
Oh, thank god. Got the checkpoint. That's all that matters. Oh, the top has spikes too.
Huh? Is Bowser here somewhere? What do I need to break? Blocks? I'm confused. Up? Around?
When I just see the Bowser face take over your screen, that means that he's here.
Isn't that what that means? Ah, what? Come on. I hit that. Don't blow up on me. No.
Welp, the ice. Does this work? Oh, it does. Okay. All right. I thought I... All right. I'm fine.
I should make a kai emote. Yeah, I just think I'm making a kai emote.
Just... All right. Spit it out. What does that do for me if I do that? What does this do?
Okay, easy. It's slippery. Just drop down? Where does this go? Oh, that was the top, right?
So I can walk around it. I get it. This is a good one. I like this one. This is a good one.
Who made this? I did. So now I can go underneath, right? Um, get out of here. Hold on. Wait.
How do I get out from under this? Oh, no. I'm just like those two. They must have done the same thing.
You know, I'm so focused on... Can I just jump over the top of this? All right. How do I die?
How do I die? Bombs can break the wooden blocks. Oh, God. Give me a break. Um,
what do you guys want to do for 200 seconds? Because I'm not starting over.
Wait, hold on. How do I die? Is this... Is this synced up? Let's do a test. Ready?
How about this? Ready? Like, you should be hearing like... Is that synced?
Is it? Okay, good. Let's see if I can do like a beat. It's too hard to do with these buttons.
Faster. I wonder how fast I can do it. This is what it's like to be in like jail here.
Just comb my hair for a little bit. I can't hit star button. I'm sorry.
Just die. I can't die. If I die, I start at the beginning. Erasable pen erasers to do fast on the
buttons. I've never heard of that technique. You can restart it without losing progress.
Are you serious? No, I can't. No, I definitely can't. Come on! Hurry up! Tell a joke. What do
you want me to say? What joke do I have right now? Besides, I can't leave the level and I can't die.
What am I supposed to say? All right. I'm an observational comedyist, so
let me... We got two turnip people, right? The ice underneath us. I'm stuck in between here.
What's an observation that I can say about this? There's nothing. There's nothing to say. I'm just
inside of the... I'm soft-locked in the game. I have nothing to say. I got it right at zero.
We're hemorrhaging viewers. That's all right. They'll be back right now. Ready?
Once I beat this first try. Three, two, one, go. I told you they'll... Look, they're back already.
They're already here. Come on, blow up. Oh, nice. Anything up here? How do I get up there?
Okay, I'm good. See, they're back. Look, we just went up by like eight viewers. Those eight people
came back. Checkpoint. Yes, we're good. That's what you got to do. Oops. Oops.
Watch out. Okay, we're good. This is a long one, but this one doesn't feel long. It feels
like it was very well thought of. And what am I supposed to do about this? Will they go up if I
jump? Uh, kind of. Oh, right. I forgot this is Super Mario. He doesn't know. He doesn't even know.
Oh my god, he doesn't know. Yes, I do. I know everything. Do the Peter Griffin laugh. Why on
earth would I do that right now? There it is. I'm not gonna do the Peter Griffin laugh. That was
good. Good level. One percent completion rate. Is that me doing all those attempts? No, it's not.
Need the Peter. I can't even do a Peter Griffin laugh. Pick this one. Pick this one. This one.
This one. This one. Try my level. You got it. Do this one. M0430R9TH. Did I do that wrong?
Was it an O instead of a zero? What just happened? That was a fucking prank level? Are you serious?
I don't even. Why? What? How would that be a prank level that says like
moth? I don't understand. Oh my god, please. Why? All right, I'm doing this one. All right,
set me real shit by the way. I don't want to like put in your fucking joke code. No joke codes. Is
this a joke code? No, it's not. Wide to pinwheel. A lot of swinging. Also watch your jumps. Good luck.
All right, let's do it. I mean, it's not a joke code, but it might be a joke level.
It's an auto scroller too. Oh, it's pinwheels. I get it. Oh, the top. I didn't even pay attention
to the top. Sorry. Oh, I didn't. How did I not? What's going on? What is going on with my fucking
hands? Why did I? I'm trying to jump off the damn thing. That's gonna make me angry today.
Boost through the whole thing. I'm just gonna damage boost through the whole thing next time too.
Don't go too high. Oh no. How am I gonna? All right, yeah, damage frames. Let's go. You get a
mushroom over there anyways. Not fast enough. Not fast enough apparently. Hey, by the way,
did I tell you? September 21st. Put the date on your calendar. Why? What? Is it like a sinking issue
here with the wireless controller here? I don't get it. All right, just go.
We talked about this last time on the last Mario Mega stream, but the easiest way to make any
streamer really, really upset and mad and annoyed is telling them that when they're losing,
like, stop pretending. It's like, even though I know you're fucking around, like, it's like,
I'm not pretending. It's like, oh, he has to be pretending. He can't be this stupid.
That's like, every, I don't care who they are. Every single streamer on Twitch, when they see
though that phrase, what is he pretending again, is like, hey, I'm not pretending. It doesn't matter
if it's fake. Let's go this way. No, that's just a coin over there, right? That was not worth it
because how am I going to get back? Just go up? I don't know if I can do that from here.
Going across? Oh, man. Okay, that's pretty cool. All right, I did, I don't know why I thought that
was going to stop. Points. Okay, so I know where to go from here. Now, can I even do this?
While being big? It's harder. Can I have somebody in the chat explain to me why that didn't catch
twice? I didn't do anything. Why didn't I, why did I not catch? Because I was invincible?
No, I clearly was in there. Can you not get grabbed when you're invincible?
All right, that's all right. I want to be small anyways. What was that? I had no momentum.
I do like this one, though.
We're good. All right, so it's gonna be tough to actually jump over this.
I got it. Okay. And then up and then over. And then from here. Oh, too tall. Watch it. Okay,
this is this part. Fire down there. I think I have to run across this. I need a running start.
I did it. Cool. Oh, yeah, yeah. Oh, it is the auto scroll portion.
Uh, all right. I'm gonna go, uh, I'm gonna go right. Left side. I like how there's two different
ways to go. Oh, come on. I don't know where I am. I really probably needed that. Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
Thank god I got it correct. And then up. Let's see. It's up and then right. What about this one?
Ooh, easy. Which way? Which way do I need to be? I don't know. I have to take a guess. Uh,
I went right last time. We're gonna go left. Got it right. I don't care about the coins.
Okay, stop. Ah! Okay, I'm fine. Can I? Are those platforms? Are they? Hold on. Oh, no. Not
another one of these. Another one of these. Where is it going? Oh, fuck. Okay, hold on.
I just panicked. Ah! Um, up. Is there another one firing on anywhere? Where's the other one?
There's one right here! Which way? Um, is there anything up? Still? Nope. Go. Oh, please. Okay.
What? No. Oh, god. No. I have to jump this. Let me take a look at what it looks like.
It's just... I need to jump from where that coin is. That's definitely what it means.
Run? Jump at this platform across. Hold your breath. Oh! Okay. And then... Shit. I think I need
to momentum here. I need to do a jump-jump, don't I? I'm not gonna make that. I need to be going as
fast with that first jump. Shit. Okay. Ah! Up? I think I'm gonna go up. Watch out for the saw.
Oh, god. Come on. No, there's only, like, a coin up here. I don't want to go up here anymore.
I don't want to go up here anymore. No. I don't want to do this hard jump. I need to... I'm dead.
I think it's peak of that jump. Holy shit! I'm okay. And then, but how do I get over this one?
I'm gonna hit it, aren't I? Ah! Does this move? Does this move? Does anyone know if that moves?
Is this gonna come up? I'm terrified. Did they come up? I did it. Game over. That was fun.
Can I breathe now? Yes, you can. Let's give that one eye. Nice job. He stopped pretending.
Sometimes you gotta pretend. What an actor. Uh, you won't pick this one. Um, yes, I will. Uh-oh,
people are starting to understand how to game my brain. You have to just put a sad face.
I have the last two or three that I've done have been, you're not gonna play mine with a sad face,
and I'm like, yeah, I will. Of course I will. Here you go, man. Uh, this is called Monty Symbiosis.
Monty Balls have teamed up with Piranha Plants. Show evolution whose boss it is.
You can do this apparently in a minute. Okay. This is a hard one. This is World 1-1.
Oh, all right. Is there a mushroom? Is that gonna hurt me? Well, that's an easy 10 point.
What's in here? All right. Oh, just getting all the secrets in this one.
I'm not gonna admin me. No. Oh, shit. You just, I can't be on the ground. Oh, this is gonna be
terrible. Okay. Watch out for those hidden blocks. Don't touch the ground. That's the name of the
game. I can touch the ground for a second. Okay. I know this one right here now, so that's good.
I don't have to sit there and freak out about mushrooms. That hitbox was dog shit, I will tell
you. Up. I feel like I want to get in there. No. Fireballs? Oh, God. Okay. They come out.
Give me that, please. Uh, wait. Come back. Come back, come back, come back, come back, come back.
Come, and I'll be back eventually. Don't worry. I've, no, no, no. Connect that because I,
that needs to come back. I need, I want to, whatever this is I want it. It's not coming
back, is it? Yeah, I can die faster than it will come back. Should I go up? Why would that vine be
there? I thought it was going to go up somewhere. All right, now switch it. Watch out for the fire.
Do they all have fire? Is that going to, just don't move. Uh oh, uh oh. Don't move. What? I,
damage boost ruined the whole thing. I don't know why I wanted to do that so bad, but I had to.
That was a good one. I didn't see them. They blended the fuck in real good. I was not paying
attention to that. He's not, I, whatever. I'm telling you right now, that was legitimate.
I thought they were grass. I thought they were grass. I have to jump. No, it's going to hit me.
It's going to double tap me. Stop. Oh, all right, I'm fine. Jump over the grass. Wait, I could,
there probably was a block. No true endings. Only bad endings here, guys. That was a fun one. Nice.
Good level. You are going to play this one. Yes, I am. Yes, I will play this one. Make sure it's
not like a poopy to poo. Maneuvering Bob-ombs. This is new. No one's played this one in the world,
probably besides me. It's a puzzle level, so I'm going to have a lot of fun with this one.
For a second, I thought my intro was still playing in the background. I was like,
how the hell did nobody tell me this yet? All right, obviously the bomb to explode this guy.
Now we need the bomb to hit the switch. Yep, okay, and we have to have you come down. Take
the bomb with us over here. All right, there's more bombs. So we got to do, put the bomb up there,
and it's got to hit it. Hit the switch. That was a little too early. Might still do it. No. Oh,
yeah. Hold on. One, two, three, four, five. Okay, it's been five seconds. How long? One,
two. So in three seconds, I have to get it over there. So we go one, two, three, one.
Law. Come on. Stop, stop, stop. One, two, three, two, two, three, one, two. What?
Put it on. No. Did I use them all? He's baiting help donations. I don't have like text to speech
on. If anything, like a help donation would be worse because I have to look over here.
And now what? Wait, wait, wait. What do I have to? You motherfucker. I didn't think two more than
two could be out at one time. I thought like only two could be out at one time. I remember because
it was... That's going to hit me. It's going to hit me still. Get up there. Hurry. I like this one.
What are you thinking? Pretending to be like mad for donations. I don't get it. I don't understand.
What are you talking about? Somebody donate and like tell me. I don't get it. I'm so stupid.
Talking about donations is baiting donations. Don't you know, even if you say the word donation,
but I need to have like banned words as a streamer. Donation prime. Why did I do that?
No, no, it's going to kill it. It's a key. See what I'm talking about? I can't say those words.
I cannot say the word prime. I can't say it because Herbert just gave 25 subs. Holy shit.
You see what I'm saying? That's a lot of subs. Thank you, Herbert. That's fucking too many.
And then LaCrona just gave $65. Do you understand? I need to have like...
I can't say the word money on stream. LaCrona, thanks with 65 bucks and Herbert for the 25 subs.
Greedy streamer sucks money out of wallet of innocent streamer. Okay, I'm never going to say
the word money again on stream. Anytime I want, I'm going to talk about like capital or
paper trading goods. That's what I'm going to say. Monthly paper trading goods subscription.
All right, so I need to stop that from coming down, but it kills it.
It's got to be there long enough for it to explode. All right, so hold on. Ready?
Go. No, what? Why does it not stay on top of it? It can't. Ban the word pretending.
That's not reaching it. It looks like it's reaching it.
Fuck. I'm not acting. Yes, I am. I'm a fucking actor. This is a puzzle one. You're not supposed
to beat this one quick. How long does this travel over there? You have to go like...
No, no, way earlier than that. Jesus. Now what? Oh, that hurts. Oh, you got to crane this. Come
on over here. Drop it. Holy shit, this is going to be horrible. All right, stay over here.
Can I just throw it in? There's too many of them. This whole thing is going to get
messed up here. I can't go over here. I can no longer jump over here. What do I do? What do I
do about this? There's too many. Okay, shit. How many do you think I can have over here?
I'm not playing that game right now. I'm playing the try to win. I don't like it to come out so
fast. All right, this next one I'm going to try. Come here. Ready? I should get it now.
Get it. Drop it over here quick. Oh, come on. That was the one. You got to get it when it's on
its way this way. Get it. Oh, like how far is it? How far does it go? Easy. No.
Please. Okay. Grab one. No. YouTuber scream. That was a gasping for air. I didn't scream.
Oh my God, please. All right. Wait. Grab it. Drop it. Please mom.
I have to like put it pushed down. What am I supposed to do?
Put that helmet on. Can I pick it up? I can't pick it up. Do I have to bounce it with my head?
Okay. Well, I don't even know that. Okay. This is like the second time I've played Mario Maker
in like three weeks. I don't know you could do this shit. I thought I was just going to go
and explode. Oops. Fuck. It's actually kind of hard. Oh no. Give me another one.
You said you knew everything. Nobody can know everything. I'm facing the right side.
I'm facing to the right. Do we die already? More than three. Interesting. Four? More than five times?
It's not going to be eight. God. Fuck me. Why? No. Don't. Please. I don't want to do this again.
I really, I don't want to do this again. Oh fuck. Die. Guys. What's going on here?
Does this end? Give that to me. Oh my God. This thing's gonna explode. That was a scream.
That was a scream. Yes. You can say I screamed because I did. That was an actual scream.
Get me out of here. Excuse me. I really don't want to do that eight more times. So I hope I don't die.
Hey, I'm like five for five right now. That's pretty. I've beaten every level that it's come
across. I haven't vetoed any yet. Uh, 50 more dollars came in from another fan. Three, two, one.
Thank you for the 50 dollars. I'm a dirty YouTube archive watcher. I'm still catching up on your
stuff since you stream so often, but it's my dream for you to play one of my levels.
And they put their level here. Nobody in chat beat this. Bribery. Well, thank you for the 50
dollars. And I'm going to play your level. I am. I just, what, what do you want me to say?
Guys, give me a break. That was fun. You got bribed and sweet talk. It's really not that hard to
make me do something. Well, I mean, that's, that's a lot of money. That's, that is hard.
That's a ton of fucking money. You don't have to pay me money to play your level, but like,
I just saw it. Don't worry. We're going to be here for a while. Don't worry. Bound across
bumpers. Bounce across the desert. Jump right as soon as you land to get extra height. 28 seconds.
Short and sweet. All right. Less than 20 seconds. It's the bumpers. I have a reasonable explanation
as to how that happened. I started to burp. I like, I could feel a burp coming out of my stomach
and I stopped for a second and just, that's a very reasonable explanation.
Not enough. I'm not pretending. That looked very much like somebody was pretending, but they
weren't. I promise. That looked like it could have, it looked like I just walked into the hole. Like,
oh shit, I, I fell down, but I missed going through the hole. But let me just like nudge
to the left a little. I fell down. But I can assure you, that's not what happened.
How do I get in there? Well, that's how. I like this one. This one's nice and like,
cool. Mario three. The best Mario that nobody plays. And what I mean by that is most people
that play Mario three play the first two or three levels and then skip to the end of the game
every time. Oops. It's a great game though. Bounce. Oh my God. What the fuck am I doing?
It's different Mario. It's a different style. That's why I've been, I've been playing. What
was I on before? I was playing a different Mario before. It's a different style and there's
different weight. Oh shit. That's a far away. Oh no. Am I in trouble? Why am I commentating
over a 10 year old's gameplay of Mario? It would be an easy string, you know. It's gonna be easy.
Somebody can do that in 28 seconds. Well, that was, that was fun. That was a fun,
just little level. It was fun to play. Thank you for that level. That was another fan.
All right. All right. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. This is says, this one says
easy fun hand warmer. I don't know what that means. Oh, right. It was my hands. And then
we'll do slime. We'll do your level right after zero. All right. Mechanism mine. Go through mine
with a fair amount of traps. Puzzle solving standard length. How much money do I have to
pay you to play my level? There is no amount of money that I will take to play level. I just do,
I just do it if it's, if I see it, there's no, you don't have to pay me to play level.
This is the worst Mario ever. This is the worst one. So I already don't like this one because it's
the one that has this. This is literally the best Mario. I'm just kidding guys. My God.
I don't need to make a Dark Souls, Souls born tier list of Mario games. Although might as well.
Oh, they're all pretty fun. All the Mario games are fun. They've fun games. They've lasted
like 60 years. I can't really think of another product that's been around for that long
that people still like. Cars. Yeah. Okay. So a car has lasted. That's fine. Yes. Oh God. What do
I do with this? The TV. The TV has, has the TV been around for 60 years so far? Kind, sort of. Not
really though. Hold on. Like what are the, let's go ahead and do this again. Oh, why have you done
that? Just damn thing. Um, what do I do now? What? Oh, I guess I'm just gonna go, go up.
The TV is so good. Why don't we have TV too? I mean, you're on TV too right now. Can I?
Oh shit. This one's pretty cool. Uh, but how does, what? Key block? That was, that won't,
what's going on here? There's no key block. Thought I had it. What the fuck is happening?
What? Did I mess it all up back here? Am I missing something? No, I,
that's up here. Is there a key block available? It has to grab that. Okay.
I don't, I think I screwed it all up though, didn't I? I think I blew it. I blew it.
I'm telling you, I swear to God, people think I'm making this shit up,
but sometimes when you press a button on the switch controller, it just like doesn't
happen. It's like a phantom button press. I promise. I'll get it this time.
I, you know, I'm already back down here. It's like it never happened. Oops. Can't do that.
That's, I don't get that. I don't get it. I'm going to not, I won't lie. I don't, I don't,
I don't get it. I don't get that one to clean. Okay. Now I need to, don't get that. Does that
despawn? All right. So we've got a scenario where I've got to press the button up there.
Go get this pullback. No, no, no. Oh my God. I still got it. No more screaming. I promise.
What the fuck do I get back up there? No, I have to go all the way up to get the helmet.
I, I'm freaking out. I don't, I don't get it. I'm fucked up. I don't understand. I'm
fucking freaking out. Well, I don't know. I just get up here. I, do I not even need the helmet?
I don't think I even need to use the P switch for here. I think I just have to follow it up.
So just take it and then like, can I just get up there? Okay. So this is why I was freaking
out because I don't, I guess I never even needed in the first place. Okay. Let's go.
I need to bring it all the way over there. No, stop picking. Oh my God. I'm going to freak the
fuck out. I need to bring it up all the way. I had to bring it up the whole way, not just right
there. I got to bring up the entire way. How am I going to do that now? How did you get down here?
I, I thought that when it came over here, I could press it. I didn't have to go all the way up.
Okay. So now, wait, what the fuck has happened? What, what does this matter?
Do I just do it now? I think do it now, right? Go all the way up. Isn't that going to fuck this up?
Huh? What the fuck? I didn't know something came out of there. I didn't know something came out of
that fucking thing. How was I supposed to know that? I didn't know that a thing came out. That's
why I spent this much time trying to figure out what the hell to do. I didn't know that someone's
going to jump out of there. You can't dock points on my intelligence because I didn't know.
I didn't know like a bomb walked out of that. That was fun though. All right, slime, where's he
going? All right, we're going to do it's time for slime's level. Let's do L6, B6. Let's go. This is
called MarioAntivirus.exe. This one's going to be great. Hackers have broken through Mario's
firewall and infected his PC with bugs. Is that supposed to, is that the Windows logo? That's
awesome. Defeat all 20. Oh, okay. First door? We'll do door one. Oh, it's just there. Is this
supposed to be the computer? Oh no, a P-switch. My worst enemy. Anything else? Let me take this in
for a second though. Anything else over here to look at? No, I just want to see. God. Oh no.
Do I have to fill this in? Any more blocks hidden?
What on earth? Oh, I got four 1-ups. Where do I go from here? Up and around. Oh shit. Okay.
To hit that I think. So let's hit this. Mushroom. Can't hit that. Wait, this is like the microchip.
Okay, I see. So I gotta get all 21? Can I not kill these? I don't think I can, right?
I have to hit the POW, don't I? All right, this is two. I gotta kill these ones. Let's see. There it
is. All right, three, five. How do I get out of here? Let's go all the way to the right.
This is big. Holy shit, this is huge. Is that the firewall?
Just leave. I can't just leave. Oh shit, that's gonna be horrible.
Oh, can I? I don't think I can. Should I try it? I don't think I'm ready for that.
Where do you go? Watch out for the icicles. Oh shit, they respawn. It's seven.
I need... Oh, I just like... It's called health, but it is technically health.
Oh, the timer, you're right. Okay, hold on. I'm not gonna do this in time. Oh god,
there's so much more. Get up there. Is there any more down here? To the left?
Did I miss any over here? I'm gonna have to do this again. Did I miss any? Nine out of 21 over
here? I think I missed one on the top left. Wasting time? Well, I'm not gonna beat it,
so I might as well just see if there's anything else. Holy shit. Okay. Oh my god.
This is so big. How do I get up here? Off of your head? Give me the... I got a key now.
Can you... I think he has to kill them, doesn't he? No, what? How am I killing them? What was it?
On his head? All right, I'm gonna try this again. This time, I'm not gonna like take in the scenes.
It's a very, very pretty level for the first batch. I still don't understand what the point
of that one is. Was that a dev kit? It's probably a dev kit, something like that.
My god. It's okay. Okay, I'm like panicking for no reason. I have like, I have like 12 minutes.
Oh, it's slippery. Shit. Is those two? It is that. Got that. Any more? Shouldn't have done that. That
was a dumb idea, but I did it anyways. Oh, there was, look, there was a secret one over here. See?
Shit, I didn't think that was gonna happen. All right, that's 10. I feel like you just spawned
that in for me. All right, I gotta go through the firewall now. Get through this, though. I'm getting
hit. Through the... I gotta just go. I have to, I gotta go for it. Go for it. Okay, I'm fine.
Don't go through this door. Mushroom in here. Now this, this... All right, hold on. What does this do?
I should have known that was gonna fucking happen. Why did I just not understand that?
That's in case you miss one. I get it. I'm gonna go all the way to the right.
Oh my god. Okay, there's all this. Um, did I just get spawned on? What the hell?
Tele-frag. All right, now I know what the door does. I don't even need to grab these. I don't know
what I'm doing. Let's do the skip. Wait till it goes over that way. Got it. There it is. There it is.
Don't get that. No reason to. Same thing I did this way. All the way around. Boink.
There it is. Okay, there it is. Ten. No, yes. You hope I'm having a good day? I'm having a good day.
Hope you're having a good day too. How is your day? It's good. Here we go. Man, my brain is too
small for that. All right, let's just do this. Oh my god. No! No! Why? I just wanted this...
All right, I have to get rid of the stupid magician. This magician's pissing me off.
That's the hacker. All right, I got a key. Oh, I got another key. I can do it again.
Two keys. How many? 20. I got 12. I got 21. I got them all. How do I get out of here? What do I have
to do? Is there like an exit door? Pipe. Pipe. Pipe. Pipe. Pipe. Pipe. Pipe. Pipe. Pipe. Like,
where? What do you mean pipe? Pipe? Pipe. Pipe. Pipe. Pipe. Pipe. Pipe. I don't know what you
mean by pipe. Okay, I'm fucking losing my mind. I'm freaking out. The hacker's gonna kill me.
Pipe! I got it. That was cool. That was actually really fun. Really well thought out level. That
was it's time for slime. Good shit. You look lovely today. Oh, okay. Although wait, somebody
has a fish. No, I'm not gonna do that. You look lovely today. Usually the fish gets me,
but today it's all about the compliments that get me today. You have RNG in your name here.
I wonder if that means anything. Jerma's family dinner. You can beat this in seven seconds.
Okay. Should I get the coins? The clown car? All right. It was an easy one. I'm gonna get
the world record on this. Seven seconds. Seven point three. Here we go. Was that longer than
seven seconds? No! That has to be pretty close. What? I just had it. Somebody just got a better
one than I did. What? It was seven three. Now it's seven oh? One more. I don't care. This is it.
Even if it's, uh, I don't think that was the one. Six. No. That was mine was cleaner. But again,
seven one. Seven. No, you guys can fucking fight each other over it. Hey, that was a short and
sweet one. Thank you. Beautiful also. Fuck you. All right. Yeah. Let's do that one. After this,
I'm gonna go pee. Come back and do some more. Mid-airs made easy. These mid-airs require no
kaizo skill. Red pipes provide hints if needed. Oh, this is apparently impossible.
One percent completion rate. Oh, this is gonna be tough. These mid-airs require no kaizo skill.
What? I don't know. I don't know what that means. This is way over my head. Gotta go up here?
I need another. Is this low gravity? What? Okay. Well, that changes everything.
So I have to go up, jump, and grab it, and jump? Throw it over? I don't know. Oh no. Give me that
back. The low gravity just fucked with me. Hold on. All right. So you just throw it out. Jump up
there. No. Why? I don't want to grab the fucking thing. Oh my god. I don't want to grab it. I
wanted this to... Okay. Well, we'll have to start over again. Oh, I didn't have to even go up there.
Okay. Use red pipes for a hint. Well, we don't need one yet. What are these for? I guess. I don't
know. I have to definitely jump up on this. It resets the level. Oh, okay. Is this autoscrolling?
Wait, hold on.
Get up there. Okay. And then, oh yeah, yay. Okay. Now fall through this.
Ah, something telling me I wasn't supposed to do that. Red pipe. Red pipe. Well, not yet. Well,
yes, fine. What is this showing me? Well, it actually is a full-on, this is how you beat it.
That's really cool, actually. That's a nice touch. What? I gotta get to look like the video.
Ugh. I have this problem in Mario where I have to hold down the face button. Why? Every... for
everything. No matter what. I have to. Even if I'm not trying to run. Okay. So what does this want
me to do here? Do I need to bring that up with me? Or damage boost and then I just need you to wait
like an extra five seconds is what I had to do. Okay. Let's see. That's gonna be something,
isn't it? What? All right. Oh, okay. We're fine. No. There's no red pipe here, guys.
I don't see a red pipe. No red pipe. Uh, I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it.
Come on. Give me another one. Oh, damn it. Okay. How far does that go?
Shit. Then go to the checkpoint. What do I do with this thing? No red pipe either. Do I have to fall
down with it or throw it over there? I didn't see what was on the other side of this. Throw it over
there and then there's a ground. I don't have to go fast. For some reason, I think I have to fall
down and then like jump on it later. No, no, no, no, no. Just go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
All right. And now, um, jump. I think I have to throw this, jump on top of it with the spring,
throw the spring, jump on the spring. I think. I can't reset the level ever again.
No. Oh, come on. Really? Did I seriously just do that to myself? I'm stuck. The doors.
Do you understand I'm trying to get to the doors on the left and I have ruined it for myself?
I feel like if I fall at the right angle, I might be able to... There it is. All right. I just...
Don't worry, but I'm probably gonna die because that's... I have to grab this,
throw this, stand on that. Let me just see how fast it goes. Okay. Grab that. That goes pretty damn
fast. Oh, it's the other way around. Oh, give me that. Give me this. Give that to me. Give me this.
I need that. Am I overthinking it? I have to jump, throw, and then... I think I am overthinking it.
What? I... Holding? Why? I wish there was a way I could... Is there a button that you can hold the
run without the pick up button? I wish I could press it. Let's try this again. So, throw the pow
and throw... Okay, throw the pow, throw the... Blow up! I did it. I'm gonna say I did it. I have to do
like a little trail. How far up do I need to go? No, no. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Did I go too high? I went too high. Shit. I can't get that back. Where's my reset button?
There's no reset door here? Shit. I gotta get it up here. No, I don't... Where's my reset door?
Usually I can get that pretty well. Although I screwed this one up last time. Oops.
Fuck. No, I usually can get this. Damn it. Holding? Why in a Mario game? Don't ever do it.
Still don't get this part though. Don't throw the pow, just use it.
I don't think that killed anything. Did that kill anything down here?
No, it didn't. I needed to see. No, it doesn't kill anything over there.
No! Just throw it. Just... I got it over there. I don't give a fuck. It's over there now, isn't it?
I'm vetoing this one. Only a few more tries and I'm vetoing this one. I didn't want to even do
that again by holding Y. Oh my god. Why would they make the run button the same as the grab button?
Everybody runs in Mario. Everybody holds that button down. Make it like L fucking 2 or something.
Why does it have to be Y? No! Fucking Y. Nothing's gonna bring me down today.
Hold X. You can't hold X and Y at the same time. You have to like turn your hand inside out. I'm
getting like tilted down. Jesus. Get me over here. Throw the... Throw the spring first and then grab
the pow. I'm gonna just go. Oh my god. I hate it. All right. Three more attempts and I'm stamping
the veto on this one. No. No. No. No. I don't think so. I'm just gonna take the... I'm just gonna
damage boost over it. I'm not gonna do that. I'm not gonna be able to do that shit. Nope. No. God
damn it. This shit is fucking so difficult. He's like throw, jump, grab. This wasn't in Mario 2.
I don't have the momentum to go all the way... I'm just gonna damage boost it I think.
Because I don't have... I don't... I'm not getting the momentum to go forward to jump on the spring.
How far... What is... So that just flies forward and then jump across. How far does this go? Grab, jump.
Get on the roof. I don't think I need to... I don't... If I get on the roof I lose the spring.
Uh that was weird. Try it again. Don't jump. I'm not jump throwing. I'm just walking.
I don't care. All right. Now this is important. I need to get this spring on that spike.
How do I do that without screwing this up? This is gonna be so bad.
I got it. I got it. Okay. I did it. I did it. Just don't touch the spikes.
And then I jump off this one. I can do this. I can do it. I'm gonna do it.
And that's fucking scary. Oh yes. Yes. Yes. There's a checkpoint. Thank God. Yes. Excellent.
I'm so happy there's a checkpoint here. What a gracious dev. I know. Thank you gracious dev.
So you gotta go. It took me a long time to die.
Damn. All right. I gotta hit that and fall and then go back and hit again.
Springs. He's throwing. Spring. Easy. I can't pick this up. So wait. Do I just bounce off this to get
faster momentum and then jump over? Hold on. How far does it go?
Okay. And did I screw it up? I think I screwed it up. I'm trying to time it so I can.
I think it's over. So you gotta go right away. Oh boy. And you gotta hit the ones up here.
The two. Oh dear. All right. You gotta do it all in one go.
Did I have to keep going? I don't think I had to keep going.
Uh and then up. Oh I don't know. I don't know. I think I have to run really fast
and jump and throw this and hit this. I think. Oops-a-daisy. Yeah that's what I have to do.
I probably could have jumped on top of that but I don't understand. Oh guess what I did. I pressed Y.
The right trigger should be grabbed. Can I remap that?
You know you're starting to get annoyed in Mario when you want to remap the controls
in Mario. Like that's when you know that you're like actually getting angry.
How do I remap the fucking controls in Mario 2? Really? Shit.
Maybe I should just try to keep going left. That would just make me jump up this way.
That wouldn't do much for me would it? I'm kind of confused but wouldn't I just jump up?
I have to actually start the hold X and Y at the same time but then you have to let go of Y.
That's so awkward. Just throw the spring. Holy shit. Okay well I have one. Is that what I'm
supposed to do? Why did it not do that? What happened? I get the secret level. 17 minutes.
Who can beat that in a minute? He missed the true ending. I don't get true endings. Don't you know
that? 1.5% completion. I'm good. Get the true ending. I don't get true endings.
That was fucking hard. That was challenging. Very cool though. Yeah it's time for a pee break.
I'll be right back. Go do what you need to do. See you guys in like two minutes. Be right back.
I'm back. So where are we going now? You will consider mine. It even has a fish.
I absolutely will consider that. Fail fish. Oh okay I get it. Now I see what you mean.
I think did you type it in wrong? I think did you mean that? Why can I not? Let's see.
This is wrong. Why can I not type? I think the code is wrong. Why is Z? What's going on?
Why is Z, I, and O not available? Because they look like 2s, 1s, and 0s?
All right. Oh so that person just it was a made-up level. All right.
I see fun cool level please. I'll do this one. Not too hard for you. What do you mean for me?
It's called thwomp. Thank you for the level. Standard puzzle solving. For me or for you?
I thought I had to hit that with my head but nope. Let's go.
Oh it's in 3D world. This sucks automatically. That's not true. Um I gotta jump up,
dodge that, jump around, get the P, and then get the V. What's going on? Oh.
Oh. Can I get it back? Secret. Secret way. I always beat it secret way.
I actually kind of want to go that way. All right. Let's go.
I just made myself fucking like two times bigger when you play
Super Mario dog shit 3D gets stuck to the wall become like fly paper when you play Super Mario
3D world. What? What happened to my? Did you see the bottom of the screen? I don't think.
Super fucking 3D fly paper. That's what this should be called.
3D world man. Oh and there's an end. They make it so you can't get up here.
All right. I'm gonna be all right. I thought you said you liked 3D world.
Oh.
I don't know. Up. I get it. Blasphemy.
I feel like I have a backpack full of cement on when I played Mario 3D world.
I'm getting three. I don't like 3D world. I remember when I opened the Wii,
whatever it was, I got it. I played Mario 3D world like 30 minutes and I was like I don't like this
game. You understand? You understand what happened? You understand? What the fuck is going
on? New Super Mario Brothers 3D whatever is it's equal parts like floaty and heavy at the same time.
So you know when you eat a huge fucking meal right at the last bite you feel like shit and you're
wicked way down like I shouldn't have eaten that last bite. I feel like I have like a stomach full
of fucking a bunch of like meat and cheese and shit. I don't understand what's happening now.
Yeah, Super Mario New Wii 3D full pizza. Can you do it again? Please? Can I get this to happen again?
Extra large fucking steak and cheese. Somebody gave me subs. JermaSucks gave me five subs.
Now just go down and then what the fuck do I do here? Oh okay YouTube.
All right I'm doing this a few more times. Only a few more times.
And no more Mario 3D world levels before I fucking puke. All right, just kill me. Do you remember
the last time we played this? What was the game that made me like very upset? It wasn't Mario
World. It wasn't Mario 2. It wasn't like Mario 64. It was these ones. I don't even have it if it's
that. Oh my god. That fucking wall jump is like equal parts impossible to do and equal parts like
too easy to get stuck. How is it possible? What the fuck happened? All right this is it. Last
no this is the last try. Keep my mouth shut. I know this game is like a 9.8 on IGN. I'm talking
about Mario 3D World. I know. I know but every game that's a Mario game has to be a nine or
you go out of business. You understand? Oh this isn't 3D World. No I know but you know the new
Super Mario Wii Brothers. Whatever the hell it's called. Luigi plays Wii. Whatever the hell it is.
Can't beat this land. Well you know it's uh this is Joel's level. Oh great. 0.1% this 58,000 attempts
here. Do you think I'm gonna be able to do this? I'm not gonna be able to do this. Oh god. I don't
even want to know. You have to get all the key things. Oh I feel so I feel right at home though.
This is Mario 3. Okay. Watch out for the Goomba. Should I go underneath? How am I gonna get under
this? Oh this just gets worse by the second. What do I do? Underneath. Oh god. Wait. Hold on. Slow down.
Slow down. Ah. No. No. I needed that. What? How do I get that and then go?
God. You have to go around? How do you pick that up? Go up on top and okay.
Oh this is gonna be hell. Okay I'm going. For a second I thought I could do that. I don't know why.
That might be a little secret though. You might actually feel good today. You know what I'm saying?
Okay it took Joel 20 hours to beat this and he's the one that made it. It actually literally took
20. I think I can do that. I think it's possible to go right when. That's the little skip. That's
the dev skip. Okay let's try this again. Oh man. It was 20 hours across two different streams.
I'm gonna try this. Hold on. Where's the one that comes out?
What doesn't come out? Why would I go this way? I thought.
Oh man. I'm not gonna be able to do this. See? That's what I mean. Then go down with it.
I can't even get this first jump correct. All right. I need to. Is it the top of the coin on
the arrow? Somebody do it. Kill it. Kill it. Somebody kill it. Kill them. It's not the last
coin. I have to get this jump down and I don't know what point it is. What else I can do? I'm
just gonna go now. No no no no no no no. Then. Oh man. That sucks. I gotta get the star and then
come back and go all the way around. Wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait. What?
Can I? Can I do that? Can I do this? Can I actually do this? If it. Oh! Joel 19 hours
when knowing how to do it. Uh yeah. I mean I'm willing to just have a little bit of fun with it
but I'm never gonna beat this. I need to at least get this first jump correct. What if I just say
fuck it? No. I'm not gonna go that way. Man this is gonna be hell. I have an idea. Though the name
of this level is called. I get it. I can't get it. Does that not work? Oh shit! What? Okay. No no no
no no no. Wait wait wait. Get me out of here. Um what do I do? I don't know. I don't know. I don't
know. You have to run. Just run and jump? I at least have to get to the end of this. You gotta
kid me. Why? I'm dead. All right just run. I'm just gonna run and then jump. Do I keep holding this?
I don't know. Oh my. Nooooo. That's fucking insane. You gotta get that little pixel.
What? How do you even program that to work? How does that work? Yeah how did he do this
for like 20 straight hours? At hour number four? I don't think I would. I think I'd be like guys
I have to leave. I'll see you like tomorrow. And tomorrow I'm not doing this. How did I get it the
first few times easily? Don't go faster than the shell. That would be a mistake.
Yeah I don't know about this one. Yeah I don't know. I don't know about this one.
Why does my microphone sound like it's on fire? It's clearly not. Come on please. I don't go that
fast. All right now I'm gonna do this. Get this and then fall here. All right going.
It was a laugh. Somebody laughed. I don't know. I don't know why this is supposed to be funny.
Why is this funny? I obviously can't jump over there. Do I just lose? I think I might just lose.
All right so that door doesn't do anything. You know how I get with this kind of shit though.
Like I'm gonna be here. I'm not gonna be here for much longer. I can't. We got like all the
viewer levels to do. I'm not gonna do this the whole time. I'll be here for a year. All right
now. So how? I shouldn't. Should I not get this? If I get the. Okay so I have to damage boost.
What? No. So I have to wait till the mushroom gets down and then get hurt and then run. This
shit over there. Do I have to jump over there or something? I thought that was it. Go. Oh my god I
have to go. I just panicked. I didn't want to hit the thing. I was gonna hit it. All right so let me
hold on a minute. If I hit the mushroom and then the mushroom touches me while I'm small. Like
walk, get hurt, run, damage boost. You can't make that jump. You can't make those jumps.
But where do I stop? It didn't even. That was. It didn't kill the thing up there. I was gonna die.
Look at this again. The shell comes down. Does it come all the way over here? Does another one come
up? Where does that one go? Okay it bounces over here and then where does it go from here?
Nowhere. It hits a switch. Okay what is it hitting? I gotta just kind of run.
Okay hold on. I can go in there when it's red? I have no idea. And then just try to stop.
Fuck. Is there a safe zone? I don't know where the safe part is. But thankfully I can do this
pretty easily now. Oh that was bullshit. I brought the shell with me the first time and I don't have
to get on top of the shell. How would I do that? This level is named after Central British time.
Yeah I know. But there's got to be like a solution. All right I'm gonna a few more tries.
Do I actually need the shell? All right I'm skipping it. I'm gonna skip it after like two more.
If I can't get, if I can't figure this out, there's probably like another 75 hours to this.
Oh god. Do I have to get all those too? The solution is to punch yourself in the groin for
a couple dozen hours. That's true. Although no that's not the solution. I at least want to
get through here one more time. Really? Shit. Okay um I can't make that jump. Hold on let me test
No there's no way. That's gonna kill me. No fuck. No come on. No no. How did I make it worse?
What is that? How do I get over there? All right this is it. I can't, I can't, I it's crazy level
and it's fun. It's fucking crazy. But I gotta, I gotta move on. You're telling me that I need to jump
over these and that's the way to do it. That's what you're trying to tell me? You're telling
you're telling me that I have to jump over each one of these. Every single one. Oh my god. You
have to keep the momentum going to just keep going. If you stop you're dead. No. No way. No way. I'm
not doing it. I'm done. I'm done. No fucking way. We're out. That's it. That's it for this one. No
more of this one. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. No. No. No. You're gonna do the whole thing
all the way down? There's no way. It's not fucking happen. You gotta be kidding me. Because then
you're gonna turn and do it down the bottom. Holy shit. How did you ever beat this? Even if you
memorize this, there's like a tiny bit of human error. I want to just see the failure. Watch the
clip. Are you serious? How would you even do this? There's no way. You've got to be fucking
kidding me. You have to follow the mushroom all the way. The whole way.
Look at this shit. Are you ready for this? You have to fucking pick this up. Thanks for watching
everybody. I can't even get past the first three blocks. It looks like he's walking it too. Is he
walking it? He wasn't running. He's walking. Come on. Get walking. I can do this. Here we go.
Wait. What's in front of me? You gotta hit and jump around it. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. I'm not
doing it. It's too hard. And that's not even like... There's no way. Only 84 people have completed
that. Out of 58,000 attempts. Now that's an incredibly difficult level. Thank you Joel for
making it fun. What's next? This one. Thank you to Germaput Sunchips in F tier. That's a pretty
great name. And then RSF. Let's give it a try. Stop acting. Minus two dying Jill. Okay. Okay.
All right. Let's try it again. Oh, I can do... I can do the... Can I even make that? I don't think
I can make that. I'm not sure I can. Whoa. Whoa. What the fuck? Okay. So that was interesting.
You gotta get on that lower level. Toad's fat ass just hit the hit. That was... Sorry. Toad's diaper
hitbox. Why am I Toad? I don't want to be Toad anymore. How do I change character? How do I
change character? Slide down. Right there. On off. And then. And then. And then. And then. And then.
And then. Ah! I gotta... Is there... Do I get another one? Do I get another turtle?
Shit. I'm holding it down. I swear to god. No! No! No! Give me that turtle. No. God damn it. Come on.
Really? I got stuck. Come here. Oh shit. No. No, no, no. Turn... Stop. Stop it. Please.
No. I gotta pick it up. Oh my god. I am gonna fuck it. My soul is leaving my body.
I'm alright. I'm not mad. I'm not mad. I'm not mad. I'm fine. Nothing's gonna make me mad today.
Tell you. You know why. September 21st. You gotta plan on September 21st to cancel it. Wait, do I...
I gotta leave that on. No! I wanted to jump on his head. Fuck. Now what? How fast is he? What?
What? I'm just gonna hold right. There's nothing else I can do there. Do I have to actually kill
that thing? No! Now he's too close. Fuck. I like this one. Come on. I wonder if there's more.
This is the one. He ain't even close. They're all cheering him on. Alright. From here I gotta jump
to... Anything else? I'm scared. Can I make this jump? What? No! I... It... The slide. I thought the
slide was gonna... It slides. Oh. Um. You know. The slide. I don't know why. You can slide up.
Can you? I don't know. I don't remember that. Can you? I don't know. God. Why did you do that?
He's dead. Wait. Is he... Is he gonna go the other way? Alright. I'm gonna kill him and then we don't
have to worry about it. I swear to God. I'm just trying. I'm trying. I'm really trying.
Damn it. This game, man. This game. It's just... It's too much sometimes. I'm trying. Now I'm just
singly jumping. Not even twist jumping. I'm just normal jumping. I think he's gonna catch me. I
don't think I did it fast enough. Alright. That was really close. And then... Is that it? There's a
troll coming up. I know it. There's gonna be some... A block or a brick or a hammer or a
block or something that's gonna stop me. I don't know what it is but it's gonna happen.
I don't know what it is. Something bad's gonna happen right here. I don't know what it is.
Uh. How do I... I need to have the shell hit that but I can't get it. Alright. So then
go in here? I think. What hap... What? Um. What do I do? Now what do I do? Which way? Which way do I go?
To the right? Oh no! There's a guy coming. There's a guy coming. Wait. No. No. It was coming. I knew
it was gonna happen. I knew it was gonna happen. I knew there was gonna be something there that
caused a huge problem. Why would there be music there if there wasn't something bad or scary or
watch out! Look out! Imagine being this high strung for a kids game. Uh. No. This is this is
not a kids game. Kids don't do this. Can't be. This is this is like a... No. Nuh-uh. This is like a
Newgrounds parody game. You know what I'm saying? This is not like Super Mario. Is it enough?
Mm-hmm. No! Oh! Just barely enough. It's just barely enough. Okay hold on. Don't screw it up.
Cross. Alright. Now it's just you land, you kill both the things, then you land and run
instantly. At least that's what I think I have to do. Let's do it. Get them both crushed. Okay.
Fall and then run. Two. Go! That was fun. That was a good one. No that was that was cool. Really
good. Nice job. Everyone's done a nice job. Just because you have a Super Mario 3D world level
doesn't mean your level is bad. It's just like you know. Here's a pallet cleanser. I'll do the
pallet cleanser for sure. Tea. I'm into the pallet cleanser level. Snow-capped mountain climbing.
Enjoy the scenic sights of snow-covered mountains and even ghost flunking. I can't
wait to play this one. Mountain climbing. This is a pallet cleanser. This is what I'm talking about.
This is great. Should I go down? I'm gonna go down. Save it. Alright. Baby level. No. Not every single
level in Mario Maker has to be like burn my eyes with hot stones. Everything doesn't have to be
like as hard as possible. I don't know why but for some reason apparently all levels
in Mario Maker have to be like blast death metal and slam monster energy drinks and scream
while you run forward and then jump like a thousand times. Sometimes you just want to do
some mountain climbing and that was fun. I did it. I don't have to go take the baseball bat.
Lean forward with the bat. Put my head on it. Spin around in a circle 20 times and then pick
up the controller. That was fun. What a nice pallet cleanser. We got a medium difficulty right here
and you got it. Nice job. Okay this is called trampolines in the sky. Challenging platforming
course. Crouch while releasing springs to drop. 13 minutes. Holy fuck. Only one person has cleared
this. Do I take this? Okay. I think I hit a switch somewhere. Don't throw it. No. Crouch
to drop. Try this again. There's the switch. That was close. So now that switch is done.
Then up here. Now the claw machine thing.
I want that 50. It's right there. It's giving me. It's not that even that greedy. It's just
clear. Okay I'm fine. All right so now we was I not supposed something happened over there
on the right? All right I don't want to die here. What happens now? Okay.
Uh spring comes out of here. I wonder. Should I just go up from here?
Can't. Um up through there? No don't kick it.
I'm gonna bring this back over here.
Um kind of. Should I go up?
Come on. I think I have to do this. Drop it. Why does my face hurt?
I don't know man. Oh shit. That's not what I wanted. There's a checkpoint right there too.
Oh my god. What have I done? How long is it going to take me to do this until I do the
mechanic that it says in the description? Yeah I gotta throw shit around. Give me.
Where's the other one? Where are my trampolines? Did I? Where's this one?
Give it to me. What? Oops. Give it here. I'm not gonna get it.
No no no no. Just fall. I'm trying to think if I could do something else there.
I gotta get up there so I have to jump from the spring over here.
Right. I'm just gonna try it. See what happens.
I didn't want to get grabbed but fine. All right now if I drop it right now.
Oh that's it. Okay I gotta get caught. Okay then get caught again and bring this around on here.
Do I wanna do this? I guess.
Up there.
No. I didn't have to go all the way back down. Why am I going so fast?
Okay that was. I gotta skip this one. It's cool but I like just my fucking finger just slipped.
I like I was in the air and then I let go but then I hit it again somehow.
I'll do this one. Frigid cavern run. Oh shit. It's another one of these.
My first level there are two 1-ups so you're under a time limit. Shit.
Oh let's give it a try. 29 seconds. Oh fuck. All right you gotta.
All right. I think you go too fast if you bounce off that one.
Oh I should have seen that coming from a mile away. Inferno. Thank you Inferno for the five community
subs. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Appreciate it. I gotta dump the whole thing. Thanks for the
five subs. Thank you. Do I need the key? Oh I need the coin. Uh oh. Ice is killing me.
You're taking a shot every time I die.
How on earth are you supposed to get that in an ice level that has 30 seconds on the clock?
Shit I didn't get it. Oh my god. Shit.
I'm going so. I'm going to slow down a little because I don't know what's even.
Damn man. How are you supposed to do that so fast?
Hope I don't need it. Let me just get up there and see. What the hell is even up here?
Do I have to jump over the whole thing with a small jump? I don't even know if I can do that.
I think I have to jump, hit the ceiling, and then land and then fall.
I think. I actually need to get up there and try again. I just don't understand what I want to do there.
Yes. No. I don't get it. All right. A handful more attention I gotta move on.
Did this bounce back and kill me?
It starts to blend together, man. It just mixes up into a bunch of colors in your brain.
Humans weren't supposed to be doing this. You know what I'm saying? People were farming 500 years ago.
Your brain's not supposed to do this. People were riding in horse and buggy and oh good evening,
madame. Yes, sir. I'll take two sheep. My eyes are wide open and we're hearing the same sounds and
my eyes are wide open and we're hearing the same sounds and the same images over and over again,
screaming at us. We weren't supposed to be doing this. The ice is killing me, too.
The ice. It's the ice. The fucking ice is killing me. I need to figure out this jump
because the ice keeps slowing me down. See what I'm saying? I get them. How the fuck?
I figured it out. I just did it. I did it. What do I do? I have 10 seconds. Go. Just get up there.
Did I just beat it? Oh my god, I beat it. I did it. I didn't mean to do that. I did it. Okay,
I can do this. And I'm gonna keep in track of how many levels I've completed by accident
that are one percent levels, two percent levels. It's been at least two or three.
Let me try this one for real. No, I can't do this again. These speed runners just get in my brain.
No!
All right, last try. That's it. I'm out. That was that one. That doesn't count.
One more try where I get to the top. My birthday candle just went out.
Don't make me laugh right now. Stop it. What? That doesn't count. That doesn't count. That doesn't
count. That doesn't count. Just wait, wait, wait, wait. Let me just get up there with the key.
Come on. Oh, I just need to get... I can't do four minutes. Come on.
This is it. I promise. Come on. Go! Go! I have the key. Please just get over here. All right,
I got the key. Got the key. Got the key. Which door? That's all this did? What? That's it.
Oh, god damn. Whatever. I don't care. That was a good one. That was fun. All right, give me
enough. Give me the next one. All right, this person said pretty please. Okay. I always go into
these streams with just like a really open mind and I like I don't want to like just start like
talking shit about games and I always goes back to like Mario 3D Wii. I always start it. I'm fine,
but like they oh it never fails. All right, this is called Sandwich? Let arrows, left arrows are
tap R, up or hold R, jump on thwomps. Left arrows are tap R, up or hold R. Left is R, up is hold R.
Left is right, up is right. This is gonna take a little bit of messing around. Left is right,
up is right. How did I get underneath? I don't even know how I got underneath them. Can you jump on
top of these in this one? No. It's the R button? That's not. Why didn't he move?
Yeah, you can spin jump. Okay. Hold R, up is... Is this like an activator? He went real fast.
I thought he was gonna move. He's going too fast. Okay. I still don't... I don't... What was the whole
point of that description? What the fuck? I know it's a reset door, but I'm trying to figure out
how to like hit this. I have no fucking idea what's happening. All I know is that I died.
Do I have to activate that one? I'm looking at the end. No, I can't make that whole thing.
Jesus. This is pretty awkward, but it's fun. Did something wrong there.
All right. What is the difference here? So maybe I should forget about the guy down here?
Just activate the one over to the right? Who gives a shit? You gotta be kidding me.
I'm doing it. I can get it. Okay, then I'm gonna fall now. Why? I thought I hit it in the head.
Come on. I'm upset about that. I'm actually upset about that. He's actually upset. No, that one was
fun. I did the secret. Classic Mario. Let's try that one. I don't think there's been... There's been
not very many classic regular Nintendo Mario levels, have there? I think there was one or two.
Bowser's Sky Gauntlet. A five-part gauntlet courtesy of the classic King Koopa. All right.
Gauntlet? A boss rush? All right, somebody said the last level and it's fucking with my head right
now. I don't know why. Somebody said that he's the only person to die to a green Koopa. Somebody
said that like five minutes ago and it's in my head right now because I saw a green Koopa.
That hitbox is weird. Holy shit. I just tried to jump on that like it was a platform. You idiot.
He's dead. I got him. I did it. Bad ending. A minute and three seconds. Not bad. All right,
this one says very important level. Let's find out. That was good. That was fun.
Mario 3D World. Your favorite. I'm not even gonna... I'm not gonna open that one.
A useful lesson. A simple level with a very important message. This one's kind of freaking
me out a little. I'm... I'm kind of afraid of this one. Okay. What's your important message that is
rank? And yeah, that's true. That's... don't... yeah. That's... no, that's a great... that's a good
message. That's a really good message actually. That's a really good one. Don't do that. That's
simple level with a very important message. 95%. So would you just like get there and like not...
you must have like saw... maybe you're just like, ah, I don't want to play this one. It's a word one.
All right, here's this one. 2WN95GG. Big boom booms castle. Collect Mario's mount
and armor to defeat the lord of castle boom. Get the mount and the armor. Sure. But I'm not...
okay, how do I... I change character by here, right? Settings. Where do you actually do this?
I don't want to be Toad anymore. Um, let's... let's be Super Mario. Okay. Sorry, Toad. You're out.
That's a normie thing to do. No, the normie thing would be I'm gonna be like somebody...
I'm gonna be like Toad! Why am I just running over this? And go! Fast. Wow, that's a big drop. Okay.
Mario is the gibbous of Mario games. That doesn't even make any sense at all.
That's too fast. It's too fast. I gotta wait till it's like almost all the way done.
It's not the gibbous. Mario is the the actual engine that the game runs on. Now let's go here.
Back up there right now. Oh, let's check this out first.
Let's go through this. Is this the armor? Does this count as like the shield of the armor?
How do I get that coin? I can't believe somebody just said spin.
And I listened to them. Why did I listen to you? There was no reason for you to listen to you.
Everybody gets so... why did you not listen to chat? Oh, now I'm all fucking tilted.
No, no, I'm all fucking tilted. How did... what, what... never mind.
There's too many coming out here. All right, this is ridiculous. I'm fucked. Holy shit, they're stuck.
No, blow it up. Hurry. I'm gonna wait till it explodes. I can't, I can't do this kind of shit.
Why? I'm telling you. I can't... where's the armor? In here? Armor... no, it's not. I think my controls
ran out of battery. I just pressed jump and it took three seconds to happen. Down blue. There's a key here.
Um, where's that fire? Should I get that? I think I'm gonna get that. Take a risk. No, don't take any risks.
Put this on. There's the armor. I got it. Oh, I can break these right with the helmet.
Oh, two keys. Um, uh, excuse me. Excuse me. That's not fair. That's not fair. Unfair. Spawn.
Why? Can I do this now? What if I don't have my mount or my helmet? Still... can I still beat it?
P? I think I just got stuck. No, I didn't. Okay. I can't move. I thought that was fire. I was about
to fucking scream. Anything over here? There's this guy. I have the P. Uh, get away from me.
Get away from me. Um, what am I? What should I do? What should I do with the P? I don't know
what to do with the P. Can I fly with the P? You piece of shit. Um, I got it. Fall. Please fall, right?
No. Okay, I got all three keys. I got the key and now I... what should I do with the block? Why is
I stuck to the ceiling? Um, wow. Oh my god. I just fucking panicked. Like the ultimate panic. Did I
get it? Okay, I need to stop. Stop, please. That was fun. That was a fun one. That was nice. That was
good. That was interesting. Except for like that, you know, spawning... bomb spawning. I mean,
I don't know. I kind of got killed. I didn't feel like I deserved that.
You are great at Mario and you are very tall. Hey, gonna have to give it to that one. I like it when
he gets mad. Escape the swamps while avoiding the hungry piranha plants. Too bad you're not
great at Mario. It's alright. That's fine. We already got over our leg meltdown. Oh no, we
didn't. Never mind. Avoid the piranha plants. It's like a pretty wholesome level, right?
Wait, what's down here? Secret? No, I screwed it up.
It's to make a Mario. Take a while. That was fun. That was a good one. Thank you for that
level. It was good. Play this one for the joke. For the jokes, okay. All right. After this,
can somebody link me one of those that you stand still and it plays a song?
Can somebody link me? It's got to be the Game of Thrones theme. I want to see that. It has to
exist. Morality based. What is this? Yoshi's Choice? Question mark. What am I doing here?
Well, that's interesting. Five seconds. Hold on. I can do that in five seconds.
I can do that shit in five seconds. How long was that? How on earth do you do that quicker?
No, I'm done. I'm just gonna do the level. So you gotta fall down and then I'll try it.
I need Yoshi again. That's longer than I thought. One more try. Oops-a-daisy. Oops-a-daisy. All right,
that was fun. Next, coming up. I'll try the tuna and pretzel connection that you've been preaching
to us if you play my level. Yeah. No, you're just spelling up pretending. I get it. Okay,
can we get a real one or what? Isn't this one real? Hey, regardless, you better try that
combination. I remember your name. I will remember. This is for me. Actually, for Jermo.
This should be challenging enough. I regret putting this one in. You can't get more than one
second. How? One bounce on the head? Right, that's gotta be it. Are you doing this right now at the
same time? One... I don't... That's... You can't go faster than that. It's not possible. Okay, okay,
okay. I'm done. I don't care. It was... No, it's 1.3370. Nobody can get faster than that. All right,
give me another one. This is a relaxing trip to Chill Peak. Don't mind if I do. Chill Peak
Mountain. Have a relaxing vacation at beautiful Chill Peak Mountain. Mario 3. I already like it.
This song is freaking me out because it doesn't belong here. Pretty chill. This is from... What
is this? Rainbow Road? No, no, no. The one where you're... The slide? That's the slide. Right, right,
right. Or what I think would be better use of this music is a non-stop gif of a hamster running in
a wheel. Video idea for some of you that have hamsters? No, I gotta fly. There's gotta be
something over there. Come on, you gotta have something over there. That was... That was a chill,
fun level. Thank you, that level. All right, just because you wrote, try it out. My very funny
level and you put ha ha ha ha ha ha in all caps. I had a great a different description but forgot.
Version 3. This is a 3% level. Reach the goal after activating all 999
POW blocks. Did this take like six years to make this? The world record is an hour.
How the fuck do I get out of here? What is happening? What am I doing wrong? Oh, all right, then...
But I can't get... I can't do anything about that.
But what? What the fuck? How do I get this thing?
Okay, low battery. Oh no, what do you mean low battery? I charge these all night.
Low battery, what? I'm gonna have to bring the dock. No, anyway, I can't. Hold on.
Hold on. This thing is a lot of the way. Go here. I don't know what that...
You're probably wondering why I did... I'm just trying to run... I got like a hundred keys.
I ran back and forth once and I got a bunch of keys, so I'm...
Oh my god. Okay, why is it giving... What's with all the keys?
Pretend it's not. It's called experimentation. I don't get it. I'm gonna come back. That just gives me...
I don't even... I can't even talk. Can you hear this? Huh? Uh, thanks for the five community subs.
That was for he to meet. Thank you, subs. Five. Appreciate it. Thanks for the five community subs.
So, I don't understand this.
What's the time frame on that? You just have to wait like eight, five seconds? Um, all right.
I don't know. No! Kill me quick! Skip this. I... Hold on. Just let me... Just give me a minute.
I'm not ready to give up yet. Let me skip to the end of that thing.
Okay. So, it's like...
What's happening here? Should I go...
Was there a spike? Did I just sit on a spike? What? Was there a spike in...
Yeah, I don't know about this one. I mean, it's funny, but I don't know if I'm gonna sit here all night.
Okay, deal. Just in here. And then, uh, should I try...
There goes a hamster! Somebody get a gif of a hamster running away.
Please. I need to see it. I gotta see if my viral video is gonna take off or not.
You guys tell me. Do you really care about this level? Hold on. It's paused. Don't worry.
That's funny. That's funny. Yeah, this is funny. The world record is actually an hour long. How do
you do this for an hour? No, it's gotta be faster than that. Faster! I need a faster run. I don't...
I just want to see what this looks like. I need to know. You know, the hamster has to be running,
like, really fast. No, there's none of these that are that fast. They're slow. Does anybody
have a fast one? Is this fast? Speed up the video on YouTube. Oh, here we go. No, this is...
Yeah, this is perfect. This is absolutely perfect. Good. All right, let's do it. This is a good break.
I'm taking a break. Let's go. And now, damn... 20 kids at the aquarium. Okay, here we go.
Here we go! That was really cute. That was a very cute video. I would share that on Facebook.
That's because I'm looking over here and people are, like, fucking furious with that.
People, like, talking so much shit about that hamster. Oh, I couldn't handle it. I'm sorry.
I think people are fucking losing their mind about how much they hate the hamster. I don't know.
My fucking grandmother was like this. It sucked. Oh my god. Every time I hear this, it sucks.
Oh, this is dumb. That's dumb. Okay, I'm gonna tell you that's dumb. I don't want to do this one
anymore. That's dumb. That's just dumb. I don't want to do that. I got it. I turned it down.
Oh, you guys are fucking hilarious. You're giving up on a minute-long level. This is not a minute-long
level. Okay, do it, pow, and then go right in the door. Go! What? Where's the trick? There's a trick
somewhere. Where's the trick? There was a trick that I was in. I got hit by the trick already.
This is the trick. Yes, it is. You're right. I got tricked. All right, this is the last attempt
and then I'm out. We'll do another one. I'm stuck right now. You know what I mean? I'm fucking stuck.
Okay, so I go up into here and then what? Does it not go in there? Did I do it? Okay, apparently
I just hold on. Okay, I held on to the wall. Now what? I'm gonna get crushed. There's somebody in
there. How do I? No, that's a joke. I can't get that. How am I supposed to get that? I'm going
to take the damage. Won't I take the damage from the... Do I have to grab that from the very bottom
pixel? All right, this is my actual final attempt. I promise. I swear this is the final attempt.
I want to see what happens there. Yeah, I'm curious. All right, let's do this again.
Hold on to the side. There we go. All right, so how do I get this? Just by jumping up and...
No, I can't go this way. Oh, come on. No, that's... Why? No, that's not fair. All right, I...
I know that's the last one, but that wasn't my fault. I know that was not my fault. That was not
even my last attempt. That was the game... You know what I'm saying? That was not a real attempt.
If I died by... Oh, I got hit by a spike! Okay, that's me. I didn't lose to that. The game lost
for me. Like, if I fell down right there, that's an attempt. If I get hit in the head by a wrench
or something, whatever, that's my fault. Okay, here we go. I know there's a little battery.
All right, break the blocks and then... Now what? Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What happens now? Huh? No, you saw... Break the... Why didn't I shrink? Break the one on the left,
somebody said, and then I freaked out. That one doesn't count. That was... Somebody in chat died
there. Not me. Somebody said, break the one on the left, break the one on the left. No, no, that
wasn't... That was somebody in chat that did that. I didn't do that. That was not something I was
gonna do. No, that was not me doing that. Hey, hit the one on the left! And I was like, okay,
this is your turn, so you do it. Nobody told you to follow his advice. No, but still...
Okay, this is it. This is op... This is on my own. Whatever I do here, this is my doing.
No one else is going to do this for me. This is my doing. All right, all right. All right, okay.
Joel just came in with a raid. What's up, Joel? I tried your level and I didn't do very well. It
was very, very hard. It was super ridiculously hard, but it was very fun, very well thought out.
I heard it took you 20 hours. I watched the part where you went all the way down and around and
died at the end, and I vicariously lived through like 12 hours of your life and decided I wasn't
gonna do it. But welcome, everybody. We're doing just random viewer levels. He said it was a pile
of shit. I did not... I did not say that. Don't listen to that. All right, how about this one?
But thank you so much for the raid. If you stick around, we're gonna do this for a little bit
while longer. Probably another couple hours or something. All right, prove that you're a gamer
and beat this level. I'll try. Is this one of those levels that laughs at you and makes you
stuck somewhere? 20 seconds? Megalovania. All right, let's go. Speedrun? It's a... oh, it's a song.
How has only one percent seen a song get done? Oh, by the way, if you've never seen... if you've
never seen Undertale, don't look. Spall the coins. Only 19 more seconds. That's right.
I was running. What? Stop, there are spoilers everywhere.
What? Now what? Oh god, I have to go up and around. Oh. Oh! What do you do here? You idiot.
You idiot. You idiot. I at least want to hear the first part of the song.
Whoa! Spin jump. Spin jump. That was close. Oh! It hit me in the fucking face! What was the point
of you... should I hold on to that? Ah! Ah! Ah! It actually came down and hit me.
And hit me. I don't... why am I bringing it? I don't even need to bring that stupid thing.
Oh my god, I'm an idiot. I did it again. Does... what happened?
What happened? I... maybe... I gotta see that end. Shoot it? I have to spin jump down there? I only
have one second remaining. Oh sh... um, I need to know what... I hit the POW when they were on the
screen. They were clearly on that screen. They were on that screen. You saw them. What happened
there? I can still do it. All right, so I hit the POW but it didn't kill them down there.
Doesn't it really blow up everything? Not fast enough. It's the time. Oh man. That was bullshit.
I got like stuck in the goddamn wall. I'll get it. How did I not touch those? I'm clearly touching
them. I don't... I'm upset about that. We're back in time again. Dead. I just hit myself in the face.
Don't jump. I have to like keep moving and I have to hold up and I have to...
It's right here. I crouched for a tenth of a second. It was like...
That's all right. Jesus! It's right there. I can smell it. Touch it! Oh, that sucked.
That sucked. That was that sucked. That's unfortunate. Come on. Move, move, move, move.
Touch it! I did it! That one was fun. I think I actually had to ground pound. That was pretty
good. There you go. Prove you're a true gamer. I'm... sometimes I'm a gamer. Not all the time,
though. All right. This one says, I swear to the Lord. Let's try this one. Plinko shell drop.
Drop the shell in a slot and see if you can get the jackpot. I feel like I'm going to really like
this one. I am. Get 60 coins. Reach the goal of grabbing 60 coins. Easy enough, I guess.
Does it matter which one of these I pick? I know I got low battery.
I know where it goes. Is this like the dev door? No. All right. I have to follow it.
I just have to see what I get. I guess I could float down with it, but then I have to come back
up. Give me 50 coins right now. Right at the bottom. 50. 50! 50! 50! No! What's the point
of having Yoshi? What does Yoshi do here? It's cute. Yeah, but... No! Oh, shit. I'm gonna do it
again. We're at the bottom. Wait, you want me to swim all the way down there? All right,
we're gonna go second here. Right, the door means elevator up. Yes. Yeah. Where did that just go?
That would make sense, wouldn't it? There would be a door here.
You're right. Come on, give me the big 50. Why do they all keep going over here?
Come on, I want to have him go down. No! I want to... Come on, go get him.
It was gonna work, too. It was gonna work! And now he has the thing in his mouth!
Despawn. I promised I wasn't gonna scream anymore, and I just did.
I was trying to drop him down, so maybe he would just float all the way down and grab the 50.
You're not actually doing this, are you? I thought I was gonna get stuck again. It is.
No, it's not. Thank God. Don't do it again. Don't do it again. It's gonna do it again.
Thank God. Come on. I'm almost done. Give me the 50. It's what Yoshi would have wanted.
50! 50! Yeah! Get the hell out of here. I win. That was a fun one. I liked it. It was fun.
We got a Life is Pain. I'll give it a try. LPM. What else we got? 1VG. Life is Pain.
Why did I pick the one that said Life is Pain? The level can only be beaten by sliding backwards.
Okay. The frozen backwards only cave. I thought I had to slide backward. Can you jump? No.
Ignore the level name and just go. All right. Fine. You can't walk. You have to go backwards.
That's what the thing says. I'm losing momentum! I know. I'm sorry. Every time I get really intense,
it sounds like somebody punching me in the stomach. I'm sorry. Walk to the left. Somebody
said keep jumping to do momentum. Right here. What if I turn a little... No. Come on. I'm not
good at it. I'm not. This is Super Mario Wii 3D. This is never gonna happen. What the fuck? Okay.
Hold on. No. Almost there. No. Do it again. I keep hitting down. It's just in my brain
because it's slide. You have to slide. Doesn't that mean you have to hold down?
Like slide backwards to win. Oops. All right. I got it. I got it. I got it. I'll do it. I got it.
I lost it already, I think. I just had to do it earlier. It's all right. It's not that bad.
I fucked it up again. You gotta go longer with the slide. Stay in thing with this.
You gotta do longer. I still get it. You don't have to jump into sliding when I stop moving.
It's all right. No. It's not all right. See? I keep having problems with that first slide.
It's okay. The game didn't fuck up yet. Cheater. No. It actually was bad because it stopped me.
Okay. Here it is. Here it is. Here it is. Here it is. This is the part. All right. All right.
No. You motherfucker. It's right there. That was it too. Shit.
This is so addicting, but it's gonna kill me. Stupid fucking low battery.
I don't care if it's low battery. Stop telling me. You told me like 10 times.
I don't need you to distract me. I know the battery's low. I know. You don't have to tell
me every five minutes. I promise. I know. I'm telling you. Humanity is gonna get to a point
where like this is not gonna be enough. We're gonna start slapping each other in the faces with
fucking frying pans in like 20 years. This is not gonna be enough. This is gonna be frying pan
streams where like I hit you in the face with a frying pan and you hit me in the face with a
fucking frying pan. It's not enough anymore. What happened there? What? I just stopped like
dead in my tracks. That was weird. It's so fucking much for my body and brain to do this a million
times. And it's with my least favorite Pokemon too. It's with my least favorite Mario game.
What is it doing that? Why is it freezing me? That's the second time that's happened. Am I
doing something wrong here? I don't understand it. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. I got it. I did it. Oh
my god. I did it. Yes. Wait. Hold on. What do I do now? Can I not touch that? I can touch that,
right? What does that mean? You fuck. That was unfortunate. I just heard the laugh. It means I
can't do it. I heard like the fucking cat noise. That was genuine. It eats away at my fucking soul.
Oh, I'm going too fast. No, I gotta slow down. So I'm so glad I did the beginning again though.
So I'm not sliding bad. Then I'm not sliding forwards. I mean backwards, I mean. That's not
gonna be like deduct points or something, right? How do I open this door? How do I open the door?
Just walk. Just walk. Just walk. Just walk. I did it. Wait. Does this matter? This doesn't fucking
matter. 39 seconds. That was crazy. He has a calming level. Oh, that's funny. Jubated. I like it.
I made this fun. Let's try it. What was the completion on this? 2%. That was fun.
PNM. 8. TG. I made this one. Four cast calls with lots of fish bones. Left, right, left. When does
it end? Short and sweet. Fish bone barrage. I know how to do this. I can't do this in like
hot dog mode. You can't play Mario Maker in hot dog mode. All right, hold on. No, I got it. I got
it. I got it. Don't worry. I'm fine. I'm gonna charge these up. Hold on a sec. Just wait.
All right. Take a pee break. I'll be right back. I got controllers here. I'm good. All right. I'm
good to go. It's starting to communicate. Yeah, I'm good. I'm ready. Okay. Was I on a level?
I think I was, right? Fish bone barrage. Well, there goes a CD. I don't know what the fuck it was.
All right. I think that's a joke. I can't get them. Maybe I can. Will those kill me if they touch me?
Probably, right? Where's like the indicator of where they land? It's like a telegraph.
Dear, what are they gonna fall? It just takes up the screen. Left, right, left, right, left, right.
Okay. Left, right. Oh, I get it. All right. That's a neat little, uh, that was right. So, they're
gonna go left side now. Two, three, left. They're gonna be on the right side. And that's the thing
that kills me. I'm looking up. So, when you're here, that's right. Because that's, now that's left.
The beeps are left and the errors are right. Hang on. Oh, shit. Not good. It's gonna be left,
isn't it? That was, that was a different beep than the other ones were, right? I thought that was
going right. Because that really looks like this one. This one goes boop. See? I, I'm not sure the
sounds matter. I think it just goes left, right, left, right. Hurry, hurry up. But, oh, shit. No,
please. I tried to aim it. I tried to block it. No, it's gonna be on the left. Shit. Oh, boy.
I thought, I don't know if we, at first, I had a little bit more time, I guess. I thought I had
way less time. What the fuck? Oh, fuck. I gotta go this way. Because that's not gonna be over.
No. Come on. I gotta stand underneath it. Which way is it gonna go? Oh, man. You have to jump
right underneath when I go. Damn it. All right. I thought, it spawned me, like, right in the thing.
I feel like it takes me two or three times to do that every single time.
I'm holding B. It just doesn't go up. Why? Shit. Okay. Block it. Block it. Please.
All right. I gotta make the jump up right before they land. Now what? All the way to the right?
Anything else to block? Oh, God. Just go in. Just go in. Get out of here. There it is. That's not
gonna, was that gonna kill me? I thought I was gonna die. That was a really good one. Cheers to
that. How do I, what do I, I can't like it. Oops. All right. We'll try this one. This one
requires no gamer skills. And I like the sound of that. MBG4C6TWG. What does that say? Wait,
did I get that wrong? B. Wait, what? I read MBG4C6TWG. MBG4C6TWG. That didn't work. MBG4C6TWG.
Yeah. Weird. All right. We'll do this one. 5TV. It's MGB not, it's MGB not MGB.
You're confusing the absolute fuck out of me right now. All right. Mario in the haunted treasure.
Mario discovers a cave full of gold, but he needs a P-switch to reach it.
Is it a storyline one? I probably shouldn't have done that. Okay. Hold on. Let me look.
Uh, what's down here? Oh, I just dropped the big one.
Oh, I should not have done that. I should not have done that.
Is this a new motorcycle ride fun? Did I ride it yet? I'm just gonna go through here.
Well, that was bad. It's good. All right. Um, I think I have to go down here. Really?
Yeah. The Hagrid out of the new universal ride. Yeah. I'm surprised more people didn't know what
I was talking about. I got a one-up on it. I got the P-block. I did it, right? That's it. What am
I standing still for? I feel like I'm doing like the secret. I feel like I'm doing the secret part.
Uh-oh. He shook me. Should I just bring this with me? All right. I did it. Oh shit. I did it.
All right. I feel like there was a few ways to go there. Short and sweet. That was pretty short.
All right. We got this one. Here's the correct spelling. M-G-B-4-C-6. M-G-B-4-C-6-T-W-G.
There we go. Okay. Bob-omb mansion. Short and sweet. This one is pretty explosive.
Let's take a look. First day of work and I dropped the vase on the ground.
Okay. I'm just gonna get over that. Do I need to do something with these?
I feel like you wouldn't have bombs if I wasn't gonna need to use them.
I can't fucking believe I missed that jump. That's one way to do it. Wait.
Ah. Oh yeah. I didn't see the other one. No. The chomp did it. I didn't see it. That's good.
This is a pretty good placement of the, uh, of the Bob-ombs, I will say.
They kind of just, they just barely get right in the way. Pretty good. Almost fucking blew that one.
All right. Hold on. Upside down P. Hit it. I knew I was gonna need this. Y'all thought I
wasn't gonna need that and I, I brought, I got it. Now I got Yoshi. What do I do with Yoshi now?
Uh, melt. All right. Hold on here. Checkpoint. Nice. I do have to say, I don't want to lose
Yoshi though because I'm not gonna get him at the checkpoint. Uh, I was off screen, so.
It's all right. I got an extra, I get to take an extra hit. Let me see what this looks like. Hold
on. Shit. Go. Damage boost. Oh my god. It's the end. I win. Clever. Clever. That's pretty good.
Bob-omb mansion. Very cool. Thank you. This one is, uh, the man on a mission, the level, the movie.
This is piquing my curiosity. Let's see what this does. The level, the movie. KMG. Mario goes to the
store for milk. All right. Uh, sorry. A zeppelin just flew by. All right. Uh, go to the store and
get the milk. Reached the goal after defeating all the booms. What the absolute fuck is that?
Oh, that's not good. How do I break the ice? Let's go. I'm going real fast. Can you actually
crash the car and die? It's too soft. I can't. What else you got? Let's go. This level made me cry
tears of joy. I'll check it out. Thank you for the level, by the way. Escape from Peerthorn
Perch. Can you escape the tricky jungle of spiky peerthorn trees? Water is rising.
Okay. Let's go. Try again. Remember we were talking about how, like, uh, did I say something
earlier about, like, a pizza? I said earlier that I was gonna eat, like, a large pizza or something,
didn't I? Um, did the guys have to get all the coins? I'm not, I'm not gonna make this. I didn't even try.
I'm not gonna eat a chicken on stream again. That's not gonna be the thing.
Is the audio a bit early? Yeah, I don't know why. Especially the switch for some reason
when I pull through this capture card. Is that a sink? I think it happens sometimes with other
ones too, but not. I feel like it's a switch thing. At least on my whatever I have for a setup here.
No. Any other compulsive jumpers in Mario? Like, I jump. I land on a surface. Jump. Okay.
I'm a compulsive jumper. I need to hit a blue switch somewhere.
Looks like it's over here. There it is. Let's kind of shoot out of there. Shell. But why
do I need a shell? I guess I could go like this.
Anybody else here an idiot too? No, just me. Get out of here. Give me a break.
Get out of here. Get out of here with that shit. Come on. Get out of here. Like, come on. Really?
I don't want to kill this because I don't know what's in that box. What was the point of that?
Get back up there quickly, I guess, to hit the switch. Really? Why did you turn so rapidly?
Did I pick? I got that one already. That's odd. Okay. I don't know if I'll get it. Three more?
There's one in there. Load that up. Oh, shit. Oh, no. Now they're gonna get down here. What have I
done? Well, they're in a nice place. Supposed to do that. Switch is over here. I think now I can
do this. No. I have to go. It's got to bounce off that. Did I screw the whole thing up? You
would think it would bounce across, right? I guess I'm just gonna stand down there and do it again.
What does that achieve for me? What do I just do? Can I jump up here?
Oh, I can go through this wood. Right, right. Then,
hold on. Anything change up here? There we go. All right. Two more. I'm thinking I'm thinking
jump and grab and fall and grab and hold and... Okay. Do I need to blow that up with a bomb?
Can you... Can I swim? Or am I gonna sink right to the bottom? I don't remember. Okay. I think
sometimes I forget. All right. On this side? Okay. There's this shit. So that wall is gone.
What are you gonna fire? Oh, it's a homing missile. Oh, fuck. I'm fine. All right. One more.
And where is this last one? What's down here? Can I see anything? All right. What is this?
It's not... All right. Just swim. Just swim. Just swim. Swim. Swim. Swim. Swim. Swim. There's
one more somewhere. Where's this last one? Uh-oh. Red platform writer. What is this? Go in? What's
it gonna drop? A bomb. But what do I do with the bomb? I don't have the key. Left. Left. Go left.
All right. Then I gotta... All right. I'm good. I'm gonna go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
I get it. Okay. I gotta go down. Take a bomb down. But right down? Straight down?
This is it. Holy shit. It's already open. I did it already. Nice. Now I got a power block
and I need to do something with this. What do I need to do with this? What do I do with this?
I don't know what this wants me to do. Um... Do I kill it? Go in the pipe?
I have... There's another... Holy shit. This is long. Oh, that's not good. I had to bounce and then grab.
Oh boy. Okay. So I got it. Now it became a speed run. Why did I not throw that earlier?
That's what I want to know. Okay. Now what? Oh. Spin. I can just throw it anywhere though, so that's
fine. Does it go in the water? This whole stream, I'll tell you. Take all the audio clips I've said.
I might as well be watching golf. Oh. Did it go in the water? Oh, it got trapped. I'm just
watching fucking golf. Really? Come on. That's bullshit. Bounced off one and hit the other.
I'm safe. Wait a minute. What's... Other keys. Just no other five keys?
That was good. Watching golf with the occasional jump scare reaction.
Yeah, that's when the guy accidentally hits it like way too far and it like soars. That's when
the guy uses like a three wood instead of a pitching wedge and he like hits it like fucking
over the building. Yeah, totally. No slack at all tonight, huh? Geez. All right. Let's do...
What about the times when I yell? Well, I'm trying to fuck the guy up that's hitting the ball.
Right? When he goes down, I go like... Now I get fucking thrown out. All right. Epic cool level.
Okay. Let's try this one. No, no, no. 50H. What the hell is this? Did I just type in somebody's
fucking like password? Did I just like get into somebody's account? Was that like your account
login? Okay. I made this for you. All right. We'll do this one. 13. Why does this one look
familiar? Did I do this one already? What is that? Of course it looks familiar and it's died to
pinwheel. Okay. All right. Your skills astound me. Here we go. This one looks normal. This one looks
normal and not like this. Okay. All right. Try this level. I feel like that one would be fun.
I feel like 30 or 40 of those, which is those. All right. Wait, wait, wait. Let's do this one.
This one looks normal. I think this is a normal one. Boing gear tower. All right. This one is real
and it's also apparently very hard. Solve and scale the highest tower. Sorry. I had to stop.
All right. Where are we going? Scale the tower. Obviously I have to do that. This looks complicated.
I might just veto this one. How do I? I think I had to try this one more time.
Damage run it maybe? Or does it matter which one of these I go into? Or
probably not. I'm assuming I probably have to damage run this. Let's go. I'm missing something.
This one is different. I'm way too fast. Fuck. Oh shit. Look out. I'm Zeppelin. I think I got it.
And then the thing shoots. Ah. It's just a P. It's just a P block. It's not a big deal. Now that'll
give me the... I have this now. Should I take them both? I can't take them both. All right. Now
this one... I don't think it's this one. Throw the spring over here. Oh. What happened? Did I do it?
Oh. Okay. I gotta get them all. All right. No, no, no. All right. So that's that one. Now we
get to do this one. So now... All right. Get... Bring it. Nothing gonna kill me? How do I get this
down? So that means should I kill the... No. That was what I just did. I need to throw the bomb.
I have to keep pushing the thwomp. Yeah. But I mean, how do I do that?
I was thinking throw a bomb down there. Let me look at this again.
Okay. Are you serious? That... Do it again. Only two more. If I die, it's over.
Now this is the one that I was doing... All right. I have no idea how to do this one.
Get up here. And then somehow I have to hit this. But how do I grab that? Because I can't jump
through. Will he hit this? I felt like that was pretty good. Okay. So now this is where I can die.
This is bad. Because I don't have any checkpoints. Is this... It's this or that's it? It's over.
Do I have to go down? Pull it up. Go down. And then... I don't know. I have no idea how the fuck to
get over there. I get one shot. Climb up. Climb down. Do I have to make that thing fall? One shot.
Here we go. What? Did that really just happen? I was... Hold on. I need to see that again.
That was dog shit. That... Come on. That was not cool. What? I'm actually... I'm pretty mad about
that. Apparently. I have to stand on that. Yeah. I have to get on... Stand on it. Well, I'm gonna...
This one's first. The other ones aren't that hard. I'm gonna do it. But then when it comes back,
what am I supposed to do? Like here. Yeah. You gotta... You gotta go up. You gotta go down. When
it goes up, you gotta go up. When it goes down, like yeah. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. You gotta fit yourself
in the slot. Whatever one it's currently on. I'm trying to go fast. No. I shouldn't be doing that.
Hasty. Hasty. Hasty. What the fuck? What? I don't... I don't want to stay on it.
It's killing me. I have to do this. It's... You got this little tiny margin. Damn it. Damn it.
Ah. Look how far away I am. What is with that? I'm not even close. All right. Let's go.
The other ones are not that hard. I should be able to do them without a problem.
What is this one? I haven't seen this one yet either. Might as well figure out how to do them
all. All right. So the theory here is to get this down, I have to throw it? Just throw it down there
and then... But do I jump down with this and then throw it over? How am I supposed to get to the
right? Then now I can just... No. But how? I gotta go backwards to the blocks. Just drop. Bingo.
Down deal. Two more. Don't accidentally hit this pipe. This one... I know how to do this one. Right.
I remember. Yeah. Oh. This one actually... I can die here. This one's kind of wonky. I can die here.
Give me another one. That was painful. It was. That was painful, but I don't want to do it again.
It was not that bad. It was good. That level was good. I had it, but I just... I don't want to do...
Oh. I don't want to do it again. Damn it. That one was fun. I knew that there was a big push there and...
Let's do this one. What time is it? All right. We'll do a few more in the night. We gotta call it.
It's getting late. Zero g d. I will be back tomorrow with... That's a good question.
Meowzer's four challenges. Complete each diverse challenge and race Meowzer to the finish. Guys,
isn't tomorrow Terraria Day? I'm gonna have to talk to Star. It was supposed to be either
tomorrow or Saturday or Saturday or depending on what he's doing.
Maybe it's tomorrow. If he's around tomorrow and wants to do it tomorrow, we'll do it tomorrow.
There's gotta be a reason for this. Of course there is.
This is cheating now. He must have watched Evo. Oh, fuck. Evo is this weekend. Oh, no.
I got too much stuff to do. Oh, no. I wanted to go. It's like right here. I gotta get on a plane
and like go to this robotics facility. Evo is this weekend. Why is there so much stuff going on?
Oh, did I get trolled? Was that like a joke? What? What? What happened? Oh, that was in one
of the trials. I was supposed to go back up. When does Evo... It was ice cubes. I'm dead.
Starts at 10 a.m. tomorrow. Well, no. I got... I'm not gonna go. I got too much going on.
It's all weekend? Yeah, but I can't because I'm streaming. I'm gonna be streaming today,
tomorrow, and the next day. I might be able to pop over there on Sunday, but then next week I'm
gonna go. I'm going to... I'm going across the country to work on the carnival stream at the
facility where it's happening. So I don't... Wait, give me the fly. Give me the fly. I'm not just
gonna not stream. Maybe I'll just go watch the finals. That's a whole separate event, right?
The finals. Should I stay in the car? I don't know why I'm still in the car. Depends on what
game. I do need the car. Am I too small to get in there now? Oh, thank God. All right, back out.
Evo sold out. Oh, well, there you go. Never mind. Scream the finals on your channel like you did
with E3. I don't... I'm not sure you were allowed to co-stream that. I don't have any idea what the
hell I'm talking about. I would not be able to commentate like Street Fighter gameplay.
Okay. No, I wouldn't want to do that. Just let him fall down there and just do it.
I need that. Two more. Easy. What? No! He was a different... He was a different... I didn't... I
thought... I thought he took a long time to shoot that. He took... He took his time to shoot that.
Fuck, that one was fun, too. Tina Belcher? All right, it's almost time to go.
I feel like I did that a lot today, too. All right, let's do...
This one's a relaxing level. Who knows if they're alive or not. W-P-T. Y-J-5.
L-K-G. Seven Heaven. Traverse Bowser Jr.'s fleet. Watch out for the cannonballs.
Is this Cake Mario? No. This is not Cake Mario. It's not my favorite Mario.
Got big. It got small. I don't need it. I don't need it for these auto-scrollers.
No. Fire. Watch out. Got it. This is it. What a nice level. Kind of relaxing and just fun.
Just jump around and jump on stuff. Watch out for the fire. Get the goombas. I thought that was a
ground. Where are you going? Guys. Guys. Okay. It might be time for me to pull the plug.
I don't know what it is. Mario is such like a fun family game. But when I play it,
I feel like I smoked a pack of cigarettes. That was a good one. Let me try to get a good jump.
That was a four out of ten. What time is it? We can do two more. Two more. Six and a half hours.
We're good. We can do like two more. Somebody said here's a baby level. Wait. Hold on. There's
cool level with wrenches. Let me do this one first. He's addicted. Well, it's kind of just fun to see
what people make. This one has wrenches. Escaping the P-Mole Fortress. Use their P-Block against
them. Use the P-Block against them. And it's also got this lava here. That deer right there has
wrenches in this level. Means it gets an automatic one point letter grade higher. I can't even make
this jump. I have to stop looking at fucking chat. Oh you guys. What the fuck. All right. Let's go.
Am I still here? Are you still alive, man? Are you still with me? Am I going to get that smell
thing that the people put in your nose and makes you go, I'm alive now. It's all about these blocks.
The car is leaving without me. They're going on vacation without me. I don't even have my fucking
backpack. That's unbelievable. What happens if they go all the way? Oh. Anybody figure this out?
Look at all those. Look at all those fucking ribbons. Whatever they are.
Holy shit. How am I supposed to do that? Oh man. No. Come back. Come back. Where's the switch?
Oh I have to hit the switch right. Holy shit. I have to just dodge until it gets all the way
over there. I have to tap it and wait. I have to wait for one pass of ribbons right here. Don't
go anywhere. Touch it. Now I have to wait. What the. That was impossible. That was an
uncompletable. That was an uncompletable bow tie pasta right there. I'm sorry.
Another night. Where was I supposed to go? All right. Come on. One more pass and that's it.
Oh shit. I need that. That's fire. Give me that. Just damage boost. Oh I fucking panicked.
I'm so pissed. That's all right. I'm right here. Oh I'm pissed. Pissed. Do you hear that? He's pissed.
Give me the mushroom. Come on. Get a mushroom out here right now. Please. Oh this. Fire.
Right. My goodness. I gotta like bait them up. All right. Get this mushroom and then relax.
Now wait. They throw two. There it is. Wait for the fire. You gotta be kidding me. Get the other
mushroom right now. Right now. Why did it not come out? Why did that not come out? I don't understand.
All right. The fire is what's killing me here. I got plenty of time so just hold on. I can't go.
I think I just tried to snipe me. I tried to jump off of them and for some reason holding B just
didn't do anything. I was holding the B button down. Come on.
I don't know. I don't. They're gonna be everywhere now. I'm in so much trouble. Look at this. They're
everywhere. Look at this. Did you see this? I have to just go fast. You gotta go as fast as you can
otherwise they just group up on you. Well not that fast. There's no power button or something
somewhere. I almost got hit by that. All right. Let me take a second before I just... Well you
have to go fast because the... Wait. Just get... I was gonna wait for the mushroom. You have to... I
have to stay... I'm gonna stand on the edge after the fire. There's one square you can stand on.
My stomach doesn't hit the... By the way if you're curious my stomach just fucking pushed
forward on the desk and hit R. I didn't think it was on there. It's such a bad spot. No. What the
fuck? Oh my god. Oh my... What the fuck? Throw him up. Yeah. Up here. Throw him. I know you...
This fire over here is... And now let me get up here. All right. Hold on right here for a second.
It's gonna hit me. Wow. Huh? You gotta kill... Okay. You kill him. I killed him. Now we just have...
I think I have to get down there now. Did it... That one was intense.
That last spot. That last screen with the vines and the wrenches and the explosions and the...
I don't know if I can do that one again. That was really cool though. All right.
We're gonna end it on one more. Yeah. Give me like a Game of Thrones theme song. You can search.
All right. Let me search then. It's not over. It's not over. It's not over. It's not over.
How am I searching? Difficulty all. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Get detailed search. Music
by popularity. Game... Okay. Here we go. Game style. All course theme. That doesn't really matter,
I guess. Is tags music? There we go. Music. Just music. Okay. Did that work? Oh, by popularity.
Rhythm challenge. This is a gourmet race. Country roads. Okay. I need to know what this one's like.
Cake Mario is the best one. Take me home country road.
That was nice. That was really nice. Fucking up the rhythm. Yeah, I know. At least make the tempo
consistent. I have one piece. This is that one piece theme song. I'm not sure I've ever even
heard this before. Wait, I have... It goes, give it up, give it up, give it up. Yeah, yo, yeah, yo.
Are they gonna do that? His name is Luffy. Right? That's not it. No, they've trapped me in here. I
can't like run out. I can't get out of here. Is that... Okay, so that's season two. Is this season
three? No. Oh, that's cool. Oh, that's the pirate ship. Wow, that's neat. Yeah. Star Fox.
Mortal Kombat. Walk, don't run. Don't tell me what to do. Here we go. Test your fight. What is it?
It's test your what? What is it? Choose to fight. What is it? What's the actual thing?
Choose to fight. That's really, really cool. Game of Thrones. The Game of Thrones theme song.
I'm not gonna click that one. I know everyone's supposed to freak the fuck out. Wait, is this
gonna... I might want to hear that one.
Maybe that one too. Train your things. Pizza delivery. All-star. Don't move. Don't move? Okay.
All right. What do you mean ruined it? That was at the very end. 24 seconds. Somebody... I gotta
get the speed run on this one. How to train your dragon. Tetris. Mario Maker. Wild. Passes. Sky.
Peaches. Castle. Quarry. Fountain. Wait, is this the like... I kind of have to know this.
I want to hear it again. I wanted to hear it again. I want to hear it again. That's really cool.
No, that's too fast. That's way too fast. Don't... I wouldn't run here.
It's gonna be slower. Maybe not. What song is it backwards? Sounds pretty much the same.
That goes forward and backwards the same. All right. One more and that's it. We're gonna do one more
song. Hotel Mario. Wait, is this the one that goes like... It is, isn't it? Yeah, it is. There's more?
Wait, I actually have to play this... I have to play this level. There's gameplay in this one,
guys. Pretty cool. And we're having a lot of spaghetti. That's a thing from like 2008.
That's it? What was that? I grew up on that meme. I think a lot of people did. That was back when
YouTube... People would just sentence splice together a bunch of dog shit. There were whole
communities around just like YouTube poops. That was old. All right, we'll do...
Donkey Kong. That's it. It was an interesting time. Yeah, you never knew what you were gonna get.
Kong? Donkey Kong. I almost just fell off. Now it's this Donkey Kong. Well, it's not that one,
is it? Nice. Where's the... That made me go a million miles per hour. That's right there.
Is it slippery or what? Whoa, these are... That's not in Mario. That's not in Donkey Kong.
They don't fire laser beams at you from the cannons. They added that in. This is an
interpretation of what that was. All right, well, hold on a second here. Now...
Ah, guys. All right, that was fun. This was a very, very fun stream for me. I enjoyed it.
This game is a lot of fun. I wish I was better at Mario. I wish I was like a better Mario
player. It's still fun though. So tomorrow... I'm not sure what's gonna happen tomorrow.
It's either gonna be Terraria with Star or Sam & Max Season 3 or something else. DOS? Yeah, depends.
One of those things will be tomorrow. I kind of... Hold on. I want to... Like, hold on a second.
I'm just curious as to what the big... The really, really popular courses are. All right.
I mean, let me... Okay, hold on. Planet... Planetary exploration. Let me just see what it is.
This is like the one of the... This is the most popular course in the world. Let me just see what
it is. This is the... This is the most popular course in the entire universe. Did we... A raid
came in? Oh, shit. That was Swordy Way. Thank you, Swordy Way, for the raid. Welcome, guys.
Is it giving me the middle finger? Oh, it's a rocket ship. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. I died.
Let me... Hold on. We're about to stop the stream, unfortunately. Sorry.
But welcome. Hope you had a good stream. All right, let's see. So you get the fire flower
and then the take off and lift off. All right, there it is. All right, that's cool. I want to
get right on top. Why is this the most popular? That's cute and interesting. It has a good song.
That's cute. The rocket ship takes off and you fly. That's nice. That's nice. There's more, too.
Look at this. It's a jellyfish. Oh, we're on the moon. I get it. He's a moon jellyfish.
I knew it. This is the best song, too. I don't think they'll ever make a Mario game that has
a song that's better than this one. They really won't ever. Stop trying to act cool. What? Am I
out of oxygen? That's a UFO. Oh, Bowser's an alien. I get it. Nice. What's he gonna take me?
What's he gonna take me? Get on there. That was really cute. That's pretty nice. Wait, batter up,
swipe the incoming shells. I know the stream's over, but hold on. And it's Cake Mario, so that's
already a plus two letter grade. Is this for the... I did it. Home run. Oh, this is it.
You guys don't even think I fucking know what I'm doing. Shit! I need another one. Give me another
ball. Where are they? Down here? Oh, no. No, do that again. I want to do that again. I fucking love
Cake Mario. All right. Boink, boink. Now, this one's fast. Oh, the next one is. It's this one
that's just like boom. Got it. Oh, that was a curve ball. I think the tail is a cape. No,
I'm saying cake. C-A-K-E, like Cake Mario, not Cape Mario. Let's see. De-stress land. Cake Mario
again. Back to back. Why do I call it Cake Mario? Do I have to actually explain this?
Back in like 1997, when you went to the grocery store to buy a birthday cake,
this is exactly what was in the display. This outline thick... it looked like this.
This is a grocery store Mario cake from like 1996. I guess I had to explain that. All right. That
felt good. And plus, he looks like the cake version. He looks like a cake.
There's another one I can say. This is Cake Mario. That's all you need to know.
Choo. Oh, why did it stop? No. Stress free. Happy. It's called Hardcore Jumps. And that is it.
This will take us... this already is seven hours. Never mind. That's back to back to back.
That's my favorite Mario. I mean, he has... there are other names for this Mario.
There's Keychain Mario. This is also Keychain Mario. In fact, I would say that the small Mario
is Keychain Mario. And the big one is Cake Mario. It's for this style.
At least five people know what I'm talking about. That was fun.
So we run 10 seconds. I'll try it. Not Cake Mario. Okay. You have to open doors and shit.
I'm gonna die. I think I'm dead. Open doors. Hit the switch. I can do it. Just kill me.
All right. Jump. And then down, down, down, down, down, down, down. Oh, that was close.
I didn't do the spring. Yeah, I'm not done. I want to do a couple more speedy ones.
Spectacular Sky Sprint. 20 seconds. There he is. Keychain Magnet Mario.
I just had to run.
I'm not sure how you do that much faster. Let me try. It's very... it's not hard.
No. 20 seconds. Teehee 2. Grab all 69 coins. Well, I know where the Teehee comes from.
Pretty clean. Is it tied? I'm tied for world record. I'm sure everybody is. Okay. Speedrun.
Here we go. Showstopper. You held right at the start like the world record holder.
Oh, that was cheeky. All right. What do we got? Short and sweet. Puzzle solving. Solve thing.
20 second snow run. We're not going to go much longer. Don't worry. Get 120 coins.
What? Oh, I went over the... Oh, that sucks. Hold on. What are you talking about? Wait. I can't even
read. I'm not going to read that. But everyone in the chat that can read what you just wrote.
What are you talking about? It's fucking gross. I don't even know what you mean by that.
What's wrong with you guys? Why are you writing that? Oh, I like these. Okay. This is only 8%
completion though. Why? That seems pretty low. Have you done Bowser's big... I've not done that.
I've not done Bowser's big burrito. Bowser's big bean burrito?
All right. What is it? What is it? I'll do it after this. What's Bowser's burrito? Is it me?
That's me. No, it's not. It's another fucking guy with the frog hat on. All right. What is it?
8 vs 3. Okay. No one. 8 vs 3. W0. 7 vs. Bowser's big bean burrito. What the fuck is this?
I just wiped out the floor. I think there's going to be a P block for that. What? Oh. I don't
understand. What are you supposed to do about that ending? Let's be real here. What is that?
Wait, that goes... I thought maybe I could... What? I pressed the button twice.
Why did you want to play that? Oh, it's... Oh, did... Dunky made this? No, no. Okay. Okay. I played it.
Okay. All right. Do 1-1 with a twist. All right. I'll do that one too. And then we're going about
1-T-W. L-L-B. Uh, 1-S-F. All right. This is it. This is truly the last one.
This is called 1-W-1-1 slip and slide. Sliding is key for speed. Can you find all three bonus
super coins? This is not the right one. Well, I'll try this one anyway. This one's fun. Oh shit.
I wasn't supposed to even do this one. Do the real one? I will. But I'm already through 1-1-W.
I'm almost halfway there. Shit. Thought I had it. Oh, that's a shitty jump.
Is there a mushroom in any of these? The audio fucked up? Yeah, it sometimes happens that for a
while. I'm sorry. It's been off for a long time. So the audio is early. The game audio is early?
Hold on. What? That's weird. I already have it set to 100 milliseconds to offset it. I have to do
it again. That's weird. I don't know why it does that. Oh shit. That's bad. Okay. Well,
I found the dev thing. No, I didn't. All right. That's fine. Not enough momentum. How am I going
to fit in there? I need to- Oh, I have to try one more time. Damn it. I'm just gonna- I'm going to
lean back in my chair. That's not going to work. Crouch? I was trying to crouch. I couldn't do it.
I was trying. I promise I was trying. Hurry up. That's one way to do it. That's how you do it,
apparently. One way. I said the same thing twice, but different ways. I said another thing the same
way, but twice. All right. What is the actual one that you guys wanted to see? Do you stand or sit
when you wipe? Neither. I lurch down and push my ass down into the toilet and shake in the water.
And then fucking like after like a 10, 20 seconds just lift up and like wipe the rest of my like
cheeks and shit. Where is the one? I played a hundred courses. Cool. YXL? Is that the one?
I need to see it like at least a few times. All right. YXL. Hopefully this is the one.
I think it is. D4C. 1-1 but with a twist. Super Mario Brothers 1-1 with a tiny twist. Are you
ready for a brand new 1-1 experience? And like three people have beaten this level
in the fucking world. 0.02 percent. I get a better return on my bank savings account annually
than that. Just saying. No one's gonna be... What is it? Impossible? Yeah. It looks like it.
1-1 with a twist. Yeah, it's kind of a very obvious twist. You just threw up shit everywhere. You
just made it impossible. Well, it's obviously left, right. Okay. Hold on now. Just give me a
second. Okay. And then that's left. Run all the way to the right. I'm going to do this by timing
only. One. Yeah. You stay over here for another second. I think you have to... Maybe I think you
have to jump up onto that one. Onto that base. Yeah. You got to get up on that base and then
to the right. Hold on. Yeah. All right. Hold on. I'm making progress here very slowly.
I made progress. I went forward more than I did. Holy shit. I almost just fucking got real damn far.
All right. Now I'm doing it. I guess you have to jump. You got to get faster than that. And
you get a straight shot over there. I think you have to jump up on top of the... You know what
I mean? Yep. I got to go faster than that. I had it. I had progress. Come on. What's the time on
this one? Like 10 seconds? Progress. I got to go early. I had to get that fucking time. I was going
so fast. This is jump over it? I think you jump over it. Yeah. You have to jump all the way over
it. Otherwise you hit by that one. No. Caught on. There it was. There it was. No. That's it. I had
it right. You got to jump over it and then you got to keep running. I had it right. You got to go
clean over it and then run. That was it. But it's got to be a little bit hair later. Later than that
too. I was almost there. I just need to get... Look where everyone's dying. I have to get like
at least past this one part. I wonder if you jump up or if you have to just wait. I have a better
idea. Silent. Watch this. I have to make it all the way over there so we don't hear like this.
Ten more tries and then I'm done. Oh wait. They can hear me. Usually I can do that and you guys
do the game audio. We'll block it out. I can't get this first jump now. No. I can't. Maybe I should
go over? No. I have to have to do it like this. That was it. I almost went too fast.
No. Am I going too late? Maybe I'm going too late. I am going too late. I gotta jump over that.
All right. I gotta jump over that. I gotta go way earlier. Shit. I got caught on the stupid
fucking metal thing. Why would anybody sit here and beat this? Holy shit. Is that safe over here?
I got a coin. Nowhere is safe. I feel like that wasn't even there before.
It's safe! No it's not. Oh you have to. Okay so you have to wait, run, and then jump to the right.
No way. Is that actually what you're supposed to do? Because it's safe in the middle there for a
second. Yeah you gotta get right over there and jump up. All right. Yeah I don't care. Yeah I'm
done. I don't give a shit. Who cares? Damn it. I just want to get to the pipe. If I get to the pipe
I win. I just want to get to the pipe. That's all I care about. I don't care about anything else.
It's the pipe. Fuck. I thought I had time to write. Why don't we do this to ourselves? Should I jump
up? Hold on. Can I? If I go fast enough can I jump on top of that? I don't. Maybe I can. No I can't.
Maybe? No you can't. No. All right. Three more tries and then I'm going to press the off button
on the switch because I won't leave if I don't. One. Damn it. That was close. Oh man. You have
to go all the way to the right and you have to run back. That one didn't count. You have to
land over here. That's one. Counts. All right. That's two. So I've got to get over there and
stand there and then run left. How did you know I was pointing at the screen? Wait. How did you know
I was pointing? I was intensely pointing at the screen. All right. That's two. Here comes three.
Is it? No. Just let me get over to the right once. That's it. I'm done. I have to turn the
switch off. All right. That's as far as I'm going to go. Turn off the switch. Okay. I'm good. Let's
go. That's it. It's too addicting. They make it too addicting. You just have to sit there and
smash your head against a wall. That's it. Thanks everybody for watching. I will see you guys
tomorrow. I'm not sure what we're going to do yet. There are plenty of options. Figure it out before
we start. Same time. So let's go back. Let's do the bits and the subs and everything earlier.
And thanks for watching. Mario Maker is always a fun time. Mario Maker is a roller coaster of
emotions for me. I go up and down and up and down and up and down over the course of the whole night.
But it's always a blast. It is. So back earlier, we had... Let's see here. We had five dollars from
Kill Ganon. Thank you, Kill Ganon. I don't have much to give, but I made this level specifically
because I wanted you to play it. And nobody has beaten it yet. Please play it. I'm proud of it.
Did we do that one? I think we did this one. Does this code is remind... I think I've seen...
I thought this code earlier. I just like rage turned off my switch. Scamming Mario levels.
I don't think you played it. Well, here. Here, you guys take this one and let me know how it is.
I'm just gonna type it because I can't... I apparently can't copy and paste it.
I feel like I did this one. He beat Bowser's big bean burrito. Yeah, I did. But sorry,
I didn't get to your level if I didn't. I wasn't doing donations for levels except for the one
time because the person put a fish in their comments. So I was kind of just pulling them
out of chat. So thank you for the five dollars. Really appreciate it. Thank you to Dork Cube for
the 250. How did you get the carnival stream off the ground this quick? But years of the blue
toothbrush already went over it, but thank you again for the 250. Appreciate it. Thank you to
Uncle Joe for the 250. Not able to catch the whole stream, but I made a remix for all the zoomers in
chat. Let me disconnect this. Oh, I just like punched my monitor. I just saw the crystal goo
shit for like flash. All right, it's fine. No, it's not. It's broken. I actually just broke the
monitor. I pulled out my headphones and my index finger just bumped it and it like broke the edge
here. Not enough to be noticeable, but enough where I'm going to look at it and go I'm an idiot
and I hate that. It's just a tiny little bit in the corner. It's fine. It may actually have even
been there before and I just noticed it now. Shit. Oh, that was definitely there before. Oh no,
I mean, I'm even stupider. That's part of the desktop background. Yeah, that's a star in the
sky on the desktop background, I think. I'll have to check that out later. But here is a remix. It's
a SoundCloud link. I need to be able to hear this though. Copy that link. Turn this down a little
That's pretty good. Here's the link for all you that want it.
Thank you for that, Uncle Joe. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
And then Zeke gave 250. Thank you, Zeke. This is probably the most wholesome video ever. Please
watch this with the stream. Oh, this is like that. Completely honest here. It's so bright out right
now because the sun is shining on the snow. There's laser beams shooting into my eyes.
You all right, Jeremy? Laser beams. Laser beams. I used to have to hang around with
chat for a long time and other people that weren't from the area. I lost a huge amount of my like
Boston accent. Laser beams. It used to be so much heavier. It still comes up from time to time. It
still does. I'm not going to watch this whole video. Say room. Room. I mean, yeah. If you have
like an English accent, you can't just like stop having it. Yeah. And okay. Yeah. Spider-Man is
really good at that. He can do that pretty well. But not all of us are like Academy Award winning
actors. Yes. There are two people that you know. They're Dr. Greghouse and Spider-Man are really,
really good at it. And the guy that played the big, the guy that played the dragon in Lord of the
Rings. Mr. Strange. Dr. Strange. Say popcorn. Popcorn. Popcorn. What's wrong with that?
I think you beat the 250. Thank you to Spamite for $3. Play my level or else I'll remove your
gamer privileges. I'm sorry I was not doing donations for levels. The one person gave $50
and put a fish in their comment and that's the only one I did. I kind of wanted this to be
throw them in here and we'll play them. But I do appreciate the level and hopefully I did get to
at least one of them because I did do a lot. I did probably at least like 20 or so. 20 or 30.
$50 for levels. Popcorn. Popcorn. Popcorn. Thank you for the $3 Spamite.
Editing your streams has given me 4% Boston accent. Max accent is probably now 20% Boston,
70% British, and 10% normal. What is normal? Hey Swyd. Thanks for the $5 Swyd Harry. Hey
Jerma. Are you going to be at Evo? I don't know. I don't know. It's going to be tough
because today is what Thursday? So Thursday, Friday, Saturday. I plan on streaming three
days in a row but I might I don't know because I'm not going to be here. I'm not going to be here
next week for at least a couple days. So it's going to be kind of it's going to be hard to go
to Evo. I might try to show up on Sunday just to kind of pop around. But if you weren't here earlier
the reason why I'm not going to be here early next week is I am going to the robot facility
to we're going to do a walkthrough. We're going to hammer down every single detail.
I've got to exchange some money and we're going to do some talking. We're going to go over everything.
I want to kind of just be like a name to a face rather than just because I want to know. I kind
of want to see what's going on. I see what they're doing. See the progress and stuff.
So I don't just want to be like hey let's do all that stuff and then hey I'll see you in September.
By the way September 21st is the day of that stream. Not likely to really be changed. I don't
think that's going to happen. It seems pretty unlikely because there's like three companies
involved. So it's not a case of like you know I feel like doing it on next Thursday.
So there was way too many people involved. So it's Saturday. It's going to be Saturday the 21st. I
believe it's Saturday. Is that a Saturday? I think it is. Yeah the 21st Saturday September.
What does the carnival stream mean? I'll give you a quick little rundown.
September 21st I am going to a robot warehouse facility to collaborate with a group of engineers.
Oh they already would have made them. That's what this next week is for.
To make a bunch of robots with another company. To then make them controllable by Twitch. To play
a bunch of carnival games. One of which the main attraction is to dunk me in a dunk tank with a
pitching machine. It's one of them. And yeah and they're all the robots are going to be controlled
by Twitch. Midway games, carnival games, there's going to be a bunch of them. There's going to be
at least a few different robots that you're going to be able to control as a collective group. Let's
hope you can do it. How did you find the people to do this for you? This has taken a year to figure
this out. I have wanted to do this stream since summertime before I moved to Vegas.
Is it going to be one game at a time? Yes. It's going to be a big carnival with a midway,
different all these booths. There might be other things there, other machines to mess around with.
Over the course of the day the stream is probably going to be, well it depends on how good you guys
can play. I mean we might have to, I don't know, if you guys can dunk me in like 10 seconds then
all right. We'll see how many times you guys can do it. In before it's a bit it is not. I can assure
you of that. These are real robots, really controlled by you guys, really happening on the
21st. It's not a bit. I can promise you that. I mean they might be jokes in that stream but that
is actually for real. That's not like a joke. You will be able to do that. Judging by chat's
pick cross ability, I don't think we're going to be very, you're not going to have to worry about
that. You're going to put any protective measures in there. We have a bunch of ways to,
the way that I was described to me, the way that we talked about it, is we can set it,
the different inputs, to have to have a certain amount of inputs for it to work.
So let's say for instance, let's say that it's going really crazy and there's like 20,000 inputs
and like 20,000 of them like to go left, right? We can make it so there has to be a certain amount
to make it even move an inch left. You know what I'm saying? We can kind of mitigate like huge,
huge just spam by making, let's say, oh turn left, needs like 3,000 inputs to go left an inch.
But right could be like two inputs. We might just have fun. We might fuck around with it.
The people that are working with me on this have done shit like this before, so they're very
knowledgeable on how all this will work. They seem to be very, very much in touch with what we want
to do. Do you get tickets? No, not yet. I've kind of fought with the idea of should I do a thing
where you like give bits and you can like play a game or something. I don't want to do that.
I feel like it's more fun when everyone's kind of fighting with each other.
It was also an idea of like have a separate segment that was, oh you have to, if you pay
money, you only are the one that gets to control the machine for like two or three throws or
something, right? But then it became, how much money is that? What's that gonna be? Is that a
dollar? Is that five dollars? Is that ten dollars? And what happens if like five fucking hundred
people do that? Are you gonna have five hundred people lined up? It's gonna take like 12 hours.
So I think it's more fun when everybody just kind of can try to control it. Because that
makes more sense as to the nature of this whole stream in the first place.
But besides that, there's another way maybe to like, oh if you, one of the things that I
thought was interesting, remember the, that like cash machine? Remember I told you guys I was like
really good at it. Maybe if like once every, once like a hundred bucks comes through, I would like
get in that thing and try to grab them. I don't know. There's a lot of different ideas that are
not connected to the robots. The robots are set in stone and we've got like two or three weeks
to figure out kind of the other stuff we want in there to supplement all the cool stuff to do with
the robots. It's not just going to be, here are a bunch of games you control with a robot. We're
gonna have little segments in between. There's gonna be maybe some actors that come through and
you know, clown around in massive gigantic fucking quotes. The whole stream will probably
be somewhere around like five to seven hours. It's gonna be a whole thing. It's gonna take that long
for you to even probably go through the games themselves. It's, this is not gonna be like a
30 minute stream. This is gonna be all day. It's gonna take probably four, five plus hours to go
through all this. What time is it gonna start? It's gonna be on eastern time, although I'm not
gonna be in Massachusetts like a lot of you might think. I will be on eastern time though.
September 21st, that's right. And besides the robot stuff, these are all just ideas that I'm
throwing out. Obviously none of this is set in stone besides the date and besides the robots
and the games that those robots are controlling. We got, remember I told you that
over the next, you know, I said this probably like two or three weeks ago, that I was going to dial
back streams to really make sure I get this rolling. I make sure I have the necessary time to
put into this and I can travel and go back and forth and make sure I can take care of this and
make it as good as I can. Like this is the reason why, because we still have to figure some of the
stuff out. But I will give more details when I have them, but I am going to hammer pretty much
every week here that the 21st is the date that you want to save if you want to be around. Should
be fun. And it's tough with stuff like this because even if I say this right now, tomorrow
a shitload of people are not even going to know that I said this. A week from now, a bunch of
people, it's not the same people every stream. So you're, there's always going to be somebody
that needs to kind of know. And I think I'm probably going to set up a command to have it
just be like, Carnival! Hey, September 21st! Because every day there's new people. So there'll
probably be a command. I'll probably play, I'll probably get like a little thing made,
like a 30 second promo video or something to play over the next like few weeks.
SusCarnival. Pin a tweet. Yeah, I'll pin a tweet too. That's a good idea. What is my pin tweet? Oh,
it's the t-shirts, right. But we'll move on. I just want to be clear about that because we did,
I talked about it a little bit at the beginning of the stream, but not to that level because we're
just kind of sitting here. But thank you to Appleshift for the 250. Hey man, I read somewhere
that your favorite band is the Gorillaz. It is. What's your favorite song of theirs? PS, my friend
Briar loves you, but since he lives in Australia, he can't usually watch your streams in full since
they're mostly while he is asleep. So I'm sending you good vibes on his behalf. Thank you for
everything. Yeah, time zones are really tricky. Some of us are just across the entire world
from each other. Australia, I think is like plus 16 hours from now from Pacific. It's like plus
14 or plus 16. It's something crazy. The whole day in the future. It's 5 PM right now, Australia.
Wow, it is almost midnight. It is 1159 PM Thursday. So you're telling me that it is 5 PM
Friday? Or is it 5 PM Saturday? No, 5 PM Friday. Damn, that's very, that's really insane.
3 PM. Jeez. And it's like 3 AM Eastern too. Time zones are fucking messed up. But my favorite song
from the Gorillaz is, I mean, I just like Stylo. Stylo just, I like the, I like the kick. Stylo.
If it wasn't Stylo, it would probably be, there's a lot. Probably, probably something from Plastic
Beach or Demon Days. Pick a random song out of either of those two albums. Everything else is
like number two. Melancholy Hill is good too. Yeah, it is. I liked a lot of the stuff in,
in Humans. That album was kind of hit or miss for me. But the ones that hit, I thought were really,
really good. Yeah, Stylo though, for sure. I don't know a lot of people that liked Humans.
Yeah, but that's what I mean though. Like half the tracks on Humans, I was kind of like,
oh, what the fuck is going on here? A lot of the tracks on Humans were just kind of like noise.
It was really experimental noise songs. And then the other half were like, oh, this is fucking,
this is awesome. This is exactly what I'm looking for. But thank you to Gnarly for the $2.50. They
just say donation. Thank you. Thank you for the donation. That was Gnarly. Daring Shepherd,
thanks for the $4. Have my paper trading goods. I will take them. Thank you. General Arse,
thanks for the $3. Play my level. I'm sorry I didn't do the levels from the donations.
Hopefully somebody played it, but I appreciate it. Thank you for the three bucks.
Vidis, thanks for the $10.80 is another level code. Beat it if you think you can.
I'm sorry I was not doing donation levels. I guess 10 bucks is a lot of money. Thank you for the
$10.80. People get scammed. Well, hold on though. I never said that I was taking donations for
levels. I never said that. I didn't say I was doing that. I said a precedent? No, I didn't.
I didn't take the second bribe level. There were two bribe levels and I didn't do the second one.
The Bala Koala gave $55 and said, hey, I heard you're taking bribes for levels and I didn't do it.
In fact, I didn't even say this donation on stream because I didn't see it. Sorry,
that's a lot of fucking money to miss during the stream. I must have been in the middle of
a meltdown, but that's $5500. I hate missing huge donations like this. I always feel like a dick,
but Bala Koala, if you're still here, that's a lot of money. Thank you so much.
If you make a robot that dabs when someone donates a $10 bill, that robot would never
stop the whole stream. I don't know. Money gets weird because I don't want to just...
Sure, okay. I could have a robot in the background that every time somebody donated $10,
the thing dabbed. I didn't even bring it up. It just was there, but I don't want to put
my financial obligations onto other people because I decided I was going to do this.
This stream is going to cost a lot of money, but you didn't tell me to do that. It wasn't like,
oh, jeez, Jerma. We voted. 20,000 of us voted and 19,990 of us want you to do a robot carnival
stream. Do it. Hey, I'm going to do this stream and it's going to cost this and this is what it's
going to be. Please pay for it now, everybody. You already did. I think that's something that
a lot of people might overlook is you already have. Where do you think I got the money to do
this stream? I didn't get it from my cryptocurrency investments. I'll tell you. He stole it.
He finally admits it. I'm just fucking kidding. Come on. He got it from gambling. Yeah, I put it
up. I put all my money on black and hit it once and freaked the fuck out and exhaled really hard
and said, holy shit, and I put it on my bank account. No, essentially to me, this stream was
made possible because there's a lot of people that donate and a lot of people that sub to this
channel, so the money that comes from that that goes into this is paid for. Now, am I a psycho
for doing this? Maybe. I don't know. It's very possible. Maybe one day we'll talk about
how much it was, but that's not a conversation for now. Enjoy it. Let's have fun and don't worry
about me. As part of your sub to shareholders, I demand the dabbing robot. And by the way,
that is like easy. If anyone wanted to like contribute or something, it could just be there,
but then I would want to make it something that it wasn't just me trying to delete money from like,
oh hey, watch the dabbing robot. It's 10 bucks. Better do it. We'll see. But let's keep going.
We're almost done. We had a Freudian weapon. Thanks for the 250. Thanks for playing my level
tonight. I knew you could do it, but I'm glad it wasn't too easy for you. Now to count down the
days till the carnival. Me too. I'm counting them down as well. Thank you. Acknowledge John for the
three bucks. Okay, I'm sorry for yelling at you when you were playing Mario, but mom said it was
my turn when you finished the level and I thought you were just playing bad on purpose.
Thank you Espadda Escalata for the 250. Jeremiah, I just want to say I enjoyed the bit where you
pretended to be a good gamer for once. Sometimes I turn it on. Sometimes. It's time for slime.
Thanks for the five dollars. Thanks for playing my level, Jeremiah Hart.
Do you know what I like? I'm just thinking about what I want, but it's not going to happen because
we've already solidified everything that was going to happen because we're getting too close.
I just thought one of those old Nickelodeon pie machines and just sitting like the...
If I say like a really bad joke and like it's not funny, then I got to go sit in like the pie pod.
You remember that fucking thing? Oh, the slime bucket. You know what? That might not be that
expensive. Having a slime bucket. Okay, I'm going to do like a secret slime action.
Hold on. Let me think about that. I'll get back to you. The ultimate minus two. Yeah, we'll see.
But thank you. Thank you to Devakitty for the 250. Jeremy, looking forward to the 21st. Me too.
In more recent news, however, I've been in the process of being approved for my HRT
for like 19 months now and hopefully the fifth is the very last of my appointments
and I'm stoked. Now if you'd excuse me, I'm going to go eat some of these 1.7 kilogram bag of
hot wings I bought for like seven dollars while enjoying my favorite bite... my favorite bite it
in Mario over and over again. And then did you call me Mario? Oh, in Mario. All right, I'm going
to do this math here. 1.7 kg is how much? What bag? How big is that bag? 1.7 kg is how many? Is it
how many in pounds? That's seven pounds. No, isn't one kilogram 2.2? So what, that's like three?
Three and a half? That's still a lot. That's a heavy bag. Seven dollars for two, three, four pounds
of wings? Enjoy them. I like want that now. I so badly want that right now. The time is it is too...
it's like late. It's like 12 o'clock. I shouldn't have jumped over the fucking stupid ass like fire
pole a thousand times. If I had just turned off the switch like 30 or 40 minutes before I did,
I would have been able to eat pizza. Great.
I'm now... I'm gonna... I'm gonna have to go like eat water. I'm gonna go microwave water and fucking
like flour. Stir it up. But thank you Devakitty. Appreciate the 250. Thank you to Manboy for the
250. Hey Jerm, I'm really excited for the carnival stream. I was going to attend my wife's and her
boyfriend's wedding on the 21st, but not anymore. Wait, wait what? It took me a second to figure that
out. Okay, sorry. Thank you Manboy for the 250. That's... well, I'm not sure you'd... thank you for
the 250. Thank you to Devakitty for the 250. Gee Willikers big stream coming up on the 21st. I was
going to attend the birthday of my firstborn on that day while also delivering my second child
and going to my grandma's 100th birthday, but there's a Jerma stream on so I won't go to any
of those really important events because I got to watch the silly streamer in the internet.
You guys can go to like your family get-togethers. Just pull up your phone and just... you pull up
your phone. No, don't do that. Don't do that. Don't pull up your phone. That's rude. Look, here's the
end-all be-all way to get out of any of this shit. No, no, not to get out of it, but you know what
I mean? Go, enjoy yourself, and then after like an hour or two, just say that like to hold your
stomach, walk up to somebody and be like, oh it's bad. I'm sorry, I've got to go now. And then like,
you know, bye, oh good to see you. And then leave and nobody cares. You're not the bad guy. In fact,
they start to think maybe they are, because why are you at my house consuming these things in my
house and now all of a sudden you have like a stomach diarrhea? Oh, I got to figure out how's
that happening. That's really bad advice. Yeah, because it was not real. Don't make it sudden,
though, or they might find out and get mad. No, yeah, I'm not saying do it immediately.
You're gonna drive up, pull into the driveway, be like, oh hey, how are you?
Oh, yeah, it's been what a great day it is. Oh, happy birthday. Oh, my stomach is really bothering
me. You know, we got to fucking get out of here. Can I use your bathroom? Or, you know, I'm just
gonna sit there in the middle. Okay, here we go. Oh, there's like 10 of us sitting around. Oh,
there's George and there's Aunt Edna. They're talking. Oh, Aunt Edna said, let me tell you
something about being Republican. And then George is like, oh, the Democrats, did you see? Oh,
my stomach and you stand up. Oh, my stomach's killing me. I'm gonna shit my... Actually,
it's a great way to get out of that. Take that advice. That's great advice. What perfect advice
that is. You can use that anywhere. You can even use that if you don't feel like getting like out
of bed. Hey, are you gonna like get out of bed? Oh, I wish I could, you know, get away from me,
my stomach, you know. Oh, you're gonna shit. Oh, okay. Oh, okay. Bye, bye, bye. Hey, the weeds are
getting kind of long outside. Oh, but you know, I would hate to shit on them. Yeah, you know,
you're right. I guess I'll do it. It's just, it's a fifth grader discovering how to lie to get out
of school. But the problem is, if you do that too often, then yeah. It's like going, going to the,
everybody, come on, everybody used to do this. You take a thermometer, right? So like mom comes
in, here's a thermometer. Oh, boy. Oh, I think you're sick today. Oh, yeah, I don't feel good
today. Well, here's the thermometer. Let's see if you got a fever. You put it in, mom leaves the
room. You go to the sink, the bathroom sink. You put on hot fucking water and you hold it under.
And you know, you're a dumb kid. You don't understand. So you sit there with burning
fucking hot water on it. And you end up at like 108 degrees on the thermometer. You put it back
in and you're like, Oh mom, something's wrong. Like, Oh, let me see, honey. Oh, you're dead.
You're not alive. You're actually not alive right now. Interesting. Oh, you know, you must be,
you can't go to school today. 107 degrees, 106 degree fever. Wow. I remember one time I put
orange juice in my mouth and went, my grandmother was there at the time. And I was like, Oh, here
we go. I'm going to be able to fool my grandmother. She's not going to be able to know that I got,
I'm just going to like put orange juice in my mouth. And like I lied on the ground,
face down. I could, I could put the orange juice in my mouth and like switched it around. So it
was real salivary. My grandmother was walking down the hall and I was waiting. Here she comes,
prone on the ground. She walked in and I was, I was putting my fist down, up and down.
Up and down. Like pretend I'm a child, pretend having a tantrum.
And just went and let it out. The orange juice. And she just looked at me. She's like, go to,
you're going to school. What are you doing? Like it did not even work at all. It was like,
she thought I was doing a joke. She was like, clean, clean that up. What are you doing?
Get it. You don't even have your clothes on. Get in the fucking car.
Clean that shit up. What is this? Oh, just kidding grandma. Kids do dumb things. But I mean,
that was, I think I was probably like at least I was old enough to know better. Let's put it that
I was like 12. You know, I was like, I was like 11 or 12. Like, come on, you're going to do like
the fake puke scenario. Actually, that's probably the perfect age for it. I also used to be scared
of the toilet. The toilet flushing sound scared me and I didn't like to go to the bathroom.
That has nothing to do with pretending to be sick. I don't know where that transition came from.
So I guess we're just kind of, I'm just letting it out, I guess. I guess we're just talking about
it. Anyways, let's keep going. Thank you to Kikira for the 250. They say, hey,
German, my boyfriend Bryce is turning 22 this week. Would you wish him a happy birthday? He
loves your content. Absolutely. Turn this off. Hey Bryce, heard you turning 22 this week.
That's a big number. You're getting there. Keep it up. Stay on track. Okay, that was,
hold on a minute. That was just like a, that was like a, that website where you pay a celebrity
to say something for 10 seconds. That was, I just did that. I just did like the celebrity,
was it called like Cameo? Fiverr? They knock out like 40 of those. No, no, no, no, no. We
ain't doing it like that. Hey Bryce, happy fucking birthday. Hope you have a good one.
22 this week. All right. No, now I'm like on it. Hold on. Get it off. Turn it off. Hey, hey,
uh, hey, Bryce, seriously, happy birthday. I'm glad you're part of this community. Hope you
have a great one. 22. Knock it out of the park. Thank you. Everybody here says hi. We all fucking,
you know, we all fucking love you over here. You're, everybody thinks you're fucking awesome.
All of us in the chat. Look at them. Do you see it? 22. That's a big one here. No, for real,
thank you so much for the 250 Kikira and a special happy birthday to Bryce. Keep, uh,
I'm not very good at this. Keep, keep, keep on. Yeah. All right. Now cut that up and like make it
sound like I'm like smart. That's not how you say his name. B-R-Y-C-E Bryce. That's not Bryce.
It's B-R-Y-C-E. That's correct. Yeah. Why is everybody yelling at me? Why is everybody
yelling at me? Or did I die on a 1% completion Mario level for the first time?
Wipe the sweat off the brow. Hey, you know, for those 1% completion levels,
there was like 4,000 people here. What is 1% of 4,000? 4. 40. So 40 of you get to say,
I did it and I could do it. 3,600 of the rest of you didn't do it. Happy birthday, Bryce.
22? Hell yeah. Jerma put sun chips in F tier thanks to the $10 and I would do it again.
Thank you, Jerma, for playing my level. It meant everything to me that you're able to enjoy it with
chat. Spamming minus two the whole time. You are honestly one of my favorite people in the world,
even if you have such shitty tastes. That was a very long birthday clip. Yeah.
Fucking comedy. But thank you for the $10. Jerma put sun chips in F tier.
I did. Abomination zero thanks to the $5. Please play this level. It's my birthday.
Hold on. Somebody's driving by really fast. Sorry, I didn't play that level. But happy birthday.
Is your name? What's your name? Abomination zero. Happy birthday. What are sun chips?
There's this weird like wavy, really grainy wheat kind of tasting, dusted with,
they're like crispy, but they're not. They're like cardboard crispy. They don't, after like you eat
three of them, you don't taste it anymore. Okay, I mean, I don't, I would eat them maybe. Okay,
let's put it this way. If a stewardess or, okay, like a flight attendant, right? Walk down the
aisle with a bag of sun chips and that's all that was left? Oh, where are the Cheez-Its? We don't
have any. Where are the pretzels? I'm sorry, we're out of those too. Where are the, what else you got
in there? What are those? Peanuts? No, we don't have those. Oh, you got sun chips. Okay, I guess
I'll have a pineapple juice. Wouldn't even need it on a plane. Hey, InvaderZ, thanks for the three
dollars. Hey, dude, my sister and I got two XL rats today and I wanted to name mine Jeremy,
but she wouldn't let me. Probably for the best. Anyway, I'm excited to be a rat dad. Love watching
your streams. Hey, can I name him Jeremy? No. All right. Music's muted. Oh, fuck. Congratulations
on the rats. They are intelligent. They're fun. They're cuddly. They're passionate. They're
empathetic. They're, they're very fast. They're very agile. Take it from somebody that has never
owned one but sees cute videos of them all the time. I'm informed. But thank you. Good luck.
That sounds awesome. Hey, Weskerun, thanks for the five dollars. Cheers, Jeremy, long time fan. First
time on stream. What up? They also subbed right before that too, so that's, that's a double.
Thank you. Thank you, Weskerun, and welcome to the stream. First time on the stream. Thank you,
Elizabeth, for the three, four, five, six, seven, eight, eight dollars. Thank you for the eight
dollars. Uh, oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, that is not, that is incorrect.
Elizabeth gave three dollars and then Errolus gave five dollars. It was Elizabeth and then Errolus.
So Elizabeth, thanks with three bucks. Am I ever going to go back to play more Dreams or did you
forget about that game? Uh, I actually just got, uh, sad because I wanted to use the move controllers
and I realized that I gave my PSVR away, which included the PS camera. So I have the move
controllers here and I was getting it set up and I go, ah, the camera's not here. I gave it away.
And then that, for some reason, was the wall, me not getting a new PS camera because I really wanted
to learn how to sculpt with the move controllers. But when does that game actually release? It was
in like creator access, right? A creator early access, early access. Is it just there still?
There was a really interesting game, but it was kind of complicated. It was not complicated in
a sense of creating things, but it takes a lot of time to be able to get anything done,
which I really don't have. I wish I had the time to dedicate like two or three weeks straight to
learning how to do that game very well, but I just don't. I just can't. It's a really cool game,
though. But thank you Errolus for the five dollars. Are my file names like filename01.file?
How do you format your file names? Well, I can tell you right now. Let's see. Let's just look
and go into like a folder and like some files that I recently named. Let's see what they say.
Oh, I gotta go through here. I do one of two things. I either just write the first word that
the thing is. Okay, so I have in this folder, I got the old emote. So this is just the title.
This is just old face, old face final. Old is also let's go into this one. Okay, let's see.
Setup. All right. A2. I don't know what any of these are. 08? No, these are like I don't even
have any like files anymore. I used to have so many more. What is this? What the fuck is this?
Oh, this is the the highlights. Let's read this. Tell me if you think this is funny.
I wrote down. Okay, so I remember the highlight stream thing that I wanted to do with the
highlights magazine. We got five to six pages of dot to dots. Five pages of Whales Where's Waldo.
Two to three hidden object pages. Two to three coloring pages. A joke section.
User submitted stories. Ads. What is ads here for? Two to three pages of ads. Was I making
a joke to myself later on that I would read later? That's weird. Gotta have ads apparently.
I don't know. I usually just write the first word. If it's a picture, I just say like, oh, it's a
let's say it's a picture of a dog like dog one. Oh, no, no, it's a this. It's a water slide slide.
I just and then they kind of use something to do slide and you write slide again and then it's
slide in parentheses two or slide parentheses one. But let's get the credits on here. Thanks for
watching guys. See you tomorrow. We will figure something out as we typically do. Here come all
of the subs. Thank you everybody. And there were a shitload of them. Resubs, community subs, gifted
subs, new subs, all of you. It's going by real fast. Yeah, good night everybody. We'll see you
tomorrow. There's still a couple bits left to do. We got future gamer thanks to 250. Did you hear
about the grasshopper pizza in retaliation to the Vegas invasion? Also, have you had any run ins
with the grasshoppers? They're everywhere. And for some weird reason, if you don't know, Las Vegas has
seen because we had such a wet spring. We had a lot of water here this past spring. So they were
able, I guess, to stop here or breed here or whatever the hell. I have no idea. But there's
millions everywhere. They're everywhere in every corner in every fucking place. Grasshoppers.
And for some weird reason, I don't know why they're like this. They're not scary. They don't bite.
They don't sting. They don't do anything bad. But they try to just fly into your face. I don't know
why. You'll open a door to leave somewhere and there'll be a couple that just jump right into
trying to get in your mouth. I don't know why they do that. You want to see something crazy?
You want to see some biblical crazy like conspiracy theory end of the world shit?
Go look up the picture of all the grasshoppers swarming the light at the Luxor.
Las Vegas has this big casino pyramid called the Luxor. It's a huge pyramid with a gigantic light
on top that beams into the stratosphere. You can see it from space. So already, like, wait,
why is there a pyramid with a giant light shooting at the sky? And now you've got grasshoppers
flying around it and inside of it. So you've got the pyramid light to the sky and the biblical,
I don't know what's going to happen. Biblical fucking grasshoppers, locusts in that pyramid.
Somebody's got it right here. Yeah. Look at that shit. That's nightmare fuel. Yeah, it is.
But it's been a lot but it's been okay. The last couple of days you see them still jumping around
but not like it was last week. But you know, whatever. I'll take grasshoppers. Yeah, you know,
I used to live in Massachusetts. I'll take plague biblical grasshoppers over one afternoon
around mosquitoes. Ever again. Just saying. But we have a couple more. We got an error list for
250 in all seriousness. Looking forward to September 21st and appreciate how much work
you put into all this. Hopefully it's worth it. I think it will be. Time will tell. It should be fun.
Wyrand thanks for the 250. Hey Jerma, I'm pretty involved in the community of the game called
Osu! and a little while ago a player mapped your song into the game and now it's a classic
in that scene and introduced a lot of people to you. Just thought it would be cool to tell
you if you haven't seen it. Is this the the rat song? I think we have seen this. Is this the rats?
We've yeah we've seen this one before. Yep. Wow, this is so cool. Yeah, I remember watching this
really late. I kind of want to play Osu! again. I've never played it. I don't know. I feel like
I would be kind of good at that game because if there's one thing that I know how to do well,
I have really good reaction speed. I do. I might not have very much of anything else,
but I know that I have really good like reaction times for stuff like that. Yeah, isn't it like a
Lycan game? Isn't Osu! essentially a Lycan rhythm game with your mouse? But here, I'll show it.
We'll skim through it. The rats song. Bring your own phone. Well, your own real phone
when you switch to Google Fi. Don't buy that. Don't buy that. Yeah, see it's like you got like
the mouse. I feel like I would be all right at this if I memorized it. I mean maybe not this good.
He's using a tablet. Holy shit. That's next level. Have they missed one time? Oh my god.
That's mesmerizing. Don't you feel like some of these people should go into surgery?
You know what I mean? Like that's like surgeon level of precision. If I was getting like an
operation and I got to pick one person that wasn't a doctor and had no medical background
to perform my surgery, I'd be like, can you get that Osu! guy down here?
There have been studies that non-gamer surgeons are much better at Super Monkey Ball than
other non-gamers. What? Did I read that wrong? No, I didn't. Did I? They don't have precision.
They have memory. Yeah, okay. So just let's say I was getting like a gallstone removed.
Make a song that was just the gallstone surgery and just tell them to do it. Give them the song.
Have them memorize it and do it really well. And it's just called gallstones.
And then I'll lie down on my back and you could just put the fucking gas on my mouth and
I'll then just play the song and let him do it. Just put a scalpel in his hand this time.
I'm of the belief that you got to be a little insane to want to be a surgeon and like cut
inside people. Surgeons love Super Monkey Ball. Why Super Monkey Ball? I don't understand.
I kind of think it's about the money. Yeah, I mean a good surgeon can make...
Well, I mean a good surgeon definitely can't make as much as a Minecraft YouTuber. So
just wait till all these surgeons figure out they can just play Minecraft.
How is he not open the link? I don't click links. Links freak me out.
Doctors put scalpel down for video game controllers. This is... What is this video?
And so that brought me to do three years of research on video games and how they
impact laparoscopic surgery. And that's what brought us here today. That video games can
help you be more efficient and also suppress errors in surgery. I can't handle this right now.
I can't handle this. I can't. It's too late. It's been nine hours. I gotta go to bed.
I can't watch surgeons play Super Monkey Ball right now. To me that's like going over the edge.
Am I going to Evo? I am might... I might be there on Sunday. I might show up on Sunday and just
kind of walk around with locusts. But thank you. Final bit from Stuff from Thing. Thanks for five
dollars. They say, Jeremy, I made this a few days ago and I wanted you to see... I wanted you to see
it. Love what you do. Oh, I did see this. This the fireman gift. It's really cute with the stretchy
legs. If I see you there can I have an autograph? No, I'm gonna be there in disguise. I'm gonna
have like the glasses and the mustache and just like with like a... I'm just gonna sit like in the
back with like a fucking hat on and like a mustache and shit. Let's play a look. All right. You want
to see? Look for the guy with the mustache. That's what I just told you but now it's a beard. Where
is he? I know Jeremy's wearing like a fake mustache. And now I'm gonna be like in a Master Chief
costume. Good luck. He's gonna be in a Master Chief costume. Spread that around. And now I'm
gonna be like dressed as like a night elf from Warcraft. Good luck. Five foot Master Chief.
You don't know how tall Master... Yeah, I'm sorry. There's a biography for Master Chief and it tells
his height. He's six feet tall. Whatever. He's not that tall. Master Chief is six feet tall.
That's not that huge for your huge super Master Chief guy. But that's it. I'll see you tomorrow.
Kind of a long one tonight but you know I've been gone for a while. So I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Same time, same place. Take care guys. Have a good one.