I
Don't care. I care shut up. I don't care about any of I care
She's seven or could she be one cuz it's upside down. No, or is she leet or she is she is she leet?
One four four seven you're talking over the movie. Oh good. This movie sucks. What is this guy's problem?
What the fuck what
Do you even know when it was things exploding
gangster wars, I think
Yeah gangster. Oh my god. We're playing on normal gravity, too
No, no, do you say grab do you say normal gravity? That was the name of the difficulty. I
Have to save you but there's a god. There's like a million people shooting
All right, I'm coming. How do you revive?
Hey, you all right buddy, and they please stop doing
That wasn't funny that wasn't funny at all, but the first one was are you alive are you really checking his pulse?
Ground is shaking shit ground is shaking shit
ground shake dude, I don't know what's going on this game is like
Shit shit ground is shaking shit
Like I seriously think he was gonna make it down ground is shaking. Will you shut up with the ground is shaking joke stairs. I
Want to play with the ball?
Whoa?
See ya
What?
Are you shaking? Why are we down here and they up there because this is the inversion idiot. That doesn't make any sense
Why wouldn't it invert everybody cuz it's only that one spot shut up you idiot
No, that's that scientifically doesn't make oh shit. I just shot her in the face
This isn't a science. I turn around
Do you see this guy?
Help me. I'm in trouble
I'm
Shit, I'd help you with this ground shaking. I'm still alive. It's okay. Oh
Man
Can't take this shit man, fuck
When's the rebellion?
Right now. This is the rebellion. This is the rebellion
We have to go against the big fat job of the hot guy. This is where they make us work
Where did these people come from? No, please tell me we can fight back. Like where does this whole like city exist?
I'm not going you can't make me move
No, you can't fuck you. I ain't working under the man
You can't make me work, bro
I
Am dead by the way, I'm dying. Kiss me. Ah, you're in the way
This guy's gotta be a fucking idiot if he can't see oh I'm showing I'm showing
So like our feet are going like sloshing
Wow, dude, you cannot be spotted you can't be seen here
You're right. The hand-holding is ridiculous. You cannot be fucking seen no matter what we do. Oh
my word, oh
My word who's coming this way. I don't think it even matters. I don't know. No, he's coming this way
Yeah, watch what happens doesn't even matter. Oh, yeah, it does
Yeah, let's see if you can do this without falling four times no holding the button didn't matter no, it doesn't matter at all
Really doesn't matter at all. It just does not matter. Oh, yeah, it does because we're hitting the wrong buttons
This is really uh, this is the tension
Your body went limp
Do you really have to ask why with this game?
Why would you ever do dead weight off of that even if you fall you'd land on your feet and run
Watch this guy fall off the roof intentionally. I don't please they all fall off the roof
What a dick
I
Like what a dick