Hey, what is going on everybody? Dermot here with Alien Isolation.
This is a brand new Steam game that came out a couple days ago.
And it's a horror game survival where you survive the alien.
Yes, it is. I'm Ripley's, uh, Ripley's, believe it or not, daughter, believe it or not.
So I guess you need to explore in this game. There was a crash, oh no.
I need to investigate the mystery of the crash, which is what I plan on doing.
Let's go ahead and go. Oh, fuck. That's him.
Can I get away without him seeing? That's the main thing that's got to be...
No, no, he's right behind me. He's right behind me. Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
If I can make it up these stairs, please. It's an alien. It's a fucking alien.
Hey, where is he? Where'd he go? The doors are all locked.
I'm trapped in this spooky game. What do I do?
Oh, I guess I could climb in here. Turn my flashlight on.
An achievement. Nice. You know, I love getting achievements, especially when...
There he is. There he is again. He's in the vent. He's in the vent. He's in the vent.
Get out of the vent. Out of the vent. Down the stairs. Through the metal detectors.
Hopefully I don't have any weapons. Okay, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Straight down, straight down, straight down the stairs.
Come on, come on, come on, come on. I know you can hide.
Hide in here. Open it. Okay.
I don't want to... If I make any noise, I'm going to be in a lot of trouble.
God, there he is. Oh, please don't come in here and kill me.
What the fuck is he doing? He's eating chicken. That's psycho.
He's eating chicken for... He's eating chicken for God's sake.
Time to go. Time to go. Get out, get out, get out, get out.
I'm going to go this way, up to the right. I think I'm in the clear.
Pretty sure I'm in the clear right now. I don't know though.
He's got a food item. He's got another food item. He's got ham now.
What does he got? Chicken, ham, drinks? What does he got? Everything?
I'm going to hide in this corner here. I've never seen the tutorial.
The tutorial said hide in a corner and he might not be able to see you.
So I'm going to take his advice in areas he's just conga-ing right now.
Which is a bad sign because they conga when they're very happy.
Aliens will do that. He must have just gotten a kill on a soldier in the top there.
I just don't want him to come this way. Thank God he's a brainless fuck.
And he went the other way. I don't know how he did not see me.
It's bright out here. But I need to be careful.
Because if he is going to pop at me again and hit me, I don't want that to happen.
No, no, no, no. Okay, okay. There he is. There he is. That was weird.
You know, hold on. He doesn't even know I'm here.
Can I just bash this guy's fucking head in?
I just beat the game. I just beat the game. I just beat Alien Isolation.