Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a gameplay commentary on Team Fortress 2.
This is gonna be a one-life gameplay with the Scout, using the default scatter gun,
the Criticola, and the Sandman. This is the first time I've ever equipped the Sandman in a commentary,
ever, and not just a commentary. I haven't put this thing on probably since it came out back
in like 2008 or 2009, whenever they released this thing. I haven't used it once since then.
This is also on CP Gravel Pit, and it's on Defense if you couldn't already tell.
Now here, let me tell you why I'm playing Scout. Scout on Gravel Pit on Defense is really,
really awesome, because if you can see in the bottom of the screen, they have to capture these
two points, and you can go back and forth between these two points very, very quickly. So if somebody
gets on A, you can run to A. If somebody gets on B, you can run over to B. The other classes don't
really have that luxury. If you're playing a Soldier or a Heavy or something like that,
or even a Pyro, even one of the normal speed classes, you can't go back and forth between A
and B that quickly. So a lot of times, what will happen is somebody will sit on one point, let's
say A, and if B is getting captured, they'll just let it get captured, because they don't want to
leave their position at A and have them cap A as well. This happens in 95% of every single
Gravel Pit gameplay I've ever been on. And the way to combat it is you need a couple of good
Scouts. If you have two, maybe three Scouts on defense on Gravel Pit, and they're doing this
running back and forth between the two points, and they're good, it's going to be really, really
difficult for the blue team to cap any of the points. Especially because you have these structured,
big, heavy bomb classes like the Heavy or the Demoman, and if they sit in their positions and
they defend where they're standing, and you got these two or three Scouts running back and forth
to try and protect both of them, you can really close off a lot of choke points, and you can really
control the game. Now this particular gameplay started with A being captured already, but the
tip still remains. If you want to try and prevent stuff like this from happening from your entire
team just stuffing onto B or stuffing onto A, you got to get a good Scout, you got to get a couple
of good Scouts, and probably even a few Engineers as well. All right, freeze it right here. Want to
talk about one quick little thing before we get back into this. This Heavy right here is guaranteed
If I keep moving forward, if I go after this Heavy, I am definitely, there's zero chance I'm going to
beat this guy. If this Heavy has any aim at all, I'm dead. Never run yourself into death. If you see
a Heavy and there's an obstacle you can get around, get around it as soon as possible, because guys,
people have such short memories when it comes to Scouts. If you don't kill a Scout, chances are
you're going to say in your head, somebody else will deal with them, and everybody does that,
and nobody ever deals with them. So use that to your advantage as many times as you can.
So tip wise, that's all I can really give you today, but let's talk about a couple of things
in the game right now, especially the end of this game. You'll see what I'm talking about in a minute
or so. It's ridiculous. For the time being though, let's talk about what's going on on the screen now.
Scout tries to get me with a ball, which ends up being his demise, because he doesn't have the
extra couple shots that I had on him. Jumping up here with the ball, nobody really pays attention
to me when I do this by the way, and I feel like it happens for a lot of people. I've been in this
situation before as well, when a Scout comes up here and just smokes you, and remember this guy's
name, remember that sniper. He's important in about 10 to 20 seconds, you'll see. Trying to get an
overheal from this Medic, but he totally ignores me, which really really stinks, because I probably
could have used it really bad right here. End up getting this Scout jumping up into the corner
again. This is the part I'm talking about now, everybody pay attention, this is ridiculous.
So I'm not sure if this was lag or what actually happened here, but watch. Insta-death. Let's do a
little bit of German investigative reporting here. So take a look at what he's doing. He's facing
completely and totally forward with his arrow cocked. Look it, he's not even looking at me,
and somehow he magically kills me by shooting forward, but shooting to the right at the Saint
I don't know. I really don't know, and watch the chat. Watch the chat, ready? He says hee hee,
almost like he knew that was gonna happen, or he planned it, and maybe it was just lag and he's
laughing about the lag. Not sure, but that's gonna be the end of the game guys. Thank you so much for
watching, I really do appreciate it, and if you liked this video, go ahead and shoot me a like,
and I'll see you guys all next time. Take care everybody.