Hey, what is going on, everybody? It's Jerma here with SCP Containment Breach, and this is another SCP game.
You saw the SCP-087 that I did a while back, well, a few days ago or so. It's the scary stuff we're dealing with, and a lot of people wanted me to play this game.
I got a lot of recommendations to play this one, and apparently this one is more fleshed out and has kind of like a story or something.
I haven't watched any videos, so I'm not going to ruin anything for myself. All I know is that this is scary. S-H-I-T with an apostrophe. I don't know why there's an apostrophe.
But, new game. I'm scared, as you can tell. I'm kind of nervous, and I'm freaking out. So name's going to be Burger Boy, because it always is. Burger Boy D.
Normal saving, enable intro sequence. That's fine, I guess. SCP... What the hell is that? Oh, there's actually dudes here with me.
What the hell? SCP-173. Uselet Object Class.
Why are we getting in here with this thing? Why would I want to walk towards that thing?
Oh my god, dude. Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god! Am I dead? Did I just die? What? You can die in this game!
Are you serious? Can I load that? Wow. Okay, let's go again.
So do I run? I must have to just turn around and run. God. Is my dog still in here? My dog is probably like... I didn't even know he was still in here.
So that's the scary freak show, dude. Alright, now I'm running, I'm running. I know what's going to happen, I'm running. Can you run? Yep.
No, no, no. Get me out of here. Bye. Goodbye. Get me out of here. How do I click? Open it. No, get me out of here. Get me out, get me out, get me out.
Why can't I open the door? What's making that noise? I made it. I made it out. He's chasing me! He's probably chasing me! He's probably chasing me. Open the door!
Open the door, open the door. Close it. Close the door, close the door, close the door. Oh my god!
Dude, what do you think about this boo boo? He's sleepy, he doesn't care. So you just have to run away from a monster, man.
No, I don't want to go that way. Um, where do I want to go? Which way do I want to go? Hit this button!
I don't know where I am! What's that black smoke? Boo!
What happened here? What happened here? I can't go back in? I can't go back in. He's going to be right there.
Just run! No, I didn't want to close the door! Open it!
Where? I think I made it. I think I finally got away. No, this is where I was before. Is there anything in here?
He's right here. If I turn around, he's going to be there.
Oh, thank god. Run. Just, I'm going to keep my looking.
I've got to go back in here. I think I must have got away from him. I had to a bit.
The time switch closes the door automatically. Okay.
Okay. So that means I can get in here. Get out of here. What's that? What's that? What's that?
Um, left or right? Left or right? Left or right? Left or right? Right. Open.
God. Oh my god! What the hell is that thing? What the hell is that thing?
Is he going to be still chasing? Is he still going to be there? Lights? I can't, I don't want to move.
My hands are off the mouse. What's going on? What is going on? What just happened?
What is happening? What the hell is happening right now? I'm like on like crack.
No freaking way, dude. No freaking way. I'm all about just running, man.
Smoke. It's always smoke. What was that? I see like the smoke. I see him right there. I see like the dude.
Oh my god. Wait. Whoa! Why, boo boo? He's here to protect me.
See you next time. Take care, everybody. Me and him are going to go eat a coconut ice cream.