Good afternoon. Sorry, I am a few minutes late. I had some car trouble that I had to take care
of and I just finished it all. So I'm ready to go. Yeah, it's just annoying stuff. Let's just
leave it at that. I drive my car every day. Sometimes you run into a problem. Well, I don't
drive every single day, right? But, you know, on most days I drive my car. I'm the vroomer.
Yeah, I do this thing where I attach like a loud noise to the back of my muffler.
And even when I'm going like 32 miles per hour, it goes. I thought it was cool. Anyways, I hope
you're having a good day. Hope you're having a good start to your week here. I have been compiling
some FMV full motion video games for the last, I don't know, probably a few weeks.
And we're going to do it for the next few days. We're going to start today with the animated stuff.
I've actually never played Dragon's Lair ever. This is one of the most iconic classic video
games ever made. I've never played it ever. I've only seen I think like 12 seconds of this game's
animation. There's a Dragon's Lair 2. I mean, why not? There are the Space Ace. And then there's
another game called Kingdom. And there's another one too. There's two Kingdoms. And most of these
are on Steam. I didn't even know these games are on Steam. They like remade these games. And I
didn't even know this. So depending on how long this takes, we're just going to go through the
animated stuff today. And then tomorrow, I'm going to try to get the other ones to work too.
You will know if I ran into a bunch of technical problems later tonight into tomorrow, because
we'll be playing Greedfall tomorrow if I can't figure it out. But which I don't want to do,
because why do I not want to do that? Because Greedfall looks really great on paper.
But apparently it's a very slow paced game. Lots of dialogue. And you know how my attention span
is about... I have the attention span about a cube worth of cheese. You know what I mean?
That's all I got. Because I go for it and whack. Anyways, let's get started. This is Dragon's Lair.
Oh, I just like... I laughed at my own shitty joke and it hurt me. It's got good music. Let's
get the music on here so you can hear it. I have joke thorns. Yeah, but wouldn't that mean that I
know? And hey, Dragon's Lair, presented by John Bluth. I think this game only takes
like 40 minutes to beat, but it's ridiculously difficult, is what I've heard. This is a
make a choice within a tenth of a second and lose. So the actual video game is about 30 minutes long,
but it might take like three hours to do this. I don't know. I'm just setting myself up for
for what I think might happen. Are you ready? Are we ready for the opening cut scene?
Derma's not good at games either. I've never heard... I've heard of this game.
I've seen the mouth animations and I was like, holy shit, those are pretty good mouth animations.
You ready? Three. All right, start over. One. Go. Oh god. Lives. Three. Five. I can't do more than
five. Play the original scene order from the arcade cabinet. Dirk will start in a new scene
if he dies. Yeah, that's... how do I do that one? What is move beeps? Move guide? Arcade cabinet.
On or off? Probably off. Mode arcade. Difficulty. They're gonna keep it on hard. This mode features
more moves and requires quicker reactions for certain scenes. Good luck. Turn it all off. What
do you mean? No, I don't even know what the fuck I'm doing. I don't even know what the
fuck I'm doing. I'm not turning off this shit. I have no idea what's going on. All right,
I'm going for it. You ready? I'm not turning the move guide off. To play Dragon's Lair,
you'll need to make the correct move at the right time. In this scene, Dirk will fall through the
drawbridge. It's time to make a move. To survive... I couldn't even read that.
I'm dead. To play Dragon's Lair, you need to make the correct move at the right time. I'm
not gonna be able to beat this. In this scene, Dirk will fall through the drawbridge and you
have to swing the... Okay, so there's sword. Can I... Do I have to press it with my mouse?
Touch the sword button. Okay, yeah.
Come on out. You made the correct move. I did. Can I... I can't do like up, down, left, right?
I'm gonna misclick so many fucking times. Throughout the game, you'll need to make up,
down, left, right, and sword. What the fuck? Slow down. All right.
Why is it starting from the beginning? Okay. Jump. Okay, got that one. That one. And this one.
What happened? Wait, what is going on? What the fuck? I have no idea what's going on.
Why have I started, like, random places? Why did I start at a random place?
I have no idea what just happened.
Am I in arcade mode? Why did I... Why did I fly through the house?
That was fucking ridiculous. I just angry burst into the castle wall. Okay, hold on a minute.
New game. Three lives, move beams, move guide, arcade cabinet, arcade.
Dirk will start in a new scene if he dies. Okay. There we are.
Now this makes fucking sense. Here we go. We're doing the laser gist version. I'm ready.
Turn the volume down. Is it long? Okay, this part, it's the squid.
Okay. Then I go in the door. Here's the... This door. I made it, right? What?
I thought I didn't press the button. Guys, I think I might have to put this on easy.
Sometimes you have to press it twice. Okay.
So then it gets us into this room. The rocket ball. Gotta go to the right.
Okay. Got it. And now there's a bed. It's too fast. It's happening too fast.
I just keep killing them. Oh, here we go. Quickly through the door.
Okay, so you have to dive through. Drink me.
What am I doing? I can't. Don't drink. I can't take it. I can't. Let's try it again.
We're in the drink me room. Don't drink. Wait. Go this way. Watch out.
I gotta wait. Slash. No, I gotta run. Slash. Up. Slash. Right. Slash. Got it. Straight. Straight.
Straight. That sucks. Straight. Straight. And...
Over. And...
This is like trying to remember a dream. You know when you have a fucking nightmare
and during the nightmare it's completely vivid. Everything is happening in real time.
Right when you wake up from the nightmare, this is what it's like remembering the dream.
It's like, what? Then I got hit in the head with a fucking rake. And then it was lava.
And then I got killed and I fell down the stairs and... Wait, I forget. I kind of don't remember.
Get the gold. How many times do I have to go around in a circle?
All right. Right. Right. And straight. Right. Right. Straight. Grab.
I get it, I think. Okay. Door. Open door. Kill it. Kill it quick. Oh my god. This is too intense.
I gotta go up. This is super fast paced. It really is. It's like a thousand miles per hour.
All right. It's slash and then up. Go. Grab an axe. And then right. Grab the axe. Right. Straight. Down. Right.
Okay. Slash. Right. Down. Right. Left. Up. I did it. Okay. Holy shit.
Just go up the stairs.
Go this way. Quick. Thank god there are continues. Otherwise, I would never complete this.
Turn off the continues. You really want me to do that shit? Are you sure about that?
Up. No continues on easy. Right. And then up. Up.
It's too much. It's ADHD. It's like super ADHD.
I don't even remember the last thing I saw. It was a spider.
Why wouldn't the spider kill me?
Use the arrow keys and space bar. Does that, does that work? Holy shit it does. Wow. Thank you.
Right. Up. And then left. Slash.
Where do I go? I'm trying. Boss fight.
Boss fight. Go. Right. Left. Up. Right. Left. Up.
Up. Left. Right. Up. Right. One hit.
The two second deaths are the funniest.
Oh shit. It's up. Down.
Which one do I go to? Which one do I go to? This is the beginning of the game.
It's the Homer Simpson. Okay. What if I continue? I don't want to continue from here.
Oh god damn it. All right. Well I should remember all this. No I don't.
I don't even feel like I'm screaming. I feel like I'm on drugs.
I make these noises during streams. That's why it's freaking me out.
I made that noise at the beginning of the stream. That was the first noise I made.
Yee boulders. I don't have a thing. Yee rapids.
Okay. Left. Right. Left. When the shower is too hot.
Now what? Back up here. Okay. Go. Come on. Where the fuck am I?
What? This is just the Sonic the Hedgehog room. From Sonic 3D Blast. Yeah, I played it.
What? I thought I was going to get in the face by one of those things.
Why did I just get scooped up by like an octopus? Hold on. This guy sucks.
This guy sucks. He's the worst. What is this guy's name? Dick Dastardly Richard.
All right. Straight. Straight. No. It's sword. Sword probably. Sword. Sword. It's sword. Sword.
Now what? Did I just get an enchantment?
I just got Dark Souls. That happens all the time.
You opened up a chest. I got a new weapon. Okay. Here we go. Got it. How many rooms are there?
Don't drink it.
Got it. Made it to the puke room.
This game is fucking wonderful. What a wonderful game.
Imagine doing this all in... Yeah. I can't imagine doing this all in one sitting with one quarter.
Without the guide? You know what? I'm turning the guide off. No. Wait, wait, wait. I'm turning
the guide off. I think it's time. I understand the game now. I'm going for it. Move guide off.
Move beeps. I'm going to keep move beeps on. We're going to put it on easy.
Easy. Move guide off. I'm going for it. What does arcade cabinet mean? Hey, I'm going to do five
lives. No. This infinity continues. Five lives? It's just a border. Okay. I think that's fine.
I'm ready. Let's go. I'm doing it. Let's do it. I get it. I understand how the game works.
Oh, fuck. That doesn't tell me when I do them either. Okay. Let me go straight.
Right. Now we go right. Right twice. Okay. We're going to go left. Left. Got it. What?
Uh oh. So what happened? What's going on here? What? It's not left. Go. Go. Okay. Got it. Get the
fucking mouse off the screen. Don't drink that. It's all right. Let's go. Let's do it. Continue.
I got infinite continues. I got infinite money. I brought right to my right is a sack of quarters.
There's like 60 bucks in the quarters over here. Forward. Forward. No, it's forward slash.
Let's forward. Forward again. Shit. No, it's slash. Forward slash. Forward slash.
Slash. Got it.
Just through the door. Hey, mister, can you get off me? My friends want to play. How old are you
anyway? 34. Hey, I have every right to be here just like you do. Forward. What? Slash. Left. Yep.
It's left. Flash. Forward. Good. Okay. Now we're going to go
again. Forward. All right. Sonic the Hedgehog room. I remember this. Down. Down again.
What? That was bullshit. All right. Wait. Now go. What the fuck?
What? It might be left or right then.
What? It's not left. It's not down. It's not right. Which one is it? Is it jump?
I'm doing too early. Well, he gets killed in the animation.
I mean, the timing is here. Now. Now. See? What the fuck?
Three. Four. I, it's not down. I think it's left.
It's left. All right. I need, I gotta make something real clear. The ding,
guys, is when I'm pressing the button at the right time. You understand? Do you understand?
Okay. Good. Left. What? No, come on. What the fuck? No. I had it. It's not, it's not the ding.
Hey, it's not the ding. God. Okay. I'm going to lose it forever.
Just do the ding. Dude, you have to press it when it dings.
I'm the one creating the dings. I did it. I didn't do anything. Slash right. Now it's left.
It's right when the scene transitions. And then down. Shit. It's up. Down and up. Slashing.
Um, wait. Now. Slash again. And then right, left. And then.
Do I lose points for fucking it up? And up. And then we have to wait. I do the thing and then here
it comes. I don't remember this one. It's the sludge. This two of these games, by the way,
if you didn't know. It's probably left. Left. Up. And then. Right. No. Okay. I have to kill that
thing. It's immediately the right. Yeah. This wasn't the arcade. I miss this kind of shit. I
really do. No. No. So it's up slash down. I think it's probably done. This stuff,
this is just so goofy. This shit's so stupid. I love it.
Oh shit. And then right. But was it 50 cents? Was it a quarter? How many lives did you get?
Well, somebody will count how many times I've died and we can count by 50 cents.
Shit. I have to move. I miss being cheated out of my money. No. Yeah. Damn. And then.
Why does he stop pursuing me? Got it. It's forward into the pool, right? From what I remember.
It's left. What? It is left. Oh, it's because this is different. It's mirrored. It was on
the right side last time. Okay. So you don't jump. Is it not a jump over? I've tried jumping over
twice. There's such a long line of kids behind you. Excuse me, manager. There's a guy over at
the dragon's lair machine and he smells. Out. Forward. I had it. Shit. And left. And then
forward. Yup. Forward. I just watched it happen.
And then it's forward again. Slash. Forward. A boss fight. Oh, this is going to be hell.
This is going to be absolute hell without the guy. I think it's up.
No, it's left.
Oh, okay. You gotta wait. It's left and then right.
Sir, the arcade's closing for the day. Can you please leave?
I'll give him a handshake. And there's a hundred dollar bill in my hand.
I got to wait for the night. It's got to leave one of these lights on.
Left, right, it is up, I think. Left, right, up, down.
Left, right, up, down. Shit. Okay, it's left, right, left, right, up, left, left, right, up.
Right. Right, up, right.
And then left, left, and then down, up. It's too much.
Oh my god. I can't. All right, I got it. I got it. I'll be good.
Left, right, up.
Oh, it's up.
I just pressed right. You got this little window to do it. God damn it.
Oh my god, you can't spam it. Somebody said spam the directions. You can't.
Kill him. I'm good.
It's right. I think it's back.
Oh, that's not left. How is it not left? You have to jump over, right?
Too early? I can't just jump in there?
Okay, it's down. I thought I tried down.
What the fuck? I, okay, I remember this part. Go forward. I remember this room. Oh, this is bad.
Shit, I had it too. Oh well.
You gotta watch the fire comes up. Did I do it? I did it. All right, new content.
Oh, you asshole. It's right. How am I up here? Wait, how did I get back to this room?
Is it the elevator? It just goes in a random order. Oh, okay.
Get out. Okay, then now we're down the elevator again. Forward.
I just tried to go up. It's up. I, I'm, ah.
Somebody count. I want to know how much money I've spent here.
I, oh no, not this shit. I have to, oh my god, this is gonna be hell. This is gonna be horrible.
Remember, this was like slash, run, run, run, slash. Left.
So it's mirrored from last time. So it's left. It's, I think it's left over and over again.
Left again. Huh? What?
God, I didn't even have a chance to see where the sword was going. Right again. And then left.
Right again. Right. Okay, then it's right again. And then it's right. Left. Right. Right.
Right. Grab. Swing. Holy shit. There was a left and a right in there, guys, and I fucking
guessed wildly and I got it. That was not just space. That was left and. I have to do this shit
again. Just on the other, it's a mirror against the screen. Does the game end? I don't know if
the game ever ends. And then it's right. I don't know how to use the elevator.
I, where am I supposed to be going in the elevator? Is it, is it not left or right?
It should be right. Isn't it just mirrored? Maybe it's forward. I've tried up, left and right on the
envelope. What the fuck? It'll punish you for doing things too early. That's the only frames I have
there. Watch, ready? Maybe wait till it gets up. Oh, all right. And then, oh yeah, okay, the statue.
Now what? These guys died so many times. It's, okay, it's slash and then right up the stairs.
Right now? What? No, it's up to the axe.
Shit. Okay, it's up and then right. I thought it was up and then slash.
And then in. Oh shit, no, it's down. You have to go all the way around and then up the stairs.
And then over. Go, hurry up, go. What are you doing? Press this. So on the stairs,
why do I have to jump to the left? Because it's not slash. I don't remember. And then up and then
go left. Yep, and then up and then up. Okay, good. Oh shit, I have to fight. All right,
I gotta fight him. Slash and I think it's run. Got it, go. Up, again, okay. Now,
I think it's another elevator. See? Up. Okay, so it's two ups. Three ups.
We should go right. Landing yet. He wasn't even done landing. Dude, so it's a double tap. You're
gonna go up, up. And then again, it's bats. Slash or maybe duck, I wonder. And it's probably slash.
The bats coming. Yep, slash, right, right again. Go. Bats, right, slash, left. It's probably
slash. It's slash. And then it's left. And then we go. What is that? What's? Oh, god damn it.
So that's also a slash. Or it might be a, you might have to run back up the stairs.
Jump, slash, left. Got it. Oh boy, here we go. I have no idea what happened. I'm gonna say jump
or slash. Probably forward, right? Or right? I don't know when to do this. So it's definitely
slash when I turn around. So that doesn't work. So try the swing. Maybe try swinging twice before
it falls? We'll probably jump. Oh, come on. That window is so tiny.
I probably have to run down or right after the sword.
No, it's not down.
Too early. They, when it goes, that's your, that's where they kill you.
So, swing twice? Because you get surrounded. How the fuck do I get away from that?
Jump. What the fuck? Forward, I, it's up. It's up. I have to go. So when they get in front of you,
you go up and then up again? Or do I go down? I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
When they get in front of you, you go up and then up again? Or left? Oh god, this is gonna be fucking
horrible. The new cuphead looks hard. Maybe it's left. Yeah, it looks left.
Damn it. Did I beat cuphead? Yeah, I did. I beat that like the first day it came out.
Damn. Where do I go? I just want to, I want to screenshot that area.
Is it, I, I tried right. I tried left. Maybe I should try down.
Down doesn't do anything. It looks like left is the waterfall, but then I go in the waterfall and
it kills me. So I'm not, I need to know where to go and the right exact moment to press the button.
Nope. Too bad I don't have a sword. The sword doesn't work.
All right, up. Okay. It's up again. It's right. It's left. Holy shit. Okay, my god. It's up,
it's right, and then it's left. But you have to do it at the exact moment. No.
Is it up again? I think it might be up again. It's not left. Oh my god, this place sucks.
It's up and I, why is that?
Oh, come on. I swung.
I'm probably so close to the end. I have to beat it. I just pressed it. I just pressed it.
Oh my god. Do I have to wait another like tenth of a second before I can press it?
Oh my, no, that's it. I didn't press anything. He just died. I gotta go earlier than that.
Yeah, it's earlier than that. And then up and then left. I don't fucking know.
No. I'm gonna wait. Maybe it's up again. No, but wouldn't up just go right into the lava?
I feel like that would just jump in the lava.
Got it. Come on. Again. It's again. Okay. No, I don't know what it would have meant.
Is it swing? It's definitely not swing because I can't kill them.
Up again. It's up again. I did it. Oh no, what am I doing in the elevator? What am I doing in
the elevator? So stop what? Stop like. What's the elevator tactic? Wait for two. Wait for one.
One, two. I'm just going with two. No, no, no, I don't want to. What the fuck?
What to do? Oh, this is new.
Okay, this is he boulders. Now you have to dodge the boulders. You gotta do it much quicker than
that. This is a long string too. Rapids. This is fucking bad. I'm gonna fucking start this
section over like 25 times, I think, man. Because that first one was up.
Up and then left. Left. Up. Left. Okay. Okay, whirlwinds. This is right. Just gotta avoid
the whirlwinds. Fuck, I must have screwed it up. All right, that's it. Oh, I forgot to grab the
chain. All right, I'm good. Now what? I think I have to duck or go to the right. No, right is
spikes. Left. You have to dodge right. It says right. It's left. Whatever the fuck it is.
You gotta do really early for that third one.
First try at that one. All right, save me. I'm going. Did I grab the diamond?
This is a new room. All right, slash twice. Yep. It's slash, slash it.
Shit, then it's up. How am I keeping up with what's happening? Well, the answer is no.
I know that wasn't a yes or no question, but it was. Kind of. Now what?
Hmm. Into the hole. Slash the hole. Watch out.
And get out. Nice. No, not this again. Twice and then right. Slash the spider. Get in. Okay.
Yep. It was up and I fucked it up.
Oh my god. I hate this room because I know what it is, but it's flipped. I memorized it from last
time. I did it. I pressed it. I pressed up. Fucking 30 rocks down. I did.
What?
Fuck you. I made it to throne room. Okay, right up. Sir, we just got a notification
that you just took out $100,000 to beat Dragon's Lair. Well, it's all right. I'm going to be able
to pay that back because this shit ain't going to take more than $75. Right. What was that?
Did you hear that noise? I beat it. It's the end. The dragon. Swing.
I think it's swing.
Am I doing that to the dragon? I'll do right instead.
No. I tried left. I tried up.
Maybe down. I'm trying to make, no, no, I don't want to swing. It's not up.
It's not left. It's not up. I'm going to try down. It's not down. It is left. What? I pressed left
so many times. What the fuck? Okay. Ready? Left. Left. What the? What? I did that like three times.
We killed us both. Left and then up. I don't know. He's back. He went back to sleep.
Did I break the glass?
Save me. The cage is locked with the key. The dragon keeps it around his neck.
This is freaking me out. To slay the dragon, use the magic sword.
Please tell me I can start from there. Oh, fuck me.
I think I have to, I don't know where to go.
Okay. It's so tall. Then watch out for the thing, the plates that fall.
And it's the over-animated, scary faces. The cage is locked with the key. The dragon keeps
it around his neck. I wonder if it's down. I think it's probably down. To slay the dragon,
use the magic sword. I'm going to try down because where do I go? Down. It's down. It's down.
Left. I don't know. Right. Down. I don't know. It's down again.
Oh, fuck.
Tell me about how to kill the dragon again.
This was video gaming at one point. Oh yeah. I know everybody loved it.
Please save me. The cage is locked with the key. The dragon keeps it around his neck.
To slay the dragon, use the magic sword.
It's down. Right here. And then it's left.
It's not. It's down again. Yep. And then. I don't know. It's probably up. It's either up or right.
Yeah, it's funny. Look, these things happen in a tenth of a second.
Look, you know how much money people used to spend on this shit? I used to go into
arcades back in the fucking early nineties and the screen would be broken. And I would
always go up to the machine and be like, I want to try that. Why is the, the, the monitor,
the screen is broken. It's because somebody like, I, okay, I got it. I'll get it this time.
It's down. Hey, you guys ready for that monologue again?
Please save me. The cage is locked with the key. The dragon keeps it around his neck.
To slay the dragon, use the magic sword.
I don't, I still don't have that memorized. It's down twice. And then it's right.
Now what? No, it was too fast. I tried to swing. I tried to swing too early. I just figured.
God, whatever. Dirk definitely Richard. He saved me. The cage is locked with the key.
The dragon keeps it around his neck. To slay the dragon, use the magic sword.
To slay the dragon, use the magic sword.
Okay.
Again.
I did, I did, he just dies. He just dies. There's no that. I didn't, he just dies.
She just dies. I have to go left or down or something. I have to grab it and jump backwards.
I, I think you grab the sword and hit down. I'm so close. It's down. It has to be.
Why am I looking? I'm literally reading chat right now. On a game you have a tenth of a second to press a button.
What the fuck am I thinking?
Please save me. Stop making me read the chat with your funny copy plaster.
He saved me. The cage is locked with the key. The dragon keeps it around his neck.
To slay the dragon, use the magic sword.
I think I'm gonna try down. I'm gonna grab sword and then press down.
Should I just not press anything? Maybe I just shouldn't press any buttons. I don't know.
If I don't press a button, does it just do it? I don't have to swing the sword. But do I? I have no idea.
Please save me. The cage is locked with the key. The dragon keeps it around his neck.
To slay the dragon, use the magic sword.
All right, I'll get it this time. I'm not gonna press anything.
Here we go. Don't touch anything. I'm dead.
That's all you guys saying. I was doing it too early. I didn't press any buttons at all.
So maybe I have to press it right when I touch it. Don't go for the sword. What?
I know I've pressed the sword button. You got like this. There's only one window where you
can press this button and it's like seven frames, six frames long. Maybe even less than that.
I fucking pressed it. This game is 60 in FPS. Yeah, so it's even smaller than what you think.
It's like two. It's one frame per. It's one or two frames.
I'm gonna try to grab. I'm gonna try to hit the sword right when I go up to grab the sword.
Let's see if that does it like right. The cage is locked with the key. The dragon keeps it around
his neck to slay the dragon. Use the magic sword. Did I press it? I'm gonna go for right when I grab
the sword right when I touch it. Space. I'm like going in space. Here we go. There's no that. No,
there is no inputs. There are no inputs. That's wrong. I'm not going for the sword. I'm not gonna
grab it. There are no inputs. You can't do an input there. No inputs. There's no inputs.
I'm not gonna touch the sword. But what the fuck do I do? He saved me. The cage is locked
with the key. The dragon keeps it around his neck to slay the dragon. Use the magic sword.
There isn't any room for me to grab the sword. Otherwise, the error sounds in play. Yeah,
that's what I mean. So it's something before you grab the sword. Maybe space bright or like the
different input or button press or another input or button press. I just said the same thing twice.
Holy shit. My brain just went backwards. I rewound. I'll fall a second. My brain.
Wow. The stream skipped. No, it was me.
So should I press space right before that transition to get the sword or should I hit
like a different right or down or left? I don't know. He saved me. The cage is locked
with the key. The dragon keeps it around his neck to slay the dragon. Use the magic sword.
All right, let's see what happens. I'm gonna try to do sword right before I go grab it.
There we go. Did it. I did it. Now what? I don't know. It's sword twice.
It's sword and then sword to block and then god if I know.
So it's sword right before you touch it. Sword again to block and then I have to move.
He saved me. The cage is locked with the key. The dragon keeps it around his neck.
It's up after. Somebody said left and somebody said up. I don't know what to believe.
I'm gonna try. I'm gonna try up.
Left Jeremy. You're all saying different shit. Okay. Left. Right.
I don't know. It's more. It's left and then I have no idea. Left and then up maybe.
I did left and then right and it's wrong. He saved me. The cage is locked with the key.
The dragon keeps it around his neck to slay the dragon. He spent all your allowance on this shit.
Magic sword. Yeah I'm happy I did. No guides by the way. I don't need guides.
Again. This is it. Left.
It's space. Oh I did it. What do I do? Grab it. Up. Don't touch anything. What? Did she
say? I said I would. That's it. That's the end of the game. I win. Watch the.
The next draw we're going to do has two characters in it and the two. I get to draw Dirk.
And the dragon singe. Now Dirk is a little tiny character and dragon is a big character. Okay.
So what I'm going to do to cheat this a little bit is I'll pull Dirk into the foreground so
that he stays kind of big and push the dragon to the background. And I think just to get this
thing to work I'm going to sketch out how I can do this. This dragon is sort of working with Dirk
like that and I can bring all the tail up around like this. I have to concentrate while I draw.
Sorry. So the dragon. What I just told you I think is really relevant here. What's the dragon doing?
Is he excited? Is he angry? Does he. Oh that's probably like a 40 minute video.
I don't want to. Why did I skip that? Because that's probably that's going to that's like a
28 minute video. I was watching that. Well let's go look go look up draw dick on oh draw Dirk on
YouTube. All right that's that one. We're just getting started. I got dragon's lair two. I've
also got space ace. I've also let's let's do let's get away from dragon's lair. Let's try this one.
Now this one is really old and has not been remastered.
So it looks like dog shit. So we're gonna try this one. I hope it opens. I don't this doesn't
even have a thing on steam I don't think. I don't know if I'm gonna beat this one. I really doubt
that I'm going to because it's so crunchy. It's kingdom the far reaches. This is a crunchy fucking
game. So let me get this right. It should. Okay hopefully this fucking opens. Oh god I can't even
fucking see. All right hold on hold on hold on. No that's my that's a command prompt. There it is.
There it is. Oh yeah it didn't even take me five seconds. I got it. I got it immediately.
It was ready to go. Let's do it. You can still see right? Everyone can see perfectly fine.
This is a crusty fucking game. Just need to be very aware of that. Virtual image productions
presents the far reaches. Kingdom the far reaches. Start apprentice start wizard.
I think this is difficulties. I don't know if I want to do start as a wizard.
Wizard. No I ain't doing that. The history. The he-man. The time of the arched kings is
past. You my old friend are the last of your races. This is fucking crunchy. Farewell.
All right so that's an evil wizard. There is one in time destroyed. What was that?
Oh shit man. He like burped out his true form for a second.
So the high race of the arched kings passed from the world destroyed by twisted.
The wisest and most powerful was our leader Morbus. This amulet is called the hand.
That's a huge fucking amulet. The most powerful magic could be focused.
Grandpa are you sure you didn't just spray paint a hubcap fucking gold.
Creating the five relics from the amulet. It's a piece of pineapple.
The last of the bloodline of the arched kings would come to challenge the might of torlok.
Morbus is gone but the one who will come remains. I am ready. Torlok is searching for
the relics and for you. His power grows while the old magic fades. Try me. I will find the
relics and rejoin them to make the hand of Morbus. I have tried 22 apprentices over the years and
they have all died but they were not of the race of the arched kings. That's that's that's
that means you're a bad teacher right? You've had 22 apprentices and they've all died.
I think that that's on you. That means you're not doing good enough like magicians teaching.
All right I'm gonna turn it up. Somebody said it's not loud enough. That should be good.
All right I'm gonna I'm not starting as a wizard. You guys serious? That's not gonna happen.
I'm doing apprentice. Have you already seen this? I just did that. It was me.
By the way this is a DVD game. You could I was actually gonna put this on a tv and play it.
Game on. What's wrong? Lathan a terrible thing has happened.
Drake's blood the wicked has imprisoned the rightful ruler and claimed the throne. You must find the
relics, the black mace, the hunting horn, and the orb of Morbus to defeat Drake's blood.
Hurry to my mansion. I am preparing scrolls to help you on your journey. The kingdoms are
counting on you. This reminds me of like that old bible animation. Last hope to find the relics of
Morbus and renew the magic that grows old as I do. But until you hold the relics be cautious
in your use of magic. I understand Daylon. I have finished new scrolls for you. Scrolls? I give you
three scrolls inscribed with spells of seeing. They bring sight to the blind and show those with
vision that which is hidden. Okay you got me a backpack with three magical scrolls. Now which
scrolls should I work on next? Which scrolls should you work on? Spell of understanding, spell of
release, spell of traveling. Spell of release? Now choose which of Glendale where once you lived
the haunted waterfalls or the eldritch forest. I mean the haunted waterfalls is absolutely
haunted waterfalls.
I have no idea what the fuck any of these people just said. I what did you say?
Uh scroll of seeing. Uh okay I don't. Lathan, tree folk forest,
tree lower pool. Okay let's go to lower pools.
Continue your quest and I will have your spells ready soon. I didn't think you'd be back this soon.
I haven't had time. I just put it in the oven. You're gonna come back in 15 minutes.
Um what the fuck do you want me to do now? What? Where the fuck am I?
Can I choose a different part of the map? Bogs on the moors. I can't see a thing not even my feet.
This guy sucks. What? Jesus. Welcome back Lathan. I have finished new scrolls for you.
Here are three scrolls inscribed with spells of release. This guy can't even walk correctly.
And accelerate that which should not be bound together. Okay. Now which scrolls should I work
on next? Which scrolls should you work on next? Okay so I have scroll of release. Didn't those
people in the water say release? Spell of traveling. Now choose where in the kingdom of
Wyver wish to go. Let's go do it. The village of Glendale where once you lived. The haunted
waterfalls or the eldritch forest. Haunted waterfalls. I have I got the spell of release.
Chocolate milk. Where's my spell? Release us? That's the one right there. How the fuck do I use it?
Press the help. That's not gonna help me. No go. Didn't they say release us?
Spell of release. So how do I just like can I like cast it?
Click it. Right click. Left click. It just closes it. Okay bye. Press three. No I don't want to.
Don't go to the lower pools. The tree folk forest. You are the wood elves? The people of the forest?
Yes and we know of your quest. Mobus was our friend and we offer you the help of the wood elf
staff. Well let me let me get it. Wait is this a trick? This is a trick isn't it?
Take the staff to the fairy circle in the forest and give it to the fairies.
Take it to the fairy circle in the forest. Forester's camp guild hall center of Glen
foresters. This is forester's camp right? That's the middle of the forest.
Go away. Strangers aren't welcome. I can't click the link. I can't alt tab out of the game otherwise it'll break.
Fairy circle.
Strength left. What? I've heard that kind of singing before. The fairies must be here.
Okay wait wait. Spell of the wood elf staff. Spell of release. Spell of seeing.
Wood elf staff.
Seeing first. I see them. What strange little fellows. Okay here's your staff.
You have returned that which can shield us from torlog. Therefore we now show you
the castle of crystal. Goodbye friend. Goodbye. Be sure to try our delicious cookies.
The one with the fudge in the middle is my favorite. Crystal castle. I can just go to it.
Spell of release. I'm holding them in my hands. I'm holding the spells in my hands.
What? No what? Crystal chivers.
So I'm not actually a wizard. Okay so that just keeps me alive. I can't go in the door.
Foresters camp. Wait zoom out. This game's not that big is it? I can't go anywhere else besides
like the one area that I am. Well then let me go to the tree. Let me go back to the foresters camp.
This guy just yells at me. What? You again? I told you to go away. Well what are you gonna do?
Okay center of glendo. Leave Wygaard Nathan. The guild lords are tools of the plague magician who
is Torlog's ally. Flee across the marsh wastes and into isles. Flee across the marsh wastes into
subtitles. Do you really think that a game that came out like 32 years ago is gonna have subtitles
in the options? A blind beggar. Spell of seeing. You healed me. When the town hears of your powers
the guild lords will have to give you safe passes to the haunted waterfall.
So the guild I got to go to the guild hall.
Go to the guild hall. This is an instant death screen. Ancient runes. I wonder how I can understand
them. Scroll of seeing. I need the scroll of understanding. So I can let me go back to the
magician then. Path. Skip. Skip. Skip it. Now which scrolls should I work on next?
I want you to work on scroll of understanding. I'll choose. It's too crusty. Is it too crusty?
The village of glendo. Just wait. Or once you lived the haunted waterfalls or the eldritch forest.
All right I need to go to the forest. Thank you. Give me the staff. I have the people of the
forest? Yes. Give me that. Take the staff. All right. Later. Your eye don't like you.
Very certain. There it is. Let's get the. I don't understand what this does.
This doesn't kill me. I just smell something and it makes me feel bad. I have no strength left.
Okay. Cool. Here's your staff.
Now I see them. What strange little fellows.
Your health is the tree branch at the top of the.
Okay. That's. That could be the worst health bar I've ever seen in my whole life.
You have returned that which. All right. Thank you. Okay. Bye. Quest complete. Now I've got the
crystal castle opened. Let's go with them. All right. You went into the kill this time.
You didn't kill me last time. Have returned. The new scrolls are complete. These scrolls of
understanding give you knowledge of ancient alphabets and unfamiliar tongues. Use them
when you encounter these barriers. Thanks. Now which scrolls should I work on next?
All right. So now I want to go to that rock. Spell of travel. I'll choose where in the kingdom
of why I wish to go. Where the hell was that? Village of Glendale. Once you lived the haunted
waterfalls. The scrolls of next game. Leave why God Nathan. The guild lords are tools of the
play magician. It's pretty good. All right. Let's go get the. There's the guilt. Wait, wait, wait.
Okay. Hold on. Out spirits of Glendale. The cure of the blind. The blindness. Go to the
guild hall. Blind beggar. You healed me when the town hears of your powers. The guild lords will
have to give you safe passes to the haunted waterfall. It is the law. Thank you.
Back up to center of Glendale and then to the guild hall.
Nathan, we're so proud of you. Everyone in Glendale has heard about how you healed the blind beggar.
Even the guild lords are impressed, Nathan. Why would that make you concerned? Oh dear,
that's not good. Guild hall. Healers belong at the waterfall. But I'm guard Stakeham. What?
Okay, does anybody have any idea what just happened? The guild hall has even heard about
your beautiful efforts and they really like you. Okay, go to guild hall. Yeah, don't let him in.
Get, seize him and send him to the pool of knowledge. I don't get it. Seize him.
That's usually something that happens when something bad happens to you afterwards.
Is this going to kill me?
All right, kids, I'm sorry. I got nothing for you. I got to go back down to where that scroll was.
No, I'm going to breathe in the fucking like fart gas. Can you tell me anything more?
Apprentice, the plague magician knows of your quest and he is waiting in the forest for you.
What are you talking about? I thought I, center of Glendale, I'm going down
and it's outskirts and then it's the scroll of understanding I can do down here. Friend,
can you help me? I, I have heard stories about relic hidden in the forest in the castle of
crystal. I've also heard that fairies guard the path. Now go Lathan, this place is not safe for you.
This what place? Why is everybody not, why does everybody hate me?
Barren rocks. There it is. Scroll of understanding. Ancient runes. I wonder how I can understand them.
Scroll of understanding. In the black keep are the runes of Iscar which hold the power of law in
that kingdom. That literally did not even help me at all. Okay, so might as well see who this is.
I'm going to be honest. Good, you have returned. If there's that much voltage going through that
crystal, that shit's going to be humming. With them, you can go anywhere. If there's 600,000
volts going through that thing, you're going to, you'll hear that from fucking 50 feet away.
You ain't going to touch that. Now, which scrolls should I work on next?
Why don't you work on the spell of release? I'll choose where it is.
Where once you lived, the haunted forest or the eldritch forest. The amps kill you, not the volts.
I'm sorry, I'm not an electrician. I have the spell of release, so why shouldn't I go to waterfall?
Release the spell of rest. You must use your magic to release us from our spell of traveling.
That's a skull. Black keep? Sea dwellers' pavilion? The high ground. Just go into the palace.
Just teleport. Wait, does teleport into the boss's room, the throne room behind him and like bash his
head with a rock? This is Drake's Blood's palace, you know, and his wizards won't like your coming
here. They get very jealous. How do you know I'm a wizard? Ha! House travels in these hard times.
What? What do you mean, who else trapped?
Hard core, yourself? I played for Grace Delight, the true ruler of Iscar, until Drake's Blood
imprisoned her in the North Tower and claimed the throne. He was corrupted by Torlok, as are many
here. Which door way? I'm gonna go up and through this door. Look at that posture pog.
I found him! I found him! You're another wizard looking for the relics. Well, you may find a way
to Alcatesh if you can make the tapestry of seeing in the south chamber reveal its secret.
Why are they letting me just walk around the castle? Where are the guards? We're just eating dinner.
That's a good air. It looks like it's been a while since good was done around here.
Oh, I bet you've come like the others to slay the king.
Rock! Um, so, this is mocking me because I'm here to kill the king.
Right, so why am I not, why am I allowed to just walk around? Okay, what about this doorway?
I can't do anything else here. Door, we'll go up here.
Oh, sure. Hello, um, I, uh, well, I... You're another wizard looking for the relics.
Well, you may find a way to Alcatesh if you can make the tapestry of seeing in the south...
Get out of here. Oh, hello, I, um, well, I, I, I, I don't know.
Look, the wizard's back. Who are the others you mentioned before?
Apprentices of daylight. They live in the palace now.
Oh no, I went into the time room. You just have this unguarded?
This is just an open doorway into like a fucking portal. Um, I don't know.
Hello? Wait, why am I here? Where's the wizard?
He's dead. I need more help. The rightful ruler of Iscar can help you, Lathan.
He died. That was his force ghost. Keep going. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Out.
Get on the high ground. Lathan, be cautious. Bandits who will steal everything you carry
roam the rocky desert. Leave me the fuck alone.
Shimmering oasis. Dunes people campsite. Temple of Syndra.
Shimmering oasis. That's going to be healing, I think.
Pool. What do you mean pool? There's no pool here.
There's no, there's no, there's no pool. That's not a pool. This is a mirage. That's sand.
A drink from the sand. That'll, I'm gonna die.
Who is, who is, Electra.
One more. This is the third attempt. Last try. This time, last try, this is it.
This time I'm going to start with the scroll of traveling because that's the best one.
Now choose where in the game. Let's go to, I just want to see.
A troublemaker if I ever saw one. But I'm. Dodge, take him.
I got instantly eaten by rats. And I will have your spells ready soon.
Oh, come on. Please. I just want the scroll. Let's go to the marsh wastes. What? Is this
an instant kill screen? The marsh wastes. What a dreary place. I can hardly see where to step.
Yeah, this is a, this is a, spell of seeing.
Wise. Wise? Wise.
Uh, nothing I can do on this screen. Okay, we're back at the shimmering oasis. Don't touch that.
Uh, how about the dunes people campsite? Do you know anything about magic about the relics?
Our legend says that the relics of Mobus can free the kingdoms from the shadow of evil.
But that is an ancient story. Okay, well, thanks. I guess.
Um, lost mines, mountain cliffs. That's a, well, that's a fall down and I scream. Let's go to the
lost mines. I advise you to seek out the Amazons of the oasis and they will help if you can prove
yourself worthy. Thank you. The different guy. Was that a different force of ghost? How many
force ghost Obi-Wans do I know? Holy shit, we made it.
There's an explosion sound too. I knew it. I.
Lathan, be cautious. Bandits who will steal everything you carry roam the rocky desert.
Desert oasis. Okay. Welcome. Since Torlok drove us from our home in the west, we have not trusted
your kind, but perhaps you are the one our legends speak of. Farewell. What do you mean farewell?
Perhaps you're the one that the legend speaks of. Bye. Get out of here.
Leave. All right. Well, we have to go into the temple then temple of syndrome.
Let's go. Stranger. Not all of us are under Torlok's influence. Look hard.
There is knowledge hidden here. All right. This doorway looks scary. This one looks safe.
You have to go to the one that looks scary, I think. For the blood sword of the Argent
Kings. Look in the black key. Black key for the sword.
Stranger. I feel like we missed a whole lot before that happened. To me, that seems like we should
have gotten at least to the middle point there where I was sacrificed to a giant demon.
Wizard mode. All right, with the wizard mode. Leave. Why God, Lathan, the guild lords are
tools of the plague magician who is Torlok's ally. Flee across the marsh wastes and into isles.
So I don't start with any spells. I can't, I don't have my crutch.
Ho fellow. Who are you? Gordon the Huntsman. I know much of these woods. For example, I know
that the crystal of Kaldar will enable you to overcome the crystal tigers. Come back sometime
and I'll share a story with you. Wait, does this mean that I'm already, I already am like a,
wizard mode is the same game? I'm going to go down to the barren rocks. If you don't complete
this game, I'm going to leave. I don't know what you want me to say. Last hope to find the relics
and why did I show up here? As I do, but until you hold the relics, be cautious in your use of magic.
I understand day long. So here's my question. The 22 wizards, I think it's just me over and over
inscribed with spells of seeing. They bring sight to the blind and show those with vision that
now, which is cool. I figured it out. All right. I want the scroll of traveling.
I'll choose where in the kingdom of why I wish to go. I want to go to the haunted waterfalls.
You must use your magic to release the spell of rest.
Right. Something in my eye. You are the world. Here's the forest. Yes. And we know what your
quest was our friend. And we all. What else? Yeah. Okay. Very circle. I don't want to do that again.
I've already done that. Just give me my scroll of teleportation, please. I go for the blind man.
It's the ball. You healed me. When the town hears of your powers,
the guild lords will have to give you safe passage to the haunted waterfalls.
It is the law. Safe passage to the waterfall. Okay. That brings us up here.
We're just going to go in order. We'll go back to the healing pools.
Thank you for not being electrified. Okay. I'm good to go. Now we're going to go from here
to the upper pools. And then, no, this is the stupid singing ghost thing.
This is like the legend of Zelda's CD-i.
All right. I want to go back to the, I just wasted a heal. Yeah, I did. Can you tell me anything
more? Apprentice, the plague magician knows of your quest. I know he does.
I need to go get my spell of travel. Go away. Strangers aren't welcome. Wasn't this the guy
that just told me come anytime and he'll tell me a story. My son was your age when he learned
that the cold fire which burns on the marsh waste can destroy the mist monsters. Thanks lady.
Hello again. Martin. I once held the second relic, the hunting horn for many a year after
Mobus was gone. Now Skylar, the keeper of the clouds holds it. That's all my story, lad. Good day.
Thanks for the story. That's the whole story. I'm going to go to the rocks.
No, fuck. No, it's all right. I want to go here. Kill me again, Marshmallow people. I want the
scroll of travel. Give me the scroll of travel. I want to go to the one place I haven't gone
and then I'm going to fucking delete this game from my inventory. Good. You have returned.
The new scrolls are complete. These scrolls contain traveling spells. This is a 20-hour game.
I'll choose. All right, it doesn't matter where I go. Let's just go to the waterfall and I'm
teleporting. There we go. I want to go to, so that's the palace. I want to go to the sea
dwellers pavilion. That's the only place I haven't gone in the whole world. Wait, I haven't gone to
Dalen's mansion. Dalen's mansion. Oh fuck, that's the magician's house. I have not completed your
scrolls yet, Lathan. Continue your quest and I will have your spells ready soon. Shit. Oh no,
god, come on. I thought it was a dude. I don't know the guy's name is Dalen. He never even
introduced himself. You may not travel in poor health. What? He says it every time you enter.
I don't have subtitles and this is all the voice acting I hear.
Oh, you are doing a very good job.
It's like talking through a sock. I want to see that ship.
Going back to the pool. Send me back to the pool.
I think he said healers belong at the waterfall.
Use them healers of all the ages. Travel far. Overlook no source of health.
There we go. Teleport to the ship. Let's go. Sea dwellers pavilion.
Shit. There is East Coast Sea. East. East Sea Coast. East West Sea Coast. Let's go West Sea Coast.
Scroll of, scroll of scene. He saw it all right. He just touched it. Yeah.
Dalen, I need more help. He didn't even die. He passed out. That doesn't count as a lie.
I fainted. Okay, this is East Coast Sea. Valley of the Argent Kings.
Okay. She has her trust right here. Only with the orb of moments can the coins be obtained.
What if I go real fast? All right, take the coins or check something else.
It's a fucking electric one. Everything has 50,000 amps going through it. 50,000 amps going through it.
Oh, and you explode. Oh, that was great. All right, so we're going to move on.
We're going to play Space Ace now. There's another one I've never played before.
I don't even know how the hell this one works. I'm going to take a quick
pee before we play this one. Oh, crap. Space Ace. Electrician and Chad actually
just said it's the volts, not the amps. I know. Okay, so give me a second.
I'll be right back. I'm going to pee. I'm going to grab a water and we'll continue.
Totally compact. Oh, crap. Oh, crap.
Get me out of here. Thank you, Kimmy. I'm just kidnapped by aliens, that's all.
Totally compact. All right, Space Ace.
Oh, crap. Far out. Let's start it. This is also Don Bluth. Oh, wait, wait, before I get in here.
Show the picture. Oh, god, that's ugly. Thank you, Kimmy. Oh, that's a great photo.
That's a good photo. Show the photo. Hold on. Let's go. Oh, shit, it is one of these.
It is one of these. It's another one of these. Okay, move guide. Move beeps on
arcade cabinet off five lives. Difficulty. I don't even know what these mean. Cadet.
You definitely want move guide. I'm doing cadet. How hard is this one compared to Dragon's Lair?
Well, what about captain? I'll try captain. I'll try it.
Cabinet is spelled wrong. I'm gonna give it a go. Let's go.
Why is the genie evil? That was the genie from Aladdin. Oh, no, it's not. It's just
it's right twice. Energize? Huh? Oh, god. Go. How the fuck did I do that?
I did it. I did it. How did I do that? Guys, I'm fucking locked in.
Up. No, it's okay. Is it down? Maybe it's down. Oh, dude, it's too much.
Huh? Put on the guide. I got through that pretty quickly without the guide.
Up. Left. Right. Energize. Is it the same actor that played
who's the antagonist from Dexter's lab? What the fuck is happening? It's up. It's up twice.
Then it's left and then left. All right. What the fuck is happening? I don't even... I gotta
turn on the guides. I think, man, this is like too ridiculous. I'm gonna try this one more time.
You get chatified. Energize. So don't move. What? What the fuck? I thought it was energized.
So that energizes... but am I not... I'm putting on the guide. I don't care.
I don't care. It's going on. It's going on. Get it on. It's going on. I can't even do it yet.
What am I supposed to do during the energize sequence though?
Doesn't he stand here? See, right? I have no idea. All right. No. Then. Right. And. Up. And. Hey.
Oh, I could care less about... I've put... There's too many in a row.
I'm putting the guide on. I'll do it on hard, but I'm putting... I ain't doing this one without
the guide. I'll tell you. I'll put it on ace. No fucking way. Don't worry. I'll still fuck it up.
Holy shit. New path. This didn't happen before. It's too fast, man. It's too quick. I don't even
have time to react to the scenes. Oh, this would have never been done without the guide. Oh, fuck.
Hard mode is so fast, it skips cutscenes and dials.
Does it? Should I put it back on what it was before? Yes, I should. Put it on cadet
so you can see all the... All right. We'll do cadet. We're just gonna... We're gonna enjoy the game.
Cadet is just... Cadet with move... Cadet no move guide. No... I don't know if I can do it.
I don't think I can do it. I can't do it. Sometimes you have to admit when you're capable of doing
something. It's still... It doesn't matter. I can still fuck it up and I still will over and over
again. This music is getting in my brain. It's the song. Let's go. What? I didn't get a guide.
I didn't get a guide for that one. Okay, remember this part? This part sucked.
Sherwin was demoralized.
It's too loud now. I have to turn it down. Hold on. I gotta turn it back down. It was way too loud.
That voice doesn't even match.
Here we go. Left. Shoot.
I hate this music so much. All right. Was it that? Okay, the...
Go. All right. I finally made it past this part.
I'll save you, Jimmy.
No way would I have done this shit without the guide.
This would have been a meltdown. An absolute total meltdown stream.
Turn back the music. Energize. Quick. Quick. Turn on your online profile.
Get on those forums. Oh, no, no, no, no. He got banned. Oh my god. It's left. Wait,
this guy's name is Dexter. There. Left. I know everyone was begging me to turn these on.
No, dude. You don't understand. Like, turn it on. Turn them on.
Oh. No, why would I do that? No, no, no, no. Please, man. Do it. Please.
We're looking out for you. Thank you. I appreciate that. You're looking out for me.
This is definitely a pants shit game. What? Look at this shit. There's too many things going on.
Turn back. Holy shit. It's just draining all of my energy.
I'm drained right now. I am. All of my fucking molecules.
I'm leaning back in my chair and I'm doing some more hard blinking.
That's Ursula. Wait, that's that. It's that person. Okay. Hold on. Give me a minute. I need to
actually blink. You know when somebody uploads an entire movie to YouTube and they do like the funny
joke words every time the person says the word cheese, it times two speeds itself. That's what
I feel like I'm watching. Okay. Let's try it again. I thought the cadet was supposed to slow this shit
down. Let's speed it up. Is there blood coming out of my nose? No, I'm all right.
It's space ace, but every time they say the word kidney, it times 10 speed.
He just ate like a bunch of Cheetos.
He didn't even eat me. Oh, come on. I did it.
I may have thrown up playing this game. I just...
I made it. Okay. I made it through that one. We're good.
What?
Somebody's screaming in my face.
It is actually painful. You're right. It's actually kind of painful to watch. I can't imagine how it
looks on your screen because it looks like this on my screen. I imagine what it looks like on yours.
I did it.
It's colors.
I'll get it. I'll get through it.
Oh, let's go. It's such a small window.
I need to hold on. I need to break. I need to take a break. I need to break. This actually is
like hurting my head. I need to fucking break. Hold on.
Oh, Frank.
All right. Just everybody relax for a minute. We need to take a second. Just everybody calm the
fuck down. Okay. Just take a second. We're going to just relax. Imagine doing this shit without
the guy. I want you all to just think about that. That's never going to happen. That would never
happen. I would fail the first sequence over a hundred times. No guide with ace difficulty.
That would be a really interesting run to watch. All right. I think I'm all right.
I've just taken a moment. I'm ready to continue. Here we go. Let's try it again.
All right. That's what we're looking for here. This is all one sequence. Remember that one.
You cannot win.
I missed it again. Oh my fucking god. I tried to hold it in. I couldn't.
Dexter, you're late. Call me ace. Huh? How funny. Thanks. I'll walk. Monster. Dexter,
the infant array is about to be fired at her. Where's the ray located? In the center of the
complex. Can you get us in there? Yes. This is fucking ridiculous. I feel like this is what
happens. I keep seeing that in my head and with my eyes open. That's not that's bad, right? I think
so. Dexter, you're late. Call me ace. Huh? How funny. Thanks. I'll walk. I'm seeing these images
after they happen. Dexter, the infant array is about to be fired at her. Where's the ray located?
In the center of the complex. Can you get us in there? Yes.
No, I'm here. Yes, he's geared for battle. What? Wait, didn't we just go that way with his own
inventory? No, I saw it again. No, I'm going to see it again in 10 seconds.
No, no, I don't want to see it again. I'm going to see it again. I don't want to see it.
Okay, I didn't get a prompt. Dexter, you're late. Call me ace. Huh? How funny. Thanks. I'll walk.
Dexter, the infant array is about to be fired at her.
Where's the ray located? In the center of the complex. Can you get us in there? Yes.
Like nuts. No, I'm here. Yes, he's geared for battle. Let's see if we shoot for for the zone
inventory. Why, yes. Let's see if we can get it. Get serious. I am. Watch out for a full buddy.
Here we come. Dexter, call me ace, huh? What happened? Did it win? Use the aquabooms. Wait,
why did I? If the webcam was on, you guys would have just been like, holy shit, dude. You need
to go to like the doctor. I'm out of oxygen. Use the aquabooms. Use the aquabooms. He's in the tank.
I did it. Okay, it's down. Shoot. How did we end up?
Okay, you know when there's that the white background? No, it's like the dots on the screen.
Why do we think that was so funny? Why was that so funny? We just, were we dead?
Dead? That's funny to you guys that you're dead. What? We're dead. No, we're in different clothes.
Go. Energize. Fight. And it's dodging.
God damn it. It was up, not. It's just a button, but that button, if it's not pressed,
within a tenth of a second, it's over. And you've got colors all over the screen and screaming and
and dodging and lightning everywhere.
Holy shit, imagine this shit on higher difficulty.
Throw it on your face cam. Sure. I don't care. Fine. If I don't do it this time.
Oh, I broke my computer. Oh great, I gotta re-plug this in. Shit. I'm good. Hey guys,
you want to see the cam? Turn cam on, man. What would my Joker laugh be? Honestly,
I'll do a pretty good one in a second. Hold on. Let's go plug in the webcam. I'll do a good one.
There's a couple ways to do the Joker. There's high pitched. Well, this is the original Joker,
which is sort of like, with your mouth open really wide. And then there's into the cartoon,
the animated Joker, which was more of like a, almost like a witch, I would say. Something along
the lines of high pitched and really, really big, big smile. Like, that's an original animated
Batman series. And then from there, we went to obviously he's stalling. Oh, for the love of God.
Fine. Here's my Joker laugh. I've been working on this. I almost just knocked over a fucking glass.
Stalling. Is this, am I even logged in? You can't even see it. Yeah, I am stalling. You're right.
And you know why? Because I only see her colors right now. How do I fucking do this? I forget how
to put the webcam on. I swear to God. There we go. Okay. Who the fuck's supposed to be sitting
there? Monkey ass. Alrighty. I set it for you so you don't have to. Is that good? All right. That's
fine. Like this shit even matters. Let's just put it over the, okay. Here we go. Oh, there's no
controller, right? Okay. That sound. We didn't get the Joker laugh. Oh, sorry. I forgot.
I forgot. I forgot. That wasn't it. That was me saying. I forgot.
Okay.
This is a fake webcam. I should just delay the webcam for five minutes. The webcam actually
makes this harder for me because not only am I aware of the stuff on screen, I'm aware of you
looking at my face. Guys, I treat face cam the same way I treat somebody who is watching me eat a
sandwich. Like I know you're looking at my face right now and it's like, I don't want you to look
at my face. All right. I got to fucking, I have to do this. I don't care. Let's go. I'm so close.
My keyboard is fucked up. It's like, did you hear that? Did you hear the space bar get hit
and it didn't happen? You heard it. I know you did. I've lost my mind. I can't do it.
I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm 10 milliseconds behind. There's been too many fucking QTEs today.
I won. I just beat it.
Oh, so that was a lot more intense and a lot shorter than, um, Dragon Age. No, not Dragon
Age. Dragon's lair. Okay. Remember I was about to say something. So that, you know, when you look
at the dots, the, the little splotches on the screen, it's like stare at the center of this
image for 25 seconds and then boom, don't start blinking. Cause it's on a white background. And
you like, oh, there's, there's Jesus, right? Or whatever it is. That's what I'm doing. That's
what happened. That's what's happening right now. Okay. So we've got Dragon's lair two. I don't know
this one. Should I do this one? Dragon's lair two time warp. I got to change the name of the game.
I feel like I just woke up. You know, okay. You know, when you stay up all night
and the sun starts to come up and you, you kind of start to see that you leave your room and there's
a window and you start to see the sun come up and it's like, that's how I feel right now.
All right. Hold on. Dragon's lair two. Okay. Look at, okay. I want you to refresh the screen.
I'll tell you when. So there's no Dragon's lair two, but there is a Dawn Bluth presents Dragon
lair 20th anniversary special edition. I think it has, it has a two in it. It does have a two,
I guess. Okay. So let's get to it. Do you want to see any extras? Should I just watch the game?
No. Okay. This is the animated FMV night. I got to go for it. Director's cut or the original?
Five lives always. Move beats. We'll take, should I do the move God on this one? Is this one horrible?
There's no difficulty on this one. Yes. This is so hard. This one is so hard.
Okay. Original or director's cut? Original? Director's cut. Original. This is,
this seems pretty contested in chat. Director. Well, I'll do director's cut. Why not? Here we go.
I got hit so hard on the ground it killed me. That's not good.
You're destroying your house lady. Why am I, what's the context here? What the
fuck is happening? Why am I getting thrown out? Kidnapped again. I'm being blamed.
We're in the dungeon. Leave me alone. Why are you still fighting me in here? You could help me. You
could be like the player two. Oh my God. Why is there a Star Wars canon here?
A spell. Give me the key. Hurry. We'll get her back. Defeat of our wizard.
Who is talking? Um, why are you still here? Okay. Thank God. I got a checkpoint.
You're gonna start all the way at the beginning. Oh, this is not good.
Holy shit. This is in the arcade. They probably saw the first one and they were just like,
you know what? Fuck it. This shit would cost thousands of dollars to beat in the arcade.
Hopefully you had like a credit card. You need to have two assistants carry the coins
to help you do this.
A prisoner.
Yes. Yeah.
I've heard this voice actor before. Pretty good jumper laugh. That one not so good.
You don't ever swing the sword into your own head. I thought it was gonna be left.
I predicted.
Talk more. I can't. I can't talk. I can't speak. I can't do it. I can't talk. I can't,
I can't talk to you. I need to just stare at this. Why is there a Doug soundtrack?
Okay. Every time there was a transition in Doug, it would do that like,
is that happening or am I making that up? How's the movie? Because I can't see it. Is this a good
movie?
I am. He's not getting better. No, I'm not getting better. We've done almost three and a
half hours of QTE cut scenes. I need to go get my eyes examined after this.
This is me. I'm gonna have to get a new prescription.
Fuck. Jeremy. Goodness. Okay. I'm doing it now.
Cursor on the screen. Let's get it right in the middle where it belongs.
Fuck. Let's do it. This is the one.
That's the guy that does wacko on an animated X. Got it.
Get her. I hit left when I shouldn't have.
I swear to God. Okay. Oh dear brother. We're brothers? I missed that part of the story.
I'm it's the machine is his brother. What is Doug? Okay. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. Let's go.
What if I just like, oh fuck. Just crush it in my hands. I have to. I'm gonna go like this.
I'm doing the thing that all of our parents told us to never do.
But in this one scenario, I think it'll work.
Oh. Exhaustion. It's QTE exhaustion. Give me a checkpoint or something. Give me a checkpoint.
It's all right. I'm here. Yes. Good.
Good. Wait, this is, this is fair. Wait, this is not, this is Alice in Wonderland.
Stop shooting me with the fucking. All right. Let's go.
I thought it was gonna be swing again.
He looks like he's in pain is what somebody said earlier. No, I'm not in pain.
I am in total focused in locked in mode. It may look like pain, but it's not.
Get in there. Swing. Kill. I mean, it's, it's beautifully animated. I will say.
No, don't start at the fucking painting. Don't start at the painting. All the way back at the damn
painting. How would you do this without a guide? Uh, you just have to be really good at catching
every flash because notice how the screen flashes. You just have to be ready like flash. And that
might, I'm not even sure that happens if you turn the guide off.
That's how you can tell you're getting old. All right. After like sitting here and pressing the
same keys, the insides of my fingers are liquidating right now. They're being liquidated.
Oh, I thought it was up. I did it. I'm back outside. Good. I went down a new area. Nimbus length.
It's blink time. New area of time. Blink. Again, I'm just like laughing at
visitors. What the fuck is happening? Yum. Yum. Yum. Yum. These games are crazy.
All right. I, oh, damn it. I need to, I wanted to see that one. I want to see if she just like
put her mouth over my head and just like, Amy, please move the cursor. I can't help it.
It's just like that. There's so much going on in every scene.
You could dissect every single one of these scenes.
Who's talking?
Eat the apple. She's going to eat the apple. What? That's the beginning.
You know, it's ridiculous about video games and gaming in general. Let's talk. Let's go over this.
So this is, this was like QTEs. Oh, wow. It's QTEs. Cutscenes. They react fast.
We went from this to being able to fail three to four or five of these in a fucking row and have
nothing happening. When did that happen? We went from one extreme to the next.
In fact, in a lot of cases, failing QTEs in games doesn't do anything. It's just,
they added an animation. All right, I gotta focus here. I don't want to do this again.
What? I'm on a guy's piano now. Is that the mad hatter? Everybody wants to eat you.
That's something else too. What was with every single fucking character who wants to eat you
in all these games from 20 years ago? Everybody wanted to just swallow you. Cats, birds, people,
monsters. It didn't matter. You were dinner for somebody in every single one of these games.
Oh, I must press left. Why is he up here with the piano? What did he just do?
Did he just flash the camera? I didn't even see it. I hope not.
All right, we're good. I have to pee so bad again.
Okay, let me ask you a question. When you have to pee, I really do feel like this sometimes.
I'm like processing all the fucking negative energy in my body right now and I'm gonna pee
it out. I really feel that way sometimes. What do you guys think? Do some Reddit analysis on my urine.
Okay, I can't look over here because that's where you guys are and you guys are a distraction.
That was an embarrassing face, I think. Remember, Jeremy, everything you do into that camera
is is there forever. Damn it. If you type in like, Jerma into Google.
Jerma985. I think it's still there. There's an image of my face that is one of the, it's like
the top thing that is always shown is the one where I'm going like, like, what's this mean?
What's that mean? When did it freeze? Are we good? I missed every single treasure. How's that
possible? It froze on that face. We didn't, wait, what was the last thing I said? I said that's the
most searched face. Okay, then I went on to say that that's the most searched face. That's like
the face that, I think I'm going down again. I don't know, something's going on here. Now,
that's the most searched face. And the thing is, I have to, when my mother sees that image,
right? Oh yeah, Jerma985, top 500 streamer, top 50 streamer. Let's look at my, you know,
I know that because that's all he talks about at Thanksgiving every year. So we all have memorized
it by now. Top 50 variety streamer, of course. So, you know, they know. And they, that's what
they have to see when they type in Jerma985. And that's probably the new one. Like, I'm going to
be honest with you, take a look at that image. Let's let, I'm going to go over this image.
You want, you want to talk about like fucking the energy that I have. Let's, I want to, I'm
going to show you this. Look at this shit. Well, we struggled to stay live apparently.
Here, look at this. Look at how much blood goes up into my brain. You want to know how, like,
how smart I am, how intelligent I am? It's because this, that, that is carrying
so much fucking liquid energy all around my body. Let's examine my face. I should have,
you know, 2020 hindsight, I should have been a runner. Look at this one too. Take a look at that
one. Look at this one down here, right below my chin. Look at how, look at how huge that one is.
Look at that. That's taking so much blood up there. That's like a, that's a tube like this thick.