Hey guys, what is with this LUL boy thing? I make a couple of typos and all of a sudden,
why would I watch German when I can watch late night TV? I mean, that's a question for you.
I don't get it because I'm not an LUL boy. Every time I write LUL, people laugh at me.
Okay, look, when I write this, right, back in my day, we didn't have emotes to show our
feelings. So if you thought something was really, really funny, you'd go like this.
But people make fun of me when I do that, so now I'm trying to be hip and be cool,
and when I do the new one, I'm not allowed to do that either. So what should I go back to do
it? Should I do this? Just don't express any of your emotions. Ah, that's a nice hot coffee.
But yeah, today we're gonna chill. The next couple days actually gonna be a little
more relaxed. I don't know why I keep saying that, but we've had some intense
stuff going on the last week or so. The VR last night went pretty late. It was all over the
place. So today we're gonna do something that I tried to do a couple years ago,
and that is play Call of Juarez Gunslinger. There was technical problems last time.
They shouldn't be there now. I tested it. Let's hope that even after testing
that we can actually do it. And then tomorrow is Chillstream 2.0. Tomorrow all bets are off for
whatever the hell is gonna be on the screen. We've got some videos we can watch. I might
just start to, I might just play the first episode of Sam and Max. Maybe we'll play Picross.
I don't know. But today we're gonna dial it back a little. And I'm just gonna play a game
that I've wanted to play for a couple years. And I forgot that I wanted to play it. Because
a couple years ago I was really into it. Labo stream. Here we go. Here comes the next
Labo. No. No, I gotta like dial it down. Let me make a tweet. Cooking stream with mom.
No. I think I've seen too many intense things over the last week. Let's just hang out and play
a cowboy game, right? And just chill. Cooking is intense. Yeah, have you ever cooked anything
before? It's a constant never-ending stress in your brain that you don't want to over or
under cook the thing that you're cooking. So you pace around. You like put your hand in
your mouth like, ah, okay, is it ready yet? No, it's not. Don't touch it. And then you
flip it and you're not supposed to flip it and you get mad at yourself. I can't cook.
I can only cook three meals and they're like 10 out of 10. So that's the only thing I can do.
So let me, let's get this on the screen here. You need to see to believe. Yeah,
you'll see one day. All right, let's get it up. All right, everybody cross your fingers.
I tested it already. But is this game going to actually work this time? I'm gonna turn
some of this down even more. That's better. All right, I'm ready. Here we go. Put the
subtitles in French. Why would I put the subtitles in French? Who here speaks French? Does anybody
here actually speak French? All right, story. New game. I told you I tested it so I want to do a
new game. This normal hard and true west. How hard is hard? I can't even select true west.
All right, is this, this is like 2010 hard. That could be very hard. Hard is normal.
I don't, uh, okay. Sticks. Sticks is the, uh, I'm doing normal. I'm not gonna do hard. This is
supposed to be a relaxing hangout stream today. Do you want me to like fucking clench my ass and
try as hard as I can? You picked the easiest. Why does it have to be easy? Why can't there be an
easy underneath that? You, sir? Be so? I haven't been here in many years. Named Silas
Greaves. Silas Greaves? The bounty hunter? Used to be. What are you doing here? Just passing
through. That's Ben 10's dad. Well, sir, it would be an honor if you would allow me to buy
you a beer. Hell, son, it would be my honor to drink it. I'm Molly. Howdy. I'm Dwight.
That's Jack and Steve. Ben's behind the bar. Oh, Ben. Ben 10. I bet you got some great
stories. A couple. Any of them true? Jack, be nice. A few. What about your shootout with
Henry Plummer's gang in Bannock Montana? Is that where you started as a bounty hunter?
That's what it says in this here dime novel. Don't believe everything you read in them dime
novels, boy. First man I hunted was back when I was riding with Billy the Kid.
You knew Billy the Kid? Damn right. L-U-L, boy. That scrawny son of a bitch had no fear.
Wouldn't back down for nobody. I heard he collected the ten stars off any crooked law
men who crossed him. It was a war, boy. The Lincoln County War. And Billy promised his
regulators would take the life of every bastard who helped bushwhack John Tunstall.
Kid had a big chip on his shoulder and a hair trigger temper. Made him dangerous as hell.
Is the game good? Is it? I know I've wanted to play it for a while, but is this a good game,
right? I remember, yeah, I remember I tried to play this like two years ago.
Fuck it, let's just play it. Who gives a shit, right? It was about 30 years ago.
Billy was hiding out in an abandoned farm near Stinking Springs. Well, property value
probably ain't high on that place. Stinking Springs. But before I tell you why I want
that son of a bitch dead, let me tell you what happened that day. I was heading back.
I think we're running fine. When suddenly I had this funny feeling. Funny ha ha? No, Steve.
The other kind of funny. Was that Joe Pesci? Why is Joe Pesci talking to me about
playing funny like a clown? Funny like ha ha funny? Uh, okay. Is there any like secrets?
Well, uh, guys, this is a plus. The game runs. Press O to see objectives.
Turn to the hideout. So it just puts it on the ground.
I knew those two morons would never let me through. I had no choice.
That was clean. You're inexperienced by killing enemies. You need it for leveling
up and gaining extra abilities. Okay. Was it Pat Garrett's posse? Oh yeah,
shift to sprint. Wait, I heard the shots and I knew I had to move fast.
Hold on. I know you want to move fast, but I need you to hold on a second. I need toggle on.
Is there toggle? Aiming vibration. Auto aim. Why is auto aim on? Oh, this is for controller.
Okay. Uh oh. Crouch toggle is on. Aim is okay. Melee. Melee is going to be this.
Quick throw dynamite is going to be this. Why can I not make it that?
No. No, fire is pee pee. Right? Right? Right, Twitch chat? Isn't that funny? Um,
I can't make my the mouse button. So there is no toggle aim, is there?
E-O-A-U. Next weapon. Wheel. One, two, three. Grab weapon. Move hand? There's a sprint toggle.
There's no aim toggle. My life is going to be hell in this game. Garrett and his army
of deputies has surrounded the entire homestead. So I'll use it as an excuse. I'll take care of it.
Actually doesn't feel that bad. I decided to help Billy and the boys out of it.
Gunning down enemies fills your concentration gauge. Press, okay, then you press Q.
All right. So this is, this is bullet storm, but in the old west.
Hey, crouch. That wasn't a headshot. Oh, these are my friends. No, they're not.
Let's move. Who's left? Who's it? Who are? Where are you? I knew that going through that front door
had been putting my butt in a shooting gallery. So I decided to get sneaky.
Is that a person doing a dog? Secret. Show nugget info. The Lincoln County War is often
considered one of the most famous examples of a range war in the history of the west.
Range wars were conflicts over the control of open range or rangeland
freely used for cattle grazing. The disputes were usually over grazing or water rights.
But in this case, the fight was over the control of dry goods trade in Lincoln County.
The quarrel rose around a conflict of interest between the Dolan Murphy faction
and a newly arrived Englishman, John Tunstall. At first, they tried to use the legal system
to resolve their dispute, but soon the fight evolved into a conflict between armed gangs.
Murphy and Dolan had ties to outlaws like John Kinney and his gang Jesse Evans,
whose outfit was known as the Boys. They were responsible for the death of Tunstall,
which became the central catalyst of the conflict. The other side had the regulators,
William Bonney, aka Billy the Kid, rode with them promising revenge on the men who
murdered Tunstall. Both sides were sworn in by different officers of the law, so technically
they were all acting within the law. After the regulators were defeated,
some of their members became fugitives and just like Billy the Kid, met untimely and violent ends.
This has been our Top 5 Coolest WTF Moments from Modern American History.
Stay Notified!
Easy target.
Minus two.
Can I look without doing it?
Yeah. Eagle Eye. Iron Sight slows down time. That's cool.
Do well revolvers. That's cool too.
I'm a trapper. I don't think I want to do this.
Deep dynamite. Higher combos and concentration.
I think I'm gonna go with the Ranger. That sounds cool.
Iron Sight slows down time. You get a fraction of concentration like slowdown,
just enough to aim perfectly. Yeah, I'm gonna get it.
Rifle ammo capacity. I'm gonna do Rav Rifle.
So I don't get points available. So now let's see how that works.
Whoa! But you can avoid lethal shots only when your sense of death is charged.
Avoid the bullet using A to dodge left or D to dodge right.
Garrett's man was running around like a bunch of chickens with their hands turned up.
That's actually pretty cool. Anybody else? Yep.
All right. Anybody who's left alive?
Luckily these shooters Garrett hired weren't the sharpest tools in the ship.
Like this is cool. A lot of them were saddle triumphs or sodbusters or drunken drifters
looking to make a few bucks.
The shooting is actually really fun. Whoa! Who's next to me?
What's melee? Oh, okay.
This game could easily be a light gun game. I can see that.
Fight your way to the rear entrance of the farmhouse.
What? I thought he was holding like a baby or something. That was fucking weird.
Does this count your headshots?
Where is this dude?
This could easily be a crossover with Mr. Mosquito.
Wait, what about secrets? I'm not going to just blow through. Hold on.
How could this be a Mr. Mosquito crossover?
Sometimes people just write a sentence and then I read it for some reason.
Is there like a sneak?
Secret. Oh, there's three in here. Hold on. How many skills do I have?
God damn it. I really crack shot.
Smart as a whip. 21 killed by age 21.
Sort of. I keep doing these like weird Spider-Man introspectives.
Rifle's the best.
Action-liver rifle's the best. Yeah, this is the bolt. I can feel the bolt.
I can hear it. That lights a lot of pluses.
That barrel just told a really funny fucking joke. It should have hurt it.
No, get out of the way. We good? No, not yet. Where?
Whoa. S? What? What's going on? Wait, what?
I didn't have to. S? S. All right. S is shoot.
Is somebody in a Heinz helicopter? All right.
Dumbass. Oh, boy. Whoa. Bring the horses from the stable.
Where are those horses? What? Oh, over here.
Now where was that? That guy was just hiding behind you. He was the door.
You were heading. What? Oh, melee. I, right, right. I changed melee to my mouse button.
I at least got to hold the page in the Choose Your Own Adventure book.
Get the bomb. It's good. Sounds like Garrett hired a whole regiment of hired guns.
Oh, Jesus.
And here comes somebody, right? That guy was hiding in there. He had the pumpkin on his head.
All right. That was a fun level. That was a fun tutorial level.
Proud, handsome, and hand-handed. Pat Garrett. See you in the next German Rumble.
Right. You're gonna be there.
Okay. Focus. Keep your energy, keep your enemy in focus using the mouse. Press space. They're
gonna keep them in the, put the camera on them. It's a little slow. Focus. Where do I need to shoot
them? That's not what my intention was, but when your opponent reaches for their gun, press
to draw you up in an aim and then shoot.
In a fair fight. Is that what that penny dreadful says? No. Right there. That ain't what I meant
when I said I met Pat Garrett. So let me start again. What? We're gonna do this whole thing
again? It's hard to control that. Don't tell them about shooting the guy in the balls.
Last thing I heard was Garrett's voice. That's not totally not on purpose. I mean,
initially it wasn't, but the second half of that maybe wasn't.
68. 70% accuracy. Rifle. Award of choice. Headshot. Honorably killed. I only got two out of
three nuggets. All right. I get one point available. What's down here? Let's see.
Truth-seeking. Don't miss any important details. Additional sounds and hints will lead
you to the hidden nuggets of truth, provided you get close enough. That's not bad. Or
ammo capacity increased. What does that lead to? Additional zoom while aiming. Hold your
breath and be more precise. You'll be able to zoom even more. And this one is fast rifle
reload. Fast rifle reload on this one, interestingly enough. I think I'll do more
ammo. We'll go this way. Do you live on a racetrack? No, I live in Vegas. We'll get
more ammo. Seems like it was a bit easy after all. Would you like to switch to hard
difficulty? I can't. What am I going to on stream say no to that?
Hey, you did that pretty easily. I think your audience might start resident sleeper-ing if
you don't go to hard.
You'd like red steel for the Wii. Yeah, that game was really just
interesting and odd, wasn't it? All right. Fistful of hot lead.
Lincoln jail. April 28th, 1881. Four months after the arrest.
They were sworn enemies of Billy's regulator. Why were you after him? I owed that son of
a bitch a bullet for what he had done to me and mine. Instead, all I got for myself
was a goddamn death sentence. Prison break sequence? It was right around then that I
heard Billy make his move. This is on hard now. I gotta get up. I was lying on my back
this whole time. That's why I think I sounded a little weird earlier. Planted a pistol
for him in the privy. What the papers didn't say is that Billy helped me escape too.
What? Okay. My first order of business was finding a firearm. I gotta find a gun. Do
I have a melee? I don't think I can do anything. All right, I gotta be careful
because it's on hard now. Oh, William. I'm not gonna do that again. Cool. Let's
get the get you get little nuggets of info. These give experience, right? They
give a lot of experience. Jesus. Okay. Fast rifle reload. Reload your rifle in the
blink of an eye. Inserting the cartridges from the bottom of your rifle can cut
down the reload by 50 percent. Uh, yeah, I think so. Sounds pretty great.
Gun? Oh, there's a gun.
10 gauge. Loudest thunder.
A man clean in half. What does this look like? I forgot that's the title.
I should take to the rooftops to make my escape. So I did.
Exit the jail. It's on hard. Okay, I can't fucking run.
That scattered gun was like a double-barreled hell wizard.
Is there like a queue or can I? Thank God. Should have built this.
So it'll be good for you, Jerbo. Okay, use the roofs to escape.
I'm just gonna go this way. Any secrets? What secrets?
Shouldn't have shot from up here. What was that?
Why is it? I'm so confused.
We're gonna get through here. God. Down here. Okay. Good thing hard mode
still has the please go this direction.
Only a grievous harm, but I knew if I was ever going to find him,
I would need to get my ever loving ass out of there.
I tried to be stealthy and sneak my way past.
He's streaming right now. I don't need to say anything.
I'm gonna take this one stealthy. Good thing I don't need to reload this.
Can't really aim it that well, but doesn't matter, you know.
Okay, got ammo now. Do I have to buy the guns? No. Make your way through the town.
Tell us more. Apparently, some of them thought I was Billy.
Oh, that was good. See, me and the kid shared a certain similarity in build and coloring.
I was just glad I had Deputy Bob's mean ass gun.
Oh no! No! Okay, I'm fine. 30 FOV. Is it?
Is it that bad? It looks like it's somewhere around. How do I change it?
It's very low. Is it? Now that you say it, now that you mentioned that, it is a little low.
I don't think, yeah, can I not change it in the game? I might not be able to change it.
Unless it's a game of an eye and eye? You can do it in the config. All right, well then yeah.
Once we get to a checkpoint, I'll do it. I'm trying to get points.
Thank you, it's making me sick. All right, yeah, I don't want to make it be sick, you know.
You can disable the screen border. Yeah, maybe I'll do that too. What the hell was that?
Can I get through there? Oh, yeah, I'm up. I'll be at checkpoint in like a minute here.
Where was the kid while you were busy getting shot at?
Plan forth reload. Gone. And that's when it occurred to me why Billy set me free.
Wow. All right, I did it. Did I not get him? It's the guy that is a door guy here.
Oh my god, what's happening? What? Was that another door guy? I have no idea what that was.
Deputy Bob Olinger was organizing a posse to put me down.
He was already a mean son of a bitch, but he was doubly pissed that I stole his mean-ass shotgun.
Anyway, it was me or them, and the only way forward led me straight to perdition.
But the cards were dealt and I had no choice but to play them.
He's nice talking about when he went to the casino last week.
That's out of the stream last day. What I did last night.
Played some fucking cards and shit. Oh damn, I almost got hit by that one.
I don't want to talk over the streamer. Oh my god, die. I wish I had my rifle.
I built into rifles, not into pistols. I could get up there and shoot a shotgun.
Holy shit, there's a guy right here.
Oh, the stables on the edge of town.
Guess Billy saved your ass, taking out Bob Olinger the way he did.
Billy didn't kill Bob. Sure he did. He dispatched him right after he shot him.
Are we gonna rewind again? No, sir.
Because Bob came right up behind me angry as hell that Billy had lit out.
Hello Bob. I said, I think you better let me go.
He's in a Peter Griffin costume. I don't think so, boy.
Not with my shotgun. So we stood there in the middle of the street, eyeball to eyeball.
He intended to kill me and I knew I had no choice but to defend myself.
Just your hand position is aimed for faster draw.
Oh fuck, I gotta play the claw game and I have to keep this guy in focus?
When you hear the heartbeat, you can draw your gun first,
but this will be noted as dishonorable and scored accordingly.
Fuck. That was quick.
You were focused so that your hand speed was 42% and your reaction time was 0.6600 milliseconds.
I'm better than that. I'm like 200 milliseconds.
What? I didn't know I had to aim a second time.
I didn't know I had to aim a second time.
I thought he just shoot with the shot over his head.
0.3 seconds. That's better.
These are going to get so hard.
I killed him in a fair fight. Everybody saw I had no damn choice.
Well, Lincoln got a might depopulated that day.
That Garret gunned down Billy three months later.
So his escape was all for naught anyway.
New skills.
What is this one?
It's not just pretty, but an engineering masterpiece
and a very deadly fire round.
The simplified trigger mechanism and longer barrel.
Faster rate of fire and better handling.
And then ultimately we get the golden rifle.
Quick fingers.
Reload rate increased by smashing handle your bullets with care.
Wait, smashing?
Smash R like Loco during the reload sequence to insert rounds faster.
Okay. Legendary weapon unlocked.
I already got a legendary weapon.
Jesus.
Already a legendary.
Okay. So I want to let's just continue for a second.
Let me get the loading screen there.
Get the save point in the top, right?
And then I'm going to change the FOV.
So where'd you go after Lincoln?
Mexico.
Until I realized nobody was looking for me.
I ended up taking a job at the Rurales.
The Mexican Rurales?
I was hired to help them track down the cowboys.
Most vicious outlaw gang in Cochise County?
Curly Bill Brocious?
Johnny Ringo?
Led by old man Clint himself.
They must have paid you a pretty penny to take him on, Brazone.
Not really.
But truth be told, I had my own reasons for going after those boys.
So somebody said that this game only has like five levels.
Are you telling me I'm more than halfway through the whole game?
That doesn't make any sense.
This game's not 20 minutes long.
So was the bastard you were after-
All right, so I got new nuggets of truth.
I already saw them.
Let me just quit out and go to the INI.
Is it really that simple?
It's not a bunch of bullshit where I have to-
I can just do it in the INI, right?
Hopefully.
Yeah, the INI.
Yeah, it's in the INI.
Okay.
Give me a second.
I'm gonna put the BRB screen up just to have it up.
And put it on 90.
Oh, there's actually like a Steam discussion link that somebody put up.
Okay.
Let's see.
FOV.
Navigate to your settings.
Your drag video SCR onto Notepad to edit its contents.
Oh yeah, pretty self-explanatory.
360 degree FOV.
No, I can't do that.
Okay, so we're gonna go to users.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, you gotta go into the actual app data, huh?
Oh, that's annoying.
Let me open up like my app data then.
App data.
It's kind of hard to get there on Windows 10.
You have to search for it.
Local...
Wait, Techland made this game.
Shit, it might not be here.
No, this is like a Windows 7 like tutorial.
I'm gonna have to do that.
Local app data.
Is Techland in here?
Techland, there it is.
Gunslinger out settings.
Here we go, video.
All right, so let's hope this doesn't break the game.
So now we're gonna drag this onto Notepad.
Or just open it with Notepad.
I'm gonna feel like it's gonna turn off.
Put it on the desktop.
How do I drag this onto Notepad though?
Because like Notepad...
I can't like open this with Notepad for some reason.
Send to open.
I can't open it with...
Yeah, usually I just right click and then open with.
There is no open with on this because it's like an SCR file.
Oh, let's just...
Okay, Notepad.
New Notepad.
Yeah, pretty much every file you can do that.
It says...
So I got test, configure, install, share, give access to.
Like give access to is where open with.
It usually is.
What is test?
What if I just drag it into Notepad?
Like into that...
Okay, I thought I had to open it with Notepad.
I can just drag it into a new Notepad.
All right, I got it.
I'm good to go.
All right, so let's do...
So I gotta add forced horizontal FOV.
Force...
Make sure I spell this shit right.
Forced, hoars, forced hoars FOV.
Forced hoars FOV and then in brackets 90.
Okay, so now how do I get rid of some of the other dumb shit?
I'm only going to do this once.
How do I get rid of the stuff on the top and the bottom?
Forced hoars FOV, forced hoars FOV 90.
What?
What are we talking about?
Oh, unless there's like a...
Anyone's got an...
Yeah, phrasing.
All right, how do I remove the vignette?
Do I have to do that here too?
Because I don't see it here.
I mean, FX level.
Full dynamic shader path.
Filter.
I don't see it here.
Gamma float.
Disables.
There it is.
Okay, so disable screen board.
Disable the hand-painted comic boarder.
Do I have...
What do I do say?
Okay, here, look.
Do I put one in here?
In the brackets, do I put one?
Or do I just get rid of the exclamation point?
Delete the bars.
Just do what the guide...
Well, the guide doesn't say...
It doesn't say anything, does it?
You can delete this file and run the game to reset the default settings.
It doesn't...
It just says...
There's like I-S-F-I-S-F-I-S-F.
Delete the exclamation point.
It doesn't disable it otherwise, okay?
So, deleting that exclamation point.
Okay.
That should work.
I'm going to save this now.
Let me make sure it actually saved it.
Okay.
Let's open it.
Let's hope it doesn't break it.
The joys of running old games on Windows 10.
Yeah.
That should be good though.
Thank you for your patience.
Coming back.
Jesus.
Why?
This is still a trend that no one seems to want to solve.
The default FOV was 82, by the way.
Okay.
Well, that makes sense.
Because it wasn't terrible, but it wasn't great either.
Okay.
Here we go.
Story.
Continue.
Did it work?
Are we good?
So, was the bastard you were after now riding with the cowboys?
Roscoe Bob Bryant was his name.
Oh.
But no.
This time it was a different bastard I was after.
He aforementioned Mr. Ringo.
And yes, he was working for Old Man Clown.
Is it read only?
Set the file to read only.
Did I add more screen border?
Did I add another layer to an extra border?
No.
I tried to just...
This is freaking me out now.
Oh, wait.
So the FOV may have changed.
And the border is now showing...
Okay.
God damn it.
All right.
Just make it nothing but border.
Whatever.
All right.
Still playing on hard, so I gotta remember that.
Just clip it in OBS.
Yeah, but that would make the FOV bad for you guys.
Because it would zoom you guys in.
So I would change the FOV to 90.
And then change it back to 80 something.
Because I have to zoom it in.
Oh, this is the new shooter.
Okay.
I need a rifle for this one.
And whatever else I had.
What?
The FOV fucked up my video game.
Those were all headshots.
All of them.
Out of nowhere.
And there never seemed to be an end.
To the cowboys.
Did I say they were Apaches?
I said Clanton's cowboys attacked me Apache style.
I was in a pitched battle.
What?
But I was holding my own against an order.
Okay.
Look at that.
I was still pretty green.
Shooting at anything I could see up in those damn holes.
Didn't see Ringo.
I'm gonna die.
He and Roscoe barbed the train.
Determined to have revenge.
But to get to Ringo, I knew I'd have to fast forward.
Oh.
Goddamn.
Unfortunately, I was running out of an example of my relative inexperience as a hundred of men.
Ammo's right here.
What are you talking about?
I got plenty of ammo.
Oh, no, no.
Pick up.
What is?
This is like too many people.
Finally, they did it.
This narration.
It's on hard mode.
It's all right.
I'll get good.
Don't worry.
Hold on.
He's resetting here?
Why would it zoom in over there?
I'm looking over here.
Finally.
Do you see how many fucking people are here, guys?
Holy shit.
What?
I suddenly spotted a way out of my predicament.
That was fucking perfect.
Was I supposed to find that?
Oh, my God.
I have no gun.
I have one bullet.
Why would you turn?
I'm trying to run away.
And he like whips his head around and stares at the guy.
Oh, God damn it.
I need ammo first.
Whatever.
I got...
What's that shotgun?
Why do I have one fucking bullet in the shotgun?
Same guy.
Yeah.
Tried to get me again.
Thank you.
Billy the Kid's massive dong for the thousand dollars.
I appreciate it.
Holy shit.
That's a lot of money.
So I just kept running.
You know, I'm just gonna keep going this way.
What?
Was that supposed to just be there or was it supposed to fall down?
I don't...
Oh, I have ammo now.
Oh, it's a joke.
Oh, okay.
It's supposed to.
Unreliable narrator.
Yep.
I just...
I didn't know what it was like.
Now I'm chasing them with dynamite.
I got him.
Okay.
That was just an explosive New Vegas build.
That's true.
I'm just playing Fallout.
Oh, fuck.
I really want to get rid of this border.
Frankie.
Mean as hell.
Old man.
Clampin'.
Turns out that was a bad idea.
Because why would you ever announce your position
and have somebody shoot you with a fucking minigun?
All right.
I'm gonna get up there.
Do I have a rifle?
Where's the next place to go?
Over there.
No!
I was really, really greedy there.
It's okay.
Where...
Where is he?
He's up.
I'm gonna hit him right in the head.
Watch this.
Ready?
That's why you guys all play like Fortnite and Apex and shit like that.
I figured it out.
I know why.
You want to do that long range shot and have it go like bang!
My hands were off the...
I didn't have my hands on the keyboard or anything.
I was hit by...
Okay.
I got tanked off on.
I'm fine.
I...
I can't even turn my camera on.
I was putting my fingers up towards my mouth and talking and moving my hands.
It's all right.
I'm right here.
I don't even...
I don't know what the fuck that was.
Can I sneak up around to shoot him in the head?
I shot him in the head three times.
No.
I'm gonna get up there.
I'm gonna put two in his chest.
Ready?
He even pulled his knife out and the gun was still shooting.
This thing is a turret.
All right.
I was gonna do it this way.
Is he gonna shoot?
What's he doing?
What the fuck is he doing?
Is he being blocked by that one little thing in the middle?
He's head glitching.
Why do bullet holes appear on the screen when you get hit?
Because I'm in a car.
There's a windshield in front of me.
I got really, really thick gamer glasses on.
That's why.
Okay, headshot.
Didn't get any nuggets of truth.
Bad.
All right.
Well, hold on.
I should get some of these.
If I'm playing on hard mode, then close combat resistance.
You can't be bulletproof, but you can be more resistant.
Yeah.
What's this next one down here?
Pick your targets faster.
Your speed of aiming any weapon will be increased by 30%.
I want this though, too.
More zoom.
Yeah.
Fuck it, dude.
We're doing this whole game.
I'm gonna beat this whole game today.
This game's awesome.
I want the zoom.
Yeah, I want this.
Gonna be a 30-minute stream.
When I take my first pee break,
I'm gonna desperately try to remove this border.
I'm gonna go shove the piss out of me as fast as I can.
Get back here and try to delete that border.
Not yet, though.
I'm not gonna do that now.
Not yet.
Okay, only 10 shots?
What is that bullshit?
All right.
This is the point of the game where I stealth.
Oh, a nice dual-combing.
What happened there?
Runner plus 100.
Look at that reaction time.
It's fucking inhuman.
It was on him!
Oh, that was his death animation.
It's all right.
All right, don't use all these bullets.
Nice.
All right.
So what's the sound?
There's an indicator now that I have that level up.
Oh, God.
Was that a...
There were killers around every corner, all wearing red bandanas.
That's how the cowboys identified each other.
What did I fail?
And I was beginning to wish I had one myself.
Check this.
I wasn't about to let Ringo unscathed, and that's what drove me home.
Come on.
You say that Ringo was infernal when you saw anyone faster, boy.
Ooh, ammo.
It's certainly not wild.
Whoa.
Drop it.
I can't drop that.
You need to aim at it.
I did.
Right in the rope.
That's all right.
All right.
When they get close, it scares me.
Take over the cowboys.
Because I, Clanton, was dumber than a box of rocks and a yellow billy to boot.
Oh, that's full rifle ammo.
Very cool.
Make your way through the saw mill.
Get to the lumber yard and find Curly Bill.
Was I?
Taking down the entire gang single-handed.
Indeed I was, Jack.
What do I need these for?
It wasn't easy, as those boys had good cover.
It actually was kind of easy.
It was pretty easy.
Nice.
All right, I'm gonna save the other ones.
Don't undermine the storyteller.
Yeah, I forget.
He's giving his tale.
He's telling his tall tale.
That's not even true.
He's embellishing on everything he's ever done or ever said.
Inflating.
This guy really is a streamer, isn't he?
All right, let's get up here.
Uh-oh.
That collective turnaround.
That like, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit.
Oh, it's fine.
I didn't get killed by it.
That's the good thing.
I accidentally avoided that.
Why would there be a big barn here?
Secret?
I don't think there's any...
Wait.
That sounded like a secret.
I was Curly Bill.
Did you see him?
How'd you get to that, Ben?
Patience.
I'm painting a picture here.
It was this beautiful waterfall in a crystal clear stream that led to a verdant valley
that was truly...
Consider your picture painted.
What happened next?
Well, finally the bastards that were still alive made a last stand.
How does...
Let me see.
No.
I'm gonna keep what I have.
All right.
Last stand incoming.
Curly Bill in here?
What the fuck?
Ow.
Wait, what am I doing?
Did I just go...
What?
Did I just ruin everything?
Curly Bill, Johnny Ringo, and his compadres took off into the lumber yard.
Okay.
I guess I was just supposed to...
No, here comes another one of these.
Takes a shot before he takes a swig.
Defeat Curly Bill.
Oh, that is Curly Bill right there.
Oh, Jesus.
There's a Metal Gear Solid boss that's just like this.
It's freaking me out.
I gotta...
Ow.
Oh, God.
What?
Which way?
This is fucking loony toons fight.
We're both aiming really close and missing.
Ow.
That scream.
He's like, no, please.
Where?
That wasn't even him.
Fuck.
Damn it.
Oh.
Got it.
Indeed.
Took me a few months before I finally tracked his ass to West Turkey Creek Canyon.
This whole story is being told out of order and incorrectly.
Next in line to take over.
Johnny Ringo.
That's incredible, sir.
I always thought that Doc Holliday was...
Shut the fuck up.
I'm trying to concentrate.
Get me killed, you fucking idiot.
We'll talk later.
All right.
Let me be real with you guys.
Back...
That's probably how all these duels ended.
Yeah, I know.
It's like, oh, the story.
Here it comes.
It pulls it out, shoots him.
Like, these guys probably got shot.
These bullets were small.
The guns were fucked up.
They jammed all the time.
They didn't work half the time.
These guys are probably lying on the ground,
just shooting back and forth with each other until one of them died.
Half the bullets didn't come out.
They're probably like, oh, fuck.
And the other guy just shot.
Hits the other guy.
They both fall down.
They crawl off of that gun, shooting at each other.
Well, sir, I always thought that Doc...
Damn it.
This is, you gotta...
You gotta keep the hand.
It's fucking hard.
Because they both move at different speeds.
Stop talking!
Oh!
It's gonna...
I'm gonna fucking lose again.
This is fucking...
This is really difficult.
Sir, I always thought that Doc Holliday was the one that killed him.
Got you.
Sorry, Dad.
The legend ain't always true.
That didn't even happen at all.
Let's rewind.
No nuggets at her.
This is bad.
All right, I said I wanted this.
Steady aim.
Additional zoom while aiming.
Got it.
No nuggets at all either.
Yeah.
Dude, it's too bad.
That's incredible, sir!
Now, quiet, quiet.
I'm trying to remember.
Trying to remember how fun that was.
Good perk.
What would it mean?
I was paid a healthy bounty for Ringo and Curly Bill.
And realized it was real money to be made.
That's why I went after Henry Plummer.
There's water in that bottle, Grandpa.
You can stop pretending to be drunk.
Be the sheriff who augmented his income by shaking down miners and robbing gold shipments.
That's the one.
That gang has thieving outlaws called the Innocents.
So it's true that you went toe-to-toe with him?
Indeed I did, son.
Indeed I did.
Smoking inside.
It's illegal now.
Sounds like you're doing the voices.
Maybe in another lifetime.
I knew I needed resources if I was going to track down Roscoe Bob Bryant.
And hunting Plummer looked like a good way to get rich quick.
As the local vigilantes exposed him as leader of the bandit.
And put a generous price on his head.
Plummer rallied his gang to plunder one last gold mine before making their escape.
And that's where I thought I'd find him.
This way.
People are going to be upset about it.
I got points for it.
Hold on.
This is like secrets.
How far can I go?
You're leaving the story.
Look, okay.
Red Dead was really fun.
But I would love a current gen western shooter.
They don't really exist anymore.
Well, there's a nugget of somewhere nearby.
Take secret.
There's a bunch of shit in here too.
Cool.
A lot of weapons.
Shotgun.
What's that called?
A ranger.
I don't think I shouldn't take any of these.
Yeah, Red Dead is...
That's explosive.
Red Dead's great.
But I like being able to actually aim one-to-one shoot.
And, you know, because Red Dead in all...
I mean, Rockstar makes great video games.
But one thing that they don't really do that well is like the combat portion.
Because when you just hold down left trigger, you just...
And you just have to...
It just auto attaches to people.
I know you can turn it off, but it's kind of detrimental to your experience.
And you're like, yeah, well, what about PC?
That game...
Is that game ever going to even release on PC?
Yeah, and you can just turn it off.
But like the game...
The game's a kind of nature.
It's there, but it's not smooth.
Yeah, it exists.
It does exist.
What is it?
Where the fuck were you?
The game is clearly intended for auto-aim, so without it, it's even worse.
Yeah, to an extent.
It is like hard to turn that off and aim with a controller.
Especially with how some people's heads just kind of poke up and...
Can be...
It's not very smooth.
Secrets.
I gotta go that way.
What about over here?
I don't think so.
Secret?
Well...
I knew that dynamite wasn't mine.
So I decided the polite thing would be to return it.
I mean, this is the shitload of it, so why not just take a munch and play with it?
It was the biggest gold rush since Sutter's mill in 48.
Unfortunately, prospectors weren't the only ones drawn to those riches.
He's like, hey!
Fuck you, don't do that.
Anybody else?
Those that ran with Plumber.
They're folks I knew from town.
Greed and easy pickings.
Try shooting...
Oh god.
James, who worked in the stable.
I'm in Jeremiah Barber, the butcher's son.
These are people that you should follow.
He's giving you his list of like other streamer friends.
Four various citizens with a double life.
Of course, they're all in the bloody fields of Shiloh and Antietam.
Oh fuck.
Not good.
That son of a bitch pretended to be tough while stealing them blind with the hug.
He set up a defensive perimeter which I had no idea how to breach.
He was a desperate individual.
In way, I was damn stubborn and stupid to realize.
Panics for a second.
That's the kind of death we've seen as there were barrels of gunpowder.
What was that?
I thought I was some kind of hero.
Okay.
I finally made it past and headed on to meet my destiny.
All right, so is there a person over there?
No.
But first, I had something I needed to figure out.
Uh oh.
A puzzle.
I had a few ideas on how to get into that mine.
Once I made my decision, I knew there was no turning back.
So my first thought was to enter the nearest mine portal.
I saw an entrance.
I feel like he's telling the story, but he has a big whiteboard.
The quickest way in.
And he's drawing all this for them.
More dangerous.
And he races as he goes, actually over this way.
Enemy pickets posted along the way.
You can't beat the innocents.
All right, we got what's in here.
Ranger.
Did dead guy say that?
Should I get the shotgun?
I'm gonna take a shotgun.
And then is there a secret in here somewhere?
Who the fuck is shooting me?
Okay.
I didn't know there was a hole in the ceiling.
It's easy to get all turned around.
Do I take the ranger?
Is the ranger better than what I have?
How do you tell which one's better?
The inlets, the sick shooter has a star next to it.
That means it's better, right?
Just a powerful revolver.
Yeah, I'll stick with what I got.
That confusing maze of corridors wouldn't even be the worst of it.
Rifle.
Come on, no secret anywhere in here.
Give me the experience.
What the hell?
Hello?
They really want me to have that rifle, don't they?
But I'm not gonna take it.
Deepest hell.
A single stumble or misstep can easily end in a deadly plunge to oblivion.
Deadly pl-
So I gotta be careful.
They can't just, like, w-
E to climb.
Wait.
Okay, I gotta be careful.
Fall damage is pretty severe.
So we're gonna do something like Donkey Kong?
A nugget is somewhere nearby.
Well, where is it?
A nugget is nearby.
It's right there.
Got it.
Level up.
Okay, do I keep going through here or do I do a different tree?
I feel like I need to do a different-
Okay, this is dual-weld revolvers.
Grab two revolvers and give them hell.
Press a wheel up or three to dual-weld.
Yeah.
I mean, I kinda have to do that.
Can't play a game about cowboys and not dual-weld revolvers.
Well, I'll just take two of these.
Okay, so you just-
Bright mouse is still zoom.
All right, cool.
Let me get down here.
I pressed D-
I pressed A and it didn't-
I-
Oh, okay.
So that wasn't a quick time event where you had to-
I had to hold A.
I thought I had to just press, like, A and move out of the way.
I didn't know it was-
I thought it was a quick time event.
Nugget!
But where?
What the hell is this?
What?
No.
No, come on.
All right, good.
It's like I was inside of this wall.
Can I get up there?
Maybe- Is it down here?
That's- Why would you do that here?
Why would you do that here?
I thought-
We didn't even get to see the domino effect!
You were saying-
I- I'm saying-
I'm saying I didn't even get to see, like, the-
He's not gonna do shit.
Maybe you are.
It's gonna hit a barrel behind me.
Why are you standing on them?
You're just gonna kill us all.
Where the fuck did he go?
Okay.
Did he blend in camouflage with the game?
I- Did I not see him?
How did I- I- I- I'm fucking blind.
I have to be.
Murderer.
Eat shit.
Okay.
There it is.
It's in here.
Okay.
So now that I'm not out there, we can do it.
So you gotta- So you gotta run.
I get it.
Could've been secret.
Am I supposed to jump off?
What the fuck?
Wait, what happened?
What did I do wrong?
Oh, that's scripted.
Scripted.
That didn't happen.
For him to have just been, like, drinking fucking Nyquil again.
I was gonna say this, no way.
Why is he saying that?
I can't tell what's scripted and what's not scripted.
I just hit my face on that board.
My entire front row of teeth are gone.
Implying this guy had any front teeth.
When am I gonna change the FOV?
I tried to do it before and it didn't work.
So when I take my pee break here after this level,
I'm gonna try to do it again.
A choice.
Is this an elevator?
Nugget.
The elevator's boring.
No, the elevator's boring.
I'm climbing the ladder.
Do I have to race this thing?
There's the- I told you this was a good idea.
Do I have to beat this?
How is a ladder less boring?
I don't know, at least I don't have to-
Who's shooting me?
Do you see anybody here?
Oh, they're already up there.
They took the elevator, okay.
I just fucked up my accuracy for the whole level.
God damn it, but I had to do that.
All right, let's take the elevator back down.
That wasn't even a cool choice.
It was just walk or don't walk.
Ferris wheel, okay.
Uh oh.
I don't care about accuracy anymore.
I don't have my rifle.
Oh, Nevada?
I've been there before.
Okay, so find Henry Plummer.
Is that him?
Can I jump over this?
I guess.
There might be a secret down here.
Oh, shit.
So there's Mr. Plummer.
He's dynamite enthusiast.
I got four to four.
Oh, okay, cool.
What?
Did somebody stab me?
Did I step on a fucking bear trap?
What the fuck?
No, don't kill me, please.
It's gonna get him.
Where's the dynamite?
I threw dynamite.
Nice.
I can't see.
Oh, no.
Okay, don't.
I need that rifle.
I don't have the rifle.
No dual welding.
And no like fucking comedy throws.
Where is he?
Oh, shit.
No, this is the...
Okay, I'm starting at the second phase.
He's back.
Shit, there he is.
Oh my god, he's throwing my...
Jesus Christ.
What?
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
I'm trying to shoot them.
Where's the...
Is this another person shooting me?
No, no.
Which way is it going?
Oh, god.
Oh, my god.
What's doing that?
Holy shit.
Is he throwing three at a time?
Who the fuck is shooting me?
I'm swear to god.
It's this guy.
Jesus.
Oh, this is it.
I didn't hit him.
Fuck.
Oh, why do I have the shotgun?
If I had my rifle, this would be...
Can I get you?
Oh, you're too far away.
Why do I even have this thing?
I said no to the rifle and took the shotgun.
I'm only going to use the rifle and the pistol.
I have one gun right now.
Look at this shit.
Don't let him collapse on me.
Where is he?
Where's the other guy?
There he is.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my god.
Where the fuck did he go?
Oh, shit.
This is supposed to be a chill stream.
No, it still is.
Told you I fucked up the accuracy.
Bad.
All right.
One level.
Where we going?
We can go up here.
Revolver ammo capacity increased.
100% more ammo.
Don't stop your killing frenzy so soon.
Your combo meter will stay active for longer.
Better chaining and longer combos earn more experience.
Yeah.
Hydrate, hydrate.
I'm all right.
I'm good.
I've had a drink writer.
In before everybody says coffee doesn't count.
Okay.
But you suck at combos.
Don't ever say that again.
All right.
Here's what I'm going to go.
I'm going to go grab another water.
Even though there was never a water here.
It was coffee.
I'm going to grab a coffee and a water.
I'm going to try to fix the FOV thing again.
So we'll do our first little pee break.
So I'm going to try to go very fast
so I can sprint back up here
to be able to fix, to try to get this done.
I'm going to like flat foot run.
John Wesley Harden.
So that's where I went.
We're in Kansas.
This game's really fun though.
I like it a lot.
No reason.
Was Harden as fast as Ringo?
Ringo was fast.
But John Wesley was as fast as the devil himself.
Yeah.
I want my heel, my bottom,
and my toes to hit the ground at the same time.
So it's like.
So like, you know, I'll give you an example like
but times 50.
All right.
I'm going to get here.
I'm going to exit the game.
I'll be right back.
One second here.
All right.
I'll be right back.
Get some water
and I'm going to run as fast as I can back here.
Exit game.
All right.
Let me try this one more time.
Somebody was linking stuff.
What were you linking?
There it is.
Okay.
Go to the configuration file.
Would you look at that?
I might be able to do this for a second before I leave.
Local data.
How come I can't get into this folder now?
It's percent.
Local data percent, right?
What did I do?
What the fuck did I do?
Local app data, right?
Okay.
Go get yourself something to drink.
I'll be right back.
See you in.
I'm just going to sprint.
See you in a minute.
So quick question.
I'm still here.
Just getting this done.
So this video file, when I opened it again,
the changes I made were gone.
Okay.
So the things that I put in on opening after closing the game are gone.
Should I make this read only?
And yeah, I'm going to have to make the video file,
this file here actually read only, right?
Okay.
All right, cool.
Did you know?
No, I saved it.
I saved it like three times.
Just make sure it's...
Now this should work.
I did everything I should from the...
Post the fight to Twitter.
I will once the Pikachu socks come in.
Next week or something.
All right, let me just make sure it's read only.
It is FOB 90, disable screen border, render viewpoint.
So that's all activated now.
Should be all saved.
All right.
Now I'm actually going to go pee.
So I'll be right back.
All right.
Let's try this again.
Open that.
Okay.
All right, cross your fingers.
Let's hope this works.
It's going to be a little loud too.
I can't really change it
because there's no windowed full screen in this game.
So loud incoming, prepare your ears.
All right, come on.
Take off the FOB.
Take off the border.
Damn it.
Why?
Come on, this is just here, right?
It's just in the first menu.
I made it read only.
I added the three things to the bottom.
I saved it.
Come on, do it.
Yes.
Oh, I feel like I can breathe.
I'm dead.
All right.
I was wine in a can.
No, it's a pineapple juice.
Oh, it went the other way this time.
Didn't hit him.
Come on.
Do I have another gun?
Oh, I have a rifle.
Come on.
None of those hit anybody.
You got to be shitting me.
I'm not going to take it.
Why ever take anything besides these two guns?
You know what I'm saying?
Like these are the best.
This is the only two guns you should have.
Nugget?
On the wall?
No.
Oh, a hundred bucks.
Oh god, this is going to be another one.
Big bets.
Fine harden.
I didn't get the...
I'm annoyed that I didn't get the secret.
All right, let's see.
Let me get like a times five.
Stay out here.
Keep it watched like this.
No worries.
They didn't ask there.
Damn it.
They knew.
Most of them.
Anybody else?
I had to spill a lot of blood.
That was a colatin.
It wasn't in that can.
All right, what's in here?
He was carousing in town with his closest friend.
Arden's boys apparently didn't want me to reach the bull's head.
They keep trying to give me what's...
I don't want that stuff.
To inform their hefe of my unwelcomed presence.
I definitely want that.
All right.
That's my close range.
This is my long range.
Jerma, can you pretend this is 50 dollars?
Thanks, man.
Pretend this game is 50 dollars?
I think this game's like six bucks.
Why would I pretend it's more money?
Hello?
Where?
I don't think this was supposed to be up here.
Jerma, come on.
Wait, what?
Bits?
Was it...
Oh, bit...
Hold.
My streamlabs is not even updated.
Hold on.
Hold on a second.
Oh, gee.
Amscoots gave 50 bucks.
No, that was yesterday.
Okay, hold on.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
I get it.
I understand now.
Do you get...
I get it.
There's the...
Not the game.
The bits.
Pretend the bits...
Can you pretend this is 50 bucks?
I was saying...
Thank you.
Wait, what the fuck are you talking about?
That's double digit IQ.
No, it's called...
I'm paying attention to the game.
And I look over and I see...
Pretend this is 50 bucks.
I got a triple digit IQ.
I already told you what it was.
126 with a few deductions.
It was 126 and I got the 18 points deducted
because I ripped the page in half
and said, you can't.
I'm not doing it.
And then it was minus 10 points
because I fell asleep during the test.
And I steeled myself for the fight ahead
for as good as I was.
Deep down I wondered if John Wesley
wasn't just a little bit better.
And then I got plus 8 points
because I got one question right
that nobody else did.
So they were like, Jesus,
we've got to get some extra points here.
It was...
What was Abraham Lincoln's wife's name?
I don't know why.
I'm the only person, I guess,
in the country that knew what that was.
Minus 10 points for trying to stream the test.
Why are none of these hitting?
Okay.
I was in Q mode.
That's absolute bullshit.
It's not bad aim.
Game is not even...
It's like fucking a bug in the game.
It's like a game bug problem, you know?
It's not my problem.
It's a game code bug fucking issue.
Like, what's with that code?
Watch this code.
Unbelievable.
Like, bracket stop.
Bracket close.
C, line one.
Like, fuck you.
You know what I mean?
Watch this.
What was that?
Oh, yeah.
Bracket if.
Stop.
Bracket close.
Hyphen.
Semicolon.
Then, entity A.
Bracket close.
Stop.
New bracket.
Thank God that was a code that worked.
Okay.
I've got to stop fucking around.
Does German know that IQ tests aren't written tests?
There's some written portions.
You've got to remember numbers sequences.
You have to...
Uh, you have to like move blocks around and create pictures with blocks.
I did one.
They take like six hours.
I've done it twice.
Guys, an IQ test is not as simple as going to like iqtest.com and it takes 30 minutes.
No, no, no.
It takes like fucking all day.
My God.
Like, just enlightened on another level I am.
See?
Let's see.
What have we got?
You did it twice so you can add the numbers together.
That's not how it works.
Uh, let's see.
Fast revolver reload.
Let's, let me look at the other one.
Fast aiming.
Throw, shoot the dynamite.
Create a nice fireworks display and do some damage as well.
After you throw a stick of dynamite, you can easily shoot it from the hip
as the crosshair of your gun will get sticky to it.
Huh, that's cool.
Dual-weld IQ tests.
Just hold them up in the air.
Look at how much smarter I am than you.
What's this one?
Headhunter.
More concentration for headshots.
Make some headshots to increase your focus.
Oh yeah, I want that.
I want this next.
You say you have high IQ, but you're a streamer.
What does, I, I don't know.
Okay.
Is it, is it like a sample size of streamers that are just like dopes or something?
I don't understand what that means.
How many channels alive right now?
Hey, it's real easy to take like the high ground.
I'm so smart.
I'm smarter than the streamer.
Are you though?
Are you telling?
How do you calculate that?
How do you know that?
Well, I know this because you didn't get a headshot on that guy behind you
and you died there.
That's why I know I'm just, I'm so much smarter than you.
What?
I don't know what's erection.
I couldn't see through the chain link fence.
Didn't you know that reaction times and hand-eye coordination is intelligence?
What are you talking about?
Dude, I, dude, it's like throwing fucking ketchup in my eyes.
I can't even see that.
Like squeezing blood in my face.
God damn.
I can't see shit.
If you get shot, all of a sudden the whole world goes blank
and there's 10 people in a circle around you.
What?
This shit, that shit's just not going to happen.
Like everything is made out of these fucking whole fences.
If you're so smart, what's a hundred times two?
I have no idea.
It's one times two, then you carry the two zeros.
I don't know.
Math does not equal intelligence.
How good you are with numbers and math is not intelligence.
It's being able to add things and subtract things together
and times them and shit.
I'd need my own if I was ever to defeat him.
Was he just stand there?
This is freaking me out.
Why is he just sitting there like this?
Am I fighting a cardboard cutout or is the guy behind me?
I'm sure of it.
Oh God, this is like a fucking wet sock.
Why would you put that in item?
No shit, I didn't want to do that.
I clicked it accidentally.
I actually clicked it accidentally.
I feel like I'm tied up right now.
What?
I tried dodge.
I'm done.
This is the one.
Did I get him?
It's scripted.
I can't kill.
Some restless Avenger took his life, shot him in the back, just like this one.
Anybody up for another beer?
That was supposed to have no skills.
Intelligence.
I get news for you.
Everyone's fucking dumb.
Some say revenge is a dish best served cold.
So whatever happened to that Bob guy?
Personally, I'd like to hear some of your other adventures.
Like, I don't know.
Do you ever go toe-to-toe with a red man?
There's only been like eight smart people to ever live.
They call it the enlightened eight.
I remember once I was after this renegade batchie.
Strangely enough, revenge was also his primary motivation.
Who are they?
I said, look, look, I'm reading the story.
Ben Franklin.
Um, Stephen Hawking.
Gray Wolf was a Chiricahua Apache medicine man who had led a war party in revenge for
a massacre against his people.
Albert Einstein.
The U.S. Army had attacked his tribe during his daughter's sacred sunrise.
The Heinz ketchup lady.
The slaughter was unspeakable.
I understood his anger, as there's nothing more traumatic than seeing those...
Who's the guy that invented the washing machine?
...cruel and painful death.
No, not Mr...
Not John Maytag.
All right, so you got...
That's, that's four.
That's enough.
I don't know.
Uh, Dr. Dre.
Uh, um, Dr. Ocher.
Two doctors on that list.
Dr. Pepper.
They all gotta be doctors.
Oh, fuck, I'm going the wrong way.
Dr. Doom.
Yeah, there's gotta be a fictional doctor on that list.
That's true.
Dr. Octopus Doll.
Dr. House.
All right, that's like 11.
That's enough, I think.
Are you implying that Dr. Pepper isn't real?
Dr. Pepper is 78 ingredients.
78 different people.
Guys, Dr. Pepper is like Satoshi Nakamoto.
It's like 30 people that made one product, one beverage.
It's like Shakespeare.
He led a band of young Apache warriors who wanted retribution.
That's a myth.
Well, you, we don't...
I don't know.
You don't know.
Oh, do you know?
You don't know?
Stop, stop.
I just, I'm just playing.
Stop it.
Who?
Did you say the turkeys were endangered?
What was that guy doing?
What?
Ooh, hey, what line of sight do you have?
Oh, I see.
The bullshit one.
Oh, he was busy.
He was inventing the what?
All right, I'm not gonna be one of those people
that just gets like really mad at like,
the fact that I didn't get any hit registration there.
Where?
Ah, all right.
Ah, I don't have to say anything.
I'll have to go is...
Ah, I already have that.
Where's it going?
Where is he?
Who's left?
Is that it?
I think that's it.
Any more game refueled?
All right.
It didn't work.
It's supposed to work.
Come on.
What?
No.
Will you tell me that drinking powdered sugar
and powdered vitamins like B2 and B12
is not going to give me superpowers?
With like orange creamsicle flavoring?
What?
No.
Okay, hold on.
Hold on.
You guys mean to tell me that glorified Kool-Aid
is not going to make me a better gamer?
What?
You need those acai berries.
A deep crevice that led to a...
Holy shit, that scared me.
Yeah, but it's not very so much cousin.
How do you feel about brain fluid?
I mean, it hurts if you drink it, but
I think that's because it's too acidic.
Why does he know that?
Okay, that scared the shit...
I thought the rock was fucking alive.
It was weird.
It was like glitching out and fucking coming at me.
Search the caves.
We got ourselves a search mission.
All right.
I want to get times like five here.
Ready?
One, two, three.
There it is.
Times four.
It didn't happen this time.
High IQ streamer scared by beehive.
That's what I thought that was for a second.
Really?
I thought they were going to come forward.
Damn.
I hope they get you.
Come on.
Really?
Be nicer to me.
Oh, secret.
No level up though.
That's pissing me off.
No level up.
It's like really fucking pissing me off now.
That wasn't a headshot.
It's like, you know, it's like fucking pissing me off now.
Played red steel too.
I know you have a Wii, you casual fuck.
That's like pissing me off.
Relax, man.
Like that's fucking pissing me off.
Just code happiness into the game.
Happiness is pissing me off.
Don't fucking be happy right now.
I don't want you.
That's makes...
I don't know.
Whatever.
Let's just go.
He was haunted with dead Indian ghosts.
You're pissing me off.
Or concerned with the live ones than the dead ones.
Smiler?
What?
No, I got such a good hit rating going right now.
Don't fuck it up because you pressed the wrong button.
Keep the streak.
It's all about the streak right now.
Come on.
Five.
Six.
Oh, that's all that's here.
They were sisters.
Religion is traditional among the Mescalero.
So what happened?
I had to get out of there.
Those girls never shut up.
Both of them nagging at me all the time.
Drove me half crazy.
Haven't seen them since.
No, I mean what happened with Grey Wolf?
Oh.
I pursued him into a cave of death.
Secret.
Now I gotta level up.
Okay.
Streamer, you're grinding my gears.
It's okay.
I wanted to headhunter, right?
Yeah.
None can hide.
Hints about enemies behind you spot enemies even beyond your field of view
during concentration.
Marcus on the edge of the screen will point at every enemy nearby.
Every nearby enemy that you would not normally see.
And then we get the golden rifle.
I want that.
We're gonna go fast.
Full fast tech tree and golden rifle.
Can you get a talent to make it so that you can actually aim?
I mean, is that like supposed to be funny?
Was that supposed to be a funny joke?
I didn't think it was very funny.
Carry great darkness in your heart.
If you do not release it, it will claim your soul.
The sound of his voice put some kind of ancient Indian spell on me.
What's going on?
Has his story unfolded in my mind?
You will come to this place again and kill many more men.
And the darkness will grow until it consumes everything.
No, this is a good way to get to like plus 10 or 20.
He said I was a great warrior.
A pile of unequal will face warriors.
Shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot!
My combo, my combo, my combo!
Snakes will bite shadows.
Definitely snakes.
And indeed, his warrior surrounded me and attacked me like hungry wolves.
Well, that was, that was not cool.
All right, you just, you broke my concentration.
Anybody else?
Is that it?
Did I shoot him in the eyelash?
Anyway, out of this trap, but suddenly one just appeared.
Come here.
Well, I got to level up.
Right here.
Yeah, this is good.
Okay, then we get executioner.
So I can spot enemies even beyond my field of view.
It'll just show me where people are.
Oh, wow.
Cheating game is now easy.
There's nobody here.
Oh, no, nevermind.
I'll take the ammo, though.
Dermot, are you joking?
I mean, I saw the like, okay, I look, I just pressed the level up button and
all of a sudden I saw like two or three stars pop up.
He never jokes.
Very serious streamer.
I hit, I pressed the button.
What was wrong with that?
Oh, chase.
He can't reach it.
I hit every single one of those shots.
What?
Wait, where the hell were you?
It's really pissing me off.
It's pissing me off.
Is that the one thing I'm going to repeat 100 times today?
Probably.
Where the fuck are you?
Where's this magic person?
Boss fight.
I, okay, I just put my head, I scratched my fucking face.
This is sometimes why I want the face cam.
So you guys can see like my proof.
I don't know, I don't know where he is.
I don't know where I, I don't.
Where are you?
What the fuck is you?
Jesus.
Okay.
Come on.
I'm getting deja vu.
Is he getting deja vu?
You have to, yeah, don't you have to like break the cycle?
So go, like go pee or something.
Go pee, pee and like shake your face a little bit
and then put some water in your face
and you'll like wake up in the real world.
Was I supposed to do something there?
Was I supposed to, I don't think I was supposed to do something.
No, throw some water in your face.
Do exactly what you do in the deja vu.
You can predict the future.
Have you ever played a first person shooter before?
I'm doing just fine, 63%.
You sound like all those headshots.
What are you talking about?
Why do you guys act like I'm from the 1800s?
This is the first time I've ever seen a movie.
You should play bullet storm.
Yeah, bullet storm looks really fun.
I played it for a little while, not very long.
Two banks at the same time?
Bullet storm is a great, it'll be a great stream.
Yeah, I like these cool stylish shooters.
What is this I see in front of me?
Magic?
I don't think it, I'm very comfortable here
seeing as the magic that's playing out in front of me.
I've never been here before.
I've never seen such a thing before.
Witchcraft, I say.
A moving picture that one can control.
No, no, no, no.
I've never heard of such a thing.
Burn it.
The brothers paid dearly for their stupidity,
but everybody knows they had it coming.
There's more to it than that.
I read all about it, so I know for a fact
that it went down very differently.
First of all, it was high noon.
A posse of U.S. deputy marshals were on the rooftop.
U.S. deputy marshals.
True thing.
Get into it.
Level up the hole in the daltons for the months.
Now they finally had them dead to rights.
Among them was a bounty hunter feared by marshals
trying to get the daltons to surrender.
This battle for the brothers was far too crowded.
Come on, somebody else come out.
Please.
No, sorry.
Back of the bank.
He saw a way to get an expect from behind.
In the back, behind the bank.
But they might be a secret.
No, no, no, no.
Really?
Come on, there's no secret here.
Oh well.
A steep ladder, laughing at danger as he did.
Bulletstorm is the most generic shooter ever created.
Jesus.
I made it.
More and more.
You know, a speedrun of this game would be really cool.
Just sprinting through and just racking up like times 20 or something.
Oh, I feel like I don't want any of these.
I don't.
I don't think I want any more.
Oh, he...
What?
That's not how you load those pistols.
Nugget?
In the...
I have level up, I'll do it afterwards.
Okay.
Any more?
That's it.
Keep telling the same story.
This game...
This is...
This game is so dumb, I love it.
No, that's not how it happened.
Let me tell you what did happen.
Go back.
It was Halloween.
And I was doing the fucked up shit that I usually do.
Smashing pumpkins.
What?
The leader, the lover, the loser.
Bob, Emmett, and Gratt.
I wasn't even out of the cutscene, I took a hit.
The shielder.
Well, his name was shielder.
He was the shielder.
What?
I thought he had a health bar.
Now I know what the hell is going on.
Don't let him get away.
Just run around and just backstab him.
Come on, come on, come on.
What?
Where are you?
Oh.
Dispatch the Dalton Brothers allies in here.
Secret up here, probably.
Oh, you better believe it.
It's in here, right?
Come on.
Where is it?
I keep touching it.
Secret?
God damn it, where is it?
Ah, in here?
Where the fuck is this thing?
It's downstairs?
Oh, it's right here.
Got it.
My god!
What the fuck?
Where is this guy?
My goodness.
Up here.
Is that gonna hit me?
Um, I can go underneath?
Wait, why did this turn into Donkey Kong?
I did it.
You can get up there.
I know you can.
Emmett Dalton.
Oh, why is he just walking over to me like the Terminator?
He just...
Why is he right here?
I thought maybe I could...
It gave me a cover system.
Is there another place I can run to?
Right over there.
Okay.
Itchy leg.
Ah, ow.
Go back this way.
Ow!
I just stopped...
Oh, fuck.
Please don't kill me.
Come on!
Got it.
Then we're gonna do another retelling of the story from the other side.
I got them all.
All right.
Executioner, deal some headshots without even aiming.
Pressing and holding Q will eat up all of your concentration
in exchange for marking nearby enemies for execution with perfect headshots.
The more concentration you sacrifice, the more of them will die.
So this is actually the dead eye from every...
Why is this the case?
Is there some lore or something behind
why every Western game has to have a slow down,
target everybody, and then...
That's in every single one of these.
Because it's cool.
I mean, it is cool, but it's in every single Western game.
There's nothing else we could do here?
It's a trope from the movies.
Yeah.
Well, let's do it.
And then we can get the golden rifle.
I got it.
I don't really care about these.
I'm not gonna use them.
So I got the two weapons I want,
which leads us...
Let's see what's over here.
Fast revolver reload.
Oh, I don't know.
I need to get one of these.
Silver shotgun.
We'll take a look later.
That's how the Wild West worked in real life.
That's how Billy the Kid died.
The sheriff slowed down time and blew his brains out.
Oh my God.
There it is.
Golden rifle.
Oh my God.
I love it.
Dude, it's an Australian rifle.
It is kind of an Australian rifle, isn't it?
Does it make a different noise?
I mean, it looks cool.
I'm not gonna shoot this.
I gotta change the title of this stream.
That was funny for like 30 seconds.
It was tough to stay on a true course.
So we kept an eye out for landmarks.
Okay, gotta go towards the bandanas.
I don't know what the title is, though.
It was never funny.
I thought it was funny.
We can disagree on what we think is funny.
Just name it trope.
What the fuck?
Fog and swamps hinder orientation.
The waypoint indicator is disabled.
Great.
I got a waypoint right here.
I'm gonna get ambushed in a second.
This watch.
No.
I really thought they were gonna come out of the shadows.
I'll take a secret.
Oh, there we go.
All right.
Oh, what the hell do I want to do here?
Yeah, I guess we could go up and then here for more combos.
Plus, that's just...
I can take more hits.
We'll go up here.
I got it.
I already did it.
What?
That was weird.
Okay, I'll go this way.
I was looking a little...
You know, this game is more than any...
If I look over at my other monitor,
that chat or at like streamlabs for a second,
I always time it.
So somehow I'm looking over to a different monitor
when one of these guys pops up and wants me to press S.
Okay, that's ridiculous.
That is so insane.
I don't even...
You don't have to see anybody.
I don't even have to aim at anyone.
It does it in 180 degrees.
Why would I pick up any of these, really?
Shotgunner.
Why do these guys have beat-em-up names now?
Can I not?
What's...
What the hell?
Why can I not hit Q?
Do I have to be a full bar?
I can't just slow it down at all?
Oh, there we go.
That was weird.
Okay, and...
What?
Oh my god, he has extra health.
To be seen.
Where are they coming from?
Do you guys see this?
Oh, throw...
Down here.
Blow this shit up.
That guy's giant.
Look at how huge that guy is.
Oh no, no, no.
He is.
Is he huge?
He's as big as the house.
I wasn't crazy right there, right?
That guy was gigantic.
He was...
Oh, okay, that was really weird.
He looked very big.
Let's just get in there with actual weapons, please.
That would be nice.
Just ended up falling inside.
So, how did you get out?
The barn doors was open.
About right then, I saw some suspicious characters
running through the bushes.
Of course, I followed them.
Oh, I got one of them.
That goddamn swamp was like a goddamn maze
and pretty soon, I had no goddamn idea where I was.
Dave?
Chat, you still with me?
So I just started walking and pretty soon...
I think they're getting bored of the game.
Dave?
Steve?
Indians surrounded me from all sides.
Did they?
I want to play.
Stop it.
I just wanted to make sure Steve was paying attention.
Now, where was I?
You were following through a swamp?
That's right.
See, Steve?
Dwight's paying attention.
Oh, I'm listening.
I was just resting my eyes.
Oh, was I?
Right.
See, there's a reason...
Just a bunch of old men talking.
...made up of brothers.
Being a brother is a very sacred thing.
It's a bond like no other.
So did you ever find the damn Daltons?
Not yet, but I did find a few of their cousins.
I swear to god, video games are not even good.
That guy's dynamite on his chest?
All right.
That's the way we're gonna go.
I thought I got two of them in a row.
I thought it went right through their ears.
Come on.
Quickly.
Anybody else?
Oh, shit.
That guy has a magic door.
Whoa, whoa.
Easy, easy, easy.
I got him.
I think I did it.
I wish I could grab the door.
That'd be fun.
This exact location is insecure.
There's a lady up here.
There's a guy lying down right there.
I just really...
Just talk about deja vu.
That is...
Okay, what is hitting me?
Uh-oh.
I shouldn't be up here.
I have full ammo with that gun.
That's it?
I guess I have full ammo.
I don't think I got him.
It's fun to do that, but it takes too many bullets.
Have I seen the new game about me on Steam?
Yeah, we played it on stream, actually.
We played it on stream.
Oh, fuck.
I'm dead.
Of course, the guy with the health pool is the one that I couldn't see.
He blended in with the bushes because he has like a fucking green coat on.
Where the fuck are these people?
Like, where the fuck are you?
Is this guy here?
Stop dying.
It's pissing me off.
Where's the shotgun guy?
He's like in there.
Where is he?
Look at that.
Together against anyone who would threaten him.
That was like inside of this tree.
Another boss fight, I think, coming up here.
Let's load the guns.
Oh, fuck.
I gotta change the title.
That's when I saw it.
A damn steamboat.
A steamboat?
In a swamp?
Yeah, Steve, but this wasn't much more than a wreck.
This looks like Borderlands.
That's not even...
Oh, my fucking god.
I didn't know what to do.
Yes, it floated over in the flood of 85.
Stretching.
Now, was it a stern wheeler or a sad wheeler?
What does that really make a difference, Steve?
It was a steamboat with a goddamn army on board.
It was in that a few salaud of bullets
come arraigning down small vigilantes
and cuffed those men that were shooting at me.
I saw some familiar faces.
That it?
There's probably a secret in here.
I would be shocked if there wasn't.
Where's it going?
That was odd.
Teleporting bullets.
Let's get up there.
Can I get in?
Climb?
A nugget.
Might be up top.
Yeah, it's probably on the edge.
Oh, my god.
That guy has a shotgun.
I set out to do so.
Surrender just ain't in my nature.
Plus, I'm stubborn as hell.
I mean, this is effective, too.
Don't always have to aim down sights.
You can just shoot them.
Gotta go that way.
That's why it's so goddamn fun.
It is very fun.
There are other game modes, too.
We gotta try those out.
There's dual mode.
There's arcade mode.
It's not just the story,
so there's a little bit more to see
once I complete the game.
Which I don't know exactly where I am
in the story right now, but
we'll find out, right?
Well.
After months of dogged pursuit.
Let's do it.
Oh, the double cross.
It's burning down.
I have to get out of the burning.
I'm going up.
I don't think I should be going up the stairs.
Am I gonna need to go down the stairs?
This is so dumb.
Oh, God.
I got up.
What the fuck?
All that.
We got a lot of information there very quickly.
I'm gonna get a lot of experience here.
19, 20, 22, 23.
Dude, these are like flaming hot Cheetos.
That's where I am in my combo right now.
I'm at flaming hot Cheeto level.
Come on, is that it?
33?
I think that's it.
No, this guy right here.
Oh, it's okay.
It's all right.
I got 33.
Oh, God.
How am I gonna do this?
The guy in the back?
No, no.
Did it.
Oh.
Who was the guy in the back?
I got it right.
So how do you dishonorably kill somebody?
You just shoot them without waiting for them to shoot first?
To pull first?
Yeah, okay, I see.
More combos.
I'm gonna do it again.
But hold on.
I want to see what's further down this tree.
Cold rage.
Damaging concentration.
Reload while sprinting.
That's actually really good.
Yeah, I think I want that.
I'm moving around a lot.
I'd run around all over the place.
This game looks super fun.
Is it a blast?
Yeah, it's fun.
I'm actually glad I get to play it.
Tried to play this like two years ago on stream
and then gave up on it because I couldn't get it to work.
And here we are now.
I want to get this.
So I'm gonna go down this way.
I don't want this sprinting reload.
Am I gonna change the stream title?
Yes.
After I get out of this.
Episode 7.
The Wild Bunch.
Juarez, 1868.
Couldn't lose.
I even want an old Spanish coin that had to be 100 years old.
We want ads later.
Not right now.
I was mighty pleased with myself the next morning as my brothers and I rode for Texas.
But before we crossed the border, those cowboys caught up with us.
It was Johnny Ringo, Roscoe Bob Bryant, and another asshole named Jim.
They wanted their money back and everything else we had.
Include maps, as those boys didn't want us coming for them later.
Bob put that old Spanish coin in my mouth and said,
I won't have it said that I left you with nothing, boy.
Am I gonna play Dreams with PS4?
Yeah.
I'm really excited for it, actually.
I've been looking forward to it.
The branch finally snapped under the weight of the three of us.
But being my older brothers was bigger and heavier.
They were already dead.
Right then I swore to myself that I would avenge them.
Ringo, you know, until I heard he was riding with the Wild Bunch.
I thought it was in like super, super early access.
Like you have to get invited to play it early access.
I don't know.
I thought that was the case.
I've been on their trail for months.
Ever since they left their hideout in the Bighorn Mountains.
All right.
So give me one second.
I'm going to...
I'm gonna pee.
Because I drank a bunch of fucking water.
And then I'm gonna finish this game.
It seems like I think we're almost at the end, right?
Another like three or four missions.
And then I'm gonna do the duels
and then the arcade mode play for a little while longer.
I'm gonna change the title of this stream to Juarez.
And that's the title.
Just Juarez and then like a dot.
I'm right back.
And I'm back.
Let's keep going.
I choked that up too much.
Fuck.
More beer.
It's not beer.
No, it's pineapple juice.
I'm a huge pineapple guy.
If you guys didn't know this.
Pineapple juice.
Pineapple slices.
Pineapple flavoring.
Except get that shit off pizza.
Yeah, I see you.
How are you?
Somebody heard that as they were driving by.
I think I'm really fucking mad.
I'm just kidding.
I love pineapple.
I just...
It's my favorite fruit ever.
It's better than apples.
It's better than pears.
Better than oranges.
I just don't like it on my pizza.
My...
I like pepperoni pizza.
That's it.
I don't like anything else.
I don't really, you know, meat lovers too much.
Just pepperoni.
With a flat crispy thin crust.
God damn it.
Now I want that.
You don't deserve pizza.
Jesus.
Why?
How do you...
How do you deserve pizza?
You just buy it.
Besides, I wanted Bryant all to myself.
I'd heard about a large shipment of gold
being transported to Wilcox, Wyoming
on the Overland Flyer.
I figured the Wild Bunch would likely
hit such a treasure.
And by God, I figured right.
Don't eat too much pineapple, though.
It has bromelain in it.
That's why your mouth hurts when you eat it.
No, that's real.
That's real.
They threw the bridge with the intention
of forcing the train to stop.
Well, I assume the Wild Bunch was likely
in the still intact part of the train high above.
So I had no choice but to make my way up.
This is a cool mission.
Your car is dangling down.
Pineapple eats you.
Yes, it does.
Oh, God.
Weirdly enough, yes, there's an enzyme
in pineapple that is a flesh-eating enzyme.
And it is eating your flesh
while you put it in your mouth
and in your body and stuff.
But it's actually kind of good for you.
Just don't eat too much.
Oh, okay.
So I knew I was headed in the right direction.
Did I miss a cool thing?
I just wasn't paying attention.
What?
Wait, rewind.
Tell the story again.
Somebody else tell a different version of it.
What the hell is what you say?
I had to negotiate an even more precarious route.
Oh, no.
I got shot in the head.
What the hell?
To get my ass out of there.
He's going to shoot the horse, calling it now.
Nope.
Not going to do that.
Thought I was going to do that, too.
Um, you think that's too easy for me to do that.
But like, oh, look at how crazy that is.
Are you happy?
Like, I did the stupid thing.
Limited train robbers.
Let's try to get some points here.
No.
Oh, right here.
Too busy dodging bullets to worry about falling to my death.
Odds were I was likely to die that day anyway.
Oh, god damn it.
I was determined to take down as many of those bastards as I could.
It's a little ledge.
It's tiny.
Come on, give me a break.
Who?
That was a cool move.
I didn't even do that.
He did it on his own.
Uh, do I have to go back on the outside?
This doesn't open.
I guess I can go this way.
Like shooting ducks in a shooting gallery.
Only difference is he's damn duck shot back.
Okay, they were just in the way.
I didn't even do that.
Somebody else fell on top of it with a match in their hand.
Um, secret.
All right.
All right, back around the corner and go up.
Joe, Jeff, and Tim.
Grand Posse versus the Wild Bunch.
Here it comes.
You've been waiting for this.
I had to fight the Wild Bunch all bonesome, as usual.
Oh, well that's great.
Oh, one dead.
Okay, another Wild Boy.
All the Wild Boys dead.
Wouldn't even that hard.
It was actually pretty easy.
Nugget.
Where?
On the outside of the train maybe?
I don't know.
Outside, left, right, down, up.
Whoa, he's alive.
Right next to me.
It's inside the...
That was...
They made that really easy to find that.
What was that?
Chase the Wild Bunch.
Does that have money?
Points given to me.
I want more levels.
Um, was it...
They're in...
Okay, I can't...
Get off it, get off.
Just get off it and hide.
What a stupid fucking idea that was.
That was the dumbest idea I've ever had.
Duck?
Determined to finally have my justice.
But the only survivor who welcomed me was George Flatnose Curry.
Who was he?
The fastest gun in the gang.
Great.
Right after Sundance, I mean.
And Kid Curry.
And maybe Elsie Lay.
Though some folks might dispute that.
Uh, you gonna go for it?
Who's gonna go for it?
I shot that fucking ground.
He stops right here for a second
so I can get a good focus right here.
This is gonna be bad.
I've already fucked it up but I think I can still get it.
I shot him!
I shot him right in the...
Does he have a bulletproof vest on?
What the fuck was that?
This is gonna be it.
What happened there?
As long as I stay above 50%.
That means I had the majority of accuracy, right?
All right.
I tried to find Bob, Brian, but it was as if he'd disappeared.
Sometime later, I heard The Wild Back together.
Kid Curry escaped from jail and now he was running the whole shebang.
So I took to their trail.
I like how it still does the story.
I was still in pursuit of my brother's killer and hoped that he was back with him.
Now what did I want to do here?
What did I actually want to do?
It was over here, right?
Oh, there I am.
Sprinting reload.
Okay.
Got.
Reload.
How many other?
All right.
I'm gonna get one, two, three, four.
The barrel's not a person.
Just in case you were wondering.
At least I got...
Because there was might have been a guy hiding in the barrel.
That would be possible, right?
Kid Curry.
I could sense him close by, however.
Not in some nasty.
I just needed a clue as to their whereabouts.
Clues?
Find clues as to the whereabouts of the...
How about the map that they drew?
I found one.
This time they were fixing to blow up a train trestle.
Property of the Union Pacific.
Indicated how they were fixing to undermine several of the weakest wooden support.
This isn't another game.
What game is this in?
Kid Curry was considered the wild in the Wild Bunch.
It was said that he fathered 85 bastard children.
Though some say it was only five.
Gun.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
What happened to my weapons?
Why did it take...
It took away my cool weapons and gave me shitty ones.
All right.
Prevent them from blowing it up.
I'll do my best.
Did I have a beep gun?
I don't remember.
Did I?
I don't think so.
Kid Curry had bragged to a whore
how he was going to rob a train heading to the U.S. Mint in Denver.
And that whore, Fat Sally, she told me.
The bridge was rigged with dynamite.
So I decided I best be careful confronting those bastards.
One misplaced shot and that could easily have happened.
That wasn't like for a joke or anything.
I just wanted to see if it actually did that.
I didn't know if that was just like a joke for like...
Okay, you can disarm them.
I didn't know.
I just was seeing if it actually did.
...to remove any dynamite that I came across.
Or I saw a ladder that somehow had escaped my attention.
Don't you blow us up now.
Don't worry, I know...
No, don't do that.
It's going to take us all out.
Okay, I got to be careful.
Disarm, right?
Disarm.
Why can I not disarm?
That's what I'm saying is what I'm trying to do.
Once that was done, I figured I'd find...
Load, load, load, load, load, load.
Oh, right in the face.
Don't, don't blow up.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, God, did I blow it up?
Don't blow things up.
That's bad.
Armored shotgunner.
That's...
Did they get him?
That was scary.
Oh, God.
We have community subs just coming.
Jerma's average dong gave...
How was it?
10? 20?
How many?
I didn't see it.
Pixel Mike, five community subs.
Jerma's average dong.
Ten community subs.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you for the community subs.
You guys are awesome.
He said it.
Yes, he did.
Let's get me a new gun.
Increased range and piercing power.
It's now easier to hit what you're aiming at
and look good while you're doing it.
Be quick as greased lightning.
You'll be able to move and run 50% faster.
Let's get it.
So it's an engraved ranger.
So it's 25% range.
So it's better range, less recoil.
What's the other one?
This is faster fire rate and faster aim speed.
No, I don't have it.
Okay, well, let's shoot the rope.
No, I didn't get it all.
Oh, what?
That guy was just wood in my brain.
You should mention that.
Actually, there was a fourth charge impeding my progress.
Is that the last guy?
Once I removed it, my path was...
Ah, come on.
He was standing still.
What the fuck?
I thought I shot him twice.
I don't want these quick shooters.
They're terrible.
Don't blow those up.
Bad move, Jeremy.
Bad move.
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Whoa.
The upgraded quick shooters are OP.
Are they?
Find an alternate path to reach the other part of the overpass.
Let's go.
Nugget.
Where the hell is it?
I think it's above me.
This place is cool, but I kind of want to get out of fucking Blighttown.
Where is it?
Is it down here?
Where's this thing?
It's right there.
Shit.
All right.
How do I get that?
It's right there.
All right.
I gotta go up and then down.
Good.
All right.
Find an alternate route.
So we gotta go that way.
So how do I get to there?
Can I just go down?
What happens if I go down?
Wait a minute.
I'm just gonna run over here.
I found a cave, and as I made my way back to the bridge,
I saw something that concerned me.
Oh, God.
Jerma's average size dong.
Five community subs.
Five?
It was too funny.
Five.
What's happening?
Chase and extinguish the fuse?
Thank you for the 20 community subs.
I really appreciate it.
Where's the fuse?
That just fucking scared the shit out of me.
But thank you.
For the 20 community subs.
Nugget?
Somewhere.
It's right there.
Okay.
Can I get up?
He's shooting the fuse.
I was trying to extinguish.
What?
Tell us!
Okay.
Thank you.
Of course, I was successful,
or clearly I wouldn't be talking to you folks here today.
Naturally, I removed the last-
It was a touchy reunion.
What?
Did somebody just cut off my story?
Did somebody come into the bar
and grab a glass and sit down
and start telling their side?
This time, I was thoroughly exhausted
and dragging my ass
as I was not a young man anymore.
I walked off accidentally.
I didn't press space.
Thank God the game knows I'm stupid.
Ah, that's right.
I forgot the nugget.
Oh, well.
It's okay.
It's all right.
Kill that idiot!
Or more precisely, they found me.
Oh, right.
My body was just moving around
in such weird directions.
All right.
Let me just chill for a sec.
What?
Why do those guys die?
He's not going for the 100% run.
No, I'm not going for the 100%.
Just when I thought things couldn't get worse.
I'm going for any percent.
When Kid Curry opened up,
it was hidden in this tunnel
and pretty well shielded.
Oh.
There's Kid Curry.
Well, he has a great line of sight.
Jeez.
All right.
There he is.
I'm trying to shoot through the hole.
I don't think that's going to work.
It's going to have to get close.
Shoot.
Right down there.
Dynamite.
There's apparently a...
There's a nugget somewhere over here.
Probably in the wagon.
Is that far enough?
That's not far enough.
I got to go...
I got to run in,
throw the ball and then run back.
That's all the damage that did.
It hurts.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
What?
I...
Is this guy real?
Oh, I'm so upset by that one.
Fuck you.
Get out of here.
Why would you set him up running straight at me?
Whoa, he fucking...
Jesus.
What?
Where'd he go?
What the fuck is it?
My fucking God.
Oh, come on.
Whatever.
I know.
Here comes the guy.
He's going to sprint over here.
Oh, God.
That's not good.
Is he still alive?
He's not still alive, right?
Okay.
Here we go.
Got him.
That's when I met Kid Curry himself.
Let's go.
Duel.
He decided to stop pussyfooting around and deal with me personally.
This is gonna hurt.
Get that speed up.
This guy's dead.
Shit.
Because he was.
I was just a bit faster.
And as he lay wounded, I demanded to know the whereabouts of Roscoe Bob Bryant.
He shouted at me.
He pointed the gun at me.
You know what this is about?
Bob went with Butch in Sundance in South America.
You ain't never finding him.
Good thing I was paying attention and not looking at chat.
Imagine letting that guy shoot you.
East down south.
You bastard.
You'll never find him.
Thanks for the info.
Headshot.
71 percent.
So, in South America.
Yeah, you kinda glossed over that one.
Well, I found Jim.
Not long after my showdown with Ringo.
At the time, he was riding with the James Younger gang.
This guy has a lot of stories.
Don't you have to think about stuff like this?
My life is not even 1 percent as interesting as this guy's.
The coolest story I have is one time I got two double cheeseburgers when I ordered one.
I'll tell you a story about the extra couple nuggets I got.
They just put like more fries in the bag.
Meanwhile, they forget my fries four times.
This is the new gun.
I didn't hit the guy right here.
This is the new one.
Yeah, engraved ranger.
Another train mission.
Oh god.
I just crouched and I took the shotgun right in the face.
Trying to duck from a shotgun.
That's not gonna happen.
I'm gonna get like 20 points here.
See if I can get it.
Damn it.
It's hard to string it together in these missions.
Jesse James.
There we go.
Legend was he could stop a train with his bare hands by staring it down.
Jesse James.
They're behind me?
Decimated after that little fiasco they had in Northfield, Minnesota.
So Jesse needed more men and took on the killer I was after along with a host of others.
I almost forgot.
Okay, this is done.
I can lead into here.
Improve damage and concentration.
Just focus to do even more damage.
All you bullet shot and concentration.
Yeah, but 50% more of the headshot is they're dead.
They already were dead.
All they do are headshots.
But it doesn't really matter.
More concentration in the bar.
That's actually good.
And then dynamite looting.
Nah, the explosive stuff really not really doing for me.
Extra damage on combos.
Yeah, let's go up this way.
Nugget somewhere.
No, they were the most famous outlaw gang ever.
And you took them all on by your lonesome.
Again, I'm finding this all a little hard to swallow.
Maybe you need to wash it down with some whiskey.
By the way, did I mention that that train was destroyed?
Come on, more.
Damn it.
Air burst.
Nugget.
Oh, God.
I thought I heard the nugget sound.
Am I going to go take a piss?
Certainly I have an urgent need to drain my one-eyed snake.
Well, I've had a few drinks and I've been sitting here for quite a spell.
Right through there.
Let me show you.
Again.
See, he pees just as much as I do.
I've never heard so much malarkey in my life.
You think he's bullshit enough?
You don't think he's Silas Greaves?
I think he's just some old drunk looking for some free liquor.
Up?
There are no enemies.
I have to tell the story so enemies can show up.
I'm just in a giant loop.
I think I met Jesse James.
Boy, you got to be kidding me.
That story makes no sense at all.
I mean, you got to be too brick short of a load to believe that story.
I don't agree.
Jack, lay off the ball.
You seriously think that tired old man went with Jesse James?
I have to break the cycle?
It was a rickety ride and quite precarious.
That worked.
I got a wisdom.
I have to pee line.
Heard so much malarkey in my life.
You think he's bullshit enough?
You don't think he's Silas Greaves?
I think he's just some old drunk looking for some free liquor.
But where is this story coming from?
I'm not telling this portion.
You don't think you met Jesse James?
Boy, you got to be kidding me.
That story makes no sense at all.
You got to be too brick short of a load to believe that cock and bull story.
I don't agree.
Jack, lay off the ball.
You seriously think that tired old man went toe to toe with Jesse James?
Well, that's better.
What?
Did I mention that this Jim was married to the infamous Bell Star?
Of course, I didn't learn that until anyway.
That went really, really fast.
He didn't even have a chance to come back.
He didn't pull his pants up.
He's sitting here with his pants around his ankles.
Hope I don't have to do the whole thing again.
Thank God.
It was definitely safer on the inside of the train.
I am on the...
I don't understand.
That wasn't the inside of the train?
Did I fall off?
I don't think that's weird.
I just got shot right in the face.
He's doing so many animations that I couldn't shoot him.
Can't believe what just happened.
I didn't even get outplayed.
Outplayed?
No, I think he shot me off the train.
Where the fuck am I right now?
What is happening?
Didn't have to go.
It wasn't like this before.
Was it?
Did this happen?
What did it just...
What did it put me?
This is not where the...
Okay.
Why did it put me there?
Did it like skip me ahead?
Yeah, it put me ahead.
That was weird.
It just like sat...
Hey, go this way.
Remember how you died twice?
Can you get like the mud off your face?
What the fuck is going on?
Where's this Gatling?
I was attacked by some asshole on a Gatling gun.
Another one of these.
Where's this nugget?
Can I climb up?
Yes, I did.
I took it out.
I don't think I can get that.
We're dynamite.
Does it really matter, Jack?
You're messing with the flow of the story here.
Got it.
Oh, Jesus.
I'm just gonna stay down.
That didn't hit him?
That looked like it hit him.
What?
Wasn't he done...
He was done shooting.
He was in the middle of...
What the fuck?
He was done shooting.
I just instantly died.
All right, you can stop any second now.
I'm gonna get up to there.
That was a lot.
No, I'm just gonna do it this way.
He's dead.
What the fuck?
Oh!
D-d-d-d-d-d-d-d!
I'm gonna...
Okay, move now.
D-d-d-d-d-d!
Will you fu...
Just stop shooting!
Why did that do so little damage?
I was gonna shoot him in the fucking head.
Dumbest thing.
Now it's my turn.
This is...
These are just like meat boy replays of me coming at that guy.
Remember when I did that?
Oh, that was crazy.
This is a hard level.
Is that it?
Oh, I got...
Jim!
Jim, you on the train?
This happened already.
Didn't we do this already?
The same exact scenario with the armored shotgun guy behind the veil...
And the nugget.
Uh...
Right?
This happened already.
Am I supposed to be doing something here?
What?
Wait.
It just took all my juice.
Jesse James!
Again?
Oh, right.
We rewound and did the whole thing again.
Actually, I...
Okay, okay.
Right, right, right.
Do I walk over here?
I have to walk through this?
No.
I almost just walked and died.
Good.
You had a showdown with Jesse James?
Of course he didn't.
Everybody knows that Jesse was killed by Bob Ford.
Yeah.
Jesse went out like John Wesley Harden,
but shot him in the back of the head.
Yes, it doesn't matter how far you run, does it, man?
Ast always catches up with you.
This shit's moving around all over the place.
Holy shit, you are awful.
Yeah, I killed Jesse James.
Just wounded him bad enough to convince him to hang up his guns.
What about that Jim fella?
What happened to him?
I figure he was up front with a gun in the engineer's head.
He was terrible.
That bastard slipped away again.
I'll tell you how I got him, but first I need to wet my whistle.
Not bad.
Then I was gonna come up here to more concentration bar
and then leading to extra damage.
Very cool.
How are the people here that never heard the phrase wet my whistle?
You never heard that before?
After my showdown with Jesse,
I continued to track his been around forever.
Frank and that son of a bitch Jim.
Get through the hostile territory and find Jim.
...into the high mountains as they were going to ground.
Ozarks, I believe.
Just like broke all my bones.
Perfect place to hide out from the authorities.
What was that little ding there?
What was that little ding?
In fact, before I could find them,
some Indians who fled the race and were hiding the terrorists found me first.
They probably thought I was a cat scout
and didn't want me telling the military where they were.
They could have been Cheyenne, but...
I think we've already replayed this mission.
He's told the story so strangely so many times.
I remember this exact location.
Remember this?
Like I fell, but it was a good advantage.
I want to get a combo here.
No, no, no.
Don't slow it down.
I want it to go fast.
Now where were the Indians?
Do you like that time?
I don't.
Did I tell you about Grey Wolf?
Yes, sir.
You did.
Yeah, see?
I remember this.
Okay.
All right.
Somebody replay it.
Somebody replay that whole thing on the clip and look at it and slow it down.
Feel like I like fucking three times.
Play it again.
What's going on right now?
Why are we...
This guy's just running around.
No, hurry, hurry.
Come on.
I need ammo.
Yes.
Mr. Graves, are you all right?
Nice.
Pretty good voice, actually.
Won't you spare me your ears?
That I can't see with eyes cold hands.
They can hold me where I am.
None can excel the door.
We stand unshaken.
Oh, oh, oh, dead.
Oh, no.
Won't you spare me your ears?
And I stand unshaken.
I didn't ruin it.
He was done.
Could you wait to call me?
Uh, do I have to dodge these?
Won't you spare me your ears?
So are you going to answer the question?
What question is that?
Jim Reed.
Did you ever find it?
Reed was indeed that song that you certainly heard.
That's right, man.
A despicable character.
I remember him laughing at me and my brothers.
He was intent on avoiding my vengeance,
but nothing was going to stop me.
Nothing.
Now, here we are.
That's Frank James.
Frank James.
Get to the hilltop and avoid the sniper's bullets.
All right, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I need, this is extra damage during combos.
After fourth level combo,
your bullets will do a hundred percent more damage.
That actually kind of sucks.
I'm going to go with some of these.
These are all based on the shotgun.
Come closer.
More concentration for full blast.
Yeah, it's all shotgun.
Yeah, I guess we'll get it.
I'll end up with the quick shooter.
We'll go down here.
Frank James.
Jesus, don't give me a second, man.
Come on.
Whoa, where is he?
Um, I have the reaction time of a pineapple.
I was just looking at the menu.
I'm in the menu doing points
and I come out and die in a tenth of a second.
That's pineapple reactions?
Why did it not go through?
He's up there.
Um, if we go this way.
That doesn't even make any sense.
I shouldn't even laugh at that
so I don't enable that kind of behavior in chat.
I shouldn't even be laughing.
I should be, I should go.
Time that guy out quick.
Okay.
That's what I should have done.
I'm guessing Frank James believed I was responsible
for the demise of his brother, Jesse.
I couldn't really disagree with the man
as I thought Jesse was dead then as well.
Make your, what's it say?
Make your what?
It could be anything.
Make your bed.
Make your taxes.
Make your gun shoot.
What does it say?
Make your what?
It could have been anything.
But he's not there.
But he was still intent on-
Secret.
Pushed in on him again.
He backed up-
Told ya.
Confirmed your angle on me.
Is it a shotgun?
Uh, I'll take that.
Oh fuck, he's shooting again.
Oh my god, I don't know where he is.
What direction is he shooting from?
Alright, straight ahead.
Oh my god, he's right there.
Fuck, I just saw him.
Okay.
He's right there.
And fault Frank for wanting his revenges.
I was there for the same damn reason myself.
I don't know where to go.
At this point, I'm guessing you think
Silas Greaves is the worst murderer
than Jim Reid ever was.
No, sir.
A man who spent half his life
killing somebody's brothers,
fathers, sons.
I think you were just looking for justice, sir.
Is that what I was talking about in your life?
Is that what it was?
Justice.
I think he's right-
Is there-
I don't-
There's nothing I can hide behind.
This rock right here
is the only thing I can hide behind.
Do you see anything else?
Fuck.
Uh, is this-
What?
The sky is falling.
He hit me.
There he is.
These-
How?
Can he hit me from here?
Is that him?
Give me the dynamite.
That was throwing him off the cliff.
I was trying to aim, so-
Oh, whatever.
What a shitty hideout.
Fuck you for having such a bad hideout.
Yeah, go back to the three little pigs.
Your house sucks.
See, I grew wings and flew down there,
and now here he is.
Bastard.
Bullshit, is he gonna pull a gun?
We parted in peace,
as Frank pointed out the path to my prey
before making his way back down the hill.
That- that's-
He- I- I'm trying to preemptively.
He was gonna shoot me or something,
that's how it always happens.
Now he's stuck in a time paradox.
It's alright.
We'll get out of it together.
You and me.
Just you and me.
Yes, I'm talking to you.
There are a lot of people here,
but you're the one I'm talking to.
Forget about all these other people here,
you know?
Right in the leg.
Drama.
It was about that time, right?
Of course it was.
Fucked up the accuracy, but it's fine.
Shit.
Not good.
Can they shoot through this?
It's just wood, right?
No, I can too.
Ooh.
Whoa!
Ow, shit.
Come on, bring it on.
Here we go.
Lightning.
It's a lot easier to know you.
Oh well.
No points?
I got four to five secrets?
What?
Pineapple reaction.
He had pineapple reaction time.
Back to episode seven.
The wild bunch.
We're going back to the future again.
This is the worst mission in the game.
Oh well.
That's encouraging to hear.
We'll see.
The good, the bad, and the dead.
Have fun with this one.
He doesn't know.
How close am I to the last weapon that I want to unlock?
I'm pretty much there.
So then we'll get the ivory handled quick shooter.
More damage and faster aim speed.
I'm going to try it at least once.
Well, that's it.
There's no-
Why would it not get-
Usually you get to do like three or four of those.
I just get to quick time event the one guy?
All right.
Why is that guy doing a backflip?
Here we go.
There it is.
I've re-handled the quick shooter.
I can't wait to try him.
Bob Bryant.
Well, it's one way to do that.
Nugget.
Ooh, there it is.
Okay.
So these are the quick shooters.
Those are fast.
Very quick!
All right, nice.
I'll use them.
Let's head back down here.
And out the door.
No, I don't want any of those.
At this point in the game, why even have boxes like this?
I have upgraded better weapons.
Every version, essentially.
I gotta go-
Why does it want to go back up here?
Uh, hang over here?
Okay.
The stair-
The stairs going up?
Yeah, I mean it wanted me to go in that building and go up here.
But where the fuck was I supposed to go up to this?
Where are the stairs?
What the hell does it want me to do?
Is he actually blind?
No!
What?
I did it.
Okay.
Secrets?
All right.
Again, just one guy.
All right, you in here?
What house are you in?
Fine.
Bush, Cassidy, and the Sundance Kid.
Yeah.
Okay.
Nugget?
What the fuck was that?
All right, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I just want the-
There's the secret.
Now, every-
I'm just gonna get-
Collapse them.
Let's take the other guns.
I feel like this is going to be more useful.
Oh, he's up there.
Five points.
God.
Oh!
Oh, wait, I'm dead?
I'm supposed to be dead?
Totally.
Dead the whole time.
Find your way through ghost town.
Can I walk out here?
Nah, I don't want those.
Can't open the door?
Ghosts?
Um, so.
Hi.
Guy that just appeared on my screen and killed me instantly.
That old war horse had died two years before.
Maybe I was dead too and confronting the ghosts of my past.
Perhaps all my sins were coming back to haunt me and drag me down to perdition.
There's two Pat Garrett's.
Holy shit.
And where is he again?
He's throwing dynamite.
What?
I tried.
Jesus.
Hide.
You can't even see him.
I can barely see their ghost faces.
You need to have that concentration bar filled for this.
Oh, come on.
How many Henry Plumbers are there?
All right, just crouch.
Come on.
I'm going this way.
No, I'm not.
I can't go that way.
There he is.
Fuck!
Which way?
All right, nope.
That's not how you do it.
I thought maybe I could just run in there and just...
No, that's not gonna happen.
I gotta get cover somewhere here.
Watch out for the dynamite.
He's gonna throw dynamite at me.
All right, there's two down.
The other one's over here.
All right, that's it.
He's over here.
Ow!
I can see him a little bit.
Wait till I heal up.
All right, I'm good.
Any more people from your past?
Any more boss rush people to deal with?
I guess not.
Hold on.
There's a nugget here right there.
All right, got a wall.
Please tell me there's a checkpoint.
Holy shit, he really did appear.
God, he really did appear.
What's left?
Oh, God.
Okay.
Up there?
Fuck!
Up here still?
Over here.
Oh, God.
Tree, save me.
Jesus.
Where the fuck?
Oh, my goodness gracious.
All right, I gotta save.
All right, hide behind a tombstone or something.
I'm going away from the story.
How?
They're all down there.
Here we go.
Wow.
God!
God damn it!
He's still alive.
I gotta hide behind the house or something.
I can't go that way.
Fuck!
No!
Where are...
It's the last one!
You've got to be fucking kidding me.
I'm dead.
This is ins...
Oh, no.
I...
You gotta be kidding me.
And okay, here's another dumb thing.
If you walk too far, you restart the whole level.
How big is this area?
Oh, this sucks ass.
All right.
Well, how the fuck am I ever gonna beat this?
I'm not gonna use...
I'm gonna try to hold this.
I say that now.
They just spray a thousand bullets.
And look, I'm going too far up in the story.
Time to restart the level.
Fast shotgun reload.
No, what can help me here?
Faster revolver reload, maybe.
Probably the faster reload.
Somebody behind me too.
I have no idea.
They got...
The guys...
This guy is next to me.
Somehow this dude got next to me.
This gun's not good for this.
I think I gotta stay with the pistols.
This takes too long to kill anything.
Even with headshots.
They're all over here.
They're fucking everywhere!
My...
Come on!
What?
Why do you have that much health?
I don't know what to do.
Oh my fucking god.
Where is he?
Which one?
Left or right?
Somebody said the Undertaker.
He just baited me so hard.
Holy fuck, man.
You gotta be kidding me.
No!
Tombstone save!
Don't do it.
Holy fuck, man.
No!
Which way?
Holy fuck.
Jesus Christ, that was insane.
That was fucking crazy.
I thought I did though.
I didn't think I was gonna beat that.
Butch Cassidy.
Sundance Kid.
The good, the bad, and the dead.
And Scylla's Grieves is...
But the kid wasn't quite deceased.
We gotta do a three-way duel?
Those two looked like they hadn't seen each other for quite a while.
Clearly they were no...
Thank god I had those improved guns.
I was hoping I wouldn't have to kill you.
I asked them about Bob Bryant.
But they were too busy with their own hated conversation.
Let me get this shit straight.
And the love of...
So is that tab party.
I didn't want to shoot anybody until I had an answer to my question.
But those boys didn't give me much of a choice.
Wait, what?
I'm gonna interfere in their game?
Use Q and E to switch your focus to the enemy who's looking at you.
Are you serious?
Wait, I have to...
Do I have to shoot them?
Who makes the move first move?
Damn.
All right, so he's looking at me now, right?
SCP Cassidy.
Whoops.
Bad speed.
This is gonna be fucking...
It's botched already.
Oh, this is looking all botched.
This is already...
I fucked this whole thing up.
I can't...
There's no way I'm gonna do this.
Is it gonna be a fucking Christmas miracle if this goes through?
8%!
Damn it.
Why was it my screen?
Look at me.
Look at me, please!
This is the one.
It was kind of anticlimactic, but it's all right.
I'll take it.
At least it's over 50%.
It is 50%, so I'm okay with that.
Never under 50.
At least no 49s, no 38s.
It's the finale.
But it ain't the truth.
So, you never found Bob?
There is no Bob.
This old sumbitch ain't even Silas Greaves.
Sir, is that true?
Have you been pulling our legs this whole time?
Not the whole time.
Man, I think you've worn out your welcome here.
Maybe you're right, Jack.
Maybe it's time to pay.
You see, Ben, or should I say Bob?
Your past always catches up with you.
I was a different man back then, crazy.
Drinking, I changed my ways, I swear to you.
If I could turn back...
Found him.
But you came, Bob.
Choose your destiny.
Revenge, redemption.
I think we got two different endings.
Revenge is kill.
Redemption is no kill.
I'm thinking redemption here.
But then there's also kill him.
You killed everyone in your path.
Why stop now?
Yeah, I get to the goal and I say, all right, I'm done.
Uh, one more?
Uh, I'm gonna...
Why'd you toy with me on those tales knowing I wanted to suss you out, Bob?
See what kind of man you turned out to be.
Maybe prod you into drawing on me.
See, all those years on your trail turned me into a killer.
Can't even remember who I was before you tried to murder me.
You, on the other hand, walked that very same path in exactly the opposite direction.
What do you mean by that?
You think your life is worth sparing, Bob?
We've been killing so much.
What's your name again?
We need to see what happened.
It's Eisenhower, sir.
Dwight Eisenhower.
What do you plan to do with him?
We got the Dwight Eisenhower reveal on redemption.
Tomorrow at West Point, sir.
So?
Didn't get that on revenge.
You do something decent with your life.
You hear me?
Sir?
Yes, sir.
Haven't said I left you with nothing.
Okay.
Now we can see the other ending.
All through the timeline, let's see how it ends the other way.
I knew it was gonna work as long as I didn't get to the loading screen.
See what happens with the revenge.
No, I chose redemption.
That's my choice.
That's my ending.
Let's see what happens on the other side.
This is my choice.
But we're peering into the eyes of other gamers, you know?
Don't have it said that I left you with nothing.
That's how you want it?
So be it.
Shit.
We actually get to play.
There's more gameplay with this ending.
There's no indicators either.
I'm not gonna blow it.
He's dead.
Did you know it was him all?
Cassidy told me Bob was in Abilene before he died.
I wasn't sure Ben was my man until he revealed how much he knew about Ringo and Reed.
The coin, of course.
That was the last nail in that particular coffin.
I better go get the sheriff.
You okay, boy?
You look a mite shook up.
Dwight, maybe you best go home.
See, we're never gonna know who he is.
Oh.
Never mind.
He shouldn't get caught up in something like this.
They tell you anyways.
I think I might head out myself at this juncture.
Unless you want to stop me, Jack.
Sir!
Mr. Greaves.
So where are you going now?
Now that you had your...
As I've sold my soul...
Yeah, I heard that.
And will never again walk.
There's a giant fucking gorilla.
That can talk.
You should get the whole team back together.
There it is.
That's a short little bite-sized game.
There are other game modes too.
We'll try them out.
That was fun.
Challenging.
Now I'm actually glad I played that on hard.
There's another difficulty after that.
Just a fun short little game.
I want to try the dual game mode and see how that's different.
What's my rating?
Uh...
Okay, it was like an 8...
It was like an 8-7.
It was like an 8-6, 8-7.
Until I got to that last encounter which made it like an 8-2.
It's always an 8-7.
Yeah, it is.
8-6.
That was an 8-6, 8-5.
No, it was good.
It was solid.
I don't think that was like the best video game I've ever played in my life.
But it was...
I would recommend you play it.
It was fun.
It's somewhere in that like 7 to 8, I'd say, out of 10.
Depending on who you are.
It doesn't need to be any higher.
It's just an arcade shooter with some fun mechanics.
I think I should be able just to go, right?
Nothing after the credits.
New modes are available.
A new game plus is now available.
Start a new story retaining all the unlocked skills and weapons.
True West difficulty is now available.
Try going through the story with minimal HUD.
And extra difficulty to get the real western experience.
All right, arcade.
What's arcade?
Position.
I guess you have like positions of people.
What's Lincoln County?
Arcade, Lincoln County.
So it's just score runs of the level.
Anything different in it or it's just...
Welcome to arcade mode.
It's all about the high scores.
You get points for kills and awards.
But the key to success is linking kills together into combos.
You have to finish the mission alive to keep your score.
Get it done quickly.
Gunslinger, Trapper, Ranger.
Okay.
Start game.
Each kill raises the combo by one.
All right.
Well, I can't hit anything.
Apparently, why can't I?
Bad.
Kill under the enemy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is not going to be a great score.
Like what?
Okay.
But did you see that?
Somebody has to look...
Did you see what just happened?
I did.
That's not me.
I did it three more times.
Did I shoot?
Restart.
Come on, somebody.
Anybody?
Ah, I didn't see over here.
It's been blocked.
Come on, somebody.
Damn it.
Oh, I'll take it.
Oh, no.
They shot Bill.
Poor Bill.
He was a good guy.
Oh, fuck.
Didn't even know he was there.
I can't believe he's still alive.
All right.
Clean it up here.
That was bad.
That's it.
That's really fun.
If you can get the whole route down, it'd be kind of cool.
So to be able to get...
All right, I get it.
I understand.
So you really need to get a route down.
Unlock the skills and replay them.
One star.
Yeah, it's designed for you to get one star
and then you replay it like 50 times
and you do much better every time.
That's cool.
What about the duels?
Let me see what the duels do.
What a real pineapple response that was.
Duel challenge.
Win a series of showdowns honorably and quickly
to become a true legend of the Wild West.
You have five lives to try it again
just in case you get shot along the way.
I'm not very good at these, but I'll try.
2,000, right?
15 stages.
Oh, God.
You're going to do all 15 people in the story?
Remember the Peter Griffin joke I made?
Make it again.
Somebody in chat do it.
I'm going to lose at the last level probably.
Honorable.
Lives left.
Continue.
I remember this guy.
Oh, yeah, I do.
Old man Clanton.
Oh, shit.
You walking...
You're going way too far off camera here.
Fuck!
At the cross.
The crosshair was on him too.
Oh, damn it.
He took like so many steps to his left.
Somebody told me that this with a controller is like 30 times easier,
but I don't have one here.
Plugged in.
Got him.
All right.
Controller is scrubbed.
This is still fun though.
I wish...
Another one of my wishes.
Where's my gamer genie?
Where's my game genie?
For me to plug these things in.
So Red Dead came out, right?
Red Dead Redemption 2.
And there was...
The duels weren't...
They weren't that elaborate.
It was kind of just...
I want a game like this.
All right, I'm just like talking.
You know, a game where the intensity of a duel is there.
Different mechanics.
Breathing.
Reaction times.
Those old...
Even those games we played on the Wii.
Those old arcade cabinet games.
Mad Dog McCree and shit.
Like, I wish somebody would make one of those.
Just make the whole game about this.
And even do a multiplayer.
I mean, you'd have to have pretty good netcode,
but still it's too niche.
Yeah, but people have said that about other stuff before,
and they became fairly popular games, all right?
Why don't I just shoot the...
Why would I just shoot the barrel?
I'm just too busy focusing 100% of the barrel.
And there is a distraction.
It's just a distraction.
I dodged it.
Yeah, he's too fast.
John Harden.
Now I need that speed.
I want to almost press my eyeballs to the screen.
Can I push one eye on this left side?
I'm not going to be able to do it.
I have to go, like, frog-eyed.
I can't see them both at the same time.
Ever played Bushido Blade?
Um, that name's really familiar.
Bushido Blade.
It's got a very familiar name.
I got this one.
It's an old PS1 game.
One hit and you die.
Is that the game with a bunch of different weapons?
It's almost like a 3D fighter.
Where you fight one person at a time.
Maybe...
Well, maybe we'll give it a try.
I vaguely remember playing that game.
Not good speed so far.
I might be able to still do it.
It's got a cool story mode where you have to fight honorably to get the best ending.
That's actually really awesome.
Just get Bushido Blade 2 if you do.
Is that one of those cases like Monster Rancher?
Where the second one is just better?
It's just a better version of the first one?
Yeah, okay.
Got them both.
You just get both for a decent price.
PlayStation 1 games are weird, though.
Some of these old games that you would think,
ah, it's probably like five bucks.
Some of them are like 50 to 100 dollars.
But if it's worth it, it's worth it, right?
I like playing on original hardware.
You know that's a meme on this channel, but it's true.
Oh, fuck!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
No!
I like my...
I have like a greasy hand right now.
I have like a fucking watery hand.
And it just like accidentally slipped.
I'll get close.
I don't know if I'll get all the way to the end, though.
This is already looking bad.
Damn it, man.
That's fucking fast.
Well, this is it.
100% speed.
I just have to do four more and not miss any shots.
Only four more.
That's it.
New high score.
Died on Jim Reid.
I could see getting addicted to that for at least a little while.
That's cool.
New game plus.
What does recollections mean?
Oh, I see.
It's the movies, the...
That's cool.
PvP would be neat.
Yeah, it would.
Wait, what am I saying?
Recollections?
The re-collections.
Recollections.
Like a 100,000 IQ streamer, right?
But I think that's a solid place to call it for tonight.
Just six hours.
I think that's a pretty decent place to call it.
I don't really want to get anything else started.
We'll do the bits.
We'll hang out for a little bit.
Should be probably like six, six and a half.
And then tomorrow, for those of you that, you know, you've been around,
you already know this, but the reason why I'm going four days in a row,
I don't typically do more than three or four days in a row,
but I'm not going to be around this next week.
My mother is coming up.
We're going to spend a bunch of time together.
I haven't seen her in a long time, so I'm going to take about five days off
because that's when she'll be here and I want to spend time with my mom.
So I'm taking a little vacation.
I'll be back because when she's gone,
I'm probably going to see her one more time.
And then I'm, you know, obviously not going to see her for like probably
another six months, a year, whenever we do something else together
as like a family, right?
So I do want to spend some time with my mother,
but I'll see you tomorrow.
Tomorrow we're going to do, we'll probably,
oh, by the way, tomorrow I'm starting at like six plus PM Pacific.
I have an appointment tomorrow, so I have to do, I'm going to the dentist.
So I got to do that in the early afternoon
and then we're just going to hang out for like a few hours
maybe a little bit more.
I might play the first episode of Sam and Max.
We'll hang out.
There's a couple of videos that I want to watch.
So tomorrow, there's no plan at all tomorrow.
I just wanted to go live again
because I'm not going to be live for a long time.
So I want to put the time in for you guys.
I want to see you guys.
I'm not going to see you for a while.
So we're just going in completely no plan tomorrow.
Should be fun.
I got good dental.
Please play more Telltale games.
We'll see.
Has my mom ever seen what I do for a living?
Yeah.
She knows.
Oh, yeah.
She's very well aware.
But thanks for watching tonight.
I hope you enjoyed.
I wanted just to kind of chill, relax, and play a game
that I've wanted to play for a while.
So we just kind of hung out and played Gunslinger
and it was great.
So it was a real comfy stream today.
I liked it.
Kind of needed this after the insanity of the last week or two.
But let's get to the bits.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Late afternoon somewhere around like six o'clock Pacific.
Depending.
I don't really have like an exact time
because I don't know how long I'm going to be at this point before.
But regardless, I'll see you.
If you're going to come hang out tomorrow, we'll see you tomorrow.
Has my mother watched the streams?
No.
I think it's one of those cases where she's like,
I know what you do and it's great.
But she's not going to sit here and watch.
My mother's very supportive.
She's great.
She really is.
And I can't wait to see her.
So I'm excited.
She'll be here real soon.
But let's go back earlier this afternoon.
To Afro Ninja, thanks for the five dollars.
Thank you.
Thank you, Zorro Carlos for the 250.
The title of this game sounds like a Family Guy cutaway joke
about some Mexican Call of Duty knockoff.
Family Guy cutaway joke.
And I made a Family Guy reference that he did have the green pants,
the white button up, and he was like had a fat stomach.
That's just the Peter Griffin.
It is.
I'm sorry.
Thank you, some guy for the 15 dollars.
It's been a long time since I posted a meme video.
Hopefully, a meme video lasts and hopefully, and honestly, sorry,
I still don't have a good video to show you.
But anyway, here's Sharktail for three minutes.
I don't want to watch Sharktail.
This is Sharktail times 31 speed.
Somebody had to upload this.
Is this some weird fucked up way to get around the
YouTube algorithm to catch content ID?
Do you download this video and then undo the times 31 speed?
Is that how that works?
Do you slow it down until you can comprehend it?
Well, thank you for the 15 dollars, first of all, some guy.
And thanks for the whole entire Sharktail.
It's a three minute video.
It's the whole movie, I guess.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Thank you, Spicy Pepe's for five dollars.
Hey, Jeremiah, I hope you're doing well.
Just wanted to say that I really appreciate you and all that you do on these streams.
I've been watching you a couple of years now and every time I click on an old YouTube video,
I'll hop into one of your streams.
I know I'll be laughing throughout it all.
I think you're the most genuine and caring human on the planet.
And you're the best.
Thank you for the five dollars, Spicy Pepe's.
And thank you for an incredibly kind fucking message.
That's thank you.
Those are, there's a lot of things that I'm glad you think of this community in these streams.
So thank you so much.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you, Smelly Boy for the 250.
Johnny Test Whip Crack.
Is that a sound effect?
AtroLux Atrix, thanks for the three bucks.
Hey, Jeremiah, can you pretend this is a 50 dollars?
I remember that, that was from earlier.
That was AtroLux.
That really confused me so much.
And then AtroLux again gave 250.
All right, I didn't expect that.
Thanks, Jeremiah.
That was accidental comedy.
Can you pretend this is 50 dollars?
Thank you, CADBTV, resident game developer here.
Thanks for the 250.
Hey, Jeremiah, I've never played this game before.
Is the objective to shoot the buildings?
You're doing great.
50 plus percent every time.
Some of those levels were 75, 71 percent.
That means seven out of every 10 shots landed into somebody.
Come on, on hard mode too?
That's not bad.
That's fine.
What's wrong with that?
There's nothing wrong with that.
Why is that?
That's like good.
That's good.
It is.
I'm going to toot my horn here
because there is no horn to toot.
That's good.
60 to 70 percent accuracy on hard mode in the game.
That's okay.
That's fine.
You don't have to worry.
What do I have to worry about?
Give us closure on if you're going to play God Hand or not.
I don't know.
I don't know what I'm going to have for breakfast tomorrow.
Are you saying that you missed 25 percent of the buildings you were shooting at?
Let's just say yes, I guess.
You guys, man.
Sometimes you guys are fucking crazy.
I love it.
Thank you, an anonymous cheerer for the $10.
Sometimes words explode inside my brain and they run into each other.
1000 bits from an anonymous cheerer.
10 bucks.
Thank you, whoever you are.
Whoever you are.
And then we had a bunch of community subs.
Jerma's average dong gave a bunch.
Pixel Mike gave a bunch.
Lots and lots of community subs given a couple hours ago.
Thank you, guys.
Chunky baloney, thanks for the $5.
Buy yourself some double cheeseburgers on me.
I really want a crispy thin crust pepperoni pizza right now.
We'll be talking about it earlier.
I'm just super like, I'm relaxed.
Anybody else just totally relaxed right now?
I'm just going to eat some pizza
and just sit on the couch and just, I can't wait.
Quick, somebody stress him out.
Don't do that.
I'm in a great spot right now.
What do you mean stress him out?
I'm frustrated with you.
Why?
What?
What are you talking about?
Just, we're just having, we're just relaxing.
Everyone's starting to stress me out.
Don't mess with my vibe, dude.
Everybody thinks you're an idiot.
No, they don't.
That's a joke.
It's a meme on the channel.
I made it up, I said.
I went, oh, I'm dumb.
Like four years ago, and everybody just doesn't know.
It's a meme on the channel, it's a joke.
Every time anybody says it, it's a funny thing that we do.
Yeah, I made that up four years ago.
And I said, it's going to be wicked funny
because everyone's going to keep saying this.
And I want this to be a thing on the channel, like guys dumb.
And people still do it now.
I'm surprised.
It's cool to see that the like streamers dumb joke
that I made that I told you guys that was funny to do.
Um, you guys still do it.
It's great.
I think it's fun.
He's deflecting.
Yeah.
Oh, wouldn't you?
If a stranger walked up to you and said, hey, hey, dude, you're dumb.
What would you do?
But first of all, you were like trying to get into the sewer, right?
You were trying to like get into the sewer with your bare hands.
But still, like, let me do me, right?
Like, would you go up to that guy and be like, hey, dude, you're dumb.
No, he's just trying to get in the sewer, whatever.
Well, okay.
If I forgot, I was just like yelling about pop tarts or something on the sidewalk.
Would you walk up to him and go, hey, dude, you're stupid.
Hey, wouldn't you?
Would be like, oh, that guy's just kind of weird.
Let him do what he's going to do.
You wouldn't do that.
You wouldn't download a car.
Okay.
Uh, thank you too.
Where are we here?
Jerma's average dong.
No, that's Jerma's.
There's so many Jerma's name something.
Jerma lied about Minecraft.
Jerma's dick.
Jerma's dong.
Jerma lied about fruity loops.
Thank you, Jerma lied about Minecraft VR for the five community subs right now.
Maybe you should stop lying.
Half of these are not even about lying.
They're about my, like, penis.
What do you mean lying?
What does that have to do with me telling anything?
Liar.
Oh my God.
But thank you to smelly boy for the 250.
This game is so cool.
It was very cool.
I liked it.
Thank you.
Have gun for the 250.
Hey, Jerma.
Did you notice that all the level names are the names of western movies?
Just altered a little bit.
I didn't even pick that up.
That's cool.
I guess the good, the bad, and the yeah, I could see that.
That's very cool.
Uh, thank you castle.
Thank you castleon or castleion for the five dollars.
Just paying you back for spamming your chat with history facts about the guys you killed.
That's fucking funny.
I'm surprised you didn't get, like, timed out.
That's cool though.
Knowledge with our games, right?
Mods were nice to me.
Well, that's good.
But thank you for the five dollars and thanks for the, uh, history.
Thank you.
Thank you pretty support for the five dollars.
Sleep tight, streamer.
I'll try.
I will try.
Sleeping, I told you, my biggest, my biggest superpower that I wish I had was
being able to go like this and go to bed.
Although that would be not good because if anybody,
if you snapped for some reason, you'd just fall asleep.
Sometimes that would, it would be good, but it wouldn't.
It would have to be something very specific.
It'd have to be, like, snap three times in a row and then, like, say a series of words.
I remember reading, uh, there was a thing on Reddit before about what would your superpower be or,
or if you, if everybody had the same superpower or something,
whatever it was, somebody said that, like, the only way that it would make it so I could
fly or if everybody could have the same superpower, but you could add something to
it or something, and one of the, one of the comments said something like,
I would make it so everybody had the ability to fly,
but I only knew that it took this insane regimen of things to do before it worked.
So nobody, we know what I'm talking about.
Produce an infinite amount of spaghetti sauce.
I don't know, but infinite.
Nice joke that I wasn't, I'm not making a joke.
There was a thing with, I, I can't remember it.
I shouldn't have even started talking about it because I don't even remember it.
I remember it was something like that though where
you choose a superpower, but everybody gets to have it.
Just type in superpower, everybody gets to have it, reddit,
and you'll find the cool comment that that guy put.
But let me get the credits up.
We have a couple more bits left.
Let's see those community subs fly on by.
What do you say?
Thank you Devakitty for the three dollars.
I got to go on a six hour train ride twice in one day to get hormone treatment
because I made the journey here two weeks ago, but only when I got to the hospital
he told me my appointment was canceled.
So I returned home feeling very defeated and your streams helped me through a tough break.
Thank you for being such a good streamer.
They say transgender pride.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that that didn't go well.
Back and forth that sucks.
Thank you for being here.
Sorry that it's not, that didn't go well, but there's another day, right?
Glad to have a spot where people can just hang out and have fun.
It's the only thing I fucking care about, so.
Fun.
I'm glad people can have it here.
Whoa, whoops.
Feed me ads.
I'm gonna do two ads.
Just wait.
Cheer 500.
God damn it, I fucked it up.
Play oblivion again.
Why did that work?
It just, it did.
Hey, peek a banana, thanks for the 250.
That just saved your heart, thank you.
If you're gonna play Sam and Max tomorrow and you're starting with episode one,
don't get the wrong impression.
It starts off slow because there's six episodes and it gets way better.
Well, whatever.
That's fine.
I'm only gonna do, I'll do the first episode, right?
We'll have like four, probably like three to five hours to kill.
So we'll have plenty of time to do at least one.
Play all, there are three different games of Sam and Max.
Bingo sunshine, five dollars.
Good to my word.
Play oblivion though.
You didn't have to do that, it's all right.
Thank you, Phil.
Look at all these fucking subs rolling by.
Can you play every game ever?
Well, I will get in there.
I've played a lot of the old ones, but thank you all.
I'll see you tomorrow.
We're gonna do, it's not, there is no plan.
I might just do like a little bit of Sam and Max.
I might watch a few videos and then we might just do fucking chat roulette.
You know what I mean?
Where, what game am I gonna play?
Whatever it is.
Try this one.
Okay, maybe we'll play for like an hour.
VR chat on open.
I don't know about that.
That doesn't mean what you think it means.
No, I mean like in chat, we're like just pick a random,
somebody said something and I pick it and we play it.
Oh god, okay.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Probably around like six o'clock Pacific.
I'll set the sauce accordingly.
See you soon.
Thanks for hanging out.
I'm glad I actually got to play gunslinger because it was a very solid,
cool, fun game.
Thank you for experiencing it with me.
See you tomorrow.
Take care of yourselves.
9 p.m. Eastern stream.
Yeah, it's because I got a, I have a dentist appointment that I can't miss.
It's probably gonna be a while scheduled.
So I'm gonna be there for a little while.
I'll see you whenever I get, I'll probably turn it on at some point.
Up to before six, maybe a little after.
I don't know.
We're just gonna do whatever.
See you soon.
Take care.
And no, not good night.
Not good night.
I'm gonna run two ads.
Otherwise people are gonna scream at me the next time I turn my stream on.
So let's run a couple ads.
Here comes a 60 second ad break.
See you guys later.
Good night.
Goodbye.
Take care.
Turning off ad block for this one.
And we'll see, we'll see what they get.
What'd you get?
Samsung?
Nice.
Stream Legends.
Stream Legends unfortunately is not ready yet because I went very into the early
morning this morning.
So I did that at somewhere around 1 a.m. Pacific today.
So that's not this, I can't do that for a long time.
Didn't get an ad?
Well I ran them.
I'm telling you, they're ending in five seconds.
And there it is.
That's it.
I will see you guys real soon.
Take care of yourselves.
Have a good one.
Good night.