Hello everybody. Welcome, welcome. I did hear, I did hear about it. I've seen it. It's crazy.
I guess we'll open with that. Uh, so the TF2 economy has, uh, doesn't exist anymore.
Unusuals are just free. Everybody gets one? Yeah, I saw that. They're gonna fix it though, right?
They're gonna pull back any item that's been opened in the last, like, day or so.
They'll do an unusual rollback period and then everybody that sold their $3,000 TF2 hat
for like three bucks. That might not, that's gonna, that's just hold on to your stuff. Just hold.
This happened before? Yeah, it'll be, I think it'll probably be fine. It is like kind of humorous
though to see screenshots of people's backpacks with like 50 unusuals that they opened like 10
minutes ago. I don't play TF2 anymore, but it's still interesting to keep up sometimes. He's
telling you not to sell. Don't, just don't sell. You can't panic sell. You do what we all do. You
hold that shit to zero and then sell it for 30 cents. Yeah, buy high, don't sell and then
panic sell for less than 95% of your initial investment. Monster Rancher is getting ported,
but I heard it was Japanese only. So, and how are they gonna do that? It's gonna be digital only
port. It's just gonna, what do you do? How do you do that without the discs? We'll see. But I heard
that was only going to Japan first. So who knows if it'll ever show up in the North American market.
Who knows? When am I gonna go to Japan? I don't know. I've wanted to take a trip to Japan.
Probably since I was 16, 17. Just one of those places that I've always wanted to go.
Never had a chance. It's just an interesting place. No, it's not, it's not, it's not because
of the anime. It's just, Japan's an interesting place. It really is. It seems really fun and
interesting. Yeah. Oh yeah. I would, I can't wait to travel to Japan because of the anime. Sure.
Not like the incredible culture and the massive history. No, no, no, no, anime. That's why I want
to go. Anyways, speaking of none of the things we're just talking about, we're going to play
DOS games today. We're going to hang out for a little bit. I said a while ago I wanted to do
DOS nights. The last time we did this is probably three weeks ago. Maybe more. So hey, DOS night
number four or five, whatever the hell it is. And I have picked a few to start just to kind of get
the ball rolling. Play Mario Sunshine or Riot. That's not a DOS game. That is a, that is Nintendo
GameCube. That's not for Microsoft distributed online systems. What do you mean? Yes, it is.
There's no MS DOS version of Mario Sunshine. Sunshine was ported to DOS. How? Doesn't DOS,
isn't the the entire operating system of DOS a hundred kilobytes? No, I'm getting lied to.
Anyways, let's go. I've already got it all set up. We'll do some picking later,
but I saw a couple that I just had to click on immediately. And the first one we're going to do
is, let's see if I can get it on here. Yeah, the first one we're going to do is called Donald Ducks
Playground by the Walt Disney Company. I just saw Donald Duck and I clicked it immediately.
Okay, here we go. Let's get it on here. Are you going to work? Please work. Please work. Please
work. Please work. There we go. Donald Ducks Playground. What are we doing? Oh, Donald wants
to build a playground in the park for his nephews. He works in these stores to earn money. Hey, here's
the word. All right, let's go. He works at the train station.
Donald buys toys for today. How do I play? When words appear here, press the enter key or a
joystick button. Okay, so the reason why I did that is so I don't have to do that for like another
three years. I get asked to do that all the fucking time. So there's this this three years worth of
me doing that like six or seven out of ten beatbox. Okay, there you go. All right,
when words appear here, press the enter key or a joystick button to get in here. Okay.
Oh, I'm kidding. I'm not gonna do it again. Please walk through a doorway to choose a level. How do
I walk through a doorway? Oh, no, no, no, no. This is a game for children, right? I mean,
I can do intermediate. He's doing the walk. If you guys know what I mean. Intermediate.
Advanced. No. All right. You have to help me though. Okay, so I have to. I'm moving way faster
now. This controls like Snake, by the way. I can't control this. Toys. How long do you want to work
a two minute shift? Yeah, I want to work a one minute shift, please. Sure. Let's go. Use the
joystick or arrow keys to change the minutes below. Press the button to start work. I mean,
press the button. Press the button? How? What button? Press it. I can't. Press the button.
There is no button to press. Is the button? How do I walk? Press any key. Enter. I think I would
have a... I need to play this. Come on. W A S D. No. M. B. B for button. P. L. K. Space. Shift.
Right. F. G. H. Z. It's not Z. Damn it, I have to play this. It's X! The Amquac Special will pass
in zero minutes. What? This is every single Super Nintendo RPG you've ever played. There's a
sequence where the character freaks out and runs around to collect stuff. And this is it. Oh, I got
it. Put it in the trash? Oh, what? What am I supposed to do? Am I just breaking shit? I'm breaking
stuff. Oh, guys, this is gonna be impossible. I need to go... What? Um, it's playing Pac-Man.
Only times five speed. I have to get it perfect. It's too many FPS. Anybody know how to... How do
I fix this? I think there's a way I can, right? Do I have to make my monitor, like, 30 hertz?
How much do... I have no money. Turn down the cycles. Right click, set FPS, custom jubated.
Fuck. Why? I have to lower the speed of the CPU. I know there's a way you can do it from inside here.
Somebody know the key? Go into the DOS box options. I know there's a way to do it. Somebody showed
me this before, didn't they? All right, well, I'm just gonna wait till 37 seconds is up.
F11? I'm just gonna wait till I fail. Somebody said, do you guys ever get tired of tormenting
this man? What do you mean tormenting this man? So, wait, control F11. Is that gonna, like, open up
fucking Siri or something? Like, somebody... I need somebody to confirm this. That's not gonna open up,
like, oh, it's me, Siri. Control F11 slows it down. It's the Siri hotkey. Time's up. Press a button
to leave. Okay, listen. You've earned nothing. For a second, I thought it was putting me in jail.
Does that work? I need at least, like, a 95% in chat. People say it's control plus shift plus T
is time. Control F11? Did it work? It did. Right? Okay, yeah. Thank God for some of these fucking
super brains in chat. Five for ten dollars. Let's see what this does. You have zero dollars.
Rocking horse. Who is that? Why am I shaking? Hey, hey, do you have any of those things I made for
my nephews? Like, slow down. That's a tetherball? Donald, like, crack duck. All right, let's go to
hardware store. Let me go to work. Do I have to work for Mickey? Hi, Mickey. Enter? No? I can't do
a Donald Duck voice, so I'm not gonna try. You forgot this tutorial for a child's game.
No, no, I didn't. What I did is I was going, all right, I was going 5,000 miles per hour
in a child's game. There's a difference. Okay, how long do you, let's, here we go.
I want to work for, I don't want to do that long. Let's do a one, a two minute shift.
All right, now, what do I have to do? Am I Donald Duck the air traffic controller?
What am I doing? Okay, we got, what? What's the plan? What do I do? Put, this goes into,
what? Okay, this is luggage, I think. Okay, luggage. Is that going in? I'm just throwing
luggage out the window. Oh, Las Vegas! I want that one. No, no, give me that. I didn't catch it,
apparently. What airport is S? I'm hitting the button when it comes by, all right? I swear.
All right, there you go. I need it. Okay, I got it. I'm good. I really hope this is, no,
I've only earned 36 cents. That's pretty unbelievable, actually. Well, I mean, for one
minute of work, what does that turn out to be for an hour? I just let go of it. Okay, you can't let
go of the ass airport. I have to actually put it back down and then, okay, awardee, come on.
So, what, 81 cents? Atlanta. All right, time's up. 81 cents for a minute of work.
That's a dollar a minute. That's a pretty good job. That's, that's $60 an hour. You earned,
did they take taxes out? No, you earned 81 cents. Okay, that's cool. So, now what do I want to buy?
I need to buy toys for the park. What about the deals? Let's go to the train station.
Donald Duck doesn't pay his taxes. No, we can't, you can't teach kids about taxes this early.
How long do you want to work? Um, you have to do at least a three minute. No, one minute. This
advanced railroad. So, I have to route cars? Pick up at Duck City. Which one is that? Duck City is,
where's Duck City? Four? What? No, no, no, no. I have to, okay, hold on. I have to route it.
Where's it going? All right, pick up at Duck City. We need to route you from, no, go this way,
Donald. What are you doing? Okay, when I press left twice, he goes right. Oh, it's because he
goes, he just stops. He stops. No, he doesn't. Three. I need to turn him. No, he's about to go
to Duckburg. I desperately want to just turn at four. It needs to happen at four or five.
Well, I didn't, I didn't do anything. I have to at least buy one item before I move on.
What's this one? Zero dollars an hour. Well, that would be zero dollars in a minute.
How long do you want to work? Uh, one, uh, two minutes. So, this is a catch the, I think I
figured it out. All right, I'm gonna make a ton of money on this one. Wait, why do they need me? He
just threw it in there. Okay, hold on. You can clearly just make the throw. Why do I have to
be here to catch it? That guy could walk two or three feet to the left and make the throw. This is
so sloppy because I can't stop moving. When I hit right, he just keeps going all the way to the
right. Donald Duck, you suck. I, oh my God. I can't do it, man. It's too, I know what's going on.
My CPU was on too slow. What the fuck happened? That just dropped off. I didn't catch that one
somehow. Oh my God, whatever. I don't care. You made what, 40 cents? That's actually a pound for
pound better than the other one. All right, what is that? I have a dollar 17. Can I get that? Can
I afford it? Let's, let's, every time I get out here, I want to go a little faster. I think I've
done all the jobs I can do. Uh, $10, $5 and $10. What about junk? Do the nephews care that much?
Old box. Slide for fort. Tire swing. It's 71 cents for the tire swing. Okay, hold on.
Rope and pulley. Ladder to tree house. All right, well, let's get the old box. Let's get him a
cardboard box. Hello, says Goofy. Walk to the item you want. Press the button to take it.
Pay me for it over here. All right, you have to pay. Where am I? Uh, just kidding, Goofy. Don't
worry. All right, I want the tire swing and I want the cardboard box. Okay, please pay for your
purchases now. Yeah, please pay for your purchases. Now you owe $1.9. You have a dollar. All right,
$1. I told you that it's playing snake. I can't stop this. Okay, 20. When you are done, move
the arrow to the register T total key and press the button. Okay, 50 cents, 75 cents,
there, 85 cents, 95 cents. Do I have enough? I don't have enough. No, I do. There's a dollar
right here. Dollar five. Do I get change? Goofy will give me change, right? All right, that's it.
Give me change, Goofy. Thank you. Please make change. Why don't, wait, did I just, do I have
to walk behind the counter and make the change? Goofy, what the hell do you do here? It's $20.
$20. I don't know anything about math, Donald. That's okay, Goofy. I'll take care of you.
No, I don't want to give it back. Oh, God. Okay, press button to leave. Goofy's just fucking
really dumb. This is just paper, Goofy. The coins are the real valuable ones. Well, that makes sense.
I'm not done with this one. I write on paper every day. Not every day that I see silver. All
right, I'm going to do this one. Move faster, Donald. Fuck. All right, I'll do two minutes.
Now that I have, I can actually do it. All right, slow down though. This is still too fast. All
right, give me, no, no, no, no, give me this. Have I figured out what the hell's going on here?
Do I have to put this up here? Actually, I don't know what I'm doing. I have no idea what I'm
doing. Do I have to get, I think I have to get this from the top shelf? I have to push the ladder.
How do I push the ladder? Oh, my God. Oh, no, catch it. I don't know. I don't understand this part.
Is this, this is once broken. It just is. Okay, I can't fix this one. This, there's no, there's not
like a, what's the Freddy pizza game? This is not, what the hell is it called? Five Nights at Freddy's.
We're like, oh, something crazy is gonna happen and Donald Duck's gonna murder somebody. That's
actually, the game is broken. All right, how do I just skip work? I, I like this Donald Duck though.
This doesn't look as really cute. Don't you think? All right, let's go. You're nothing. I have six
cents. When does this game end? Can I leave this area, this part of town? That's went in the well?
No. Oh, the park. This is the park. Okay, let's go. Can I like piss on the hydrant?
Duckburg, the city park. Like, can I get on the train? Wait, oh, I looked both ways before
crossing the street. Donald Duck is really like fucking playing with his life here. All right,
let's go. Is this still Donald Duck? No, this is Huey. Do I have to bring the items with me?
Are these Mickey's gallows? Can I just walk the, all the way? Is there anything over here?
No, I have to go. That's like the boy's little hut or something, right? Can you get hit by the
train? I'm going to say 100%. No, I don't think they would code in Donald Duck getting hit by a
fucking train. In, all right, I'm gonna do the airport one again. Now I got money on this one.
I'm gonna get some more money. All right, I'm gonna do two minutes of this and then,
I know you guys want me to move on, but I can't. This is gonna be really very fast. Hold on, slow
it down. Okay, I'll get, I'm gonna do this quick. No, no, get it. BMG, BTR, JFK, and TVL.
Let me make it, let me just at least get one more like cool item for the, for the kids,
you know what I mean? What? Oh fuck, come on. BTR, JFK, BMG. You idiot. How much more time do I have?
I have a lot of time. I gotta get five bucks to buy something cool in like Mickey's store.
Where's the mini store? I don't know who's in there. BTR. I have a new strategy. It's called
do the minimum amount of work. What? Well, it's BTL. No, I'm gonna stick with the original strategy.
BTR. That's close enough. Dollar 35? I should have just stayed in BTR. Come on. Like three of them
just went by. Four of them went by. Where are, come on, where are they? They had no more? Maybe,
maybe the game knows I'm trying to do that. Oh, whatever. Dollar 62. He's still playing this. I
know. Sometimes when you find one you have to stick with it to see what happens. We got paper money
now. I'm gonna do, what's another easy one? The train one is too all over the place for me.
This one. I'll get this one. The farm one. It's been on this game for a half an hour.
No, I haven't. It has not been a half an hour. Has it? Yeah, it actually has been half an hour.
Oh man. Um, it's all right. It's all right. Let me just, let me just put one object in. Let me just
go to my house. What? Why did I drop that? No, this one sucks. Okay, can I afford anything for two
dollars? No, this is not enough money. I'm doing it really well right now. It doesn't matter.
That's it. How did that not go in the tomato bucket? Oh my god. 33 cents. All right, I'm gonna buy
something. Look, it's teaching kids how to count money with their hands. All right, here we go.
I'm gonna go buy a cool toy and then I'll be done. And we can move on to the next one that I have
here. Donald Duck can barely make ends meet, yet he spends his last change on his children's gifts
for Christmas. Donald can go hungry tonight for his children's joy in their faces. What the fuck?
That's fucked up. All right, what do we got? All right, I can do the, uh, tether ball is a dollar
ninety-nine. Rocking horse is, okay, let's get the rocking horse. Please pay for your money. All
right, I don't want, I want to keep the dollar. Put it on the counter. When you are done, move,
yeah, to the, to the t. Yeah, I know. 57 cents. Press done now. Um, what do you mean press done
now? It's gonna tell me I'm wrong. Sorry, no sale. Yeah, there's no, like, bartering system.
All right, that's 55.57. One more penny. Your purchase will be delivered. Well, delivered where?
How do I just go back to my house? Where is it being delivered to? To the park? All right,
if it's not at the park, then I'm moving on. Please, this game is killing me. I like this one.
Where is my stuff? They're not actually sending it to me. Wait, oh shit. Found it. And you guys
didn't want to see. I can play with all the toys as Huey. Tire swing. Nice. Really, really nice.
All right, what else is there? Where's my box? Do you see the cardboard box? That was kind of cute
for 30 seconds. Yeah, we had to get a payoff, even if it took 40 minutes. So what is supposed
to go up there? Keep playing this so chat can suffer. Um, a little confused by, uh, so Donald
Duck somehow can't afford to buy cardboard boxes and has to work for a dollar, but has a Elon Musk
space shuttle in his backyard. Well, we know how he lost all of his money. Why is this a slide?
Hold on. This is important. Is this a like a water slide? That's a themed water slide.
That's my favorite. Jump on and jump off. That's all you need. This can be so many things. I want
to go to the slide. Can I go to the other side? No, that's it. It's just a rocket back here. Get
the ladder. Hold on. Do I have to get the ladder? How much is the ladder? Speed up time? I think it
says maximum speed. Yeah, this is at max speed, guys. All right, let me just get the ladder and
let me go up. I want to do the slide. This will be quick. Where's the ladder? Hardware. How much is
it? No, it's not. Where is it? Uh, ship's wheel. Hand walking rope. Nope. Where is it? There it is.
$2.95. What do I have? $1.46. I got it. I'll do this really fast. We're gonna do uh just uh this
one airport one. It's really fast speed. I make a dollar. I'm done. Just hold on. Wait one minute.
Go. I just want to see if we can get up on the top of the slide because this is going too fast.
All right, I need uh I need lip. BTL. Come on. Oh, come on. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Stop,
stop, stop, stop. Really? I need a dollar. I need one dollar. Pick it up. Oh god. No, that's BTR.
I need SFD. It's, it's on too fast. How much do I have? 171, 181, 199. How much is the ladder?
Two something, right? I'll do it again. I need to see what the ladder does. Like this is the only,
I will never have this opportunity again my entire life. Nobody will, you'll never see this again,
ever. Don't you need to know? I need like 50 cents, 60 cents. I need to know. Oh my god,
why can I not pick anything up? BTL, PSP. I just, it's hard. I can't even read them.
Come on, one more. Oh my god. BTL. All right, I got it. I got enough. I'm gonna have exact change.
No, not. All right, I'm good. Let's go. It was 240 something, wasn't it? Speed it up. Don't get the
ladder. Get the catwalk. I, for real? Catwalk, catwalk to rocket slide. Oh, fuck, it's 299.
Do I need both? I need both. All right, I'll do this quick. That, this is the one that makes the
most money. I have to do this like a few times. How many times do I have to do this? Get a loan.
That's not how this works. Um, no, I gotta do, I have to do this one. I have to. Just, I'm gonna do,
okay. I'm gonna do this for five minutes. No, I'm not. That's way too long. Three minutes. It's
four minutes. All right, this is the last time you're ever gonna see this. Okay, slow it down,
slow it down. I got, I got four minutes of the worst content you will ever see on the stream
is this game. But it's okay because, no, actually, never mind. I take that back. This is the best.
I just need like three bucks. HML. No, no, no. PSP, HML, lax, ATL. How did I miss that?
Okay, double, triple, come on. Oh my god, I'm throwing in the wrong one. What an idiot.
I just need to see what it does. PSP, lax. I'm gonna stay back here. They're easy. Okay, I'm gonna,
you have to stay all the way to the right so I can see them. That's a dollar. What do I even
have in my hands? Okay, lax. Atlanta. Uh, Atlanta. Shit. Two hours on this, two hours on this Donald
fuck garbage. It's been, it's been an hour, but it's been 50 minutes. Just hold on. Just hold on.
Don't worry. It'll, it'll be worth it. What is PSP? What airport is PSP? Pennsylvania?
Philadelphia? PlayStation Portable. Yeah, I know. I understand that that's the joke, but what is it
actually? I definitely have enough for both now. What's going on? I still have a minute and 25
seconds left in my shift. Oh, he's coming back. Okay, he's wrapping around. PSP, please stop playing.
Nope, I'm not gonna. Oh, there's only one more.
You guys, you guys, come on. Let me have, I mean, you gotta let me have some, some time.
I want to see what the slide looks like in the Donald Duck game. Give me a break. Just because
I want to sit here and see what it does. And look, every, all, all the people that have been talking
shit right now. We'll see. We'll see when you see the slide. I guarantee you half the people that
are like, oh, no, no, get out of here. I'm going to be like, oh, pub champ. When I slide down that
fucking thing. Oh, I have to work, right? Worth, totally worth. I'm going to see worth, read out,
just spam like a thousand times. All right. I need, uh, I need hue. I definitely have enough,
I think. Two seconds. All right. 297. I got three bills now. It's 240 for the
all right. I definitely have enough. I got five bucks at least.
Oh, it's do, it's counting the coins up and giving me new denominations.
All right. I got $5 and 60 cents. I'm ready. And look, everybody else doesn't understand.
I get to be in the Guinness book of world records for an incredibly specific thing.
I streamed this for an hour. No one else on earth has ever done that.
Ever. I get to be in that book. You know, I, I, you know, I'll probably list it in that book,
like a hundred times. You have $5 catwalk to the rocket slide. Yes. And then the ladder, right?
Hand walking rope, ship's wheel, trampoline, summer salt bar. Okay. So then I do this and
get the ladder. Please pay. All right. Just take it. Just take my money already. I got like
3,400 people here that are just screaming at me to hurry this up. All right. Let's do,
I'm getting three bucks and give me back one penny. No, uh, please make change. Yes.
Why is this going so slow? Done. All right. Now we do the ladder. Okay. Let me just make sure.
Rings ladder to rocket ship.
Okay. I have to, I just bought the scaffolding. I can't not do this. It's been too long. One minute.
Go. I just need to throw three packages. Just wait, just hold on. Just bear with me. I just
need to do, I'm just going to stand here and do JFK only. How many, how many, what do I need?
It's 2.99, right? I have enough now. JFK, come on. JFK, come on. All right. It's not showing me JFK.
Throw like an Oak Oak and JFK only. I got enough, right? Yeah. No, I have to. Yeah. I definitely
have enough. 100%. I'm just going to go in there and just dump all my change on the counter and
just leave. I don't even care about making change. Oh, it's going to do another dollar. If the rocket,
if the rocket lifts off and takes off as like a funny cartoon joke, you owe me an apology.
If I just slide down the slide and that's it, I owe you an apology. We're both in on this.
Ladder to the rocket ship, 2.95. Let's go. Please pay for your purchases. Give me the dollar.
Is the dollar, is it implying it's very heavy? Because look at my hand.
Oh, I got a frog in my throat. All right. That's, I need to 2.95. Dollar,
125, 150, 175, $2. Okay. 2.25, 250. I'm a fucking old lady paying for an ice cream.
2.75. Okay. 2.80. 2.90. I'm just sitting there behind her just going like, get a fucking credit
card. It's not hard. It's very easy. All right. What was it? What? I forgot. 2.95. What am I at?
You startled me. I don't know. Where? How much is up there? Let's go. I like to pay with exact
change so the government can't track me. I don't think the government gives a shit that you find a
large ice cream from Ben and Jerry's. All right. Come on. Buy the boom box. Here we go. This is it.
Oh, this is going to be awesome. I can't wait. That's straw man propaganda.
I'm going in. Let's go. It's going to take off. Do it. Take off. This is huge. All right. This
counts. You thought I was just going to be that top screen. This counts. Oh my God. Why is there
like a 200 foot? No, no, no, no, no, no. Go back. I wouldn't do this. This is scary. All right. You
owe me an apology. You owe me an apology. All right. Are you kidding me? He just did a double
front flip. You owe me an apology. I'm doing it again. The one resident sleeper in there is like
probably my favorite. I would puke if I was up here. This is not safe. These are children.
Double front flip. You don't get an apology from me. That's better than the ship taking off.
Okay. Lame. Lame. So bald. I'm not going to read that. All right. Let me ask you a question.
If I kept this and turn the volume up all the way and muted my microphone and left the room
and zoomed in on the box, would the viewers go up or down? Okay. Uh, this next one, I remember
playing this a long time ago. I don't remember anything about it, but I remember it being a
thing. Um, shuffle puck cafe. I'm not going to do that. Apologize now. I'm sorry that you feel
that way. So shuffle puck cafe is a, you fight against other people playing shuffle puck. Of
course you do. Anyways, uh, I don't know if I want to select my video card game. Is it mouse?
This game is weird. You know, um, what's that Christopher Robin game where you have to hit
the baseball and hit a home run Winnie the Pooh, Christopher Robin baseball, whatever it's called,
the whole, like whatever it is, it's kind of like that. They progressively just get insanely
difficult. Okay. Here we go. So, uh, you pick an opponent. Let's pick the pig. This is not,
this is not a porn game. What are you talking about? Oh my God. That was, is it turned up or
did I, does it turn down? I think I might've turned it up too high. Should I turn it down?
It's air hockey. Yeah. Why did I not say air hockey? It's a game where you, you
shuffle puck again. It's air hockey. As you can tell, it's pretty hard. It's especially,
it's running at like, my game is running at like 20 frames a second. His game is running at like
60 frames a second. It's not fair. This is what happens when a PC player plays a console player.
This is why you can't, the cross-platform don't work. All right. Hold on. I'm going to try
something, a tactic here. I'm going to try to go into the top right corner every time.
No. Oh my God. Look, he's lining up a shot.
It's not as easy as it looks. It's look, look at the frames. Come on. Like give me a break.
It's not frame perfect. Like you think it is. Go back to, no, this is not one of the hard ones.
Hold on. I'm just going to, I think, I think the pig is hard. How many points does it take
for me to get embarrassed? I wonder. Okay. Hold on. Oh, I'm using that technique. If I have like
10 frames a second, then I can fill the whole board with a giant paddle. Why are we playing
to 15? We shouldn't be playing to 15. That's what makes no sense. I know it's just let it fall in.
Just do it. Just get it. Do it. Do it. I'm going to play the easy one.
And this game was so much fun though. It read at so much better frame rate in my brain.
When I played it, I played this on an original Mac. All right. I lost. Game. Wait. Define keys.
Champions. Biff raunch is 15 and 14. Okay. Paddle. No, I can't lose. Somebody said, okay.
I don't think this is regulation. He's got a chalkboard eraser and I have an entire lane
of bowling bumpers. See, he's easy though. Look at this. Watch how slow. I'm just going to show
you. Watch how slow he does this. See that the pig was hard. It was a hard one. All right. I'm
going to, I can drop the, all right. I'm going to, I'm going to put it down to a smaller. Look at
that. That's so much easier. I hold on. How do I, can I like, there we go. All right. Paddle size.
Let's put it back to normal. It was a 20. All right. I will beat you. Locker, no blocker,
small blocker, custom blocker, whatever that means. All right. Here we go. All right. Let's go. Yeah.
He's absolutely stupid. Like I will win no matter what. I have to give myself a,
no. Look at, see, I went right to the hardest thing in the game. That was my problem. Make it
one or you're a fake gamer. I don't think you can even do that. I'm going to win. This is embarrassing.
No, new opponent. This is just, this is, this is a hustle. No, it's not. Chalk eraser versus a piece
of chalk. I wonder if I do it really hard. If it'll break through his hologram shield. Do it.
You're going to make them cry. No, new opponent. This is like, this is embarrassing for you. I
don't want to just have you lose by this much. Let's do, let's go back to 20 and new opponent.
I know there's a, I think the robot is the hardest thing in the whole game.
I think the robot's actually impossible. So let's see. Why was the pig so hard? The robot is always
the hardest one. This guy's the champion. Did I do something? Did I change a setting? Why was the
pig so unbearable? But the robot's not. I swear I have this memory of it being like around the edges.
I must have fucked something up. You just sucked when you last played. No, no way.
No way. New opponent. Look, here he is. I didn't just suck when I last played. I'm sorry guys.
That's not the case. His cursor is actually teleporting. See if I can beat him though. I'll
try. Jesus. Ooh, it's going to be close. I'll do it. I can do it. Boomer versus a zoomer.
I'm an idiot. Why does everybody have to be a boomer and everybody have to be a zoomer?
And I don't even know which one is who in that scenario. Why is it always going to be about
boomer? Seriously, don't ask me how actual 12 year old me was able to do this. Nice. All right,
I got the advantage. This is the champion, right? It's because you probably used a bigger paddle.
You know, I probably did. I'm trying to sneak it into the corner. I'm still in game. All right,
I'm going to wait till his cursor is on the left and then go. I'm trying to do a tennis strategy.
It's not really working. He doesn't know about the second form. They don't evolve. Hey, I say
that's what happens when I look over a chat. If I was in a tournament and we were about to start,
I wouldn't look over at the audience and go, what did somebody just say? No, I would play. Let's go.
No professional athlete in the world like a baseball player doesn't get up to the batter's
box with the bat in his hand, step into the plate and right before the pitcher starts to pitch
turns around and like asks a question to the fucking people in the stands behind him.
No, he just focuses and he plays the damn game. I was imagining a baseball player is standing
in the batter's box and he's responding to somebody that's behind him calling him bald.
Or this looks like looks like Jay Albertson at the plate here seems to be arguing with somebody
behind home plate, the home plate baseball. That was a ball, but it looks like they're screaming.
He's pointing at his head saying it's I'm not. I'm not. I'm not sure what he's talking about here,
Frank. What does that mean? No, he took the helmet off. He took the helmet off. He's pointing his
hair. He's getting loud now. He's been ejected from the game. This is the only fucking platform
where this happens. All right. I got, I got some more. What about a comedy show? Yeah, but
you're not like a professional comedy athlete. A comedian doesn't go on stage and open up shuffle
puck and play it with his back to the audience. All right. I can still do it. Come on. Three more.
Well, why wouldn't you? I don't know. I'm not supposed to be looking over here. All right.
Tied it up. Two more and I beat this guy. One more. Here we go. Oh,
no. Give me the ball. Give me the puck. Give me the puck. You lose. Hey, take those shoulders
back to Alderman. You fucking idiot. Who's next? I think this is the hard one. This guy's only
playing with one hand. He's like drinking. So am I, but I'm drinking coffee. That's the difference.
You can do it. Who plays air hockey with two hands? Oh yeah. It's not a Ouija board.
So who's the hardest person in here? It's definitely not you. You don't have enough power.
All right. That was, I had insane amount of spin on that. Look at this. He's all defense. He has
no offense. I'm just gonna walk away from the table. What about who's under here? Oh, he put
his hand up. Yeah, you're real bad. Not even up to a challenge. It's not even worth, it's not worth
my time. It's not. I'm sorry. Hey, thanks for playing. I'm way, way higher on like the tier list
than you, but I could make you feel happy. You want me to make you like feel better?
Oops. Okay. There you go. You got a point. Good work. You, yeah. Do not Disney movie me. I'm not
gonna let that happen. I'm out. Here we go. Is her paddle smaller? Why does she have a smaller paddle?
The hell was that? Uh, so that's cheating. So you, that you cheated. I don't get to do that.
Okay. That's an automatic disqualification. Ah, the role play gets harder when you beat him enough.
I know this one character in this game that you have magic powers. That's really cool. Actually,
that's really cool. Who's anybody in the back? What about, what was that? What was this little guy?
Is this the guy? Is the little Yoda guy? That's impossible. This is me. This is me. I did the
same thing. This is me. That's weird. I did this like fucking 25 minutes ago. Same tactic. I can't
fucking believe it. And he's going to lose with one point. That's unbelievable. All right. Who's
the last character? Who's this? Uh, looks like a beer. All right. Well, I didn't know you're
going to do that. Sorry. I beat the hardest. I beat the one up. I beat the champion. Maybe not.
He does this little wind up. Oh man. Is it bad? Uh, is this Biff? I got to score at least one
point on Biff right in the corner. I might, I might be able to do it. It's, it's really possible.
That was so fast. You can't even see it. Ah, shit. That technique doesn't work. Stop doing it. Oh,
I'm going to lose. I'm just realizing that this, yeah, there's not very much safety here.
Imagine playing, um, air hockey with somebody without the barrier in front of you. You would
get so hurt. I actually broke my finger before playing air hockey when I was younger. I had those
friends and you know, some of you guys have them because when you play air hockey,
there's this unwritten agreement that you're not going to fucking murder each other.
Nobody wants to go as hard as they can. Crack, crack, crack. You have an unwritten rule that
you're just going to play and no one's going to really go as hard as they can. See, my friends
didn't do that. Friends of mine would try to go as hard as they can. And what would end up happening
is it would hit the sides and bounce up and it was not cool. And sometimes they would do it too
hard and it would hit the sides, bounce up and like, like kind of like go by. And you'd be like,
stop that bullshit. Let's stop that. Well, one of those times it bounced up, caught me right in the
finger. And then we all got grounded. I, why did I get grounded? I have nothing to do with it.
Fuck. He's going to embarrass me. Did this happen last week? No, it happened when I was like 14.
They need to make these things out of like a squishy material nowadays. Do they still make
these things in a hard plastic? You know, many times I've been in an arcade and you just hear
you look behind you and that thing is on its edge rolling down. It's like easy guys.
Oh, you should have to wear like a big heavy glove. Yeah. Before you play this game,
you should have to put on, it will not activate unless you put on this big, heavy fucking gauntlet
that's like like 20 pounds. So you can't do it hard. I think I saw all the opponents, right?
Yeah. This is the guy's the hardest. So I think we saw everybody. Unless there's somebody down here.
No, this is just Martini guy. Play the robot. You want us to beat the robot badly and see what he
does? Robot, robot. All right. I'll beat the robot and then look, he's, he's very easy.
There's a droid setting. Anybody else do this when you play air hockey with somebody?
I don't like air hockey. I don't because it's a lot of money.
Usually it's like a $1.50. It's usually one to $2 to play it. And usually the other person is
way more excited to play than you are. And you have to deal with instead of Oh, I really want
to go play time crisis. That sounds like a lot of fun. Now you have to block out the next like
30 straight minutes to pretend to enjoy playing air hockey. You can't leave the table. It's to
say somebody Oh, you know, you scored one and I scored one. And then Oh, you missed. Oh, wait,
this is nice. Nice like volley we've got going here. It lasts for like 20 to 30 minutes.
And the table keeps producing air out of the holes until somebody wins. So you can't just leave.
Nobody wants to take over your game for you because they want to do their own. But usually
this one just dominant person. That's the one that they want to play there that you're that I want
to let's do air hockey. Yeah. You just don't give a shit. Now I've been the air hockey enthusiast
before. But there's never really a time when both people are incredibly enthusiastic about it.
Sometimes it's even both are very not enthusiastic about it. You walk around the arcade four times.
Oh, you even play air hockey, I guess. And then you both lazily play it. And neither one of you
has any fun. I have fun. Maybe you shouldn't go to the arcade. We had an air air hockey table when I
was kid, but friends of mine did the exact thing you're describing. And I didn't I was afraid to
play it because I didn't want to break my finger. Yeah. And something else too. I'll tell you another
thing. I don't I don't like the loud noises it makes. Is that am I weird? Anytime somebody gets
like into back, back, back, back, back. It's like it's I don't like it. It's really fucking loud.
It's like freaking me out. When you see your friend like queue up for like a big hit and you're like,
don't do it, please don't do it, please. And they go, boom. It's like, oh, I don't want that. All
right. So we'll just do it again. Droid. Oh, oh, no, I'm turning. I'm turning him into that friend.
This is gonna crash my computer. Speed. I'm gonna break my finger. All right, serve.
I'm gonna sneeze it. I'm really sorry. I'm fine. Okay, let's go. Okay. Have I did I make it
unbeatable? I didn't make it unbeatable. I can do this. It's not unbeatable. If I score one point,
if I score one point, I deserve an apology. He bounces off the edges way too fast from his
serve. Remember I told you Winnie the Pooh home run derby? That's why I said that. Make my paddle
80. No, I can't. I gotta do it legit. What was that little pause? I don't think I'll ever score.
He's at 200. No apologies. That's all right. That's okay. Not gonna move. I have to apologize to you.
Yeah, okay. That's fair. I thought I had it right there. Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry, guys. It's my
fault. And that is Shufflepuck. The weird part about Shufflepuck is I used to sit here for hours
and play this. And I've kind of done everything you can do in this game in 25 minutes. Wait a
minute. Hold on. Death is here. Secret character. Is there somebody under the robe? Eat that. Do
Max paddle? No, I don't think I need that. No, it's not death. It's just some kids doing the
trench coat trick to get into the bar. Because they're not 21. I got one point. That's all I care
about. Let me get one more point. Last one. No, I quit. Lost to kids? No, I'm sorry. That rephrase
that. Lost to three kids. All right. That's it. Let's do the next one. Which one? I knew I wanted
to play this and I knew I wanted to play Donald Duck. I have one or two more that I thought were
interesting. Which is it? Yeah, I know. I already like leaked them. I leaked them out already because
you saw the top of the browser. Dino Park Tycoon is the next one. It's already been leaked. Can
we vote on the games? Yes. But I wanted to do these first because they looked the most interesting to
me because I saw them pop up randomly. So I wanted to try them. This is Dino Park Tycoon.
It's very possible that I may or may not sit here for another four hours. I don't know. Okay, new
game. The bank has approved a business loan of $5,000. Payments will be made monthly. Remember
that you have to buy land, fencing, dinosaurs, and food. Good luck on your venture. Thank you.
Buy land at the real estate office. Dino Diner. Dino City Big Big Sale. Otherwise,
dinosaurs are people, but they also put people in the parks. Is that what I'm understanding here?
So that's weird. Okay, let's go buy real estate. VA, HA, FHA approved. Okay, so we can do
the desert, plains, or the marsh. Peaceful and remote, dry, hot, and flat. 500 bucks an acre.
The plains is mild weather, fertile land, close to towns, a thousand dollars per acre.
Or the marsh. Wet, swampy, plants, and reptiles really love it. I think I have to do desert. This
is the first try. That's cute. What a cute game. All right, so buy. Select a plot of land to
purchase. Front gate is here. Public restrooms. Office food? Foods. This one? Sold. How much money
should I spend? Food? All right, all of it. No, I only have four grand. I'm not going to buy it all.
This is good for now. What about one place in the office? All right, I'm going to do one
office. Restrooms are included, aren't they? All right, that's good. Okay, I got food, one extra
little part of the park, and then an office space here. The other money I can spend on dinosaurs.
Buy fencing at the general store. Order form. All right, you can find it all in the general store
catalog. Fences. Wood. Thousand dollars a pen. Cement wall or electricity. This wood fence,
wood keeps in dinosaurs? Which one's the cheapest? Let's do wood. Oh, shit. Okay,
I'm going to put it over here. Should I do it on all of them? Do I need a fence around the office?
I don't need a fence around the office. That's going to be fine. All right, that's done.
Hire an employee here. I'm almost out of money. 1,400 bucks a month? I don't have any,
I have no money. Maintenance, concession, security, tour guide, management?
Maintenance? Uh, did you just put that in his nose? Maintenance. Holy shit, he's ripping off
his nose. That's a fake nose. His real nose is underneath. I don't know why, why does he want
to make his nose bigger? I'm not going to be able to afford a dinosaur. Don't hire anybody. Hold on.
One maintenance worker. I'm going to need it. Buy a dinosaur at Dino City. Albertosaurus,
Ankylosaurus, Colophysis, Dino-niches, Edmontosaurus, Allosaurus, Corythosaurus.
These are too expensive. Um, I can only afford a Coli-physis or a Dionysus. Diono-chis,
Dionysus, Colo-cholophysis. All right, let's do a Dino. Is it Dino-niches? Dino-niches?
Dino-niches? All right, I'm going to do Dino. Get it. Buy it. What do I do with the egg? I have
250. It's already hatched. Okay. Oh, okay. Put it over here. One Dino. Cool. Now what do I do?
Buy food for the dinosaur. What does he eat? I don't know what this dinosaur eats. Somebody
look it up. Type in, is a Dio-niches a herbivore? Is it meat? $25 a unit. Get out of here. All right,
nobody move. Small feeder. I guess I'm just, it's, let's do two, three, four units. How much is too
much? Set an admission. Oh, here we go. Let's make the money back. Admission prices. Business,
business is bought and sold. Tickets. Nobody is coming to the park. Uh, what? General ledger,
inventory, visits, food, gifts, staff, profit, loss. How do I do this? Check profit statement.
Where's, where's like a guy bank? Current balance. Snacks? So I can't set these? Am I missing
something here? Set the price of the park. You have one Dino and two unused pens. Yeah, tickets,
but it says nobody is coming to the park. No, I don't want to sell the park. You have no
concessions to sell food. Get a loan. Uh, did I do it? Dino, diner, land, general store employment,
staff. Okay. Some more tour guides might be nice. You have four units of meat. You have one. How
do I set the park? Is it, it's not, is it just free? Set admission prices in here. Visits? Oh,
okay. Hold on. Ticket prices for winter. That's fine. Spring. It's going to be more summer. Way
more fall as it can be for this is prime season here. All right. That looks good. Select the park
icon to start. I'm ready to go. Here we go. Is that the dinosaur? Why is he doing a fighting game
entrance? Meat. He does one unit of meat a week. Oh, I'm making money rapidly. All right. Where's
the other pens? This place sucks. This place is terrible. There's a dug hole with water port in
it. It's one dinosaur. There's no paths. I like the song though. All right. Let me get another,
let me get another dinosaur. Cops are here. 4,000? All right. Buy food with dinosaur. How many days
has it been? No, I want another dinosaur. I want an expensive one, a nice one. There's more. Where's
the T-Rex? T-Rex 9750. That's what I want. I have a wait until then. I need a tour guide.
Your dinosaur is going hungry. Buy food. What? Just get this shit out of me.
Should I do a medium unit? Okay. I need a tour guide. Tour guide 900 bucks a month.
That's right. Okay. The tour guide for my one dinosaur in my pool. All right. I want some more.
Let me get a T-Rex in here. Is he getting bigger? I'm real. I just hired that person 900 bucks a
month to just be standing here pointing this way, which effectively a wooden sign could do.
A wooden sign that says Dionosaurus with a blurb about what the dinosaur is could be right here
with the arrow pointing that way. End of winter quarter. Why am I losing money? Oh, right, right,
right. Auction today? For what? Next up we have an Ankylosaurus. Can we have a starting bid at
3,000? We've got 3,000. The guy with the straw hat. Can I get 3,100? 3,300. Is that a good look
it up? What kind of is it? Is it a good dinosaur? Five and a half, five and a half, five and a half,
five and a half. I'm gonna bid Mickey Mouse. This is this animal kingdom. This is where it started.
This is so much money. 5,000?
It's me, right? Did I overpay? 48.50? Is that too much? What should I? All right, go over here.
Next up we have... I blew all my money. A lot of five and a halfs. Sounds like a washing machine.
That's really good. He sounds like... Hey, I'll bid on this one! Juan De Baron, South American
rancher and animal trainer. Tours dinosaur troop worldwide. Headlines Las Vegas. Bid. All right,
no more, no more, no more. 2,100 is my last... I'm up. I'm not going higher than 23. No, you guys
are paying too much. No one's bidding. It said Bernie is bidding big. I've gotta have that
dinosaur. It's really important that I get that home with me. I'm just gonna leave. What the...
I'm just standing here. Wait, let me see. Friz Farflung, genetic research engineer working on
secret government project dealing with dinosaur relativity. I don't have five and a half. I have
two and a six. All right, let's go. Holy shit, that thing is sick. What does it eat? Vegetarian.
Eats three units a week. Oh man. Uh, okay, I gotta... food. Buy food, food, food, food, yeah.
This thing, it's got... how many units? Three units of wheat?
Bushes and trees? This is like more high quality food, right? Three, six, nine, 12. Okay, we'll do...
Do I get 12 of like the high quality food? And then I need to get a little bit... hold on. How
much was that dinosaur if I bought it in real life? Well, I mean, if I bought it from here.
Was it called an ankylosaurus? I got a pretty good deal. I paid almost a thousand dollars less.
A tour guide quit. I mean, lack of payment. You may not have enough money to pay your bills at the
end of the month. Go to the bank if you need a loan. Uh, a maintenance per... there are no employees
here to feed the dinosaurs. Uh, why is everybody gone? Hire an employee... hold on a second. Wait,
wait, wait, wait. Just hold on. You do not have the money for your loan payment this month. The
bank is foreclosed on your park. Better luck next time. I didn't even get a second. What? I had
nine thousand dollars. It told you everybody quit and then you opened the park. Oh, I did...
one more time. One more, one more, one more. I know I got it. I know what to do now.
This time, I'm gonna buy one. We're gonna go to the marsh. I'm gonna buy an office space here
and I'm gonna buy one here. I'm gonna buy two. Okay, don't let this distract you from the fact
that Jerma sneezed into his hands. Would you rather me open up my pants and sneeze down
into my underwear? What are you talking about? I need fences, wood. I'm gonna go right here and
right here. Two dinosaur enclosures. I'm already out of money. How? I'm going right to the bank.
What did I do that was different? Hire an employee here. No, no, no, not yet. Where's the... I need
the bank. Okay, I need, uh, I need to borrow some money. Sorry, your credit limit has been reached.
What? That's a dog shit interest rate too. You should be ashamed of yourself.
Hold on. What am I supposed to do? All right, I'm only supposed to have one enclosure.
I have an idea. Okay, just bear with me for a second. Just bear with me for one second.
I'm gonna make it really expensive. Not that expensive though. That's too much. That's the
roller coaster tycoon with the little AI walks up to the line and immediately turns away.
No, we're gonna make it expensive. And I don't have enough for an employee. I have enough for
a dinosaur, don't I? I don't even have enough for a dinosaur. New plan. Cheapest place. That
was not the cheapest place. That's why. Fuck. Okay, it's all right. Just one spot and a spot
for the office. Done. We're gonna fence in that one spot and I'm gonna buy it, uh, uh, somebody.
Wood? No, no, no, no. He's everyone's like, no, no. Why, why, what happened? What do you mean no?
I'll be fine. This time I'm not gonna do it. Um, look, I'm gonna, everything's gonna be fine.
Just wait. I just need a tour guide. Higher. Okay. Done. 2,500. I'm gonna buy a cheap dinosaur.
Let's go with a, uh, a pentaceratops. That's not, that's not as more expensive. That's okay,
though. No, how about an ornithomimus? Yeah. Right here. Ornithomimus is in there now. I have an
employee. Now I just gotta get food and I'm gonna jack the prices up like crazy and I'm not gonna
spend money. So an ornithomimus eats what exactly? Meats and plants. What's cheaper? 12 bucks or 25
bucks a unit. What about seeds? A dollar a unit. That's cheap. You look it up. What, what, what
shit over here? Oh, I'm crushing the bugs. Okay. I get it. Does it eat plants? I didn't look. Can
I just like scrape this off and put it on toast and feed it to him? I'm gonna look it up. Office.
Okay. Dinosaurs, right? Where's my guide to dinosaurs? Types of dinosaurs. There it is.
Occasionally bipedal and ranged in size from a dog to an elephant. Now that's not it. Where is it?
Ornith, ornithor, ornithomimus. What does it eat? A guide to dinosaurs through the ages.
Types of dinosaurs. Theories about dinosaurs. Okay, here we go. Ornithor, ornithomimus.
Vegetarian eats two units a week. You got it. Let's jack the prices up. Not that much. Six,
six fifties. Fine. Seven in the summer. All right. Two units of vegetables a week.
We have a tour guide. We're gonna do small feeders. I'll buy 10 units. Fuck, that was me.
That was me. That's it. That was ha ha ha. At least I own it. Open the park. Let's go.
Here we go. Come on. Where are all the people? Oh boy. Seven dollars to see a single stupid
dinosaur nobody's ever heard of. What's wrong with that? This dinosaur is cool. Why do you
have such a problem with this dinosaur? I think he's cool. Although I need more people. Spend
money on your dinosaur is going hungry. Okay, now I'm gonna let's go to the I have two spots,
right? Should I get another employee? No, I need to build up money first. Maybe I should get another
small dot. Maybe I should get two of them. They get along in the same pan. I put I put them in
the same pen, right? I gotta lower the prices. You're right. It's too expensive. You're right.
You're right. You're right. You're right. You're right. Drop prices. Oh, people are not happy.
Drop it. Five. 450. All right. That should help. There we go. Load up. End of winter quarter.
I'm not gonna click it. I'm not gonna click it. It'll screw everything up. All right. I need more
dino food. How many units I got? Plenty. Let's get some more high quality food in here. All right.
Good. How do I? I got it. I have a pen. I have a second pen. I need a meat eater. Which one of
these eats meat? Does the pentaceratops eat meat? Because I have 10 of them. Who eats meat here?
Me. I do. How about the iguanodon? No. I have to go look it up. Vegetarian. Vegetarian.
Vegetarian. Vegetarian. Vegetarian. Vegetarian. Vegetarian. Vegetarian. Vegetarian.
Meat. No. I already had you. Vegetarian. Meat. No. Vegetarian. Vegetarian.
The allosaurus is two units of meat a week. I want an allosaurus.
No. Climate is wrong. I need a wetlands dinosaur. What's the cotton candy one? That's
the tyrannosaurus? Okay. No. That's splatoon dinosaur. He was just underground sliding around
in splatoon. Uh. Vegetarian. Vegetarian. Marsh. Here we go. Does nobody from the marsh eat meat?
Desert. Desert. Marsh. Vegetarian. Marsh. Vegetarian. Come on. Really? You gotta be
kidding me. None of... I have to just get another... whatever. I'm just gonna get another
dinosaurus. Whatever the hell it is. Or an allosaurus. How much money do I have?
I'm doing it. There's no pen here. I need to get a pen. Please don't come out of the pen.
Stop. I know. I know. But how do I put the fence on? No. No. No. Back up. Back up. Quick. Quick. Feed
the dinosaur. All right. I... I need to go to the general store and get fence. Wood. Right here.
God damn. All right. Will this... I can't even buy another one of these. This thing eats meat.
Just give it to me. That's the one I had last game. Hire people? Not yet. I'll blow all my money. I
need to wait till I have over like 10-15 grand. We're good. Okay. I got two dinosaurs now. How
much meat do I have? Pay the loan. Pay the loan. Pay the loan. Pay the loan. Current loan amount.
Pay off. Monthly payment. I'm doing fine. I don't need to do that. I'm fine. I'm doing a monthly
payment. All right. Now I need to go to food. Make sure I have enough food. I'm almost out of food.
Let's do like 20. Let's just get a bunch. 30. All right. End of spring quarter. I got 10 grand.
I'm gonna hire some people. Management. That's very expensive. Concessions. Tour guide. Maintenance.
Let's get a veterinarian. I thought she just crunched into that egg. Like bit into it.
All right. We have a veterinarian now. 2,700 bucks a month. I have a tour guide. I'm gonna do
a concessions chef. 3,800 bucks a month. All right. Slow down. Maintenance. I already have maintenance
guide, don't I? All right. This is half my money. I can't do anything else. I bought so much food.
Who's going hungry? What? We're good. I need another pen. General store.
Should I get another pen? General store. Concessions. Food stand. Sell treats like dino dogs.
Wait. We're eating them. Restrooms. Get them up there. Buy them. A gift stand.
Parking lot. Food stand. That's 5,000. I can't do it. I have a chef who's just walking around in
a chef costume. He's not doing anything. I handed him a broom and I was like, can you sweep up a
little? I'm doing it. Fuck it. All right. Do I have food here? Is it there? Okay. I think I'm good.
Uh oh. Bleeding money. Bleeding money. What do I do? I have to fire somebody. Fire the chef.
Where's the other pen? Wait. Hold on. No, no, no, no, no. Go back, back, back. Who is starving?
I am bleeding money. Bushes and trees. Buy a worker. I have like 10 workers. No, no, no, no, no,
less, less, less, less. End of the summer quarter. Let's put those ticket prices up or down. I need
to look at my, I gotta go to the office. I gotta look at see what's going on here. Check profit
statement. Last month's profits were 900 bucks. Not bad. Let's see. All right. Okay. This is going
to come down though. Wait. Food. Clerks. Stands. How do I make this more money? Staff. 5200 bucks
a month. Who can we lose? Nobody. Um, it's, everything's going fine. I'm going to need
another dinosaur though. A big one. One that can pull in big numbers. Are we doing enough food?
I'm going to get a T-Rex next. I'm already out of fucking food again. All right. Uh,
let me go to real estate for a second. So we've got one here. Spot up there. Spot up here.
What do I got? 5900. How much is a T-Rex? I did it. Okay. Now I'm going to save money until I get,
I can afford a T-Rex. I'm firing somebody too. I'm bleeding money, I think. Fire the tour guide.
No, I think the tour guide is necessary. Should I make the prices cheaper or should I make them
more expensive? Cheaper? To get more people? Why can I not set the prices? Do I have to set the
prices per year? I don't get to change my prices. It's, everything's fine. 49 cheap winter tickets
and expensive summer tickets. Yeah, that's what my theory was before too. This would be an 8 out of
10 stream, but that fly is making it a 6 out of 10. You can't fuck out of here. Your annual income
tax for the park was $333. You're going to tax me. End of the year. Make any changes for first
quarter now. Clock has stopped and will resume when you leave the office. Here we go. So let's
make the ticket price in the winter, 4 bucks. Spring, 5 bucks. Summer, 6 bucks. Fall, 5 bucks.
650. Does it lay the house out? I can't make it that cheap. $7 for summer? That's kind of high.
3, no, 350, 450, 7, 5. 650 and 5. Same thing with food. Let's go. It looks fine, right?
Staff, 52 per month. All right. That seems pretty good. What about my bank loan? Okay. Current
balance is, why is the balance of more than what I, current loan amount, 33. All right. Okay,
I was going to say, what are you talking about? I think that's good. Snacks. You have one concessions
and one food stand. People are vandalizing the property. Get security. Shit. 45 people
came to the park yesterday. That's really bad. How many people go to Disney World every day?
Like 300,000 people. That's not good. 45? All right. I think I'm ready. You have 11 units of
meat and 12 units of plants. All right, let's go. What else do we got? Advertising. Somebody
just said that. Flyers. Cheap way to reach people. Just hand these out. Flyers. Newspaper. What's
this? Free our extra super special deluxe bonus gift package when you spend $10,000 or more.
Oh, all right. All right. Let's do, let's do cheap flyers. And I also need a fence. My money. My
money. My money. Open the park. Ah, why? What's happening? What's happening? Why is this? Hey,
what's happening? What's going on? I need a loan right now. All right. I just got a loan.
I'm just hemorrhaging money. What am I hemorrhaging money on? The staff? There's too
many people that work here. I had to buy food. Oh, I'm in trouble. I have to fire everybody.
How do I fire people? Bring them all in. Bring every, you may not have enough money to pay your
bills at the end of the month. Go to the bank if you need a loan. How do I fire? Fire. Fire. Fire.
Fire. You fired. You fired. You fired. Fire. Fire. Fire. Fire. Fire. Fire. Staff. How do I fire people?
How do I fire people? There's no way I can't. People are throwing rocks.
I'll sell it. You've made the top 10 list. What's your name? Yoink. See you later. Somebody else's
problem now. Stop playing and hope they don't notice. Well, that's that. That was cute. That
was cute. Uh, the next one that I have here selected, this should be an interesting one.
It's called Rockstar. Well, you, you play as a rock star. You have to be a rock star or something.
It's just seem like a fun thing to do. Uh, those mesmerizing new age hypnosis. The wizard game.
Proudly. No, Fred, your amusement and amazement, bewilderment and confusion. The latest
psychedelic is driving against rock star. Welcome to the wonderful world of wizard games. You've
never seen anything like this before. We don't waste your money on fancy packaging and glossy
advertising. We won't insult your intelligence with childish graphic challenges. We just write
unique games that you will be addicted to where nothing is ever the same twice. You're not entering
the world of your own imagination where nothing can be taken for granted. So beware all concepts,
coding and artwork by wizard games credit where credit is. Do you want to load an existing game?
Uh, no, the folders, the full enhanced version. Uh, so you want to be a rock and roll star? Well,
listen now to what I say. Just get yourself an electric guitar and find some time to learn
how to play in a week or two. That's what this game is all about. In a week, learn how to play
the guitar in a week. Sex, drugs and rock and roll. You have learned to play and got a band together
and now you are chasing the big time. You want to be a megastar to top the world popularity polls
and have number one records everywhere. To achieve this, you must work hard, tour extensively,
spend lots of time and money in recording studios and video studios, do radio and tv
sessions and interviews and generally plan a campaign for world domination. Of course,
you'll find also time to enjoy yourself. There'll be groupies and parties and holidays and plenty
opportunities for overindulgence, but you mustn't overdo it or you'll end up in hospital or even
dead. Luckily your manager, dodgy Sam, your band and your friends question mark are there to give
you loving advice and protection, but are you up to it? Can you cope with the music business and be
a rock star? What skill level do you want to play at? One to five. Two. Three. I'm not doing five.
Three. What is your stage name? Jax. No, not Yoink. Electric Jerma? Electric? Larry Electric?
Is that lame? That's too lame, right? Electric Leo. I don't hate that one. I like Electric Leo.
No, not Larry the Loser. I'm doing Electric Leo. All right, let's go. Done. Do you want to change
any other artists' names? This is a whole roster of... I'm not doing that. Press highlight a key
or cursor keys and return to... All right, you are doing nothing. What do you want to do? Laze
around for a while. Write songs and practice. Gig. Record a single or album. Have a holiday.
Visit your doctor. Consult your analyst. Unwind in a sanitarium. Let's go to the doctor. That was
very fast. Hold on. I should probably slow this down. You are surprisingly healthy. You should
stop smoking. You are quite healthy, really. Eat an apple every day. Let's go back to the doctor.
You're quite healthy, really. You should stop smoking. All right, but my health is... All right,
let's go. Let's laze around for a while. New music maker UK popularity poll published today. New
single released by AYDS called Yellow Basket. New single released by The Giant Panda called Swelling
Up. Just do drugs. Your current drug habits are booze. Fairly regular. More drugs, please.
Lots more drugs. Better cut down a bit. Give it up. Continue with the game. Where's my... Do I have
money? Well, what happened? What do you do for drugs? I dabble in some weed air in there.
What happens if I do them all? Okay, I've done them all. So I've done every drug. 100% psycho.
All right, let's write a song. Oh no. What the fuck? What the fuck? What? What? Wait. Whoa. Whoa.
Whoa. Okay. No, no, no, no, no. What the fuck? Out. Out. Out. Jesus Christ. That's not fucking
cool. Not cool. Out. Out. Get it out. Holy shit. Not fucking cool. I'm out of here. New game.
Damn it. It's your turn. For the love of God. Where do you want to go? They always gotta fuck
it up. That could have been fun too. Not cool. That's not fucking cool. Come on. Let's go.
Where should we go now? It is up to you. Choose wisely. Very wisely. Why can you not see this?
Oh, it broke. It broke. It broke. All right. Now you can go. You really don't want to play Scrabble.
Codename Iceman. You, you don't want me to play Scrabble. No, you don't. You don't. I can't believe
you really want me to do this. You guys wanted me to get away from the Donald Duck game. Let's be
clear. Stop playing Donald Duck, but dear God, by a huge majority, get into Scrabble and play that
for an hour. Okay. The people who have spoken. It is a great game, but okay. The deluxe computer
edition of Scrabble. 1948. Computers didn't even exist. Look at that mouse. That's an old fucking
mouse. I don't even remember how to play Scrabble. I really don't remember. Okay. Play. File. New game.
How many players? Three. Enter the name of player one. Me. Scale level.
Human. Name of player two. CPU one. Scale level a nine. CPU two. But dumb.
CPU dumb. It's gonna be a one. Here we go. Me. Why can I see their titles? Me. Enter your word.
All right. So we start here. I got best. What's going on? Best? Okay. Wait, this computer is
going through every possible fucking word. What? That's so unfair.
CPU dumb has decided to do. Do. That was some like doctor strange shit right there.
All right. Well, in my turn sprinted. Okay. What can I do? Uh, how about
to fabulous. We west fast.
I got one shaft. Oh, I wonder what the next CPU is going to do. It's broke.
Why use off its brain power for the last one? Why is it when I move the mouse? I don't understand.
It's going to every letter and doing every single dictionary possibility. Hurry up, please.
I'm doles. All right. CPU dumb is thinking fibs. My score. My time. Um, you know, uh,
he, the beep wash, wash. No, I don't have it. Uh, gas fast,
spew. And that's, uh, words. That's a double word score, right? Spew. All right. Come on,
hurry up. I don't even take this long. Why was the first one so fast? And this is just,
it's, it sits at every single point to stays there. Go on, hurry up. I don't have enough ram
fi y at a timer. 10 seconds. Let's go. Hurry up. Not so easy. Is it? Wow. X. What did the dumb
one do? T. Oh shit. Um, hex, hex, hex. Oh, don't do it. Don't fucking do it. What? CPU dumb is
thinking pine. Okay. Um, it's not enough time. Hex. What the fuck? CPU dumb is thinking now.
What will it replace? What? What do you mean? What word was that? What word? Oh shit. Um, age.
I don't know. No, no, no, no. Just stop. So all right. I gotta be looking with, uh, time.
I can't do that in 10 seconds. It's not going to happen. CPU one wins. Don't matter. Change the
timer. 30 seconds. Well, I could just, I could just change it to 10 seconds every time, right?
Yeah. I can just take forever. They get 10 seconds. Okay. So we've got, uh, fate time.
Will that work? That it's not time. That's how you misspell time when you talk really fast.
Timer, timer, timer. Uh, add tad mad. I could do mad, mad, mad. CPU one is stumped.
Well, that means they're replacing their words. They're, they're okay. What do you win Scrabble
when you run out of letters? Mad max fibs. Tim. I could do gin, right? G where? Right here. Like
the drink. And then that's it, right? Tiny hex new. Oh no, I'm giving you an infinite time here.
Enough. No. Okay. It's so unfair. Remap. Okay. CPU dumb is thinking. Doesn't have any words. Okay.
I'm done. I don't want to play this anymore. The timer.
Other options. Edit. No two letter words. No S words. No swear words. No S words.
Special. All right. Let's, let's turn off no S words. Let's see what that does. So then let's
say, let's write shit. All right. We got E. E. Mad. Tiffany. I need another. Okay. I need an F.
I need an F. Is there an F somewhere? Oh my God. It has to be an F somewhere, right?
Where's Tiffany? It can be, the blank can be anything, but I need, all right. Is there,
I can't go like Tiffany. Can I go up? This, okay. You can do nifty. Holy shit. I can go up.
That's 48 points. What do you mean it doesn't work like that? It's Tiffany. What does it say?
I have 48 points.
This is, somebody said this isn't Japanese. Like what, what, what don't, they don't, what are you
talking about? I don't even know what that means. Who reads up? I just didn't know the rules. Why
does it have 48 points then? Bottom to top. Just go with nifty. Oh, my fucking stomach hurts.
That's only going to give me 36 points. If I do the upside down Tiffany, it's 48.
Affinity? Good thing we have a timer. No, it doesn't fit.
How is that less than the upside down Tiffany? Do you understand? I'm doing it. T-I-F. T-I-F.
T-I-F. I'm losing. Listen to me. T-I-F. Tiffany. Tiffany. 48 points. Lock it in.
Oh, I added it to the dictionary. Hurry up. Let's go. CPU one.
In. You're supposed to be a nine CPU level. CPU dumb wrote. Oh, oh yeah. Oh, what? Oh shit.
I'm the timer. What are you going to do? Pass. My turn. E-E-E-Gok. E-Gokturbest.
That's a word. What do you mean the word empty? Yeah, it is.
217 points. Let's go. You can literally add anything. A. A. Chad. Car. You can do better
than that. Your time is up. No, it's not. Okay. What are you going to do? Veg. This is like a
super word score, right? I was hoping I could get like a T. I would do like Vegeta. Fucking stupid
timer. I could do like instead of Vegeta, it could be like Vegeva or like Vigova. Vrejiza.
R-R-R-Rigova? V-V-V-Vigova. Oh my God. The timer. I have to get out of this.
Rude. All right. Turn the timer off now, please. My favorite Dragon Ball Z character. Vegeva.
Vigova. What's his power level? Vigova? Uh. I'm the guy that you play... Listen. You play
plane scrabble with somebody that is shit faced and they're too drunk for you
to explain that what they're doing is stupid or wrong there you just got to
have to let them do it Oh Vegeta yeah oh yeah okay dude whatever like I should
probably slow down this is all fucked up I'm currently losing so what has the
most points what did that letter just go where'd the letter go and why can I not
pick it up you Tiffany you Tiffany oh yeah that's that's Tiffany you're right
you're right yeah you Tiffany yeah that that's her name that's not a word but
nah yeah you Tiffany I Tiffany you Tiffany I Tiffany whatever you were
drinking tonight man I would highly recommend you don't anymore see if you
want is gonna pass you you yeah the goof the goof out me wins with 343 points
no plus one me and that will lead us in to our first break of the night I'm
right back I'll see you guys in a small moment you're back shall we continue I
think we shall over here the list we are gonna do we'll do like another one or
two here click on the screen if you'd like dungeons of death super carts not
playing Scrabble again Mickey jigsaw puzzles could be kind of fun
codename ice we need more Disney more Donald okay dungeons of death it is thank
you for voting let's check it out is it gonna load come on loading dungeon of
death there it is loading images sorry said this sounds way cooler than it
probably is I'll start a new challenge I guess we'll do the introduction the
kingdom is in need of a new king there are no more descendants to the throne
the king has decided to issue a challenge the first person to survive
the dungeon will become the new king rescue the crown from the dungeon of
death and become king or die in the process make your way down to the bottom
of the dungeon find the portal door and teleport into the throne room all right
starting a challenge and to the number of dungeon levels 6 to 12 let's just go
with like 8 I didn't purchase food healing potion extreme healing potion
how much money do I have 150 okay let's buy food enter item number to buy food
let's do like 20 food a healing potion I don't know should I scroll I'm gonna do
two scrolls I don't have enough for a magic potion how about some crossbow
bolts all right I'll keep like 35 bucks all right let's go that's all I want and
buying seven oh dear all right so I'm in a dead end I guess I'm just gonna go
forward how do I fight you may not go in that direction yeah cuz it's a ghost in
front of me how do I fight the ghost pass what no I don't want to pass this
isn't Scrabble I want to fight Oh a cherry just you may not go in that
direction open the chest so I can open okay I just I pressed Oh open take grab
get okay you get some money get gee what is this okay get the key oh it's a
little item store all right don't I have a bow how about you shoot minutes I
think I'm sleeping oh my god look at the food how do you how do I stop sleeping
how do I stop sleeping stop sleeping stop sleeping wake up please you sleep
for an hour okay I didn't touch anything listen my hands are off the keyboard
hands up they're up here do you hear this I'm not touching shit they're in
the air see I'm not touching the fucking keyboard he ate all the food and just
lay down I'm dead you body needs seven hours of sleep I guess hold on let me
try this again I was eating in my sleep yeah makes no sense so s is sleep not
shoot let's get that right so shoot maybe is F for fire all right online
instructions a attack there will be two bars one to aim up and down and one to
aim left and right the bars in position press enter the second bar will then be
displayed when that bar is in position so it's a golf game Tiger Woods presents
dungeon of death open get E is heal sleep these view whoa whoa easy easy all
right this is T's teleport fireball is F spells purple online commands yeah all
right I think I got it let's take some more food because that was ridiculous
I'm gonna take two healing potions I'll take some more bolts because that's all
I have for this and I'll take one scroll and that's it let's go I'm ready a is
attack there's already a dragon in front of me did I hit it you and you missed
who's but somebody's just behind him oh my god direct hit okay hit the monster
how much help does the monster have F a fireball now don't sleep don't sleep
thank God I killed you've killed the monster in here hey hi it's my turn this
is like I was gonna say Chad mr. Krabs but I don't think that was very funny
take it as he will you find some food on the dead monster more food that's blood
yeah those Larry the lobster is just Chad Krabs you're right so why would I
need to say that why is there no spooky music I don't know and then MPs I thought
it was a an NPC yeah in the head let's go for the head I don't think that
person was attacking me giant rat it is a giant rat missed it was deflection
actually I didn't miss kill the monster all right I hit the door there is a door
blocking your way open there's no closed chest here maybe they need a key when
they're keying that chest you are hurt opening the chest how did I stub my toe
on it I don't know how snake didn't really know we walked by each other
right them up pretty decent graphics though for a game that came out when
none of you were alive I don't have any more bows oh turn around and run run
run away where how are you appearing in front of me heal Frankie healing potion
II I'm gonna run away and sleep why is he always in front of me how do I get
rid of this stupid snake please leave me alone
there's snakes in every direction sleep oh I think I pressed it three times I
went one two three did I I went like one to three all right I think it's only
gonna be three hours we've just read a food and it's gonna start coming down
but I should be awake eat all the food over the course of two days and you
sleep and then die in your sleep because you don't eat any food in an hour those
those apples are poisonous you don't eat a shitload of apples
and then die unless they're poisoned maybe I pressed it four times drink a
health potion come on I didn't press it more than one whatever I'm dead I didn't
press it more than three times it just I think it gets stuck no that was fun it
was snake in every corner of the room that's all right now what eight forty
apples in one hour of sleep and then dies Mickey's jigsaw puzzles Disney
theme tonight apparently has he done Scrabble I did Scrabble it went as well
as you think it did okay how do you vote you just click the screen wherever you
want if you click there a little bubble will appear like for instance if you
click on RBI baseball right now a bubble will appear right now on the screen just
do it just do it watch see there you go wire that's right there Mickey's jigsaw
puzzle let's open it up can I just do a little one we're not to sit her all day
right use the arrow keys to highlight an option and then press enter to select it
video system I think that's fine mouse timer on grid lines on text messages on
you can still you printer is set up I think this is fine I know what's gonna
okay Mickey's jigsaw puzzle which one do I want to do the dungeon what's the next
picture Mickey in space nothing in that drink the band I do like the band Mickey
playing football Mickey playing football Mickey surfing on the sidewalk with a
skateboard skateboarding well there he is I see him baseball ballet looks like
or gymnastics tennis dance studio but what's that what's in there why is the
urine in there that's not water is it beer juice nobody what it's honey that's
not honey there's bubbles in it over the wall we've also got many talking on
the phone the tree house dangerous to be up there Mickey we have the horseback
riding the magician show and under the sea all right wait there's more please
insert another puzzle disk into the drive oh never mind which one I think
the band one is pretty good oh shit I broke it reload this shit you reloaded
it'll be fun the band I think it should be the band or the underwater underwater
a band which one literally the first one I see underwater a band when I look at
so how is this gonna be hard how long is gonna be why do I watch this stream I
don't know all right four pieces should I do four or it's 64 that's gonna take
too long let me just see what it looks like this is actually gonna be pretty
easy all right so uh time I will do this in 15 minutes puzzle pieces all
right let's go oh it's got the outlines it's like it's cheating that's the
outline there I got it I'm gonna do it right all right so I knew that that's
fine I knew that was gonna be there here we go always at the corners first 15
minutes this is Donald he's over here always do the edges first if you get the
top edge top part here it's Donald right here okay I need more top edges and go
puzzles off what do you mean it's fucked up it's fine why do you guys tell me
this is not the top edge hey what what are you talking about you go around a
circle you do the whole thing around the edges and then you do it you go you do
the all edges first looking for one more where is it they already have my is it
already out so hold on is it okay okay okay it has to be up here whole top edge
is done now we do the whole left side you got to get the outline of the picture
first bingo what cuz I didn't have it up it's don't whatever I want to figure it
out I need the whole left side you don't think I'm gonna do this in 15 minutes
you lost your mind how do you got that piece Donald's already in the right spot
what is this I got some of right edge here if you see an edge just pick it up
bottom corner that's not it might be an edge I see one yeah I do too we got any
more edges and you know if I need the bottom bottom doesn't need to perfect
just get it in the right spot bottom just get it there there's the corner I
don't see any more edges there we go there's a shoe oh I got it we're good oh
dear it's fine 64 pieces is nothing it really is nothing I got 10 straight
minutes of this I can start to build out now I see hmm it was goofy I'm going
against it I shouldn't be doing this stop doing this there's no reason to do
this just do what I know I get it done right are you gonna edge right here
microphone it's the bottom edge right here look at that saxophone edge his
arms out long they are okay hold on saxophone it's a little weird okay I
think I'm good now I can sort of build out his goofy space six minutes we're
fine get this out of the way the hand is down
here somewhere the guitar in front of your lap it's all right it'll be fine
this is goofy bottom piece all right bottom piece I got plenty of time so
don't worry about me something's wrong though what's wrong let go of this I
want to put it down there we go huh let's do goofy's mouth how's that wrong
because this is wrong let's do this is Mickey's guitar how is he playing the
guitar does he have three hands okay that's goo I thought he was like arms
rough like this like both hands extended they got the same gloves on guys give me
a break they have the same size hand and they're both wearing this teal blue
Robin's egg glove this could have been this this could have been this it's
identical all right hold on that I think that's in the right spot it's down here
at the floor all right I actually am running out of time um put it down how
do I put it down shit okay hold on wait this is like right here somewhere right
there I'm good I'm good I'm gonna make this Mickey's head one of his ears okay
good whose pants are these this is no it's not Mickey's okay right there come
on where is this where is this where is this I don't know I don't know put it
down okay this is Donald's back is the drum it goes right here good okay done
good good good good I got time is the disco ball what is this what piece is
this right here stereo is over where's the stereo right there I got three
minutes I'm fine I dicked around too much there's something on fire what's
the flaming thing here oh they're all holding microphones I got it I can say I
can relax but you can't relax because I this would be the most embarrassing thing
in the world if I did not do this in 15 minutes I would seriously have to I would
have to go to the doctor if I couldn't do this in 15 minutes you know I'm
saying it would be like what's the problem are you all right
tell me your symptoms I couldn't do a children's puzzle in 15 minutes oh oh
okay let's figure that out I guess we're done with this one 13 minutes and 7
seconds it still took 13 minutes that's fine I can videotape it let's see what
happens nice nice all right they have fun animations no I don't want to do I
want to do like okay here's the deal if I can't do a 16 piece puzzle in less
than three minutes no and if I can't do this in 60 seconds I'm gonna go to the
doctor tomorrow okay hold on I need I wanted a picture though new picture 16
well okay what what is actually completely viable for me to do in 60
seconds 16 pieces like be realistic 20 pieces 16 it's gonna take a minute to
click and drag that many times 16 pieces 60 seconds which one we gonna do
you do dance studio no hold on I want to do with the wisdom I'm on the phone all
right I'm gonna do I'm gonna do I'm on the phone 16 pieces I have one minute
where's the shoe no it's not fair it's not fair it's not fair hold on I can't
do this in 60 seconds I can't even put this piece down I'm losing time because
I can't put it down stop stop stop stop stop do it again fuck Mickey's what
happened I'm gonna try it again okay in the amount of time it takes to click and
drag items and not be able to put them down and that was like 40 seconds that I
lost for no reason I'm doing it again okay I'll pick a different one different
because that oh no you okay we'll do the dance studio we'll do they are the
gymnastics okay ready go yeah I don't have to go to the doctor I don't have
to go to the doctor 59 seconds aim assist I'll fucking get out of here it
was using aim assist somebody wrote this is fucking lame laughing my ass off no
stop all right I'm done with this one thanks a lot Vicky I feel like this has
been some really good ones on this list we're to know there's only a couple that
I think people even wanted to see it kind of knew it was gonna happen one of
these two code name Iceman or super carts oh it's screwed up it's screwed up
hold on try it again there was infinite clicks were on didn't make it count go
ahead god 50-50 I'm just gonna do them both okay let's just do them both let's
do super carts and then code name Iceman and then we'll scroll down that's too
close super carts you demand a recount well you're gonna you get to see it you
get to just get two presidents at the same time this thing just asked me if I
had a VR headset what does that mean loading super carts by manic media
productions we fixed this mmm that should be better better configure
keys redefine keys accelerate break left right reverse I'm assuming it they're
accelerate will be w break will be s left right reverse will be our select
will be e activate will be enter right it makes sense confirm I don't care
about two-player mode new game go carding arcade mode level let's do it
let's go carding Kevin Charlie Klaus Aki Ivan this is guy with a cigarette
cigar in his mouth Klaus get in the shadows of the Hollywood Hills the LA
one circuit is one of the high heart widest easiest most laid-back track of
the series so lay back that it's act truly on the beach
place of my in how are you all down here hey I use that eat eat eat
turbo hey why did you come out of nowhere that pattern keeps my head there
again I'll do a better this time was it that loud how loud was that let me see
was it I was it actually that loud there again I'll do a better this time oh
Jesus this is horrible it was like it the whole time shit I'm sorry all right
codename Iceman okay this is an old Sierra game so that means I'll probably
give up at about ten minutes because it's gonna have me combine like three
items and I'm not gonna know what to do with the shoehorn the bubblegum and the
empty bottle I will not know what to do with them
Mike is muted Mike is not muted I'm very clearly not muted I'm turning it down
there we go codename Iceman by Sierra open beautiful island of Tahiti where
warm self-sacrifices caress the emerald clear waters of a sun-filled paradise
place of fun and relaxation place where love and romance can be found a wonderland
where anyone can get lost in its magic we find our man lieutenant commander John
B. Westland of the United States Navy enjoying a well-deserved lead from his
recent story opens with commander Westland on the beach soaking up the
sun that's me I get up I stand up oh god stand go flex you've left me
responseless okay can I go in the house okay I can enter this clubhouse what does
it say open door you can't go in the lobby without your shirt oh I have to
go get this shirt Jeremy this is a porn game no it's not this is not a porn game
it's not what are those shoes what's on the table on the table you see news
magazine grab the news magazine why do you power and the United States and
Russia find themselves in a tug-of-war as they negotiate for the oil here there
after reading the article you begin to think hmm what a dangerous explosive
situation this could be now stand up put your shirt back on put on shirt nice go
in clubhouse I have score one out of 300 equip shirt that's good okay talk
talk hello the clerk chirps can I help you food hi hello no the clerk is still
talking I'm trying to talk to this person examine search search plant
we're here or over here either one where you going made it into the bar her face
lightly flushed the young blonde lady says hi big fella sit and join me I'm
drinking my ties sit damn good posture Wow drink order drink how about another
one how about another one really I'm happy I just ordered this as I'm gone am
I pretending to drink this glasses empty I'll take another one now are we ready
let's have a Mai Tai together order a Mai Tai now hi let's have a Mai Tai
together I just or it's in your hand I just brought it to us no I ordered a
her a Mai Tai I want one too no he's filling up her glass I want the Mai Tai
no order myself a Mai Tai okay I'm never gonna okay I could go for a Mai Tai
right now how many of these do you want I have to type flirt no this is like a
game about the Cold War oh what happened what happened what happened
help help what help lady help the lady what what did you do I ain't drunk I'm
just drinking uh do I finally get to fucking drink one what about some talk
who's it wills is over here hey what cap you like beef or what huh I order food
close enough I like beef sure I don't understand like call bartender stand
talk looking straight ahead he says how you doing Mac I don't think I can do
anything else in here he doesn't say any order food you know close enough all
right well I'm just getting out sit by this way what about this can I sit here
sorry I'm all over don't sit there no I'm out I might be drunk too I just walk
this down the door is it leave exit how do I get the fuck out of here leave bar
I'm not over to the confused okay I made it can I go anywhere else no the play
can't examine the plan doesn't do anything dry shit pants something tells
me that's not gonna work oh people okay look you have to try what about in here
doors locked I'm not gonna kick the door down holy shit you guys think you guys
are fucking sadistic what should I do oh the doors look kick the door down burn
the house burn the house down smash glass I don't doesn't understand smash
okay this person just kind of in the way can I just like move them to follow
them persons open door is this open maybe this one is oh my god why would
you go all the way over to this door I wanted you to do this one fine kick door
you can't do that after all punch door talk to the door the door doesn't seem
to hear you knock there's no answer slap self I'll try this one can I like
wake like wake up awaken awaken wake up no answer it was locked can't go into
these houses swim around that person what I have to go put my shirt on the
beach chair it's just a window tell me all these things I shouldn't be doing I
don't know what thing I should do is why is everybody like ignoring me can I go
the other way what the hell am I supposed to do all right put shirt down
take off shirt get in there volleyball play volleyball well jump in here glad
you joined in two against one is making me tired how do I win how do you not
understand laugh I'm getting a really look at my score I've gotten more
points playing volleyball than I have done anything else is this what you do
oh shit somebody did fuck it up there goes the ball wait you're going too deep
don't you know don't go past your armpits that's my mother I told you
don't ever go past your armpits that's an actual rule follow that what get in
there did I do it do I have to type you will find the correct rescue procedure
listed in the game documentation you'll find the correct rescue procedure listed
in the game documentation click the top of the screen or press escape to use the
menus all right no you oh shit okay hold on speed sound
damn it hold on shake and shout call for help establish airway look and listen
and feel give two good breath look listen feel check pulse what the fuck
are you talking about shake and shout after gently shaking the victim you try
getting response by saying are you okay call for help turning to the others you
shout please someone go for emergency medical aid in excitedly the man says
I'll take care of that and he stomped all he just stepped on her like three
times then establish airway quickly you tilt her head back and open her mouth
sweeping the open mouth with your finger you make sure nothing is blocking her
airway okay then what happens after this now you look shake and shout look
listen look and listen look listen and feel look listen and feel you place your
ear close to the victim's mouth and you try to listen and hear feel for a breath
at the same time you look to see if the chest is moving okay emote only mode oh
shit I don't know what to do I don't know what the next part is behave
yourselves behave yourselves so I can know what to do next behave or I'll turn
I'll turn chat off forever what do I do next breathe check pulse it's been a long
time you will find the correct answer oh shit look and listen give two good
breath give two good breath you pinch the nostrils closed open your mouth wide
and take a deep breath you make a tight seal over the victim's mouth and breathe
into her mouth you take another deep breath and breathe into her mouth again
watching her chest rise look at this look at this face just like that work I
don't know look listen and feel after giving the victim two ventilations you
look listen and feel again however you still can't get a response
compressed chest check pulse you check the cardioid artery for five to ten
seconds trying to find a pulse unfortunately you don't compress chest
is there anything else I can do begin compression but isn't she dead quickly
you locate the bottom of the sternum using your index and middle fingers you
measure up the chest finding the proper point to start the compressions using
the heel of your hands keeping your fingers from touching the chest you
start chest compressions at a ratio of 15 compressions to two breaths you act
fast compressing the chest one and a half two inches at a rate of a hundred
a hundred eighty two hundred and the excitement you think to yourself I must
check her pulse in one minute she's already dead okay she's alive again back
to life this is actually just a CPR tutorial it's getting stronger oh it
took you long enough you watch as the doctor examines the girl where have you
been the doctor turns to you and says well sir thanks to you this young lady
is going to be just fine she starts moaning and mumbling and
attempting to get up she insists on standing so you help her up I don't know
they should be standing they were dead for about five minutes the young lady
you just rescued thanks you for saving her life it was fortunate for me that
you were here and that you're a strong swimmer okay welcome back to to life 18
points I thought this wasn't this cold like code name Iron Man or something how
does this work is I thought this is like a cold war game ice man right now what
do I do there's the same two huts that's odd what the hell just happened you
don't have the key to open the door there's no response go get your shirt
and then walk to the top to reach the hotel I'm gonna probably put the speed
up on this faster faster faster there we go let's think about talking but they
I'll just say ignore you I kind of the ball I get shirt go all the way to the
top put on shirt all right now go up what's happening can you see like
through here because this bar the bar is here can I check in you talk hello the
clerk how can I help you get key yes sir here you are oh nice all right okay I
got key that's all the music you get no more than that it was this one or the
other one I missed a phone number just tell it to me all right use key you
can't do that what open the door there we go this is my room bed out here stop
getting stuck is there anything else out here why do I have a reverse skylight
that's a that's to watch the fish to see that's just a hole in the ground you
left me sleep although it's a relaxing thought you really don't have the time
for slumber okay so what the hell am I supposed to do in here look at plant
look a couch sit on couch of course you're gonna go all the way to the
across why would you sit you've already sitting you can't do that here and now
I can't use a phone in my own hotel room wait is it am I just sitting in blood is
that blood all over this no stand up what does this do for me like check
drawer check draw bed table open drawer open the drawer all right what do we got
there's nothing in there you pick up the loose change in the drawer the drawer is
empty well I just picked something up what I'd pick up ID card your Navy ID
card and change 50 cents all right so close it up what the hell do I do with
my ID card now jump on bed it's not gonna work just go right throw ID in
into ocean what's that take clothes take suit it's too much too hot here look in
the closet you see the unopened left side of your closet so open it open left
side you just said side how do you not understand it you just said it left
closet hello everybody there hello that was weird I think that was a surfer
problem I don't think that was a cox problem yeah I think that was like an
ingest server problem yeah no I thought my internet looks like pretty clean I
think meet my connection to twitch's server got screwed up why do I sound 20
years older it aged me look in shirt pocket okay you've left me respond
there's nothing there there's a time skip we're gonna right side of the
closet but I just did look at right side of closet all right all right I'm gonna
check pockets there's nothing there all right I think I think it's time to close
the book on this one check the pocket hold on check shirt check the shirt open
door check pockets yeah why is this I don't know why this game is called ice
man I have no idea okay check suit pocket suit pocket look pocket there's a
little black book in the pocket take it out take black book okay Jesus all right
we got two phone numbers here we have GG baloney and general Braxton okay with
my phone do I have a cell phone use phone okay what's the number shit hang
up hang up the phone I have a diary let's do let's call that's called GG
baloney one two oh two five okay five five five eight oh eight three five five
five five eight oh was it eight three there's no answer did I do it right one
two seven two nine two seven two nine why is nobody answering the phone I have
to use dashes oh my god they still didn't answer the phone it doesn't matter one
two oh two five five five eight oh eight three what was the other one to
something to nine two seven two nine Brackton Brack's is not at home did I
get the other one wrong eight what was the other one eight eight something eight
oh eight three really racking up a hotel bill here can you call it the police
there's no answer the police didn't answer they were busy I would check to
see if this phone is real check the back is the cable plugged in and is it fed
into the wall eight oh eight nine what do you mean eight oh eight nine that's
not it that's not a phone number eight oh eight nine huh that's a three that's
not nine all right I'm out of here I'm done with this game no don't open the
closet leave we both can't fit down this at the same time I don't know how it's
possible for two humans to do this door stuck all right let's just let me get to
25 points and then I will delete this game so where should I go in the bar oh
I don't need to click open door it's just doing it all right order no how's
everybody doing anything new here what's happening I'm not supposed to be here
walk to right door walk to girl I thought do it again say it again her
husband still hasn't showed up aren't you at least going to buy me a drink
first walk to right door walk to girl at bottom right hand corner look girl talk
girl buy girl drink walk to right door walk to girl at bottom right hand corner
look girl talk girl buy drink okay is that it cool all right cool good talk
girl hello buy a drink no I'm not gonna buy the drink from the girl buy drink I
have to be sitting to buy a drink since when buy a drink and then bring the
drink over here no don't I took a sip out of it give drink you can't do that
oh it's the husband buy girl drink buy girl drink you're not close enough look
no I was just over here and I did buy drink here and it said I'm not close
enough you're not close enough buy girl drink I buy girl drink no buy girl drink
okay I am legitimately standing on the chair that she's sitting I wouldn't mind
sharing a bottle of champagne with you hey bartender you're gonna have a bottle
of champagne and two glasses oh thank you would you pour me a glass okay cool
um thank you see you later okay bye just a little bold don't you think she says
and we haven't even what are you talking about oh dance you want dance
these people are on drugs these people are on drugs what was in that champagne it
definitely wasn't alcohol that little shake a little wiggle is the best how
do I don't have any points that's not any points for this speed the game up
that's as fast as it goes I'm doing the Pee Wee Herman right now that was legit
the tequila that was Pee Wee Herman there he's flossing so what am I
supposed to do stop is that it talk girl sit talk girl just hello sit talk girl
what's going on would you like to come back to my place oh god how do I say yes
how do I say yes do I just say yes yes oh I might it's just a porn thing I think
I did it I made it to the end I made it to the game that person's been lying
down there that person's not I don't think it was alive I'm not seeing any
like diaphragm movement that person's just lying there dead kiss kiss okay
after a tender embrace she murmurs would you like to come in for a while how do I
cut all audio and video come over and have a seat does this actually happen
no no no no it doesn't no sit are we watching TV that is on the wall here you
know John this vacation has been beautiful for me except for one thing I
lost an earring today that is very important to me I've searched
everywhere and for the life of me I can't find it I know it was on when I
left the room but I didn't notice it missing until just before walking into
the hotel lobby I know I'd be the happiest woman alive if I could find it
can you go find it for me I'll find it anything else we've talked enough for
the evening don't you think yeah okay go smooch go for a kiss one
goodbye what was that explosion what I'd like to talk about kids like whoa no no
no no no nope nope nope nope nope I can't even do this this is fucking too
much it's got 25 oh let me show that I'm like naked I think I am naked am I
naked under here if I stand up but we're gonna get like it's like a two
pixel dick I have to be okay I don't know it might happen we're gonna get a
pixel dick I think hold on no okay everything's fine after anything stand
up pick up note open door walk around the beach just outside when you walk
past the earring it'll sparkle get earring look at earring I love what
people are giving me like the absolute like this is how this is just every
spoiler stand up pick up note you can't do that pick look note you see a note
grab note you pick up the note okay what's the note say read note you read
a note apparently written by Stacy dear John thanks for making my vacation so
wonderful you were sleeping so peacefully I just couldn't bring myself
to wake you I have urgent business to tend to and I must leave I wish you the
best and hope we meet again soon by the way thanks for the two hundred
dollars that was in your wallet sucker get robbed okay so what was the next
part I need I need the the walkthrough copypasta again okay walk around the
beach just outside when you walk past walk around the beach just outside when
you walk past the earring and the sparkle get the earring look at earring
open earring okay earring just outside looking for the earring when you walk
past the earring it'll sparkle there it is pick up you pick up the object and
sure enough it's an earring open earring after carefully removing the top you
discover that the earring is hollow so what's in it the earring look inside
earring inside the earring is a tiny roll of microfilm oh mercy mercy you think
to yourself that beautiful woman is an undercover agent so that's way worse
than what I said but for whom you wonder is an afterthought uh-huh do you wonder
anything else no brain fart there you remove the microfilm now I have to
watch the microfilm right now call the general swallow the microfilm this too
many copypastas gonna walk left till you get the two huts I already have the I
already got the card I got the change walk left you find two let's walk to the
top to the next scene you find number six there open door open closet if it
didn't I already that walk to the top the left to reach the next scene why
don't you just open the guide yourself so you can read it is this person
following me this person is following me they're like right up me they okay hold
on somebody just has the game facts right here I'm just opening up the game
fact I'm just gonna read it myself I don't I don't give a shit about this
show me the car back show me the game back okay go to hotel at entrance look
stand deposit change to buy the Times magazine all right going in so I don't
need to do this go back to the hotel at the entrance look stand deposit change
to buy the Times magazine look stand through the plastic window you see the
latest edition of the Tahitian Times okay deposit change you deposit 50 cents
or remove a copy of the paper reading the front page you learn that the Cold
War between the USSR and the United States is beginning to heat up the
Russian-supported radical terrorist group has taken the United States
ambassador to the Middle East is hostage you further learn that the terrorist
group is demanding ten million dollars ransom in order to purchase arms the
demand is not met within 30 days the ambassador will be shot and his body
dumped in the okay in front of the embassy in response to the Soviet
naval buildup in the Mediterranean the United States has ordered its seventh
fleet into the area president has bowed that if the ambassador is not released on
harm within a reasonable amount of time the United States will not hesitate to
take an aggressive military stance against the cowardly perpetrators after
reading the paper and discarding it you think to yourself this is really
something after just a short time on the military leave the whole world goes to
pot okay go in the hotel I don't understand open oh my god okay the clerk
says to you oh mr. Westland I have an urgent message for you it's from a
general Braxton she informs you informs me what oh talk what can I do for you
what oh I have an urgent message for you she informs you in go on with the
informing please read message yep get message you take the message from the
clerk read message message reads call immediately you couldn't have just left
the message with the clerk to tell me to call why do I have to read that this
isn't your hut well which one is mine where's mine isn't mine this isn't my
hut alright is the identical other two huts that are over here call the general
what's the general's number it's five five five two seven two nine two seven
two nine general after a few rings someone on the other end answers the
voice bellows general Braxton here what can I do for you what's with the did I
just prank call the general am I am I calling my high school crush to ask the
dance or do I did I call the general which one is general Braxton what can I
do for you oh my god you identify yourself to the general and tell him
that you received his message after the mutual hellos and how have you how have
you been greetings the general says where on earth have you been Johnny we've
got an explosive situation on our hands and even playing around on that island
due to the sensitive nature of what we are dealing with I can't give any details
over the phone I need you here in Washington as soon as possible report
to the maximum security briefing room after acknowledging your orders to
Washington you say goodbye and hang up the phone click then apparently I have
to call somebody else how would I know who this person was I have to call a
dinghy phone number dial the number talk use phone dial the no sins key dinghy
phone number where did we get that I don't remember that oh this was I think
it's a sign hold on yeah it is a sign somewhere so I just have it somebody has
it all right what is it just put it in you know what I'm saying was it 202-555
was was right somebody had it I just saw it no that's not it I don't know what
the fucking number you just told me last I have to go look at it it's a sign
it's gonna be over here somewhere it's in the hotel one two oh two eight six
seven five three oh nah yeah I know that song I know that song you can't go look
at sign open door you tried you did it was it was a solid attempt okay read
sign there's a sign on the wall but you can't read it from here so get closer
no oh call JG Wentworth I can't leave 877-NOW leave the bar you did it last
time thank you I have to do like opera singers for that those commercials if
you have an annuity and you need cash no like a subway or something there we go
six nine six nine of course it's like pretend low how does that service even
work so if you have if you get paid an annuity or something right you can say
hey JG Wentworth take all that money you get the annuity right but then they
give you like a percentage of what it would be upfront so let's say it was
over the course of a 10-year period you're gonna get $100,000 you would call
JG Wentworth and they'd give you like like sixty eight thousand or sixty
eight hundred six whatever it is sixty eight thousand immediately right or is
it way worse than that so it's oh it's ten thousand dollars a year for ten
years but I want sixty five thousand dollars right now that's where those
services make money hence the 877 cash now you need cash now right I mean
there's no answer wasn't that the number six nine six nine I don't need the like
area code oh no stinky dingy transport no sinky dingy transport can I help you
are these 50 cents that's all I have yes I need a boat please give me a boat
can I help you advise the person of your location and that you need
transportation to the airport you told to meet the dinghy in front of the hotel
entrance click okay thank you why am I taking a dinghy why not I'm you hold on
so I'm on an island across the world that I'm gonna take this dinghy to
Washington I'll be there in six months maybe not I'll be there in like five
years it's gonna take a long time this is just a ploy to get rid of me yes okay
commander Westland we want you to go to West ford what's what's this guy's name
Westman commander Westman it's a very important mission you must take the
Washington they're just trying to get rid of me next stop Tahiti Airport
commander what's his name Westman Weston Westman Westland no no no my character's
name Wentworth oh I'm just here you land at Dulles Airport no time for back
tracking what are you talking about what's this character's name don't get
it watch out the door opens automatically are you command Westland
that's it right it was right yes show ID the exams are closely thanks you as he
returns it and says please have a seat
here we are the Pentagon quite the parking lot for the Pentagon the the
Pentagon has less spaces than a strip mall and aren't they supposed to be
like 5,000 people working in here that's quite the ride share it's a 7-eleven
has more parking spaces than the Pentagon apparently your ID please thank
you very much commander you've been expected please pass through which one
you hear the whine of the elevator as it approaches sir I must see proper
identification before you pass thank you very much commander you may pass
through I just didn't have that commander commander how are you sorry
about that what hold on I can't go back up no what do you mean you only allow
access to elevators for your briefing did by like I'm a four-year-old that
blocked me out of the game have a nice day sir
it's amazing this is one cowardly act of kidnapping two powers it's very urgent
that you get here commander Westland please ride an elevator up and then an
elevator down and then fucking leave my stomach is gonna fucking explode alright
I think that's where I end this one I mean how do we go further from this I'm
not sure you can get any better than the elevator briefing now what talk I'm here
to pick up commander Westland he says are you commander Westland show ID okay
yes may see your orders please oh just rip it now just hulk out and run my ass
off if I can go back on the plane and go back up the elevator restore is this
gonna work yeah it's there is no restore point it's over supposed to say I did
not okay yeah maybe I was supposed to save the game but did you honestly think
I was gonna be in this one for more than an hour I don't think so that was great I'm gonna
go take one more break I'll be right back we'll do a few more I will see you in a minute okay
this next one we're gonna do this will probably be either will this one will be the last one one
more or two more and it's gonna be I just saw it and I just had to click it this is a Mavis
beacon teaches typing I need to improve okay today's lesson ASDF keys welcome to Mavis beacon
teaches typing meet Mavis here's a quick tour of Mavis beacon teaches typing press a key to begin
press escape to stop the tour when Mavis prepares a new lesson she explains its goals and format
here you may take the suggestion or do something else among your many options are the arcade race
free typing practice keys and fingers proficient keys display and progress graphing you can even
build your own lesson using Mavis's suggestion as a start okay let's go to the classroom you
and Mavis will walk on specific work on specific problems this is where your lessons appear if
this is where your lessons appear if this were a real lesson you type what you see here okay all
right all right you got it workshop as well you practice what you've learned let's go there now
here's the workshop meters and gauges will measure and hone your skills text from fascinating
sources like on the left the meter show accuracy speed and lesson completion on the right are the
clock and the metronome we learned best when learning is fun here in the arcade you're pitted
against a merciless opponent this is gonna be a lot of fun over 20 graphs show you how you're
doing you may choose you may use this information if you choose to create your own lesson there's a
lot more but it's fun all right let's go start the lessons what's your first name what's your
last name whatever I don't care please rate your typing skill what's a keyboard okay but
need some work expert seeking perfection I'm okay I'm not a beginner but I need some work your age
here's how I prepared your personal data is it my personal data term Albertson your age
ranges 14 to adult your skill level is intermediate your typing speed your goal is 35 words per minute
time limit for a session is unlimited today's date is what is it what what is that what how is my
typing I want to change nothing a hundred what's average what's the average like 45 48 something
like I know it's a bit least like 40 or 50 right if he's really good 40 I'm gonna do 50 50 words
per minute okay looks good looks good to me don't look up there that's a secret one okay problem
diagnosis for intermediate typists intermediate type is review your current skills welcome for
the next few lessons we'll do some general exercises to get a feel for your typing later
we'll tailor lessons especially for you let's begin with some warm-ups covering all the keys
watch this cursor and as always type the character right above it good luck and have fun all right so
the next key you type will start the lesson once started you may use the escape key to end the
lesson early 60 okay there we go what's why is it what's going on jaw dry in a farm bulky
zebras fine find they can folks weary men with quavery juvenile zest for excitement what I don't
know what these are what's the seashell that okay it's at how do I do this one it's killing my words
for a minute how do I do which one is this one what's the up one it's not even all my keyboard
there it is what did interest in parking by the quay george quickly began to be vexed by the
power of blizzards squawking gorillas could hex the brave it's not like the band but brazen this is
just nonsense I would be better if it was a real fucking paragraph Ben works at squeezing 20 very
juicy plums with flexed arms like that's nobody this is not real stuff done since you're an
immediate typist we assume you know the locations of all the keys without looking and how to type
them if you don't either change your personal file or try out the keys it and fingers feature
I have to drop down to I am a four to eight year old the metronome has been set to five
words per minute faster than you typed previously see if you can keep pace we won't score your
accuracy this lesson so go for all the speed you can I'm ready okay your typing is faster
than the metronome can go wait here is where you'll work on specific problems while you're
typing as fast as the metronome can go if you type two characters per beat you'll stay in time
the next key you type will start the lesson so have to be c-a-n-j-e-r-r-y-s-e-q-e-q-p-p-p
okay can jerry's equipment files can jerry's equipment file saws axe hoe knives can jerry's
equipment file saws the weight lifter whipping will you pack my jugs of liquid veneer in 45 000
boxes could the visor jinx what ben works at squeezing 20 no no it's not bare hands it's
flexed paris two bound in four lots uh of lazy knowing oxen came by quietly evading the jam
put your five big axes and three pieces of quartz the brawny jaguar held fast till
the 10 quaking victims ah 49 words per minute i'm pretty good adjusted words per minute that's fine
let's put your skills to a fun test in a moment you'll be behind the wheel of your typing racer
i'm looking down on my keyboard yes i have to i've been i can't i have to look i have to look
because i know where the keys are but i don't here's the thing i know where every key is
in fact just to make sure i could prove this to people but how does no i'm i was going to
draw a keyboard without looking but how but i can't prove that i listen i know where every key is
on the keyboard but my problem is not in knowing where the keys are my problem is hand placement
and when i move my finger let's say for instance like f g t r that little spot there like asdf
put do it do this with me at the same time pinky on a ring finger on s middle d index f
and then jkl semi right your thumbs are open sit there with me so you have jkl semi asdf
i know that r is right here above f i know it is but i can't i'll miss because i can't see it
i can't see the physical button and it's hard for me i can't do it i miss i know that the letters
are there but the my placement of my fingers and moving my hands across the keyboard my i can't do
i'm fucking dumb okay just try it it's not gonna work anthony smith corona may equal his world
record speed of 32 words per minute can you leave him in the dust begin typing to start your
engine all right i'm gonna try it jkl semi brazen gazelles
i can't see i need to know what they are because i can't i need to get it into memory so i can
write it i'll catch up to him slow down he's doing just as bad as i am neck and neck
i have to look up and down up and down up and down to see that the next
word i'm dumping the water out of the boat as it's sinking what
ah
oh my god it's the eyes up eyes down eyes up eyes down eyes up eyes down to see the word that was
coming in right after it oh i don't think i can do that again oh what skill type is never
look at the keys as they type let's see how accurate you can be on these hurdle words without
the key tops showing what do you mean key tops you must type each key correctly before moving
ahead the next key you type will start the lesson i have to can my face i don't need clothes on
oh fuck hold on let me just put like a t-shirt on do i have a shirt on in here i'll just put
like a blanket around me okay that should be good i'm just gonna stuff it in here and then all right
that should be all right let's see right that's okay right let me just let me check it first
that's not good enough i gotta hold on okay that's better better okay shit you're in a snuggie
hold on hold on i can't snuggie okay i'm just gonna look straight ahead you're ready
asdfjklsemi okay okay i got that i got that pretty good accumulate oh shit my my robe is
falling i okay i looked for a second one second i did this sucks holy shit look at the neck do i
have that much skin i do not have that much skin what you gotta be fucking kidding me the word of
rubber mask of my own face i don't want to do this anymore do i have to do the whole alphabet okay
almost done i can't do it i actually can't do this i can't do this you look like a ventriloquist
dummy why don't i just go get a goddamn shirt on that's better these words are hard this is
like the brain hurt words okay that was fun get this off of me cameras off right yeah get this
fucking thing off me uh i don't want to do this anymore my head hurts i'm gonna try to do this as
fast as possible i don't care if i make errors did i mess up too many times he was not used to
the heaviness of the earth's atmosphere yeah i would how the fuck do some of you guys do this
shit how do you do 100 words a minute i don't even know how that's possible that's so so fast
speed hold on a minute speed by key i hit n r y and h the fastest that's kind of interesting
all right so yeah n r y h i d are the ones i hit the fastest all right uh words minute by session
no accuracy by key i can always get the z i the s j and t are my problem zones all of them
are apparently number of keys i don't think even did any of those errors by hand my left hand
if only i didn't have this left hand that actually kind of makes sense though
errors by row interesting recovery rate after errors t r e a okay that's funny
uh backspace errors n has the most interesting that's pretty funny surprisingly good software
i mean this i think don't they still make this i so doesn't doesn't mavis
are they still just they still have it right all right let me uh let's do one more
holy fuck i thought the camera was still on underneath that window then i didn't turn it
but it did so thank god otherwise that would have been really embarrassing
uh we can't we gotta end on burger blaster you already showed yourself shirtless none
enough but that i'm not that's not that wasn't a full body shirtless this is close up chest
and i've got some i gotta do i've got some work that i need to do here we're gonna end on burger
uh scenario whatever it's called i think we played this one before but it's a different version
is this the same game fire what is this game holy shit this is awesome wrong piece all right
i need the bottom button right bottom button there it is missed the catch how did i miss the catch
okay and we need a patty that's not i didn't get it no i got it oh come on now i know what's
wrong the speed is up as much as it can possibly go i was wondering what the hell was going on
yeah i'm looking at chat i don't like why can i not stop this all right grab the burger pretty
good shot this is now in slow mo i think this is on normal all right maybe it's normal now
now it's normal now maybe now i think it's normal now i need the top one no i didn't want to shoot
damn it top one where are the top buns this is just a worse version of the donald duck suitcase
there we go there's the super mario world mushroom top platform you know that's my favorite
piece of art from super mario world there's a mario uh no it's mario one sorry i'm not trying
to shoot it's actually original mario uh all right i'm not ending on this one that one was not very
good all right streamer's choice i already got one ready for you oh boy oh fuck i'm gonna be
here for a while yep i'll be here for a little while damn it do i have to really play this i knew
i wanted to play it all right i'm gonna give myself a time limit here uh we're gonna play
press your luck with the game with the whammies are we are we not try it again we are not going
to play unfortunately unfortunately we're not it will not load that's uh unfortunate okay
streamer's choice sucked yeah unfortunately will this one work to go out on will junior pac-man
work what's the difference between junior pac-man and regular pac-man 16 i got them all well i know
it's way too high this shit is on hyper speed i'm trying to make it slower getting a lot of points
fuck all right i i maybe it's not i'm trying to make it slower but it won't do it it's going too
fast it's going too far i have to be level one even if it's on times three speed i didn't even
do anything i didn't press any buttons you would have heard it you would have heard that
i did not press anything just go go go go go i can do it this is fucked up sometimes the presses
don't work all right it's just fucked up this is really messed up i can feel it hanging oh
who's that character why is there an apple pac-man this game is playing the brown note
oh almost got me not quite
ah my hand come on i can get past this i have two more lives i'm done after this
give me the drum why is it my hand hurt so much i don't understand my hand is killing me my right
hand my pinky my ring finger are killing me i don't know what it is what's happening to me
i'm gonna start taking like glucosamine god damn it ow that shit doesn't work does it not
use a controller no that was just a little fun thing to do at the end
yeah i saved you all right that's gonna be it right at the six hour mark those were quite a few
uh games by the way i can still hear it though so i have to turn this off get out of my head what
the fuck okay i don't know if it's just me is it just me because when i took out my headphone
it was like is that happening anybody else take your headphones out right now it was like
um i my voice right now is dude that was fucking wild shattered eardrum no it wasn't but it was
on very low it's just that sound just permeated my brain maybe you should go to the doctor tomorrow
yeah maybe no anyways that's gonna be it so i not 100 positive about this there is probably
gonna be a stream tomorrow depending on if um i can get this all set up i don't know how long
that will be or maybe i won't i don't know it depends on how this whole thing gets set up
i'm not sure i was invited to play uh terraria with mr star so i don't know if he's streaming it or
if i'm gonna turn on a stream we might just play i don't really know what's gonna happen
so i really don't know because i usually do three days on and then a few days off i do usually two
three days on and then two or three days off so tomorrow is very tentative to i really have no
idea if there is a stream tomorrow it'll be kind of random there's no time tomorrow if it's like oh
hey it's set up and the server works and everything works fine and it's like six o'clock or something
pacific then i'll just turn it on or something so i don't really have a time frame for tomorrow
i have no idea just whenever it happens if it happens there you go there is uh still the
possibility that because the last thing that star said was we need to get like some mod thing
and that was it i don't know if maybe there'll be server issues i don't know it might happen
should be interesting regardless but uh i will see you probably tomorrow take care everybody
good to see you we are going to go back to uh six hours ago uh should be pretty quick tonight
for the bits thank you joining me on some of the sometimes these ms dos games are just so all over
the place i love doing this sometimes you can get a little fucked up and you have to you know change
and shit but it's such a wild list and a wild amount of different things to see so i love doing
it but let's go back uh to earlier this evening well has name thanks to the 15
dollars and 10 cents has name just admit it you're a closet weeb i told you i i watch one anime
a year last year was one punch man this year um i don't know but thank you for the 15 dollars
not jojo i don't think it's gonna be jojo full metal alchemist i already saw that one
watch jojo so the green screens can make sense maybe but thank you for the 15 dollars half
noon it's time for slime thanks for the three dollars glad you're finally coming back to dos
guess it's time to make germa dos 2 video well the first one was unbelievable it was really funny
so if there's enough over the next few weeks of content to do it then hell yeah
first one was awesome bake me home thanks for the 250 germa pretend like the next sentence in this
message doesn't exist because there's oh okay uh there's nothing there there's nothing there
though so how would i pretend if it's if there is nothing there uh thank you cult of personality
for the 250 germa just press the turbo button on your dos computer should have thought about that
you're right i should have thought about that damn hey gnarly thanks for the 250
so when is the next league of legends stream i love watching your pro gameplay and hearing
your strategies for the game um you just snapped a memory into my brain i made a grandpa video
where i walked into towers in league of legends it's the only time i think i've ever opened the
client of that game does that still exist did i upload that on my channel or was that on an
old machinima channel years ago because i know i the whole grandpa call of duty stuff all were
i think they were all did were deleted yeah they were all completely wiped out
watch it on stream now i'm not gonna watch that video on stream i'm not watching that on stream
it's not gonna happen maybe okay put it in the queue put it in the queue for the video community
i would do with them watch it on stream you'll see it eventually but thank you
i think i was playing as a little with a little mummy a little mummy character
what's his name amumu amumu yeah how do i remember this somehow but thank you to uh swiggity swanky
for the five bucks i'm not sure if you still follow tf2 anymore but there's been this bug
in older crates where players are unlocking rare unusuals as common as dirt items and the hat
economy is crashing and we uh we talked about it in the very beginning of the stream right when it
turned on actually if you were not here i kind of gave my thoughts on it they'll patch it they'll
probably rewind everything and it'll be like as if it never happened and if that doesn't happen
then who has any idea what's going to happen after that
it's being called the crate depression oh god of course it is but it's an interesting scenario
i wonder how it'll play out in the long run i'm sure it'll be already fixed and patched by
probably the this time tomorrow but thank you the five dollars interesting stuff thank you nile
orion for the three dollars i didn't expect to end up laughing till i cry at a fucking game of
scrabble take my bits and shut up that was all over the place it was all over the place but it
was great fun as it always is all these games have their own little weird charms to them
but thank you for the three bucks glad you had a good time the great lord walden thanks for the
five dollars they say life is pain pain pain life is pain pe life is pain thank you for that
let's get the credits rolling here they come thank you for all the subs all the resubs all
the community subs everybody there were a couple of uh random gifted subs tonight much love to you
i may or may not see you tomorrow if it doesn't happen tomorrow then i'm sure we'll probably
rain check it if there's an issue maybe i'll see you tomorrow but we're gonna finish up the bits
we have four dollars and 44 cents from fraudian weapon thank you fraudian no message just four
four four three dollars from gts 223 they said do a sexy pose joke talking about the previous game
ice man and then finally ape apples apioles thanks for the five dollars and they say thanks
for laughs germa oh so i found this on my way through dc found this on my way through dc
for some reason i can't load this image i don't know a germa town germa town
oh well it's germa german town do they have fiber maybe i'll move but that's very interesting
um with a jer too but thank you so much eight and then finally here at the very end we have uncle joe
for 250 thanks for the 250 oh yeah yeah sorry sorry sorry this is uh this is german town german
town road somewhere that's my name but uh uncle joe says i shittily remixed your beatboxing well
more like just adding 808 what is 808 let's find out 808 808 i did all this with my mouth
why do you have that in here
all right i'll see you guys tomorrow take care of yourselves see you soon
much love to you good night take care