Hey, what is going on everybody Jerma here with a sorcery exclamation mark gameplay commentary and before don't this is a text-based adventure type game
Don't nobody freak out. I just want to let you know beforehand
This is not like a hack and slash a party up and like throw fireballs at people that you kind of do
But it's very slow. It's very deliberate. It's a game to lie down and relax and play in bed
It's got like hundreds of thousands of words. So if you don't like reading
Wait a second. It's a fantasy world. It's like a choose-your-own-adventure book
Just calm down for a second just chill out. Okay. No, it's a fun game. Trust me. You just have to sit
Okay, so sorcery is
Like I said previously a text-based adventure game where your choices and your paps can lead to different conclusions
And it's based on a series of game books by Steve Jackson
Which is why it's called Steve Jackson sorcery and it's a whole lot of fun for the longest time
I've been saying to myself man
I wish they would bring back the choose-your-own-adventure books or the game books from back in like the 80s in the early 90s
Who remembers the old goosebump books? Remember those old like goose by?
There was one it was like a carnival and there were multiple ways you could die
Multiple ways you could escape and it was a ton of fun when I was a teenager sitting down lying in my bed
Flipping through these books. It was exciting because you never knew if the decision you were gonna make was gonna be the right one
Or will it be the wrong one? And is this way you die?
That feeling made me want to read
It made me want to pick up another one of these books and fine and try my luck at how far I can get in this
Susparner
That was cool back in the day and now it seems like this company Inkle who is the the group responsible for
Porting Steve Jackson series over to iOS and Android
They're doing a great job and it's fun to see them actually do this and then try to revitalize this old platform
That has sort of fallen off the beaten path in the last 15 20 years or so
But the way the game actually plays is sort of a good condensed version of the old books
There is an entire spell casting system with dozens of spells in this game that you can cast in a million different
Situations and see how they all turn out and there's a combat system as well
There is an actual sword play system over the course of your travels
You're going to encounter people like this guy that are pretty strong. You'll also encounter pretty weak enemies as well
They're not all as difficult and powerful as this guy, but it's a tug-of-war system, right?
So if I swing my sword harder than he does
I'm going to do the damage to him and vice versa. We have stamina meters
So you don't want to drain all your stamina in one swing which will then force you to defend and when you defend you are
Guaranteed to take one point of damage if the other enemy decides to swing at you
so you really want to play the cat-and-mouse game you want to play the tug-of-war game and
Try to keep your stamina above zero because when it hits zero you die
But regardless of any of this it spices up
What could just be a typical text adventure and Inkle has done an amazing job at making this not just feel like I'm reading a book and
Choosing little choices and reading the outcomes. I actually feel like I'm part of this little game world
It's like a board game the way you move your character around the map
It's a huge detailed world that you actually get to move around and then read about where you just went
And this is book two of the sorcery series. There is four books. There is four books
that's full, but there are four books in this series and
Episode three or part three should be coming out within the next I don't know
I know this just recently came out last year
So I don't want to like throw the developers under the bus and be like yeah sorcery three will come out in March of
2015 no, I don't know all I know is that they're working on it
They just released a new game not that long ago
So they're probably in between projects, but I would say pick up both of them if you like this kind of thing
It's gonna cost you
$3 for sorcery one the first part of the adventure and
five bucks for sorcery two
Eight bucks for the whole thing the whole experience so far
Depending on how many times you play through it and try to get all the different items and all the different weapons and all the
Scenarios to play out. It's probably gonna take you quite some time
I don't really want to put a hour number on it because you I don't want to put that in your head
I don't want to say oh the game will take you three and a half hours because you then you you're thinking about that
You're not engrossed in the story
It's gonna vary for every single person how long it takes them to play through their first time
Because some people will do some stuff very quickly other people will be going
Sort of around in a circle and trying to find a way it's it's a lot
It's different for everybody and it's enjoyable. Nonetheless, however, you play through it eight bucks again. It's on Android
It's on the app store links will be in the description if you want to check it out check it out
That's gonna wrap up the video guys. Thank you so much for watching really do appreciate it. I'll take y'all every day. That's a fair
Everybody take care