Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma and MLC Stealth here. Go ahead and say hello.
With a Team Force 2 game-ly commentary.
That's not what this is. This is Modern Warfare 5th Week.
Oh, where is this guy?
Much better game.
How did I know? What just happened?
Oh, this is a live commentary, by the way. If you couldn't already tell, playing with
MLC Stealth, he is like the Call of Duty guru. So I'm trying to...
This is on the PC where I don't know how to aim or shoot.
You're ten times better than I am. So I'm just going to follow you. Or am I?
Have fun getting free deaths.
Because I'm going to lead you off a cliff.
Oh, this guy's screwed.
Oh, P90X, get jacked. What?
Wait, why am I running Specialist right now? I mean, not Specialist.
So you can get the easy MOAB.
No, but I'm Support right now. I don't want to be Support.
Oh, well. I wanted to have Predator drones drop on people's skulls. Oh, there you are.
Predator drones.
For those of you that care, I'm using this as the P90 with...
I believe it has range and suppressing on it. Suppressor.
Where did you go?
I took towards the enemies to kill them all.
Watch out for that bogey up in that tower.
Tango 6.
I made that up.
Negative zero snipe me.
Oh, God. Oh, come on.
What? I got like a double kill with a javelin.
What just even happened? How did I not kill him?
He didn't even hit me. He like went through me like a damn ghost.
So where are you? Oh, God.
Everyone just saw how terrible I am.
What do you think of Patrick Swayze?
I can't believe I didn't kill this guy. I got to see this again.
I like unloaded on this guy and he just owned me.
So wait, what do I think of who? Patrick Swayze?
And Demi Moore. Do you think she was good in Ghost?
I don't know. I don't even see that movie.
Did you see that movie? Oh, God.
This is not turning out well for Jerem.
Oh, that guy just got like a triple kill with his akimbo FMGs.
He must be really good. That's not going to happen again.
He's really good.
That's not going to happen again.
Tango on the roof.
Come on, man. Hit more. How many times do I have to hit somebody before I kill them?
Oh, I am using FMG. Never mind.
Oh, it's double team. Up top. Up top.
Negative zero down. Flashbang now.
Oh, my God. That took so long to kill that guy.
There's bogeys above us in the roof.
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God. I'm scared.
No. No.
Ah. Do I?
How did that guy kill you?
I don't know. Be careful.
So for those of you wondering if you don't know who Stealth is,
Stealth, go ahead and give a little brief synopsis of who you are.
Oh, I don't know.
I play Call of Duty.
Oh, I'm just some guy.
I'm five foot ten. My favorite color is a combination of blue and red.
Some call that purple.
What?
I really like Hot Pockets. I think that's a pretty tasty treat.
And I sometimes upload Call of Duty because I like this game.
AKA, you got like a feast at this game and you get like Moabs every 15 seconds.
I don't know.
Oh, nice. Switch right there.
Yeah, you switched and let him shoot me instead of you.
I'm up top. I don't know what you're talking about.
Oh, my God. How many times do you have to...
Thank you for saving my life right there.
You owe me so many things now.
I got an advanced UAV. You want it?
Should I do it right now?
Oh, like now. Do it. Also Stealth Bomber.
Get inside the building. Get inside the building.
Wait, wait, wait. What? I can't get in.
Did you just lie to me? Did that not just even happen?
It absolutely just happened.
I had some like Chips Ahoy cookies still in my mouth.
So, Jerma, who are you? Tell like my people who you are.
I'm a crazy dude that tries to shoot people from a thousand miles away with an SMG and doesn't get any luck.
No, I'm a... I don't know. I do Team Fortress 2 and all kinds of weird dumb stuff.
Pretty much that's who I am.
So what do you think about Scientology?
I think it's a religion that was created.
And that's pretty much all I really know about it.
I know Tom Cruise is one.
I don't know if that's like... Oh God.
He was pretty good on that recent movie.
Come on.
Oh, don't worry. I'm only 9 and 11.
That's a weird combo.
Yeah, that's better than like 1 and 11 on the other team.
If my math's right, that's slightly better.
You know what's tricky though?
I have the game volume turned almost all the way down for recording purposes.
So I'm just like, dare who? Who's that right in front of me?
So that is why you did not hear the demon stealth bomber coming to kill us all.
I can't see anything.
What just even happened to me?
I'm lost and forgotten.
You're lost in translation?
But yeah, if you're watching this on my channel, his link will be in the description.
If you're watching this on my channel, there's going to be a link in my 10 videos ago and you're going to have to search for it.
I will not make his link easy to find.
Yeah, make sure it's incredibly difficult.
Wait, wait, wait. Come back here.
You. Turn around.
I was just killed by this guy in this room. Get him.
Because I can't. I'm too stupid.
Oh, behind you. Behind us too.
No, I got him. Don't worry.
This game scares the absolute crap out of me.
It really does. Like this.
Did we win?
Yeah, absolutely.
Well, there we go.
Zero quit out.
Hey, I went 12 and 12. Oh my God.
Campers win again.
That's what Phoenix said.
Dude, look at that jumping shot to end it. That was pretty awesome.