Oh, hello again, everybody. Let me just make sure the audio is working. Is it? It is. Would you look at that? It's beautiful.
Hey! Welcome to VR Day 2. We did VR Day 1 yesterday, and we're gonna keep going.
I've got some special treats for you. I'm gonna play Superhot VR first, and then after that, I got all the Beat Saber mods.
Sorry, this thing's like weighing my head down. I like this.
I got the Beat Saber mods, Superhot VR, and then pertaining to time, we're gonna see if I go back to budget cuts or not, and how I feel.
How do you feel? How are you doing today?
Superhot VR sounds crazy. It looks crazy, so I'm really looking forward to it.
Oh, my legs soar. My whole body is sore. I did like a five straight hour Zumba workout yesterday.
I haven't moved around that much in probably like five months. But let me tweet this out. I'll be here in two seconds.
Hey, we can get started. Okay, it's taking like 15 seconds. This tweet is still apparently sending the tweet.
I don't know how. It's like, oh, we're still sending .2k of data. What the hell are you talking about?
Is it there? Can you guys see my tweet? Oh, fuck, I just bumped it. I'm sorry. No, you can't.
Okay, well, let me try that again. That's odd.
All right, I'll be right back again. I literally cannot send a tweet. It will not let me do it.
Does Twitter have like, does it have server problems or something? What is this bullshit? Did I get banned?
Why would I get banned from Twitter? I write like, stream starting now.
Hey guys, sorry for the internet problem. Streams will happen tomorrow.
What do you guys think about Starbucks lids? Why would I get banned?
All right, well, fuck it. No tweet, apparently, because like Twitter sucks.
Banned for spam? I make a tweet like once every three days. Are you kidding me?
How many people do you guys follow that put a goddamn tweet up every 30 minutes?
But anyways, let's see how I look today. I came ready today. That's right.
Active wear. I got active gear on. This is like a breathable shirt.
What's with my autofocus? What is this piece of shit camera doing?
Oh, that's right. Every time my computer turns back on, all the autofocus settings are on default.
But we've been made a goddamn computer. Like, seriously.
It's better? All right, we're good.
All right, so we're going to play Superhot VR right now.
And by right now, I mean like right, like right now.
Let me just get in. I'm going to take one more sip of wine.
I also untangled the cord here. And boy, was that a pain in the ass.
Get this off. Okay, I got to like sign an agreement with Twitch.
Twitch with, what is that doing?
All right, I'm going in. See you guys soon.
Yeah, because you know, I'm not going to be able to see anybody.
I'm not going to be able to, I can't see what you guys are writing, you know?
That's like the worst part about it.
Let me just get my tools here.
The worst part about this is just not being able to, oh, what's that?
There you are. I fucking got at work in two.
All right, how do I say yes?
Okay, how do I play the game? Superhot.
Update. Why is it in a different language?
Your game. Yeah, I'm in it, right?
Yeah, I'm playing it, right?
Whoa! Ooh, that's painful.
That's so, that's so loud. Hold on.
No, it's not. It's face loud, you know what I mean?
It's really face loud. Just give me one second.
I'm just going to put on my fucking headphones.
All right, what do they want me to do?
Okay, going back in.
I got to stand like in the right, I got to make sure I'm in the right spot.
Wait, what was my latte?
What? I can't even drink out of this.
Fucking computers, but if it's not a computer, it's a material object.
This is all ice.
It's really heavy.
Like, there's a shitload of liquid in here.
Like, why can't I drink out of this?
Oh, that was a good latte.
All right, sounds good to me.
I just put a little too much ice in it because, you know,
you got to cool a latte down somehow.
You can't just not.
All right, what's the woman to do with the latte?
Thank God it shows your hands.
What are you guys saying about me?
Oh my God, you got to read.
It's hard for me to read.
It's a little, it's, well, all right, there we go.
I'm ready.
Grab gun.
I did it!
Time moves when you move.
Oh, yeah, I forgot about that.
I completely forgot about this.
This game was, like, wild.
Super hot.
Did I even kill that guy?
Time moves when you move, right?
So, shouldn't this be moving?
Yes, that's right.
Yes, I'm your surgeon.
Just give me one moment here.
I've got to make one incision.
I'm 85.
I've been doing this for a long time.
Don't worry.
What do I do?
Why am I so small?
Shouldn't I be taller than this?
The lighthouses are not correct.
I should not be...
Can I not reach him?
Oh, okay.
Oh.
Last round.
Whose last round?
My last round?
What are they getting away from?
Right in the fucking head.
What are you guys saying?
Ooh, super hot.
Ooh, I missed.
You missed it.
Fuck him.
You know what I'm doing.
Super hot.
That's so cool.
What an interesting...
Now, thank you to VR Josh, by the way,
for telling me how to do that.
It was kind of hard.
With a big white background,
it's hard to see everything, but...
Turnable, look out.
There's someone else in the room.
He's going to shoot me, right?
Oh, that's so weird.
He's going to shoot me right in the head.
Imagine you had this.
He's going to shoot me right in the...
Can I grab the gun?
I missed.
Super hot.
This is...
Hey, how's the audio?
Is the audio good?
What do you guys think?
Yeah?
It's good?
Looks good?
Oh.
Thank you.
You can throw...
This is going to be so fun.
I can't wait to throw
glasses at somebody.
Straps.
It's easy to forget
because you get so immersed.
These are my hands.
It's easy to get immersed.
Okay.
We good?
We're good.
All right, let's go.
Hard catch.
How do I...
I should have probably
paid attention to how to throw it.
How do I let it go?
What?
There it is.
Okay.
All right.
Come on down here.
Oh.
Oh, shoot.
There it is.
Super hot.
That's so cool.
Yeah, I can go
a little fucking laughing at it.
Give it a try.
Give...
What am I getting?
Don't think so.
Whoa, another gun.
There's another gun there.
Oops.
No, I made it.
Damn it.
Oh, raise your hand.
Like this?
Is he going to pop it?
Oh, raise your hand.
Like this?
Is he going to punch?
I'm going to try.
What?
What did I do wrong?
What did I do?
Raise your hands.
Did I get hit?
Like, am I supposed
to just block a punch here?
Like, block.
Nobody behind me, right?
I think I got hit.
Yeah, I must have gotten hit
by somebody over here.
All right.
Light is canceled.
Whoa.
Oh, my face.
Why did I have to do that all the time?
Why did I have to do that
all over again?
Damn it.
Oh, this is so fun.
All right, I got it.
How close am I to the fucking wall?
Oh, fuck.
Get him.
Oh, give me the gun.
Oh, fucking crazy.
This is insane.
Concrete security.
Got the gun in the back.
Calculator.
Where's the gun?
Time to pay.
The guy is going to act quick
and grab the gun first.
Where, why are you?
Super.
Halt.
They come from all angles
and you turn around.
Oh, this is unbelievable.
Are you ready to play?
I think I am.
I hope I am.
Show your dedication.
This is sick.
It is.
It really is.
Show your dedication.
Aim for the head.
Okay?
Oh, I get it.
Oh, God.
I got like the floating tank.
Oh, I got like fingers.
What do you think about that?
No, there we go.
I can see you guys much better.
Oh.
There we go.
Beat.
Super hot disc beat.
What's in these games and discs?
I thought they were just bugs in my room.
Disc beat.
Where am I in my room?
Please put on your headset.
Oh, fuck.
It's on.
Oh, you mean like this thing.
Can I bring it down?
It's on.
How do I get it on?
I didn't.
What do we got?
How to the helicopter?
No.
All right.
Closing down.
Okay, I got two machine guns.
Let's get the dominations here.
Guy with the big gun.
Right.
Two left.
Got both guns.
We're going to go bang, bang, bang, bang.
Here we go.
Oh, fuck.
Bang, bang, bang.
Here we go.
That didn't really work.
That's it, right?
Keep going.
Why?
No.
Oh.
All right.
He was right.
Damn, that was fucking nasty.
Nasty.
Give me this thing under here.
Oh, you're not going to rob this bank.
Emergency exit.
Just making sure no one was behind me.
Here we go.
I've got a place to hide.
Distract them.
Oh, fuck.
I've got a place to hide.
Hi.
Distract them.
Here we go.
We're going to get...
They all have guns.
Get the fuck out of here.
This is fucking so fun.
Seriously.
Welcome back.
This is...
Oh, god.
I'm like a child.
Right here.
Bingo.
Right in the head.
Just in case.
No, I'm not going to get him with that one.
Let's get him with this one.
I dodged.
All right.
We'll get him with this one, motherfucker.
Right in the knee.
Oh, fuck.
I'm going to get him with this one, motherfucker.
Right in the knee.
Oops.
It's all right.
We don't even need it.
Oh, my god.
He was right behind me.
Got that one.
Yay!
Okay, I've got playing Nerf fun time in the living room, mom.
My older brother's way better than me at Nerf.
What?
What happened?
Right in the knee.
Oh, it worked.
Good.
All right.
What happened here?
Oh, yes.
I got it.
Holy shit.
Okay, hold on.
I've got to punch this guy.
The guy with the gun somewhere.
Right in the gut.
Watch that bullet.
I can see it.
Oh, come on.
Come on, man.
I don't even know where I am.
I need to fucking figure out where I am.
How did I fucking miss you all?
Who's left?
Where?
Got it.
Yes.
Same deal.
Bingo.
In his head.
I'm ready.
Okay, here we go.
Right there.
No.
Pick it up.
God damn it.
Who's going to throw?
I got a bullet over here.
I'm dead.
Oh my god.
My goodness.
This is his fucking insanity.
Oh, he hit me right in the stomach.
Oh.
Oh, my god.
This is insane.
Insanity.
I didn't hit him in the stomach.
Fuck.
Are you kidding me?
You can block bullets with your gun.
Oh.
Come on.
Get him.
Oh, this one's fucking hard.
I'm losing it.
Alright.
Slow! Slow!
Oh, God!
Oh, look at him shaking!
That was fucking intense. That was great.
Bye-bye!
What comes up...
Oh, I didn't get them!
Man, I'm gonna use nothing.
You guys are working on your chest a little more.
That's what I'm talking about! It's fragile!
Make them pay.
Who shot the gun?
I heard a gunshot. I don't know where it came from.
Oh, my God.
Let loose!
I assume let loose means this.
Let loose! There it is.
Wait for it.
Do I have a gun?
I don't have a weapon.
I don't have a gun.
Chad, I don't have a gun.
What? Oh.
That was supposed to happen, okay?
Anything else change in the environment?
Alright, hold on. Where am I? I gotta be careful.
I gotta take a step over here.
Get it in there.
Do I have to put the helmet back on, too?
If I can fucking reach it, right?
This is gonna be fuel for so many fires
made out of gasoline on this channel.
I swear to God.
Come on.
I tried to block with my hands!
Get away from me, please.
Oh, whoa.
Oh.
Up top.
That's both, right?
Fuck.
Right in the head.
Right in the leg.
Yes.
Get out of my fucking life.
Oops, that only has two shots.
Okay, get ready.
Whew.
Special delivery.
Gun.
Axe.
That's so bad.
You know what? Come on over here.
Let's do this all day.
He's going for the balls.
He's gonna shoot me right in the nuts.
Oh.
Holy shit in my face.
I'm trying to catch a knife.
Beautiful. Let's go.
Give me that fucking thing.
I ain't even messing around anymore.
Let's go.
Here we go.
Bring it on. Let's go.
Fast.
To the wall.
Guys, am I gonna back into the wall?
I can't look at the thing.
Fucker.
Whoa, when you shoot.
Oh, I had it.
Fuck, when you shoot the gun right.
God damn it.
Oh, where am I?
Where is this?
I don't know where this is.
I'm running into something.
All right, I'm gonna do it.
Old-fashioned way.
Come on.
Where am I?
I didn't hit him.
I don't know how that happened, but it did.
Damn it.
What?
Oh, come on.
What, did it hit the wall?
God damn it.
I'm losing my...
I missed.
All right, slow down.
Slow down.
Okay.
Here we go.
I gotta grab the gun and then block the bullets, I think.
There's nothing else here.
Okay.
I just gotta dodge.
Why did he walk that way?
Okay.
Shh.
Oh no.
What is this?
What am I hitting?
Oh God!
It's just...
Super.
Halt.
That was fucking wild.
I think I bumped into the lighthouse again.
It's so much worse when you're in your face in real life.
Bam.
Just one.
There's a guy walking around here.
I don't see anybody else.
Oh, there he is.
Last words.
I don't see anything around me.
How am I gonna get out of this?
Oh, I did it.
Surprise, mother hacker.
Oh, over and out.
Couple people up top.
Let's go with the easy stuff first.
Bingo.
Head shot.
And then let's get one more head shot.
That's a good measure of this guy right here.
Why don't we make it a quadruple head shot.
I think that's what we're going for here.
Super.
Halt.
Almost at him.
Super.
Halt.
Triple head shot.
Alright.
Calling his shots.
That would have been great.
Okay.
What?
Dodge this.
I dodged it.
I did what you asked.
I think I'm getting close to the camera.
Is somebody behind me?
Alright.
Yep.
Take a peek.
You're in the way.
Here.
What?
Oh, I got him.
Okay.
Wrong door.
Oh.
Is somebody else gonna open the door?
Oops.
Come to me.
What are these days?
I'll get this right.
Get out of the way.
Butter hands.
Yep.
Crash the party.
What exploded in his head?
Did I shoot a bullet over there?
And hit him in the face?
I have no idea what's happening.
Show your commitment.
Look down.
Oh boy, this is actually pretty...
If you got a fear of heights, this is not a game that you'd want to be doing right now.
You gotta hand it over to a friend who goes...
I felt myself falling.
I can feel it.
Ugh.
Any more discs?
Don't do it.
Can I unmute now?
What do you mean, unmute?
What are you talking about?
No.
Bodies are disposable.
Mind is software.
So, when I first heard this game, when they announced it, when they came out with it,
I thought this was just a VR mode for the original game.
I did not know that it was a completely made-from-the-ground-up VR experience.
And it's fantastic so far.
Don't worry, I got it.
Okay, so we got...
I can charge up my fists by holding.
So I have to grip.
I have to hold the grips down, too.
I have, like, laser hands.
Try again.
Can I only do that once?
I think I can only do that one time.
I should have done it on this guy.
It's all good.
Again.
Now, my, like, little kid powers aren't working.
My, like, imaginary powers.
Uh, kid, I don't think it's gonna work.
Come on, why is it not doing anything?
Am I missing something here?
Help me out here, what's going on?
Triggers and grips, yeah.
Triggers.
Grips.
Have to get closer?
Triggers.
Grips.
I'm not sure I can get much closer than this.
I'm, like, out of the play zone right now.
Uh, maybe something screwed up?
Yeah, I'll help you here.
What?
Did I, like, chop?
What the fuck is going on right now?
Do I have to get shot in the hands?
You have to dab to activate.
Well, let's try again.
Mind blown.
Try again.
You can only do it once.
Okay, again.
Throw the gun forward and catch it.
Catch the bullets.
I can't, like, throw them.
I mean, it looks like I can do it, but I can't.
Is it getting baited?
Do I just have to...
I think I just have to dodge.
Because it...
I can't go, like, closer, I guess.
Like, I'll walk into the computer.
Okay.
Throw the gun forward.
Well, let's...
Did I actually get hit by that?
Why would I have known to throw the gun forward?
Come here, give me the gun.
Shoot it.
Go on, shoot me.
Shoot me.
Try it.
I mean, who...
Uh, this is the first time we've had an experience like this.
Did I miss?
God damn it, I fucking missed.
Wait.
Again?
What does it say?
What was the countdown for?
Shoot, hit me!
I'm right here, right in the face!
Alright, I get it.
Groundhog Day.
I don't even care anymore about dying.
I'm not even gonna shoot you.
I'm gonna take the gun and punch you in the face.
Yes, I am.
Oh, watch out for the fucking wall.
See, this is why I think hard to do this shit.
I need it in the other hand.
I can't aim with my fucking left hand.
That other one.
Shoulder.
Alright, good.
That's right, throw this gun like down the street!
Again?
You're almost ready.
Super.
Hot.
Oh.
Ooh, a nice hat.
Oh, no, it's a dog bowl.
Come on, let's go.
Give me the...
The hammer.
I wish I could keep the hammer.
Shoot them.
I don't think so.
Alright, fine.
Thought he was gonna move to his left.
Walk into it.
Ah, you didn't walk into it.
I'm trying to space invaders you motherfucker.
Let's go.
Holy fuck.
Now I got him.
I didn't think that would have been cool.
Fuck.
Give it to me.
Come on.
Okay, now where was I?
Where did I go?
Down there?
Shit!
Jesus Christ, did they go over the shotgun other one?
I turned skinny and didn't get hit by that.
I went so skinny, you have no idea how skinny I just got.
What about to go somewhere else?
Like that way?
Down in there?
I don't know where it's gonna put me.
It is in there.
Okay.
I don't even need to do that.
Come on, you stopped at the fucking exact moment.
Give me that.
Where am I?
Hello?
Alright, now I'm going up there.
Right?
We'll try two of them and see if I can get it.
Eh, not quite.
Jesus Christ, that was fucking fast.
Fucking fast.
That's not a gun.
Ah!
Damn it.
A stupid fucking wall.
It's like you have to move around so much.
I have like the minimum of what you're allowed to have to play VR at a room scale.
Locked in a goddamn box.
It's my own damn fault.
I wanted to be able to walk around in a circle.
I don't have like a fucking 1300 square foot living room.
I'm like trapped in a fucking ice cube tray.
Alright, I'm fucking, I gotta slow down.
I'm getting angry.
That didn't hit him?
Come on.
I didn't throw it.
Ah!
What?
How the fuck did I not hit him?
I don't even have the balls in this thing, but let's fucking play with it.
It's gone.
Okay, back where I was.
Let me get like situated so I can walk into a fucking wall.
Got it.
Butt.
Um.
Okay.
That way, I think.
Right?
Doesn't matter.
It was that way.
That's a good wall.
Fuck, that's gonna hit me in the head.
Hit him!
I got him right in the fucking face.
Super.
Whew!
Wee!
Sure, I'll take him.
Oh man, that's coming for me.
Oh, that's wild.
What the fuck was that?
Okay.
One more guy.
Good?
Good.
Give me that gun.
Come to me.
Come to me, gun.
Come on.
Ugh.
I'm gonna fall over.
Super.
Hot.
You what?
Super.
Hot.
This is so fucking fun.
Ugh.
It is a workout though, I'll tell you.
In my little fucking ice cube box.
Hot.
I don't know where the wall is.
That's the fake wall.
Oh, we've got one guy here.
Right in his face.
Ike.
Okay, hold on.
Where?
I gotta be careful.
There's like swinging shit.
The walls are so wide I can't even see where the borders are.
For instance, what the hell happened here?
Where did I just go?
Got him.
Fuck.
I'm gonna fucking swing so hard down and it's gonna be bad.
I'm so self-conscious about it.
That was a double knife throw.
I liked it.
Okay.
Escape.
Oh.
What am I escaping to?
I don't understand.
Where am I going?
That's it.
Oh.
Got the knife.
And that's it, I think.
Super.
Oh, shit.
Shot the bullet out of the ear.
Prove your worth.
Breach the pyramid.
Obey.
This is one of those scenarios where I shouldn't have obeyed.
Did I do the wrong thing?
I don't know.
I may have.
Yeah, I'll get it.
This is the broken disk.
Alright, we got a shoe.
No, we don't.
We don't have a shoe.
Dance, dance, dance.
Oh.
Foo.
This is gonna be hard to do.
Has he shot yet?
Fuck.
I can't even get over there.
I'm just rolling around on the ground.
He's going for the ground shot.
What have I left in my legs?
Ah!
You fucking demon.
Get over here!
I just got shot right in the head immediately.
Oh, my mouth!
He shoots.
Dodge this way.
Punch him in the face.
Okay, he blocks like three shots for me.
I'm gonna stand in the corner over here.
I'm gonna hit something.
Let's move this way.
Okay, just gotta get it.
Ah!
Jesus Christ!
Ha ha ha ha!
Dodge this.
I dodged it.
I cue balled that guy.
No, no, no.
Don't use this yet.
Oh, yeah!
Kill it.
Scout scatter gun.
It really is.
You're right.
It kind of is the scout scatter gun, isn't it?
Alright, we got double knives.
Let's go for it.
Hello.
Um.
Easy.
I fucked it up.
Ah!
Right in the face!
Alright, we getting away?
What if I do like the beam thing?
They gave me weapons everywhere.
Intercept.
I think I was supposed to do that.
One guy right there.
One guy over there.
Damn it.
Oh, I'm in fucking trouble, gad.
Oi!
Ai, ai, ai, ai, ai.
He's gonna be right behind me, isn't he?
Interfere.
Shit in my fucking face, dude.
No, no, no!
Super hot.
Intensity levels, I guess.
An 8 or a 9.
Meat cleaver time.
Where am I?
Okay, I think I'm in the right spot.
Gonna go across.
So down like this.
Down like that.
Grab the other one.
Grab his head.
Oh, there's a guy right there.
You know how cool that would've been?
I'm gonna fucking do that to me this time.
Bingo!
Oi!
Got cocky.
I got too cocky on that one.
I'm cocky.
It's alright.
Oh, what?
He's showing on the way over here.
Fuck you.
He's raining bullets.
One shot.
Get it.
Yes.
Alright, this one's done.
Holy fuck.
Alright.
Where am I at?
Get situated here.
Get the fuck outta here.
Survive.
No, I just have to put it down.
Wait, ai, ai, ai.
I need a gun.
None of those hit.
That's gonna get him right in the fucking face.
Drum roll.
Ah.
Super hot.
Wait.
Super.
Hot.
Super hot.
Super.
Tilt the camera so I can see you while you...
I can't...
Tilt the camera.
Hot.
Super hot.
I can't do that.
Like, in the middle of a game?
You can see me down here.
Ok.
Story the pyramid.
You will be rewarded.
I'll give it a try.
Let's go.
Okay, what the fuck is going on? I don't like it with his looks.
Oh, it goes into my brain.
Alright, are we almost done I think?
Right in the hand.
That one stings.
I can't shoot with my fucking left hand.
Savaged it.
Oh fuck, I didn't see the guys over there. God damn it.
Going too fast. Come on, speed it up.
Oh!
Oh, the rush.
Going through my body. Fucking Jesus.
Just left one more, right?
Last Bastion.
I blew it. I blew it. I think I may have blew it. I blew it.
Nobody comes up behind you in this fucking game, right?
I thought it was blocking me.
Alright, honest to God, what the fuck is this bullshit?
Final order. Destroy the pyramid.
You are now free. What's wrong with you?
I don't get it. What do you mean?
It was perfect timing when that car drove by. You sounded really like a car.
Go out this way. You know what to do.
What do you mean I know what to do?
Destroy the computer. You're right.
Destroy VR. This is the thing about how VR is going to start to become too much like reality.
And people are going to get sucked in.
Super. Halt. Super. Halt. Super. Halt.
I think that's it. Or maybe not.
One of us. Mind is software.
Too cool to look. What is wrong with you?
It's high noon. Nice combo.
Oh, you are now free.
Prison Hunter. New experience. Savage.
Faster.
Don't die. What is this?
Oh, new discs.
What is this one?
This is don't die. There's a couple of them.
What is this? Is this just the game?
Oh, okay. I can pick.
Outer Heaven. Restaurant. Airplane. Pyramid. Yeah, you can just pick.
That's cool. How do I exit? Probably like this, right?
Yeah. Don't die. Headshot only. Hardcore. Speedrun. Real time.
Oh, yeah. Yikes.
What is don't die?
And then there's endless.
Give it a try.
Don't die.
So is this one of the levels? I don't get it.
Are we just going to go through the whole thing?
Super. Halt. Super. Halt.
Alright, I didn't die.
Halt.
Where's my money?
Break in.
Well, it was fun.
What about this?
I want to see how crazy this is.
Alright, this is real time.
There's no slowdown. It's just in real time.
I wonder how bad I'm going to be.
Let's just go to like...
Red.
Real time. I don't get it.
I don't understand. What's going on?
Oh, it's just time. It's just a speedrun.
Okay.
Knocked it up already.
Super. Halt.
32?
32 seconds.
I'm going to clean that up a little bit.
Alright, let me get out of here.
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on.
Don't die. Headshot only. Hardcore. Speedrun.
Speedrun.
Game time.
Speedrun. Real time.
Okay.
Okay, I get it.
This is really, really cool.
But I'm going to get some water.
Because I've been in here for like, how long? An hour or two?
How long have I been in here for?
Five minutes.
Alright, let me get some water.
Uh-oh. Pulling hair.
Actually pulling hair out of my head.
Uh-oh. This is bad.
Oh, god damn it.
I just heard a snap.
You know, I was thinking about writing a novel.
Called The Bus Station.
Alright, give me a second.
Starbucks barista hair right now.
What would you like?
Was it a venti? Yeah, okay. I'll be right back with that.
Ugh.
Why are you so sweaty?
Well, you know, it's like, tough.
If you're like, a person making your food look like this, don't order there.
I would fucking leave.
I'd be like, you know what? I'll go to Dunkin' Donuts.
Hour and a half? Wow, I didn't think it was...
I thought it was shorter than that.
That was a blast.
I will be right back.
I'm going to get myself something to drink.
That was so sad.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
So, uh, let's go
into Beat Saber.
Because I have
uh, I've installed
the mod, so let's hope it works.
And go get random songs.
Change it to Beat Saber.
So I should, there should be an option
in Beat Saber now.
Just get this back
to where it needs to be.
Let's get out of Super Hot.
And load up Beat Saber.
Okay, Beat Saber coming up.
Make sure I get you guys a good view.
I went outside looking in the mirror.
I'm like, red.
I'm as red as the shirt I'm wearing.
Full room VR.
My god, it's a workout. It's great though.
Alright, so
let's get back in.
Get you guys back in the right spot.
Let me just, cause once it's on
you can't really take it off.
Alright, now I should be able to go like this.
Hey, look at that.
Hi guys.
Okay, so I was in there
I was in this game for about 30 or 40 minutes yesterday.
There was like
8 dubstep songs.
So we're gonna try to find something new.
Uh, you guys maybe can help me out here
with how to do all this.
Uh, isn't
No, this is wrong.
This is the right hand, right?
Well, alright. I'm just gonna have to go like this
from time to time.
You guys are on another hand now.
Do the whole Shrek movie.
What do you mean, do the whole
Shrek movie?
Can you do that?
I can't do that.
Do the fucking whole Shrek movie?
You guys are gonna get me in
trouble. At least do Dancing Queen.
Yeah, you know what, you're right.
Okay, so, uh, mods.
More songs.
Take on me.
Oh, come on!
Yes, let's do it!
Wait, it doesn't have, it's only expert?
No, only expert.
I can't do this on hard?
Oh!
Who doesn't seem to go
on the shadow ways anyway?
Who does?
I can't do that while I do this!
I can't do this! I can't do that!
Expert plus only?
God damn it, I just wanna play it!
I don't wanna do expert plus?
Go back. Okay, let's beat it
from Michael Jackson. This is a classic.
Hopefully I don't get the
Twitch channel deleted. By the way,
uh, say goodbye
to the VOD. VOD ain't gonna
exist. Hope you will, hope you
enjoy this livestream,
cause that's what you're gonna get.
Alright, let's go. I'm gonna, I'm gonna
get into this and fucking get it. Perfect.
Alright, come on.
Uh, user has been banned for 72 hours.
Reason being,
DMCA claims
that Michael Jackson was staked.
Wow!
To jump over it?
Michael Jackson!
I can't stop hearing beat it now.
Beat. Beat for beat it.
This is
ridiculous. Alright, you know
this is just a way cooler guitar
hero. This is just a better
guitar hero. It just kinda is.
Alright, let's go back to
uh, let's go songs. More songs.
Let's get an interesting one. Wait, what?
Okay. Living on
a prayer.
Is every song on here?
I mean, that's a pretty good one.
Uh.
You know
I have to do this, right?
Okay. If I get
past the first
10 seconds,
then I win, okay?
10 seconds and I win.
I just gotta get past the first part.
Do it again. Fast the first part. That's it.
Only the first part.
I did it!
I'm done. I did it. I got it.
I did it. Okay.
Is this sort by? Sort by plays.
Attack on Titan?
What is this?
What is Attack on Titan?
Super Warrior Brothers theme? Let's go.
I'm gonna get Attack on Titan.
Uh.
I don't give a shit about anything else. Nothing else matters.
I don't care about fucking anything else.
Let's go. Best song ever made.
This is the best song that I've ever
heard in my whole life.
That was the other color. Yeah!
To the corridor.
Here it comes. Break it down.
Yeah! This is the
worst song I've ever heard in my
entire life. How do I
click that guy? Get rid of
him forever.
Right? Does this have a...
Look at me!
Random pattern.
Alright. What else did I get? Mario,
September. Did I get something else?
Oh.
Block that.
Okay. Alright. More songs.
He's a pirate.
You're welcome by
Moana.
The Skyrim theme.
Hey. I'm here. I'm here. I'm here.
The Imperial
March.
Star Wars. This is
easy. How about
Meme Mega Mashup? No.
I refuse.
I'm picking the worst fucking things.
Wait. Was that?
Alright. Let's do these.
What's going on?
Ding ding.
How long is this
song? Can it be over yet, please?
I don't want
people to come to the channel randomly and not know who I am.
I think this is cool. It is fucking
cool. Oh my god.
Give me a break. I want to be out of here.
Okay. Who cares?
Let's try this with an expert.
When I wake up
I don't want to be
I'm gonna be the
person next to you
And I'm gonna
Well, I know I'm gonna be
the man who gets stuck next to you
And if I ever
Yeah, I know I'm gonna be
I'm gonna be the man
Slippering to you
But I will get miles
And I will do
One thousand miles
Then I'll follow that
It's like walking. You're walking.
This game sucks.
No. I'm just kidding. It's great.
How about that?
I
I can't. It hurts my head.
Gerudo Valley
Evangelion
How many zones are on here?
Toxicity is on here.
Do dare. The Force.
That's a remix. Me channel theme.
Okay. The Pokemon
theme. No, no, no, no, no.
We're going too far here.
I can do the whole thing. They go like
Hey, hey.
Oh, I can't wait
till they do their fucking reunion tour.
I'm gonna be in the front row.
They're coming to Vegas real soon.
Sing along. I want to see it.
Be your fool
In this game for you
So I'm leaving
you behind
Hey!
I'm here. Beat.
Is this a remix?
Is it gonna be a remix?
This is hard. It's probably gonna be like
Oh yeah.
How would you
It's not a remix?
The song is perfect
as it is. I thought it was gonna
do like a huge drop. Alright.
This is coming up.
This one's coming up.
This is a lot of bombs.
Hey!
Dude!
Play Germacrap.
This is like, it's just
the whole thing, right?
Oh god.
Well, I'm in the game. I might as well
just do it, right? How long is it?
This is not easy!
Okay.
Okay. Germacrap.
I can't
I can't feel it.
I actually have to crouch.
I missed!
This is how we do it.
I've only done Minecraft like
three times in my life!
I'm so stupid!
See? This is why
I'm in it, you guys. You see?
Why would I think it would?
And I just jumped off of it.
Okay. Remember this.
Where are we? 20 East? I have no idea.
Fuck!
We gotta get trees.
First thing you gotta get. I'm getting
stamina! I'm losing stamina.
Hopefully you guys are
playing video games.
Nobody got it. Who cares?
If somebody got like a drink!
It's not easy!
Oh my fucking god!
I can do it on no fail mode?
No, I don't even want to do that.
It's like 19 minutes long.
This is gonna be fucking hard too. God damn it.
I'm scared. This is an expert.
Not mislabeled as easy.
Not going too bad.
Let's see! That's a good song.
Search.
Do the rat song. Do the rat song.
Play your dang what?
Rats rats rats. Alright, hold on, hold on, hold on.
I mean there's two of them.
We'll get the original and then we'll get both.
I'm not gonna be able to do that. I'm an expert.
Alright, let's go.
Oh!
What the fuck? I said that the whole thing.
Do it again.
Better than I ha- Let's just see.
Let's see how it goes.
Here comes the sequel.
There it is.
There are the two rat songs.
But how the fuck am I supposed to do this?
Is this just a dance number?
I think it's a dance number.
It's a jackass right now.
You can't not look like a
jackass when you're in VR 363.
That's what I'm gonna do for that one.
That's right. Here's my favorite part.
Okay, better not get rid of Vincent Price's part.
Here it comes, here it comes.
Here it comes, here it comes. I don't care about it.
Just do it.
Here it comes.
No, what? You don't cut Vincent Price off.
What the hell was that?
I can't believe it.
I don't know.
Doom basket case.
Doom OST.
Somebody just gave $50.
Who was it?
It just rocketed up the screen.
That's what that was. Thank you for the 50 bucks.
That's a huge fucking money drop.
Let me see if I can see it.
I can't see it. I have to come out of the whole thing to see it.
Take two steps to your right.
Better?
Take two steps to your...
But the thing tells me to stand here.
Save. Why was I like over here?
I was like over here.
Rule of thirds, guys.
Rule of thirds.
Alright, this is good. I put it right here, right?
Alright, I got a couple more. What were they?
I'm the giant rat
that makes all of the
rules.
Let's see what kind of troll we can get ourselves.
Alright.
Any requests?
Basket case?
Is that even on here?
How about American Idiot?
How about Wake Me Up When September Ends?
What is this one?
Which one is this one?
I don't even know which one this one is, but I'm going to do it.
I need to hear it first.
This one?
There it is.
This song is definitely
about me.
This song is about me.
My shadow
The only one that walks beside me
Eek!
I'm bringing up My Shadow.
It's everybody's favorite part. It's the only part of the song that everyone knows how to sing.
When the city sleeps
and I'm the only one
that walks beside me
My shadow's the only one
Today is
only way
to go around and find me
My shadow
and find me
Okay, stop it!
One more time?
We have a resident
sleeper.
It's boring as fuck.
Alright, fine. We'll do
a meme song. What do you guys want for a meme
song?
Brass Butin was on the list. I saw that
a shitload of times. Is that actually on here?
Brass Butin Funk Overload
and then there's
Funk Overload
Is this what you guys want?
This is the real song, right?
Is this the actual one?
I don't have the regular one.
This is the original?
Jackass alert!
Hey!
I got it wrong.
I got it wrong. Break it!
Lusting
and his hunger for power
became known to more and more people.
The demands to do
something about this outrageous
man became louder
and louder.
It still goes. This is a long song.
Wait! One more time?
Alright, now let's do this one!
This is the Super Saiyan
version of that song.
It's just times
two speed.
President Slaver!
Uh oh!
Get out of here!
One more brass beat and we're out.
We're out.
I don't give a shit!
Let's go!
There's so many!
I don't give a shit!
Let's go!
I can't feel it!
You guys are fucking
so in my head. God damn it!
It was the end of the song.
I could just feel them fucking in my body.
That you guys were just...
I was getting resident sleeper.
Toonuk Toonuk?
Alright, this is a mod request. I know what this one is.
I couldn't pay attention.
This is it, right? There's only one expert though.
Why are they all expert only?
Make them hard.
Oh yeah, this song is fucking
fire. I remember this one.
Bring it on!
It's a good song.
What could he do after?
What is it?
Oh, those fuckups at the time!
You get the first note wrong.
Resident sleeper.
Wait, is it resident sleeper
game or resident sleeper
song?
I don't know.
Resident sleeper.
Wait, is it resident sleeper
game or resident sleeper song?
That's really important distinction.
Everybody's screaming.
What's Tachyon?
Tachyon.
Looks like you wanted me to see that.
You want me to do it?
Yes, yes, yes, yes. Jesus!
Alright.
Like this, right?
I don't think it exists, guys.
Sorry. Did I spell it right?
Like that, right?
I think you guys got ultimate baited.
I'm sorry.
No, I don't think it's here.
Alright, I don't know what any of this shit is.
Do space channel five?
That's a good idea. Space channel!
Wait, is there no space channel?
Jojo?
Bustin?
If Bustin's on here, I'll try it.
Like that, right?
Is this it? Which is the right one?
Which is the correct one?
The top one or the middle one?
Alright. What else are we going to queue up here?
I don't... Jojo's Bizarre Adventure...
I don't even know... How am I even going to
pretend I know the beat to those songs?
I've never seen Jojo. Why would I...
Jojo? Jojo.
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure opening four.
Which one of these
openings am I going to pick?
We've got opening two.
I'm seeing a lot of twos.
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure opening
two.
Okay. I'll play this for 30 seconds
and I'm instant deleting it.
Alright. So we got... We got...
Here we go.
Ray Parker Jr. Here we go with
Scouse Busters.
Let me tell you something.
I lost the first note.
I lost the first note. I fucked it up.
Is it moving around?
It's like having to step like all the way over here.
I have like the room scale
shit. So I gotta like move and
box me up. I got it. Let's go. Let's do it.
It's the first time I've failed fucking hardly.
Freaking man.
C.
C. I'll take C.
Alright. I'm going to say like two or three
more songs and I'm going to have to take another like water break.
Alright. Right. I forgot.
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure.
Nope. God. I have no idea
how that song goes.
There's a bunch of fucking trumpets.
Yo.
Alright. Let's do
YMCA. Africa.
Where is it? Is it up? Where is it?
Oh. Here it is.
Okay. We've got AfriQ.
How about Dancing Queen?
This fucking...
This stream is going down.
YMCA.
YMCA. And then I delete
the VOD. This version with no bombs?
Nah. That's fine.
Alright. Let's go. We'll do these and I'll see
how I'm doing. I'm going to get some more water though.
YMCA is right here.
Here we go.
No. No. No.
I wore special tech wear today.
See? Like heat wear. This is like
workout clothes.
Imagine how embarrassing that would be if you were at a wedding.
That was like a wedding DJ.
Alright everybody. Let's go on.
And here comes the bride
and groom. Mr. and Mrs.
Oh I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry. I don't know what happened
folks. This doesn't usually happen.
I just like burrow in the wedding. I'm so sorry.
What the fuck?
That was so dumb.
Ladies and gentlemen, please
welcome
the bridesmaids.
Here they come.
Accompanying Ashley
it's the
groom's best friend
Michael.
I'm going to do like this. You're going to go out there and cheer.
YMCA.
He's fucking
bummed. No. No. We're done with
that one. We're done with that one.
I'm not doing that one again.
And ladies and gentlemen
please welcome
the father and mother of the group.
I'm so sorry. I don't know.
It's my first time doing a fucking wedding DJ job.
I'm so sorry.
That's too much fucking squicking around.
Switching around and shit.
First dance rune.
I'm getting gamer fatigue too.
Gamer fatigue is settling in.
Here we go. Here we go. I made it.
Here we go.
Someone's caught on me.
Damn it!
I was so sad about that one.
Alright. Fuck gamer fatigue. You know how it is.
What else do I have here?
Alright. We'll do one more. What's the number one?
Take a break.
I will in a second. One more song.
Let's go.
So far they're popular. We've picked a bunch.
Sort by
like plays, alright?
Midnight City.
Pirate the Box.
American Idiot, really?
Dota? This is not what I'm going on about.
We're leaving.
I'm going to take a break in a second. This is the last song I'm going to do.
Where is it?
Where the fuck did it go? Pure Imagination.
Am I stupid?
Did I not download it?
Am I actually dumb here?
I might be stupid.
It's queued.
Maybe this one wasn't done downloading.
Okay. 100%. No fucking
no mix ups.
Pure Imagination.
This is the one I'm going on. This is it.
Make a wish. Make a wish?
Count to three.
Toddler Tantrum.
That's right!
Boomer Emo.
This is a classic song, guys.
From a classic movie.
From a classic actor.
I've got to be like dancing around.
That's my problem.
Simply look around.
You will need to change
the world.
Pure Imagination.
Living in
the only
way
in which you
truly
wish.
I have one more idea for good measure. Let's go ahead.
I love these Boomer songs.
Alright, that's it.
That's it.
Did I spell it wrong?
Like this?
Like talk?
Which one?
Like this one?
This one right here.
Alright, alright, alright, alright.
Is it on? Expert? I'm not going to be able to do this.
I'll give it one attempt. I'll try.
Alright.
Alright, I'll try it once.
This is the last song.
I've got to get at it. I'm going to take a break.
We'll see.
Let me see how I'm doing.
Alright, let's do it.
What the fuck?
I didn't even get to the fucking title of the song.
Get in with the team.
Hey, you got it.
You got to hear it.
I have the high ground. What is this?
I have the high ground.
I don't understand.
It's over, Anakin.
Oh my god, it's the fight.
I have the high ground.
You underestimate my power.
Don't try it.
Oh yeah, he cuts his legs.
Why don't you make
what I think is E.
I got the E. What does that mean?
Did I get another one? I got the Force theme.
It's in there. Who the fuck is it?
Here we go.
This is actually the last one.
Sorry. Here it comes.
This is not Star Wars.
I think this thing is glued to my face.
If I pull it off, I think skin's going to come off.
Should I be concerned about this?
I'm going to hurt myself, I think.
It's going to be like
the jelly skin is going to come out.
Like 40 strings attached to my face.
Don't end on that one.
What's the hardest one in the whole game?
Fire and Flames? Is it the hardest one
in the whole game? It's probably
Cotton Eye Joe?
It is Han Solo.
No it's not. Why the fuck would the hardest thing in the game
be Han Solo?
Let's do Fire and Flames on Expert Plus.
I'm going to fit.
Fire and Flames.
I think I'm just going to have to live in here.
This is the last one.
Then I've got to take a break.
This is not the song.
Give me a fucking break.
What the fuck? It's impossible.
Let me try it again.
I got fucking at least kind of far. I got far enough.
I can get it. It's like
just goes like this.
Easy with the hair.
Uh oh. This is bad.
What year is it?
Alright. Put that down. I'm going to get some more water.
I'll be right back. What a goddamn blast.
Fucking rat's nest.
Alright. I will be right back.
I'm going to get some water. I'll see you guys in
two to three minutes. Something like that.
Okay. So here's the plan.
Hello. Hi.
The plan is
we take a break from Intense VR.
And we're going to move on to
a bartender simulator.
You just make drinks.
You just sit there. You relax. You like poor shit.
We're just going to chill. We're going to wind down.
Because I'm like
it's like a three and a half hour workout.
Does anybody else get this
sweaty and disgusting when they play VR?
Am I like the only streamer that
his whole body deteriorates?
Okay.
So give me one second. I've got to get it set up.
I'll be right back while I get the game
ready to go. See you soon.
Alright. Give me
a second.
I promise that I'm
this fucking gross every stream.
This looks like I haven't
showered or bathed
in weeks.
I've got my gear on. Like I've got my
wear on.
Alright. I apparently didn't install
this game. I thought I did.
So we've got three minutes to just hang out.
Which is good. This is a good enough time for me to
relax for a minute.
Alright. So let me tell you my first impressions.
Super hot. VR was phenomenal.
Experience is only like an hour and a half or so.
One to two hours long. Which is I mean
what you get is worth it I think.
There's a lot of replayability to try to get your scores
better. The game was amazing.
Beat Saber is just
a new, better version
of what Guitar Hero tried to do.
Like years ago.
It gets you up. It gets you moving.
You actually have to feel the beat with your hands.
I mean Rock Band and shit like that
with the drums. That was cool.
But you weren't like inside of the beat.
It's got a receding hairline. What?
I can't do the whole. Guys I can't do the whole
Shrek movie. If I do the whole
Shrek movie. I'll be lucky if this
stream. I'm gonna get like a
I'm gonna get a knock on my fucking door.
Like Twitch staff.
Hey man. Like don't fucking. Don't do that.
Don't like just play random movie clips.
And uh
Full copyright songs.
Alright. Let me get ready.
Should be back on like this.
You just did?
Oh I know. This looks
I don't even care. You know like
sometimes you give a shit about your appearance.
When the webcam goes on.
And I know the webcam's on.
Usually I'm a little self conscious.
I want to make sure that I look okay.
How's my face look? Do I look alright?
Do I look okay?
I don't care right now. And you can just tell.
And these images are gonna
come back to haunt me in like fucking
two years.
I don't even care. Like I just don't
Typically I'd be like oh hold on. Before I turn
the camera on. Let me like. Okay.
Hey guys. Hey what's up?
Hey. What are you guys up to?
Gives a shit.
Alright. One minute. You look like you just
exited a time machine.
My DNA's been scrambled.
I don't think this is on Twitch.
VR like bartender?
I don't think I can even make this a
bartender.
No.
What am I supposed to put for a category?
Is there just like a general
VR? I can't put a category
here. There's no just
general VR.
What about like virtual games and demos?
I guess. Yeah.
Let's put it to games and demos.
Your hair immediately after you take the headset off
gives me so much anxiety. Well I'm getting a haircut.
I'll get my haircut.
Alright. We're ready to do this.
I'm gonna get back in.
Take another sip of this. My
handy drink.
Here we go.
I have no idea what this game is. All I know is it was $20.
So let's hope it was worth $20.
Windows Firewall has
blocked this game. Why?
For one thing it's pretty fucking loud.
Turn it down a little.
Okay. Let's go.
This is Bartender Simulator.
Imagine paying $20 to give yourself
malware. I apologize in advance
for the puke cam that's about to show up
here.
Okay. Nightclub
Bar...
One more sip of this. I'm gonna need it.
Controls are down there.
Let's get into the position.
I'm like centered with the frame.
I am. I look asshole.
Alright. I'm in.
There's in my hands.
I need the audio.
Imagine sending... Why is this
so delayed?
So this is good to go, right?
Nightclub Bar.
Bartender VR Simulator.
Single Drink Pro Mode.
Profile Tutorial.
Start each new drink by placing
a napkin on the counter.
I just want to relax, guys. Don't put the drink on the napkin
until you have finished preparing it.
Place the
ingredients back to where you got them from.
Be precise when pouring
liquids. Your precision
will be rewarded, while
carelessness may result in failure.
Here comes the spill joke.
You earn points for making the drinks
as fast as possible and by demonstrating
the technique.
I've been doing one of those and like
I fell over there and I can't
reach it. What? In the practice mode,
you will be given verbal instructions and
messages displayed on your screen.
It's really fucking loud.
Should you need guidance in the game mode,
you can always press the hint button
located on the screen. Okay, so get the pours correct.
Every time you press this button,
you will lose some of the money that you have already
earned. It's about making
money?
After mastering the drinks introduced in the
four bars, you will be rewarded with
a certificate for completing the Bartender
VR virtual course.
Okay. This will allow you
to go and further prove yourself
in the pro mode.
Okay. Have fun.
Thanks a lot.
The narrator who was a little too close to the microphone.
Here we go! Nightclub bar
practice.
I just saw a free there.
What does that mean?
Welcome. While working at this nightclub bar,
you will learn how to prepare
four different drinks.
Kuba Libre, Muscovile,
Cano, and Gin and Tonic.
Please remember to start the drink
by placing the napkin on the bar.
Do not place any drink on
the napkin until it's ready to serve.
You will prepare your drink
either by holding the glass in your hand
or by placing it on the metal tip tray
at the edge of the bar.
Be precise when pouring ingredients.
Extra points are awarded.
No! I gotta hit that lady!
Haha! My hands!
There's clads everywhere!
On the right side of the screen.
Have fun and good luck!
What? I can't stop!
I have to get out of this!
Kuba Libre. Place a napkin on the
bar top.
And fill it with ice cubes.
Place a napkin on the bar top.
It's like that game
at the arcade
with the footballs and there's like the three holes.
That lady's head is like a hundred points.
That was it!
Kuba Libre. Place a napkin
on the bar top. Yes! Okay, I can move on.
Place a napkin on
the bar top. Fuck!
Kuba Libre. Place a napkin
on the bar top. Long glass
and fill it with ice cubes.
Pour in 40 milliliters
of white rum and 100 milliliters
of cola.
40! Get it in the ice!
Ah! I was taking it in the ice!
I was trying to keep it cold!
Kuba Libre. Place a napkin
on the bar top. Pour in
40 milliliters of white rum
and 100 milliliters of cola.
Oops! Okay, cola!
Where's the coke? Where's the cola?
Where's the cola?
I don't see any cola!
What am I doing wrong?
Alright, okay.
Alright, alright, let's go.
Place a napkin. Take a long glass.
Pour in 40 milliliters of white rum
and 100 milliliters of cola.
Where's the bottle opener? Okay, there it is.
Add a straw.
Serve the drink on the net.
Alright, there you go.
Thank you!
Place a napkin on the bar top
and fill it with ice cubes.
Where can I get you?
Pour in 30 milliliters of
30 milliliters of sweet vermouth.
Americano. Place a napkin
on the bar top.
Your drink sucks!
Fill it with ice cubes.
In 30 milliliters of bitter
and 30 milliliters of sweet vermouth.
Sweet vermouth and bitter. This is bitter right here!
This shit's empty! Wrong liquid!
What?!
Americano. Place a napkin
on the bar top. Americano.
Take a long glass and fill it
with ice cubes.
Pour in 30 milliliters of
30 milliliters of sweet vermouth.
Sweet vermouth.
Do I have that shit here?
That vodka...there it is.
I lost my...what is it?
30?
Pour in 80 milliliters of soda.
80?
That's a lot. That's too much.
Add one orange zest.
Add a straw.
Serve the drink
on the napkin.
I lost my audio.
Moscow Mule. Place a napkin on the bar top.
These are actually pretty good.
I like these.
I like Moscow Mules.
This is 13 cents?
Alright, so this is a napkin on the bar.
Take a mug
and fill it with ice cubes.
Take a mug.
Pour in 40 milliliters of vodka
and 100 milliliters of ginger beer.
Ginger beer.
I like tea.
Dashes of bitters.
Lime. Get it in there.
Add a straw.
Serve the drink on the napkin.
There you go.
57 cents.
Gin and tonic.
I hate this drink.
I think this is disgusting.
I think gin is disgusting.
It tastes like pine salt.
Pour in 40 milliliters of gin
and 100 milliliters of tonic.
One of these.
Here we go.
Imagine they spin the drink.
You make the whole drink and the guy's like
Alright, let's flip it.
Welcome to fucking Las Vegas.
He's like flipping shit around
to see a drink.
Gin and tonic. Place a napkin on the bar top.
That's wrong.
Let's just get the tutorial done.
Hey, welcome to Las Vegas.
Place a napkin on the bar top.
Alright, gin and tonic.
Long glass and fill it with ice.
Are you arguing at my bar?
Cool down a little.
Cool down a little, you fucking asshole.
Gin and 100 milliliters of tonic.
Where's the trash?
Add a straw.
Serve the drink on the napkin.
44 cents.
Alright, I'm ready.
Time to do the challenge mode.
Here we go.
Welcome. It's time to check
what you have learned.
As soon as you press the stop button on the screen
you will have 10 minutes to prepare
as many drinks as possible.
The drinks, which you have already learned
to make in the bar, will be selected
on a random basis.
Please follow the rules that you have learned
during the practice level.
If you don't know how to prepare a particular drink
you can use...
This bartender is fucking annoying.
Then let's go with vodka.
How many?
Moscow mule. Place a napkin on the bartop.
Vodka.
Ice.
Gin and tonic.
Um, gin and...
Gin and tonic. Place a napkin on the bartop.
Gin and tonic.
Okay, gin. Give me that gin with a 40, right?
Hold on.
Tea!
Cuba Libre. Place a napkin on the bartop.
Take a long glass
and fill it with ice cubes.
Pour in 40 milliliters of white rum
and 100 milliliters of cola.
And then...
straw...
wine. And then straw.
Moscow mule.
This is... Okay, this is wine.
What?
I'm gonna do a napkin first.
White rum and cola is the
chupacabra.
What's it called?
What's this actually called?
White rum and cola.
You know what? I got a fucking better idea.
Here's the better idea.
Let's go. 40 milliliter
white rum and then cola.
And then a lime
and a fucking straw.
There you go, man.
What's next? Gin and tonic.
Come on! Tricks!
What trick did I do? Gin and tonic.
Gin and tonic again.
Moscow mule.
Okay, we got it now.
Moscow vodka.
What is that? It's ginger beer.
Pour in 40 milliliters of vodka and 100 milliliters of ginger beer.
And then what is it?
Bitters?
Americano.
How much do I have to do? Okay, I got 32 bucks.
What's Americano?
I don't fucking remember.
Soda? 30!
Oh my god!
Gin and tonic. I know this one.
Come on! That was pretty cool.
What is Americano?
30.
Then what?
Soda?
Sweet vermouth.
And then what is it? A fucking lime?
80?
Who orders this fucking drink?
God!
Pour in 40 milliliters of white rum
and 100 milliliters of cola.
What are you...
3 minutes left?
52 dollars?
I know this one well.
Fuck it.
No, I know what...
Place a napkin on the bar top.
Which one is it? White rum and coke?
And 100 milliliters of cola.
What did I do wrong?
Bitters and sweet vermouth.
And 30 milliliters of sweet vermouth.
30. And then it's soda, right?
It doesn't want me to do the two.
It really does not like that I do that.
It hates that, actually. It doesn't want me to do it.
It doesn't want me to do it. That's fine.
No tricks allowed.
This one is ginger beer.
And sweet vermouth.
80.
I just want to make sure what it was.
I thought it was 100.
And then what fruit is it? What fucking fruit is it?
Orange zest.
Good luck. I got 10 seconds to make another drink.
Moscow mule.
Screenshot?
What did I take a screenshot of?
Whoa, I just fell over. That was weird.
Beach bar. Single drink.
Pro mode.
When am I going to learn how to do tricks?
Ketchup and mustard. Rice?
Hey, Lloyd!
Hey, Harry!
Oh, it's so spicy!
It's so spicy!
Anybody know what that is?
Excuse me.
Where the fuck were you yesterday?
Bar spoon?
What's this gigantic cigarette?
Let me just test this out.
It needs a little more salt.
I hit something.
I'm hitting something.
What am I hitting? I can't even go over there.
I can't go over there.
Let's get a napkin out here.
Make a mojito.
Four limes. You got it.
One, two.
Why don't you pick it up upside down?
Why would you pick that up upside down?
20 milliliters of sugar syrup.
Sugar syrup?
Which one of these is sugar?
40? 20?
Sugar and limes and you mash them up.
10 mint leaves.
Put the long glass with crushed ice.
This is fucking popcorn.
Pour in 40 milliliters of white rum.
White rum and then soda.
40 milliliters of soda.
Where's my... oh.
Where'd you...
Alright, that's done.
More crushed ice.
I'm not going to remember all this shit.
Two straws?
Decorate with a sprig of mint.
Oh.
Serve the drink on the napkin.
How am I ever going to remember that?
Piperino.
Place a napkin on the bar top.
Place a napkin there?
Put it in one place.
Four lime wedges into the whiskey glass.
We've got it.
Two, three, four.
Take the muddler and muddle the limes.
Where is the mud? There it is.
Fill the glass up with crushed ice.
Oh, that's cubed ice.
Wrong one.
40 milliliters of kashasa.
Kashasa?
40 is kashasa.
And then sugar.
That's not the right one. Where's sugar?
Sugar syrup.
Place the bar spoon in the whiskey glass.
The way I mix it up?
This is just like an ear wax cleaning video.
This is just the doctor office close-up videos that people watch for some reason.
Top up with more crushed ice.
Decorate with a wedge of lime.
I'm not going to remember any of this.
Add two short straws.
Two short straws?
Serve the drink on the napkin.
Am I going to bump into this?
I'm going to hit something. The wall is right here.
Am I going to hit something?
You can take it. It's right there.
Piperino.
Place the napkin on the bottle.
Can I even make it if I toss it?
No. It's not going to work.
It's your drink.
Welcome to the beach.
There it is.
Oh my god.
It just explodes.
Alright, let me get through this one.
I'm going to just be very...
Take a whiskey glass and drop four lime wedges into it.
Who even wants this?
I'm hitting something.
Take the muddle and muddle the lines.
Fill the glass up with crushed ice.
Pour in 40 milliliters of cachaa and 40 milliliters of sugar syrup.
Place the bar spoon in the whiskey glass and stir the drink.
Decorate with a wedge of lime.
Two short straws.
Place the bar spoon in the whiskey glass and stir the drink.
Decorate with a wedge of lime.
Two short straws.
Serve the drink on the napkin.
What's wrong with you sir?
Place the napkin on the bar top.
Glass. One of these.
Ice cubes this time.
Pour in 80 milliliters of prosecco
and 60 milliliters of aperitivo.
Aperitivo. 60 of aperitivo.
The prosecco.
That's peach prosecco.
That's peach secco.
Prosecco. That's vodka.
There's prosecco.
80 of prosecco.
Top up with 40 milliliters of soda.
Fuck!
Place the napkin on the bar top.
No, I'm not going to be able to get that one.
Take a coke and fill it up with ice cubes.
That's going to be interesting.
Pour in 80 milliliters of prosecco
and 60 milliliters of aperitivo.
And then 60 of aperitivo
which is this one, 60.
Top up with 40 milliliters of soda.
Down, get the soda.
40.
Comes out fast.
Add one orange zest.
Orange zest.
Add a short straw.
Serve the drink on the napkin.
I may as well just drink this.
I think the poll is right here.
Sex on the beach.
Place a napkin on the bar top.
Take a long glass
and fill it with ice cubes.
Pour in 40 milliliters of vodka
and 20 milliliters of peach schnapps.
And 20 of peach schnapps.
How about this one for you?
Pay attention to that.
Sex on the beach.
Place a napkin on the bar top.
Okay, let's put a napkin up there.
Take a long glass and fill it with ice cubes.
Uh, god damn it.
Pour in 40 milliliters of vodka
and 20 milliliters of peach schnapps.
Top up with 60 milliliters of orange juice.
60 of orange juice?
And 60 milliliters of cranberry juice.
Oh.
Ah, it's such a hot day.
Oh, thank god.
I really needed that.
It looks good.
What was I doing? Oh, 60.
These can't break.
I made it a plastic.
Slice of orange and a cherry.
And two long straws.
Two long straws?
Ooh.
Serve the drink on the napkin.
Here you go!
That's it.
Now let's go to the menu.
Single drink, nightclub,
beach bar,
rooftop. What a single drink.
This is gin and tonic.
Do I get like actual customers or is this it?
Gin and tonic.
How many gin and tonics can I make in 10 minutes?
I'm not sure there's anything else
left to do.
I do like the challenge mode.
Rooftop lounge.
Rooftop VIP bar.
Tutorial profile settings.
What else is there to do?
Is the pro mode the thing that I need to do?
Free play?
Okay, let's do
free play at the beach.
Alright, what do we need here?
When your drink is ready, serve it on the napkin
and check what you have made.
I can make my own drinks?
Really?
Nice! Okay, I'm going to show you guys
the best fucking drink that you can ever drink.
Whiskey glass.
Get it up there.
They have whiskey.
You need a good whiskey here.
I don't have any whiskey, so
never mind, get rid of that.
A regular tall glass.
Just a few cubes of ice, not very many.
That's it, you're good. That's enough of that.
The game is going to be mad if I don't fill it up.
I'm only allowed to put a certain
amount of ice, it has to be full.
I'm going to go with a
vodka. Make sure it's
good, high quality vodka. You want to fill it up about
I'd say
like the whole glass.
Even if it's a little more, it's okay.
Then what you want to do
is you want to grab a lime.
Stick a lime up on the end there.
What I like to do is I like to do a little splash
of cranberry.
Just to get it in. There it is.
There you go, get a napkin on there.
That's what I call a fucking vodka drink.
The next one
that I'm going to show you is this, the real one.
First of all, get fucking ice cubes in there.
Flip it up there. Flip it vodka, I'm talking about
about 40 milliliters.
Grab yourself a soda can here. Snap it off.
Bingo. Throw it up.
Best of the way. That's enough.
Get it out of there. Grab the cranberry. Get it in there too.
This is like a vodka soda cranberry.
Grab a lime.
A couple of them actually.
You can forego the lime if you want.
Grab a straw.
Finish it off with some crushed ice.
There you go. Order up!
Okay, I'm fine.
Okay. Here's another one.
You can impress some of your friends at a party
if you do this one. First of all, you get a glass.
You want to fill it up with
orange zest. The whole thing.
This takes like the skin of probably
four or five oranges.
Get about a hundred. And then you put a little bit
of orange juice in there.
Just enough to get it so you know it gets happy.
Grab the squisher. Squish it.
Then you got a little orange
puree in here.
And then what you want to do is you want to go to the
Do you have any milk?
Just pretend this is
Or you can use heavy cream too.
Just pretend this is heavy cream.
Put like seventy-three milliliters of heavy cream
in there. That's when you want to get it shaken up.
You want to stir it a little.
Okay. Now
you want sugar syrup.
Which is right here. Just enough.
Okay. Now you want crushed ice.
It's important that it's the crushed ice
because you're going to do something here.
Get that full up. Just that's pretty good.
Now we're going to add a little bit of vodka.
Just enough to the rim. About
thirty milliliters. Stir it up again.
So it gets all happy and all crushed up
Okay. Now what you're going to do is
you're going to grab a little orange puree.
Grab yourself a
just another little orange with a cherry
just to get on there so it looks nice.
And I like to do
usually you share this.
Okay. Well forget about that.
I call this one the orange
creamsicle dream.
Bon Appetit.
Just awful.
This next one I'm going to show you.
Get yourself a few glasses.
Get a little bit of vodka.
Across all the glasses. This is important.
I need some more glasses
though. This one goes up here.
Oh. Well I guess I can't do that.
Never mind. I'll just line them up the way I had them before.
I've got the ice in all of my vodka
in all three of them.
Okay. A little bit of Prosecco.
Okay. Then we're going to top it off
with some cream soda.
To give it a little kick at the end.
This is like five or six
customers out here watching this. You know what I mean?
You want to leave a little bit of room
because
nobody wants a full drink
stuffed in their mouth.
And then what you do after this is you stand back
as the bartender
and this one is called
the ball throwing midway game that nobody
can beat.
You've got to get it right in the middle.
It's kind of gritty.
But I don't think it worked.
Ah. Well I almost got it.
More!
Imagine throwing a fucking baseball
right in the middle of that.
Alright. This next one is called
Gerber
ran out of stuff to do in the game
because the game is really just kind of a giant
tutorial. How can I ruin this?
How do I ruin the whole thing?
What you do is you take the fucking
get it all over there
and all over the fucking bar.
You say, oh yeah, oh yeah
Rachel, oh what a sunny day, huh?
Well that was fun.
Fire this van.
Yeah, yeah, I moved here
in fucking October.
It was fucking fun.
Oh, what's that? What's that? Oh.
You do business out here.
Oh, that's wonderful.
Oh, you and your wife?
That's just great, man.
What did you want? You wanted cranberry, right?
You wanted cranberry mule? Yeah.
Yeah, I'm sure that's great.
You guys are all having a great time like partying here.
And I fucking have to live here, you know.
I heard about your room, by the way.
Guys, like
screaming and yelling past
4am.
I'm not sure you know that there's other guests here at this
hotel and resort.
All five of you. All five of you.
You're probably wondering,
oh wait, no, no, this one's for me.
Here you go
fucking Greg, Dan,
Jake, Barry,
and Tim. Yeah, all of that.
Cheers to all of us, right? You're on
vacation, goddamn it, not me.
Alright, I gotta get out of this game.
You come out here,
you fucking make a ton of noise,
you be loud and
annoying, you have your goddamn boat out there.
Sell that thing.
Sell that thing and build a fucking school!
Fucking assholes!
Alright, let's go.
He's going full
socialist.
He's got
a fridge shared
up.
Alright,
I think that's where I'm gonna call it.
I'm exhausted. It's pretty much
the exact same amount of time as last time,
like four and a half hours.
I'm like fucking beat right now. Beat saver
like just took the whole rest of the
night all out of me.
So, here's the question. I'm gonna turn off
this music. I got a question for
you guys.
Are we dropping frames, I think? A little bit.
So, my question to you all
is, let's get that off
screen for a minute.
Hey, it's me. Remember the person
that said that they get really bad anxiety when I
take this off?
This is like intent, holy shit.
This is like intentional.
So,
I am not gonna be streaming for the next day or two.
I'll be back.
Because I did want to do three days
in a row. And we did three days in a row here.
And I'm pro-
Do you guys want me to come back with more VR?
Or do you want me to like pivot away for a little while?
What do you think? I still fucking love it.
Yes, yes. More, more, more.
Yes. More, please.
Yeah, there's so much more to
do. I have
a list. A very long one.
Alright. So, I'm gonna leave
the room set up the way it is, but I'm gonna take like
a couple days. I have a doctor's appointment tomorrow.
So, I can't really-
It's tomorrow afternoon.
And then the day after that, I have some
house stuff that I'd like to get done.
So, you won't see me for probably two days.
I'll come back here and we'll do some more VR.
But, this is fucking a lot of fun.
What a blast.
I just wish I had the stamina to do it for more
than like five hours.
Ah, is it a-
Dude, okay, I just-
This is why you gotta take breaks.
In this space here. Look at what just
happened. I just tried to place my
glass on my desk.
And I like went too far and almost dropped it.
This is why, like, you gotta
spend some time in the real world.
But, I'll see you guys in a couple days.
We're gonna pivot to the bits. Thanks for joining me.
I've had a lot of fun the last few days.
I just can only
do it for so long before I have to go
like take a shower. If you spend
too long in VR, you're gonna get stuck there.
That's what happens when you practice
throwing and breaking
glasses. I was really throwing
them too. I was really trying to throw
those with weight behind
them. Superhot VR was incredible.
Beat Saber, obviously, a ton of fun.
And we're gonna go to the bits.
For those of you that are maybe new
to the stream, I don't read
bits during a stream. Or subs.
We do like a bit reading segment
where we wind down at the end.
That's exactly what we're about to do right now.
First time viewer here.
But, thanks again.
If you want something, if you want to see something in VR,
I highly recommend you go to the discord
and put
40 months from
Leatherjacket. Oh my god.
If you want some certain VR games, I know
Gorn is on the list. That's like
another one that I really want to play. There's like two or three others
that I really want to play.
But please go to the recommended channel. I'll look at them over
the course of the next couple days.
We'll see what we can do. But let's go
back to earlier, about
five hours ago. We had five
dollars come in from Miss Melon T.
Five bucks. Thank you so much, Miss Melon T.
Hey, Jerma, I ordered the Night Sky shirt the minute
it was announced. Still waiting
for it to get here since I'm all the way in Australia.
But I love the design so much, I was
inspired to remake it completely from scratch
in pixel art.
As well as adding a few extra stuff.
Hope you both and chat
like it. That's
fucking awesome. Let's see.
That is so
cool. That's awesome.
Unfortunately, Jerma Mercury
is not on that shirt, and neither is Saturn.
So you added those other planets.
Those planets got voted off.
Well, nicely done.
Thank you.
I'll get out of this. I'm still like
in the program here.
I think I need to go like this.
Okay, there we go.
I'm the best emote.
There we are.
Now I can see.
But thank you for the five dollars as well.
Binary Man, thanks for five bucks,
Binary Man. I'm honestly so sorry,
Jerma, I really am. Please don't hate me for
this. Don't hate me for this.
This is a video called The Pinnacle of Gamers.
Let me get it on here.
I'm sorry. God damn it.
I'm so close to the vibe is still
over here. I just like probably blew out somebody's ears. I'm really
sorry. That was like
an explosion.
Is this gonna play?
Okay, here we go.
This is called The Pinnacle of Gamers.
Did you speed this up or was I actually doing that?
What the fuck did you do that for?
Oh my god.
Oh, you dick.
You dick.
You fucking dick.
Alright, I'm telling you, I like to play videos
that people send me, but I'm gonna be
real frank with you here.
Don't pee in the soup. Do not piss
in the soup. Otherwise they're gonna have to get
pre-screened. If you don't know what I'm talking about,
if one guy pisses in the soup, nobody can eat it.
Link the video? I'm not gonna link that video.
That's too loud. Who was that?
I'm really sorry for this.
Well, I'm really sorry for like the
three day ban you're about to get.
Show no mercy. I can't show mercy
on that one. You're not streaming
until then. Yes, I am.
I'm streaming on the third day.
He's getting suspended from school before a vacation.
Don't worry.
Don't do that shit.
Really, come on. Don't make me have
to fucking change that policy because you want
to blow out everybody's ear drums.
One guy.
But anyways,
thank you Soup or Seal for the $2.50.
I do that to you guys all
the time. But mine's not intentional
and they're never that loud.
Any time I accidentally blow out ear drums is because
like a game setting is too high.
Or I open up a game for the first time and it's loud.
That was like, I'm gonna put it to red.
As loud as possible.
My dad's not mad. He's disappointed.
No, I'm good. I did like the video
up until the last tenth of a second.
But thank you Soup or Seal for the $2.50.
Here's an MS Paint drawing of you as a coal miner.
Jesus.
I hope you like it. Thank you Soup or Seal
for the $2.50.
God, that makes me look like a zombie
from a Resident Evil game. I look fucking
terrible. Look at that lower
right corner. Look at that Resident
Evil. I'm about to turn
45 year old man.
Rude? No, I'm not talking
about the drawing. I'm talking about me.
My actual face. That's the cover
of a horror novel. Yeah, that's like the scary
stories. Oh my goodness.
But that's
fucking awesome.
Thank you for the fucking
coal miner. I don't have
my eyes. Why do I have
no eyes?
But thank you. Thank you Alec
for the $1. How's a nice chicken
sandwich sound? Actually sounds pretty good.
Sounds pretty good. Thank you
for the $1. Thank you
Magellan for the five community subs
earlier. Beginning of the stream. Thank you
so much. Hey Divus, thanks for two bucks.
Two bucks from Divus, that's it.
Freudian weapon, thanks for the $2.50.
Your aiming is impeccable
as always, Jerma checks.
From Superhot. I feel like
it did okay. Maybe
like after 45 minutes or so.
I thought I was doing pretty good.
Check the chat link. Manhole
cover. Vocal streamer rescue
from Vegas sewer claims faulty
room scale.
Alright,
I'm not gonna lie, I thought the thing in the top left
was a pizza or a waffle.
And then I realized, wait,
that's a sewer cover.
That's so great. But thank you
Freudian for the $2.50. Thank you Nate
for the $1. Hey Jerma, I saw an old
Twitter post with your Sega CD
that has a Sega Genesis on the right.
Do I still have it? I do
not. I do not.
Unfortunately the Sega CD and Genesis are both
gone, but thank you. Thank you
Smashly for the ten community
subs. Ten coming in from Smashly.
Thank you. It's a lot of
subs to give.
But it's unfortunate, talking
about the Sega, Sega was it?
Not Dreamcast. The CD.
I actually came across like three
or four more Sega CD games that I really
want to play. I'm so disappointed
that I couldn't bring it with me in the move. I gave
it away and I don't have it anymore
and I'm like, I want to play the Cliff
Hanger game. I might have to get
another one. But
we'll see about that. Ask for
it back? I can't ask
for it back. Hey thank you Freudian Weapon for
the $2.50. Where is my venti
soy latte? Talking about my hair.
Talking about my hair.
Theo Mighty Bob
thanks for the two bucks. Freudian Weapon thanks
for the $2.50. This stream has been
amazing man. I don't care if the VOD is deleted
or muted. Hope you had a blast. Cause I
sure as hell did. Rock on sir.
Yeah, as much as I, I mean I
only complained about how small my room was once.
It was a very flash
rage. It wasn't really that. I wasn't
really angry. It's been a phenomenal
experience so far. The VOD is going to
get hit horribly though. So
unfortunately there's not much I can do about
that. But thank you Freudian. It was a blast.
Hope you had a good time too. Sticks Renegade
thanks for the $2.45. Do
all the single furries.
I'm not going to play all the single
furries on Beat Saber. Thank you
Nate for the $1
and Bozak for the $1 back to
back here. It's a me channel
theme. Too bad it was all shut down.
That's true. That's very true.
Hey JelloX, thanks for the
$2.50. Hey Jerbo, going to
Navy Bootcamp in two days. Thanks for
all the entertainment. Hopefully I can catch the streams
sometime soon. I wish you
the best of luck. Good luck to you. Hopefully we can see you
again real soon. Thank you so much
for being around. Good luck.
Yeah, hopefully we can see you again soon.
And thank you so much for the $2.50.
Bozak came in with another $3.00.
They say PogChamp.
Jermo for Super Bowl Halftime Show
2020. Oh, because of Sweet Victory.
Thank you so much for the
$3.00 Bozak and Jero. What did I get for a
grade on that one? That one got hard.
A lot of different
angle changes in the middle.
Thank you Nate again for $2.00.
Sweet Victory. Do you hate the NFL for what they
did to Spongebob?
I mean the halftime show is
unfortunate, but the halftime show usually is just
they just get like a bunch of actors
to come show up in the front row and dance
around and they do some songs.
So I mean,
some Super Bowl halftime shows are
really good. I mean,
I guess if you bring in Spongebob
for three seconds, you can't even give him
like ten. You can't even give Spongebob
like fifteen seconds.
What can you do? I think that was
probably the best Super Bowl halftime show.
It was probably Bruno Mars.
He did it, what, like three or four years ago?
He went fucking hard.
He played like every instrument.
It was very, very well done.
You can't have a Super Bowl halftime show ever again
when Bruno Mars put on that show.
Michael Jackson too from way back.
Well I'm talking like recently, the last like ten years.
Last like five to ten years.
Prince, yeah.
It's really good Super Bowl halftime shows.
Janet Jackson, oh yeah.
But in very recent memory,
I remember Bruno Mars was ridiculous.
He was like
singing and moving around and doing all these awesome
choreography. Then he went and like sat down at a drum set
and just played like a fucking whole
drum solo and was singing still.
It was like, how the hell are you this
talented? How could you do that?
It was great. But thank you
Gapsy for this one.
The one dollar. Do the pirate spy
song. I didn't catch it, unfortunately.
He played Beat Saber.
I did.
Ninety percent of that show was lip synced.
Here's something you guys need to understand
about songs, right?
Okay, I'm going to show you something.
The reason why they lip sync
all those songs
is because when you go like this
when you're like jumping and fucking
throwing your hands everywhere, like kicking
and shit. Okay, let's
make up a song here. It's going to be called
like Let's Get To It
Let's Get With It, right? That's like the name
of the song. And it's like
bang, bang, like let's get to it
let's get with it. So I'm going to
show you how hard that is to do while you like
fucking throwing your arms around, moving around.
Let's get with it. Let's get to it.
You can't, it's not impossible.
You're like, it's not
you can't do it. So what they do is they just
lip sync and they have like a thing go over.
So it sounds like the song that you like
that you've heard before.
If you're like jumping and like swinging around
you're going to sound all fucked up.
It's called vocal training?
Beyonce does it?
Alright, but like
can you explain
Broadway? Broadway is
they're all
they are c- in the world at like .96
speed. You know what I'm saying? But the rest of
us. Alright I'm wrong, I
admit that I'm wrong. But I'm not though
because it's hard. I'll admit that I'm wrong.
That's okay. Sometimes
you're wrong, but like
99.9999.9 percent
of the time, I'm right.
I'll take one,
I said something wrong or incorrect
at 650
5,000 times that I've
ever said anything correct. I would put my bet on that horse the first time he's ever been wrong.
I wouldn't. Neither would I. That's that's like a bet that you you'd get paid a shitload from me
saying something correct, but you'd be you'd be risking your money a lot. That's a very high
risk investment, but thank you to... I don't even remember how that started. Oh right,
Bozak for the three dollars. Thank you. No, that was... what the hell? How did I get on that?
I don't remember. But Freudian Weapon, it was Freudian Weapon was the one that gave fifty three
dollars. Fifty three dollars and fifty cents from Freudian Weapon. I heard it, but I couldn't come
out of the VR. I was stuck in there, but it was over 53 bucks. Thank you so much. They say,
hi it's me again derailing your stream. You're such a delight to watch. Love all that you do,
and you really do help brighten my day whenever I watch your streams or videos. So thanks so much
for keeping me going. Thank you, Freudian Weapon. I didn't derail the stream. I didn't really have
a chance to see it. It's not derailing the stream, by the way. If somebody drops like 50,
100 fucking bucks, it's okay to, you know, I just want to make sure that I don't miss it
because that's a lot of money. Oh, it's the Bruno Mars halftime show thing. Oh okay,
right, right, right. But thank you, Freudian Weapon. Much love to you. Thank you
for your huge amount of money. Purple rose tattoo. Thanks for the five bucks. You should do in
italics teaches germa how to play Civ stream. I would get bored out of my mind. I respect
those games. Civilization. What a great franchise, right? I could never sit down
and play those games. Ever. To me, it's a giant board game that lasts. They seem
interesting. They're really cool for what they are. It's just not something that I
would want to play. That's the kind of thing that I would watch over somebody's
shoulder and say, Oh, now what's going on over there? What's happening there?
Oh, well, you see, I'm taking the, uh, I'm taking these troops and moving over here
to this country and I got a diplomatic thing with that guy. So I can be careful
and she's coming back this way and I got a big diplomatic with her and I've got my
resources. I've got a coal. Uh, I've got VR coal. I've got wood and I just nodding.
I had just pretending. Oh yeah, no, no, that's cool. It's cool. Nice. Nice. So
how am I like, and I'm going to make, I'm going to ask a question that is me pretending
to what pretend to understand what I just heard. So when you get, uh, like 100 wood,
can you like turn that into something else or do you use that to build? I don't, I have no
idea what I'm talking about. I don't give a shit, but I'm just pretending that I do know
what I'm talking about. So who do you have selected for, uh, I know that like Gandhi's
in the game. Who is this Gandhi in this game? Now I'm pretending to know or understand what
I'm watching. I do that to everyone. I only do that in specific cases where someone's playing
civilization. I'm out of water and coffee. And that's a good thing because it's 9 PM
question marks at the end of everything you say. Yeah. Because then you can't be wrong.
Nothing you say is stupid. If you have a question mark at the end of your sentence.
So does a thousand wood give you something? Oh, I see. So those troops over there
are stronger than those troops that are next to them. You can never be wrong. And then
the person loves the loves that you just asked that question. And then they'll just
talk for like four or five straight minutes and you're having a pretend conversation with
somebody. It's really easy. What? My professor says every sentence like that.
That's because your professor, the professor knows that he can never be wrong when he does
that. If you want to challenge that professor, it's just like, I'm just posing the question.
That's for you to answer and you to understand and for us to come together
and get the question answered. Yoda. Now, but Civ is cool. Just not a fan of those kinds
of games. I'm not a big strategy player. Never have been, probably never will be.
It's some type of currency thing. I'm not sure. I use that really well.
Hey, future gamer. Thanks for the one dollar. Payday 2 VR has it so you can play with non-VR
users. An interesting stream idea. Really? That person's probably such a burden.
The person's probably so sloppy looking. But thank you to future gamer. Thank you.
For the two dollars and fifty cents. Jerma. You think you're gonna take me out that easy,
you scumbag? And then Star says, I've been waiting a long time for this. And I say,
Jerma. I say, come get it. And then Star says, my ride is going to whip your ass.
I say, Jerma, in your dreams. What the hell is this? Come get me, you streamer.
I don't know what that is, but thanks for the two dollars and fifty cents.
And some, there's a dialogue here between me, Star, and it's Helix. Thank you, though.
Frodian Weapon, thanks for the two dollars and fifty cents, Frodian.
These Beat Saber songs have been some of my favorites. How did you know?
But seriously though, I'm considering investing in a Vive and you aren't helping. This looks
so much fun. It is. I'm not going to pretend that that wasn't the last, that wasn't the most
fun I've had in a long time. Just in a pure video game sense, right? Well, I mean,
okay, Resident Evil 2 was amazing. It was a great experience. Start to finish. And then you got
super hot VR, Beat Saber, spells and sorcery, blade and sorcery, whatever. But man, if some
of those experiences aren't the most interesting, intense, and fun things I've done in probably
the last five years. Sorry if I am influencing a purchase, but it just is. You mean to tell
me that was fake excitement playing Africa? No, that was just a chill stream. We were just
chilling, taking pictures. I had an equally amount of fun time in that game. Just wasn't
the best thing I've ever done. But we see more Beat Saber. It was really fun to watch
you play. I don't see why not. Maybe I could like kind of warm up with VR with Beat Saber
and get a playlist or something. I don't, I'm not opposed to that. The next time I do VR,
whether it's two days from now or so, but not sit there for like an hour and a half or two
hours. I was in there for like an hour and a half. I would say probably warm up with it
for like 30 minutes. I am into it. But thank you, Frodeon. Thank you C4G for the $2.50.
Carly Rae Jepsen or I will cry will get it on the list. Here's the one unfortunate
thing about doing Beat Saber all the time. All the VODs will just get ruined. And maybe
that's something we should go out on rather than start with. Because there's a possibility
that it might kill the whole VOD. I don't know. I will have to look into that for real.
Carl, who's crying? We don't know. Oh, oh, oh, oh. But thanks for the $2.50. Hey Renix,
thanks for the $5. Do reptile theme from Mortal Kombat. He had his own theme? Did he?
How about that? Hey, thank you Superintendent Chalmers for the $1. Hey,
Jerma, next time you play Beat Saber, duct tape the controllers together and play
Duel of Fates. I would not be able to get the duct tape off. I would need some extra help
there. But thank you, Frodeon Weapon for the $2.50. Don't mind me. Just contributing to my
absolute favorite streamer. You stream to the highlight of my day, man. These past few have
been an absolute blast. Thanks so much. I've had a lot of fun. Three days in a row. It's
been great. And there's way more to look forward to. So we're gonna be doing it again.
Thank you, Frodeon. Slavik, thank you for the $4.00 SlavikGod. He says these drunk boys. Drunk?
I wasn't drunk. Maybe I was drunk in the head from being in the device for more than two or
three hours. But thank you Slavik for the $4.00. Busterboy, thanks for $1.00. Hey Jerma,
we're just gonna let you know earlier today I was telling myself I hope you don't play
Beat Saber because I really wanted to see it and I had to work. But you did it anyways.
Thanks. Well, I mean, I did say last night that my plan was to play it again today.
So I'm sorry, but I did. PaintedPotatoes, thanks for the $1.00 poop. Okay. GTX 1080 Quad
SLI, thanks for the $2.50. Hey Jerma, recently started watching you again, let me tell you.
I haven't laughed this hard in a while. The movie night was god tier and I can't wait for
the next one. Also, you should play Pavlov VR next time you stream. That would be great.
Also, could you say Nappy is epic. That would make his day. There you go. Thank you for the
$2.50. Pavlov is Counter-Strike in VR. I would get stomped. I would get absolutely destroyed.
I have a list though that I need to go through from recommendations and things that
I knew I wanted to play. I will play Vive as much as I need to, to get what I want out of it,
right? But thank you, GTX 1080. MultiTrip, thanks for the $2.50. If you had to die with
the Vive on, what VR game would you like to die inside? None of them. Die in the Vive.
I don't know. Revive the Human Simulator. It's a realistic, incredibly realistic being
revived simulator. Maybe it'll bring me back. I love that game. No, maybe I'll play it. Hey,
Topac. Thanks for the $5, Topac. I want to see Shito again. Show Shito. Shito is going to put
the VR headset on next time. I have a blast. Shito is not dead. He's just sleeping for a
long time. He'll be back. He's just in a closet somewhere, hanging out. He likes to be
in there. He likes to be in like a shoebox. He has a little bed in his shoebox and he likes
to be in there. Thank you, TimmyTim10 for the $1.00. You're my comedy humor joke idol.
Not just because you're funny, but because you're so genuine. If a scandal comes out and you
kick the homeless person once, I'll be crushed. Fuck you, Jeremy. Why did you do that?
Why the fuck did you do that? I didn't do that. Well, thank you for the $1.00,
but I did not do the thing I'm being accused of. There you go. That's kind of fucked up. It is
bad. It's really fucked up, actually. Good thing I didn't do it, but thank you. Hey, Zalaski.
Thanks for the $2.55. And we get the inevitable. Turma is bald. Actually bald image. Thank you
for the $2.55. Hey, FutureGamer. Thanks for the $1.00. Not mine, they say. Oh, that's the,
yeah, we saw that one already in the man cover. Manhole, whatever the hell it is. Hey, Convo
Breaker. Thanks for the $2.50. Hey, Jerma. Love you in a platonic way. Nothing creepy.
I hope. Well, I hope so, too. I hope. Anyways, you didn't tweet out the stream today,
and I missed most of it because of that. Yeah, I don't know what the hell that was about.
I tried to tweet twice, and it just wouldn't go through. So I'm sorry that if you usually
go through Twitter to find out if I'm streaming, I tried twice. My Twitter account got banned for
no reason. No, it's fine. It's probably just like an internet thing. That's probably too far away
from the Wi-Fi box or something, strangely enough. I love the VR streams more than most,
and now I'm going to have to watch it later without being able to call you funny names like
GeniusBoomer and GodGamer. As much as I like having a VOD to watch while you're gone,
still makes me sad. Please keep tweeting consistently. Also, play Pyre. Yeah, I wish
there was something I could do. I tried it twice. Five minutes apart. But I really appreciate it,
Convo Breaker. I got the Discord app. Yeah, if you're in the Discord, usually there's a ping,
I think, right? When the stream goes live, usually the whole Discord gets a ping.
So Twitter's probably less reliable than that. If you want total reliability, then you could
join the Discord server and get a ping. Because Twitter's weird because Twitter can just
kind of get buried in a feed sometimes. But thank you. Snoozingcopter, thanks for the
$1. So this is the last time I can give you 100 bits without my message not being read, huh?
In honor, can we watch this video? Imagine someone walking in a field of flowers,
falling off a tiny slope, and then keeps walking. Let's see.
Is this the right video? What did you just link me? Oh, this is when the kid falls off
and rolls down the hill. That's the wrong video. Why is this one playing?
There's the greatest voice crack in history. So we're supposed to imagine
someone walking in a field of flowers and falling off a tiny slope and then they just
keep walking. All right, now I get it. That's funny. Thank you, though, Snoozingcopter.
And yes, as of this stream, 250 is now the minimum. I put it in, I changed some of the
information down in the info. So if anyone scrolls down, new viewers will be able to see it.
As of today, 250 is the minimum. As of today, to be read. You can still give 10
cents or 20 or 25 cents if you want. That's fine. Don't worry about, you know, oh wait,
hold on, I can't even give bits if it's less than 250. No, that's still available.
Just to be read at the end is 250. End of a bit era. Greedy streamer. Greed. No, if you've
been here, you know, I've talked about it a lot over the last month or two. First, we raised
it to one. Let me put up like a shield here. In my defense, I don't want it to get to
a position where I don't read anything you say under $5 to $10, you know what I mean?
No, I know you're joking, but there are probably people that are probably actually annoyed by this.
But there are, you know, I don't do TTS. A ton of streamers that have similar view counts
have like $3.50, $5 TTS that just pops up. I'm not ever going to do that. I'm not going
to ever put it behind like 10 bucks at the end of a stream, but this is, I do things
sort of differently. We hang out at the end. We're just memeing. No, I know. I know,
trust me, I know like 98% of everybody. We've talked about it plenty of times,
but if anyone is upset by this, which I'm sure there are, it's not, no, I just want to just
give me more money. Please, I'll take some more money, please. That's not the intention.
It's just to keep it efficient. That's all there is to it. Post stream hangout is always
fun, and I want to keep it like that because I never want to get to a point where I'm
sitting here going, oh, let me look at the time. What time is it? Oh, it's been a while,
like three hours in the stream end. I want to keep, I still want to give attention
to like every comment, every message that comes through. I don't just want to blow
through them. I hope you understand, but it sounds like most of you do,
and we're almost done with the bits here. Got a few more. Where are we? Hey, Marsh
Mila, thanks for the two bucks. You should play VR Minecraft. Does it exist? But no,
that's just regular Minecraft, but no, that wouldn't change very much. VR Minecraft,
it's really good unironically, really. That's, maybe, but that's really somewhere in the
bottom of the list. That's like the macaroni and cheese. You get all the macaroni and cheese
out of the pot, and then you're just scraping the bottom of the pan and getting all the
sticked on gross macaroni. I mean, I'm still going to eat it, but it's down there. Hey,
Bingo Sunshine, thanks for five dollars, Bingo Sunshine. Jerma, why didn't you search for the
opening and ending themes from your favorite anime, Full Metal Alchemist, Brotherhood,
and Beat Saber? There's some bangers in there, and you know it. Yeah, I'll play it again. I
like it. I think it's really fun. I'm definitely going to play it again, but thank you,
Bingo Sunshine, and thank you for the suggestion. Hey, Dragon Breath, thanks for the
one dollar Dragon Breath. I made a silly video last night of you in VR. It's not long,
it doesn't deafen you at the end. Hey, well, that's good. Let's put it on here.
This is called, that's the cutest Jerma I've ever seen.
I need that link. Hold on, hold on, hold on. That's fucking ridiculous.
I've never seen it in my entire life. There you go. That was great. Thank you.
Thank you, Topac, for the one dollar. These bits, they are. Those are bits. Hey, Skull Girl,
thank you for the 250. Jerma, thanks for playing my JermaCraft map, even though you
suck at it. It was a pleasure, but I just downloaded Beat Saber yesterday, and I jumped
into hard and expert only. I think in like the four hours I've played, I'm doing alright.
Okay, I'm doing okay. I'm doing good enough to pass the exam, but no, that was hilarious.
Thank you. We also, where am I here? I got lost. Thank you, Timmy Tim Tam, for the one
dollar. Damn, the Jerma bucks inflation rate is crazy. Inflation rate? Thank you, Nate,
for the one dollar. Could you say Sega does what Nintendon't? No, but I was a Super Nintendo
fan. I thought the Super Nintendo was king during that era. You got the, I mean, forget
about blast processing from the Sega Genesis. What about the sound quality? The sound system
that was in the SNES? I mean, the Super Nintendo had really good sound and music,
but thank you. Yeah, you're a friend, Quincy. Thanks for the five dollars. Hey, Jerma,
you should check out the Waltz of the Wizard. It's a free VR game. It has a lot of things
to goof around with. I think you'd enjoy it. Waltz of the Wizard? Yeah, I'll play it.
I'll play them all. I will play them all. There was a Dinosaur Island game. It's called
like Island like 359 or something. You have to survive on an island with dinosaurs.
I want to play that. It's too many things to do, but yeah, hell yeah. And then Topac,
thanks for the 250. Tons of people say this daily, but thanks for the awesome streams.
Recently graduated and your streams helped me put me through engineering. No kidding.
Always come back to VODs or otherwise just to chill and hang out. Take care. Get better
soon. Get better soon? Are you talking about the doctor's appointment? Well, the doctor's
appointment is about like an ongoing annoying issue I've had to deal with the last like six
to eight months. Nothing major. It's just for some reason. There's like some weird stuff
that I'm trying to figure out that's not major, but it's just annoying.
And I'm going tomorrow. Let's figure it out. But yeah, thank you so much for the 250.
And I'm happy that you have fun. And that's an honor that I helped in any way
help you get through engineering. That's a smart cookie there. Thank you, Topac.
And CDT, thanks for the 250. If you're worried about losing viewership during
the after stream talk, why not just turn on FaceCam? It's all the people want.
No, I don't care about losing people during the end. It was a question of
the stream going on for, you know, five to eight hours. And then it being late,
and we're just kind of hanging out at the end. And it's like two, three, four,
five a.m. for a lot of people. It's like gets to be 11, 12, one, two a.m. for me.
It's just to streamline the process and make it more efficient. Yeah, the view count drop
at the end of the stream doesn't bother me. I mean, maybe, okay, if I like really,
really, really gave a shit about what my Twitch analytics page looks like,
then I'd be like, oh, my average viewer count, my total average,
I got to get that up. No, that doesn't bother me at all. It bothers me.
But thank you. It's clear that you care, Jeremy. You dropped Kenshi because of like five guys who
didn't like it. No, I'm going to call, I'm going to call Bologna on that one. You go watch that
Kenshi VOD. And you go from the first, the first stream to the second stream. And you
tell me how many resident sleepers, you don't, you don't know how many, how many people were
like do anything. Oh, it was like do anything else. Next, next, anything else. Five guys
at two zeros. It was more than five guys. Burgers and fries. Some people only know you as a Kenshi
streamer. Yeah. Some people came to that stream and then never came to another one again.
I'm just the Kenshi guy. It was maybe like a hundred people repeating the same thing.
Have you guys heard of this Kenshi streamer? Yeah. What's his name? J, Jerma? Jerma985.
No, I don't think I'll be going back though. But thank you to CDT. 250. Clueless sniper.
Thanks for the $1. Have you thought about playing Skyrim VR? All like the new games,
all like the games that came out and then gave themselves VR after the fact,
I'm not really interested in yet. I'd like to play the games that are VR from the ground up
that were made only to be played in VR. And then we can do like Doom in VR,
Skyrim in VR. But I'd rather do the actual VR true experiences first. I don't really have
an interest in playing Skyrim. So I don't know if putting my head inside of my character's face
is enough to make me want to play it, but probably eventually. And CDT, thanks a dollar.
Also, where is Autos Adventure 3? That's why you moved to Vegas, right?
Autos Adventure 3 is every day. We have an adventure every day.
And then Nate dropped this photo of a PlayStation Super Nintendo. Thank you for the
$1 Nate. Yeah, this is Sony and Nintendo worked together for a long time. And then
there was an issue, right? That made them split off and then Sony ended up doing their own thing.
Where is, where is, where is? There's a penis in that picture. Don't fucking tell me that.
No, there's not. Thank you for that photo. And here come the credits. Thank you to all
the new subs, but only the old ones. You'll be scrolling up here in just a moment. The
controller looks like the NES controller. Yeah, it does. You're setting sus for Wednesday. Yes,
you are. Wednesday between 3 and 4 PM Pacific. I'll see you guys again with more VR and we'll
do the same thing. Maybe we'll do another like two or three days on a row of VR.
I don't want to overdo it though. I feel like four or five VR streams in a row
might be worth taking a break. And instead of doing like three, four to five hour streams
in a row, do like, you know, something else. Cause I do have plenty of other things to do,
but we will definitely be back on Wednesday with more VR. I'm not going to be the VR
streamer. I have, yeah, I got space channel five part one. I've got sea man. We've got a
couple of dream cat. I got a ton of PlayStation two. There's like some new games that came out
as well. It might be worth playing far cry new Dawn for a stream just to fuck around
it and have some fun. Who knows? Fix the webcam setup for Wednesday for a better angle. See,
the issue with a better angle is because I tried to get it as wide as I could for the room,
I'm always going to be moving around and I can't see in real time like where I am.
So I'm always probably going to be in, cause look, sometimes I was just in the corner
just sitting there staring at the wall and I didn't even know that I was over there.
So I tried to get like as good of a wide angle of me standing. Maybe I'll try to
get a little better for next time. Maybe I'll add, maybe I'll make it bigger and try to make
it like, I don't think I can make the camera wider. Put cameras everywhere.
What was the percentage of time that I was looking at the webcam versus looking over
in a corner? Was it more than 50% of the time that I wasn't actually standing straight
at the camera? Your back was turned a lot. 80% you were off screen. You were halfway off the screen.
Well also when I go down too, you frequently ended up on the side of the room.
I spent a lot of time on the floor. Yeah, I did. Do you ever watch your own VOD to see
these things? No, I mean, not necessarily. I'll go back and just see what it looks like.
Got a tracking camera. During bartender sim you were half off the screen most of the time.
You almost hit your door at least eight times.
At one point you were right in our face and kept bumping into the mic.
Pro, hold on, I'm gonna see this. Somebody's linked a clip. Yeah, I am. Just like over in
the corner. This is so stupid. It's just like, it's just my room.
Oh, that's so funny. I wouldn't want to be in that room.
You were fucking dangerous in there. But thank you all. I'll see you guys on Wednesday.
We had uh two more bits come in right at the end here. Nate for two bucks.
Nintendo betrayed Sony by going to the rival Philips. Yeah, until Philips CDI came out and it
was a it was abysmal. But thank you. Thank you Commando for the two bucks. Next time in
the laser sword game you play do uh hadway what is love please. Song suits you. We'll
get a playlist. And then topac right at the very end. One dollar. Say Bible Thump. Why Bible
Thump? Mic abuse. Hold on, I want to see this. You just don't know. You have no idea.
That could be a microphone or that could be a wall. That could be a window shade.
All right, I'll see you guys on Wednesday. Have a great rest of your night.
Take care guys. See you very soon.