Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
And tonight, gonna be playing as the Heavy with the Tomislav the Sandvich and the Killing Gloves of Boxing.
And guys, I've done something I haven't done in a very long time. I've stayed up for over 24 hours for a gaming session.
I'm a little bit delirious right now. I haven't done this since I was in college.
And it's kind of hard to talk into the mic to be very, very honest with you. It's hard for me to form words.
I feel like I've been hit in the head by a sausage or something.
But I want to make this video because I want to talk about this very important topic.
And it is being excited for a game again.
Now, in the comments section before I get into this video, I want you to leave me a comment about the last game that you were this excited for where you were to stay up for over 24 hours.
This game for me, that game for me is Diablo III.
So Diablo III came out and me, Shibby, Star, MLC Stealth, Burger Boy, and Boo's been in the calls with us.
But we have all been playing this game pretty much nonstop since its release.
And maybe this is the endorphins talking right now because I haven't slept or anything.
But yeah, I feel like a million bucks.
Something about those long gaming sessions where you get with a group of friends.
You all are having a great time, all on a call, all or even if you're at somebody's house.
Back in the day when I was in college, I would be in a dormitory with seven or six or seven other guys.
And we'd all be playing a game and we could all yell at each other.
We could all, you know, trash talk, have fun because that's what it's all about.
So these videos that I've been recording off and on, I figured out a potential series to do with Diablo III.
But I'm not going to really tell you yet because it's kind of in the works.
But it's going to be very, very interesting if it goes through.
You might see a video tomorrow or the next day about some of our travels in Diablo III.
Me, Shibby, Star, and Brett, MLC Stealth.
So keep on the eye out. Keep your eye out for that.
And I have got a couple of PMs of people wondering if I'm going to do certain things with the server and stuff like that.
But Team Fortress 2 has kind of been on the back burner at least the last 48 hours
because I've just been having a grand old time in Diablo III.
And just touching back again on long sessions and being really psyched for a game that finally comes out.
You've been waiting for so long when it finally launches.
The midnight release of a game is a really awesome event.
If you have never been to one of those before, please go.
Try and get yourself to one of them.
If you're not old enough, if you're kind of young, you might have to wait a few years to be allowed to go to those
or to get some more freedom so you can stay up a little later.
But they are so cool because you just walk into the front door,
whether it's, you know, you go to your GameStop or Walmart or wherever is having this midnight release.
And it's just everybody collectively there for the same reason.
It's the same thing. It's almost like going to a mini gaming convention.
It's very, very odd. You walk in the front door and there's people that are just like,
Oh my God, everyone's talking about the game.
Everyone's talking about what the story is going to happen.
Who's going to do this? What's going to do that?
And it really is interesting. It's really a lot of fun.
And it gets you right into the zone, makes you go right into game mode.
And I've been in that mode for, like I said, exactly 48 hours.
And I want to touch upon the gameplay.
Did you see what was just going on right there? I thought that was hysterical.
I was just unloading my minigun on that sentry and it wouldn't go down.
And I was hoping that at some point that engineer was going to run out of metal.
And somebody came up behind me. We were like crossing the streams,
Ghostbuster style, trying to take out that sentry.
And finally he picked it up, which was a move that was going to end in his demise.
And it actually did. But I thought that was hysterical.
I'm just holding the mouse button down, going like, how much metal does this dude have?
But the next game that I plan on doing something like this for,
I don't even know if it's going to happen.
You can never plan these out. You can never plan out these long gaming sessions
that end in tireless nights where you stay up all night.
But probably, probably Grand Theft Auto V.
That might be the next 24 to 48 hour game session where I inhale coffee for three days.
But that's probably the only one I can think of that would be next.
Other than that, nothing I can really think of off the top of my head.
But there will always be another one.
There's always going to be that new game coming out.
There's always going to be that new amazing title that you're waiting for.
But to be totally honest, Diablo III and the Diablo franchise
has a very, very big stake in my heart because it's my childhood.
When I heard that Diablo III was going to have a sequel, I almost estabricated.
You know, it was ridiculous. I freaked out.
And it's because Diablo I and II I played when I was a young teenager.
And it's like seeing your childhood come back to life.
And it's amazing with these things.
And I say the same thing about the Neverhood with the Doug to Naples game.
I just wish they would be something else.
And you always reach for something. You always reach for more.
And you hope, God, maybe one day they'll bring that series back to life.
And I'm sure a lot of you guys share the same passion that I do
for gaming and video game culture in general.
So it can be a real amazing day when you finally sit down with that game.
And Diablo is that game for me.
This video is very, very ranty.
And I do apologize for that.
But like I said, my brain is like scrambled eggs right now.
But before this video ends, just the final thought here is,
like I said in the very beginning,
shoot me some comments and give me some of your experiences
with your longtime franchises you want to see revived
or some of your crazy gaming sessions.
Because we are in this all together as a community.
And Otto is about to...
Get away from those wires.
He's like biting the wires from my computer.
I'm going to break this computer. Get out of here.
So that is going to wrap up this particular video, guys.
Thank you all so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it.
And I'll catch you guys all next time.
I've got to get some sleep.
So take care, everybody.