I made it. I made it. I made it. I made it. I'm here. I made it. I just had to pee. I was here.
I just peed. You didn't. I did. I don't know, those have been making me real irritated lately.
Like just today. Only today. Usually I like, I like don't give a shit at all about that. And it's
like, okay, it's funny. It's the rumor that that person has driven by here like 12 times in the
last like six minutes. And after 10 is when you start to be like, all right, like, can
can you just get to where you're going? It's what is your destination at this point?
It's at this point, I'm convinced that you're on an AI path. And like, what do I need to go out there
and like activate the cutscene or something? So am I missing my cue? Anyway, yes, yes, yes.
Anyways, today we are going to do something that I've been talking about for a while.
We're going to do the community activities. Dot to dots. Spot the differences. Where's Waldo?
Except it's me. Funny stories that the community has written. And then so, right. Now I have a lot
of these. There are, I believe, 45 dot to dot activities. I think there are 10. Where's Waldo's?
I think there are 10 spot the difference activities. And there are about two to three
hundred stories and jokes. So I don't think we're going to be able to get through all of those
today because I have to, I have to get on an airplane. This is the last stream you're going
to see from me until the carnival. This is going to be just a chill, relaxing, hey everybody, let's
let's just chill like yesterday. This is the last time you're going to see me until it turns on
and you're at the carnival. So without further ado, let me make sure I look okay.
Is he saying goodbye? I'm saying goodbye for like four days. It's not really not even that big of a
deal considering, like guys, I've taken, I've taken like four or five days off in a row
just like randomly before. So I'm acting like, oh it's the last time you're going to see me in four
days. I took like a full week off like two months ago. What am I talking about? It's all good.
Without further ado, ladies and gentlemen, I'd like to introduce to you
first segment of our stream this afternoon. Let me, let me actually get on camera for the first
time in a long time and I actually like took a shower today. So, hey, he looks fresh. Oh,
wait, wait, wait. I should get a haircut pretty recently. So let's get a greasy forehead. I have
oily combination skin. So good. Yeah. You and my doctor have something in common. You both know
that. Great. Cool. Oh, it's, it's Otto. Everybody. Okay. Let me tell you something. Everybody that
has a dog. If you do not over the course of your life, get a mug with your dog on it. I mean,
are you, are you really like a true dog owner? I'm not sure. Look at this shit. This is the first
one we're going to do. There are a lot of these. So if you don't know how a dot to dot works,
what could this be? Yeah, I know. A dot to dot is you have to start at one with your finger on the,
with the pencil, right? And you got to go, for instance, I'm not going to be zoomed in for these
because that's cheating. So you go one, two to three to four to five. You guys know how to do
this. It's very self-explanatory. I've got a, I've got an application here that is a really,
really neat thing. I can draw all over the screen. I can draw whatever I want. See what I mean?
And this is not on my computer. This is, this is a virtual machine. This is a virtual painting
machine. I can, I can, I can clear it. I can save it. It's pretty good technology.
I fucked it up. No, I just told you that I have a virtual painting technology thing.
I could go like this. He ruined it. You went, what'd you say? Microsoft paint? No,
this isn't Microsoft paint. I don't remember what this application is called, but it's actually,
yes, I do. I only know what this thing is called because of it has this name. I believe this
application is called Epic Pen. I think that is, that's actually what this is called. All right,
so let's get started. I think many people have trickled in now. People know this is going on.
It's a smart board. No, it's an Epic Pen. So let's go with the pencil and we already know
what this one is. I mean, come on, give me a break. See, I'm going to fuck these up.
That's be aware of that. I will screw at least half of these up. A little down here. One, two,
three, four, five, six, seven. Ooh, it's getting tricky down here. Here comes a jump scare.
Okay. Seven, eight, nine, 10. I got colors here. I can change colors. What color is,
wait, I have to change. What color is fireman's face? Fire. Oh, it's yellow. I fucked it all up
already. Clear it. Six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16. Whoa, it's getting weird.
It's going in a circle. 22, 23. Don't go that way. Don't go that way. 24, 25, 20. Whoa, whoa,
is it a trick? No, it's not a trick. This is the fire. This is the fire. Right. Okay. This is the
fire. That was, that was cool. All right. Cool. Nice work. Six, seven, 28, 29, 30.
And we go up where it gives the flame. 31, 32, 33, 34, 35. All the way up here. Here. This is
pretty good. Two, and wrap it across to 53. First one is done. Look at how happy he looks.
Very, very good. That one was easy. Let me tell you. Let me tell you. Oh, let me tell you.
Jerma starts at half of his sentences, but let me tell you. Let me tell you something. Let me tell
you. Somebody, some of you guys decided to, I guess, be funny. And there were a bunch of
these in here that were just like triangles, just like one, two, three, and like a square.
Like that, that ain't, that ain't going to show up on stream. That's it. There's the first one.
That's fireman. While I do this, I'm going to put on some stories. Just, I want to, we've got to
get the first one done. I got to show you how it works. So I'm going to put on some stories now.
These are the stories that people have written. And yes, when I say I'm putting on the stories,
I'm literally, I'm literally going to have text to speech save them too,
because I've got to concentrate on this shit. Here we go. I was walking down the street the other day
and noticed something weird on the sidewalk. Something weird on the side. It looked like
nothing I had ever seen before. As I got closer, I could feel something emitting from it.
I grabbed the handle and pulled as hard as I could and a burnt crisp of a man fell out.
Thank you. Good lady. He said, I have been locked inside that walk in oven for days.
He then face planted so hard that he turned to dust and disappeared.
Okay. I got to pay attention. I haven't seen him since. Elizabeth L from Stockholm, Sweden,
closing square bracket. I saw German at a grocery store in Boston yesterday.
I told him how cool it was to meet him in person, but I didn't want to be a douche and bother him
and ask him for photos or anything. Oh, he said, oh, like you're doing now. Right.
Closing square bracket. Back when army of two first came out, me and my college roommates,
sweetmates were all way too into halo three to really care. I didn't even think army of two was
on my radar in 2008. My college sweetmates would sneak into my room while I wasn't there and play
halo three without my permission on my Xbox. But more importantly, they would look at my DVD
collection. I had like 215 DVDs in alphabetical order and they would pay thanks for the five
dollars where they would move to random titles in different places and see how long it would take
me to notice. Yeah, I know that says a lot more about me than it does about them, but I could tell
every time that was the joke. I would just scan briefly over my DVDs every day and see if they
had taken one was usually the issue wasn't I wasn't checking to see if they put them out of order.
I was checking because they would turn up missing. This is your only opportunity you're ever going
to hear and find someone across the hallway who borrowed one without asking. And what do you know?
The DVD is missing from inside of its jewel case. Where did it go? No one knows. Oh, I found it.
It's in two pieces now. No, I'm not still angry about that. Is this part is this still closing
square bracket? No closing square bracket. There was once a man at an airport without a passport.
He was making a sound like a snort unable to retort. Good. As a last resort, he tried to act
like an athlete for a sport. He landed in a court which to him was like a resort. Taking public
transport, he went to a port. For his to port his height was listed which by all accounts was short.
Closing square bracket. One time at a friend's house I was hungry and looted his pan. How do
you talk? How do you speak with a TTS stream? I can't talk. This person's streaming for me.
Bear in mind two factors. This the robot is streaming for me. I can't even talk to you guys.
Hey, what's up? One time at a friend's house I was hungry and looted his pantry for something to eat.
I found a jar of what I had assumed to be homeless and attempted to open it. Oh,
you never do. Bear in mind two factors. I had a brand new shirt on and the lid on the jar still
had the sealing plastic on it. I used my shirt as a way to get extra grip against the protest
of my friends. One of which says you're going to spill the oil on the top all over your new shirt
to which I replied no the plastic is still on it. It's okay. Immediately after this the lid slid off
and I spilled oil all over my shirt. My next genius plan was to eat an entire spoonful of
the hummus which I did. That's not that bad. Only after realizing that the hummus in my mouth was
possibly the worst thing I have ever tasted I finally realized that the substance in the jar
was in fact raw garb and soybean paste. What? I ran to the sink and attempted to spit out the
glob now forming into a paste in my mouth only to realize to my horror that the paste had stuck to
every inch of my mouth between my teeth, under my tongue, and on the ridges on the roof of my mouth.
In desperation I attempted to turn the sink on to wash my mouth out and pulled up on what I
believed to be the sink's handle only for the handle to come off. What? Where are you? Is this
a home alone house? It was a soap dispenser. Hold on, I gotta turn these off. Are you sure?
Was like Macaulay Calkin fucking walking around? Did you like in your peripheral was like a little
kid running up the stairs going like oh and like having paint cans behind him? Okay, hold on,
I need to say I need a break from I gotta take a break here because I only did one of these.
I can't pay attention. It's been like two minutes. Has it? It has been like 15. It's been 16 minutes.
All right, well there's fireman. There's another fireman. Looks good. Very cool. That one's that
one's that was not that was less interpretation. That's more of like a true emo right there.
Looks good. Oh, I don't want to do that. Spy red. All right, I'm dubbed. Here comes another one.
I have to do these like individually guys. This is called Cheerio land. Wait, what happened to my
audio? There is a land called Cheerio land populated entirely by Cheerios. All of the
different Cheerios live in a caste system with the Honey Nut Cheerios in the leader class,
the Chocolate Cheerios acting as the Lords and Nobles, the Frosted Cheerios being the somewhat
well-off peasants and the normal Cheerios as the poor and destitute. One day, a normal Cheerio
fell in love with a Honey Nut Cheerio, but the only way he could see her was if he eventually
became a Honey Nut Cheerio himself. Okay. He goes to the Cheerio wizard who is the only person
capable of upgrading Cheerios to the next level. All right. After working hard for years under the
supervision of the Cheerio wizard, he is eventually upgraded to a Frosted Cheerio, a Chocolate Cheerio
and finally becomes a Honey Nut Cheerio. He meets the love of his life at last and together
they celebrate by going to a nearby fair. After a few hours, they get thirsty and they go to get
some fruit punch. However, they had to wait in a long line for lemonade because there was no punch
line. What? I fucked that whole thing up, didn't I? Hold on. There's no punch line. You don't write
a whole story like that, man. I don't have a punch line. Oh, because I went the other way, right?
Sorry. I was listening to the Cheerio, like the hierarchy system. I was having trouble paying
attention. Here we go. 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50. It's down here. What's going on here?
So we go 50. Oh, these are the sneakers. I see. Okay. You got me on this one. Hey, you got me.
Nice work. 59, 7, there it is. Another fireman. He wears sneakers? Oh, well, no, well, these things.
His legs. Story time. Now. Hold on. We got plenty of time, so don't worry. Story. Now. Story. Now.
Story. Now. All right. Here, I'll give you two stories in a row. Okay. How's that sound?
Hopefully these hopefully these were vetted. Okay. Two stories back to back. Next image.
There used to be a boy who always jumped over the fence. His father told him not to jump over
the fence because every time he jumped over the fence, he broke a little bit of it. Not to say
that he was worried about his son, but the boy didn't listen and still jumped over and over.
Displeased and worried, the father broke the fence down and build a gate on the place where
once the fence was standing. Yet the boy still jumped over the gate even though he could easily
open it. So, the father left the gate open all the time and all kind of strangers traveled
trough the open gate and thanked the father for the easy passage and the father wondered,
did the boy did that on purpose? In the evening, he asked his son why he jumped over the fence
and gate and the son replied with a very simple response. I jumped over the fence to prove myself
that I'm not 5'3 and actually big enough to jump over. Suddenly the father jumped up and started
to make painful noises and he was not able to control his flatulence anymore while shouting at
his son, son I pay for your twitch prime so you better support that streamer! Exclamation mark!
And then something, tell me a sad story. Where is the joy in the life that you have lived?
And then he began to play a recording. He started with me, then it was Paul, and then it was myself.
It was great. And then it was all of us. It made me think, why is that so tragic? And I thought,
well, if they want you to find joy in death, we can do that. But we could not find joy in what we did.
And we didn't. Why didn't we find happiness in the moment? Then I remember going to the doctor
and talking to a psychiatrist. This doctor comes in and says, this is the most beautiful thing I've
ever seen. I said, it's just sad. She said, there is nothing beautiful about what you're saying.
And then she said, it's just something that must be given. It has to be given willingly.
What the fuck is this story? It was so difficult to find that. She talked to me for three hours and
told me that if you don't choose the path of joy, death won't have any meaning for you.
And then she said, you'll be happy. You have always loved life the way it's meant to be lived
and to come to terms with death and what it is. That's that one. All right. Nice. All right. It's
my turn to stream now. Thank you. We go back and forth here. So this is, it looks like German Venus.
I mean, no, that's too bad. We're sharing time here. This is definitely German Venus. I don't
know what I did wrong with the eye though. I think I fucked up the eye. The yellow wasn't
coming out that well. This is the mouth. It was 60. 60's over here. I might have to do smaller,
a little smaller on the inside here. Use white? How do I use white on a white background?
That's just what my eye looks like. My eye doesn't look like that. 61. We might have to go,
I might have to go a tier lower for this. Yeah, we'll go, we'll go on a tier lower.
A finer line here. 62. 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. We're 69 in here. 69, 70. This looks fucked up.
73, 74, 75, 76, 77, 78, 79, 80. It's coming together all the way up.
77, 88. All right. That actually doesn't look that bad. That looks pretty good.
89. It was 90. Straight up. And then this is the nose. This is going to be complicated up here.
100 and plus. 100 plus. Get a story. We'll get two new stories when I do a new, a new game board,
okay? 90, wait a minute. 90, 91, 92, 93. How's that, that doesn't work, does it? Do I have to
go like around? Like this, this? Cross the lines. Do I have to cross it? I thought you don't cross
the streams in a dot to dot. I get, oh wait, it's making the nostril. What does it make,
what's it making? I don't think that worked. I have to keep, I have to finish it. Hold on.
One, two, three. All the way around. Down here and then pull it back up here. 18, 19, 120,
121, 5, 26, 27. That's 20. All the way around. It's another circle. 30, 31, 32. All the way around
here. Where's 35? 36, 37, 38, 39, 40. Hold on. Let's clean it up a little bit. Maybe get the,
let me get a little bit bigger. Let me see if I can get in here and just like clean it up.
This doesn't look right to me. It's, that's supposed to be the nose and I, did I go backwards?
There it is. Let me see if I go like this. Yeah, no, no, it works. Very good. Hey, what do you say
we get a couple more stories? You guys like those? That was German Venus. Don't curve lines. Well,
I didn't look, see? Like I, I wasn't like curving. I was following it up here. I mean, you have to
curve. Otherwise, what are you gonna, I wouldn't curve them. All right, let's get another story on
here. Let's see. I'll do three this time. I just like saw the, you guys, I literally, okay,
these ones are long. This is a long ass story. The next two are like long ass stories. I don't,
I don't know. All I saw was the last word here. This might be a spoiler for Infinity War. Okay,
so just, if you haven't seen Infinity War, you're gonna have to leave. You're gonna have to leave
now. This might be an Infinity War Marvel spoiler. I just saw a word. Or just hurry up and go watch
the movie now. Just go watch one of those YouTube videos where they explain the whole story in like
four minutes. That's how long it's going to take to get there. All right, we'll do that one too.
Okay, here we go. Next. Next, please. No, I want to introduce the next one. I'm not just,
we're not gonna have to get blown out by the other streamer who's like more popular than I am. That's
the problem. The TTS guy is more popular than me right now and it's, I'm not okay with that.
I'm having trouble with that. Okay, so this one. All right, yeah, well, I'll put on the popular guy.
Hey guys, I had the circus come to my town last week and I had a lot of fun. Cool. The main
attraction was called the Short Streamer and my goodness, I never laughed so hard. The crowd kept
chanting ClayTF2 at him and he was very angry. I felt so bad for him, I bought him a drive.
Pepper after the show and he said that it was the nicest thing anyone ever did for him and I felt
so good about myself. About the month later, the Short Streamer wrote to me saying he got into a
fight with someone named Grill Mastic's BBQ and needed bits for the hospital bill. I wrote back
and said I couldn't help him but I wished him luck. The next week, someone who looked like he was
made of glue and wearing a cape stood outside of my door. I had to flee the state because I
feared for my life and hitched a balloon ride to Las Vegas. Turns out the Short Streamer was also
on this balloon with me and we had an epic fight which ended with me throwing him off over the
desert. I don't know where the Short Streamer or the glue man are but if you see anyone who looks
like that please report him to the authorities. Closing square bracket. Lights began to shine
through the vent grate. A faint light that could remind anyone of a comfy Boston basement.
Tim began to lightly step across the ventilation tunnel. His tired legs skittery on the steel as
he almost escaped. Freedom at last, Tim thought. Years of living in the vent of Jerma's cave,
he was finally in the home stretch. As he approached the vent, he could hear the faint
streamer in the chasms below. He couldn't entirely make him out but he could hear something about
dieting. It didn't matter to him. All that mattered was freedom from the dwarven dungeon.
His eyes peered through the vent and across the room he found his destination. The door on the
other side of the room. That must be it, he thought. Once he would be able to make it across, he would
most likely find the hallways of the gamer king he was always told about. It would lead him to
the world of outside. He couldn't dream of success yet. He still needed to fly across the chaotic pit.
The human dwarf hybrid resided. Tim could even see his followers on one of the monitors,
spamming a subtraction by two for some reason. Tim wasted no time. He flew through the vent
and onto the nearest surface he could find. He began to shake as this was the final moment
where it all mattered. Freedom from years of torment of living in Jerma's gamer cave.
No more. Snap. Closing square bracket. So, one day a church was looking for a replacement.
What's everybody mind? What did I do? Oh, the story. It's the story. Okay, I was like,
what happened? I'm just like drawing. What did I do? Oh, that was the word. I know it was in the
story. I don't know. I'm just a fucking idiot. Here it goes. Here comes the next story.
So, one day a church was looking for a replacement for the guy they had to climb the tower every
hour and ring the huge church bell. None of applicants were strong enough to do it. Well,
finally one day a man with no arms came up to apply for the job. The priest said,
but how can you ring it with no arms? And the man took a few steps back and ran head first
into the bell, getting it to ring. He got the job. He did his job well and was on time every hour.
Until one day after so many blows to the head, when he reared back and ran, he missed and went
straight off the tower. As people started to gather around him on the ground, frantic, a woman asked
the man beside her, does anyone know who this is? The man replied, I don't know, but his face rings
a bell. What? What did I do? I fucked up something over here. What did I do over here? What happened
over here? No, I did this right. Oh, oh, oh, I know this is correct. This is actually correct.
This is, this is an earbud. Wow. That's detailed. All right. Where's 51? 51. I don't see 51.
50, 51. Where's 51? Did everybody see 51? I see 52, 51. There it is. Well, those are two excellent
stories. Excellent stories, I guess. 5, 56. Am I wearing a monocle? 58. That was three stories.
59, 60. Okay. 61, 62, 63, 64, 67, 68, 69, 70. Oh, fuck. I screwed it up. No, I didn't. 71, 72,
3. Up here, 74, 75, 76, 79. Is this my nose? 80, 81. Oh my god. 82, 83. I know what this is.
I know what this is. This is the, that thing. I already know it. I was wondering why this looks
so fucked up. 87, 88, 89, 90, 82. Look at how tight these are. 93. Where's 94? There's 84,
93. Oh, it's right here. 4, 95, 100, 101, 102, 103. Oh, it's coming together. I can see it.
104, 107. It's right in the middle here. 8, 10. This is fucking scary. It was 12. Right below.
12. Back up to 13. Where is the dot in 18? 18. Down. 120, 121. I look a fucking hundred years old.
125, 126, 127, 128. That's wrong? What do you mean that's wrong? No, it's not. I missed 120. No,
I didn't, did I? Oh, fuck. I can't do that. Wait, let me just see where they are. Okay. No, I'm using
epic pen. Okay. That's not, what do you mean cheating? Everyone just told me to zoom in.
All right. 117, 118, 119, 120. I got 120 last time.
22, 123, 4. Oh, that's fucking 5. 125. Is that it right there? Is that 125? I think so, right?
Right, okay. Right there. 126, 127, 128.
Those of you that are wondering if this just looks fucking horrible,
you always have to remember, this is, this image looks worse than this. The actual source image
looks worse than this. So, give me a break here. This is not about bad line work. You want us looking
at your ear the whole time? Fine, I'll sit back like this. Yeah, that'll be, I complained about
this already. That's the second image when you type in germa, 985 into Google. Thanks, guys.
Really looking forward to like getting that fucking TV show. 33, 34. Okay, then this goes
up and around. Big eyebrow. 40, 41, 42, 43. Is my like skin melting? 45, 46, 47, 48, 49,
50, 51, 54, 67, 58, 59, 160, 161. It's done. There you are. Oh, also, what I, I forgot to do is,
I need a, I just need a white screen. Hold on. Because after I'm done, I want to just put them
on a white screen. I think I should be able to do that with just, I just need a white, hold on.
Let me turn this off for a second. I need to find it. Where is it? No, not this, this.
Give me one second. I need to make like a new window. Yeah, that's better. Okay. Here we go.
Just a pure white screen. No, I don't want a 24-hour video of a white screen. Why the
fuck does that exist? I just want a white background. 24 hours of white screen. 10 hours
of incredible white screen. I just want a fucking wallpaper. Okay, that's, that's good. Why? All
right. So, uh, that's good. I'm just going to go like this and I can hide it. So here we go.
You ready? Are you ready to see? Here is what we're looking at now. I think it actually looks
pretty good. Good Lord, the tabs. Welcome to the rest of your life on this string. You look like
Ron Swanson. No, there we go. I can see that. All right, let's keep going. Let's get a couple
of stories. Okay. We'll do three stories this time. This is just a warm up guys.
Just wait till we get to the where's wall though. Using ad block plus instead of uBlock origin.
I don't fucking know. Guys, I only use ad block for the websites that take over your whole computer.
You know what I'm saying? I only use ad block for the websites that have a whole like, they go like
this. You open up the webpage and then you see a banner ad and you're like, okay, whatever. I don't
care. And then that banner ad scrolls down with you and takes over the whole page. It's another page
on top of the page. I don't know why people think that's a good idea. It is the fucking dumbest
thing I've ever seen in my entire life. It's like, it's like, if you went to like CVS, right? You
were walking into CVS and somebody was just standing in front of you screaming in your face
and they're going like this and they're getting in your fucking way and blocking you and screaming
in your face. It's like, look, I just want to go into the CVS. Okay. I don't care. You stand over
there and you scream. Okay. Stand to the side of the door and fucking yell in my face, like from
like eight feet away. Hey, hey. All right. That guy's, I gotta get past that guy. Don't put it
right here. Don't make me move and you're just on my fucking body. Stand like over there and scream
at me while I'm going into the CVS. If I see a website that does that, it immediately goes on
my shit list. Why do I use a CVS as a store example every time? Because it's CVS every 15 feet.
There's a CVS literally every fucking like 10 feet in America. Show us your search history.
No, I'm not going to show you my fucking search history. Do you know why that is?
It has nothing to do with- Oh, wait a minute. We might see his pornography. No, like I don't
want- I got like bank information in here. Oh, let me hit P. No, there's all my- that's all my bank
accounts. Oh, that's funny. You better got him. He's scared. I don't- I don't want you to know
what I- like I may have typed in like a restaurant that's down the street. Like, oh, whoops.
No, you ain't getting shit. Uh-uh. That ain't fucking happening. This is all you get. All you
get, you can just imagine what all those tabs are. Show us every tab. Yeah, you can just imagine
what's on there, huh? In fact, I'll show you the next one. All right, let's go. All right,
I got stories to tell. Bear guards? What the fuck is this one? This is so long. Oh my god. Okay,
we're just doing two because this one is like three- this one's like three minutes long at least.
Hey, you guys relaxed yet? Here we go. Don't you wish you could see those fucking tabs? Man,
I wish we could see those fucking tabs. I'll zoom in for this one because I can- I can- it can fit.
See? The man stands in a room of glass. In front of him is a table with a bowl. Inside the bowl
is a berry. Surrounding the room people scream and shout. Some yell, eat the berry. While others
yell, don't eat the berry. It's poisoned. The man looks around the room and sees the berry.
He places a fork under the berry and chews on it. The man places another fork under the berry and
chews again. At this point, the man realizes he has eaten poison, thus giving a death sentence
to anyone trying to make it through the maze. What? He runs through the maze until he is
outside the cave surrounded by many poisonous berries. Suddenly, the man collapses on his back,
screaming. At this point, all eyes are on the man. His eyes are full of poison and he wants to escape.
However, he is surrounded by hundreds of berry hunters. Some of them fight, some just sit there,
waiting the turn to fight. I can't do this. Eventually, the man breaks free and takes off.
The man takes off with all of the other bears and they run after him, as all the berry hunters turn
towards the man and laugh at how pathetic he is. The man tries to flee, but before he can do so,
the bear guards arrive and shackle him. They take him back to the room he was in originally and
place another berry down on the table. They then leave, and the cycle starts again. Written by
and talked to transformer from yahoo california i had a dream that there was a four person swimming
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa hold on a second there slow down
there's a rat uh the bear guards the bear the poison coming out of his eyes i think it's my
favorite it's a giant rat that's correct i think i can just go like this and you guys should be
able just to see woohoo look at that i need to like finish it though don't i see that's cute
very nice thank you now let's zoom this back out and do the next one clear it and i'm gonna
bucket the next story is coming don't worry california closing square bracket i had a dream
that there was a four person swimming pool battle royale where you eliminate people by either
beating them unconscious in the pool or knocking them out of the pool after numerous failures
against children i knew that i needed to step up my game i put on a snorkel and immediately became
a god at the game soon enough i made it to the big leagues my competition was big geo with
spider-man powers and a lime with spider-man powers the first of three matches begun and i got
destroyed without my snorkel geo subdued me while geacho bashed my rib cage in i put on nose and eye
goggles after the round and i made a full rebound geo and the lime watched in horror from the ceiling
as i pummeled geocchio i snatched the lime from the ceiling and drowned him eliminating him geo
was a different story approaching him was too risky to do head-on while i was catching my breath
he managed to pin my arm to the poolside i began to panic but opportunity struck the lime's dead
body floated near me and as geo delivered another web shot i threw the lime at geo the collision
i'm not gonna spend time on this one okay once again this is not a mystery i was able to defeat
geos this is not a fucking mystery after this match everyone forfeit except for me due to rain
and i won seven thousand dollars wait how do you go from 106 to 107 here 106 107 108 109 what 126
where's 127 there's 120 it's like in here somewhere what the fuck is happening hold on
go back what the fuck is happening 43 47 all the way up here 57 58 59 60 61 63 64 65 66 67
70 71 72 73 74 75 76 77 78 2 i got like an itchy ass eye 86 87
89 90 91 92 all the way down here through here to 106 and then i have to go all the way across to here
don't connect them well this is dot this is dot the dot connect the dots
holy shit i like stop paying attention wait go back yeah you have to connect the dots 108
109 10 11 12 13 14 15 oh this is an ear stream i forgot i have to lean back
25 26 27 28 up here 45 46 all right this is where i got all fucked up
849 51 52 53 55 is right here is it right next to it 7
65 66 67 68 69 what is this is this my mouth 70 71 72 73 74
75 76 77 is that correct that's a dab yeah that's maybe the yo-yo that yeah that's that's a
well that's that there it is there's the dab that's pretty good okay we gotta get a couple
more stories on here some i don't know how some of you guys come up with this shit
okay here's this one uh this is a long one here okay let's get these on next dot to dot image is
let's clear it i do have blue you're right i got blue what do you mean you're right you know what
he said that i did all right let's go start one you're gonna play what's going on six flags is
the best amusement park it is a park for fun and i think it is pretty amazing when we visited our
park had a really nice view from the park you can see the entire park at your own pace for five
dollars this is a fun cheap ride for eight dollars you'll get a ride or two that takes you
through the whole park including a little fun boat ride down the park's pirate ship
oh that's fun so you get your ride some food and then you go back down in the boat and ride
through the fun ride the ride includes the ride itself with the boat fun ride a few drinks and
some souvenirs it is a great place to hang out with your friends and a great place to visit during
the day all in all this place is well worth the seven dollars they have tons of rides i've been
looking forward to some of our friends coming there including the great wall of china the three
kings king kong the world's biggest monkey rides all the giant bats closing square bracket for as
long as i can remember i've always had a fascination with birds i always like to spot them with big
binoculars i borrowed from my parents and write them down in my big blue bird book i would write
things like new blue feathered sparrow making a nest in the big oak tree and such i would even
put photographs next to it the description sometimes so anyway it's quite natural then
that when i saw a small redheaded woodpecker on the sidewalk i was curious woodpeckers aren't city
birds in fact i don't think i've ever seen one outside of the woods what was it doing here
was it lost maybe it was hurt sir i sneakily walked up to it preparing to pick it up and take
it home to care for it and release it back into the forest it was just walking across the sidewalk
for some reason not even flying as i came closer though i could make out its details more and more
clearly and they just didn't make sense this all culminated when i was standing only one or two
feet away from the little creature and it turned around and i t spoke who a who a who a ha ha who a
who a who a ha ha who a who a who a ha ha so naturally i took out my flamethrower and torched
that down to the ground i already warned that psychotic little ship never to come within 10
feet of me again after he drilled my previous house to the ground good riddance what did that
i know what it feels like now to have tts on stream you wonder why i don't ever have it on
i could not scream i would not be able to i would just sit there and be like when is it when do i
go in now do i go in now do i say anything now i wouldn't be able to pay attention to anything
there would be something on the screen that i'd need to be reading and i would hear like
who a who a who a who a and then i went to the bird torch to my face and i'd be like what the
fuck is it i can't pay attention i don't know how some people can do that you have to have
lightning focus to have something in the in one of your ears be going like
so yeah guys i went to the supermarket and it was uh wow what an interesting story i'm gonna tell
you uh i got salsa and you just hear that in your ear the whole time i would be like
that's like unstreamable for me i have adhd so let me ask you a question um if you were we're
gonna do something right now because i need to i need to prove this i have to prove something
sometimes you know i'm saying sometimes you just have to prove a point okay so you and i are going
to have a conversation now okay you and me this is you and me this other person is it's not part
of our conversation hey dude uh hey i wanted to go to uh breakfast with you next week you have
you have enough do you have any time next week hey hey hey hey hey hey i was thinking maybe we
could go to look at me look at me uh maybe look at me oh mcdonald's has a good man look at me
breakfast i think that's right look at me you're not looking at why you're not looking at me
yeah no i think hey um one time i shit my pants well i've had the doctor's i shit my pants yesterday
i have a doctor's shit pants i have to go to doctor of appointment tomorrow i shit my pants
yesterday why you're not listening to me they cut stop imagine that happens in real life
stop interrupting the streamer wait no that wasn't supposed to be me this is me talking
this is not me um this is not me talking my pants yesterday i know i heard isn't that funny i shit
my pants i think i'm interrupting the streamer i'm the one on camera oh my you get the idea
we're gonna move on the idea is if somebody's talking in your ear and trying to interrupt your
conversation eventually you're gonna be like i can't hear i cannot talk to this person about
like the mcdonald's breakfast menu who should stream vote now you wait a minute let's call back
here to about 20 minutes ago you cannot tell me that you do not like advertisements that take
over your fucking screen that make a bunch of noise and then tell me that i'm incorrect with this
you cannot say that oh that one's out of the fucking park i knocked that one out
anyways uh let's continue hello so naturally now imagine that's like an ad for the new fucking
2020 ford how quickly are you clicking the x on that screen just saying all right uh let's go
oh i'm having a fucking blast all right let's get a new story and let's do the bird sleep at
all last night why would lying in bed for what seems to be an hour as well as getting a little
unnerved i can't help but return to my computer and used my time watching past vod's of this twitch
streamer i'm very familiar with he's a popular streamer yet unfamiliar to some being he is the
top 1000 streamer but me and him have a sort of history going between this
i met this person a long time ago at a twitch party and we were seemingly getting along i thought
i'm still really upset on what he said to me my name and to my fans that went to his stream
of course the past is the past but somehow his words still affect me to this day i haven't
grilled for a long time mainly through physical issues on my back and hopefully one day i can
return to what i enjoy a lot my therapist is currently helping me through all this and
hopefully with enough exercise and healthy foods i will return streaming again never really hated
you before and after harrington i see you're quite busy with plans becoming a clown in the circus and
chat repeating the words peepee poo poo but really i hope our conflict in the past won't affect our
relationship now for all you remaining griller fans keep up with my twitter for more steamy
updates xbbq grill master x barbecue thank you for that that was a great uh story oop don't
fuck it up speaking of fucking things up this does not look right to me this looks like a
like a spoon or a fork or something did i blow this one already two three four fifty five
six up here 60 all right what is he like going this is not a dab right why did i change the
thickness uh because it's it's easy because sometimes when they get clumped up it's hard
to get them up i do like this one though this is the most difficult arcade game in um at least
in north america i don't know about other countries and continents was everybody blinking what's going
on here i'm seeing a shit little blanks what is what's this what when did i do that did i do that
today when hold on did i sneeze it's something sterva sour let's get back to the activity please
i'm almost done with the uh chicken 69 70 71 72 73 that's it is that it that's it that's it
uh france apparently that's the that's the keyblade version of france somebody said keyblade
and then i said france and i morphed it together for a fucking perfect piece of common
put on background music blank stair streamer no music distracts me i don't like it let's get
another story that was the bird from the arcade game that played excellent excellent okay let's
try this one i'll do two three in a row i'm just scrolling down this there's so many stories
all right we'll grab these two all right that looks good next dot to dot what is it actually
don't remember i know what that is still gonna be fun to do though i was wandering alone in
the woods one day when i came across a little door carved into the stump of an old oak tree
magical stuff okay i knelt down and knocked carefully with one finger hoping not to startle
its inhabitant the little door slowly creaked open and out popped the head of a curious little
creature it asks in a tiny timid voice just a traveler i respond do you mind if i poke my
head inside not at all replies the creature retreating back into its hovel i lay down on
my stomach and open the door and as soon as i stick my head through the opening the gremlin
rips ass all over my face i recoil in disgust and destroy its entire house god i fucking hate
elves the euphoric land of nacho fries is getting an upgrade wait wait this is not
closing square bracket there you go the euphoric land of nacho fries is getting an upgrade
oh an upgrade announced thursday that it's ratcheting up the heat on its new favorite
side dish with two new test items two new items of rattlesnake fries and reaper rush fries are
variants on the much-loved fries that will eat more like a meal however unlike plain old nacho
fries the hilarious names of these seasoned starch sticks tell you absolutely nothing about what
they're so here goes rattlesnake fries are a big basket of fries topped with nacho cheese steak
creamy jalapeno sauce and pickled jalapenos its grim brethren is named after the carolina reaper
pepper these spicy fellas are available as fries and sauce or in a supreme version topped with
nacho cheese seasoned beef reaper rush sauce diced tomatoes and sour cream
the bad news is that for the time being these new additions are only available as test items
the rattlesnake fries and rattlesnake burrito because you can get that pile of toppings
inside a burrito too is only available starting august 16th in columbus ohio the reaper fries
and reaper burrito are only available beginning august 16th in cincinnati ohio all of the items
will stick around until mid september closing square bracket the good news is that taco bell
also announced it's once again extending the stay of nacho fries it's a different one those
will now be available nationwide through mid september enjoy them while you can those two
those are two separate stories okay do rattlesnake fries actually exist or is that just somebody
just throwing up nonsense maybe one maybe two three eighty four i like this one's cute look
at how cute this one is got it there it is that is germa chump uh some would argue the best emote
on the whole platform on this especially germa 985 channel that's cool i've heard the argument
that's the best emote uh on on 985 okay very cool germa rat germa chump let's keep going oh
shit it's i gotta flip it somebody's gonna be getting this tonight owo griller that's me
that's me what will young jeremy be giving himself tonight connect the dots below to find out what it
is worst stream of the year i gotta flip it hold on i gotta flip this one hold on i gotta flip it i
gotta flip it i gotta flip it can i even flip this on stream oh shit i don't think i can flip
this on stream oh yeah i can now i got it now i just flip it how do you flip something in
microsoft fly i got it turn the monitor sideways i got it i got it everything i got it i got it i
got it i got it i got it i do like the mario tennis in the background of this one too
all right let's go this one's gonna be gold uh oh oh i'm using the free version i don't have
the upgraded epic pro pen gold here we go i'm gonna do those two thicker one two three
wait no no no that's it's it's color this is color coded what a cheat you're cheap
what do you mean i'm cheap how am i cheap because i i'm using it for its purpose it's designed
purpose three wait what what did i do one oh it's segmented oh clever actually clever okay
and then the blue is up here one two three four five six seven eight nine it's a rat
okay then down here one two three four five two three i'm not gonna write that i was just gonna
write like game sucks and point to mario tennis but i'm not gonna do that that's adorable thank you
that's fucking beautiful all right can i how quickly can i not bad that was pretty fast wait
wait pretty good i will say all right let's do the next one i get a couple more stories here too
this just kind of freaks me out a little uh here look i just i forgot what this program did and i
got scared that i like did burn in on my monitor all right uh next song is i mean come on it's
gonna be okay next uh story okay wait i'm in the wrong thing i'm in the wrong hold on i'm
okay okay now i'm in stories here we go here comes another one everybody loves to just like
make me like a little elf like a little goblin i would not be a goblin okay i would be let me i'm
just gonna give you a this is real this is real life this is reality if if i was like one of those
lol fantasy like creatures i would be a hobbit okay this kind of face don't fit on a goblin
sorry i have like something stuck in my in my teeth let's go people are gonna be real mad
about this one not the story the the image one time i was at my local walmart minding my business
when i felt something brush against my leg glancing down i chuckled as i saw a small child who only
came up to around my knees walking past with an armful of cheesy watch where you're going kid i
said smiling at him before turning away suddenly i felt a sharp pain in my foot and looked down
to see the small child underneath me glaring up angrily at the comparative giant above him
what the heck did you just call me he demanded in a surprisingly deep bostonian accent that
sounded familiar i leant down to examine the child more closely before recoiling in shock
this was no child it was germa i'll have you know i'm a top 1000 streamer who beat dark souls 3
on stream germa continued his comically small face contorted with rage naturally i quickly
apologized and asked for a photo declaring he was my favorite compact streamer eventually after
promising 10 000 bits as compensation for the cheesy i had squashed germa let me take a photo
with him it was kim who was about my height she hurried over and scooped up the reluctant germa
in her arms before depositing him in her shopping trolley where he saturday with his arms crossed
she thanked me for taking care of him and talked him into accepting 1000 bits from me instead
before bidding her farewells and walking away just once and will there ever be a story where
i'm not like the little mutant that like bites people why would why can't somebody tell a story
of me as like fucking zoos or something like as a god now that would be that would nobody would see
that coming all right let's finish this one this is i this is pokemon and a jojo pose i like this
pikachu rat that's a nice touch connect said you were three out of ten oh no you would no no no no
for a second i thought you're saying like i'm a three out of ten no i'm definitely not a failing
grade i can tell you i promise you i got let me tell you something i can tell you something let
me tell you i can tell you cadences those cadence we have cadences top 1000 streamer i've gone up
since then i'm top like 860 oh god phylactery phylactery coming in with another 69
fucking subs 69 subs fucking every stream every single stream yo you've lost your mind but i do
appreciate it that's a shit load of money the madman the madman did it again that's it how many total
you're almost at a thousand community subs you know that is as way too many that's a fucking
million that may as well be a million oh my god yo can i get one you hang around long enough you
probably will but let's say that's uh that's a fucking lot of money you give it almost every
stream and i know i don't want to sound like i'm just glossing over that like hey thanks for the
70 subs okay let's go um but seriously it's you you have given so much fucking money that like
i can't even comprehend it thank you so much for your insane contributions hope i put it to good
use now let's do more dot to dots wait i gotta do i gotta show the screen now i like that did you
know that somebody linked me an image of them scanning my face into a uh a program and the
program said that i was 91 attractive my forehead was too small i read all your tweets guys i read
all of them i don't reply to fucking anybody but i well i don't reply to everybody i do read them
did you give more subs you gave 28 more subs that's fucking ridiculous man thank you
you made it to a thousand subs i would probably tell you at this point that's good that's good
that's that's good that's a lot of fucking money for one person to be holding that many subs
that is insane a thousand sub gifted badge at one time responsible at the same time
this this one guy this truly this truly one guy is responsible for a fucking thousand of your
subscriptions that's a pretty ridiculous one guy statement he owns 25 of my entire stock
i gotta be careful because if he gets past like 50 then i'm gonna lose the fucking company
it's the beginning of the hostile takeover no file actor i'm just kidding you've done way more
than enough more like a trillion times more than enough thank you so fucking much dude that's
insane hope you enjoy the carnival way to go all right let's keep going fun fun fun dot to dot
what is it it's funny this is actually fun it's very funny because i got a similar joke
i got a similar joke this that means great minds think alike anyways uh i know what this is
because i mean come on it's me seven eight nine
i'm so happy to see this because like this is that's what like in my own face cam and i
feel like i have to like like over animate my face no am i just like that do i do this i just saw
myself in the viewfinder here and i was like let me tell you something like what why am i
over animating my face do i do that i gotta ask fucking my friends his his actor friends
i got actors 42 43 let me go down from here 48 49 50 51 52 53 54 55 57 58 59
i'm gonna sneeze on camera and i don't i can't do anything that was real i swear to god that was
fucking real i can hold in sneezes actually really well but i always feel like i look like such a
psycho i'll be sitting in public i get a especially at a restaurant i if i have a big sneeze and i'm
in a restaurant i i don't want to do that i don't want to be the person that hold on another one
i don't want to be the person that everybody looks over to and goes what the fuck because
regardless everybody coughs everybody sneezes everybody it happens you get like the thing your
this sensitivity and your nose and you end up doing it right whatever but you feel horrible
when you do that if i'm sitting in like a nice restaurant all of a sudden you're like
you just i feel every eye i feel all the forks and hear the fork and i fucking i hear and feel
the eyes looking at me so when i'm at a restaurant it's like i dump it into the back of my eyes
you contrary to popular belief when you hold in a sneeze it's not like your throat or your chest
or your your nose that actually has the pain and the suffering it's your eyes so when i like you
you sneeze like back here in the back of your eyes and it's like so that's why you try to do it
in a way where you can sneeze but still not sneeze so right there what happened was just pull the
clip back i sneezed but it was like i got all of it out that i needed to i didn't hold it in i'm
the fucking expert at this at this point if you sneeze into your on your hands you're a degenerate
would you rather i sneeze into your burrito do you want me to like grab the plate from in
front of you and sneeze onto the plate of your fucking king salmon which what would you like me
to do into your elbow so you want me to go like and then like boom now you have a point of contact
here that is not closed and it's just going to go boom that way straight directly on your fucking
face you want to do that into your shirt okay let's go into my shirt here now what i've done
is i have just ruined the rest of my night because that's here now that's all over me
it's like it's in my body now and like i have to take a shower what are you supposed to do do it
straight upwards no you you either go like this so that there is no escape now and then you go
and you you wash your hands if you go like this there's only one place for it to go i've seen
people go like this and it's like no no no no no what are you thinking you're just concentrating
a cannon to be able to shoot it out or if you really i like desperate grab a fucking cup and
like no don't do that elbow you do i got you if you do it then you got this all over you
on your nice shirt and then what are you going to wipe it off what if it's a big snot
what happens if you have a huge fucking snot all over you now and you have a meeting in 20 minutes
oh good to meet you good what the fuck is that on your shaking hand dick get off of me don't look
at me those those of you that just haven't been in the business world you never compromise your
shaking hand or your or your greeting hand both of your hand all you can't do that do not compromise
your shaking hand so if you have to do it make sure you sneeze into the elbow that is not going
to be used as your compromised greeting hand or just fucking have tissues done end of story i'm
talking about emergency scenarios i just missed all those who is it sneeze into their hand
sneeze into your hand and then shake their hand well that would be a disgusting awful thing to do
it's me drink cold water no you don't have to do that does it have a nose no there it goes all right
let's get into the story on here not even halfway through all these stories i'm just scrolling try
to find random ones all right let's i'll put like three or four on now all right some of these are
like just just a sentence of making fun of me so hold on what it means blind keep posting the link
and they would i don't want to show it on camera what is it blind disgusting streamer whatever
that's it's that's not embarrassing to me that doesn't this is not like an embarrassing thing
it's just i sneezed in fact the thing you linked earlier could have been a sneeze where is it
but how are these two image how the two images different oh nice run well i can't sneeze i'm not
allowed to sneeze nice run let me get it right nice run why sneeze what i'm not allowed to sneeze
give me five minutes with a voice and i'll get it fucking perfect throw one out here anybody
anything i don't care what is throw something out anything my dad okay son how are you hey
david it's me your dad next one please daffy duck daffy duck is the is the looney tunes one right
you're you're despicable some things you can't do oh that was not good that was very bad some
things i'm glad i turned the camera off though so that you can't prove that was me you that you don't
you don't know that was me or not because the fucking camera was off that's a 600
fucking million iq play dude tom hanks i can't even how what happened here i forgot to turn
the camera up dude germa 985 hey hey yo all right what's going on it's me germa the only thing that
i have is a boston fucking accent dude everything else is fucking who cares just go like this and
fucking make a boston fucking accent dude what am i doing oh yeah right this all right let's go
next one do a saudi accent the saudi accents like this every word just fucking runs into each other
even i sound so much from saudi because they just every word just runs right into the next word
they're getting cabs and shit and they they're going out so go to the socks here where's elmo
i can do elmo like that no i'm not doing fucking elmo we like i'm doing something
what am i doing oh no we're like in the middle of something here here quiet every oh children
all the children please quiet for a story the draw strings of my pants just flopped directly
into a urinal double utf that i even do now i've been walking around like i'm wearing a diaper
because i don't want them to touch me jeremy e nevada closing square bracket a couple weeks
ago i had a nightmare this wasn't an ordinary nightmare it was a nightmare inside a nightmare
inception type stuff it started out with me being trapped with other random people inside this old
cabin in the woods we couldn't leave the room i'll spare the insane details but it was scary
very scary it ended up with a man relieving himself in the corner of the room at that point
it became obvious to me that this was a nightmare i told myself i had to wake up after waking up i
told myself nice i finally woke up from this nightmare oh cool there's a can of nesty in my
bed let me take a sip i never drink nesty especially not in bed i realized i was still
dreaming and i had to wake up again after waking up for the second time i looked around making sure
was truly awake i think i am awake i remain unsure i now have trouble sleeping every night
wondering if i never woke up actually good link i'm just wait i'm busy just hold on a minute i'm
busy i'm in the middle of my project 33 34 8 all right we're going this way now two around the
shoulder here look at those big broad fucking shoulders those are shoulders that people dream
about having ah five and then go up 56 57 this is a good one broad shoulders short legs no
let me correct you broad shoulders short legs long torso i do have a vibe i have like a swimmer's
body i have a long body like i have my my chest to my legs is very long but how how how do i know
that i look at myself naked every single fucking day all right do i have glasses on
i gotta okay i gotta you're gonna get an air stream for a little bit
oh man 81 was 82 straight down from here really 82 83 from here to here from here to there
that's a scary mask yes it is all right hold on no this is what do i have teeth showing in this
no i don't it's open mouth what i'm not going no i go am i going no i'm going like this this
is rick and morty rick and morty i see the link you don't have to it's a series of like numbers
as spam all right that was good sure all right okay okay okay all right everybody my goodness
that's 100 oh there we go all right what do you what do you want me to look at here
go ahead let's see it if this is a variation of a sneeze i'm not i'm not going to even open it
hold on is it a sneeze are you guys really spamming another link that's just a sneeze again
that's fucking scary i don't know what that is uh okay hold on and this is the other one it's not
a sneeze i who i look like somebody who the fuck do i look like in this image is this like freaking
me out this is what you guys wanted me to see so bad it was like a megamind again another
megamind image this one though is fucking with my head because i feel like i could look like that
in like 40 years 30 years all right let's get another uh couple stories okay i think this one
might be a scary story so get your this is a scary fucking neat face emote monka s ready
because this is going to be scary i think guys i'm not fucking around okay we'll do this one this
one's a poem got to get the bracket in there so you know it's a new segment all right let's go
next one incoming incoming now here's the rare event where i don't really have any idea what this
is pretty rare that i don't know that i don't know what this is but let's get the let's get
the stories going should i do let's just do the regular i had a dream one day i was walking
through a field of corn down a lonely dirt road went to my right i passed an ugly old scarecrow
his face was dirty and covered in straw his arm sticks with gloves nailed on his straw had let
more light through than it kept out i glanced at him and quickly turned away his gaze was too stern
his face too creepy along the path i went not sure where i was going or where i'd been
i see the scarecrow up ahead as if i'd somehow gone back a mile but i hadn't you couldn't get
lost on a path straight as this i kept going shying away from his gaze as i kept walking i
saw him again and again i lost my nerve and ran ran as fast as i could until i didn't see him
anymore i felt confident and shouted with joy spinning around ecstatic in victory only i was
cut short because on the path behind me there he was in the middle of the dirt road i stood stock
still too scared to breath once again i panic and sprint running until i lose my breath i glance
behind me and he's only closer i turn to keep running but there he is again closer still i
keep turning and turning too scared and confused to know what's happening until there he is in
front of me face to face closing square bracket they say there's a mirror below the town they
say it shows the truest reflection of yourself the few who claim they have seen it say it's in a
cavern lit by mushrooms the few all say they saw different things some say you'll see idyllic
images the perfect you or your spirit animal some say you won't like what you see i want to know
the truth i asked anyone who'd listen what they knew of the mirror i did anything to find someone
who knew then i found one of the few what the fuck is this this is the guy for is this commander
video what this is like a beekeeper i just did it correctly it's a gnome uh yeah is it no this
is a beekeeper this is like the command this commander video thank you for commander video
i did it wrong how did i do it wrong 2324 25 26 27 28 29 30 31 32 33 34 35 36 30 i didn't do it wrong
just squint really hard oh right okay so it's the wireframe of the gnome in the new gnome 3d video
game called hoops i did it again wait wait let me start this i wasn't paying attention to this story
this is i want to listen to the dream one again i had a dream one day no no no no where is it this
one the mirror they say there's a mirror below the town they say it shows the truest reflection
of yourself the few who claim they have seen it say it's in a cavern lit by mushrooms the few all
say they saw different things some say you'll see idyllic images the perfect you or your spirit
some say you won't like what you see i want to know the truth i asked anyone who'd listen what
they knew of the mirror i did anything to find someone who knew then i found one of the few then
he told me the way to the mirror he warned me i needed arms and armor he warned me i wouldn't
like what i saw but i wanted to know the truth i followed his directions to the t following the
map he gave i found the mirror sitting in a cavern lit by mushrooms i gazed into the mirror
only to see nothing okay i gazed downwards and i beheld my true self before me was a man half
my height clad in a purple hoodie and garish makeup before me he wore a red wig and chanted
aloha by ear i didn't want to know the truth no no it's it's not it's not it's not it's just the
lines they just look strange pepe needs your help connect the dots to get him back into shape
or else monka s will be removed from twitch chat forever oh no help hurry i'm never gonna do it in
time i don't have there's no green we'll do blue oh no i'm gonna hurry i'm gonna do it wait a minute
this is garfield without the whiskers okay let's get another story
that was weird i just i saw it here wait a minute hold wait a minute wait a minute
it's homer simpson too i'm going too deep i think all right let's put on some music
18 19 20 21 22 23 let's do it quick 41 42 43 44 45 46 47 48 49 50 that's it i did it oh wait it's
sans too sans is seriously like i'm done with sans you know that's too easy i thought it's too
easy to make like i'm done i'm done with sans i think me and sans are done yeah i don't think i
i don't i don't i'm done with sans sans isn't done with you i got it fun fact member of the boston
celtics i know who this is come on this looks good when am i gonna play delta rune again i'll
play it in seven years in the next episode comes up all right so let's just do the black ink how's
that look can you see it zoom in a little let me get another story because i mean those are those
are fan favorites okay i don't this this one's confusing i don't know i don't know what the
fuck this one means but i am scanning through these very just preliminary preliminary preliminary
preliminary preliminary preliminary what am i trying to say spell it for me i am i am
preliminarily i am primarily how do you say that word i am beforehand going to put this up and
look at it preliminarily preliminarily preliminarily there it is thank you for the english majors
preliminary preliminary i think i need to fucking eat a bowl of cereal
preliminarily okay what the fuck that means but i'm gonna just hope it's not anything fucking bad
i don't even know what this means but congratulations here come two more stories
let's go i was walking home from school many many moons ago this other kid got off her bike
and held my hand she wanted me to say hi to her but i said no i looked back up to see her riding
away flipping me the mighty bird gut wrenching this is a moment my friends we all have an amazing
chance to make a difference in someone's life your kindness and compassion may make a difference to
a person your compassion and help may even stop an accident your presence may keep an entire church
going your presence with a friend will give them a lift and allow them to walk many more miles
a smile may brighten someone's day but a middle finger will ruin a lifetime
when you return i'll have solved the problem of gravity you have my w-a-h-h-d closing square
bracket i'm here to announce our new game at e3 it's called tales from the tomb raider you'll
probably hear plenty of that from people over in australia in the united states it'll be called
tale from the tomb raider cerny it's not going to be called tale from the tomb raider yet it's
going to be called tales from the tomb raider i love the sound of that name it's going to be
called tale from the tomb raider for some sort of convention in 2014 the tomb raider title is
being developed by a group of team members and they're actually talking about a new game cerny
one of these days we're going to announce that game at e3 this year or soon after or maybe even
early next year but at this point we're actually trying to convince people to actually buy and
play the game instead of just to enjoy the game and see their own photos in its world
but as far as we know this isn't a sequel or reboot right now sir i know it's not called
tale of the tomb raider it's tale of the tomb raider tales of the tomb raider what's this g
oh it's a g cool nice i like it tale from the tale of the room raider nice job oh i just want
to get a few more stories all right i'm loading up just like three of them in a row half of them are
just nonsense anyways it's not like what am i going to do okay let's do this one i'm just
scrolling i'm just scrolling some of these are long this is long these some of these are really
long okay here we go i got these are this three of them here i need to separate i don't have any
brackets anymore i love them out of brackets okay here we go next image what the fuck is this one
one time in seventh grade one was trying to jump down the stairs to impress all the girls
i was leaning forward from the top step and holding the railing about halfway down the stairs
planning on swinging from the top to the bottom well my hand slipped and i ended up tumbling head
over heels down the stairs and i landed flat on my back i tried to recover all cool by sitting up
and saying well that just happened and went to my next class which was gym i think we played dodge
ball or something whatever it was it was pretty boring then after class my teacher came up to me
and said did you fall down the stairs earlier today i said yeah but it's not big deal she told
me to go to the nurse's office which i did and when i told them what happened they called my
mom and sent me home so i got to go home early and watch tv because i tried and failed to impress
some girls in seventh grade pretty good deal if i'm honest closing square bracket that's a cool
story parts of this story in an online chat room i mean but i thought it's worth sharing it in their
entirety i had two dreams recently that had an individual that must have made some impact with
how dreams work and remembering them is uncommon the recent dream had him crashing at my place to
avoid paying for a hotel originally thinking it was gonna be an awkward experience we ended up just
talking story on the couch and at the beach the first dream though we driving around north shore
sunny day ocean peeking over the hill in front empty fields on either side with an occasional
tree grove to break up the monogamy it was just us and the road eventually they pulled off the
road to park i watched them step out and round the front and with no rhyme or reason they started to
take the pants off shocked i grabbed for the door handle but i woke up before i could heart pounding
with the dream still fresh i mumbled since when did you drive joma if they ever read this somehow
thank you so much for the talk it was fun and we had a lot of laughs i'm also said some things
that were uplifting and made me reflect on some things gosh i really wish i could remember what
was said thank you again but what are you talking about i think i should be flattered but you know
first impressions are important right closing square bracket one two oatmeal kirby is wanted
on four counts of homicide and seven counts of grand theft larceny kirby was last seen in dream
land sucking off bark from these weird face trees officers tried to detain kirby but he managed to
escape by eating them whole there were absolutely no survivors but we managed to recover this
information off of the live feed of one of our officers we believe that kirby's current motives
are to overtake king ddd and quote wear his ass like a helmet we can only speculate the motives
his partner meta knight was also seen blowing a guy in the alley if you see kirby do not approach
him if he offers you oatmeal he's trying to fuck you do not approach him he will get inside of you
any way he can he is a dangerous and lethal character do not go near him i know this first
hand because when i was in the field and he was just a new suspect i thought oh that's just a
little pink blob he's not gonna do anything three stories i am having a lot of trouble trying to
see what this one is 41 42 43 44 47 down to 48 50 down to 51 52 53 54 55 56
57 what am i making here 62 is it a ghost 67 68 i'm squinting it looks like somebody going like
oh right 67 78 79 80 81 oh okay it's it's the it's the walk that's pretty good i got you got
your credit for that one that's pretty good for connect the dots image the smile to the eye into
the hair that's pretty good one that was great i want that as a shirt this that's fucking awesome
coming up next another one at first glance it's kind of hard to determine you want it with the
numbers why with the numbers where's my like twitch page oh it's over here all right let's
get another uh i just saw one line on that one i don't want to put that one on what the fuck is
this one okay i'm having like i'm having fun just browsing through the stories and trying to figure
out if this is a real story a fake story or you made this in talk to transformer i think half of
these were made in talk to transformer in fact this one even says made with talk to transformer
on it we'll try these we'll try these few here all right this is this is a length lengthy one
all right i'll change the voice too okay all right let's do this one and i'm going to start
the puzzle hee-hee look hold on not yet me and my pa went hunting the other day and we saw this
huge bear like the bear was at least five feet tall and must have been heavier than my mom's sedan
my the bear my pa told me to stay low so that it wouldn't sense us i found that funny since i
didn't know bears come with a radar we ended up going fishing afterward because my pa told me
bears can't swim closing square bracket jeremy elbertson is a clown his father is an alcoholic
so when elbertson began acting as a stand-up comedian it seemed a natural fit but elbertson
doesn't just act like he's doing a performance wait he's actually training and he's living a
life that is full of stress and responsibility what happened with this one elbertson is trying
to reach happiness but as he puts it my main goal right now is to go through the stages of
grief and get it over with what with his mother dead and his father battling addiction elbertson
is at a crossroads in his life hold on wait wait what what happened he talks to people about the
reasons for his struggle how he got there and what's next all while helping some students take the
first steps into stand-up comedy you've already done a comedy album but you're a jerk what inspired
you're not wrong i never really intended to make a comedy record i just wanted to make my voice
hear and be heard but i have a lot closing square bracket that's the talk transfer last week that i
went to the movie theater with germa it must have been a hilarious movie because germa was
convulsing in laughter we're talking visible shaking here i'll lean over to germa and ask if
he's hold on wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute y'all have a lot of fucking dreams about
me can i just say you know i had this dream about germa was like fucking eating people and he like
peed his own face and then he was like punching me why do i why am i like hurting everybody in
your dreams yeah let's put on uh how about this one i don't know who is this i had a dream last
week that i went to the movie theater with germa it must have been a hilarious movie because germa
was convulsing in laughter we're talking visible shaking here i lean over to germa and ask if he's
feeling all right germa answers fit as a fiddle son now do your old dad a favor and get us some
poppin corn keep the change so germa hands me some bills i walk out to the concession stand and there
is a huge line in front of me is a bayou chain smoking in public behind me is a very polite
she told me i could go in front of him since all he wanted was a diet water after what must have
been 20 minutes in line i get to the front one large poppin corn please i asked very politely
to the vendor named peter peter responds with or without butter my knees get weak my palms are
sweaty fettuccine begins to drip out of my pocket and i meekly answer with i hand him the money that
germa lent me i'm sorry sir we don't accept canadian tire money that's when i knew i must
have been dreaming for one germa isn't canadian too this is canadian tire money i begrudgingly
pay the vendor five germa bucks and returned to my seat next to germa this is a guy like popcorn
and he says this movie sucks let's get out of here it's this what is this it's germa tv oh i
thought okay i thought it was like a guy this is a hand he's like sitting down and this is his mouth
and this is his eyes he's got like sunglasses on you know what i'm saying all right sunglasses
mouth sitting down just like relaxing going like yeah i'm gonna change germa tv to that this is
what the new email will be that's fucking funny though i have no idea what this was until the
very end people will use it even less good all right no that one was good that one was fun who
chat dot to dot who asked germa if he ate ass uh one guy yeah it wasn't one it was just one guy
right oh fuck yeah this is what that is what you tell me i got more colors what am i stupid
i didn't know i had more than that all right let's do it is it actually gonna be germa one guy
i'm gonna be so happy if it is it is isn't it oh yes 12 down here here comes a broom
i just got a brief room brief room here comes the big one now that was that was a distant room
still happened though 18 and 19 back over here 20 20 where's 21 oh just wait to keep going
122 24 is right here then we do the same thing this way 26 27 i fucked it up 29 30 31 yeah
the nose the nose i love this wait 27 where no no 20 29 30 31 33 34 35
36 wait did i screw it up what does it look like ah shit no 38 39 no i fucked it up again come on
40 243 there it is this emote used to cost 25 a month yeah it did this was this was a 25
dollar a month emote what a fucking ripoff eight to 43 i screwed it up where eight to 43
eight no this is nine right here that's nine let's see what it looks like oh no we lost the hair
it's all good now there's no 25 dollar emote no it's not i had ideas before but
i don't know what am i gonna put there okay this is him falling and seeing the ground before him
and being like oh no this is it he's falling he's falling he's falling oh fuck this is the end
right there okay that's that one let's keep going i feel like i can get this one done pretty quick
all right anybody let anyone stories in what dreams anybody had okay we'll get this one
we'll do bracket here this one uh i'm not gonna i i don't want to do the i no i'm not doing that
one all right we'll do this one and then i'm gonna take a break from stories we're gonna put some
music on let's go when i was younger my father would take me to my bedroom door frame and measure
my height with a marker once a month that evening i remember waking up on the first of every month
excited that i would be able to see how far i have grown since the previous month now as a child i
always had a head larger than my body the doctor said that this is normal for a child of my age
and that my body will eventually catch up to the size of my head after a few years i had finally
reached an impasse my head was somewhat normal sized and my full height on the door frame was
a humbling five feet six inches my father told me that since i was at my later teenage years that
my body would stop growing as fast this disappointed me perhaps i would grow more in a few years
13 years later i was sick and tired of it all i tried getting into really good shape ate super
healthy and even went to a chiropractor to make my back the straightest there is i didn't even
get one centimeter then just yesterday i decided to change the formula around i cut my hair short
it stretches all day listens when yeah and went to bed super early without measuring my height
the next morning i woke up and immediately measured myself i grew two centimeters guys
there's still hope for us short folks out there keep trying closing square bracket sky went into
germa's stream the other day and he was just doing this impression of two viewers talking
it was really weird he would act like one of the viewers had recommended the stream to the other
but that that viewer had become disillusioned with the stream after seeing something weird
yeah it was just strange man not sure what i expected but please don't link me to that streamer
ever again thank you closing square bracket germa 985 wanted to go to the potluck as a member of the
community after a lot of back and forth he got his own pass with a note to the people that were
coming for the event i would really appreciate your attendance what that was how most of my friends
made their way here they came by their friends and told them where to start going
it's kind of a shame that the people in charge of keeping the community running don't share that
same mindset when asked if he was expecting a big response from his own friends no i mean it's not
even close we have probably only a couple of hundred people that are showing up to see the
first time we put on the event that may have been the result of just a few hundred people showing up
and a lot of that might not have been the result of that there wasn't really any indication that
something was going to take off like this for us just who this is who were coming would appreciate
us that was it that was i don't know what that story was we're gonna go smaller uh let's do the
red down here no no no yeah what what what does what does he look like he's got uh glasses on
right glasses first six seven eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen yeah these these are the
shades free advertisement for another streamer by the way i don't like to do this okay now
we've got to go like uh no we can stay here what color is his hair brown right what's the beef
yeah that comes from his stream i know that's his little phrase whenever he gets into a back and
forth of chat guys shut up i can see it i picked up the item already and i combined it with the
green herb god what's the beef and everyone fucking lashed their asses off wicked fucking
funny that you wouldn't he wouldn't know comedy if it poopooed on his poopooed on him you know
what i mean what i'm saying all right here's the hair now from 56 57 where we go who's 58
where's 58 58 oh there it is are you really dissing somebody that helped you on the come up
wait wait wait shirt shirts red i know everything about this guy i know what color shirts he has
i know his comedy schtick routine 84 85 all right looking good girl master looking good
what happened down here no gm right the more the germa talks the more i think real masters on the
is the right one i have no fault in that in the problems that we had uh let's put up some tunes
what do you say what do you say some music oh wait right right i'm an idiot i want to do this
now if that ain't if that ain't somebody's like new twitter profile for if it was me and i wanted
something very minimalistic and artistic at the same time like if i was a youtuber or something
that would probably be what it was except the only difference is put this on like a darker
background and have these lines be brighter glowing neon almost like it was a sign you know
like a neon sign outside of a bar and then have like gmbb uh bx xq whatever be at bb xq
bb yeah barbecue bbq x well i don't know the fucking whatever his name is bb xq
bbq x i don't know what his name is grill master x barbecue that's just a kind of funny idea
have like a little neon sign of your i don't want to look at it that
it's my shit i'm gonna have one of those on like in the back here all right what about some tunes
anybody got any tunes i just helped his brand uh what we got for tunes nes pictionary really is
that fun pictionary nes why uh where did this come from is that seriously like a thing you want to
hear pictionary nes i've never heard of this it's a minute long this is a minute one of that
this is for the regular nintendo that's pretty good for the regular nintendo wait look at the base
all right the channel is getting rated so shine the spotlight on the dissenter to make out the
outline let's see so this one looks a little complicated 13 14 this button i'll be like a
ball sack 19 oh what's 19 over here 21 8 29 30 31 32 33 all the way up around the left side
that was good what's next put on the loop wig the holy blade yeah absolutely that is the best song
in a video game just in case anyone had any idea all right you want us to lock the fuck in on this
one i'm gonna put both headphones in and lock in what a weird stream whatever oh say hey can you
turn it down my mom is sleeping dude i am fucking so uh this is crab this is italics crab the
dissenter is italics pretty good i should have done it in red that was my mistake this is the
goatee we missed 96 i didn't miss anything i'm fine that's pretty good that looks good all right
i don't want to do any spoilers but i want to see what's left a lot well let's hold on
no we're like more than halfway through the dot to dots we have like another 15 or so
this is fun i'm like i'm actually i'm really enjoying this shit it's just fun to just do this
did you do all the stories uh yes i did most of the stories already don't you have a plane to catch
no i got plenty of time we have to hear the whole ludwig song though because i ain't gonna go out
with all the whole entire ludwig song it's my favorite song so sorry we're gonna have to
fucking listen to it i need a good one actually no not ludwig we need to have like a bopping song
for the next one what's like what's like a what's a good bopping song i need a good one i can't do
it do pluck i feel like i've done pluck we're just gonna do the we're gonna do the pluck beach
i don't know i don't want it i'm sorry i've done it before i've done it already
avengers the event the avengers theme hold on the avengers the one that goes like
why all right fine stream will be bopping real soon oh fuck this whole thing's gonna
get claimed oh no no that's a bad idea that's a bad idea but i can't do that i can't do anything
anybody have any music they've made recently there's got to be video game related fuck did
i just really kill it my entire bod because i played 15 seconds of the avengers theme song
please don't do that metal gear solid no you know what i want i want the metal gear five theme song
is this claimed this is in the game right right it is right this is in the game this is a song from
a movie we bopping pretty good finger work there 52 oh it's right next to it 54 85 there it is
i think he has an extra finger but that's all right it's okay that's great connect the dots
from one to 80 and this page will be bopping it already is it already what's next dear germa i've
drawn your face so many times it's time for you to draw mine wait this is your face it's time for
you to draw my face this is your face all right let's do it what do we start with one two wait am
i zoomed out okay there it is two nine's up here down to ten wait i fucked it up this is a mouth
10 11 12 13 teen 16 wait no no no i fucked it up 15 16 here teen 17 17 17 19 18 there it is right
there behind 19 20 21 22 23 24 this is really detailed 27 28 29 which 34 all right here and
then 35 36 37 ah that looks ugly i screwed it up 38 where's 38 i don't want to drink any more
coffee what am i doing it's a mistake 40 38 right there eight 39 40 41 oh that's a no that's ugly
39 40 41 42 oh this is this is jubated okay all right i get it what i just leave up on 44
six 47 it's time for you to draw my face i get it pretty good wait i can do that better 950
51 52 almost done with the left side oh no no back it up 350 now we do we're gonna do the head
um do cleaner than that this is really good use a use a ruler why would i use a ruler when i was
like 12 years old i didn't use a ruler i used my i did it with my hand i'm not gonna use the line
tool this is this is how you do dot to dot with your hand why would i use the line tool this is
cheating and by the way you gotta pay to use the line tool 263 465 here's the ear oh boy this is
gonna be tricky in this one 75 is right there 76 down here to 77 78 is back across 79 is over
here 82 83 84 i like it got him let's see what it looks like with the uh this is just an edit of
view this is a bald edit of you bald that's that's pretty good that's pretty good i mean
there's a little bit of issue over here but that's pretty good that's awesome good shit good shit
all right we need some new music here i i can't take like doing doing doing doing doing doing
anymore as much as i love it metal gear solid pokemon katamari persona five i've never i've
never played persona i don't want to get spoiled on the music in case i ever decided to play that
game which i probably won't jet set radio that's not a bad one so less oh so less has good music
yeah let's listen to let's just put celeste on there's some good music in celeste it worked what
worked putting on good fucking osts guys this is the chill stream before i leave to the carnival
somebody got scammed who got scammed don't get scammed never give anybody your fucking credit card
number unless you pay for something on amazon all right let's go clear it good stuff surprise a new
friend in the germa funhouse who could it possibly be let's form bonds with him and find out shoot him
205 times with your laser pointer i do appreciate that it's color coded it is it's color coded
where are we starting one with blue right wait this is different blue i need a darker blue gotta
be a thicker line for that one what why am i putting this much time into this why do i care
about this everyone knows what this is already done the thing's already completed in front of you
wait a minute why is this different color no that should be the same color okay let's go thinner
uh i'm gonna do uh the beard i'm good is this the gnome why am i even asking that fucking question
under the institute already all right can we just pretend i did this one it's a gnome it's gonna it's
like the who thing no 14 skip this please i now i can't i'm already halfway skip do not skip skip
do not skip skip it don't skip it don't skip it is it right all right that's it now we got uh up here
14 15 16 17 18 i am half-assed i'm half-assing this one i shouldn't be doing that now i know what
the image is he already ate half the bowl of berries all right now let's switch to um let's
orange this looks fucked up this doesn't look right actually does it looks kind of looks
correct actually that's not bad that's a good one whoa this is high resolution no pull back
holy shit what is this this is finish the gnome okay i'm just gonna go for it so this we're gonna
do just black turn up the music i can do that ignored what what did i ignore who am i ignoring
what did i do i who did i ignore what happened that's me on the left no that's me on the right
now this is two of me's all right here we go let's just start it i don't i don't ignore people
oh it's the chin thing of course it is down here wrap the hair around this one has high detail i
like it i pretty much liked all of them they've all been pretty good 39 40 by the way if you're
looking for these if you want to do this just for fun uh all of these are in that discord art
already right now if you go to the dot to dot section if they're just there there's like 40
50 all right this is where it gets i gotta focus on this one because this is where the detail comes
over this is like a whole hand here we go i said that's that and then it comes got kind of a
fucked up finger there a little bit i guess what's 54 whoa we'll go all the way up this is this big
square all the way this is a big picture a big painting this is fucking awesome but what is
this a painting of somebody all right i'm gonna start to actually 80 what the fuck is this down
here up here is this an ear really good connections on this one the connect the way that the lines
don't cross everything very very well very well made wait slow it down three here cross to 104
so this is like a did i make this wait 112 then turns into 113 114 115 what in the name of god is
this it's one of my paintings from that painting game oh okay oh that's right on the phone that's
right i forgot about that this one this one was great that was awesome let's get the uh
the white on it although without the without the actual internal uh detail let's you still
actually can tell what's going on here though it kind of looks like a sand castle that i built
but i'm very proud of it that's awesome the chin is spot on too it is nice go work
jerma please play pikmin 3 it's only 20 bucks on the wee you e-shop and i think you'd like it
the wee you e-shop is close forever isn't it am i wrong i'm not wrong that looks good right there
so are these pikmins i have to do different colors for different pigments it's a blue and red and a
yellow pigment right let's start over here this one i'm gonna say this one's red this is the red
pigment over here i'm gonna guess that's probably wrong but i'm still gonna do it because this is
where i have to start here we go start up one is this a pigment oh it's definitely a pigment
yeah it is all right now i gotta do back to black here is this a beetle or is this picked up
is this is there i think this is purple um 99 certain this is purple purple is a big fat one
right there is no purple here yeah there is kind of sort of get some undertale music we'll do
undertale next uh thank you everybody i don't think i even said this but thanks everybody for
even contributing any of these i wanted to find something that we could just do for fun
for like the day before i left and this has been a lot of fun it's been just cool just to see what
you guys come up with so thank you for contributing these things it's good shit thank you now where
we go 29 and this is a big circle six point seven there we go down 50 all right i do have to ask
though is is pikmin actually really really a really good game to play on stream should i
stream pikmin what do you guys think i have played pikmin before but not in a very very long
time it's not a really good stream game a lot of people saying yes but still this is different
pikmin okay i'm gonna go with yellow 66 this is a cute little picture two three
three all right now this is the fruit this is a blue pikmin oh i fucked it up
shit it's all right you can just use your imagination this one i don't know what color
that one is it has like a horn so the other horn this is probably uh blue and if it's not then i'm
sorry i've ruined everything 15 16 17 18 19 i'm gonna go like this too you know what let's just
let's finish it ah there we go 24 27 28 oh shit this is this is part of red let me get to here
look at that i kind of want to that looks cool is that a berry is it that you pick up berries in
that game ever thought of doing a drawing pad with a computer no i don't i'm not very artistic i can't
do stuff like that i what you see with me with the mouse is as good as i can do with a pen in
my hand so no that wouldn't help i would just spend money on a tablet just for no reason
am i colorblind no no i'm not is that some kind of fucking joke trying to get me my expense
all right let's go that was a good one too i think we're nearing the end of the dot to dots and then
we're at we're at the pretty much we're at a big meaty stuff at that point we're gonna need rock
music this is the relaxing portion of the stream hopefully maybe if you got a fireplace
they don't use it because it's summertime so just open a window all right scoff at him i made this
boy is this this is lightning man this is definitely lightning man without a doubt we're
gonna do broader strokes on that lightning man deserves better yeah this is lightning man
or gatorade man i love it scoff at him there's a whole no it's not sponsored i don't drink
gatorade there's a whole family of little people that are lightning based fire based they're all
elemental based we could have a whole elemental family in fact maybe one day introducing germa
the frog hey guys can you fill me in connect the dots and color inside the lines all right frog
gonna have to be green let's do the smaller one i'm going to pull it back just a hair i zoomed
it in too far that oh wow there's a okay this one's gonna be tricky i promised undertale music
after this after this one all right this is an ear part into the stream here
actually pretty clean to do this this is actually fairly clean
f i i got overwhelmed by the amount of numbers but no they're very much
tightly knit together to go through them oh no no no no don't go that easy don't
don't predict where it's supposed to go follow the rule 41 there it is five all right let me
squint in here i definitely have like a fucking i definitely have nerd neck right now sometimes
you need to do full nerd neck to be able to get what you want to have done
eight nine sixty oh that's the full foot nerd neck oh shit no no no no no i almost just blew the whole
thing 71 all right more finesse work with the hands here 77 77 77 is there 77 do you guys see 77
i don't see 77 i was gonna go i will go into 78
six seven eighty eight ninety one two ninety three ninety four ninety five ninety six
that feels good to do that all right almost at 103 then from here we're doing the arm the second
part of the arm connect the dots la la la la la let's la la la i was friends with a dude and i
found out he was a furry after telling me he put on his bulk mask and ran into the woods i could
hear him howling as he ran deeper till he was gone that's a really great made-up sentence
from here we're wrapping around this one 10 right here hey 15 16 17 oh it's just like traversing
water i'm just trying to navigate my boat to the right spot more almost done time to go to the
head all right this is where it gets tricky i think i fucked something up here it was a
too long watch it easy 44 45 46 jesus 60 oh i gotta take a second with 63 right here
667 68 69 70 oh we're closing it 78 79 the hair part comes right down to the middle that's cool
80 to 81 86 87 to the end how am i doing i'm doing good how are you how are you doing hope you're
doing well that one was elaborate let's see what it looks like i mean if i did that by hand i'm
not sure i could do a better job what's the music this is the uh celeste ost that's good enough yeah
good shit let's clear it thank you for that my fan of frogs i mean yes i do like i do like frogs a
lot connect the dots i know this one's gonna be we have to do the germa 985 germa color which i
don't really they don't have it it's like this one or this one which one's closer i mean probably
this one unfortunately i don't have the uh lighter version of this green and maybe this one connect
the dots that's pretty close that was one stroke all right now this is the we're getting into the
heart not yet no not yet here we go complete the j 46 very cute we don't even need the other one
can we get more emotes of the j it's a good character design it is a really good character
design like give all that credit to blordow because it was they made that i said this is
kind of what i'm looking for and he was like let's go and he made an awesome fucking little character
it's a j yeah it's a j all right i did promise that i was gonna put on undertale so let's do it
i did promise who's that famous hollywood movie star hint it's not me let's put on change this
to who could it be i don't want to listen to the whole undertale soundtrack because the soundtrack
is so good in undertale that it's going to make me like sad when i hear like the sad songs we'll do
the boss themes yeah i don't want to get like sad right now then it's a very emotional song
soundtrack sometimes all right i know who this is surprise more of you don't know this is going
to be tricky hold on i'm going to come down with it ah no we did the whole damn thing with a thicker
pen oh it's okay i got it shito very cute i like it good stuff oh wait actually let's see let's
look at it with the uh without let's put it on put on the scanner very nice what is this one
it looks kind of like i don't know i'm not gonna take a guess yet
i need to get some uh i need to get in there starting at the bottom it's obviously me
but are you looking at me i wonder if you're not looking at me then what are you doing
30 that's what it is i love it all right 41 here oh did i blow it up no i think i got it still
that's awesome the one of four moves that i have i do on camera whenever i have a
fucking face cam one i'm either gonna go like look at me look at me or i'm gonna go like
it's like it's my go-to when i'm out of things to say you can always tell because i'm gonna go
oh by the way um best song on the osd you blank that one blank another let me see if i can get
this i think i got it solved it all right let's get in there what do we start this is the barrel
you know the barrel the not the barrel the ball the bottle say what it is he's no he's
not holding a drumstick that's a bottle all right let's go i'm starting over here
20 21 all right i think we have to take the pencil off here 22 is right here
31 38 59 50 51 52 53 that's actually pretty good at that ended at 60 61 73 76 77 thrown up bottle
and then this is the explosion 70 started 78 right yeah 78 79 82 83
84 86 oh wait it's up there i can still get it 87 88 89 90 91 92 93
where's 94 in the middle that's not where's 94 is that it wait that's it like that that's it right
there you go now this one we don't need the screen for it because this obviously is a great artwork
on here the show you missed 94 try another i like i like the little explosion that's cool
can we already hear this one skip it i like to touch here with adding the little activity like
oh can you guess the word i like it uh i mean don't skip it i'm skipping it you can hear the end there
you go this is called the hint this is called it's a goon one is this sans well
now that's that was shitty uh i guess we're going all the way around
there was portal it is the whole thing so what the fuck hold on i got a 18 not all right 2021
22 was eyebrow then from here we got to go to here without touching anything right i i guess
down to 27 29 was 30 am i doing this right i guess 44 was for looking for 45 down down here not bad
46 47 48 49 anybody have any idea what this is this is peter this has been my sister's ringtone
since 2015 looking for 54 right here i get the fuck up there 455 is that 63 i think that's 63
up here and then 64 65 60 is this 68 no it's over there wait 64 is down here 62 63 64 65
66 67 68 where's 69 oh 70 i'm just gonna go for it oops seven four what is this is this a is this
just a goon i think it's just i don't know what this is is it sans no well whatever it is
interesting interesting line decision that's i feel like i needed a ruler with this one
all right i need some new music he hates it what what are you talking about i just said
interesting fucking line work here it is wait let me see oh i i've never i've never seen this before
all right let's skip uh let's skip to uh about hotline mammy's not that idea how about what's
like the oh i forgot to tell you guys this is oh really important i forgot i um so i played this
has nothing to do with anything that we're doing right now today i played the first hour and a
half or so of god of war the new one uh that's that might be the best hour that might be the
best first hour of any video game i've ever played my whole life like that initial like few fights
might be the coolest thing i've ever seen in a video game the first like hour and a half you
know exactly what i'm talking about that's it was un fucking believable and i can't believe i didn't
even try to play this game like two years ago four years ago when i came up why don't i play it
on stream um i don't know because i feel like i just kind of wanted to play it and just sit back
and go sometimes you want to do that with a video game you know you can do that good i could do that
here he hates us i still have like the goon on screen i know i need a new ost wait let me
just take a look and see how many we got left on the dot to dots we have all right we have left we
have like six dot to dots remaining and then we got to get into the fucking hard shit put on the
full metal alchemist ost i can't i don't want this stream to get claimed this is a comfy stream i
don't want to i want people to be able to watch this bot if they feel like it and i want it to be
a comfortable stream now we'll do hot we'll do hotline in miami that's a good one um that's
kind of odd why am i when i typed in hotline miami the thumbnail is still sans and like papyrus
that was strange yeah this is pretty good this is good all right here we go let's go back to it we
only got about five or six more of these that i like this one already don't even i i don't even
know what it is i have no idea what this one is i could be anything your enemy in the digital age
uh germa says who ruins the stream when the connection goes bad i couldn't guess oh wait
it's already there dude i'm doing this pretty sloppy but you know it's all right because i'm
trying to hold it i do that's why i don't have face cams on by the way you just saw it in real
time why i don't do that don't summon it 21 22 24 25 26 who is it it's cox i like this down here
my arm is a little bigger though chest is a little bit bigger than that i got like a little my neck
is a little thicker too i've got a bigger breast too over there this is a little bigger this is
bigger down here as well this is a little bit bigger i got a big fucking brain in there good
shit cox sucks what's that in the bush i know what it is let's do it over here one two three
it's the slug 29 into 31 32 33 nice that one was clean i think that one was that's a one stroker
just gotta go here up around it's beautiful he looks so happy because he is turn the volume up
you got it good shit this one jerma you need to help auto find the location of autos adventure
three lines start and stop it alamander just gave five community subs thank you for the five subs
five dropped right now thank you appreciate that uh you need to help find auto lines start and stop
it between one and four lines stop okay i'm gonna go just piece by piece here this one has very
specific directions one through four lines start and stop like that okay five through 12
stuff is start and stop so up here i think this is autos dog bowl 13 through 91 13 through 91 so
from here is one line to 91 i missed 31 come on you can do better than that dude
31 32 by seven this is the tail i know i'm it's all right all right so to 91
we're gonna do all of it all the way around oh nice leg good work on the leg
that's tricky to do that the way down here 22 73 is it perspective on this
what is this is perspective it's i think this perspective on here is it looking this way or
this way i'm gonna do that cleaner big circle 89 90 91 oh shit that's awesome 92 to 96 and then 97
to 104 and then 105 to 108 hyper realistic dog butthole all right so what i'm supposed to find
find the location of autos adventure 3 in here that's a full-on like this is so this is so good
it's so good that is um that is what my dog's butthole looks like that's what it looks like
i don't know how you got that detail so correct next song oh yeah this is no the song is this a
10-hour version of this oh this is my favorite song the one that goes like
this is the one all right let's take a look at what the uh screen on it
is nice like fried egg butthole that's awesome good work
disney character all right i'm gonna say uh is it a mouse it's goofy from mcdonald's speedrun this
one good luck i don't think i'll try this is too i need to see i gotta go darker than that
16 17 18 19 20 22 23 24 25 up here 27 they share is sharing they're sharing a bubble
28 29 30 31 46
50 back again 51 52 is this the chuck e cheese raft who is this
this is this is like from chuck e cheese or something
faster faster i don't know what 64 is 64 where is it 64 right down here
65 down here back up to 66
bad 12 13 21 24 125 is this cat in the hat is it no 123 24 i need 25 right here 26 127 28 29
30 31 32 33 4 35 36 37 38 43 done that's a cat of some sort it's a swedish cartoon character
what's the character's name is this just ripped from an actual connect the dots book
this is from a swedish children's book so somebody just copy and pasted a swedish children's book
highlights activity book section oh i guess that makes sense it's pretty good though
nice job his name is findus is it findus or find us good shit before you begin to make sure to
draw you make sure you draw your face in the circle this one has 181 why does it say owo
owo what's that why do you have that here is this a skip is it is this is this a skip scenario
this is a skip scenario there's a dick skip skip skip no no no i need i need like certainty here
i don't this is a tail this is like okay this is a dragon ball character to me this is a dragon ball
z character or a hyper evolved pokemon that is intelligent they can talk to people i've never
seen either one of those two things hyper evolved pokemon that can speak or a dragon ball z character
it has my face on it um all right well i'm gonna what what no guys you brought it's not
i'm going for it i'm getting baited here to not do this one he's so stupid don't do this why
you guys are freaking me out i don't you guys are freaking me out right now it's clearly just like a
person standing here it's just somebody's standing 29 it's just a hand sitting like this on the side
this is just yeah that's not what's wrong with this is just the sicko it's a rat
this is a rat this is me this is my rat i don't know this is my sleep paralysis demon
it's just a rat that's just a rat standing there like a superhero it's a rat superhero donald duck
doesn't wear pants guys what's wrong what are you talking about it was the last time you saw like
donald duck wear a pair of fucking underwear he doesn't he wears a t-shirt and by the way what
a sicko you wear a t-shirt but you don't wear pants why not just have him have no clothes on
no he's beat he oh yeah oh i got a t-shirt on that's it uh thank thanks for that that was that was
all right well there's instructions here let's see if we can get it all on there we can
this shito this one says when you see the pencil icon pick the pencil up and look for the next
number nice instructions i appreciate it some numbers are diagonally close to each other and
have the same star good to know okay all right so i'm gonna go with uh what color should i do
hey someone's talking this shito let's just go black and i'll keep that same line the same one
start at one if you see a pencil means pick it up 13 14 16 17 18 i see a pencil wait a minute
should i pick it up from here or there's a 32 i think that's 32 yeah that's 32 pick pencil up
32 pick up pencil okay so then 33 is over here 34 is the same one as six
36 37 38 5 46 47 pick up the pencil 48 49 50 51 52 pick up the pencil wait i did is it it i did it
wait 53 55 56 what is it toilet but what do you mean is it i don't but what what do you mean is
a toilet what is it is this supposed to be legs my toilet tweet hey i have a new tweet now so that
doesn't work anymore i thought it was a rat's face going like like up with you know what i mean i
thought it was here's the rat's mouth rat's nose and eyes and it's lying back going like this
with his hands it was like legs down these were his legs right here legs legs mouth open nose
that's just uh that's fucked up thank you for that one i like the instructions too that was
very clear no numbers i'll just take a guess i don't think you need numbers it seems pretty
unnecessary i got it kind of all right i got it now what does this say oh this says i know what
this says it says oh yes what oh yes that's oh yes oh yes yes there oh yes that's too easy
is hey guess what whoa i'm not going to show it yet because i don't want to see it either
this is uh the portion of the stream where i'm going to do where's waldo's this is spoiler for
what what is this oh this is all right if you've never seen infinity war let me tell you if you've
never seen the movie infinity war or its sequel i believe this is a scene where there is a uh there
is a thing happening if you've never seen both if you've never seen all the infinity war in marvel
war end war end game don't look and don't look at all okay although this is very basic it's just like
this is people just standing around i just they're okay let me tell you all right let me tell you
there are people standing around in the movie end game at some point okay just if you've never
seen the movie don't fucking look at the screen it's that simple what here's how this is going to
work i am allowed to use the windows magnifying glass i will give you an example of what that
means for instance if i need to i get to use it i get to sit back that's cheating that's not i get
to use the windows magnifying glass at 125 i think i gotta explain the rules do they give me a chance
to explain the rules for instance so let's say for let's just say that i want you know i've got my
little magnifying glass here i've got to find i've got to find me and i might have to sit back you
guys can know i'll be sitting back here i i get to use this only at 125 percent where's baldo
that's op it's not op you don't worry you'll be fine so here we go remember if you've never seen
that i almost just turned off the computer because i did the wrong command i saw the windows thing
pop up and i almost turned the fucking computer off okay here we go first where's waldo i gotta
find me in these the sequence of images here you never seen infinity war or endgame fucking
go make lunch and then come back and like figure it out here we go one two if you've never seen
endgame before it's okay all right okay i have no fucking idea wait hold on what's my magnifying
glass wait a minute you're gonna do something cheeky here me and like the big guy helmet
there it is you just put me like in the back here i'm just standing here with everybody
yeah that all right this one was pretty easy it's just like it's i'm like i'm not even like
the right are you i'm not even in like the uniform i'm just here that's fucking hilarious
all right i got it that one that's it for that one okay here we go here comes the next one
don't fucking help me here guys do not help me it's that's you don't want to
know and i need to get correct music i need like children's music
no this is fucking makeup tutorial music i don't want the makeup tutorial music
or like close-up of my hands diy hack video i don't no no i want children's
royalty-free music here this is gonna work all right let's do the next one
this could this could be an undertale okay hey but i'm kidding this is the this is undertale
ost the track 12 okay here we go i need my magnifier oh it's pac-man he loves the celtic
is that it no
this chuck schnoz will break pizza who else is here all right are you punching this guy in the
face easy beanbag sonic come on man am i missing anybody else oh i didn't i thought that was a
smoke oh shit there's dick dash to lead richard very cool i found me there i am i found it look
at that jet blue i okay wait is that actually in did you put that in here no all right well
that's pretty fucking cool let's do the next one hold on i need a new song i just noticed beanbag
sonic why is my come on computer to find i have to check to make a checklist here hold on find
i'm getting off camera for this one just because i need to you guys need to be able to see the
whole thing i find wall dad blue man chuck schnoz well sans undertale and auto what about me
i gotta get my checkbox here all right i there's auto this where sans i don't even need
magnify sans undertale chuck schnoz well where is it that's pretty well hidden that's good job
glue man found it that's me found me wall dad right there what's glue man probably back here
somewhere hidden okay there's way more characters in there than i'm finding but i can't find blue
man where's blue man where the fuck are you me again this green screen how am i finding every
single person but not glue man what the fuck is he magnifying glass please i'll take it
look back i don't see him where is he i seriously don't see him oh this is gonna take me forever
got him right there bingo game completed check done next children's song please oh my fucking
god what in the name of i holy shit hello jeremy help find and save auto from all the nine eight
five germa clones i have no fucking idea i have to start at the top i need to get that i gotta
magnify this i'm doing i'm doing a this is fucking funny what is that oh he's smiling
it's not even me i thought i was actually naked in this picture what is that what the fuck is
that guys this is this is like the detective at the police station has the board with all the
fucking images and all the notes and shit and i'm like the psycho murderer that they're trying to
track down
many strange photos this is my life in 200 images what am i looking for auto that's these half of
these are just scary hold on i want to get closer this one what the fuck is this picture
it's like the realistic bart simpson artist made blueberry this time all right got this one
me crying all right hold on is that kim's face twice on my face i think that's what that is
i'm fucking losing my mind right now i want to see them all oh
wait what is that i need to make this bigger jack nicholson what the fuck is that why am i
in like a weird like slug outfit why is that gumby a car when did i put on a gumby costume
when did i put on a gumby costume oh christmas that's right where's auto oh i hate this image
this image i hate this image i still have not found auto
this could also be every weird image that i've just taken from chat and put on the screen to me
that is me what's with the hair why why is my hair black did i like dye my hair look at that i love
that one too another image that i hate i hate this image too i want this picture where did you get it
wherever you got this picture i want it so bad that's son of the mask but you made him not have
green skin that's terrifying is that is that musk this is this is precious i want to frame this
what is coming out of my mouth where is auto oh i need to lean back what is this a calculator
i got him ding ding ding ding ding there's auto
these are so creepy oh this is great fuck is that picture from that's like an old camera
where did you get this i don't know where that picture's from
just in here is like some old photo of me in like high school that's fucking funny this is great i
love this awesome job on this this probably took a long time for you to make so thank great
fucking work this is awesome we could forget like the jim carrey like nerd neck the thing
let us smart click you want to smart click which one's your favorite well that's gonna be hard
all right i'll let you okay you guys have to smart click to find which one is your favorite
image on the screen that's not a bad idea i'm gonna make it can i make it any bigger
oh kind of but i'm like lose no i don't lose anything oh i don't lose anything all right
well good luck let me get that open all right what's your favorite image go ahead no don't
do it yet this needs to be authentic now it's authentic go ahead and click the screen i can't
where is that one i'm trying to see it looks like the mcchicken mayonnaise face the big chin
red shirt one the neuro story lecture dump i mean you guys might not be able to click down
the elon musk one the corn or i'm not sure it's that looks like it's i like the big like weird
pancake thing the big the big squished blueberry face is my favorite i think
oh the one is you guys clicking on the pizza
it's you as wally wheat that's awesome
all right let's actually i haven't taken any let me take a break we still have um we actually
don't have that much left to do we're almost done we have like four or five more of these and
then like a handful yeah we got like another probably half an hour 40 minutes not yet what
are you talking about we're not done yet we will be done very like we'll be done soon we'll be
done soon i'll be right back just want to go i haven't gone to the bathroom or anything let me
get some water and um let me get some water and get something to drink i'll be back in like two
three minutes drb what's up i'm back what are you guys doing yeah what is this oh that's
interesting let's go ahead and do a fucking comparison because you know like anybody that
ever wants to talk shit to me about getting older oh interesting let's see give me a second just
get it on here it is because i'm going to do a side-by-side comparison for you all would you
look at that interesting so hmm oh germa you're such a fucking boomer what a boomer you are
wow you're old huh this is like 20 fucking four years ago no big deal i morphed into this it was
like and i got bigger stronger that's not even a real image i'm sorry guys that's a fucking deep
fake i hate to be the guy that ruins everybody's party here make the colors the same how the fuck
am i gonna do that let me get a color here oh all right i'm done i'm done with this although
i'm gonna keep this filter though because i think it makes me look cool add film grain i don't think
i can add film grain to this well here's the greedy grinner i'll be taking that one and i've
got like fucking dots all over my face and they mapped it in my face and it's like a fully
animated cgi cutscene why don't you have that blizzard i feel like this hurts people's eyes
so get get that get that young motherfucker off the screen we've evolved into this man
that was just a boy we've turned into a man get this off too shut these off shut it all off
let's move on to the next one this is well uh this is a soccer game it's a soccer game i mean i
already i already it's i'm right here wait is that's wait hold on it's throwing me off here
somebody's throwing me off that's not me that's somebody in the raptor mask wait i need i need
my marker i gotta i gotta get my marker hold on what is this i do did you you do is that me
got it bingo done i love how you went in and you just you warped other people's faces for no
reason is anybody else why are we all at the like us soccer game oh there's another one
yeah that's shibby is that shibby no i think this is a guy at the game
okay who else we got i think that's it there i am who has the mask on the star is right here
got it let's keep going can you find the five foot four streamers so you can spot a few other
things um okay well first of all this where is where is this i mean i can see uh this is
obviously who doesn't love some good old uh ccc right it's a glue man is it is this oh is it i
don't what is this say it say what c c and c oh the coffee and the cheetos and then there's
chicken there as well interesting there i am found me done next slide please i think that's
all i can see in here always that fucking face i swear that's like gonna be my that's gonna be
my legacy is that fucking close-up of my like deranged face let's keep going oh boy now this
is a this is fully done here hey germa mites saw saw some real pog champ moments today
super jex fighting the green screen auto peaking a giant rat and a giant ant and three germas
few hysterical can you find them all to the germa mites over the world in jupiter now where's the
freelance police department germa where are they they are um they're currently unavailable
so we need super jex fighting the green screen which is right here auto peaking auto peaking
i need some more music let's go with uh how about what's up in the background turn off the smart
click is still on oh it is it is just still turned on whoops okay that's enough of that
all right auto peaking and a giant rat and giant ant and three germas there's one here
i do appreciate the technique i do like that it's i'm just right in the middle and i'm just sitting
here scanning everything but i got it so there's there's two more got the auto peaking there's one
another there's two giant ant giant ant the sky theory oh i love this this is awesome just win
forehead oh there's a giant ant the french fry ant what a lovable character i got the giant i need
the giant rat and then one more germa can you find the freelance police i sure can paul vera
undertaker fruit is demon lord the egg oh no what happened to she tell that's not good what
happened giant voice of rat there's the seagulls from that other weird fucked up game giant rat
this auto hey there you are so that's auto peaking giant rat giant ant and then i need one more
germa does this count that doesn't count that's not it wait no there it is okay that is what i'm
looking for show auto oh i got you there you are but that's odd michael that's true
hmm so where's third me i think that counts because i mean it's clipped up here right it's
yeah that's clipped up there the one in the ring well that's that's not me that's jex this one right
here or not right here got it done right there i didn't even see batboy he's just flying around
this is awesome a lot of uh work went into this so nice job this is great what's going on at the
top i i don't know i'm trying to figure out what that is yeah the chewing gums is best
there's a dab oh it's a dab oh that's okay yeah i see nice let's keep going oh boy oh boy
germa's trip to the beach can you find germa amongst the beach crowd i look like that find him
oh this is gonna be hard i'm gonna say you scam of my eyes no not by the tent the chewbacca not
not by chewbacca well if it were me i'd be right here right there got it got it there it is peeking
around the sign nice awesome nice job that was a good one too nice okay cool you're in the lower
left corner you know what you got that's right that's it all right let's keep going holy shit
greetings germaniacs holy fuck here i am out for another zany adventure this time in beautiful
las vegas but oh no it seems all these wacky germa 985 references have leaked into reality
can you find me amidst the chaos before cox turns off my stream i'm dressed as but legally
distinct from the beloved children's book character waldo wow this is awesome oh look at that for
is the owl okay bad boy there's so many references there's so much here this is
wonderful all right so i remember that that's from one of those what the plate ps2 game there's uh
the snake or otherwise the italics who says the wasps all right looking for me and i look like
where's waldo but i do not where's waldo that i love this part that's incredibly accurate
green screen is mr cheese nip sans of course got it got it right there yoink there it is right
right that's it right uh-huh let me get a little there it is i'm not i'm not done looking at this
picture though this is awesome super hot oliviers sims elvis what's his feet
all right we got santa a clown oh there's one guy what does it say the amazing presto
majestic poopoo peepee odd michael i love this this is great painting over the image
scout uh this is the old video what does it say cow slot machine there's a naked person
what whoreson wells right there widow maker aiming at them and up there's all this is
this is awesome this is insanely elaborate like every character is connected to every other
character next to them it's like a rube goldberg machine of references to the channel this is
awesome easy p oh no i'm okay i don't know what that is oh no waterman overboard
this is awesome why does uh why does pac-man have a big lump on his head do you get hit in the head
here are the 30 movie maker characters his brain fluid i think that's mitis it's italics
and star i think hey found me again there it is sea man most disturbing shit ever
bart simpson okay mario is fishing oh go fish i get it this is awesome let's keep going i think
we caught everything i got a good look at this uh flanker there's the witch which was supposed
to be an emote but i never did it this is oh there's oh this is i i have no words for this
is awesome jewel wizardry she told let's keep going the top 10 emotes that never left beta testing
all right i i'm apparently in this picture somewhere you're gonna stuff me down here with
the birds have i ever worn like a white sweater or something that would pick an image from that
just dump me in here or put maybe like in the claws or something like that i'm like trying to
grab one i'm trying to like grab a seagull found them you're drowning trying to save them what is
going on here these are a bunch of seagulls and what's what is this why is it like a giant fight
why are they like they're fighting each other they're like why what's what i don't understand
this this constant bird conflict something like that but all right let's keep going there i found
it good shit all right we have made it to spot the difference i've got my trusty pen here i do
want to get some music on for this because we are at the point of the stream where there's only about
five ten things left to do let's get let's get some relaxing music on
balding yes this guy's balding i'm talking like what is an incredibly relaxing tune
that you could just sink back into your chair and just go star do valley oh yeah
you got it absolutely that's a good one all right can you spot all eight differences
98.5 percent can't get more than six there's eight let's get my pen ready this is bobby
f bugleberry's um christmas themed halloween uh printer i'm i forgot completely forgot about
the printer printing out messages that thing didn't work that thing was supposed to print out
bit messages whenever they came through and it worked probably seven or eight times speaking
to the printer bingo no logo all right what about let's take a look at blueberry what am i eating
shito is not in this spot beanbag sonic is not in this spot that's what that's three
no pumpkin all right so that's four me we look back and forth here something on the tree
oh got it there's no uh hat belt oh this doesn't the tree doesn't have a shadow
one two three four five six there's two more look at the presents again what about the printer
or nothing with the paper one of the stripes is going to be gone or something oh shit there's one
more you gave him hair it's got to be something with the jacket or the pants no i got it it's
santa's nose no let me know santa's nose see that's right look red no red what i did i was
right about the glove i was one two three four five six seven five six i got it hey there it is
i'm not i didn't really i thought it was the one that's a good that's a good uh throw offer
got them all let's see the next one fortnight victory royale find all 11 differences for an
epic number one victory bl god okay let's start up here uh the balloon is in the sky here and not
here there are 11 yeah up there what about beanbag sonic anything in the tree hold on
what about the parachute right here stand in there not standing there fireman in the distance
not in the mountains over here something written what does that say something written here what
does that say love late streamer right okay uh garfield's censored you know i got a patch
right there i forgot there was a pickaxe in this game what about the generator it's gonna be one
of these like stains here flowers tail no tail on the rat how we go what we got one two three
four five six wait a minute something looks off here why why does this look off i can't tell
that all right uh dick dash leader russians patch is different i only got a couple more wrong three
four five six seven eight nine ten is one more thing what's the last thing it's gotta be something
down here something the shins that's correct no that's correct too these are both right
explosion in the back something there's 215 blades of grass on the top one and 214
blades of grass on the bottom one now that would just be bad game design i think it's something to
do with the explosion garfield i mean why put gar got it i knew it you don't put a garfield like
dick thing here without something underneath it done that was tricky it was good though i like
the fortnight i've never i don't like fortnight but i like the fortnight uh setting the local movie
theater purchased two different films by mistake the projectionist can't tell which one is the
real one can you find 20 differences between the posters 20 differences so that they know which
film is the genuine one tip one for text each part that's been replaced counts as one change
okay there are many subtle changes but small differences in position don't count right so
oh this is a half a quarter of an inch taller than this one no all right look at 20 we got
a i'm gonna do a different color here let's just do like red and i'm also gonna make it smaller
all right for instance we got already right here this is a different color
no i'm gonna go back to yellow it's easy to see that all right let's start at the top though no
okay you got the germa son back here no son starring germa 985 jeremy elbertson and jerry harrington
okay during germa 985 right jeremy elbertson no jex sorry and second germa
yeah yeah i can't see the yellow yellow couldn't be a worse color well what do you want me to do
orange i've made the line sticker what about green that's a good day that shows up pretty well
okay all right i'm looking at the wand all right you got nothing there's no i'm not wearing the
cape in this one the movie versus the movie uh mouth open with the tongue hanging out not in this one
anything else on that helmet height is just a number and so is 985 he's not smart he's not
brave he's infectious all right well this whole thing wait did it say each part that's been
replaced counts as one change so this would be what two three i would okay i'll count this one
as two that's like kind of two right okay what about the face over here my mouth on this one
i'm clothes lipped in this one not wearing the police badge with the sunglasses they look normal
i'll put the hands down here does this hat count here does that count kind of i mean that's pretty
subtle but i'm gonna i'm gonna say yeah down here mouth does that my mouth being open a little more
and c17 versus r coming soon no dot dot dots it's his whole face i guess it is kind it is right
no no no no i don't think that's correct directed by erasmus rotorosmas rotor i wrote i'm gonna
sneeze again that's jumpscare
all right so what we got erasmus rotor odomasis rotor odomasis produced by erasmus rotamidus
executive producer erasmus rotamidus one of these words is gonna be different written by catering by
burger boy uh-huh that's one screenplay by soundtrack edited by soundtrack by
wait what soundtrack by funding by thank you you various artists viewers like you i feel like this
is not oh here we go this too this box what were the lightsaber what am i missing i think it is the
chin this is different all right what about back up here anything with the or i'm what am i at like
18 19 it's like one or two more things these mouths are different yes they are no this look
that's different look look look look i'll get the magnifying glass i'll prove it look check it out
take a look at that see the the brightness has been turned up on it remember this thing's
just subtle differences that's a very subtle difference but it's there so i got them all the
middle face too is wrong yeah i guess like the eyes too like up here all right how many do i have
one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen
sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty 21 22 23 24 25 25 uh all right i think i got them all
middle face is one all right well then 24 the j is wrong 25 what's with the lightsaber how is it
different he's got over completion shirt i don't see it the brightness on the shirt got it 26
that was good shit let's keep going i'll go can you spot the eight differences between these two
pictures i love this this is awesome give me the original source of that i want this the source
it's sans auto okay well obviously there's a giant fucking spider on my head here and then
i have no idea what this is is that a is it an unreal tournament weapon
there's eight differences i only see one there are no other differences in this whole picture
uh are you serious oh that's the body of the spider i thought it was like a fucking
gears of war weapon or something right okay i didn't know that was the body i don't know how
whatever that was a good one let's keep going you ever flew to vegas and is now suffering from
traumatic hallucinations due to eating his friends on the balloon that's not confirmed it didn't
happen help him determine what is real by spotting the 10 differences this is fucking stupid
this is stupid fucking garfield t-pose is the first thing i have to see
so uh i don't what do i even have to say about this do i have any words at all not really
how many are there i think i got them all one two three four five six seven what about the
rats i'm going on the rat what is that thing that's like vinny right that's like the vinny
meat thing that's that's vinny's meat right all right what else what's going on with elvis
anything no i don't see any difference with elvis that's the stupid the one bush in all of this
whole valley here this gnome yeah is just fucking with my head i think i got them all
anybody see anything else but which one is real um this one this one has the sun this is jupiter
jupiter's not in our sky the sun is this one's the real one check please and pac-man's yellow
guys really i feel like there's something with the rat but i i don't see anything
i'm just gonna circle just in case got it i'm doing that fucking walk since i was like 17
all right i think is there any more is there one more there are spot the eight differences
between the alternate realities well i'll tell you you missed you missed a very very very good
opportunity here for this to be like this and then like me to be hurt on the ground with like
a sword in me from pinball because i can tell you that that would be not correct that'd be not a
real reality well first of all shito is pink uh this is a mcchicken and uh i mean why would i
ever order this when i could order that except what the hell have you put on here why would you
ever put that shredded disgusting fucking lettuce no it's making that way with the sky get the hat
yeah right here what about the sides you guys love garfield i think you just pretend to not like
i think you guys really love garfield i'm convinced slug down here all right what are
we at what about the wave a patch the burger something with pinwheel yeah right here different
emote shoes head pinwheel one two three four five six you got missing a lantern up here
i think i got it one two three four five six seven eight got it have we reached the end
hello gerba if you're reading this transmission we need your help demon grandpa traveled back
in time in an attempt to reverse his ultimate untimely death in doing so he created a paradox
the timeline is destabilizing causing anomalies to appear spot all 13 differences to restore the
timeline and save the world well right off the bat he said he's not wearing a fireman shirt
okay
beanbag sonic was not here auto was not here god damn it but look i've talked about this a million
i'm gonna now we'll go over this after okay there's that is me ear pods that was a real
that subtle there's an ear pod oh somebody's just missing okay the top hat
okay one two three four five six seven eight nine different color oh wait different design
i thought you were gonna do like a instead of you're gonna put the thumb out or something
right here it's on the other side i'm getting close hold on one two three four five six seven
eight nine ten eleven twelve is one more over here i know she does blocking it the pin the
the dots there it's a rat done bingo completed 13 all right very very cool all right now it's
time for me to shut the music off cut the music we're going in fucking tight on this one
i want you look at i want to show you something here this is fucking important
let's get it let's get a line here i want you to look at this area here right here we're gonna
go and even close me i would like you to see take a look at everybody's arms all right this is
important because why on earth let's go over this quickly so i'm bending my knees right now
they're bent the i'm i'm leaning forward bending my knees and slumping down right now the i i if
i were to extend my knees and look at look at i'm out in front i'm not side to side here look at
this shoulder shoulder shoulder shoulder shoulder shoulder right no no i'm in i'm i'm out in front
down see i'm leaning forward and down if i extend these legs i come up from here to here right here
is the line where i would be if i were standing up straight i don't know how many times i have to
go over this i'll go over this a thousand times take a look at this too i want you to see this
are you fucking kidding me like are you serious that is an arm wrestle you lose arm look at this
all right look at this down here and yes that's another thing that i've had to explain before
but do you think that my look i hold on this is the ground you want to talk about like oh
i've measured how far the ground was the ground is right here do you really fucking seriously
think in a million years that when i rest my arms on my sides my hands are like a foot and a half
from the ground that would mean i would have to have like four and a half foot long arms and that's
just evidence here that's i'll draw a little thing for you just to get this out of the way
here we go he's like a ruler right here right here's the ruler this is like this is like five
feet right here this is five feet five this is like six feet right here right there right there
right there right there it's actually kind of funny because this is actually how fucking tall
i probably am you're doing me a favor here you're showing like how tall i actually am
that's a clean five seven and a half to five eight it's betting on shoes it's like right here
maybe it maybe like a hair taller it's a nerd neck let's take a look at that neck what do you think
all right neck no fucking around let's go back to the original that's a nice fucking neck i look like
a pizza hut worker what the fuck are you talking about what does that even mean what does a pizza
hut worker mean i guess you know what i'm i'm gonna you want i'm gonna show you guys something
i'm gonna show you guys something i'm gonna get you know what you know what i'm gonna do i am going
to hit up some of these wonderful people here and i'm gonna ask for other i'm gonna ask for pictures
from this event where i'm standing next to some of these people who i'm standing next to some of
these people and we'll get the proof the real proof i will recreate this whole photo yeah i've
seen that clip from slin he's taking the piss he's playing the game he's playing he's in on the joke
i'm fucking this goddamn tall right here right there you know what fuck it i'm like up here
extend my neck this way i'm like this fucking tall what's the next one now sometimes you're
gonna just prove something it's just so fucking obvious i remember i remember looking at this
picture and i fucking remember going holy shit that doesn't look good that looks real fucking bad
and then it was like i was like ah you know whatever i don't think anyone's gonna notice
or care and it turned into like a three year long issue four years later little did i think
that this fucking photo measure yourself with a tape measure on stream i will
no i don't know how about this i just just see me at twitchcon and we'll fucking stand next to
each other all right how about this if you come up to me at twitchcon and you and you think i'm
under five five and i'm right let's say i'm over five six five seven you owe me five thousand
dollars will you take that bet are you gonna take that bet oh i'm gonna make a lot of money at
twitchcon all right let's go help one of oh this is shito help one of jimmy's clones accidentally
stabbed himself so hard that he somehow managed to create an alternate dimension where there are
only ten subtle differences pretty boring actually seriously you can't even make an interesting
dimension damn clone this is awesome this is like fucking fantastic all right let's go i'm
gonna go with uh first of all i have a sans eye right off the bat fireman's in my mouth
fucking wicked bald uh glue man is facing the other direction oh wait glue man's also facing
the other direction i think over here this is different one of my sound cubes all right what
else what about the eye the hair chin is extended on this one sooner or later people are gonna
think that that's like how long my real chin is and then it's like oh wow germa's not only five
two he also has like a big goblin chin that one's actually true though unfortunately for me yeah
that is actually true so i mean what can i what am i gonna do about that right you measure my chin
at twitchcon we'll see if it's fucking six and a half inches long all right what else we got here
one two three four five six seven there's still three more things what about anything else on the
earbud looking for the eyebrows the nose right here three four five six seven eight nine one
more thing something with the arm finger hair nose no oh you're yeah you're right i would not
have gotten that if i didn't cheat that's very subtle sweaty armpits you can't see that from here
we need to actually just take a second and just marvel at how great this is this is fucking
fantastic this looks like it's still from a video awesome i mean but it is yen wen so i mean that
they just make consistently fucking incredible work good shit are we done no there's more there
is like a couple more i think i thought that was it bonus feature spot the difference help the rats
follow the real germa okay this is great too they're all good they're all great open mouth here
closed j the music is different missing this and missing a note all right what about up to your
ear they're different shirt fireman versus the night sky hair eyes mouth rats let's see
tail tail tail is different whiskers whiskers whiskers eyes are different no tail versus tail
what about legs they all have four legs oh no you don't you have an extra leg i hope you have a
third whisker what about the noses nose nose nose nose nose nose nose what about the eyes
ball you all have two eyes the germ is the note that's the only difference
uh okay yeah that makes sense there's a height difference don't don't get me going again all
right anything else yeah there i know there is i've seen it i see it go get the ruler i'm gonna
fucking get a ruler the bottom one is bending down hey watch it chito chito i think that's it
you guys see anything else i think i got it all very cute good to go awesome awesome job very
cute very cool what's next hey remember this one i do let's do it again 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18
19 20 21 22 23 24 yeah just loop it no there were all the activities uh that was took six hours to
do that i thought it was going to be shorter i thought this was only going to be like a couple
hours but there was a lot there was a ton of uh contributions so there still is a bunch of jokes
and a bunch of brain teasers so what i'm going to do is i'm going to compile these jokes and brain
teasers i'm going to pull out some of my favorites we're going to go over them not today because i
did not realize that i'd been streaming for six hours i was kind of having too much fun
i was really only supposed to stream for three or four but i was having too much fun with all
this stuff i did most of the stories the stories were ridiculous too jokes and brain teasers i can
compile and do them and i might just do that i might just pull them out randomly like whenever
i feel like just doing something just hanging out there's a shitload of them yeah i am going to bid
you all farewell this is the last time you are all going to see or hear my voice and face
until the 21st got a lot to do the next time this stream is live you will be at the carnival
he tricked us into giving him free jokes for the rest of the year and that's the play you figured
it out the carnival i i have a i pinned a tweet and i have a thing you can do have not hashtag
exclamation point carnival i'll tell you the date it's 10 21st starting at around 12 p.m eastern
that's right i'm going back to eastern time for this but there's a lot to do in the meantime the
few companies that are involved i we have to pin down a lot of things when are we going to get
access to the robots where would it end when and where we will be streaming this from there's an
event coordinator and there is the robot company so there is a lot to do i will see you guys
saturday those of you still sticking around we will be doing the end of the
stream stuff i'm gonna go like this and i'm gonna go like this thank you for that tonight i knew i
was trying the reason why i wanted to really do this this is gonna sound it's not gonna sound bad
or anything but it's gonna sound uh maybe weird to some of you this was a test of community night
stuff this is a test i tested you i think you you i think it was great i wanted to do something
chill and i wanted to have a bunch of community contributed stuff artwork i wanted to see how
long it would take to do this kind of stuff i have a pretty good idea of submissions and
all the mods that were involved in it too thank you everybody for making the stream like this
happened i knew i wanted something the day before i was pretty much going to leave to just be
relaxing and hang out and just see how a community night went this is a community night this is the
first one essentially is the one what you just watched thank you for being a part of it let's
continue on to the bits earlier today we had five dollars from bake me home you should have a
contest to design a germa odin emote don't give us any prompts just let us come up with what we
think germa odin should be i probably will do another emote contest eventually i have i have
like a lot of slots now they need to be filled i just need to get on it but that's not a bad idea
thank you slalom for the five dollars my colonoscopy went well thanks germ and then
they say come to brazil uh that's i'm really happy to hear that it went well i told you it's easy it's
a lot more strange and nerve-wracking than the procedure actually is so i'm glad to hear it went
well thank you so much for the five dollars germa wild one wild two wild three uh yeah the prep is
the worst part of this the the thing about a colonoscopy is just not being able to eat
once you cross that threshold of not being able to eat solid food for two or three straight days
is when you start to succumb to madness just drinking clear chicken broth and eating jello
is gah it's horrible and the worst part is even when after you're done you still you're all kind
of fucked up so you you're not the second you get out of a colonoscopy you're not sitting there
going oh where can't wait to go to burger king no you're like on like drugs and shit you just
want to go home and go to bed and just relax and maybe eat something small but i'm glad to
hear it went well thank you for the five dollars thank you to sam freelance police for the five
dollars germa i gave you five dollars on the dragon's lair stream but you got coxed so you
never saw it i'm sorry about that i hate when that happens because it just deletes every sub
and every bit that was there and then having to go back and sort of reread everything is almost
like that a day or two has gone by and it's none of it it's relevant none of it's relevant anymore
for the day in that few hours i just always feel fucking terrible when it happens so
we sometimes try to go back and i've done it a few times going back and reading them
but i'm sorry that it happened i wish i could correct it i wish that stuff didn't happen but
does but they say uh i've been watching your stuff since i was like 13 i'm 19 now
i just left my home country of portugal to move to germany for game design university
this is my first night all alone you have any tips on living alone far away from your parents
thanks for all the laughs and for being with me on the journey uh that sounds like quite a journey
yeah congratulations going to a game design university it's awesome the i don't know how
relevant this is to you but it was very relevant for me and i don't know what the
obviously it might not be possible with you know being at a university or wherever you're living
at the university or something but i lived alone for a very long time and the number one thing
that i would say to anybody that lives alone is get a dog get a dog get a cat get an animal get
some kind of companion because then you're not and if that's not possible you know obviously if
you can't bring into a living situation a a friend like a pet a companion right then the best thing
you can do is to try to find stuff to do that you're interested in that you can find other
people that like the same shit that you do i've said this advice before but everybody's on the
same fucking page nobody knows anybody and all you have are your interests everything else is
left completely at the door nobody knows anybody nobody knows how you were in high school nobody
knows who your friends are nobody knows what your life is like or who you kind of are as a person
so you're only basing stuff on interests and if you can find a group of people that are interested
in the same thing you kind of just start at that i like this you like this too i don't know who you
are and you don't know me either but we're literally sitting next to each other in this fucking class
and i like that shit too and then you just start talking you just start hanging out you start doing
group projects a lot of colleges do that they do group projects and they put you together and
that's really the the way to do it or have like i said get an animal because if you have an animal
you are you're never alone because that whatever like for instance auto right i was always alone
in that place that i was living in it's just me and auto and that was it and you know sometimes
it was a little weird you know i'd get up and i'd make food and it's just like okay like
i'm like creeping up the stairs and there's no humans but no i but it didn't matter because
within five seconds of me thinking about that oh there's auto lying on the pillow hey auto and
he's like hi i'm here i'm happy to see you so you get to essentially have that kind of interaction
with something take it for a walk play around lie down on the couch with them and stuff like that
it was it was always very easy to just chill with your little furry friend but hopefully
that helps good luck take care thank you for the five dollars sam freelance police appreciate it
50 thanks for the four dollars and eight cents i bet you there is at least one triangle picture
there was i did not use it uh the other one that i was considered there was a there's one or two
others that i didn't like maybe three maybe four total well i i've you know 2020 hindsight
there was like three or four of the of the vine meats and i was gonna use one and then i was like
oh wow i just glossed over them and instead i put in the just circle of the germa sun it was just
the one that was a circle i don't know why i was like yeah i guess i'll just not put that i don't
know why i didn't put that in i think it's because i saw two or three of them in a row and there was
like three or four fireman's in a row right there too so i was like oh shit i don't want to have
maybe i should do like maybe just change it up yes there was a triangle it's if you want to do it
it's pretty hard it's in that discord right now you can go look at it right now
nova ostra thanks for the three dollars hey germo you're the best streamer on twitch thank you you
always make me laugh no matter what you do love you that's just an insanely nice thing to have
anybody ever say thank you i just i'm just doing my thing here that's that's what that's all i'm
gonna do and that's all i ever will do i'm glad you enjoy the streams thank you hey plank thank
you plank v2 for the 20 bucks 20 dollars from plank if you went back 10 years and asked yourself
where you would be would you have pictured this thanks for making my days uh no there was no way
to predict that this is gonna happen because it didn't exist something like live streaming
whether it's video games or edited video type content or irl content or this stuff didn't exist
so there was no way to ever know this would ever be a thing that anybody did
even back with youtube youtube yeah i mean youtube was a thing but i never knew that i never thought
at all that youtube was going to turn into a way for me to make like money and be like a job
essentially in no way yeah there was you couldn't there was no monetization on videos
when i was making videos that happened a couple years really after i started at least a year or
two and then once it became knowledgeable that you could get ad revenue from your videos
the whole thing erupted erupted people started coming in and holy shit we can make money from
our youtube videos now and the whole space just went crazy i just kind of kept doing what i was
doing and i'll be honest not very much has changed in regards to how i approach what i do here
but no i there's no way i would have known what would i but what would i've done if i didn't do
it i would work with animals or something i've done volunteer work before with animal um
oh i can't think of the word animal shelters i've done
volunteer work with animal shelters i really maybe would have tried to been like a vet tech
or something i liked computers maybe i would have done some computer stuff it stuff i don't know i've
talked about a few times but i don't know i can't tell you who knows in 10 years i might be doing
that i can't predict you what's going to happen in five years 10 years no idea you could be a
mosquito doctor uh we had big bits just coming right now from the man himself phylactery lich
50 dollars from phylactery 5000 bits thank you again for the ultra money they say hey germa i'm
not going to be able to watch the carnival live i have to work so i can afford to give you more
subs can you go ahead and move it to sunday that would be great i tell you i i better be like
one percent of your income i better be like point two percent of your income he's he's getting
closer to owning 20 he's got 20 30 percent of the stream he doesn't own 50 of the company yet don't
do it no i can't change that that date is not something i am able to change remember it's not
just me i have hired two separate companies to make the stream possible all the robot contracting
out with andy mark to make the robots and then the company that is producing the actual stream
portion event location and crew they're hey can i do it on sunday instead it's like what the
fuck are you talking about no it's set in stone with these two different companies
and as much as it would you know every you always want more time but i don't think we don't need it
i mean you guys gotta remember i this has been something that's been being worked on for a few
months more than that so it's not a thing where it's like oh we can move it i guess i had to
liquidate bald coin for this one but there are multiple companies involved i mean i'm not
changing the date but if that if it ever came down to it if it was kind of just me and another
person and maybe one other thing and we contracted out robots and now there's like 20 people that are
involved in this split between two potentially even three different companies so no that's that
is that's completely out of my hands at this point we all agreed on a date that things could happen
when people were available for things when this company was going to be available
to produce it and where they were going to produce it those are all things that i cannot change
do we have to fight over the robots in a way in a matter of speaking yes in a matter of speaking
yes for control you know what i'm saying i'm prepared i'm prepared but let's go back what
we were doing before phylactery again you've given fucking hundreds and hundreds of dollars today
and yesterday and day before and a day before and like a week before that and two weeks before that
it's a ton of money dude but thanks thank you also to uh grack store for the 10 bucks
draw as fast as you can and then they wink what's the wink for draw as fast as you can
thanks to the 10 dollars crack so i appreciate it uh jack the mac thanks to the five dollars
germ i got some bad news i got a tip on grill master uh barbecue we all know that you destroyed
him but i've come to learn that he is slowly regenerating in the darkest recesses of castle
griffin steed he's weak but you're the only one who knows how to stop him please help us all
thanks for the five dollars thank you trauma advocate for the 10 bucks thousand bits
germ i don't have time to watch your streams but i love catching up on your goofs on youtube
thanks and hope you keep up the good work you can thank mac and effectator for
making all of the second germa content they do a great job wonderful wonderful wonderful stuff
thank you so much for the 10 dollars and i'm glad you can uh at least kind of catch up on
youtube that was the point of that channel is for people that don't or can't want to sit around
and watch an entire five six seven plus hour stream there's another avenue for you to
experience at least some of the stuff that we did that's why it's there
hey happy birthday theis for the thanks for the 10 dollars happy birthday theis i'm on break i just
stopped by to throw bread at you throw bread what's oh money money right well hey thanks
hopefully you had a good break thanks for the 10 bucks we also had a very good cobalt thanks for
the three bucks berry gold berry gold gold bold berry berry gold i can't fucking say this name
merrygold round berry gold oh my god berry good cobalt sometimes i i get locked and my brain just
tries to read a word and it gets stuck but thank you uh to you for the three dollars you did it
yeah my my mind sometimes just runs around in a circle but thank you for the three dollars they
say germa i'm in a depressive rut and your second germa channel is keeping me going these days uh
these the days those days that i just stay in bed thank you for being a great streamer and a
wonderful being thanks for three dollars and like i just said i'm happy that the youtube channel as
well is there for people to enjoy i really hope you feel better when you get in a rut it's
sucks hopefully you can figure it out hopefully you can ride it out and figure out what you need
to do thank you for three dollars i'm glad you enjoyed that channel thank you so much for the
three bucks and then here was the 69 subs from phylactery every time i always have when i have my
stream labs open over here and i get to a point where somebody like phylactery gave
30 40 50 60 plus subs it is just a it's just a huge scroll it's an overwhelming scroll
so thank you again for that and then you topped it off again with 28
thanks a lot man the ultra scroll yeah and then tath tathly bash tathly bash thanks for the
ten dollars thousand bits my girlfriend and i've been watching you since the tf2 days
uh you may very well be one of the greatest entertainers of our time
and catching the stream is always a highlight of our night that is quite a statement that's
thank you for that i never thought i would ever hear anybody say something like that so
first of all thanks i i really appreciate it and then they say uh catching the stream is always a
highlight of our night i'd love to see you play through the jack and dexter trilogy soon as it
would bring together my favorite series with my favorite streamer stay legendary new england
misses you i miss new england too all the time but i love las vegas leave a las vegas as they say
but thanks jack and dexter um i've never played them i know that people love them
i don't have one second in any of those games i wonder if that would be fun to stream might
just start at one didn't they remake them there's a remaster right
there's the jack and dexter remake should i do the original or should i play the remake
remaster once play the remake okay it's just a remaster all right all right yeah put it on the
list put in the recommended channel i'll see it and i'll put it down their hd ports that's all
right though i'm gonna get the credits on screen we're just about at the end here i'm flying up
here they are again thanks everybody for the subs this is an insane amount of you know and
some of you are responsible for a shitload of these people i hope that i can continue
to make you laugh and make you happy hopefully this coming weekend is one of those
locations because this channel is seeing a a huge amount of people and money and
i'm gonna try so thanks again to all of you this stream will be very interesting regardless thank
you to cold warhol for the thousand bits ten bucks howdy germa hope you're doing well i want
you to know that i really appreciate all the time and effort that's been put into the carnival
by you and everyone else working on it and that'll be absolutely worth it lots of love and have a
safe flight yeah i'm i can't wait this is the type of shit that i want to do fucking way more
often and this is this this is the stepping stone to do it thank you so much for the 10 bucks
guild hero thanks for 10 bucks love you germa you always know how to make my bad days great
well i hope you have i hope you have less of them hope you have more good days than bad thank you
for the ten dollars appreciate it take care of yourself we also had five dollars from bone jackal
hey germa great stream as usual buddy but next time you turn on face game you should probably
scrub down your tongue first what i know this was the big community book stream but you really
didn't need to roll out the white carpet for us what what did i do scrub your tongue what did i
have like gunk on my tongue what was it does anybody know what they're talking about i don't
think i ever opened my mouth to show you my tongue disgusting tongue bacteria what it's just a joke
i i i'm assuming but i don't even know what it's a reference to well thanks for the five dollars
bone jackal appreciate it apple ship thanks for the 250 hey man just want to say thank you for
another wonderful stream let you know how much i'm looking forward to the carnival i put it on my
calendar and cleared my schedule and although i haven't been here long you genuinely improved
my quality of life by a ton you're a constant source of inspiration comfort and good vibes
and i cannot wait to see what you do next to have a good one thank you apple shift and
we're happy to have new people you know the more the merrier the more people the merrier
i hope you enjoy the stream on saturday thanks again hey skitter leaf thanks the five dollars
they say subway subway subway subway subway for the bonus bits thank you first time donator love
you streams they really helped me get through my work days pikmin's my favorite video game franchise
it would mean the world to see you play one of them add these to the list jack and dexter the
pikmin stuff uh see you at the carnival see you at the carnival should be fun hey alamanda thanks
for the five dollars can't always make it to the streams because of uni but i watched the vods
religiously thought i'd send some love you deserve it thank you for the five dollars just somebody
rolling in and dropping five bucks thank you thank you thank you thank you and then they
subscribed right after that like literally right after that so thank you again back to back there
i have a little bit of a frog in my throat i said remember i told you that on face cam on i've
burped like seven times since it's been off and then alamanda gave five community subs too
all in the span of back to back to back they gave five dollars they subscribed and then they
subscribed five people thank you thank you that's i i still just can't believe
i can't believe it i'm glad you have fun here thank you uh we have uh joke nigh
for three bucks they just say kappa pogchamp and then pogchamp again thank you for the three
dollars appreciate that dork cube thanks for the 250 what do you think the lady behind the
walgreens photo counter would say if you asked to have a board of 985 pictures of yourself blown up
so you could hang it on your wall well i don't think that's uh necessarily strange what would
be strange is the subject matter of all of those photos because let's say i was doing a thing
where hey this is me this is all my baby pictures all the way through when i was two into when i
was five here's my first day of school here's to me and my friends and you have hundreds of
pictures like a collage of your whole life people do that the only difference is this is scary
pictures of me manipulated to make me look as scary as possible all over the last same time
period i think that they would be more curious and concerned about that than the amount of pictures
but no probably i don't know maybe they wouldn't say anything but thanks to the 250 dork cube thank
you gnarly for the 250 fun stream tonight if that blueberry germa face doesn't become an emote i'll
piss can't wait for saturday have a good week it really should it's too good have a good week to
you too hopefully we see you saturday invader z thanks for the five dollars these streams have
made me laugh and smile harder more than i have in the last three years and i'm so excited for
the carnival i took off work for it i hear that frequently that people have taken work off or
taken time off of something to see this and do this so hopefully hopefully it's worth it hopefully
you think it's worth it that was worth doing thank you hey flug boy thanks for the 250 they
say just to bring back this when i met you at pax i'm five nine and i'm slouching and my friend on
the left is six feet tall would you look at this interesting your friend on the left is six feet
tall wow i mean i look like a fucking psycho in this picture but i'm gonna put it on stream
oh this is the ultimate fucking proof this is the ultimate proof thank you so much for giving this
to me look at that this dude six feet tall right next to me i mean don't don't don't pay attention
to like this fucking face holy shit dude let me see i look like i'm fucking high i'm just
gonna leave this on for the rest of the stream i've ruined the picture no i didn't this is this is a
good picture let me tell you by comparison this is a great photo of me i take awful pictures i can
never take pictures i look like shit in every photo i've ever taken of myself ever i look awful
i cannot take photos i don't know what to do with myself i could be on video all day
but the second that you i have to have a still face i nope not gonna happen here's that one
image that you wanted what do you mean what's this one image but thank you flug boy for this one
right yes i did want this image very desperately i love it great good shit but thank you flug boy
for that documented evidence and proof that i am a large person thank you c4g thanks for the 250
germa i have to use the stupid sandwich emoji to give you extra money what happened to the brain
to you're explaining it right now never mind thanks for the 250 germa caveman what's the
context to use that though i feel like germa caveman would show up less than germa tv does
thank you c4g espada escalata thanks for the 250 just want to take a look on the carnival stream
and i hope the flight goes smoothly looking forward to dunking you on saturday before your
robot army takes over the world good luck it ain't gonna be easy the english alphabet thanks for 10
bucks a thousand bits germa you're the best great stream thank you for always being you thank you
english alphabet i really appreciate it and thank you for your 10 dollars another 10 dollars came
in from mary gr thanks for all the fun tonight really love seeing all the love from the community
and all the old references no it's great there's a lot of people in this community that are really
good at stuff they're really talented artists here really really funny people really funny
fucking video editors and shit that you're everywhere i have to do this stuff you understand
because you guys you guys are so fucking funny and talented and it's ridiculous what am i not
going to do something like this i have to showcase it thank you bible black for the 10 community subs
right now thank you 10 more people just got subbed eventually it's gonna eventually everybody will
be at this point he did it he said it don't talk what are we talking about he said it he said it
he said it he said it what did i do it's a it's porn oh but thank you mary gr for the 10 bucks
and also thank you for the 10 community subs right there from uh bible black i'm unaware whatever
i'm always unaware that's how i don't know hey pigeon thanks for the five dollars
five bucks from pigeon they say put up a poster with your logo on it asking if anybody knew who
you were and if they did to add me on discord nobody responded saying they knew you but still
you're a huge factor determining who is a good friend material just something i think you should
know put up a post where'd you put a poster up what do you mean poster i put up a poster with
your logo on it like on a telephone pole to say hey did anybody know this streamer he's missing
call me he's this tall they also say oh they say two semesters ago in college right there's the
follow-up okay well uh there you go well thanks for the five bucks and i'm sorry that you didn't
get any uh any leads but thank you hey pinwheel 64 thanks for the six dollars when are we going
to get ecto shack two uh i don't know when are we gonna get any old like new grounds material
that i did when we're gonna get salt what am i gonna do salty swamp three it's turbo's birthday
soon you answered pinwheels question lordel's new stream over screen looks good this is not it
no i have a i have you know there's a lot of things old you know college and high school projects
that i worked on before new ground stuff all of the things that i was doing when i was younger
you know i am now i am now me and i just do me and whatever the fuck i do is what i do and that's
pretty much it i don't have a plan for anything that's really important if there's one thing you
need to know about me that's very important i don't have a plan for anything i just kind of
do whatever my plans are usually like one month in advance a week in advance potentially even a
day in advance i don't even have a plan for the 21st oh shit oh i'm gonna i'm fucked then
no i'm kidding but thank you pinwheel for the five dollars six dollars actually
pinwheel 64 that's actually a pretty great username i will tell you hey superintendent
chalmers thanks for 250 uh germa i made a louis anderson emote in may of 2017 and completely
forgot about it i recently rediscovered it and made it into a bttv emote germa louis oh god louis
anderson well do you have like a link how do i see it i want to see it i need a link we posted it
where where is it it's not on the it's not on the bit message oh there it knows edit not everyone
has bttv oh is this it right here well there it is let's put it on the screen why not
okay i'm okay i just realized this shit was still on the screen that's gotta go the first
time i looked over at obs in like 15 straight minutes well there it is thank you superintendent
chalmers for uh revisiting back in 2017 enable it enable it i have to i gotta fucking enable a lot
of things i really do and i'm just so slow to the punch on a lot of this stuff but thank you
thank you clueless sniper for the 250 hey germa just want to wish you good luck at the carnival
before you leave try not to cause a robot uprising while you're gone i'll try i will try hey uh
sha shads fen thanks for the 250 germa a friend of ours wanted to flex on you by showing you their
rebranding i mean this rebranding like it for the business you may be short but we will always
love you the same thanks for being my literal number one comedian flex on you by showing you
his rebranding okay i probably should i should have seen that coming i could have seen that
coming i don't know what the fuck i was thinking louis just moved what are you talking about thank
you too shads fen for that appreciate it thank you also to sir newt for the this 27 dollars from
sir newt thank you sir newt really appreciate it they say enjoy my money germa uh i i will put it
to good use i will try to put it to as much use as i can however i can do that that's a lot of
fucking money thank you sir newt whether it's a dollar five cents 27 dollars 100 dollars or zero
if you don't give money ever just thanks for being here thanks for watching that's i wish
that there was more that i could say whenever anybody gives me a lot of money but whenever
you know like for instance we're talking about like oh my god somebody is like responsible for
a thousand subs i can't fucking believe that shit i can't believe that somebody would give
me 27 bucks i can't like i'm shocked i'm floored i'm humbled i thank you for ever doing something
like that i hope i put it to good use but thank you also thank you to apple shift for the 250
one more thing i was rewatching your tearless stream and i just wanted to say that we both have
the exact same order for taco bell the cheesy gordita crunch with nacho cheese Doritos logos tacos
yes that's the best thing on the whole menu and just like to thank a fellow man of taste
ps i'm five one so if we ever met you'd be seven inches taller than me see see well it
don't matter how tall you are don't let anybody ever tell you that way how tall you are how skinny
you are how big you are how you don't just don't even listen to them take louis off the screen what
what are you will you guys relax what are you doing take louis off the screen okay louis is
off the screen don't worry what were you saying oh the cheesy gordita crunch right no it's absolutely
it's the best it is the best item on the whole menu so yeah i of course it's like it is the best
thank you to uh nicolai does gaming thanks for the five dollars appreciate it five bucks
and they say uh love your content man watch your second german channel all the time and i hope to
start tuning into your streams more yeah um second channel is a huge huge deal it does such a good
job at having people be able to see things if they can't catch streams i'm so happy with it
if you catch more streams then i'm i'll be glad to see you thanks for coming around thank you
we also had five dollars from flug boy who says i will say when you when i did meet you i was
quite surprised at you being pretty much the same height as me the same height as you right
as the memes really did fuck with that heart wait wait what'd you say i will say when i
did meet you i was quite surprised at you being pretty much the same height as me the memes really
did fuck with that harsh thank you for showing my ugly mug on stream pretty much the same height as
me yeah i know right don't ever listen to what anybody ever tells you on the internet okay
almost nine and a half times out of ten this shit is not real so you gotta you gotta decipher what
is real and what is fake it's hard but thank you so much plug boy i really appreciate that we also
had another five dollars come in from nikolai does gaming again i don't have that emote i'll
link you pictures from my trip to russia though but trip to russia hope you have a good time what
are you guys saying what are you guys saying what help help help help help run from what louis louis
louis on screen there's nothing i'm looking at obs right now there's nothing there you guys are
gonna need to relax but thank you uh nikolai appreciate it bala koala thanks for the six
dollars and sixty cents uh something is something this is something that i something that i something
that i said today that was the clip that says i'm five four that's not right that is inaccurate
why does this clip have sixty one thousand views that's inaccurate how many times did you guys
watch this did did like a hundred of you guys watch this like six thousand fucking times
ten of you guys watched this six thousand times why does this have so many views it was on reddit
why was this on reddit what what does this why would this be on reddit oh god thank you
for that appreciate it and that is where the stream is gonna end take care everybody see you
soon wish me luck i got a lot of work to do you'll see me again on saturday for hopefully a really
really really fun time hopefully it will be take care all of you i'll see you soon enjoy the carnival
see you on the 21st take care good night you never see any tall people there getting tall
i stopped at the big and tall you never see any tall people there you never run into anyone's knee
boom i love your canned corn i uh i'll tell you this if i get one more x on my clothing i'm next
year's super bowl so um quit putting x's on the clothing try putting pictures of mammals in the
different sections do you have this in a wildebeest