Hey, what is going on everybody, Jerma here with a brand new series.
This is going to be Fairway Solitaire first and foremost, and it's gonna be the start
like I said of a new series called Little Gems.
Now what do you mean Little Gems?
Well I'm talking about mobile games, I'm talking about Android, iPhone, iPad, anything
on a mobile platform.
And the reason why I decided to do this is because I'm always on my damn iPhone.
I'm always playing a game when I'm waiting in line for the DMV or I'm at the doctors
or something like that.
I'm always just sitting on it and I have a lot of favorites.
So I guess the whole purpose of this series is to give you guys, before you buy, because
I know it can be really, you never know with mobile games.
It's so hard to tell if a game is actually good because nobody really covers it and it's
not a whole lot of press on any of these games anyways.
So you could buy a game that you think, oh this looks okay, what do people say about
it?
It's got okay reviews and then you play it and you hate it.
So I'll be the middle man, let me play these games for you and give you my favorites baby.
So Fairway Solitaire, already in the middle of this game right here in the very beginning.
The way this game works, first of all it's for Windows, Mac, that's right you can get
it for your PC, iPhone and iPad.
I actually first played this for the iPhone and then I said oh my god I gotta get this
for the PC too because it's so addicting.
So if you ever played Mahjong or you ever played Solitaire, imagine this is like a strange
mix between the two, as you see in the bottom I of course have my face card and I have to
clear this entire deck, this whole place.
Now I don't have to, but the thing is if I don't clear this, look in the top left of
the screen, it's kind of like golf.
You can be above par, you can be even at par or you can be under par, hence the Fairway
in Fairway Solitaire.
So the way it works you have to go one above or one below the current face card you have
and you can just keep going in a chain.
That's the whole point, you want to get yourself in a chain and that's where this game becomes
so addicting, it just grabs a hold of you because you want to go 7, 8, 9, 8, 7, 8, 9,
10, Jack and you get massive amounts of points for stringing things together.
Not to mention the awesome sound effects that are in this game, it sounds like you're at
a driving range.
I love that noise.
It just brings me back, me and Burger Boy used to go to a place called Starland and
we'd hit a bucket of balls and just that steel on ball, ugh, I can't explain it, it's just
an awesome noise.
So how you win this game, before I talk about that I want to bring up the golf bag here.
In the lower right you're going to see there's a 9 iron sitting in there.
If I click this 9, it will turn the queen into a 9 card which can be insanely helpful.
It doesn't stop your streaks and it doesn't take up a card.
So how you get these, you have to buy them with the game's currency.
They're 500 golf bucks or you have to find them luckily in the world and that doesn't
really happen, they don't show up that often in the world.
So it is recommended that you buy them.
And how you get golf bucks, you have to string combos together really well or I think you
can do it by completing courses at a good point score.
So how you win this game, you have to complete courses at even or under par.
If you go over par, you will have to start the entire course from the very beginning.
Not the level, the entire course.
So it is very much recommended that you take your time and really try to get even or at
least one over or one under on the various holes of that course.
Because if you go like 4 or 5 over par on one particular hole, you're going to have
a ton of catching up to do.
So it's best to stay as close to even as you can possibly get.
So the addiction factor of this game is at an insane level.
I can't even begin to tell you how many hours I've sunk into this game already.
Just like I said, sitting at doctor's offices, sitting in plane rides, sitting in terminals,
anything.
This game just melts through time.
And that's what you want in a mobile game.
I think in any mobile platform game, you want a time waster.
This is a time waster.
And it's got a bunch of levels, a ton of unlockables, a ton of different things you can do with
the golf bucks.
So there's a lot here.
It kind of reminds me of PopCap games, games like Plants vs. Zombies or Insane Aquarium.
There's just a lot of stuff to do.
There's a challenge mode.
So I highly recommend this.
It's only $3.99 on the iTunes store and $2.99 on the website as well.
There's also a free version of this game.
It's kind of old and outdated, but it is still supported by the developer.
But you can get an hour long free trial if you go to Big Fish Games.
All the links will be in the description.
All the relevant things you need to know will be there as well.
And also the reason why I have the circle over the cards, that's not in the game.
I put that in there after in the editing process because you can't see where you're touching.
You can't see where you're clicking when you capture this game.
So that's the reason why you're seeing that.
That's not going to be on your screen.
So that's going to wrap up the video, guys.
Thank you so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it.
And let me know if you like the new series.
Let me know if you want to see more.
If you have any games you want me to try that are on a mobile platform, then definitely
let me know.
Leave me a comment on this video and maybe I'll check it out.
We'll see.
So yeah, guys, that's going to wrap it up.
I'll see you all soon.
And take care, everybody.