What the hell are you doing? You dropped your burger on the ground there.
You dropped your burger on the ground.
Hey, have you ever seen that movie Super Mario Bros. 2?
It's pretty cool. You see the main character, Super Mario, he goes like this.
And he gets into the... where's the game?
That doesn't even hurt. That doesn't even hurt.
Where's the gun?
Give me that gun.
Give me this gun. Give me that gun. I win.
You really like this joke.
You got me.
Today is your unlucky day, motherfucker.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh yeah. Gotcha. Gotcha, motherfucker.
I don't think that's going to stop being funny.
What's wrong? Having some trouble? Come on now. What do you got?
You got a pistol. I got a pistol. I'm going to shoot you with this pistol.
Duck. Jump.
Get wrecked. I mean, get wrecked.
It's actually kind of hard. It's hard to hit B and make the mouth open and play the game at the same time.
Watch out. I got a shotgun. I got one too. I'm going to blast you.
You going to blast me? I'm going to throw it.
You think you're going to blast me?
Well, I'm not going to now. I don't have a shotgun anymore.
Come chase me.
What?
Come chase me?
I don't know. Come chase me.
You're the one with the gun. Chase me.
We're going to do it just like they used to do in the old times.
Back to back. Ten paces.
Turn around. Okay.
In ten paces. Go.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Die.
Miscalculation.
My die was like eight syllables.
That's the fucking Earthworm. I just found the Earthworm gym gun, dude.
Dude, look. Look. Look. This is the gun from Earthworm gym.
Cool, huh? Cool.
Duck Game. On Steam. Currently part of the Steam sale.
Pick it up today. You're going to have fun with all your friends.
Like this guy. He's my friend. But is he really though? I don't know. Could he be? I have no idea.
Friends. I love friends.
This whole thing. This whole thing sucks.
You know, when I sit up here and stare at this red beam, I think about my life and where I've been and where I'll go.
And what? Aliens. Are we the aliens to aliens?
I just want to watch the world burn.
That's a Batman quote.
I wonder how long this recording has been.
Hello there. Welcome to the shoe shop.
Okay, so I have this pair of shoes for only $12.
I'll take them.
Okay, good.
Yes, my old nemesis. The hamburger head. Those of you that know who he is.
He's a dastardly villain. And he must be destroyed.
We have to come down here.
Yeah, I know. I will eventually. I'm doing my monologue.
It's incredibly important to the story arc of my character.
I seriously don't know how many more of these I can even tolerate as a person.
That's the moon gun.
I'm going to catch it in my mouth.
No, no, don't die.
There he is. Ladies and gentlemen, that's the guy that had my character.
I have to go to kill that guy. It's part of my character storyline.
Bastard.
All right, so your first day on a job here at Edwards Construction.
You got to be careful.
Told you to be careful.
And that's when she told me to go to school.
She wanted to see me.
Well, you're really fucking this up, aren't you?
Are we the aliens to that planet?
Could be. Makes sense, in my opinion.
Although a more existential way to look at it is probably like this.
Can you believe Carol? Carol in accounting.
Man, she really gave me the ride.
I have to get back to work.
Yeah, you do. I don't know why you've been doing that.
Seems kind of expensive.
All right, I'm ready.
Okay, I'm going to catch it in my mouth.
Hey, I just want to say congratulations on being number one.
You don't talk to me.
You deserve that trophy.
You're second place. I win.