Hey, what's up, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and
tonight, I'm gonna be playing as the Engineer. The title, I'll explain the title in a second,
but I'll give you the loadout. The loadout is gonna be the Strange Frontier Justice,
the Wrangler, and the Strange Wrench. Now, this gameplay is not the best in the world.
I don't even think I make it onto the leaderboard, but that's not why I made the video. I made
this video to show you guys the Parade of Traveling Engineers. Now, what the hell does
that mean? What is a Traveling Parade of Engineers? Well, as you will see, I'm gonna cut around
in this gameplay. This is not really a gameplay to show you massive kill streaks and stuff
like that. There's a lot of funny things that happen in this, so I really just had to make
a video on it. So, this is Badwater. This is the last point on Badwater, and as a lot
of you guys know, there are two great places for Sentry Guns here. One across the way,
as you see to the right, and over here on the left. So, take a look at this Engineer
right here. So, I say, all right, this is fine. We know two Sentries, whatever, we'll
deal with it, and then, hey, yo, well, hello. We now have three Sentries over here, and
the right side is bare. And I decide, I say, okay, this can't happen. I have to try and
do a risky maneuver. I grab the Sentry and make a run for the right side. I end up getting
over there unscathed. Fast forwarding about 40 seconds here, and as you'll see, the Sentry
is built up to level three, and I have a dispenser here now. So, I'm okay. I got the
Wrangler, pull it out, deal with a pesky soldier, and things are looking up. You know, they're
almost at the point, but I got a good Sentry here, got a good position. I'm not worried
about a thing. And then, here comes the Travelling Parade of Engineers with their two Sentries
in the same spot as mine, and I go, okay, I'll help you build it, and let me get me
out of here. Quick, quick, go, go, go, go. I try to get over to the other side again,
the side where I just was less than a minute and a half ago, and so now there's a sniper
shooting at me, and I'm freaking out trying to jump all over the place and crouch and
stuff because I don't want to get killed. So, less than 10 seconds go by, and look what
happens. This dude comes over, drops one right next to mine again, and this is where I kind
of just give up. I say, whatever, we'll do a double defense. I'm not going to sit here.
I'm not going to bring my Sentry all over the place. There's four Engineers on the team
now, so if you take a look over there, I go, oh, uh, whatever. And this is the part of
the gameplay when things all fall apart, and I just start to turn on my Troll Mode. Now,
not on my own team, of course. I'm talking about the other team. I start to build Sentries
in just odd places, places that could be really easily destroyed, taking out my shotgun, trying
to get some crit shots into people, and I actually do get a pretty good one coming up
here. So, this is Troll Sentry number one. I think this is actually the one and only
Troll Sentry in this particular gameplay, so I bring it up here, trying to get it in
a spot where it'll guaranteed kill anyone that walks up to there, and remember, I have
the Wrangler, so it's just me being a real jerk, being a real bastard, just shooting
people with the Wrangler as they walk by, smack that spy a couple of times, get the
kill on it, and then look at this. Look at the traveling parade of Engineers over here.
I just, I want to briefly explain to maybe some of the newer guys that don't know what
I'm talking about, but the reason why that is a bad idea is if an Uber Demoman comes
around that corner, it's only going to take him probably five seconds to destroy every
single building over there, because you've got to remember, it only takes three stickies
to destroy a Level 3 Sentry gun, and the Demoman in his sticky launcher has eight stickies,
so all he really has to do is turn that corner and just start, boom, boom, boom, just spamming
stickies all over the place, and he will take out everything. So a good rule of thumb
is to always stay at least ten, maybe fifteen feet away from the nearest Engineer and his
Sentry gun. Now I know that sometimes that really just is not possible. The situation
you just saw earlier is a great example of that. If there's at least three or four Engineers
on a team, you're going to be sharing space with people, but if you can at least make
a conscious effort to stay as far away from each other as possible, you're just giving
your team a better chance of victory. So this Sentry goes down, not big surprise. Oh,
Heavy cameo right there. Thanks a lot, Heavy. I appreciate it. You are very welcome. Apparently
the Heavy is General Grievous from Star Wars. That was a terrible Heavy impression. You
got anything else for us, Heavy? I am going to add your Engineer wrench to my collection.
What the hell am I doing right now? Like I'm recording this and listening back to it. What
am I doing? Anyways, get the nice revenge shot on that Medic and I see that this Engineer
has built up a wrangled Sentry and I'm going to do something about it. So right when he
goes to repair it, I'm watching him, watching him, there he goes. I run at him. He must
have been like, what the hell are you doing? Get the kill on him right there, but his Sentry
obviously turns around and blows me to hell. So this is the end of the gameplay here, guys.
Got a Sentry built up in overtime and it kills a few people, but that's not the reason why
I'm showing you the end here. I don't get on the leaderboard like I say, but there's
one little clip here at the end where I shoot a Demoman that sticky jumped across the map
and I was laughing so hard. I thought it was one of the funniest things I'd ever seen.
So this is going to be the end of the gameplay here, guys. Thank you so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it and I will see you guys all next time. Take care, everybody.