Oh, I didn't see that guy. Oh, let's just take this guy out. Oh, this is gonna be funny. Watch this.
Bottom shop! Anybody in this room? Probably. Meeting chamber. All right, there's probably a bunch of
people in here. I guess not. Where's the bone? 19. It's right in here. There it is. Pick it up!
Dark matter. Oh, they're in there. Okay. So is it time to throw a grenade in that room?
Is that what we're doing? Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Do I have to poison these guys? Combine the two glasses. Poison. Oh my god, hold on. I don't know
what to do. All right, hold on. Let me look at this. So who am I supposed to even be killing? Campbell's
glass. Kernel's glass. Eliminate Campbell. Poison one or both of the glasses. Wait for the Campbell
to enter. Okay. I'm gonna poison both of them. Poison. Poison both. Oh god! They're opening the
door. Where is he? Oh, here we go. This is where we poison. Wait, I wasn't supposed to do that?
Oh crap, that's the guy I was supposed to save. Hold on a minute. Hold on. Hey guys, don't drink
those yet. I want to just... Before you drink those, I have something to say. One of them is
poisoned. Please don't drink it and be... Okay. Yeah, thanks guys. See ya. Yeah, don't drink that
poison yet. All right, this time I'm not going to poison her uncle because I was not supposed
to do that. Poison Campbell. Let's go. Oh man, I so badly want to throw a grenade in the room.
So badly. Oh, I so... What? Oh no. This wasn't supposed to happen like this. This wasn't supposed
to happen. This wasn't supposed to happen. They're like fighting in the other room. Hold on. Am I
actually going to get away with this? This guy is fighting in this room. He's dead right in the
corner. I can't believe it. There was like gunfire out here. Oh man.
Man, that was hard laughing right there.
I can't believe that happened.