Hello everybody, Jerma here with a live commentary and a face cam video.
Because I know a lot of you guys were asking about this and I've never done this before. Let me take that back.
I have done this before on my live streams and I've done video blogs before, you know the deal.
But I figured why not just do this because I have a lot of time on my hands. So I set up this camera.
It's like duct taped on a pole sitting on the ground. It's just it gets ridiculous.
It actually took me like 25 minutes to set this up. So I was kind of raging about that.
But anyways, let's play some Huntsman Sniper.
This is on Shibby's server because my server is broken and doesn't work and I don't know if it ever will. Who knows?
I have no idea. Trying to fix that as of right now. I don't know.
So let's get started using the Huntsman, the Jurati and the what the hell am I using for a knife? The Tribalman Shiv.
Okay, so let's do it. See if I can't get some cool gameplay live even though that never happens.
This is on Nightfall. Payload Race Nightfall. A map that I've played probably three times in my life.
And I wish people would play it more because I guys I'm kind of getting sick of, you know, Dust Bowl, Badwater.
You know, they're getting kind of old. You know what needs to happen?
There's got to be an update for Team Fortress 2 because I'll tell you right now,
it's hard to find a server now that doesn't have bots in it.
The only servers that really aren't running bots anymore. I mean, this right now, it's 3.30 Eastern Time.
And every server I've tried to go to is just full of bots. And it's just like, what is going on?
There has to be some kind of update soon. Bring some more people into Team Fortress. Make people play.
I guess because of Skyrim and, you know, Modern Warfare 3 makes a little bit of sense.
So let's get this going. Out this window. Not in his head.
He's looking around for me. See that? He was like, oh, no, give me a kill. Hello.
I got the guy behind him. I shot at him and I got the guy behind him.
That didn't make any sense. Are we really? Wow. We're going to win this game that quick.
I can't wait to watch that back because I want to see what the hell even just happened right there.
Nobody on their card except this Pyro. No. One more second and I would have had him.
I'll have him right now though. Oh, that was close.
That was close. All right. I need some heals. I'm on fire, doctor.
No, it's a heavy coming around this corner. No, not a headshot.
Oh, my God. Two heavies. All right. Here we go. They're both dead.
Nice job, team. Push that cat. Oh, there we go. There we go.
Oh, this guy's got it out for me. Tribe him with Shiv. Tribe him with Shiv.
Oh, God. Cabot. Nice. That's one way to do it.
That's one way to do it. Get out the Shiv. Get out the Shiv and start smashing people.
I missed. Well, that went well for the first round. Let's do another one.
Get a sip of my water. That's right. I said water. W-A-T-A-H. Water.
Oh, I'm going to puke. I got to get out here, man. Jesus, what am I doing?
Oh, this guy's toast. Not high enough. Not too high.
It's been a... There it is. It's been a while since I've used the Huntsman.
So, there it is. Get out of my face, Scout. Oh, no. Get out of the car. Oh, God.
Got him right in his face. And there is a sniper shooting over here.
Oh, my God. No, that's not a sniper. That's a... Speaking of pyro.
I didn't even speak in a pyro when I talked. Oh, I need the Gerardi. Come on, come on, come on.
Did I get us both? Nice, I got us both. God, I need health. I'm going to get sniped
right in the face by a rocket. Oh, there it is. Come on. Heal me.
Get me up to at least like 70 or 80 before I go anywhere. That's good.
Oh, my God. No. It's all right. It's all right. We're good. Get on the car so I can heal.
I knew it. I knew you were a spy. We got anybody? We got a medic?
We do not have a medic. Get this guy right here. Bang. Get this guy right here, too.
Get down. Get down. Come on. Let's go, cot. Let's go. That's a spy. Spy. Oh, we got it.
I got it. Get out of here. Get out of here. This thing is so weak. We did it. Oh, man.
All right. Well, thank you, everybody, so much for watching. I really appreciate it.
And I'm going to drink the rest of this water on camera. I'm going to chug the water. Here we go.
Ready? One, two, three. I can't do it. I'm going to puke. Puke is going to come out of my mouth.
No, but thanks, everybody, for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you guys all next time. Take care, everybody.