There's a lot of people in this call. I'm so sorry. I just like everybody's eardrums up
What's going on everybody
Hold on. Let's let's meet this. What's going on guys? Welcome. I am
About to participate in can you hear the voices?
We're playing fortnight. I hope you guys are ready. I
He's that he's saying no tanks
It's a tournament. I guess I'm on a team
All right is I will be going to each of you you the captain and your co-captain are immune
But I will be flipping a coin one person from your team will be switching to a different team
Okay, so what's going on today and we plan in a fortnight competition I got slime on my team I got Nick on my team
I've got I might change teams right now. I have no idea
I've never played a game of fortnight. It was seemed like cool
You are you should hear this
I kind of feels like i've been into my own discord voice channel
Which doesn't exist anymore. I know it's sad. I've just brought it up. All right, so I i'm gonna take my headphones out
I hate leadway. Where do I go?
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Okay. Hey guys
Hey, what the fuck is happening?
um
So I can someone help me. All right. All right. How do you add a friend? How do you add?
All right, how do you add a friend?
Yeah, you add us as a friend and you need to pick a co-captain. Okay
Those are your two biggest priorities. All right doesn't matter who yeah, do we have a text channel?
No, you just type it in general
Uh, I just pick just pick slime. All right slime. You are you are the co-captain. Thank you, sir
I will serve you well, sir. How do I get what do you guys name?
Uh here what's yours? Just just just add me. It's really easy
It's uh, it's royale coming my way
r-o-y-a-l-e
c-o-m-i-n not g
Royale coming coming my way
But do I have the settings right?
Uh, since you're not accepting friend requests, okay, how do I do that?
Uh settings. Yeah, so cog in the bottom left. Yep
And then you're gonna go up to the person in the bottom the top right got it
Friend invite permission anyone friend invite. Okay, got it. Wait, if you're if you're live, this might hurt you for a second
Yeah, you might get a lot. Oh shit. Just just that I am swag is for men
So okay, what are your names? Am I gonna get crashed out of here? All right. I have I have you got okay
I all you need is swag is for men and then the rest can and then you can close it up again
Okay, swag is for men. Yeah, it's not just for boys. Wait, so what do I go to do that?
If you just see it like if you see that request come
Is there a uh, there wouldn't happen to be a place where you could see all friend requests, right?
Is there I think you just click on the top left where the
Like the little hamburger thing is hook it and then you go in it should have like a list of people who've added you
Oh, it does. Okay. So what am I looking for?
Swag is for men or bahama papa either one. It's it's for it's not just for boys is what oh Jesus. This is bad
I you might be in a queue
No, just in a party
No, no, no, I mean like in a queue to be on my pending friends list. Sure, right?
Oh, no, how do I can I turn can I turn this off turn it off now? Yeah
And then you can filter through the the dregs of humanity
Oh god, damn it
All right. You also you also could have sent me one. I could just said yeah, let that's that's gonna be easier
Easier
One word I just just take it up my whole fucking screen
The ui is is is I was good. I was gonna say what is this like a hundred billion dollar company this ui
Hold on. Don't get mad. It's like netscape. No, you're right. You're right control through the emotions. Yeah, i'm gonna i'm gonna keep it under control
Wish I should have just said this in silence
Are you trying to type in dvorak dude? What's going on?
Okay, fine. How do I add a player?
Oh my god, go to the friends list in the top left
And then the second one the second tab on the left side of the screen. It's a plus button
Like that then fine. Yeah, that's what I just did
Wait, did you send it to me?
Ahama papa, right? Did you make a space or no? No. Yeah, it's there. Oh, I got it
All right. Okay. I got
I'm so sorry. I fucked this whole thing. You're fine. No, you're the best
All right. Now i'm gonna turn this off right? I can turn off the friend notifications, right? I'm getting so many god damn it
I'm dude. I'm sorry. I know it's not your fault. I i've ruined everything
No, everything's fine. This is the cost of a victory royale
You are the president and we are your chaperones. Okay, so realize that so let me let me turn you guys all up first of all
Hi, sorry. Like hi guys
How's it going?
We turned real quick make things easy. So fine. Okay, this is my buddy alec
One of the one of the best night players. Uh, I'm nick. We've met slime you guys have met as well just in case
Okay, and so now now you're added so now in the general chat germa you need to say
Captain germa co-captain slime. Do I how do I get a skin?
Okay
Credit card information goes in vbucks come out. How do I type in chat?
The general chat in discord. Oh
Yeah, if you buy a balenciaga skin, you'll match us, but I want you to express yourself. However, i'm just gonna stay like this
I'm just gonna stay like this. I I don't I this that's too much work. I feel like we're about to start in 10 seconds
You can get tick tock dances in the game as well if that change really yeah
Here check this out. Hold on. Let me go into the general. Is it the general text channel general text channel in discord?
Yeah, you'll see my most recent messages when you're troubleshooting. Okay, so i'm gonna say
slime
Is co-captain?
right
Yes
Hello germa in squad. Hi, sorry. I I I everything's under control
Slime is your co-captain. Yes. Slime is your co-captain nick heads or tails call it in the air
Uh tails never fails. All right tails never fails. Let's see if you're right. It never failed fine. Okay is leaving
No
Wow team. Oh no going with pay money wubby
Oh, that's a great squad. You're gonna actually have a lot of fun. Okay. All right. All right next squad next squad
Who's coming to our squad?
I guess what do we get?
Wait, which one is that nick pay money wubby? Uh, yeah, so it's placed his name in here
It's it's 13. Yeah, there's a number. Okay. I'm so sorry get sap nap. Have I just gone forever?
Uh, I think I think I think you move every time
Okay, maybe I think I don't know but either way this is you guys asking me where the vape pen is
I was actually gonna get one but I didn't want to get like addicted to nicotine for a joke
I it was like last second. I was gonna go to like the gas station and get one
I know
So, uh, what were the rules again, there was some very specific rules we had to follow, right?
Okay, one is no tanks. So there's tanks you can get inside of and drive around those are banned and it's honor system
You just can't get in them. Uh, there are battle buses that are very chunky and big you can get in those
But tanks are uh, and then the other rule is no using tents
Which you're not going to worry about but it's a way to transport good weapons across games
So like you can go into a tent that you find
A weapon that you've stored, you know in the tent, which is like this universal bookshelf and pull it
You can't do that. So okay doesn't really apply to us because we're honorable fighters sap nap. Hello guys. I'm on the team now
What's up? It's a pleasure to have you. We are the best team here. That's true
All right, we're gonna win. I've got some pretty good fps, uh background. I'm not concerned about it
That's and that's what i've been saying
To all the haters the fakes. Yeah, I got I got I got some I can do it. We got to kick final k out forever
Nick. Oh, yeah, you're right. Uh, what's your guy's name? I need to add one of you guys. This is true
You can add bahama papa
It's one word. Hold on. Let me open my friends list for a moment. Okay
I don't know the spell bahama or papa one of the two. I don't know which one pretty phonetic
It's b a h a m a p a p a that's what I put searching for users
Okay, got it. I feel like i'm gonna realize a lot. Are you are you real h o c? No, i'm pant does
I just sent you a friend request. Okay, hold on. I gotta fucking not see there you go. Got it. Awesome
I think we got a pretty good squad
I mean so many star quests and they're all from people with faze in their name. All right trying to buy some nnts, bro
All right, fortnight andy it's like there's like a hundred people in this tournament. We're all fortnight andy's today
True. So is it we're playing against everybody at the same time right now?
Yeah, we're gonna we're gonna drop from uh from a bus in the sky and then it's kill everyone you see except for us
Okay, is it friendly fire? No, no
We should try and land on one of the uh blimps and i'm down over because once you take over the blimp
It's a really good people like rarely come up to fight you and if you do you have high ground
Yeah, I like that that map for context germa has not ever played fortnight
Which should be a problem it shouldn't know but I believe there should be a sort of a get down mr
president strategy employed
I mean I
I did make it really clear that I have no experience
Like I said, yes, dude, i'm gonna get a bow and arrow
Temple when you start. Yes, sir. You made it clear. Yes, sir
I'm gonna we're gonna land and i'm gonna get like like a bow and arrow through my neck and i'm just gonna be and
I'm gonna pull it out and i'm gonna and i'm gonna weep
Okay
Because this is war. Well, we got this i'm actually excited a good squad
We should drive germa in the back of a car
Can I just fire out of can I fire out of a window or something you can you can it's a lot like gta
You can like crack the window. Uh, I think you're a party leader nick. So you should do the um, oh, okay
Your code drop the code should be dropped
Nope. Nope, not yet jk ludwig changing teams. Okay, we're good. I thought we're in trouble. I feel so bad
The fourth player on our team with like a really really old friend of mine who like doesn't know anyone here
And uh, we needed a fourth. So I grabbed him and then ludwig did this switch thing
He got sent away
Get sent to war. Oh, no
What team were you on sapnap? I was on connor's team
See
You play you play minecraft, right? Yeah. Okay
That's good for us. That's good for we have building experience here. That is huge for us. Wait, I thought about that. Is it building?
No, no building building's off, but it's gonna come with like ancient knowledge that only he could have oh, thank god
I was about to be very sad
You do not say jfk 985
In this chat
So, uh, how do I toggle aim?
Right click
Oh, I see. I see ads. I don't I like to toggle. I don't like to hold
Oh, you want to change it? Uh, I see. Okay, so you're gonna go to your settings
You're gonna click the uh arrow keys on the right third to right third to last. Uh-huh. Um,
Let's see this. I got this target, but there's no target toggle. Oh, man. Maybe you're right
Maybe you can't do that. Can you really not? Um, am I the only person that cares about that?
You're not no, you are not I don't but you are not the only person
You are weird and different but we accept you here
I made a script to do toggle in um, that revenant game revenant. Oh, I found it. I found it
It's the second the gear icon on the top in the second menu. It's toggle targeting in combat section
Oh targeting in
So you scroll down to combat in the in the gear icon
Uh on in your settings menu and just toggle targeting on oh, hell. Yeah
And so you are seen invalid in the eyes of fortnight. Yeah, that's cool. I'm happy about it
I said I don't want to show like
I'm just gonna see something right now. I'm gonna steal me. Uh sapnap. Do you have a
Balenciaga skin or yeah, I do I can run it
I mean that would be huge because that would mean a lot it would be like we're the three balenciaga secret agents
And then we have germo
Is there like a default like skins I can choose from
Uh, yeah, there are I think
I think I know I don't think there's any broke talk in this game. I'm not kidding
I don't think there's you can't oh you just randomized. I mean, I mean I just downloaded the game like an hour ago
Well, I bought a dog with a balenciaga hoodie, so
We're just different. I have so many tick tock. Yes him. Oh, I i'll gift you dude. Can you get me spider-man?
Uh, if i'm in the shop, I can do it. You just said that with like so much
I don't see spider-man. I see someone named big chug us. I don't know. Wait, there's a big
Spider-man was battle pass from last uh last
What's it called season? There's matrix stuff. Yeah, this is a metro. I don't want doctor strange
That means I bought it right now and I don't want anybody to know that that's true. That is loser behavior
Okay, buy as a gift
Enable 2 fa brother. Okay. Hold on. I think I can do this. No, it's opening a different
I cannot all right. Don't let me tell you right now. Do not like risk putting your phone number
into uh into like the
Internet to give me the spider-man skin
I think I will I think we're okay with this
Do you have spider-man in your thing? I don't I don't
Spider-man I had him but that was like a week ago
Wait spider-man was in your shop. Yeah, he was in like the the bottom of the shop or maybe it somebody said, uh
Odd watchers skip. I don't think you want to skip this and by the way, this is not the only thing i'm doing today
I got a very big plans today. I got
Every boss in every from souls game tier list that i'm going to take a lot of time on and it's ready to go
That's happening after this. I think
I think dude there there's a splash screen when I loaded a game earlier
And it said only you can prevent vbuck like stealing and says don't share your account info and there's like a cat
pointing at the screen
I was like damn they they this is this is the good message
Everybody's freaking out saying that I should turn on the streamer mode because the dmca music
Oh, yeah, yes, there's doja cat. There's real music in the car when you get in unless you want to get fucking crazy
I'm crazy. I feel like I i just leave it on that is i don't know what's getting but i'll be honest
Do I really care if the fortnight section of this stream gets nuked?
What are they gonna do send the weekend? I i am honestly if if this if this gets like muted this part of the stream
And I don't really necessarily care
You also like can't cancel it. Okay licensed audio mute all
Yeah, why is it gondam style? That's so good. Yeah, there's a dance
Uh, it's just so big 10 years ago and they brought it back for fortnight
There's no music replacements. You just kind of do that. I don't think there's no I don't I don't think
Why do I feel like the whole game muted? But no, it's um, good to see you guys again. We're good to hear from you again
Yes, sir. We were we were very excited to hear that you were our captain
I found out I was your captain when um, I can't when I came in the call, so i'm ready to leave the ship
Steer it in the right direction
Yeah
A ludwig augren production. Can I can I paint you a little picture of how we how we got here?
So last fortnight monday, um, we had a son on our team
uh
Who has played a little more than you have but has has played probably a just as significant amount of as you have
And uh, we got destroyed. We got second to last
Um since then ludwig nick me and hasan since then we have put in some serious hours
We've been dropping tilted constantly
Uh, we've been discussing strategy
um
We consulted our friend's little brother
Uh, because he that was huge that was because he because he's like 16
So we asked him how he would approach this and I think we're ready to place top three
I I mean look I I might not know fortnight, but you get the you take the building out
I have like three four thousand hours in team fortress too. Yeah, you point and you shoot, you know
And I mean like I've just completed elden ring. It's just a better cartoon shooter
You're gonna be fine. Yeah, you got it. Everybody said congratulations, but it's all right
Oh, you're talking about yeah, it's super weird
Well, I mean I just said I just I just completed elden ring and I just figured that it was gonna get like a bunch of like
Claps and stuff, but no. Yeah, I heard that I I heard that so
Fortnight so better what what are people spending better for no one asked?
Codes up codes up. Oh
Okay, putting our code in so should I ready up? Um once I do yeah
At sapnap. It's a pleasure to meet you by the way
All right. We should be able to ready
I have the code in
Oh, sorry. I was using the restroom. It's a pleasure to meet you as well. I had my wireless headset on
You were listening to us while you were in the restroom. Yeah, you did special
That's the bond. I just left my headset on muted my mic got up and went to pee
That's a good idea actually and I heard just in case I was gonna miss someone is it time to ready up?
Uh, I think so. Yeah, i'm hitting it. Uh, should we just do it? Yes, sir. All right
Surprise for the table. I gotta put both headphones in for this
Okay, jerma big big, uh big thing for I think battle royales in general
The worst thing you can hear when your teammate when something is happening to your teammate is they're over there
Because no one knows what you're talking about, right? So there's a ping button
I believe it's mapped to z very helpful for saying over there and then it's like beep beep. You got it also
Um, I do have some battle royale experience not with this one of g-mobile. Okay, wait
Mobile, that's not a joke. I actually I played the mobile pubg a lot of airport hours. Were you nice, sir?
I mean I was just in I was just did it in bed just lying in bed
Oh, yeah, I think you need to ready up nick. I did what?
So I understand the concept of the shrinking zone of like the landing in different places picking up web
Okay, what's a good weapon? What should I be looking for? I think the the meta is like aug plus. Um, what's the the shotgun?
the big amount of ammo
The drum one I think drum. Yeah, I think it's aug plus drum plus
Uh the things that launch you and then two heels is what I was told. That's like the meta. There's uh, there's smgs
They're kind of unwieldy
Usually not worth it
But the the rifles are like where your bread and butter is going to be are your mouths moving on your characters when you know
They're not okay. Oh, yeah the dog
Everyone keeps saying that I was like, whoa, that's kind of cool. Are we supposed to switch to na west?
We are on na west. Oh, okay. This ain't gonna start in 30 minutes, right?
Um, it should start immediately or once everyone's ready once everyone's in
I think the 30 minute thing you're seeing is like a different thing. It's like the duo tournament. Okay pop up
I feel like I feel like i'm gonna surprise a lot of people
Why does it say only 28 cute am I I didn't do it wrong, right? No, I think i'm just waiting or
No, i'm not buying i'm not gonna buy a skin. No, it's too late. I'm just gonna play
Remember you might be cracked in this I might be this is a surprise to us
Yeah, I didn't I wasn't expecting that but I mean it's whatever i'm ready to i'm ready to game
Ready to click heads. Oh, yeah, I love that dude. So I know this this healing right like bandages and that kind of thing
Yeah
So big big thing you want to remember if you so there's little pots and small pots and they give you different amounts of shield
Uh, you're gonna want to use those little pots first
Okay
The reason being is if you already have 50 shield and you try to take a little pot the game doesn't let you
So you want to use the little pots to hit 50 and then use the big pot to hit 100
Yo, can one of you guys discord live stream?
uh
Yeah, I probably should be me ty just one. Thank you. I love it a little late, but uh
The thought that counts I work on like 1500 millisecond ping so you get the internal delay
So that happens when you're almost 40 one day the zoomers will be old bro. Not me. That'll be funny. You guys
Not um, i'm chilling
I've been using lotion. I'm like all
I'm all slippery and
Hard to catch. No, no, seriously though. Actually actually moisturize your faces like seriously do that
I was once told by a makeup professional doing makeup on my face for a thing
She said if you moisturize you will never age and she said it with like this ancient wisdom and I was like, yes
Okay, now that that's actually dead serious like when you come out of the shower
You had like a really good light face moisturizer. That should be the first thing you do after you dry your face
Dry your face. Let it sit for a second moisturize. Trust me. I'm gonna remember this forever
You your 40 year old face is gonna thank you when you're fucking 40 and old and weird. You'll be looking smooth
Moist I might be weird, but i'll be in otter. I'll be moving around
You should have a whole skincare routine. I don't know. It should really we really should be pushing this
I think it's hard for dudes, you know
I wasn't caught this, you know as a young man
I just ate taco bell and wore hoodies and rolled around
And slop. Yeah, so so that's not dude culture. I think you're trying to imply that
I didn't I wasn't doing that
Yeah, I know. It's just like the normal like american
And rolled around and slop. Yeah, it's like what you did. Like it's what I did culturally
I am literate. He's from colorado is kind of like part of the whole yeah is what I think there colorado is nice
I like colorado colorado. Yeah, it's some great slop
People say i'm actually the american psycho no, I I just like I I want to take care of my face
Is it psychotic to moisturize honestly once this goes it's over dude you as a patrick bateman deep fake is so funny
I'm thinking about that right now
One of my favorite moments I think it's like jackass one the movie, uh, it's like johnny noxville like
He he he gets hit by like a claymore mine that has like rubber balls in it
And they hit him all over his body his body's like insanely bruised and he's like kind of limping out after it happens
And he's like circling his face. He's like is this okay face good. Oh, we're good. Right?
No, it's true. I mean I used to be in the gym all the time
I used to work out all the time like three four days a week and then like I started to kind of get like that
Weird like attack on titan monster body where like my my like stomach's like too big
But like my shoulders are not wide enough to make sense and my like waist is small. My ass is huge
Yeah, you look like you look like someone was just fucking around in the tony hawk building character
Can be kind of uh, so I mean I gotta make sure this stays around
And the hair too the hair's got to stick around for a while too. I gotta be honest with you
Yeah, I started to look like the pill from osmosis jones
Uh
People are demanding I buy a skin. I don't what's what's even available. You should buy a skin
I wasn't gonna say that but I don't want to like go get my credit card mentioned it
Yeah, get get your money up. Not your phone up. Yeah, it's pretty big. Do I have to put my credit card in?
Well, it's it's not gonna run on magic. This isn't unicef
Hold on. Let me let me turn all my kid
I don't want anyone to see like the reflection of my eyes of my screen putting my credit card in
How much money how much money do I need?
Uh
How much what's the v-book transfer like 20 30 100 bucks, whatever?
100 what no, I put a hundred like 20 50 like you put a hundred dollars in
Oh
About 100 the 799 one. How about that one? That's pretty good. Thank god. I'm not showing this on screen, right? No
Yeah, thousands enough for like like bubble gum or like maybe like one of your shoes
Okay, so add funds to wallet right place the order
Did it work?
Thank you. Okay, so I should have
Okay. So now if I go to item shop, I have a thousand I have one thousand v bucks
Okay, it doesn't sound as much as it might be but that will get you a skin. All right. So what what should I do?
Well now you can go to the item shop on the top and sort of browse and anything you can afford
Which is not much for the thousand it is true
You can but I think you can get i'm seeing envoy which is like a hot like green haired spy woman
um, you don't have enough for the
Fish in astronaut suit. I don't have enough to do this. I have to buy the
I'd buy on okay. What else is there?
This is the only thing that's available. This is all that's available. It's envoy or I believe wind walker echo
Which is like a sort of like a mage. I don't know
Wind it's uncommon green. Oh, okay wind walker echo. I guess i'm gonna do
Envoy what matches more with you guys envoy is very is much more dripped out
Like wind walker is like a fantasy character, right? We're dogs wearing balenciaga, which has nothing to do with fantasy, right?
All right. So i'm gonna put another thousand v bucks in my man. I should have just bought the other one
Wait, can you not get the how much is the the dog?
For me, it says 600 but maybe it's because already I don't know. Um, dude
I missed the I missed the 12 extra coins too for me. The dog says 1200
Okay, maybe that just like upgrades the dog. I think it's because okay. I see. It's like a I see
Because I own some of it. It's less. Yeah, I got the pack. So it doesn't even show me the um, the price anymore
Okay, I got two I got two thousand v bucks. You don't want to put that skin on before the match starts
Which is in like a minute. So you want to click locker in the top? Okay, but when you buy it
Oh you oh after you buy they already bought it my bad big chungus. That's what I was thinking is is really your style
Because he looks like the attack on time guy like he looks like he has like guys screaming
That would look great on you
Fuck it up germa. How do I claim this?
Wait, I think I think it's starting right now. You might be fucked. He's got it equipped. Did I do it? We're in
Did I equip it? All right, let's fucking go. This is not gonna be close. That's what i've been saying. I think I got it
Yes, okay. I'm i'm assuming sapnap. You are the best player here. Yes, uh, I bestow that upon you
And so what what that means for me is I want you to feel comfortable making shot calls
And we will we will follow you as if you are a compass command cavern. We should drop like right now
All right dropping. Okay, it's spacebar germa because I know all right, we need to fight for the blimp
There's gonna be people here. So try and grab a gun immediately and take control of them
Got it
Oh, there's npcs that that are gonna be on this blimp. They're called io soldiers
They're not real characters, but they can uh, they can dice you up. It doesn't look like we have too many people here with us
Nice. There's one other at least one other player for sure
Guys how do I land?
Oh, what?
What do you mean? What's what's oh you're on top? Yeah, you gotta find a way in
You can also maybe pickaxe the roof and get in. Oh people are shooting at us. I'm in i'm in i'm in
Okay
Oh, that's pretty big. I need a weapon
Oh i'm getting beamed what the hell is what is that? Oh, it's the fucking teleporting. Uh,
Dude doctor doctor scones. Yeah, he's downstairs if you guys might kill him and get his good gun. He's got a gun
He's kind of scary
Oh fuck i've never seen this guy to be honest. I got I got a gun
He's really beefy, but if we all shoot him he dies kind of fast
Here you go
Yeah, i'm coming to you
fire
Where'd he go?
Oh
I'm dead over here. I think it's a real guy. Yeah
real person
I'm down i'm down
I'm coming up the back back back back back back
No way
We got destroyed
Restarting restarting restarting
Huh?
Wait, we're restarting
Oh, yes, that's so big
Yes, sir
So we just get in the lobby we just get killed. Yeah, just back out just back out
Okay, jeremy jeremy we're restarting that game didn't count we got really lucky. Oh, wow
Return to love it. Okay. I did not know that fucking guy was gonna be there
Yeah, we had to we dealt with the npc and then we got run up on yeah
Okay, someone in tarik's team is really bad
I don't know who it was. I saw I don't know who it was but they were like, yeah, they were really good
Oh, that was probably slicker. Oh, we know that's not on their team. Wait, who's their new player?
So that was an npc we were fighting
The teleporting person really the really powerful guy was an npc, but then a real team dropped on our blimp
Oh crap, there's a new there's a new code now
Okay, i'll put that in
I was unlucky that we just randomly got put off the spawn next to those guys. Holy shit. Yeah
once they like
Once tarik and I don't even know who else got in there. They just annihilated us
Maybe it's better to fly or go to like a further blimp only because like really confident players like them are just going to insta drop
Yeah, I didn't I wanted I chose that one because I didn't see other like the ones that were further
All the ones I saw were tilted and what's the other crossroad one whatever it's called
Yeah, and I know that puns's team was gonna go for one of those two and I didn't want to fight puns. Oh fair enough
You got a new code in did you get the new code in nick? Uh, yeah. Yeah, I I read it up. All right ready
Uh, jeremy got ready up. Oh, yeah, my bad. It's only four games instead of five
So local bars is bad documented. So that might be the person on tarix. Why did why would restarting what happened?
Uh, I don't know there must have been some error and then we also lost time
So now there's only four matches instead of five. Oh, okay
So I think I have enough to buy one dance this time. Oh, that's so big. That is so big that helps
How about no sweat test it out? See how you like it? Sure
Whatever dude, I can't get the the gamer rage wanting. Oh my god my shop refresh. That's crazy
Because it looked a lot like this. So no head
That's not the right one
I know that's the default dance. Oh, yes, sir. Good luck slime. Thank you protect saikuno from guns insane name to have in chat
But also I agree. Why did your guy only use one hand for that dance? Is that a thing? I think that's the dance
That one just tilts me
Yeah, I just get mad looking at it. Just know after I kill someone I will be popping this. Yeah
I'm right there with you
Do
The one-handed floss
So I so badly want to do this at one of the fortnight concerts. Wait, is it okay? No, that's it's the code
We're already on. Okay, someone's a tarik scene thought we were randoms. Why would they think that that's weird to think
Why would you think royale come in my way is anyone but german 95? That's such a bot name
Randoms
Swag is for men
Yeah, these do at least a couple of these feel like bot names. I'll have a papa for sure
Pan i've had i've had this day since season two. Is it pen is the is the
It's just supposed to be pandas, but like pandas is taken
I got it. So I just was like
Till then it does it does mess with the brain a bit because you want to say pan
Does pan does a human mouth doesn't allow for that
Some people saying they can get thanos. Yeah thanos in the game
Thor dude, no shit will smith is in this game
Uh, I think moist had it on last week right after the the oscar's thing
It was really funny to see will smith jumping around but
I wouldn't have picked like the saturday morning cartoon bane if I knew that I could get thanos
Yeah, that's the thing you got to tune in next shop to see what what the vbucks you can spend you know
That's how they get you. Oh, so you can't just go back into the catalog and buy a bunch of stuff that they did
Yeah, I guess that adds exclusivity to it, right in a way
Do you guys think that um, what are your thoughts on the three stooges making their appearance here in the next few weeks?
I think that it's a game where four people can squad up. So there's an instant problem
Wow, that's true. Unless there was a fourth stooge like the bonus jonas
Well, what about mo or curly or something? You think that they have a chance with the bowl cut maybe yeah shemp
Everyone should have to play as the beetles
Oh shit, the beetles could be added. No, that's fucked up because two of them two of them were murdered bro. You can't do that
You literally can't all right. Here we go. Here we go
By the way, Anthony paul mccartney is a fig if the three stooges are the three stooges are not added to this game
By april 23rd, I believe I have to eat a glove on stream
That is a that is so unfortunate like a latex glove or like a mechanic
I mean, I I was so confident like two years ago. I gave a random date in the future
You know, I have a friend that did the same thing
He he said at the beginning of 2018. Dr. Phil will die this year and he didn't
So kind of kind of ate his own words on that one. What do you mean go here? Um, let's see
Maybe we can crank whatever this is
Yeah, i'm done. I'll be late. Yeah, let's do it
Yep
I think the later too the more safe we get well, I don't know
I think everyone I think everyone is thinking that so it's kind of a toss-up
I do like this spot though. I think I think we can do a lot of good work
We can see there's a lot of people dropping right now
So we're waiting we're waiting to get all the way to the end here
Yeah, drop drop when it says like 900 on the meters away from the ping. Oh
I guess you could like maybe now. Yeah, i'm gonna go now. I don't really see too many people so
Looks good
What's the best way to make it so I go over there and not across the whole game?
um
I don't exactly know what you're saying. You can you can pop your thing early by pressing space bar
Okay, if you don't want to go too low. Yeah
Which should be fine for where we're dropping because you want to be higher
I think we're good. I don't think anyone's dropping here
We might be able to loot the town under us too and then come back up
This actually looks really good and there's gonna be cars in this town. So we don't have to worry about circle
Oh, there's one person
So it's probably one team
So we're going into the blimp
Yeah, they missed the blimp. They're gonna go they're gonna. Oh, no, they made it they're going inside right now
I'm bad. I'm bad. I'm bad. I'm bad. I'm bad. I'm so sorry
I I picked I hit a pixel. Did you fall? Yeah, I fell i'll come down
I'm so sorry
They're inside
I'm gonna revive nick and come right back up
It might be worth to actually bail on the blimp because we have two down here
Yeah, there's one on top of right now if I jump off my safe
If you if you jump off you can you'll take the ball down we might have to just like hit the town
Right in front of me
I'm going for a gun
Right there shit
Okay, fuck we're actually just only play that was mendo xqc
Holy shit, we're playing the best game right now
Dude, i've never played one minute of this game. Okay. I don't even I don't know how to land the fucking sky dive
Uh, that was that wasn't bad
Ludwig, what are you doing in the call? Oh, sorry. Sorry. Just spectating. What do you want? Ludwig?
I'll do what you guys are doing spectating
I don't like this guy anyone else sort of sharing that feeling
Did did you think it's fair that tarik is playing this video game? Oh, he must be gone. Oh, he's gone
Yeah, he left. So what happened there?
Um, okay, I trolled, uh, my my character's foot hit like a pixel which made me insta drop off my
Parasail and then I just went straight down. Oh shit
And then we dropped with maybe the best team in the lobby at the moment. Oh
People going for blimps. Are we uh screwing ourselves by going blimp? We might have to we might have to
With that with an audible
That's fine. What I think what is in the blimp? That's very important
It's less about what's in there and it's more that you have high ground constantly
Okay, and and teams like the whole goal is just to live the longest, right?
So if you can like have a really high spot where it's hard for people to kill you
Uh then and also be in a place where people don't often like try to take over late then it's just good
This person's in a tent. No, dude, if they're tenting i'm not a narc. I would never oh wait
Wait, what happened?
Wait, maybe you're maybe you're allowed to tent to heal but not to store
I think we ran into some bad luck boys and I think it's it's no it's no big deal
i'm telling you
Just give me a weapon and I and I and i'll shine
I don't think I haven't held a weapon either one of these two
Dude shroudy shroud is just literally melting. No
He took out mango's team single-handedly
He's the he is god's gift to all of gaming and he's in the same tournament moki got tarik. Okay, good to know
Scalps. Dr. Lupo is he's good, right? Dr. Lupo is I believe a very seasoned player very good, right?
I feel like this is the one to watch at the moment
Sakuno's team is a is a powerhouse of content tarik got rebooted
But you can get in that thing
Yeah, you can like launch yourself
I didn't know you could gonzo the great out of that. I would have just done that
What would you call it gonzo the great?
Yeah, okay
Whoa, that's cool
It's inside the mind of sakuno right now
Dude dodger lupo's fortnight level 153
Oh shit
Guys, it's too late to get a vape pen. I can't do it right now
Yeah, blimps seem to be what everyone is trying to do
Yeah
I think we should avoid blimps
What's another good place to to hang out?
I'm behind i'm not sure. I think it's just about like, uh
It's kind of lucky right because like you could say like oh drop far away, but then other teams are also saying drop far away
We're really just trying to set ourselves up with like enough gear and decent positions so that we don't have to worry about looting
If we can just get live off the spawn
We can it'll help us a lot
Yeah, just on's like just the most it's just coin
Yeah
Guys, i'm not gonna order a vape pen off of uber eats
That would be the stupidest fucking thing ever
uber eats
No, i'm not vaping a vape pet. I'm not gonna inhale nicotine for fun
The place is the very end but people who drop before the autodrop will just get there first
So if we want to go to the end, let's just drop before the end, you know
Yeah
I mean like how much are you craving like nicotine where you need to uber eat?
Why is there a car over there? This is just like a there's just like a regular red sedan just parked on a hill
Yeah, there's just some car ass cars in this game and then there's like lambos with jet rockets
Wait, there are people
That was that was a good that was a good shot
Watching a tubbo right now
How do you switch teams? You're watching. Oh, you just keep pressing next. Yeah, he's gonna keep going
I'm trying to learn as I watch
All the teams are just like trying to get as high as possible
For one second. I thought that was like a cars crossover and there was a car's skin. That was like lightning mcqueen
the price that's oh, I just turned to a
Ooh ipn and it's chun li from street fighter with the dump truck tubbo is bruno mars
Shit
I bet epic could just make celebrity deathmatch with all the ip they own
Or like have access to licensing too. So this squad is all still up
which is the
Crash yawn disguise toast. Oh, no, somebody's dead
Crashing just died. Oh, no, no questions right here
Yeah, uh the the health bar is like really bugged sometimes it'll just show people are dead when they're not
I feel like i'm stuck in between two teams
Yeah, i've had that happen to me. That's why I was asking like how do you switch teams?
But I just kept pressing next player and eventually I got out of the ken jutsu
I I don't I don't care about the flavored vape pens. I'm not gonna
Eat like inhale like apple cinnamon nicotine. No, I don't want to do that
Is there a way to see the list of yo, guess what you shouldn't either
You shouldn't even know what that is
You shouldn't even know what that is. You're not old enough to know what that is. I'm playing fortnight today
Yeah, i'm stuck in the tier zoo team now
Yeah, I said that you're spectating me now. I'm just gonna i'm just gonna sit here
Enjoy the view while I can I hate being like trying to switch out
Oh my god, every team is trying so hard. Holy shit
This is great. The tier zoos team is just in bushes at the edge of the map the very very edge daily doses bad, man
So you kind of just want to grab you want to get a bunch of items get a spot
And just kind of defend that spot till the circle that starts to kind of encroach on you, right?
Yeah
you also kind of want to play to kill people though like I think I think like the way that the
the team like tier zoos team is playing whether there's play on the edge of the map like
Best case scenario they get to like the final couple teams and they're in like a pretty bad position
And then they like maybe they probably die
And you get points for every kill your team has. Oh, okay. So you do
So you get like a certain amount of points for like placing top three
But you every kill you get also adds on top of that. So like you do have some level of pressure to be aggressive
Okay, which is why being somewhat central and being high up is good because then you get to see people trying to rotate
Uh, but you're also in like a good spot looking at uh, justin minx's team looks like it's going down here
Uh-oh
Oh, this is trouble
This is a lot of trouble
Oh
Not quite
Oh thermal is so busted man
so this is uh
I'm very invested
It's a good team right here. Who's anonymous 257. I want to know who that is. Yeah, I was wondering that too
Actually, we can look at this. Yeah, it's not it's not looking it's it's probably shra and actually, I don't know
That team is lily. It's lily
Is it lily? I don't hate fortnight. I just don't understand fortnight
So how many squads are still up? Uh, well, there's 40 people
But it doesn't say the team amount there's a big fight going on with timmy's team
I feel like i'm playing against like professional soccer players in a game of football
And I like am a video gamer
Oh my god, it's like when one of those celebrity athletes comes to your school to visit, uh, and you're like an elementary school
And they're just like giant giant mountains of humans and you're like damn and then it's oh we're gonna play
We're gonna play some uh baseball together and they just hit like five home runs and everybody cheers
Well, they're reviving holy shit dude alec, uh
My friend who got taken off our team his team is just destroyed
Happy for him. Um, I am happy for it was actually it's actually either you or him
What is going on over here, by the way?
It takes a long time to revive somebody does it?
Yeah, it takes 10 seconds, but you can double up you can like cut it in half if two people revive
Why was she just spray painting herself in the face
Uh, it's a heal. Oh, okay. Yeah, it heals you like 15 every like
Something every like half a second
That was oh
Who is that?
It's like the whole team
Who is prospering?
Oh, wow. I got puns puns is the only one on his team left. Oh, yeah, he is
Oh, he's right behind the team. This team doesn't see him
Somebody just said dude, why please tell me this is fake
My april fools joke was four days late. All right
Please tell me this is fake
I can assure you it's real but I can tell you it's a few days late
And I don't have the fake pen, but whatever
I'm just playing for it. I'm not kidding. I'm playing for it and i'm not kidding
I'm watching shroud and he's not he's not thirsting at all
He downs him and he moves on to the next chump. Yeah honorable gamer
It's xqc doing
He watched them to get revived so you can put them back down
Uh, he's like, please fucking rez. Oh, he's just better
Shit
Oh
Suc down
That was that was crazy
Tuber reaction. I gotta do something man was watching tv
Who's the shark who has the shark skin? It's just an actual shark in the game
It's like what the fuck is this?
Yeah, this game is terrible because they weren't doing anything I was like why are they not attacking this person
I thought it was like a transformation where he did like getting so oh my god. Yeah, dude
He's nuts
Dude, lovely wouldn't let our friend's little brother play because he's good at fortnight, but he let shroud in the tournament
Oh, like fucked up bro
Okay, he's down what shrouds is what shrouds name
Trouty rowdy rowdy. Oh my god. What can I not?
Oh, he just he literally just died. Oh, okay. The rest of his team is up
Huns is just big chilling. This is batman
Oh nade shots down. Is this the end of the team? Oh, they're rezzing. They got nade up. He has a med kit
Uh, did they where stream 2022? You can't say that yet. It's not over. He chowed with his level one account
Just vibing. Oh, whoever they're fighting right now is just so dead
What am I gonna add to make it better bro, I just told you we were doing tier lists after this
This is not gonna last that this is only gonna be like another like half hour 40 minutes
Do you guys see puns? He's just been hiding. Yeah
That is so smart, I almost just call this guy han solo what's bubblefets in the game?
Yeah, I think so. I think they just yeah, they just saw her stuff
That's kind of cool. All right daily doses team. It's wiped. Wait puns can win this
Oh, he fucked up. Oh tarik's the only one left on this team, I think unless the health bars are glitched while these whole teams is up
Oh
They should rush they should rush the nade team
Wait, is it one v one? No
I'm not gonna do a vape flavor tier list. I don't know what it even tastes like
It's probably probably tastes like ass. All right, so they're all going at f. They're like, oh my god. He like fifth partied
Oh, it's a four v one
Oh
What shot? Oh, that's toast toast to the last
Wait that oh, I was just on bubby's um pov and then I went right to do this when he headshot him
Anthony alex in the final team
That is crazy
Let's get evolved. Oh, that's
Okay, wow
All right rough start but
I think frost was prospering guys pretty good. I think we'll be all right this time
With the last first one didn't count second one. We just got unlucky like everybody went there and I was still figuring out how to detach the parachute
Um, I know how to do that. I know how to detach the parachute now
I think we're in a better position than we were before
We got it now. I'm optimistic. You know what they say jerma. You gotta be down to come back
Yeah
Also, you only ever win or learn that's a good way to put it. I learned so much
Just now watching that whole game the entire game
Is
They're predicting a lot of strats I actually got the most perspective because I got to watch every player who wasn't me
Why is it headshotting everybody? Okay. Let's get this second code going
Oh, man
I have to leave
I'll be right back. Wait, what happened? How do I get out of here?
uh top left
Or escape key maybe and then oh just bottom left is maybe a cancel bottom left. Yeah
Someone said we're not last which is kind of hype
No, we are we finished 19th. There's 19 teams. I'm banning that guy
Easy, so there's 19 teams. We came in 19th place. Yeah, I think we we got well, we got really unlucky. We really did
It's not over. I wish there was still five matches but
People in my chat are voting to see if we're gonna win the next round
um
It's not a it's not a uh straight bet. What would you say they go?
What if you were taking odds on this? What's the odds that we come in first place next next game?
one in 19
No
I think it's 100 percent
Yeah, 100 percent. I'm on the 100 percent. We're winning this one. We got unlucky like
Yeah, I think the payout would be like
6000 to one
If you would have bet on us right now
Are the odds that's hype. Yeah, somebody could make a lot of money
I just feel like the results of the last match were indicative of our team's overall skill. Mm-hmm or
Connectiveness or
Chemistry. Yeah, I think I think I think we should stay away from blimps because blimps are a little confusing
They're like genuinely confusing to navigate on the inside and get to and get up and down and we can just go to like
Just some town and loot up, you know
Also want to make sure I get because I don't want to be a moron when we start this
If one of you guys goes down
Is is it you know you get to a position where you can like a left for dead revive somebody, right?
Just like e hold e tap. Yeah, you hold it. You hold it. Okay
Yeah, and you can't you can't move around like physically while doing it. You have to just stay still
Okay, you're kind of using your your positional currency by rising. This is cool regardless
No, it's only cool if we win. I was gonna wait till we won and then we could
Say this is only fun because we won
Not now
It's just unlucky we got
Doing the we two teams that are like really really really good teams that have really good players
We ran into them back to back first second
It is crazy that we fought tarik's team and then we got a lucky reset and then we fought xqc's team
Yeah, I know right. I killed I killed someone on that blimp. I killed I don't know who they were like that's some weird name
I think it might have been
ipn
I wish I would have landed on the blimp dude if we would have killed that team
Um, it's so nice. Fuck the stream's not over yet
Oh, I can't wait. I can't wait for those worst dream 2022 andes
To wait till I do the full from software every single boss ever tier list because that's coming up and I want I want to
See your face when you see how fun that is
But I get cool backpacks i'm gonna buy something right now. You got me inspired hot bullet time is so swag
I'm i'm very confident. We'll at least
We will at least land this time
And at least congregate somewhere with weapons
Desert get you a rifle in your hand. I have fish sticks in the oven. Um
Man, let me ask you guys this in the call here. Yeah, so
You know how in the back of a lot of frozen foods?
it's like
50 plus minutes sometimes to heat up but it's like four minutes in the microwave
Yeah, how?
When do you guys decide to use the oven?
Can I tell you my my filthy little secret my my filthy little dirty secret I have sure
uh
I prefer microwaved food totally oven-made food. Yeah. Yeah, you're just like you're just like a sludge monster
It's because it's fast just because it's faster and you know, you can for me for me for me
It's because it's faster like I know no for me. It is taste. That's why I am a filthy monster
I actually think that how do I put this?
You know how like you know shit that you put in the oven in microwave
It's already like a certain quality threshold that it can't break through
Like it has a hard ceiling of how good it can be also game two's in the thing
I have the code in there and we're ready. We're ready. Yeah. Awesome
What's the last thing you guys ate that was a like a microwaved food or a frozen food?
Uh
Microwaving I I do microwave leftovers all the time. That's just simple. No, but like a packaged like disgusting trash meal
I had a uh
I had a di giorno pizza on my trip to arizona a couple weeks ago brotherhood. Yeah, that's all right
No, but I mean I I wouldn't put that in the microwave
I would never put would you ever put a chicken pot pie in the microwave? Yeah. Oh, come on. I used to eat those
That's why i'm only this tall
It's stunted your growth the frozen chicken pot pie has to go in the oven even it takes like an hour it has to
Yeah, maybe for you. I guess yeah
Maybe if you maybe you're free from the 50s and you and you hand crank your radio
Can you do it in black and white? Yeah, i'm fucking busy brother
All right, so what everyone what would you put it up? Oh god damn. I'm such a driver ready
It's always talking about chicken pot pies
Is that why they came somebody said they came to watch you stream?
We're just sitting here talking about frozen food and I didn't ready up yet. Sorry about the banter
Savnet, what's the last frozen food thing you ate? Dude, I actually don't remember you live healthy. Yeah, you're eating good
That's really good though. Let's be honest. I I have yeah, I I try to eat pretty good
Yeah, I don't I don't remember the last frozen food thing, but yeah, I really don't
I used to grind final fantasy 14 and just eat pop tarts all day in college
I think I just like 2 000 calories a day in pop tarts again. It's why my bones i'm sure are hollow like a bird's
I remember my first year of college. I'd yeah, I used to eat so much like yeah pop tarts and like
What's it called hot pockets and that type of stuff? I'd tear it up
You know what actually is good in the microwave is those trader joe's, uh tiki masalas those are unbelievable trader joe's
Constantly is blowing me away. That actually might be the best frozen food item that exists
Is the tiki masala from trader joe's like honest to god? It's it's there's nothing that compares frozen wise germa
Who is your best friend? Um
Uh burger boy. Wait, what was that burger boy? Are we getting owned burger boy these nuts in your mouth?
Whoa, hey
I don't know
I try to get ahead of it
Oh burger boy. Look, I don't have a best friend because I think that that's stupid because it called it
All of your other
All of your other friends then have to know oh that's your best friend
No, I have everyone's on the same playing field for me dibs. Well, we're not we're not there yet
You can't a centrist. How is that a centrist?
It's a centrist position. Yeah, that person is correct
No, they are not because I don't have a best friend makes me a centrist. Yeah. Yes, sir. Mr. President, sir
Sapnap, who's your best friend? Um
I guess like my my takes I have like a few you know what I mean?
That's fair like my with my group of like friends that i'm like really close with i'd probably be like dream george
carl quackety
It's a circle rather than like yeah, it's like a circle. It's not like yeah, you are incredibly well rounded
Can I just say like you're right?
You've got like you have a good standing with friends. Yeah
You are very well rounded you go for the blimp. You know when to knock over the blimp
I'm gonna need you to start pointing out some flaws if you're gonna gel with this team
Well, let me guess you care too much you work too hard. Yeah, I guess i'm just too goated show up early
No, okay. I'm really bad. I i'm bad showing up on time
So what's what's the plan here guys? What are we doing? All right, we're in the game and I think you guys want to crank it shifty shafts
Let's do it wherever you guys want to go wherever you guys want to go. I think shifty shafts is good
Um, I think if there's a lot of people we stay together. We stay together like a tight unit
Yeah, yeah exactly we we crank it to the lumber yards. There's like a million people here
sounds good
It's like a team
Yeah, like a team they're dropping before we pivot
You guys want to pivot?
I'm too close to pivot. I can't get it anymore. All right. All right, we're sticking to it stick to it, baby
Fuck I got a sniper rifle. Oh
I'm with you. There's one gonna chase us right now. We'll get down get down behind it down here down here
I'm down
Oh, no, i'm coming
No way i'm fucking down again. Shit
Okay, back to me back to me back to me. Yeah, i'm coming to you
Oh fuck. Oh my god. No, not again
Anthony live anthony live
Oh my god, what the fuck don't fight anthony you're gonna live you're gonna live me up and run
i'm living
No, please
What's happening we got killed by shroud and we got killed by
This is ridiculous
In the casino of life we seem to fucking keep losing dude, is that is that for real are you kidding?
Holy shit, i'm gonna lose my fucking mind. I swear
We gotta pick a spot on the map. That's like in the ocean
We are going so fucking far away. We just want to I just want to at least stream the game for five minutes
Dude shroud is just tearing everyone up. I'm sorry. Oh my god
He's just better
He's literally using the deagle. I i'm mad up. Oh shit
I mean it i'm mad about losing to him, but it's it's just you love to see him walk away, too
You know what I mean?
What the fuck no dude ludwig undefin he better fucking undefin what say something ludwig
What can I help you every fucking drop? We have dropped into goddamn shroud
You know shroud is uh, you know, he's pretty fucking good
Yeah, here's the thing pay money wubbies beating him. So
Yeah, he's held out by his teammates, dude
This is unreal
No, this is
Hey
No, we we've landed three separate spots. We've ran into shroud twice and xqc's came the other time
Hey, good luck game three guys. Good luck game three
I just want to hold a weapon to watch the whole fucking game again. Oh my god, dude
I just I just want to know what it's like to shoot a weapon
I know
No, I I knew because like I ran downstairs like like in the mines and I was like destroying someone and I got
Two tapped by a deag and I was like damn whoever two tapped me with that deag is really good
And then I saw the fucking kill feed and I was like god damn it
Bro, okay. Now you can nominate for worst room
um
After that one because it'd be like what am I supposed to do about it?
What am I supposed to do?
Is that oh I land we land and which is dead. I I haven't even held a weapon yet
I don't even know what this is like
I don't know what the trajectory of moving your character feels like
Like I don't know what the the knots per second it is when you actually walk around
I don't think i've walked around. I think i've landed with the parachute
And died in five to ten seconds
Oh my god
I mean, it's funny, but I mean, I was just sure a lot of content going on for me
You know you want to come over zap nap
He's earned it honestly
He's had too good for too long
Yeah, I said I think i'm gonna surprise some people if I had a
I have had fucking minecraft axe in my hand
And i'm I don't know what like all these places are I haven't even held a weapon yet
If you put a weapon in my hand
But I like I was about to I was about to walk around the corner and melee swing at shroud
Do you understand like what out dire it is right now on this team? We just keep I
He would have thought I was a bot. He would have thought I was about this is path
So what if
Sorry, okay. What if we if there's a team we just fucking go away like we don't take the initial flight ever
Yeah, we loot first. We loot first no matter what even if we think the team's bad
So it's like if we see a team, uh, you know, we just mark a different spot overshoot or something like that
I think that's our best chance to get out of the yeah
Maybe we even maybe we even drop really high so that we have advantage on like where people are going
We can decide
We would we don't we don't need to hit the ground first if we're going somewhere. No one went
Oh, no daily dose
I love that guy
He's hiding he's trying not to die I hate that guy but I like his content so I should have done
You hate him because he's
Seating the game looks like he's trying to get him water. He's like water, please
I feel like he's gonna put his head in there and start shrinking
Someone said at least we're consistent and that is true and valid and right he's lost in the desert
Oh, no
What? Oh, they're on the same team. Okay
crowds in a semi-truck man
rocket launcher
This is a cool fortnight react stream
Yeah, yeah reacting to the ludwig tournament
Hey, i'm doing tier lists after this. I was gonna be live anyways
wubby currently
exchanging fire
Damn
Oh, he's good at this game like really good
Yeah, I actually didn't watch him play less the whole last game and then he's just
Finished first
I think he had it like that
Me can we at the very least get in a laugh out loud car?
Yeah, buddy we can do that
Can we like if we're gonna die and we lose then to get in the last place
Can we at least do like the funny we're in the car joke?
Okay for all you war stream ever andes, all right
And so i'm not i'm not i'm gonna redress it anymore. I'm not gonna address it anymore. I'm just telling you
You need to respect me for a minute
Respect me for one moment
Okay
Worst stream ever andes need to quiet
w
We seem to get I feel like I actually feel like we have a good chance if we can just get
Like stay alive
Do I have I have died with no gun in my hand both matches me too
I I turn the corner and there's two people dead and then
And then I get like I don't know like an assassin throws a knife in the back of my neck
I don't even know what happens to me
I'm getting so much shit in my chat. Everybody hates me. Oh my god
Shroud is so good
Yeah, I just said that you guys were like hating so they'd be like, oh, i'm sorry, dude. Oh
Wait, what did what did what we say?
I'm watching his incredible gameplay. It's good
What what what bro you're killing it? Thanks
I'm gonna the camera and say
No, you got knocked out by a team on blimp. Oh
By dr. Lupo. He's pretty good. Oh stan took down shroud. He's not gonna talk stop talking about that for six months
What was gonna get what was gonna get a headshot writer? Yeah, i'm watching too. Check it out
Let's get bingo writer headshot. Oh
oh
Tariq is not missing
Good recovery. Yeah, those types of players are good at not missing. Just kidding starting to miss
People think that i'm cursing this team
No, it's possible. Let me tell you the problem's not you
I would I honestly wish it was
Tariq is so good
Mango down mochi down valkyrie down. Oh, I think valkyrie's on mango's team, which is such a funny crossover
Trout's team is dipping his xqc still love. I want to watch xqc stream. Yeah. Thank you. I still love
I feel like i'm just watching twitch right now. Just going through the fortnight channel
And we're they're all playing fortnight
Yeah, this is awesome. Here we go. All right, just do a magic trick while we wait. Um
I don't think I have the availability to do that. I could
I'll be right back. I'm gonna do a magic trick for everybody. I'll be right back
Wait, what?
Dude, he he changed his mind. He should have been firm with the chat. He said I don't have the availability for that
I'll be right back. Hey, can we go to mcdonald's please please please please please please no five seconds. Yeah, let's get in the car
Yeah, okay, you'd be good
So what's the germa responsive chat messages like they're work emails?
Stream title is just playing fortnight. I'm not kidding
Who?
germa
Oh this guy's a leather banana
I don't like that. I don't like even it being called that sexual you play you play minecraft, right tap nap
Yeah
Do you do you still enjoy it these days as much as you used to when you got into it?
Um, I think now these days it's i'm much more relying on like I need to be playing with like my friends before
I used to like sweat minecraft. I was just playing just to be like good. So now it's more social
Yeah, it's like if your friends don't want to play you're probably not playing. Yeah, exactly
Oh shit, that's why I don't play csgo. We're the same. Oh god. I played so much csgo
All my friends switched to valorant and I was like, I can't I guess i'm playing valorant now, which is fine
But I missed the ak-47
Yeah, I just miss cracking cases. Honestly, that's
If they would just put opening cases in valorant, I would I would have nothing left in counter-strike. I'm in
Okay, i'm back. I just I like counter-strike's movement got a little trick for you here
You'd like to see it feels like a little clunky, but valorant. I actually enjoy valorant more
Like just a quick one. Yeah, I I agree with that. I think uh, pretty much like I think that I like that counter-strike
Rewards you for being good at b-hopping. My hands are so greasy instead of making b-hopping and like not a thing. Yeah
I also think that they made a counter-strafing
Not a thing. So yeah counter-strafing is like it's like bad like you can't there's no
there's no jiggle peeking right i'm like in csgo like
like you can jiggle peek a corner and just like
tap heads and valorant it's not as
Yeah, and valorant you can just let go of the movement key and it you're accurate the same speed as if you counter-strike
Yeah, when I jiggle in valorant, I feel like i'm getting made fun of like in a discord or somewhere
Look at this guy. What is what is what do you think he's doing? He's playing the wrong game
You play valorant a lot slap sap amp. Yeah, I do. What's your rank diamond three diamond? Oh, he's a gamer
Yes, sir. Me too. I'm also that i'm actually immortal
20 20
26 we should play I think I think I was d3 at the end of the season and I think i'm d2 right now
I haven't played much. I haven't been home for like the whole entire last month
We can get our we can get our ego up after this play some valorant. Yeah
All right, guys
That's a game I win at I'd like for you guys to make it just a quick quick u-turn over to my stream for a second
Yeah, I knew that get it open. It's cracking. Let's see
I'd like to show you I've got two hands here holding a penny you can see
This hand is nothing in it. Let's just go and make sure there's no strings there
No strings. Yeah, i'm on i'm on you i'm on no strings at all
And if we could turn that penny be nice if we could turn that into 50 cents, wouldn't it?
That'd be pretty cool. You know turn that into 50 cents, wouldn't it? Oh shit
That's kind of clean
50x yeah, that's a 50x 50x on on
Whoa on might of raw
My stream sucks
Yeah, no, I I know a little bit of magic why you stream you could just do that like a hundred more times and
You'd be set. It's exponential if it keeps doubling. Would you like to know how to do it?
Would you let me to do the thing where the guy doesn't have the whole tv show about all the magic
The masked magician. Yeah, that show is so awesome
You know magicians were pissed about that. Really? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah that guy was in like a lot of trouble
What
Is he like I like I like how they did shit. I like the idea of like a large group of magicians
I'm going to make your wife disappear
So if you guys want to like, you know
Impress your friends and stuff you you have to open with like the fun line of gosh man
That's stock market
Don't you wish you could die, you know buy buy a stock or security and have it go up by 50x
Like you start with that like, you know corny shit and then they go. Whoa, they lean in they get really curious
And then what you say is you say i've got a penny here and what you've got you do have a penny
But what you also have is you hold the two quarters here as well. The two quarters sit
Uh, is that perpendicular? What is that? Oh, I see. Yeah perpendicular. Oh, that's correct
So you make the ad it blocks everything especially it's like how could you even hold those quarters there show them the other hand
And then and then and then say excuse me you you in the audience. Excuse me
Would you would you like to buy one cent in my my new stock here and then they go
Of course, I will in this context really quick just so I can clarify i'm trying to learn
Um, so you're already on stage as a magician. Yes got it
Okay
Okay, so what we do is you take your thumb raise the bottom of the penny slide it underneath the second quarter grip
Hole with the other hand hide it behind the quarter. Oh, let's slide a hand
Yeah, no, that that's how you do it. Why do you ever do the thing where you uh, you put the salt shaker under the napkin
And you smash it
Uh, yeah, you like slide it off the table first and then you like smash it. Yeah, that's a good one
That's that's a that's a wow. That's a wild classic. Okay, so let's try to uh, pick a weapon up this time
Yeah, let's try to like survive longer than two minutes. Yes
I feel good about this game. Actually you take two turns like your your pokemon like rests for two turns
Then it comes out with like a really big attack. Yeah, we got we're winning this next game. Fuck it
I don't care speak it into the world bro. I'm with you
Okay, you want to hear the the prediction that's running over here? What's that is will I pick up a gun before I die?
And honestly like those odds are not great if you really think about
Yeah, if you're looking at statistics purely then the odds are not in your favor yet gambler fallacy, bro
It's not like it's going to influence the next event, you know
Think about that temple sapper. Honestly, I have two chap sticks
Um two different flavors play one game of fortnight with sap now. I got minecrafters following me. What happened to my skin?
I had a skin that I was happy. It made me look like a sweat and now I can't find it anywhere. I found it
Look, oh yeah, we're gonna be scared of us. That's yeah
Maybe we should all change skins because we sort of train people to think that we're easy
Yeah, they see they see like the the the blintz yaga and they're like, ah, really? That's all these fuckers
We're gonna ride guys. Can they see my level? Uh, I don't think they can when they spectate you
Yeah, all right, but not in the game. They don't go look level one get them
I don't think a single person has been able to spectate you yet, though
Any of us that is true. I didn't think about that. There's just nothing to watch for any of us. All right
I got my sweat costume. Oh, it's probably like, you know, where are these guys? What are they?
Are they even here? Do they go home? Yeah. Yeah, that's it. It's true
What you see lewis announcement? Wait, what do you do winning team?
All gets a $1,000 massage chair delivered to their home. All right guys, come on
We gotta quit fucking around now if we win the rest of them. We have a chance
It's true. We have two more matches. We have three, right?
No, they got rid of the fifth one. So we have to the time. Yeah. Oh my god. I know
Even if we win the next year, I don't even think we could win
We have to kill like the half the server. I wouldn't put it past us though. We have that
And I think we do have it we've actually gotten kind of it's been a little it's been a little rough where we've landed
Yeah, what the fuck? I'm so mad. I can't believe it. I can't wait to be diving
Look over and diving right next to me at the exact same speed as shroud
He just winks at you and just like oh, oh
Okay, if that happens, i'm just telling you guys i'm gonna pop parachute and i'm just going i'm just floating him to somewhere else
He's abandoning us mr president goes to the fallout shelter
I know I know shroud's skin now so I can determine if it's him. I think i'll actually beat that prediction though
I think i'll get a gun before dying this time
We have such a cool squad too. We could do so much fun
We could get in the car we could go jump around the buildings and stuff like come on we have this is such a cool squad
That's what i'm saying. I'm trying to have a goddamn wonder years episode with my boys
I never finished that show. I need to finish that
I remember was on netflix and I grinded it. I was
Why was that show so good
It's a really good question. I seemingly I like I remember it being like insanely good when I was watching it
Wait, what show?
Wonder years
It was a good show. Is it just is coming of age american coming of age just like hit the sweet spot in our brains
Maybe well that show was um, his brother had a mullet. That was how long was that show on the air?
I feel like it was on for a really long time. All right, we got the game three code
All right, let's get involved
All right
This is our game. I am trying so hard everyone ready up including you germa. Yep. Yep. I know I was waiting for it
I want them a massage chair. That would be I mean kind of cool
My boss are i'm just gonna buy one with the company card
Even if we lose I don't give a shit. I'm charging ludwig's card a thousand dollars for a massage chair
Regardless if we drop next to shroud this match, I am buying a massage chair on company dime
In between the match
We put it on the podcast next week. We call it a business expense. This is this is mogul moves
He's just telling me he ordered an extra three accidentally or something
Yeah, my bad. Oh shit
That would be for you three. I don't deserve one
No, you deserve one. No, you deserve one. What the hell get that mentality up. I don't want to hear that
Yeah, come on it doesn't matter because we're just gonna win it anyways, but like on the off chance we don't
Right. Yeah, even if we do win i'm buying a second one to let him know that his tournament was bad
Nick myth is in our house fishing for compliments. Somebody said
Even though I just pulled up his stream ludwig's stream. Should we go ask him for help?
He hops on my setup, bro, hop on my fucking pc, please
Let's do it. We're gonna do it this time. It's gonna be good
We are gonna be golden. We're gonna it's gonna be awesome
You sound like you're about to go on the stage for the talent show
To do my magic tricks. I feel so good right now. We're gonna be electric. I got the coin trick
The crowd can't even see the types of coins you're holding
So far away, what is that? My go-to magic trick was uh, that one from you guys you ever see now you see me
Yes
There's the intro scene where he like flips the deck of cards and he's like did you see that card and he pulls it
Out and the one the audience all saw that was my go-to
I my brain can't even remember half that movie. My that movie is just a trailer of people like throwing cards at each other
That that's not you see me too
Oh, what's the one where they robbed the they robbed the bank? That's the first one. That's the first one. That was pretty cool
When somebody was like the eye or something, right?
Uh, there's like something like
Yeah, yeah, it was like a magical like super magician, right and he was like, yeah. Yeah
It was the main FBI agent, right?
Spoilers. Oh shit. I did I I I have a t-vote. I have a t-vote
I didn't get didn't get to see the last arc. How old is that movie? Is it are you allowed to my guess?
My guess is
2013 maybe 2012. That's a good guess
See now you see me
2013 on the dot. Let's fucking go nice. Nice job
I thought it was entertaining though. It was an entertaining movie. I loved it in the fun watch
Morgan freeman's in it. Oh, yeah, morgan freeman is in that movie
Don't they like switch a room where he's like standing somewhere and then they like teleport him or something somewhere else
Yeah, one probably put him like a jail cell at one point. It's kind of crazy. It was a good watch. Yeah
What's the the actress in hot rod is in it? What's your name? Fisher?
Yeah, yeah
She's in uh bored to death, which is a really funny show hbo
All right, the prestige was a magic movie as well. What are the magic movies were there?
uh
aladdin
The illusionist I think is one magic mike harry potter is not no it doesn't count
i'm talking like a magician that goes on stage and like
Look a disappearing act and here like a magician not inside lou and davis, but it's the magic of the illusionist is
The illusionist is the uh, the ed norton
I'll write a movie
All right, guys, let's uh, let's let's go for at least 18th place this time. This is it
All right, look guys. We got one. We got one minute and 23 seconds to actually play the game
Swing your little pickaxe around have some fun
What does it feel like to shoot it
That's all I need one bullet. That's all I need. Oh man
Oh, i'm gonna oh
Is there bullet drop?
There is okay. All right. Let's like you guys want to go chonkers speedway. It's kind of fuck. I don't know
I don't even want to call anything. No, I think that's a good idea
Chonkers let's go to chonkers
And but let's stay together and if a shitload of people go we audible drop it
I'm gonna drop high and i'm gonna give intel. Yeah, what's that's the marker you guys put? Yeah. Yeah
I swear to fucking god
If shroud is here, i'm gonna lose it. Lovely is already spectating us. I don't like that. Yeah
I gotta be I think i'll be far away from chonkers speedway. I hope not
All right. I don't see anyone. I don't see anyone. This might be our we have one
Person who's with us. There's there's one person
They might drop early though
Is it one person or a team?
It has to be a team. No one would drop alone. Yeah, we have a team with us. We have a team with us
All right, we have to fuck them up
Do we want to fight or do we want to run?
We're going to fight
Fucking we're fighting. Okay. This has worked for us every time. So I mean
Someone's already in a car. They're in a car
Well, i'm getting shot at
It's gonna be a gun right here, right? All right. I cracked this guy's shield and oh motherfucker
I'm gonna gonna come into you uh sap map
Sounds good
I'm I need this
There's a guy on the hill on
Okay over there on that side
Yo, can you grab that keg? That's right. There's that a keg
Need a fucking gun
No, this is like a this is a tent. It's chest over here. All right, i'm gonna get this chest
jerma get a fucking gun in your hands
Got it got a gun
The test is where daily dose is in radius. So
Yeah, daily doses team is in our uh in our thing
Hey, this is this is looking pretty good boys. I like this so far
All right. So what else what else am I looking for here ammo weapons?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, all the above you want to get full shield you want to get a good assault rifle
That's not gray
And you're pretty you're pretty much it. All right
I got heels I think
What i've six small parts as well. Stop doing this i'm gonna get a headshot
Every gun i've seen is great. Holy shit. Eat these jerma eat them. You can eat two. I got many guys
Yeah, let's get back on
Um, what about the tire? How do I get right? I don't want this
What did I just do? I just threw it like it like an ape. Okay. All right. All right
Okay
All right, this zone's kind of far. Do you guys want to start? Oh, we have cars actually
Yeah, I think we just I think we just rely on the car and we don't engage people like uh, yeah
Yeah, we should say the fuck away from everyone. We should definitely grab as much uh,
Health and shield as we can for sure
I have uh, I have what's it called splash. I could throw it at everyone. I've got six minis
I don't know. I went in the dumpster
Yeah
No, I thought I was dead dude, I was like what the fuck somebody like sniped me it was terrifying
Yeah, you you transported right? Yeah, I jumped off a building and it went in the dump. I'm so sorry. I just know it's okay
It's the same thing. That was important. I got my adrenaline up and that's gonna help me aim
I'm so i'm too i'm too neurotic to play this game
I think I think we're we're pretty mentally beaten, you know, so we gotta
It's it's very fair to feel good to actually like run around and shit. Holy fuck seriously
Yeah, I didn't know this game had controls
I gotta do this before we'd all right. Oh my god. We're far away from that. Aren't we pretty far?
Let's just start cranking it that way
You're pretty far nick. Yeah, i'm coming. Is there a reason why batman is on the screen right now blinking?
Yeah, that's like it's about if we kill him on the map. There's a yellow circle. That's where he is
Shock grenades are big that cars us that's nick. Yep
All right. We picked a good place to drop this time
All right, my loot pretty trash. Yeah, I got I got I got some minis up here someone wants to grab those. I have no space
We need to get like a keg would be really nice so we can all get up to 100 shield. I can splash us
All right, let's meet up in this house. Let's splash
Okay, there's no there's a blimp here. So be careful that there might be people on it
Let's see
The car
Here, what's splash up right here? I don't see anybody in the blimp
So is a smart thing to do just to yell out the number at the top of the screen
Yeah, that's pretty good. There's also 319. That works like like when when people shoot there's a red little uh thing that pops up on it
Wait, you say there's people 319
No, no, no, that was a dummy call out. Yeah, okay
Did no one go to this blimp? I'm kind of scared to go to this blimp and loot it
But this town looks unlooted below it. Yeah, we also don't have a lot of time
Yeah, but we can you we can use that we should go to the bump
What's with the bump because we can use the blimp to fly to your own frames. Oh
Uh, anyone have can you hold smalls? Uh sound up you hold small pots. I got I got six already
Actually, I can eat the big
Yeah, I could I would eat it. Never mind. I'll hold it. I got it
Dude, there's so much loot in this town. We should just yeah, let's loot loot this town and then use wait
This chest is open. This chest is open. Yep. That's true. Could be team here. I'm going over here
Going on the blimp
I'm gonna go with you. I'm not gonna i'm kind of scared to go in it
Maybe i'll take a little gandy. Yeah, this is looted. I'm just gonna stay on top of the blimp
i'm actually use use the blimp to
Glide out
That's a call
We all had enough. Yep. Yeah, and then we're just gonna fly away using the like the propeller things
I bet the team that was here already left. Yeah, I think they did as well
I think we should just be
Pussies and just stay like on the edge of the zone. Yeah. Oh shit. We gotta go now. Oh my god
It's coming out. It's not gonna hurt too bad. But yeah, i'm already in right on you
Okay, there's a blimp right here probably guaranteed a team on it. So stay away from that
There's some people in there. We should stay away from tilted in general. That's gonna be fucking
terrible
We should just keep looting these outer
Little things like this little hut and shit
There's still 60 people alive, bro. There's a green og in here. Just pretty nice on one set. I will need that
Did I heal a little bit or should I take this big?
Yep, when you when we get safe you can heal up but you shouldn't really need to because you can't heal with a bandage
And it's a waste of a medkit
Uh, there's mushrooms over here on my ping if you want to get your shield finish off
Okay, so the teams that are in tilted are gonna start moving towards us because of the next circle
So we should probably run like completely out of here. It's like let's go this way
Oh, there's a team people fighting in front of us. There's a fucking tank. Oh, it's a battle bus. Oh shit
Yeah, we should stay the fuck away from that. I do have a rocket. I have three purple rockets
No, we shouldn't fight on a thing give away in the I can kill one
Not nice. Nice. Good job. Finish up. Nice. We gotta kill
I didn't see anything. I was spraying myself in the face
No, that's
You're doing your job. You're you're using less that player made a call out where we are
So we should probably reposition. Yep
Do you think the rest of the teams right they're either right up here? I see over here. Wait, a car just turned on right next to me
Guy but jumping. Okay, I think we're getting run up on and done up on
Careful. Oh shit. I'm getting hit
This guy right here in front of me
Chilling i'm coming to you. I'm gonna come to you. I'm gonna fight with you. I'm backing up here
Yep, I don't really like maybe we just go back where we came from
Oh right right fire
Covering fire. Ah
Right there on my ping. He's he's coming behind us. He's flanking that tree. No, no, no, no, no
On us on us on us
God I don't I don't even I have a stay alive. Stay alive. Stay alive
I want you to I want you to stay all the way to the end, baby. Ah, that was excuse me
Okay, of course
Oh
Don't even engage to stay alive get get us towards the end. There's we have I think we have so many meds on
We have so many meds on us that you can stay in the oh shit. There's a guy right there
What I need is pause pause my fucking spotify
You're like the little brother that their mother forced them to play with their older brother
I mean, yeah, this is the first okay. I don't even know what the weapons distances are
It's fun, but
Because they're gonna dip right now and then you have a bunch of heels
I hope these okay as long as they didn't take them all turn the shadow with shadows off help
I don't why why am I dropping frames? That's fucking annoying then with this tree
Hey, all you gotta do stay alive simple enough. All right storm coming in
There's no fucking heels. Holy shit
Hold on. Okay
Yes, oh so swag that was the most swag thing i've ever seen
Holy shit, that was pretty cool
You got a great circle
Dude, holy shit. If you actually get those rezzes off
This is doable
I don't know the only fuck the only one is there it's gonna be tough reboot van
Yeah, when you die, you drop a little card and you go to the van and you can redeploy us
But you got to collect the card which he just did
Yeah, the frames are dropping because I went back to the original ingest server a week ago and now it's having problems again
Hooray, that's fucking fantastic. So i'm just gonna go to the other one and never turn back
You gotta be worried about getting fucking sniped from someone. There's so many players. Like they have one like has to be near you
Yeah, I know. Hopefully I can catch someone coming into the circle or something
So if you get to that van you can revive everybody
Yeah, wait, can I get in that battle bus?
That's a player. You saw one. Yeah. Yeah, hopefully the bus is probably out of gas if it's just sitting there
Oh, I can maybe steal some kills here. Oh nice. Yes, sir
That's x bro
The party bus
Oh shit i'm on fire with yes, sir
That was that was ridiculous. What just happened?
Someone blew it up with I think a rocket
X is probably still downed on that. Uh, Ron. No, no his friends are picking him up for sure
Yep, I didn't want to check do this. No, no, no, no, no. Yeah, I think you're in a good spot
Oh
How do you see me there that's crazy way better way better this time boys
Wow
All right, i'm reporting him
That's really the only option. Yeah
Dude, oh my xqc shroud xqc shroud delta was or no xqc shroud shot xqc
Yeah, I guess he knew maybe he just knew from where I shot him last time. He was just waiting looking for me there
I'm gonna brib one second. I'm switching twitch servers
All good. Look that was a lot better. We got all right. I'm switching servers
I'll switch the servers stream's gonna go off for 30 seconds. I'll be right back. Okay, i'm back
You got a gun germa and that's huge. That means you're improving. That's huge. Oh puns is down
Oh connor's down. Oh, I think that's it for the one and he's about to go down too. Yep. Well, it's all up to george
He's me man 13. All right, so we're not 19th
No, we are far from it us getting two kills that game probably solidified us not last
Which I can't stress this enough for you germa that is enormous when you live with the guy running the tournament
He's he's just gonna be such a pain in my ass about this
Why what do you mean?
well, ludwig is very competitive person and uh
I kind of made a big deal about
the fortnight tournament from last week
and uh
He's just he's just gonna he's just gonna rub it in and he's too strong. So I can't I can't
Is ludwig playing in this tournament?
No, he's just commenting. Oh, okay. He did last time he played and then hosted it
But I think that's too much which is understandable. Yeah jumping or he's spectating that much too
Is there gonna be one next week as well every monday?
Until he decides not to do him anymore
He really did pick a terrible day, huh? Anthony
Second worst dream. Hey refresh i'm back
No more dropped frames. I'm never going back to that server again
What right when I said it are you kidding me at a specific time ludwig londay?
Then he adds the fortnight event. Why is he going past it? I guess I guess
Drum shotgun is that good if he's like passing up a purple
Uh auto shotgun it is the drum. It's like drum over any other shotgun
Carl seems really deep into this
What the fuck why did it get worse? Oh my god, i'm about my internet's about to go off
Am I still in the call with you guys?
Yeah, yeah, yeah
My connection to the twitch servers are fucking awful right now
Wait carl's are you guys watching carl like his team could just annihilate this. Yeah. Yeah, this is there there's
They're set if I was him. I would just open fire on these guys. I wonder who's igle. Who's who's telling him to hold back?
I don't know. I guess the only reason yeah
If it was this this is the thing that's the most annoying thing about the twitch server shit
If this was my internet, I would be that call would be all robotic. What the fuck
Why does twitch hate my connection coming in? It's fucking annoying. I'll be right back one more time, dude
I I cannot connect to twitch my my internet is perfect. What like what the fuck?
I don't understand why this keeps happening
I cannot connect to twitch's twitch's server is a junk for me, but i'm in the game. My internet's fine
Um, listen
Oh carl get shot out of the sky
Look at this. Oh, it's a 4v1
Unreal
But I my call's not robotic. It's only connecting to twitch. What the fuck i'm trying something else. I'm trying something else be right back
Okay, let's try let's try this guys. I don't fucking get it
Murdered it out
Okay, when this is over i'm mutating ludwig. I'm deleting his phone number. I'm queuing valor and feel something dude
Well, let's just move out
I'm tired
I'm weary
Okay, so I i'm just like routing my traffic
In about you know, I don't know why twitch hates my connection so much sometimes
But I went to three or four different servers. What the fuck is happening? All right. We're good
All right. I'm good to go. I'm back
They couldn't hold us down forever
That was better though. That was better. We got one more
Yeah, one more last game. Let's try I kind of want I kind of want there just to be five
Dude, right the false start at the beginning was well was great for us. I won't lie
Yeah
That's fixed now cool. Yeah, so I have no idea why that keeps happening
randomly for no reason
my
Data coming in through twitch from vegas. It just hates it and it just kills me
But I jump around to like five different servers and it's like, okay. I'm gonna here you go. You're fine
Literally like as if the problem never existed
None of my internet goes down. I'm at full speed full speed ahead. Nothing. I don't get it
You got zero viewers. Shut up
Laying in bed, can I be honest? I've gotten a battle royale
In uh pubg mobile before oh really you played too
And when it first came out in high school, I played it a little bit when I was on class
That's high. That's dude
How old are you?
Uh, 21. Oh my god. I'm 10 years older than you kids had it so good. You know what I did we played psp
Grant f. Dotto liberty city stories and we wi-fi like
Multi-playered I shot my friend jfk style out of a convertible with a sniper rifle on a psp
It's actually my greatest gaming achievement to this day
I
You say that you're 10 years older got some news for you
I am the middle bear here, huh? Super mario brothers released by the regular nintendo
That's fucked up
Yeah, I was I was a model warfare 2 land in high school
I had to get uh
My father would always come over and say hey get me six lives and get me to the last boss
And i'll beat it because we just couldn't do it me and my siblings
So we would have we would spend the whole game trying to get to six lives to get to the last part
The last level where bowser was and my dad would take the controller and he would beat it as long as we had six lives
Why?
Why was he why was he it was like a sweatshop?
Well, no, he was just he knew he could beat the game at that point
He'd almost memorize the level but in case he died three or four times
He didn't want to upset his children. What if he didn't do it anthony ready up. Oh, sorry. Sorry. That is extremely funny
How many stepped up how many pubg mobile victor rails under your belt? Oh god, I don't know
Maybe I feel like whenever I was playing I was playing against like bots
So I got quite a few but like it wasn't it didn't feel like good like, you know what I mean?
I feel rewarding. You know what I want
I want pubg like the actual game to come back that game whenever that came out that was like
Peak like that was one of the most funs i've had on it was so fun
Yeah, it was ridiculous. Like I remember my friends me my buddies in high school
The bit was we just drop pochinki and then just run it
Dropping school. Yeah, there was pochinki. There was school. I never dropped school school was too much for me
It was just ridiculous. Yeah, it's a 10 second game if you land but it was it was just so fun
I think it was it was showing how fun it was
Even though the game was like such a buggy piece of shit. We all put up with it because we're like this is sick
Yeah, and still buggy piece of shit to the people playing daisy daisy was huge. Oh my god, dude
I loved daisy. I loved daisy so much like so so much. I used to like play like rp servers
I thought the rp servers were more fun
Because like there's like dedicated zones where you could kill people just like randomly and otherwise you had to like rob them
Which was really fun
Yeah
That was a real interesting social experiment because people would that was one of the first times people were just kind of given a piece
Of just big land and just go for it. Oh you you no, no, don't shoot me. Don't shoot me
Let's talk about this, right?
That would happen. It was like a weird like kind of experiment
Which is putting like a hundred what how many people were allowed in a daisy server?
I think like 50 60. Yeah
I all I know is I was like an absolute menace in that game like a menace. Were you evil? Oh, yeah
Like I I would like I'd like kill people and then like eat them and shit
Yeah, you could eat them. You could you could cut them up and eat them for food
The fuck
No, no, I was fucked up like I would like rob two people tie them up because you can put them in handcuffs kill their friend
And like make them eat their friend
All the most fucked up shit I could do I would just do it. Hey, how's your homie taste, bro?
I called you a well-rounded individual about 45 minutes ago
I'd also I'd also like oh, yeah, that's so funny
I would just I would just like like I would just like because like it was called like
Bambi's like whenever you like fresh spawn
So I was like I would like go get geared up like from like what was it northwest airfield?
Just get like ridiculously looted go down go back down to spawn and just like like do just do terrible things to the bambi's
Yeah, just eat the new
Like like somebody walk up like hey dude, you're looted like i'm like standing over a corpse
I was like and I was like like all right, you're gonna eat this guy now
Yeah
That was the one where you could like build cars, right?
It was really hard
Yeah
If you had a car and the cars were so buggy like, you know
Many times i'd have like the most gear ever and like we're just driving down a highway and I just die randomly
I'm dead
It's like, okay
Yeah cars were fun, you know on like a few servers I played on they like
Coated in building like you could like I built bases and shit. It was it was awesome
That was a really cool time in gaming though. It was before a lot of the battle royale stuff
But people treated it like kind of like a br, but it sort of wasn't but it was yeah. It was like the proto
because I remember just the only exposure I got to that was watching videos of people like just
Just like basically not eat other people but like hold people hostage and like because you talk to them and stuff, right?
And there were just videos of people interacting with each other
When did rust come out because rust was a lot of this stuff too, right?
I don't remember. Did is that the one? Yeah, daniel sl those videos are so fucking funny, dude
He's just clicking his mouse like the sap nap when you were in high school. What was the popular call of duty game?
I don't know whenever I was in high school. I stopped playing cod
That's when that's when I went full pc
Like I got my pc like I built my pc in like eighth grade and then when I got into high school
I just thought I was too good for like cod and xbox and stuff. I was like, oh i'm a pc gamer
I'm playing college which lines up because when I was in college you were in high school
And then I did a lot of whenever because I was a young impressionable child. I did csgo gambling
And yes, sir
The thing was though. I was really good at it. I know you can't be good at gambling
I was just I was incredibly lucky
I won i'm not even kidding thousands of dollars and I cashed it out and just went on like a spending spree in high school
Like freshman year. Oh my god
The sickest thing I ever cracked was a classic knife that I named larry david ssbm. Oh, yeah
So no, did you guys play tf2? We guys tf2 players. I played a little bit of like a few games
Okay, where are we cranking this? All right boys
I say
Bro, you guys want to fuck adventure? Yeah, let's do it camp cuddle. Yeah, let's go camp cuddle again
It's an early drop. It's an early drop and we gotta let you know like early now
Okay
While we're in the air flying
I will also say the way I won like one of the gambling things I won on csgo is I put five dollars into a 4k pot
And sniped it like with a point. It was a 0.015 chance. Oh my god. It was just ridiculous
Oh the restart in the game restarting wait
I'm seeing that right? All right, let's just everyone go totally go tilted go tilted while we can wait just right down
Wait, we can win this game. We the last ones to disconnect restart. Oh, that's so smart, which is i'm going tilted
Fucking don't restart
We can win this game and then in our hearts. We'll know we won one dude. Yes
We actually need the momentum
Still fighting
Yeah, so germa
Germa, yep
We're staying in the game
So we can win it ludwig's in here. He's gonna undefin soon. Do not respond to him. Okay
I need a gun. I got a keg meister right here. If you guys want to get this
I'm gonna run this person over and I would kill
There's only 23 people left. I gotta kill
He's got nade. Yes, sir
Wait, you got nade
Did I?
Yeah, you did nades good
Oh shit
Oh, they have the new code. Wait, we might I don't want to miss out on the actual game
All right. Yeah, leave leave leave leave leave
There's still 19 people here
Hold on. Where the fuck is nade shot? I left. Yeah, we gotta leave. We gotta leave
That one doesn't count. Well, I see so i'm about to fucking wreck their day
I'll get a fuck ludwig chant going right now. Oh, I've lost connection. Oh
All right, i'm getting 2v1. I'm disconnecting. Yeah, okay sucks
Oh, I got I got to be won by tarik. God damn it
Does that one doesn't count? What was that connection problem?
I don't know some some tournament organizing issue. Well, let's be fair. There are like a hundred people plus right?
There's a lot everyone clap for the to is really quick. Let's just fucking give it up
Where's the stream?
Yeah, sorry i'm having to disconnect like three or four times. I I gotta talk to somebody at twitch
Just be like why does like randomly like once every two or three weeks?
You just hate all of the data that's coming from my connection
Now it's fine. It's weird. I don't get it. We're not done after this
I'm gonna do I want to do a big tier list. It should be a lot of fun. So stick around fuck. Okay
You still in the game?
Yeah, you're so you're still there
There's six people dude, you gotta back out. They're starting. Ah, fuck
There's four people
They're not starting yet. They won't start without us. They won't start. It's not I had nothing to do this
Oh, they're saying cue up. You're freaking
Let it go just let it go
Because they're all leaving okay, okay. Okay. Okay. I'm out. I'm out. I'm leaving. I'm leaving. I don't know how escape return to lobby
There you go
I got I got the victory. All right
Oh, you got it fucking good
Yes, all right ready up ready up ready up as soon as it loads
I'm ready
For real suck my dick. Ludwig
We should get the points for that. We should get the points for that
I'm ready to fortnight
Yes. Yes
All right, let's get ourselves pumped up at this one. I would like a full harmonization of just holding a note, please
Okay, what note i'm gonna go a little bit high
We need somebody to go low. We need somebody to go medium when he's gonna go very low
I'll go. What's the tune? What's the tune?
I'll go. Uh
It's uh
Can you match that? Okay
Here we go
Hold it one two three
Fort fortnight that was pretty fucking tight one of you one of you one of you didn't do it. Did you win that game?
Yeah, what's up? Okay. Cool. Cool. Cool. Nice
Can you add the points please? All right. Good luck guys
I don't want to mute you my malware bytes has an update
We gotta update that
Yeah, you don't want that to pop up in the middle of the match. That's shroud bro. He's in your computer
That's quite that's now that's making your guns shoot you
That's a gamer challenge. Don't you think like run a full?
Not quick scan a full virus scan and like beat like a game like a do like a speed run or something
That shit finishes. Well, that shit gets all over into your files and like lags your computer and shit
So like do a full complete like hour and a half long scan of your computer while at the same time like getting victory rail
Number one victory royale. Yeah, frag your hard drive
Get down get down pink kills on the board right now. Just wiped out tomato town
Everyone is in 77 all in
19 times four i'm so pumped. Yes, sir
It sounded like you fell out of a window
All right, boys, let's go started final all right
Boys tonight is to the knights will never tonight we dine in minecraft hell
Yes, and to the friends will never forget
This is actually going to be the one this is the one right here. We're going to place at least in the top 10
Have you seen this?
Come on, let's go. Here we go. All right, let's do it now. We got to get the fuck away from everyone
I say we go camp cuddle again. I love it. I don't love that. I love that. I love that
So it's going to be at least one team there. We have to assert domination over them
Okay, just get in the lane get a weapon and fire
Get a gun blow their brains out. Tell me when to drop
Crank it right about
now
I can't cut re royale. Yeah, we're the camp cuddlers. We're the camp cuddlers. We're the camp cuddlers
i'm cuddling
Cuddle cuddle cuddle. Let me know in a parachute. I'm not on my
Space to 72 to 72 i'm cuddling i'm cranking the parachute now
I will say
I don't see anyone really. I don't see anybody here. We might have camp cuddle to ourselves
I'm cranking that filter boy. Are you serious? We got it
Dude, is it the whole last camp?
Shit bro. I might stay here forever
Who said we gotta leave?
It's our wonder years
You know, we've been getting killed caught right off the bat constantly
We can just chill here and live our lives
And you give me a sniper rifle with six lives in it six shots in it and get me to the final boss and i'll do it
Whatever it takes
I know I can make it through we really are alone. This is just
This is it's just kind of nice
I know I can make it through
Let's go
All right, i'm going to this gas station over here
Actually, no i'm not i'm looting this shit
There's a guy dropping on on the okay a guy just dropped on my ping on that roof so we are not alone
Make sure you're kitted
Oh, fuck i'm dead
Oh, never i got killed like that. She's lit. Yo right here right here. She's so lit
All right, you got my card. She's one shot
Where is she where is she she's in the building she's in the building she's ran out the other side
She's ran out the other side
Wait, I think I think I think we play for the card and dip
Yeah, you just got the the reboot van is like right here
You guys can just grab that shit and reboot like instantly pretty much and you can triple reboot and it'll do it
Hella fast. I got card. I got cards. Get out here. Good. I'll go back. Go back. Go back. Yep
I mean you guys can just triple reboot it and it'll go real fast. Okay. Yeah, everyone go everyone follow
They're not gonna expect the triple reboot. Where is it?
It's on the it's to the left. Sorry. It's like, oh no. Yeah, I see I see
It's right there. Oh, they're really close
Right, they're like seven
Go go press e press e press e press and hold e everyone
No
Yeah, we booted it. All right running through at this house
What happened give me the car the door get the fuck out of here get the fuck
Wait, you can hear the car
Let's go
Go to the right go to the right. There's a road fucking shit
Follow the road. The road will let you drive fast. Yeah, pump the music too. We need music
Go
What is that
We deserve it
What do we do just kill it just kill it yeah just shoot it
Oh, yeah big pot
I already bullets. I need bullets. Where do you get bullets?
Oh, we're okay
Wait
I need bullets for the gun. Someone's gonna find this out here in the open just shooting this fucking llama
Or it's a keg. All right. Come here. Everyone. Come here
All right, bro. I have my inventory just I have three four big pots and another keg. Wait the keg's over here
No, well, how do you get over here?
Oh fuck
All right. Uh, does anybody have any ammo? Do you guys have any shotgun ammo?
Uh, yes here. Yo, I actually have a ludicrous amount of ammo
Do you guys have any extra guns I can have I only have is a pistol right now
I have a shotgun and I can give you this just whoever's got an egg. Oh, yeah, i'll take that. All right
What's that?
What is that?
Make sure you're on your shield. All right. Let's let's let's run. Let's go to greasy. Let's go to let's go to the greasy
All right, let's get in the car. Oh, no, no, no
We can but we need to get all right. You're right. It might explode. You're right
I'm so glad
I can't believe we got out of that shit
That was ridiculous
All right. We need to just stay the fuck away from everybody. Just do not engage anything over here. Yeah, uh in this building
That's pain not working. Oh wait, there's a guy right here. I'll find you
Run run run i'm popping a keg on us. Anyway, where the fuck are you?
Give me one give me one fucking shot, baby. That's all I need
We are we are we're pinched by like three teams right now. I think we go down the hill
Oh down down down down down down down
Oh something on our car
Fuck the car blow the car up run down the hill
Okay, all in us. All right, we run down the hill and then we crank it to the to the left
Oh, there's some loot here. What the fuck?
Wait, we just got blessed
There's a pickup truck here
Hey, we got a truck. The guy did pick up our car
Fishing rod. It's right from the hill, right? Oh wait over there
They're they're fighting. They're fighting. They're fighting. I tagged a motherfucker twice broken shield
Bro, all I have is gray weapons. What the fuck i'm fucking pretty starved right now. I got a blue weapon
Should I give it to somebody that knows how to play the game?
No, it's yours. It's yours
Oh fuck I got a beam. They got a beam
I need I need red. Oh guys
We need we need to get to the fucking we need to get in the car and get the fuck out
I need rest. I need rest. I'm resin you going double res double res double res
I'm gonna hit you
Also me i'm coming around getting shot at
Do you have a way to get out of here? I guess you just run
Behind yep
Yes, we killed that motherfucker
Oh, oh no, oh no
I don't know what the fuck this person is. I don't know what the person is. I don't know what the person is
That's not last
Holy shit
Like why was everywhere we ran there was just people there. I have no idea what's going on in this game
Hey, at least we thirsted one of those people. Yes, sir. We needed that
The whole squad needed that
Oh that game was like so funny. That was a goddamn movie
All I heard was hey this people everywhere was surrounded by three teams and i'm just like
It's too stressful. How do people play this game? It's extremely stressful. Yeah
How do people play this this this game is like so intense all these all these brs
Oh
That was a fun one. I'm good with that. I call that a moral victory royale. That was that was awesome
Holy shit, we were just getting like shot at by so many people and we all hopped in the car, but that was so funny
Yeah
The call for the triple reboot was was very blessed because then they threw a group. He's somebody said he's way too old for this game
Yeah, I I mean I I don't know it was fun. Whatever. I don't I don't know what the fuck is happening
I just know there's like colors on the screen and there's people surrounding it. I would I don't know
This is hard. Is it I don't know what to do heart. We did no no one not even fucking close
That was fun
That was awesome. Well, it's just a uh, it's a nice react content from here on out
Yeah, i've never seen someone just sit in the first
Uh red like this for so long. I guess it just really doesn't hurt you that bad
No, it doesn't the first zone just like barely hurts. He does one tick of damage
Hey, like look you see this if only I had the vape I would have been better
Dude, let me tell you what was the last time?
That I played an fps like or a shooter on stream. It's probably been like
three years
You did the encouragement guy video you played oh destiny too. That's right. That was a fucking pog game
This is in my head off
I think every team that we interacted with followed us like they were like, let's go get those guys
And then we all ended up in the same place
And then not only did they do that, but then they all continued to only shoot it up
They were like waving at each other like neighbors, dude
Like oh you're killing these idiots, too
That's awesome. Yeah, you guys suck every round they just fucking lose
Us
We had the car that was fun. That was fun in the car with you guys. Let me just say
Music blasting hanging out the window. I would I wouldn't care
God, I wish there was a fifth game. I know
I really do. I really want there to be i'm gonna ask can we have a fifth?
Can we do a thug finals fifth game thug finals? Yeah, and then dude, let's just get a car again
That was like the I remember when we had the car. It was it was very special
Well, I need to I need to watch this clip
Professional gamer. I've never that's not in my bio
I don't know. How do you get i'm trying to desperately jump over we need to get in the car and get the fuck out
Oh my god, this is bad
This is really bad. This is fucking terrible
Holy shit. Okay, let's put this on camera for a sec. This is really really bad
Like this is remarkably awful
It's like remarkable how bad this is
But why wasn't I jumping up oh guys we need we need to get to the fucking we need to get in the car and
Get the fuck out
Going out
Honestly, dude all I could see all I could see was purple I couldn't see anything else
It was just purple. I couldn't see anything
Hey, they left they left bro. Yeah, they they ff actually that should boost us on the right. They forfeited wait what somebody forfeited
Yeah, number nine like everyone left. Oh shit, but we'll see what place they're in like they're not yeah
They're that team was in
13th place. So like they weren't gonna
Win anyways, I guess whoever's in first isn't gonna want another game
But okay, so here's the thing. I don't play like vr's and when I hear somebody start to scream like oh my they're here
Oh my god, they're here. I'm just like they're here somebody's here. I don't know who's here, but i'm gonna die
We're dying. We're dead. We're gonna die
What is going on here? Just uh
Just vibing xqc is still here
Two in a squad a lot, but he's kind of nuts that
That was insane
Desync i'm about to play chug jug with you chopped and screwed
This part wait was he just shooting at birds?
Was that a person he might have been shooting at a bird some birds drop loot, oh
Oh, that was an advanced move
Dude xqc is fucking amazing
Just born to game
Forced to stream. I think I think alex is gonna win the turn
Somebody's like my cat's staring at something on the wall
Your cat is somebody in chat will investigate it
Oh their cat. Yeah
I was thinking they were commenting on maybe your cat in uh in the background, but you have an extremely small cam
And maybe not even a cat correct. Well, I love the size of your camera
It's just enough
I don't want to there's lots of real estate that information people need to see
Yes, sir
Plus I don't want people to see my pores and shit and chad warden's all about the games
If your camera is this small boogers in your nose cannot be picked up it's like the pixels can't they blend together
Nick that reference might thread the needle of all three of us. Yeah, I don't know. Isn't that crazy? I don't know
Oh x in trouble
He's healing up
And he has a he's has a grenade. He's gonna blast out of here like jimmy's fucking neutron
What
Excuse you see this shit is a movie right now. Sorry like the simpsons
What happened
No, they're all good gone. I said I think xqc might win because they're getting so many elams right now. Yeah, it's insane
No, that's the amount of people I can't tell
I've been watching them kill a lot of people
This is intense xqc has been like 10 hp twice in this game and now he's full max and he's running at someone like an animal
Oh, oh he's going in
There it is
Whoa
Oh my god, no way
They didn't even know they with each other was there
You didn't think I blasted out. This is crazy. I have so much to learn
It's behind i'm learning. I'm just you know what?
I'm gonna stick to what I know. I'm not cut out for this at all
I really not I would have saw that that person in the bush. I would have put both my hands up and gone
And I would and I would have like grabbed my ticket
Ticket
And I would be dead I would that would be like I would hold my chest like this as if a mouse came in the room
Clutching your pearls
I just can't but I can watch I can watch these games all day
Hit him with the oh dear heavens. Yeah, it would be like that
Oh shit. Oh heaven's me
This is crazy, they're just fucking killing everyone bro. Oh my god the person was a firework
They shot themselves it was like fourth of july
Oh my they're just gaming better than everyone else
Xx cleans it up right here
So it's like
Maybe 4v4v1 or like 4v3v2. I kind of don't want to move away from xqc's camera
Oh, I think it's
One team is another
Bro, he's just the main character
Stop moaning
What is splash you up king?
Is it mango's team is is wait am I like moaning am I what do you mean moaning?
Am I don't stop doing that? I don't know what i'm doing
It's loud in my ears. I can't hear what sounds are coming on my mouth
They just destroyed that whole building
That was ridiculous. That was like the three little pigs in there. Oh, yeah
This is the daily dose team there it is. Oh wow
Surely they won right? There's no way
I'm just impressed. That's good
Geez that's it clap good game. Oh
You know what?
We chose to learn today. We didn't choose to win. That's right. We just hold the back
Can I just say that was?
Gentlemen that was that was very fun. You guys it was an honor honor. It was an honor captain
That was a lot of good fun. That was really fun. I'm glad I was on uh your guys team
Yeah, same I wouldn't have had any other way
We got a fucking juicy juicy cinematic moment
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry that you had a gigantic anchor
Uh that no was thrown out the first five seconds of the game
Wasn't that way tarik tarik just rolled up and he just put one right against my forehead. That anchor's name was shroud. Yeah
And then shroud just killing us off the rip every single game that was the that was the problem
All right. I'm gonna get out of here before ludwig gets in the chat. I can't face him
I'm I'm a small weak man mentally. Oh, no
and uh
Actually, I might go downstairs and say how to myth but all right gg's boys is right. See ya
We come in last place
Noticing a pattern mario kart tournament was invited to came in last place
Super auto pets tournament. I was invited to came in last place
Fortnite tournament. I was invited to came in last place
Well, wait, is that entirely true? I think I came in like eighth seventh or eighth in the mario kart tournament
It's all good though. Whatever. Well, I was supposed to stream tomorrow, but I was like, you know what fuck it
Let's just go early and ludwig's like do you want to do it? I'm like, uh,
I guess sure
Why not? It's fun
Hang out with uh, hang out with some boys
Don't feel embarrassed i'm not embarrassed that last round was fun. The first one was fun, too. This was all fun. All right
What we are doing now
Well, but seriously though like I like doing this stuff
Fun to obviously like meet meet new people hang out with some new people, right?
Obviously, yeah that the streamer rewards I spent time with some of those guys
Oh, no. Yeah, it was fun. I look at it like it doesn't matter
I'm i'm annoyed at the internet problem. It's not the fact that I came in last place in the fortnight tournament
So what we're gonna do now?
We're gonna take a quick break
I'm gonna get a refill of my drink and then ladies and gentlemen, i've got something very very special for you. I've got
every from software boss ever
That I need to place on a tier list because I completed elden ring
This is going to be one of the most important streams i've ever done one of the most important streams i've ever done
When we come back in just a few minutes. See you guys in a minute. I'm still here. I'm typing
I've have to I know it's a hot mic. I didn't mute it yet. I haven't left. I gotta change the
The title. All right now i'll be ready