Hey, what is happening everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
Gonna be playing as the Pyro tonight. Two one-life gameplays back-to-back as the Pyro,
using the strange degreaser, the strange flare gun, and because I never use melee as a Pyro,
I have on the stupid guitar thing. The third degree, that's what it's called. So these
are two back-to-back one-life gameplays, like I said, on Hightower. And Hightower is one of
those awesome Pyro maps because you can really just hide around corners, jump at people, blast
people off the edge of the cliff. So it's a whole lot of fun. I suggest you try Pyro on here if
you've never done it before. So what I want to talk about in this gameplay, I want to talk about
the flare gun because I want to give you guys some tips and strategies on how I use this thing,
how I get most of my kills with this thing, and just general basic strategy and tips for you guys
because some people have a lot of trouble with this item. And I did a video about the flare gun
a while back, probably like three months ago, and I didn't really go into that much detail. I talked
about it for a little bit, but I want to give at least a minute or two of this video's time to
explaining how I use this item. Now let me back up for just a second. I want to show you what I'm
talking about as I'm talking about it. So your compression blast shoots people up in a straight
line. They go up in a straight line and they come down in a straight line. There's no running,
there's no moving all over the place. They just go up and come down. So it's really easy to get
the timing down. And some people will ask me, they'll say, Jerma, if you're going to do the
compression blast in the air, why not use the reserve shooter or why not use the shotgun?
Which they're both really, really good options. They're awesome options. The reason why I don't
use them anymore is because the flare gun does 90 damage when you crit somebody. And you're going
to crit them if you do this technique. You light them on fire, blast them in the air, and they're
also going to take afterburn damage as well. So it would take two or three shotgun shots to get the
same amount of damage you'll get with these crits. And I know it does take only about one and a half
seconds to shoot your shotgun twice or three times even. And it does take about two and a half seconds
to shoot the flare gun, but it really does even out. They both equal about the same amount of
damage if you have good aim. So it really is just personal preference finding what you want to play
with. I just like the flare gun because I love getting those crits and I like having the long
range option. Getting one more look at what I'm talking about right there and then I get myself
killed. I don't know what it is about engineer buildings, but look it, I'm just standing still
right now aiming at it. I think it just puts you in a trance whenever you see an engineer building.
You're like, I gotta get rid of that damn thing. But anyways, this is the second gameplay. This is
the second one life gameplay. Had to spray that picture of Burger Boy right there because
everybody loves Burger Boy. So coming up right here, this is really, really ridiculous. I couldn't
believe I survived this whole thing. MLC Stealth is my medic right now. He gets himself killed.
Actually, I probably get him killed for going too overzealous right here. I get the reflect shot
on this demo man, get the kill on him, turn around, Stealth is being attacked, Stealth goes down as
the medic. And then it's just me and this guy in this room being ridiculous. And then another pyro
comes in here and I'm just like, Oh my God, swinging all over the place. And I actually get
the kill on both of them and look at how much health I have. And to be honest with you guys,
if I had the shotgun right there, I probably wouldn't have even pulled it out. Only because
when you get closed off in an area with another pyro and you're a pyro, you pretty much just chaos
spray and get all crazy. There was three pyros in that room. So there's really all you can do is just
spray and pray and hope you get the kill on somebody. That's really all you can do. I mean,
maybe I could have done one or two meat shots, but it was just so chaotic in that tiny little
room. I really don't think I would have pulled it off. So coming up, this is the best and worst
part of Hightower. If you're on the receiving end, it's the worst. If you're on the delivering end,
it's the funniest best thing in the world. Blowing people off of the edge right there at that cart
turnaround. Speaking of the cart, this is when we all get on it. We all start to push it because
really it's just been sitting here the whole time, not really moving that much. You get a lucky crit
shot on that scout that was jumping over the edge there, and this needs to be said, I'll bring it
up again, the afterburn kills him. So if you crit any of the classes with 150 health or less,
you will kill them with the afterburn. The only way that won't happen is if there's a medic on the
team healing people, overhealing people, et cetera, or they pick up a health kit. That's the only way
they will escape that. Moving the cart right along here, this is the part on Hightower where
pretty much every single game ends in a stalemate, because they both get to this point right here
where this large hill is, and neither team ever seems to be able to push it all the way up.
Especially if there are engineers here, because even if you take it out with an uber charge,
you still have to push the cart all the way up, and literally the spawn doors are right there.
So it can be quite a challenge sometimes. Sentry gun up in that little loft right there,
I end up taking it out with the flare gun. There was a bunch of spam going at that thing,
so I think I just luckily got the last shot on it. Then Stealth does an uber charge right here,
and he gives it to the soldier, then he gives it to me, and was not really expecting that,
but I think he was practicing his transition uber. So this is going to be the end of the
gameplay right here. I get on the cart going upwards, and instead of just jumping around
and trying to get rid of this sniper that's aiming at me, I really didn't even know he was aiming at
me to begin with, but I get myself shot right in the face, and the cart goes all the way down.
We could have won, but whatever. You take and you give, right?
So thank you guys so much for watching, I really do appreciate it,
and I will see you guys all soon. Take care, everybody.