Yo, yo, yo, what up guys, it's Germa, bringing you a live commentary tonight. I'm gonna play a bunch of crap. Hopefully it's not longer than like a friggin' like 30 minutes or something like that, but what do you think about that intro?
That's a pretty sick intro, huh? I agree. Thank you Smokin' Jojo Davis for that sick intro with the germ floatin' and bloatin'. Oh, come on. Nothing better than that. Nothing.
Alright, let's get started though. Let's see. You know, let's see, is Star or Shibby's server around right now? Usually they're like always full. You know what, whatever. Let's go to, uh, we can do Badwater on the Revenger. Let's do this.
Oh, great. Server not responding. Oh, great. Hey, does this happen to anybody else? This seems to happen on like an hourly basis for me. Like, ready? I'm gonna try and go into any server. Oh, nope, can't go into that one. Nope, sorry. No, sorry. Every server doesn't work.
I was afraid this was gonna happen, so let's just wait a second and go look at my items. Oh, cool. Oh, I got paint. I don't remember that happening. Let's put it over in my like, my dogshit junk folder. Whatever, let's go.
I was afraid this was gonna happen. You know, this is, uh, come on. Let's get into, uh, that paint kinda sucks. Uh, yo! GentlemanGummy, I'll accept it. Hold on, give me a second, brother. Mmm. No, I guarantee none of these are gonna work. Nope. Well, I'm gonna cut and we'll come back to this in about two seconds.
Alright, so we're back. I got into a Dust Bowl server. Oh, I'm an idiot. It's a Gold Rush server. Duh. Okay, let's, uh, let's go with Heavy, go with Brass Beast, Gloves of Killing Boxing, and we're doing the family business. I'm gonna try out something new here. Let's see. Let's do this.
I was trying this earlier. I'm trying to get crits with this and then whip out the shotgun like smoke people, you know what I mean? We'll see. We'll see. I don't know. How many people are in here? Ah, there's quite a few. Looks like it just started too, so yeah. Alright, let's do it. Bye.
There's a guy that's jumping right over. What was that? Okay, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on a second. What the fuck was that? What the hell was that? You guys saw that. What was that, like that blue plasma shit? I don't know about this server. I don't know about this. Did I pick like a Warcraft Mods? Okay. Look at this guy's rocket launcher. What the fuck? Yeah, goodbye. See you later. Not playing in this server. I'm gonna cut again. Let's see.
So it was just brought to my attention that that was not like a server mod. That's a new item? Is that a new rocket launcher or something? I have no idea what's going on. Apparently they just updated the game, maybe. I don't know. That was crazy.
So anyways, there's people in here. I won't freak out the next... Hey. Hey. Okay, so what the hell is going on? That's a real item, huh? Oh right, this is getting weird. I'm like really confused. I'm like freaking out.
Apparently that's a new rocket launcher, I guess. I don't know. That's weird. Well anyways, I can't even like play it right now. I'm like freaking out. Alright, so is it... Hold on a second. No, you must have to get it. Turn crits off. I don't know. I don't know, guys. I'm just as confused as you are. Because I'm recording this in real time. This is not... See, look, there it is. Wow.
So apparently there's a pulse cannon in the game now for the soldier. I'm confused. I can't even like think. Let me just own somebody with this thing. Yeah, Brass Beast. Wow. Does it have new stats or something? I'm going to ask. I'm just going to be a turd and ask.
Hey, does the new rocket launcher have stats or is it just a new skin? Let's see if anybody like... It has... Really? What the hell? Do they do like an alien update? What does it do? It must just be... Wow. I have no idea.
Anyways, this is Dust Bowl. I'm playing as the Brass Beast Heavy with the family business and the gloves of killing boxing. Can't talk. Hold on, scout. See, I'm trying to do a new setup here where I... Oh my god, another scout. Oh, get it off.
So I'm trying this new setup where if I kill somebody with the gloves of killing boxing, then I'll be able to whip out the shotgun and get eight crits in a row with that thing. Because you can't really switch over to the minigun, especially the Brass Beast. It's a lot more difficult to do that.
So I'm going to try this setup. The Brass Beast, I hate it. I'm really bad with it. But I want to get good with it and use this setup because I feel like nobody uses the damn shotgun because it sucks. But I'm going to find a use for it. Are you a spy? No.
So there's a new shotgun. I mean, there's no shotgun. There's a new rocket launcher in the game that shoots pulse cannons, apparently. And this guy's got it. Look at that. I thought it was like a Warcraft mod. Everybody's got this thing. What the hell is going on?
What? Screw this. This is insane. I'm going to get up here and see if this whole group is going down. Maybe not. I'm just so confused. Oh, there it is. Does not require ammo. Oh my god, I just had it. So there's no ammo. Let's see if I can find somebody with it.
Oh my god. You got to be shitting me. It's a ranged sapper for the soldier. You got to be shitting me. I am annoyed right now. That actually really, really just pissed me off. Why would they give a ranged sap to the soldier? I don't understand. I don't get it.
I have no idea. I'm not going to pretend like I know what Valve is thinking. But that just seems odd. That seems very odd. Let me just kill like a ton of... Oh yeah. Get owned. Get owned. Is there a medic around here? Wow. So there's no ammo. Did they add stuff for other classes? I'm going to ask. I'm going to be a noob. That's it. No, that's not a spy. Did they add stuff for other classes too or is it just that thing for the soldier? Wow.
Wow. So apparently they just added this insanely overpowered rocket launcher. For no reason I guess. I need some health. Let's see if I can try and get this thing going. See if I can try and do what I was planning on doing. Kill somebody with the gloves and whip out the shotgun and just start killing people like crazy.
Let me sneak up here. Wow. That guy didn't even see me for a second. There we go. Here it comes baby. There it is. There it is. See that's what I wanted to do but apparently this crazy new rocket launcher is insane. No random critical hits and this weapon deals reduced damage to build...
Okay so you can sap buildings but it doesn't do like good damage to buildings. I don't get it. They just did the Uber update. What are they doing? Oh we're going to do an Uber update with like a pack for all the classes and then we're just going to add like a freaking lightning gun for the soldier. Let me break. Yeah lower them out here. Yeah lower them out here. Nice.
So apparently according to people in the chat they're saying that this is not the end. I guess there's like two more like rocket launchers or something that people are going to be able to get. That's weird. I don't know. I don't know what to think about this. As a crit sticky I'm dead. No I guess not. Oh nice shot. So I don't know. This is all happening right now so I don't know what to say besides this is insane.
I just logged on and I'm just like yeah I'll play some TF2 and see like you saw I ran out of the... I thought there was like a dickhead server with like you know like crazy mods on it. Wow. Insane. Whatever. I just don't know what to say. Oh come on let's see if I can get the note. Let's go. Let's go. Oh let's go. Come on. Come on. I got one more shot and you're gone. One more shot and you're gone. Yeah but I'm going to die too aren't I?
Oh no sandwich. No sandwich. Bad idea but I'm trying to get used to this new setup because it could be pretty powerful. Oh you don't even know where I am. You know what? Screw this. I'm going to try it again. Get somebody off god like this guy. Oh come on. Come on Frank Oz. You like wonderful man with a wonderful voice.
Those of you guys that don't know who Frank Oz is he's the voice of Yoda and he's a guy one of the original Muppets and stuff like that. He's a pretty good guy. So who do you think is going to get the next... Look at everybody's using it. So what are you supposed to do? Can you remove the sappers or something? Come on. Unkill that medic. Nice.
So it's a sapper. It disables buildings for four seconds and it's part of a set? What's the other part of... God I should really go to the blog and read up on this but I'm not. I don't care. I'm doing terrible right now too. Actually maybe not. 14 and 8. I'm too concerned about this new update that I have not heard of until five seconds ago. So let's just go back down here and try this again. No pyros.
The brass beast is... It's really good but... Oh god. And it fucking fills your screen. That item sucks. When somebody shoots you with it it fills your screen with goo and you can't see anything. Oh god. I really should have done a little bit of practice and looked up some things before I came on to do a live commentary because there's a bunch of new items that I've never seen or heard of before.
You know what? I'm going to have to go with a bread and butter class. The only thing you can do is if you're in a situation where you're getting owned by like new items and unfamiliar things is just go with a bread and butter class. I'm going spy with my regular loadout. So let's see what I can do here.
Oh by the way it disables cloak too. How funny would that be? Just kill me. Just kill me you friggin butt head. Get out of my way. Get out of my way. Oh this guy's laughing? He thinks he's funny? Wow nobody's... Ah these guys saw me. Okay let's get back here. That rocket launcher is insane man. Oh hopefully nobody heard that. Well we capped the point. Nice. Come on back up. Back up right into this. Oh not quite. I don't know why I did that. Just felt like it.
But yeah I guess new stuff's gone the way. Maybe meet the pyro deep. Whoa whoa frapsalag how are you? Oh get off the point. Get those guys off the point. I'm on your team. Oh and no cloak left. I don't know. I don't know about this. I don't know about this guys. I don't know about this. What the hell are you guys doing? What are these people doing? Oh my god.
We got three medics doing absolutely nothing in the spawn. And somehow we're still going to win. Well we're not going to win. We might win. Oh god. If we do this with three medics just you know being idiots in the spawn that would be fine. Like I'm just a regular spy right now and people aren't doing anything. In fact this is going to be really funny if I kill this guy. No no no. I'll be a sniper. Oh bad place. Really bad place. I can't believe nobody saw that.
Yeah this guy did. I'm sorry. My brain is like just a mess right now trying to think about what else is going to happen in this update. Is it even on the blog? I haven't checked the Team Fortress 2 blog in a million years since the uber update so. Once this is over you better believe. You bet your ass that's where I'm going immediately. What are you doing? That's a spy probably. Bye. Oh if you're wondering I'm not going to use the. Oh shit.
Go ahead and kill me. I dare you. Oh you had to be that guy and do that to me. Whatever. You had to be that guy and not just take the swing. Yeah but you bet your bottom dollar that's where I'm going in a second. I'm done recording this. Which will probably be right after this round ends. Just because I need to know exactly what they're doing and what's going on.
Crap. Cut the crap. Oh you stole my thunder. I'm an idiot. I'm doing this is bad. This is like 22 and 18 for me is like 2 and 90. I think we're still going to win though. But like I was saying before. We're about to win now. How did I top score this server? How did I top score this server?
Wow. I'm going to take that with a grain of salt because yeah I don't see how that happened but cool. You'd think that they would test this in the beta and go whoa shit maybe we shouldn't put that in the game. Is that a spy probably? No it's not. What a waste of a Jurati.
Do I even want to record for the next minute and a half? Because I'm sure you know what's going to happen. We're going to lose. No I'm staying Sniper. I'm going to stay Huntsman Sniper on principle. Look at this mess. I can't believe I'm missing. Wow I'm on fire.
Okay we only got a minute left of this and then I'm going to stop it because I need to. This is not a good day for live commentary. But you know what I'm uploading anyways. Let me just get this one dude. You're dead. Let me just get this one guy.
Oh you got me. Wow. Fucking ridiculous. Pardon my French but like really effing ridiculous. It's still a century up there too. Unbelievable. Unbelievable. Well anyways thanks for watching guys. Hopefully you got to see the new item in all of its great insane glory.
Because our team can't even get out of the spawn for the last like three rounds. So thanks for watching. Hopefully this gets sorted out in the next week or so and people aren't all getting locked in their spawns by a red team. So thanks again for watching and I'll see you guys later. Take care man.