All right, I want to get a controller for this one.
This seems like a controller game, so I'm going to use it.
Oh, the chopsticks. Shit. Yeah, we'll do that later.
Don't let me forget that. I'll do it. I promise.
Just I can't right now. I'm ready to go.
I'll make sure the audio is not loud. All right, let's go.
Hey, I got to change the... Do I have to change the title?
The title right now.
Being more considerate.
Oh, I think that's fine.
I'll do it. I promise.
Hold on.
The game has to change though.
Stream info. All right.
This is going to change to Roswell Agent.
Agent Roswell. There it is.
That's the name of this game, right?
Yeah, okay. All right. Coming back.
I can use chopsticks. Yes, I can.
This is... Oh, there we go. Okay.
I don't know how bad this audio is going to be. I have no idea.
Okay, new game.
Does the controller even work?
Hey, okay, hold on. Does this work?
No face cam? You'll get it later.
Long drive two?
There's a car in this game.
I don't know if it's exactly what you think it is.
Going after the power? All right.
Am I moving this? No, I don't think so.
Okay, there's a person over there.
Is this me? Oh, fuck. It's WASD.
Shit, I can't use the controller.
Power to the base is cutting out.
Take a Jeep to the electrical substation on the hill and check it out.
Okay, left shift is run. Mouse look.
Change controls after prologue.
Pick up, activate. Have a gun.
Jump and break. Pick up, activate.
Fire weapon. Okay, pick up.
This is a first-person shooter?
I thought this was like a third-person game.
Okay, I need to get the Jeep.
Oh, first and th- You can switch?
Holy shit. Okay, this is awesome.
Okay, zoom, unzoom, yep.
Menu, mission.
Power to the base is cutting out.
Take a Jeep to the electrical substation on the hill.
Inventory. Okay.
Change controls.
It's like weapon type. Reload, scroll as weapon.
C is kick.
There's a kick, okay.
Roll. Are these other- Who are these people?
Did we work together?
Melee? Do I work with these people?
Grenade? Are these enemies or are these people that-
I don't- I know. I don't have grenades.
Grenade type? Okay.
I need a Jeep.
These are my- These are like good guys, right?
We're on the same team?
I think we're on the same team.
All right, I need a Jeep.
Where's there a Je- I can run faster than a car can drive, okay?
That's a Jeep?
This is not a Jeep.
Where's her Jeep?
Back at the tower?
Oh shit, there's a Jeep right there.
Okay, I got a Jeep.
Ladies and gentlemen, plus one letter grade.
Okay, drive.
While driving, use return to recover your vehicle if stuck.
You can do it.
Drive to the electrical grid on the what?
Oh, it's over there.
Is there- Can I do- I can't do first person with this.
All right, I got it.
Nice. Okay, cool.
So I'd go in here and turn off the electricity?
Activate- Activated.
Oh! Can I kill it from here?
It's smoking.
Holy shit, it's an alien.
What am I supposed to do about this?
Okay, what's my task?
Oh shit, hold on.
He's running.
Okay.
Reset the circuit breaker.
You drive to that crash site and investigate wreckage.
What crash site?
Oh shit, all right, let's go.
They come in peace?
Oh, come on.
All right, it crashed over here?
I didn't even see it crash.
Let's get on the road, please.
I only have 30 bullets.
Is that bad?
All right, check for survivors at the crash site.
Keep a lookout to the sky for more.
All right, let's see if there's anybody here.
Anybody here?
LAPD, open up.
Okay, I don't know what's going on there, but-
There's nobody alive here.
Okay, whatever.
This is destroyed.
What about over here?
Are they like invading?
There's a shitload of them.
What the- Okay.
What the fuck is happening?
Help! Somebody help me!
I have no ammo left.
What the fuck?
They're going to like cut into me.
Okay, what just happened?
What did they do?
What did they just do to me?
They turned the contrast up.
After first contact with the visitors in Roswell
and the abduction of a military sergeant,
a task force is created to deal with the possible threat of alien invaders.
That task force is known as BATE,
the Bureau for Alien Investigation and Termination.
As the son of the missing sergeant,
you enroll to become an elite operative of the bureau.
After the Apollo moon landings in July 1969,
UFO activity spikes as reports and sightings
are flooding into the visitors returning,
clearly in great numbers and strength.
Your job is to investigate these incidents
and terminate any- anybody that's extraterrestrial.
Well, the bureau creates a long-term strategy to deal with them.
You are Agent Roswell.
Okay.
Hello?
My computer.
Wait, what about the ball game?
Welcome to A-
What?
What the fuck?
This is spoilers.
No, exit.
Exit. That's spoilers.
I don't want to see those.
Arm 1, City 1, Desert 1, Pine Valley.
Side mission.
All right, let's do City 1.
We've identified a group of radicals who call themselves CETA,
supporters of extraterrestrial arrivals.
This group intends to contact or signal the aliens to land on Earth.
They believe they will bring about a new world order
free from governments and capitalism.
They have been trying to rally support for their cause around the city.
They've also stolen sensitive documents from another agent.
Disband all CETA activity in the city and get back to the documents.
It's a level creator?
So these people are working with the aliens.
All right, I have a radar.
Get in your car stored in the underground car park.
I can kick- I can like fucking kick people.
I don't want to-
Oh my god, put that down.
Put that down.
How do I put things away?
How do I put weapons away?
How do you put a weapon away?
I don't know.
Can I just take any car?
I can't just steal a car?
Yeah, I can.
What's wrong with this one?
The police?
I don't think it matters what car I take.
But I'm absolutely taking the motorcycle.
There's no way I'm not taking this.
Okay.
Police, I need to-
Stop, stop, stop it.
I need that bike.
I need the bike.
I want the bike.
No.
Okay.
Can I get the motorcycle?
Shit.
I don't think-
Can I turn it around?
I don't think I can get it to turn.
Holy shit.
Oh my god, that was awful.
Where did she go?
Fuck you.
What?
It just disappears.
All right, just give me my car.
That was a gunshot.
Why am I kicking gunshots?
Why is like 30 people screaming?
Holy shit.
What?
Oh my god, that's so much blood.
That was so much blood.
There was just not that much blood inside of somebody.
Holy f-
Oh my god.
Okay.
Can I eat?
How much does food cost?
How do I get under there?
That like stock scream.
How do I go underground?
No, don't-
Is there like a subway?
How do I get underground?
This bus cannot figure out what's going on
because the thing's in the way.
What are they doing?
Why are they fighting?
What is this guy doing?
Hit the eject button.
The guy ejected.
I'm gonna steal this
because this guy has no idea what's going on.
All right, get out of the car.
Get out of the car.
That's enough.
Get out.
Get out of the car.
What?
Where did you come from?
You spawned as-
What?
Why is your car so much more armor?
All right, I'm playing the game.
I hear a helicopter.
Why is there a-
Why is this game Grand Theft Auto?
This just became a really just low grade Grand Theft Auto.
Okay, well I'm just-
I don't know where this thing is.
I don't know how to get to the underground lair.
I have no idea.
Now there's a problem.
God.
What is he doing?
Okay.
I need to get this car.
What?
No!
It's not in this game.
It's impossible.
It's literally impossible.
Are you serious?
You've got to be kidding me.
Is it the same person?
I don't know.
Why did you put this in here?
I can't fucking believe it.
I am shocked right now.
It's something that felt real familiar.
I'll be honest.
I want the bike.
Is that actually in the game?
Yeah, it is.
What is that guy just-
Why is that guy floating around?
I cannot ride bikes.
It's down there.
Okay.
If you guys don't know why I just freaked out,
that's in Grab That Auto 5.
It's an old video I made.
We played a bunch of shitty GTA clones
and that song appeared in like four or five of them in a row.
Oh, that's shocking to see that.
Seeing what happens.
All right, so where's my car?
Yeah, like five years ago.
All right.
What the fuck?
I can't fucking believe it.
What does it want me to do?
Get in your car in the underground car park.
Where is my car?
Oh, is that it?
Yeah, I did not just put a-
That's not my car.
Oh, destroy three protest rally trucks.
So these are the people that want the aliens to take over.
Is that what I'm understanding?
My fucking right ear hurts.
Ow.
What the fuck?
Wait, why do I have this?
Oh my god.
Why is all of a sudden it's a James Bond car?
What is it saying?
Abduct me.
Aliens, come in peace.
No, I put-
I don't want this.
I don't want to put that out.
I want to read the signs.
What does it say?
Extraterrestrials are here.
Welcome to Earth.
I love UFOs.
I mean, they're not doing anything wrong.
Like, what's illegal about this?
The aliens are attacking.
Beam me up.
How do I do-
I have to destroy these?
Where's my car?
Beam me up.
Things were different in the 50s.
I need to, like, knock out their truck?
Did I do it?
Abduct me now.
I mean, look, if somebody wanted the aliens to abduct him,
like, I can't tell you not to do that.
Do they want to, like, take over Earth?
Do you have the-
Oh, yeah, right.
Did I do anything?
Okay, I think I did it.
All right, watch out.
Get out of the way.
I mean, do we know the motive?
The briefing that we got said that they want the aliens to take over
and they want to, like, kill everybody and abduct everybody.
That's what we're-
That's what we're understanding.
Little green men are cool.
This is, like, people just-
This is-
I don't see anything going on that's wrong.
All right, I want to-
Watch out.
Little suss men.
Put the cars in the ocean?
Yeah.
You're supposed to be wrong.
That's what's wrong.
Move, move, move.
Out of the way.
Oh, boy.
This would be a great time for you to move out of the way.
Move out of the way.
Good.
All right.
You're going to soft lock yourself?
I don't think I am.
This is going right into the ocean.
Okay, I think I have to-
I have to ditch both cars.
Oh, fuck.
Hold on.
Is there an invisible wall?
No, all right.
What happened to this person?
Watch out.
Why are there just people lying on the ground?
Like, ran over.
Why am I driving the taxi?
I don't know.
Because it was available.
Okay.
Move this out of the way.
What did I-
Did I-
Is that the mission complete music?
I can't tell.
No, no, it's just-
Okay, it's regular music.
Okay.
I have to destroy it.
I want to get some more info here.
Oh my god.
All right, I'm good.
Shut down the illegal pirate radio broadcasters
attempting to signal the aliens.
But people are just trying to signal the aliens?
Have the aliens attacked yet?
I need a little-
I need to understand more of what's going on.
Have the aliens attacked yet?
They have?
At the start of the game?
Did they attack like a city?
They literally killed your father.
Oh, okay.
What the fuck was that?
Hey!
Who's shooting at me?
Oh, wait, that was-
What the fuck?
So this is the radio tower.
So they're trying to signal the aliens.
My fucking head.
That was so loud.
Is it fall damage?
Yep.
Watch out.
I swear to god, you walk faster than driving.
I kind of want to skateboard or something too though.
I did not want to do that.
Can I not take the skateboard?
So where are the aliens now?
All right, get up here.
Are you gonna shoot me?
Yep, he's trying to shoot me.
How do you dodge roll?
Okay.
All right, I shot him in the fucking head.
All right, so it's like-
Is there anybody up here?
I don't even know how to react to this game.
Uh-oh, ultimate fall joke incoming.
I saw it.
Do you think I'll die?
What do you think?
Is this a fall that will kill me?
Nope.
Okay, we're fine.
All right, there's a guy on the roof though.
I have to be aware.
And if he shoots me once, I'm dead.
This thing is giving me like anxiety.
I don't like how close it's getting.
I don't like how weird it's acting.
All right, can I aggro?
God damn it, he's gonna shoot me once and I'm gonna die.
You're up even higher.
Wait, where are you?
Are you just sitting right there?
I did it.
You've regen health over time.
Yeah, don't stand too close to this.
It's gonna explode and kill me.
All right, I'm on the rooftops.
The aliens don't have any more broadcasting equipment.
I stole sacred files from bait.
Retrieve them.
There's an activity in the industrial district.
Check the garages and roofs.
Where are the aliens?
You're the alien.
Where are they?
That's heavy.
That's heavy base.
I like the heavy base.
What else you got?
All right, I like it.
This feels very iPad gamey.
No, this is not porn music.
This is, watch out.
To me, this is first name, last name, dev on App Store.
It's not like, oh, Firestuff Studios.
No, this is first name, last name, dev on the App Store.
All right, so I have to stop them from, all right, let's stop them.
All right, there's one.
How many people?
I do have to get, this is not good.
Wait, recover.
You're under arrest.
Can I land on him, please?
I got him.
It hurts.
All right, hold on.
What's the goal?
Okay, all right, all right, all right.
I gotta get the boxes full of files.
Files in here.
Okay, got it.
Well, there's files.
What was even in here?
Is that gonna explode?
Of course it is, okay.
There's no files?
Where are these files?
There's nothing even in here.
Check the garages and the roofs.
Dude, this is literally Saints Row.
I should literally play Saints Row on stream.
Don't you think?
I should literally play Saints Row.
Any of these other ones open?
Only the first two?
Yeah, I'd play like Saints Row 2.
I'm out of bullets.
Okay, we're fine.
Give me that gun.
No!
There's a shitload of people up there.
Give me that gun.
Can I not pick it up?
Please fall off so I don't have to...
I gotta get up there.
I don't even know how many files I have to find.
Oh, shit, there we go.
Okay, how many more?
Recovered a box.
I think there's one or two more, maybe?
Play two, three, and four.
I at least wanna do two and three.
Absolutely, without a doubt.
How the fuck am I...
How was I supposed to do that?
How was I ever supposed to do that?
Are you serious?
I don't even know missions yet.
Oh, fuck off.
Really?
Oh, what?
I wanna see the aliens.
All right, no fucking around.
I'm doing this quick.
I wanna see aliens.
Yeah, no more fucking around.
We're keeping this on.
I'm trying to not take one point of damage.
I can't believe this game fucked everything up.
It's got tire marks all over his butt.
Okay.
Can't fire?
Can't shoot.
I thought this car had guns.
Did I?
Okay, I'm stuck under here.
Get the fuck out of here!
I think he crushed his head.
Jesus.
Why do I have a sniper?
Where did I get a sniper rifle from?
How are you still alive?
I don't understand.
Okay.
This game sucks.
We can't review the game until we get to see the aliens.
Don't you...
I can't review it until we see aliens on the screen.
Hold off your judgments.
Hold them now.
Wait, this is a shotgun.
This weapon sucks.
Absolute fucking ass.
Are you kidding me?
What just happened?
Somebody's car exploded.
What?
What is this head lean?
I shot him right in the head.
Throw a grenade?
I don't have any grenades.
This is fucked you.
God damn it.
He's gonna kill me.
It's over.
This sucks.
What the fuck?
How?
He's inside of the thing.
He's inside?
Jeremiah, I don't think there's gonna be aliens.
There's gonna be aliens.
You have to wait.
I have a sniper rifle.
I'm just gonna snipe from like another building.
Yeah.
I'm just sniping from another building.
I'm climbing up and I'm gonna snipe.
Did you pay for this?
Yes, I did.
I think it's...
I think it's gonna be fun.
We have to get out of this segment.
Just trust me.
You gotta trust.
It's hard.
Okay, this is really hard to drive.
It just skids around all over the place.
Why?
Is the handbrake on?
I would not be driving it like this.
Okay, I gotta climb up somewhere.
I want a good view.
Let's get off.
There's only one guy up here.
Fucking god.
This fucking game.
I shot him in the head.
I shot him in his head.
In his head.
Oh my god.
Give me the sniper.
Sniper.
Give me the fucking sniper rifle.
Which one is it?
Oh, give me this weapon.
Okay, shooting people in the head doesn't matter.
Okay, good.
Now, are there plans up here?
I need to see the aliens in the city.
I'm sorry, guys.
This is how it works.
Here we go.
Plans.
There are three or four...
There's a lot more plans.
Holy shit, this sucks.
All right, what about the other buildings?
There's two plans in this building.
There's aliens in the room with you right now.
They were.
You just saw me get like shocked or whatever, electrocuted.
I did mocap for this game.
Did you really?
Oh, nice.
You did the mocap?
I have to see an alien.
I'm sorry.
That's the way it is.
Real mocap actor.
That's pretty sick, dude.
What was it like?
Was it cool?
Where the fuck is this thing?
This...
It has to be one more.
Where?
It's in one of these random buildings.
Come on.
We're here.
Over here.
Okay, right here.
My neck just got so itchy for no reason.
No, other side.
All right.
Finally, this one's done.
Mission complete.
Thank God.
All right.
Nice.
Awesome.
Okay, city two.
We believe that the aliens have the ability to hide in plain sight.
Use the detector to identify any aliens disguised as pedestrians.
We report they're at three locations marked on your radar.
Exterminate any you uncover immediately.
I've had more fun watching you paint walls and house flipper.
Once I see the aliens, don't worry.
Hey, Beepo.
Thanks for the five community subs.
All right.
So this is my...
Get to the location.
So this determines if somebody's an alien.
Does this hurt?
This does not seem to hurt.
3090 omega low.
You really telling me 3090 omega low in a game like this?
Here comes day Dallas levels of subordination.
I don't think so.
Not even close.
All right.
Somebody over here is an alien.
Do I want other people to know?
Which one is an alien?
There's more?
How are there more aliens?
Do I go somewhere else?
What is what?
What is that?
Oh, shit.
Is it like a false alarm or does it actually do it?
Next location.
Okay.
We've seen the aliens now.
Now I need to check everybody.
Oh, shit.
You're ready to stay calm.
All right.
You're all clean.
It doesn't have another game prepared.
Omega low day.
You know, you've got a great eye.
You've got a great eye.
You should.
Yeah, you should.
It doesn't have anything else planned for today.
Well, not technically.
No, you didn't have anything else.
No, it's just the plan.
Although there are other actually there are other options,
but I want to play tomorrow.
I don't want to do the game.
I'm supposed to play tomorrow today.
You guys aliens?
Nobody.
Okay.
Let me see what else I got.
I want to see one more area and then fine.
I want to see one more zone and then I'll be fine.
Jump King DLC?
No, not at a chance in hell.
Not in a million years.
Nope.
Pawn shop.
Yeah, the pawn shop game is tomorrow.
And I feel like that's an entire stream.
What we're looking for right now is a way to potentially
have another maybe like hour and a half.
I'm running people over.
All right.
It's down there.
What?
Where the where is it?
Deltarune?
I don't want to play Deltarune.
It's been so long since chapter one that I have to play chapter one
before I do chapter two again.
So we're going to do that next weekend.
I forget everything.
I don't want to jump into chapter two without I literally
I couldn't even tell you the main character's name is.
I couldn't tell you like this like three or four characters.
I have no idea what their names are.
What the fuck is how do I get down there?
Alien.
Is that not an alien?
That was an alien though.
All right.
Well, how do I get down?
Oh, it destroyed it destroyed all human.
Not this time.
I have no idea where the fuck is supposed to go.
He's not dead.
Apparently underground or down under somewhere.
I don't get it.
Like Picross.
We'll see what I have.
All right.
We'll switch games.
Don't worry.
Everybody relax.
I just wanted to see the aliens.
I don't know how to get.
Okay.
What about this farm and desert desert one?
All right.
Desert.
I just want to see the desert one.
Play the long drive.
No, I don't think so.
Check out the junkyard.
This is actually kind of cool.
Next game is just this game.
No, we'll play something else for like an hour.
I have to see if it's possible.
Every game of the gas station.
You need to know it works.
I can't move.
All right.
Let me see what I hold on.
Can I fly?
If you can fly a plane.
Look, give me a break, right?
Just hold on.
Really?
Come on.
Ah, all right.
Fine.
It was cool.
I liked it.
But I think we saw what we wanted to see.
And I'm going to move on.
We got minus two letter grade.
No, what are you talking about?
That's not fair.
All right.
We got.
Oh, shit.
I have that stupid.
Well, not stupid.
No, I have this too.
I got this too.
All right.
By a show of hands, I downloaded this.
I downloaded this game the other day.
It's called Animal Ultimate Simulator Battle.
What's it called?
Animal Revolt Battle Sim.
It looked like it was kind of insane.
Is it a YouTuber game?
It's a YouTuber bait.
Let's try it.
Whatever.
I'm not playing the game.
I'm not playing Pawn Shop.
I want to play that tomorrow.
Get the chopsticks.
I'll get the chopsticks in a minute.
Before the stream ends, I promise.
All right, give me a second.
Let me open this game up.
See if this is like a funny game or not.