Hey, April Fools. I'm not late today. There's the joke. There's the prank. I'm pranking you right now.
You're being pranked. Got ya. Oh man, you see your face. Oh, I got ya. How's my stomach? It's doing
alright. It's doing better. Good enough to stream. Yeah, today we're going to be playing Breath of
the Wild. I know a lot of people thought this wasn't going to happen. I've been saying I was
going to play Breath of the Wild over and over and over again for the last three or four months.
And now I'm finally doing it. How am I supposed to work if you keep streaming? I don't know. Go
do what you need to do and then earn your own after. It's been two months. I think it's been
longer than that. When was the last time I played Breath of the Wild? How long? It's been three or
four months. Oh, the mods are having a little bit of fun here. Good luck writing the word the
because I think that gets you timed out. Good luck. Mods are going to get rid of all like the
fucking like like the all the only speaking vowels or what are consonants allowed? Is that
the right word? What's that word? That's other letters. Consonant. Yeah, apparently the channel
was an emote only for the last like 16 to 17 hours, which is I guess kind of funny.
We all got into the chat today and I was we were talking to mod chat and it's like, wait a minute.
Oh, it's just been on emote only all night and all day. Oh, well, I already left it on last night.
Oops, 16 hours, bro. The words are the blocked words are now the is and how I'll put stupid on
there to put stupid, put going too slow, put the brain, put a ton of words that you know,
because nobody can say anything about my gameplay today. Take the word. I want gameplay.
I want gamer. I want gaming on that list. Only leave the nice words. Leave smart, talented,
funny, handsome. You know what I mean? That's all. That's all I want. Now we're just going to play.
Cam's not going to go on today and I assure you it's not a scenario where the cam is off
and slowly my room is going to get comedically sucked into a black hole and I'm going to turn
it on and be getting sucked into a black hole out a window or something that's not going to happen.
I know it's like April Fool's and a lot of people like expect something that's not happening today.
I'm just going to play Breath of the Wild. So there you are. I love OK, here are the terms
and phrases that are blocked right now and it reads like a funny story. Let me let me read you
the block list in in the order that I feel like reading it in. How is the gamer going too slow?
Brain sucks. Those are all individual blocked words. How is the gamer going too slow? Brain sucks.
Those are all words you cannot say today and I just happen to read them in an order that is
in order that I want to make sure it can't be written. Mods, just keep anytime you see
somebody talking shit, just add that to the block list until it's only just like happy positive
energy. Positive vibes only. Smelly? Nah, that doesn't offend me. Keep that on. That's fine.
Just keep it going. Well, don't just say words. Come on. Bald? Yep. All I'm telling you is your
chat experience today is probably going to be a little fucked up. So just be aware of that.
I know somebody's going to write the word the get timed out and they're going to be pissed,
but just I just know it's a fun. It's a funny day today. Okay, it's a funny day.
Just don't worry. What about asymmetrical? Like asymmetrical face?
Old. Well, that's just that's a factual statement. So I mean, I'm not old. No, remove that.
Remove tiny. Yeah, they'll they'll get a good list going. Anyways, haven't seen this in a while.
Have you? I don't be really honest with everybody here. I have no idea how to play. I have no
idea how to play this game anymore. It's been like three months. What am I? What do I do?
I think I have this marked. Where was I even going? This is marked. Where's the next guardian?
Just reset. I'm not going to reset. Is it here? I think I wouldn't have marked that if it wasn't
where I was going. We're going there. I've got to play. Okay, I'm good. It's B to open the glider.
How do I grab a rock? How do I grab the side of the how do I grab? Okay, it's X. Why can't I hear
this very well? There we go. You're a noob. Put that on the list too. Wait, no, I remember I got
attacked by like lightning and shit. I don't think I can go this way. I remember. Don't forget to
tweet. Oh shit, you're right. Thanks. I didn't. No, I didn't. This tweet sucks. Whatever. Oh,
did I lose my verified status? Do you want me to read you the draft tweet? That's never getting
posted, but it's a draft tweet. I haven't I had a draft tweet for when I lost verified status.
It didn't happen yet, so I can't post it because it didn't happen yet. So I'm just going to read
it to you now and then not post it. Okay, so this tweet is what does it say here? Okay,
drafts. Okay, this is what I was going to post when I lost verified status. It's not even that
funny, but I'm going to read it. Twitter removed my verified badge. How do I stop it? Is there a
questionnaire I can take? Can anyone lend a hand? Restarting my router didn't seem to do anything.
All my speed tests are perfect. I don't understand. That's pretty. That's all right. This is all right.
I think the funny part for me for that tweet is all my speed tests are perfect. Minus two is now
blocked. Oh, all right. Okay. All right. Look at that. Am I going to die from this? Probably.
Mods. Mods. They're finding a way to get around it. Fix it. I don't know how to play. I don't know
how to play the game. What did I just do? What? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. How to restart
the game. That was the moonlight scimitar. What was that? Was that a valuable weapon? I don't
remember how to play. Is that bad? Should I actually go back? I'm going back. I have no
idea what that was. I don't. It's a legendary weapon. Look at this thing. Twenty five damage.
Are you kidding me? I don't want to do that. All right. Let's keep going. That's where I was
going anyways. We're good. All right. Let me figure. Okay. X. No, this is Y. Y is attack.
B is jump. A is confirm. X is run. Left trigger is whatever this is. Is this block?
Okay, that's block. Left bumper is camera. This one's way better. Okay. Right bumper is
throw weapon. Don't do that. Right trigger is arrow. Up is powers. Left is shields. Right is
swords. What? Down is horse. But I haven't I haven't used the horse in like 40 hours of
gameplay. All right, let's go. I'm ready. This is a good skit. This is so stupid. You spelled it with
S T U V money sign T U P 1 D. It's like you guys are trying to get around the name filter in video
games. How do I spell fuck face without getting around the filter? Oh, I'll do like, uh, E E F
F like F H, uh, U, um, Ampersand new voice on log.
It doesn't spell fuck face. E E F H U Ampersand. What is that?
Remove stupid from the fucking board pull immediately. I can see it over here.
Well, you never heard the word Ampersand before. All right. I already realized I'm chilling out
today. Hey, you know what? Yeah. How's that? What's Perry? How do I make it so it doesn't do this
weird globe? What just happened? This thing's about to break. What is happening to my character?
What is going on? Why is this guy like harder than a boss? I'm getting hurt too. I'm cold.
I don't think it's supposed to go this way. I'm not I am not supposed to do what I'm supposed
to be doing right now. I'm not I'm not supposed to be going this way. This is not the way you're
supposed to go. I haven't played the game in three months. I don't know what route I was on.
I'm going this way. Do you know what they should make in video games? And I know people can be
like, oh, here he goes again. But listen to me. If the game knows you haven't played in three months,
I wish I could watch like a fucking recap video. Like a one minute recap like
that's in the background. We see you haven't played breath of the wild in six months.
Let us give you a quick crash course on everything that's happened and everything you need to know.
I'm doing this. You did your bit this bit already with Metal Gear Solid. There's a whole second
YouTube channel that you did this already. You read the sign, bro. For real, you just skipped
the entire oasis. So did I? Why are you so mean? All right, we will have a little fun today because
I would like for you to bet if I can beat this in 10 minutes. And I don't know if I would bet on me
right now, because I don't even know what the buttons do. I don't want you to see after three
months. There's no way. Well, then you know what to do. I would rather go broke a believer
than be rich and doubter. Wow. That's like really nice. That's like actually really sweet of you.
We believe in you. I hate you. Yeah, I know that all things must be balanced. All right. Are we
ready? In three, I'm looking at we make sure one of the mods has a clock. It's 10 minutes.
Three, two, one, go. I fuck. I think I give up. I don't know if I can do this.
This looks really complicated. I don't just put it down. Whoa. What? Oh, how do I safely? OK.
I need more barrels. What the fuck? Are there any more barrels? What is this? That goes over here,
which then this connects to here. I need way more shit. How am I supposed to get up here?
There's only one barrel in this whole area. How am I supposed to do? I forgot I had this power.
OK, I need another barrel. What if I do this? Can I? Everybody wants to help so bad. OK,
so what does this do? This counts as electricity. Can I get this electricity? Oh, this counts as
electricity. This counts as electricity. Shit. Another barrel. That's not a shit scenario.
That's a nice. Honestly, R1. I'm so used to. OK, I got another barrel. This is going right here.
How much do we have time? Am I good on time? Shit. I got to replace this right here. All right. OK.
What happened? What? What is going on? What the fuck? I walked over the. Now I'm just like,
all right, well, come on. The timer is still going. I know. I know. I know. I know. I know.
I'm working on it. I'm working on it. Why would you ever vote for me right now? Like ever? Like,
what were you thinking? What were you thinking today? You really thought this is going to work
out? I'm surprised. What were you thinking? What are you doing? You're doing the pointing
and laughing emote. Who cares? Stop touching electricity, you fucking moron. OK. All right.
We're good. I got plenty of time. I got six minutes. Six minutes is a lot of time. Thunder
blade. Oh, God damn it. Nice. Oh, this thing's Ricky. Ricky. Cool. This thing is
Ricky. Cool. What? I was going to say Rick, like from Rick and Morty.
It's wicked. Cool. How do I open that? I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
Oh, dude, I forgot to tell you guys, I turned on the new Space Jam movie
and I couldn't follow anything that was going on. I hadn't. I actually had no idea what was
happening in the movie. The first 50 minutes of that movie were just, it reminded me of like
Kingdom Hearts in a way. But Kingdom Hearts just kind of did it way better. It was like, oh, hey,
look, we're going to, hey, I just want to let you know that we, there's a character that is cool.
We're going to go to their world for 15 minutes and then we're going to leave. And by the way,
it's just the fucking Looney Tunes. None of the other characters do anything. Let's go to the
Batman world for like five fucking five minutes and that's it. Batman's not going to be in the
fucking movie, by the way. It's only, it's just the Looney Tunes. We're just going to go visit
every world, Kingdom Hearts style for like five minutes. That's the first, oh, I got to play.
All right. Where is it? Right there. Oh shit. Hold on. It's in here. Dude, don't do this to me
right now. There's money on the line right now. Okay. This is connected to here. That's already
going up there, which I think that just, hold on. Wait, hold on. That's going to give me that.
And then, wait, oh fuck. How do I, that has to go there. Is there another barrel I don't have?
There must be another barrel or something. How do I open this? Unless I have to get in here first.
Hold on. Is there another barrel? Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Look, look, look, look, look, look.
No, there's another, where's there another barrel? Do I need another barrel? I'm so close,
but where's the, what do I got time? Get over here. Come on. Come on. I'm so close. Stop. What
do I got? 20 seconds, Twi. I got 20 seconds. 20 seconds. Oh, everybody eat shit. I just did it.
And time with like five, 10 seconds to spare. You had like three seconds left. It was frame perfect.
I mean, I'm, wait, is it, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on a second.
Do we need to review it? We need to review the VOD. Apparently it was like one frame
is potential away from, it's one frame. It was, it may have been off by a frame. No. What? No,
it's not. Hold on. Let me get the VOD. Really? No way. So it's 10 minutes exactly. Right? Hold on.
I'll get it. Everybody hold for a second. Hold on. I gotta go. Is the VOD might not have it yet.
Sometimes it takes a few minutes. Okay. Recent broadcast. All right. Okay. Hold on. Let me get
this on stream. This is weird. I'm like putting the VOD in here. Okay. Okay. All right. I got
the VOD here. The question is now, so where was it? It was, it's where I say three, two, one, go.
All right. I got to plug my headphones into another, cause they're plugged into the, it's over.
It was 1001. It was 10, zero, zero, zero, one. What? Hold on. I, this is crazy. I need to plug
this in one sec. All right. What's the time here? Why am I not talking? Is there audio on this stream?
Where's the audio? There's no audio. I don't, why am I not talking? I don't know if I can do this.
The only thing I said. What the fuck? Okay. Um, looking at, we may, looking at, we may, two, one,
go. Okay. It's 1726. Forgot I had this power vote for me. Oh God. And by the way, it's Batman's
world kingdom heart style for like five. The VOD isn't even caught up yet. The VOD isn't even caught
up yet guys. We need to wait. Uh, we have to wait just a minute. Refresh it. Hold on. All right.
Refreshed. Okay. Let's go back to where it was there. Okay. So we got it. So what was it? 26,
right? So it's 1726. Two, one, go. Yep. It's 1726. Fuck. How do I? Oh, everybody. I just did it.
Three, 24, 25, 26. Wait, no, I don't know. I think that counts. I just did it. I guys, that counts.
1726. How do I do playback speed? I jumped. I jumped guys. I've my buttons. Do you understand
that? I'm telling you right now. I think I count that because one very important thing
I hit jump instead of accept because remember it all video games are swapped, right? It's like,
oh, B is A on Xbox and A is B and X is Y and that's, I don't know. Do we count that?
It really is like one frame. I don't know. It's, it's like, it's like a frame or two late.
Fuck you. You've stopped playing and talked about space jam for two minutes.
Um, does it count? I don't know. I've never had to deliberate this long on something like this.
What, what about walking through the door? Honestly, I think walking, I think walking
through the door is the solution. That's what I would say. Like I've walked through the book.
It's over. I win, right? It wasn't in 10 minutes. I don't have frames for this though.
Oh, shut up. You're annoying. Okay. I'm going to do space. I think I'm saying it. Do you hear that?
It's like, like I say time right when it's in 26 still. You know what? I don't know. I don't
know what to do. I think it, but what if it's wrong? What the fuck? If I just shut up about
space jam. I didn't do it. I did. I don't think I did it. I don't think I did it.
Because you know what, in mod chat, we're talking about this. People, uh, in mod chat, it's being
brought to my attention that in previous times it was when I accepted the reward. It looks like I
accepted the reward a 10th of a second too late because I jumped and it was one full second later
I accept the reward. I'm sorry everybody, but we, we have, we got, I'm sorry everybody. That's the
way it works. You shouldn't be mad at the frame perfect loss. You should be mad at me talking
about space jam for five minutes. Yeah, that we gotta, we gotta, that we gotta go by the truth
and that was the truth. I know. I'm so sorry. That's the truth. We gotta go by the truth.
All right. Okay, let's go. Bugs of Bunny can fuck off. Bugs of Bunny can fuck off. What? What's
going on? What? What's going on? What? What's still open? My stream is not open.
My stream is not open. My stream is not open. I'm telling you right now. My stream is not open.
Oh, okay. The banner is playing the stream. If you just go to German 985, the banner plays it.
No, it doesn't. What the fuck is going on? Yeah. The banner is playing the stream. All right. Let's
get back to it. Sorry, everybody. Okay. Sorry. Oh, sorry. I gotta plug this back in.
Taze on day. That's a classic. All right. That was cool. I got the floor. What's up? Oh, I was just
so focused just now. Do you have business with me? I don't know. What are you doing? But no,
I'm not a spy. I'm a merchant. I may not look like it, but I'm actually the leader of a caravan.
I've traveled all the way here, but this town doesn't allow men to go in. So that's why I had
to, um, be spying. It's research. It's research. And think what you want. But I finally found some
key info on how to sneak into Gerudo town. Oh, in key info. Let me share with you my heroic tale.
It's been close to a week now. The guards have kicked me out more times than I can count.
I almost gave up hope. However, I have learned only recently of a man that slipped into this
well guarded town or that men is frequently traveling between Kara Kara Bazaar and Gerudo
town and waiting here trying to spot him as he traveled. This is bright. I'm surprised he can
read. They're from the town. It said in between the town. Okay. So this is the road. Good travel on
the road. No fun allowed. There is no fun allowed. Not today. Why do I not have a horse? I have not
had a horse the entire playthrough. I have to walk this whole way. This got to be a state.
Frank 2 is right here. You're not too far away. What? Oh, it's too hot for the horse. Oh, shit.
Okay. By the way, why am I not on the road? There is no road. Use your shield. All right. How do I
do that? It's like a weird button combination, right? Remember what's wrong, babe? You've barely
touched your gruel. No, I'm not. I'm not feeling it today. L plus A. There it is. Okay. Holy shit.
That was cool. Okay. I don't see anybody. Do you? My boss, I get the feeling that he isn't coming
back from Gerudo town anytime soon. Hope he's okay. Man snuck in. What? There's a man who got
into Gerudo town? And the boss says he comes here to the Kara Kara Bazaar? I guess it must be true
if the boss said so. Never seen anyone around who respects me as a super sneaky guy. There was that
pretty Hylian gal at the general store. It's unusual to see a Hylian girl dress like a Gerudo.
Her Gerudo clothes. I wonder where she bought them. Maybe if I wore those clothes. Ah, nah. I'm
so out of my element with all this sneaky stuff. Okay. What's our use for a weapon? What's the
shittiest thing that I have? Probably this. This thing sucks, right? Oh, that thing kind of sucks,
doesn't it? What's the matter? You got this look on your face that almost screams I gotta talk to
you right now. Buy my stuff. Buy my book. Buy my book. Buy my book. Buy my book. Somebody knows
what that is. Okay. I have a lot of junk, but I don't want to sell anything right now. Okay.
Uh, hi. Who are you? Uh, you, you're a voe, aren't you? Gotta go. I am. Why? Hmm. No, I bet mama
would have a problem with a delicate voe like you. Oh yes, I'm Ronson. I hail from Gerudo town.
The search for the love of my life is so exhausted by it. I'm exhausted by it.
Search. Uh, I don't know why I'm even saying this. It's no business of a Hylian like you, but
I'm constantly being bothered by my mother over not having found the love of my life.
Why the rush? You don't know? Really? It's incredibly rare for a male to be born
to the Gerudo. For our own survival as a people, we travel to find husbands. I've
proven myself to be a gifted tailor, but none of the voe I've met seem to appreciate a well hemmed
garment. I was hoping my craft would help me find a mate, but it doesn't seem like there's much work
for a tailor around here. I wonder if there's really, if there really is someone out there for
me. What's this person doing? A treasure hidden inside a sandstorm by an ancient civilization.
Sounds like an adventure just waiting to happen. They say the sandstorm lets up for a few hours
each day, but I haven't seen it settle down for even an instant. Shifty merchants. Sorry,
no idea what you're talking about. The only things- did you fart? No. The only things I'm
interested in right now are this sandstorm and the treasure hiding inside its storming sands.
Okay, well, who are you? Okay, so there's a treasure over there? Okay. Who do I need to talk to?
Any suspicious vendors. From my point of view, pretty much any merchant that is in Gerudo looks
suspicious, you realize. Still, no, it's my chair squeaking. The general store. Okay, where's the
general store? I thought that was a lion. Isn't this the general store right here? Oh, maybe this
is the general store. What do you got? That divine beast, it feels like it gets a little bit closer
every day. I wonder how long it'll be before I can get back to Gerudo town. Gerudo town.
There's a town to the southwest made up almost entirely of Gerudo. It's the largest settlement
in these parts. It's got a lively market and a canteen. The town's active from morning to night.
But well, they have a rule that'll affect you guys aren't allowed in. No vo may enter, they say.
Okay, I know. I'll take care of it. I got the divine beast, I got it. The sound of the divine
beast walking might be loud, but the beds are still comfy. Do you want to stay? No. What does this
even go to? I can't just take that? All right, so there's somebody in here I need to talk to?
Is it you? Oh, have you seen a sneaky guy? Sneaky what? You mean a vo sneaking around town. I
haven't seen anyone like that. There's a Hylian Vi who likes to relax on the roof, though in the
afternoon it's probably too hot up there. Do I have to sleep or something? Climb, climb,
stop doing that. Somebody's sleeping up here. Please don't turn face cam on. No, I'm not going
to. All right, hi. Oh my, what a lovely young lad you are. Do you need something from me?
Um, yes. What's that? You've heard about a man who snuck into Gerudo town. Oh, I don't
know anything. I don't know anything about him. Sorry, I couldn't be more help. Um, either one of
these? Gwent? You're making my cheeks warm looking at me like that. Um, which one of these do I do?
This one? I'm sure you agree that these clothes only help my looks, right? Now that I think about
it, the style would look quite fetching on you. I'd have to charge you of course, but I bet people
would see you completely differently if you wore them. What do you think? Do you want to buy them
for 600 rupees? Fuck out of here. Are you kidding me? Oh my fucking shins. All right, I need to sell
something. What do I have that's worth anything? All right, scream. Scream if I'm going to delete
something that's valuable because I forget this. There's certain things I can get rid of, like the
amber pieces or something, right? Are these valuable? What's the thing I can sell? It's been
three months. Sell the parts. I have a lot of these, you're right. It's not worth that much,
though. Sell the gems. Sell the gems. Sell the gems. Um, like this? Is this okay? How many do I need?
I have 225. Is that okay? That's okay, right? Just don't sell the luminous ore. Okay, this is more
than that. I hope I'm not doing something wrong. All right, let's go. Haha, softlocked April fools.
I keep holding X to go faster, but that's not how you do it. You have to jump. It's okay,
you'll find more. Yeah, I'll be all right. Gems don't have any purpose but just to sell. Okay.
All right, let's do it. All right, I already did this, right? Six. Is this a- I'm not going
to get scammed or something, am I? That's a lot of money. E. You look adorable. Ah, hee hee hee.
Just as I thought, you bake for quite a good looking gal. That's a traditional Gerudo outfit.
It's such a striking look around here. I doubt anyone would even suspect that you're a man.
On top of that, it breathes so well that it's sure to help you deal with the desert heat,
at least a little. So glad I was able to help you out. If you're free to grab something to
eat sometime, keep me in mind. What was that? What was that? Oh, if you want to get more ladies
clothing, come back any time. Okay, all right, let's go. Does this have any- does this have,
like, armor? Protects from the harsh sun. Wait, does this give me heat resistant?
Ooh, all right, cool. Let's go. Now I can just get in. I can just walk in, right?
Don't jump in the lava. I can teleport? Oh, that's right. I forgot. I forgot that was a
feature of this video game. Drip acquired. Bro forgot about fast travel. When you're going to
do a blink cosplay. Why can't you just cheat millions of rupees in? Because that's cheating.
All right, so can I just go in? What's going on over there? All right, I'm going in.
I can just walk in? Hi. Okay. Vore strictly forbidden. Take your time. Okay. If you stop
by the canteen, do yourself a favor and order a noble pursuit. It's hands down the best ring
I've ever had. This is a bright ass place. This area is 95% bloom. Okay. I already have all this,
don't I? It's your brightness? I don't think it's my brightness. I don't have any money to buy
anything. Take- you can take the outfit off now? No, I can't. Yes, you can. I said I couldn't- I
have to- hold on. There's the Gerudo chief. Yet another traveler. What did you get in here?
Seems you have something rather interesting there. I didn't know they spoke in this game.
Some of them do. Declare your business but come no closer. Hold on, Ulyara. This one appears to be
more than a common traveler. You there, what is your name? Link. And what is it you've come all
the way here to tell me? I only got one option. I can calm Naboris. You think you have what it takes
to subdue something so powerful as a divine beast. The only ones who could ever control them
were champions like Lady Urbosa. And all of the champions died in the Calamity a hundred years
ago. Hmm. Ulyara, a memory just jumped into my head. Something my mother spoke of. When the
Calamity happened, the princes of Hyrule placed a fallen swordsman into a deep sleep. That swordsman,
much like our new friend here, was named Link. That would always seem more legend than fact.
But Lady Riju, do those same stories not also say that a Hylian champion carried a legendary
sword? I see no such weapon in this person's care. They do indeed, if I recall correctly.
It was called the sword that seals the darkness. A princess of Hyrule supposedly hid it away
at every target in America. And every Walmart in America. What if the device on this one's hip?
It appears to be a precious relic of the Sheikah. I can't imagine they would give something so
valuable to a simple drifter, can you? I don't remember ever hearing of a Hylian Vi among the
champions. Wait a minute. You're a Vo. A Vo within our walls is a great crime, but a Vo who is a
champion? Well, we'd never mistreat a friend of Lady Urbosa. If you're here to help us with
Naboris, then we are allies. You saw it on your way to our town. Divine Beast Va Naboris cloaked in
a massive sandstorm hurling lightning at any who dare approach. We have to do something to stop it,
but we have yet to find any way to appease the Divine Beast on our own.
If you truly are a champion, perhaps you will be able to enter Naboris and calm its anger.
Lady Riju. Am I saying that right? Is it Riju? Riju? Am I saying it wrong? Is it Riju? Riju.
Riju. Okay. Perhaps if this person were first to prove his worth by recovering your stolen
thunder helm. Ah yes, an interesting suggestion. You see, there is only one thing in all the
Hyrule that can withstand the lightning from Naboris. Thunder Helm, a family heirloom and
relic of Gerudo. But as Buliaras says, it was stolen from us. You didn't worry Lady Riju,
if he truly is a champion, this should be an easy task for him. As long as he's not streaming on
Twitch. He's not a streamer. It'll take less than probably 30 minutes, but if he is a streamer,
then we're fucked for at least like six hours. You can't even minus two. Don't worry. I got it
covered. Our soldiers can tell you all you need to know about the thieves that stole Lady Riju's
heirloom. Head through this arch. It will lead you to the barracks. Then seek out Captain Teek
and ask for full report. Without my heirloom, you'll never be able to approach Naboris. Okay.
So I have to get that. Okay. Where are the gems? Hello. What are you doing in here? This is the
barracks for the chief's guards. Not a place for tourists to gather. We're on high alert after the
recent theft. So you should clear out. Turn down the brightness. I don't... Did I fuck it up?
Hold on a second. My apologies. I'm the officer in charge of the soldiers, Captain Teek. The
chief's heirloom was stolen by thieves belonging to the Yiga clan the other day. So everyone is on
edge. We've determined that the Yiga's hideout is in Carusa Valley. The soldiers are all exhausted.
So I was just thinking about requesting some extra help. Listen up. This Hylian Vi has agreed to help
us. So offer her any information you can. Consider her a part of our unit. If you have any questions,
my troops would be happy to help. Is it bright? I don't think I can even do that. Turn up the
brightness. Wait hold on. There's not like gamma on this or something that I have turned up. No
there's not. I think that's just how it is guys. Gotcha April Fools. Getting real fucking sick of
putting this up. Okay let's go. I don't have any money but okay. So this is the Divine Beast. So I
need to get... Where's the helm? They said what? Some town or valley or something? Over here. Okay.
So I gotta go over here. Check your quests. Ah okay. I think I just have to go up there.
Let's go that way. Oh you're a Hylian Vi. We don't see too many of you. I can't tell how old you are
but you look a little young to be coming to my shop. We make special drinks here. Drinks that
are definitely just for adults. How old is Link? Our featured cocktail is called Noble Pursuit. Many
of our customers come here specifically to order it. A light sweet taste. The cool sensation from
Meatship. It's like drinking distilled motivation. Okay so I can't I can't drink it. Link is 17.
Okay he's 117. What? He slept for 100 years. Oh huh? He was very tired. It was at the start of the
game. That was four months ago. I don't remember that. I feel like I've been asleep for 100 years.
Okay so I think I'm just gonna go up here but I don't have like a place to go.
Was it actually in the quest log? I don't see it anywhere. Oh I have to talk to everybody okay.
The yellow circle on the map. Yeah that's really far up. What are you doing in here?
I'm an archaeologist of sorts. I was just poring over some ancient text that I discovered the other
day and I finally decoded it. Well part of it at least but the rest it's not far off.
With this discovery I'll finally be able to make a name for myself as an archaeologist.
Of course you and I meeting here is no coincidence. I've never been one to question fate.
I can't explain why but I trust you for some reason. I'll tell you the details of my research.
Let's hear it. There's a temple east of here near the entrance to the
Gerudo desert. It's dedicated to the seven giant statues of the heroines said to be the divine
protectors of Gerudo. It's at this temple that I originally discovered the ancient script or reads
when the symbols of the seven find their place the blessed path will be revealed. That's all I've
been able to get. You know I'm going way too fast. It's believed that people once came from around
the world in search of the heroine's blessing but as far as I can tell it doesn't appear that anyone
has found it yet. I'm not sure what exactly it means but maybe I'll find out once I've deciphered
more of the text. I'm not sure if this is related but it said that heroines held powers that were
part of a bigger whole. Each heroine had a different power, skill, spirit, endurance, knowledge,
flight, motion, and gentleness. Interesting. But they all look the same to me. I should understand
the entire script before long but that's only the beginning of my problems. That divine beast has
been moving around the area making it harder for me to conduct my research. There's no respect for
academia. What would my because what there's the seven deadly sins and then this is seven deadly
virtues whatever it is right. There's an opposite. What are the virtues? A lot of people don't know
that there are seven virtues and there are seven sins. Everyone's like oh you know envy, lust,
pride, greed. Nobody ever talks about the virtues. The seven heavenly virtues. It's charity,
um charity, humility, what are they? Humility, charity, humility, charity, chastity, gratitude,
temperance, patience, and diligence. Those are the seven virtues versus the seven sins. Yeah all we
ever hear about is like oh greed and envy. I want to hear more about fucking temperance. What's
temperance's deal? Okay so let's talk. Go play Binding of Isaac then. Okay you are you serious?
Why did you let her go by herself? I apologize she said she just wanted to check it out.
Oh as if we aren't busy enough searching for the chief's heirloom. Now we have to find
Barta too. If the captain hears about this fiasco she'll punish us for sure. Probably a hundred laps
around Jevudo desert again. Catholic Andy. I did I'm just saying we have everyone always does a
bunch of shit about the seven deadly sins but we never hear about fucking chastity. We never hear
about um harmony or whatever the other one is. We never hear about charity well charity yeah.
It's chastity. What is hold on a second why is everybody freaking out about this?
The state or practice of refraining from extramarital or especially from all sexual intercourse.
Chastity is no sex. The virtues most virtuous of all streamers.
Yeah what am I talking about? I'm sitting here going like you know we keep hearing about greed
and lust. I want to hear more about no sexual intercourse. I want to hear about no sex, no
alcohol, no drugs. I also want to hear about um being polite to I want to be where's politeness.
What are the other ones? Hold on I need to break this down. The seven virtues.
Humility okay humility. I think everybody could do with a little bit of humility right. What's
wrong with that? Charity. What's wrong with that? Gratitude. I think people you know being
gratitude being thankful and patience. That's a really big one. Patience is a huge one.
Diligence. That's a big one. Temperance. Let me look this up before this temperance doesn't
mean like sex or anything right? Temperance is the moderation in action thought or feeling
restraint. Moderation in the indulgence or passions. I would be temperance. We got fucking
oh we we got we got the most virtuous of all the virtues. Temperance. All things in moderation.
Temperance Andy. The only thing I knew about temperance was it spawned the blood donation
machine in Isaac. That's it. That's the only thing I knew. All right these guys are fucking
horrible. These guys are got a lot of health. This thing breaks. Okay oh yeah it's jump over
or jump to the side right. I'm gonna jump over it and do the big flurry. It didn't count.
Oh dude don't even. What the fuck? What do you even have any food? Kind of stealth boost.
Oh I'll eat this. Oh my god I hate this enemy. They just do a gigantic aoe that you can't get
away from. Everyone's so much faster than me. I'm just running. You won. I'm I lost. I'm
are you kidding me? What is going on with these enemies? Why are they like tuned up times a
hundred fucking million? What? I'm not even going that way. You have no armor on? Oh shit I had
armor on last time and still do the same thing. I'm reading mod chat. I did know what that is.
I've heard that before. I just I thought it meant something else too. What the fuck does you think
it meant? I I don't know. There's no way I'm gonna climb that. What's going on over here?
No temperance? Yeah I'm showing a lot of temperance right now by not fucking banning
like 4 000 of you from the chat. Can I launch this? That's patience not temperance. Oh well
temperance is restraint. Restraint, moderation. It's gonna go the correct way. This dude is a
heretic. You have to balance the virtues with the sins. There was one time that Holly and I
were eating and watching tv and we were watching a video of somebody eating a bunch of food. It was
one of those like oh look eat videos. I forget which one it was what we were even fucking watching
but we were eating a pie together. Yeah a mukbang. Yeah we were eating a pie and it was a banana
cream pie. We were just eating out of the tin together and I remember I was pointing at the
screen going this is this is sin. This is sin right here and we're eating a fucking pie out
of the tin together. It was like what what am I talking about? I was going this is sin. This is
sin right here and I had a mouthful of whipped cream and banana cream and I was shoveling it
into my mouth on the fucking couch and she started laughing her ass off. I'm just like what what?
She's like do you this is sin looking into a mirror. No you don't understand this is sin.
This is delicious banana cream pie by the way honey. Oh yeah I'll take a lot of spoonful full
of it. It was just such it was such a hypocrite. Why did that scare the shit out of me?
Is he a ghost? What's wrong with Link? He's just like oh he's a ghost. Can I make it up here?
No I didn't start saying okay no no no no no I think people have uh or let me let me give some
more context. I didn't start by chanting that. We had watched like five of them in a row sitting
there eating this pie and at at some point during this pie eating watching mukbangs is when I just
started pointing at the screen saying it. I don't know we were just watching. I think people just
don't people underestimate how much media I consume all the time. I watch a lot of shit. I
watch tons of streamers and YouTube channels and TV shows. I just don't really talk about it. No yes
where am I going? I could have just teleported over here. I thought you didn't watch much movie
or TVs. Years ago that was the case. I want to say the last the last like six to twelve months
we've been watching a lot of media. I'm just hanging out on the couch. I am catching up with
almost a decade of TV I've not watched. So think about how awesome the position I'm in is. Think
of all the TV shows that have been huge. All the all the animes that you keep telling me to watch
that I've not seen a single episode of that is a queued up. I got Better Call Saul. I got I media
this this I forgot I forgot to play the game. God damn it I hate when this happens. Oh my god
what is going on right now? I think I'm screwed here. Let's teleport again. Good call. There's
so much TV. There's so much movie. All the movies too. Oh you know what we saw um recently as well
we saw the new Puss in Boots. That was really cool. That was that was a really just nice movie.
It was a really nice movie. Okay I'm gonna go this way because that's I think this is the correct way
to go to get up there. It was very good. So um I I don't want to speak completely out of my ass
because I don't know who was you know animation director on that movie but I really like this new
trend of animated movies especially with the action sequences dropping their frame rates down
a little. It's almost like that low frame rate feeling where oh this again Into the Spider-Verse
did that where each frame was almost deliberate. I really love that style a lot. It's kind of like
comic-y yeah. I don't like the high frame rate shit. I you know anti-technology Andy that's fine.
A 60 fps like a full like movie shot in like 48 fps and on those like plasma screen TVs
where it's like 500 hertz it's just it's just it's a movie now. It's a movie now. It's not I can't
suspend my disbelief that much anymore. I remember watching I think it was one of the Lord of the
Rings in 48. I think maybe it was The Hobbit or something and it was at 48 144 hertz 240 hertz or
something. It was just I felt like somebody was videotaping it with a camcorder. They were actors
on the screen. It wasn't a movie anymore. Now you want to go? It's the self-opera effect. Exactly.
Exactly. Stop. Oh my goodness. What did I just spawn? Look at all those gems. All right goodbye.
Frame rate really only matters for games. I miss like 16 millimeter too. I know I'm an old person
but though a lot of movies that are filmed in 16 and 30 millimeter film
they act they feel different. They hit way differently. A lot of people here.
Why even fight them? All right don't kill me please. These drop a lot of money. Holy shit.
Okay what's this? Duplex bow. Fire two arrows at once.
How do I change my bow? Oh it has to be out first. Okay this thing's almost broken so I'm
just gonna get rid of it. And now what? Torch? Is this some puzzle bullshit? This is some puzzle
bullshit isn't it? I can't even carry anything. I have to get rid of this because it's gonna want
me to walk around with the torch. I'm gonna light the torch here. Yep okay. What the hell do you
want me to do? Be more positive? Oh sure actually. So even if I don't know where I'm going I think
it's fine. I should be fine. It takes a little longer but that's okay. This door has fire on it.
I'm imagining it has something to do with my flame in my hand. Oh I can go this way.
That's where I came from. It's okay to check though. Maybe I burn the door? Really good. That
was a good idea. I just had a really good idea. I'm not gonna hurt them. Nothing over here.
It's okay. It was worth a try. Fuck away from me. You little monsters. Let me try doing this.
Oh I can move these. Maybe I should burn them. Customer service. Oh that's another okay um you
know also I've seen a little bit of uh we've watched some of the old Jackie Chan movies.
If have any of you ever seen Drunken Master? Holy shit those movies are fucking unbelievable.
The old police story movies? Wow. If you've never seen police story, if you've never seen Drunken
Master 1 and 2 please please for the love of god within the next two or three days go watch them.
The amount of of skill and the amount of of dedication that that they did in those movies
they were fucking unbelievable. It's required reading for the stream now. Gremlins 2 is on
there. Drunken Master 2 is on there too. Are you okay? Yeah I'm good. Are you? Which ones? Police
story and then Drunken Master. Jackie Chan it's gone. The old catalog of the old 80s and 90s
movies. Just go watch them all. I promise you won't be disappointed. They're just outrageous
with how talented and the martial arts are. They don't make them like that anymore and I will say
that. They don't make them like that anymore. They really don't. Go ahead. Say it. Go ahead.
They don't. Batches me. Go ahead. They don't make them like that anymore. John Wick? John Wick is
John Wick is good. John Wick is very good but I still don't think I still think the old Jackie
Chan movies are are better. I do. John Wick is awesome but I still think that those old Jackie
Chan movies are are just they're the greatest of all time. They're yeah and it's like it's kind of
unfair to compare them anyways. What was even in this chest? I don't know. I'm just picking stuff.
I've been putting it down now. It was money okay. I actually bad chested during the one of the I
think it was the third um the third John Wick movie. I actually was bad chesting. I was like
what the fuck? Whoa. Oh yeah. During Drunken Master I couldn't even have an emotion. It was just my
eyes were just glued to the screen. I didn't even have time to bad chest. It was like what the fuck.
This is unbelievable. My jaw can't even go down. Oh you know what what a really big difference
between John Wick and the old Jackie Chan movies are? Uh not very not a lot of firearms. The use
of like guns. It was mostly martial arts. Okay so what am I doing here? And some of the shit they
pull off in John Wick with the firearms is crazy right? It's hard to compare them. I just break
these? Take. Can I not push these out of the way? Vicious sickle. I have that's right. I have bombs.
Thought it's been too long. Okay what's going on here? Oh I didn't get this one. I need to draw.
I don't want to break it but I want to drop it. I hear some sparklies. Oh it's that. Yeah I've seen
Kung Fu Hustle. Kung Fu Hustle is awesome too. What made you want to hop on Zelda again? Immense
peer pressure by 30 to 40 000 people. Wait what's going on? You mean to tell me I opened up every
single one of them and the last one I opened was the right one? I'm sitting here looking for a
puzzle. All right let me eat some of these bananas. I need to. I didn't cook. I forgot to cook. Uh oh.
I hope there's nothing that dangerous in here. Oh shit someone's in there. What are you doing here?
This is the hideout of those Yiga thieves who stole the thunder helm. If they spot you they'll
call their friends for sure. There's no way you can take them all on. Only you had some way of
distracting them but I don't know how. All I ever see them do is patrol and eat bananas. I haven't
seen anything else that you could exploit as a weakness. Poison the bananas. Poison the bananas.
I played enough Hitman. Okay. I don't know what weapon to use. They all seem too good. What do I
use? I don't know what to do. Oh you have emote only ma. Oh no. But I don't want to break a good
weapon. Whatever I'm gonna use this. No I'm not. I'm gonna use. I'm just gonna use the torch. It's
not an instant kill. I just wanted the treasure. Just give me the chest. What's in it? Oh a sapphire.
Oh my god this banana is right there. I know what to do. I know what to do. I know what to do.
All right so I have to shoot the bananas down. They probably go for the bananas. All right so
bananas are on this side over there. Look at the bananas. What are you doing? I'll take them if
you don't. Open them. What are you doing? Oh you're gonna eat the banana? Is it here? This sound?
All right this sound. Dude what the? I'm doing this because fuck this place. Oh my god never mind.
You see the banana? Get the fuck out of here. Get out of here. Oh fuck. Oh shit. Are you coming
over here? Is there any more bananas? Oh my god. What the fuck is going on here? Forced stealth
missions. Drop every game of full letter grid. That's the rule. I didn't make it. I just follow
the rule. So it's a good thing that uh Breath of the Wild started at 11. What just happened? Hey
can you help me? I don't know what I did but there's like people fighting me. Open that up.
Let me in there. Okay so bananas. Will you just stop playing? Stop playing around and kill me
already. Stop messing around and get get the job done. You're messing around. Thank you. So bananas.
I have a lot of them. Can I throw them? Can I just? Can I put them on the ground? Well that
does that work? Hold. It does work. Okay that fixes a lot of things. So this one should be,
I just need to have patience. Come on I gotta do one of the virtues. Prove that I'm a virtuous
streamer. Patience. Temperance. Shut up. That's lame. I'm telling you there's not, there's one
thing a gamer doesn't want to hear in a game. It's this. Nobody wants to hear that.
Oh nobody wants to hear that in any game. Where'd they go? Okay all right. Just I don't want to
waste the bananas. The bananas just dropped next to you. Bananas are next to you. How did you not
want to eat those? If I kill them does it just, can I just skip this whole section if everybody
here dies? Yeah? All right let's go. I'm taking out the fucking royal claymore for this one.
No I'm not. I'll use this. I don't, what is, where am I? Okay cool. Just hold five of them.
I'm just gonna throw a handful of these on fucking ground. Look what I got. I came to the potluck.
Here look what I, look at this. Okay I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I could have killed him if I didn't
have the fucking torch equipped. I'll do it for real this time. This part sucks. I'm glad
my face cam isn't on. Actually let's turn it on for a second so you can see probably how red I am.
Oh my god. I hate this. So I just want to play the game. I hate like, oh sneak. Oh wait. Wait a
second. Wait hold on. Wait for them to walk around the corner. Oh I hate these in games.
Shit. Oh that's the fastest way to die. Go get out of here. I'm never gonna be able to do this.
This is gonna be worse than the forest. Bro I didn't even pick up the bananas. I'm so flustered
right now. Did I? I'm so flustered I didn't even realize that I did pick up the bananas and I got
mad because I didn't think I'd picked up the bananas but I already picked them up. That's next level
tilted. All right just wait. Let's just sit here for 25 minutes while he walks around. Go get it.
Okay back here again. How did that miss? I want to get that but I don't even care. Why does he not
see it? The banana's right next to you. What's going on? Is this bugged? What's happening here?
Are you gonna see it now? That was dumb. You didn't, this guy see me? What the fuck is happening in
this video game right now? I don't give a shit. I'm going. I'm gonna use the royal claymore. I'm
not fucking around anymore. Holy shit that's the absolute. I just, I got their whole stash. Oh my
goodness gracious. All right can you guys help me? Am I missing an item or something? Because
like this seems impossible. No? My armor is loud. I'm gonna fucking take it off. I feel like I'm
making the same amount of sounds I wore earlier. I'm looking at the sound meter. The purple line
that's still bad. The weapons too? I don't think that's doing anything. All right so what the hell
happened here? This doesn't really sense. Here's your banana. Go get it. Why are you looking at me?
Is anybody up here? Is somebody gonna see me up here? I hope not. I got your whole stash. Fuck all
of you. Yeah I'm gonna watch this. Okay where do I need to go? That's where I died. I gotta go
across that way right? This is gonna be a really ballsy move. What are you fucking talking about?
Get up there. No! Why didn't I jump? Why didn't I go up? What? Are you fucking shitting me?
Why couldn't I climb over that? You gotta be fucking kidding me. Why couldn't I climb up the
lip? It's not like it was any different than any other lip in this whole game so far. What is this
shit area? Why did you make me come here? This sucks. The sounds and shit too. They can hear you.
They can see you. They can see you from across the whole fucking map. This motherfucker right here
sees me every time I shoot the banana down on the right side which is in my brain. It's hey
go look there's a banana over there. He don't care. He doesn't care. Huh? What's this guy's deal?
Why won't he go to the banana? It's right there dude. Go get that banana. No no no no do not put
a bomb down. Whatever you do please don't put the bomb down. Oh fuck I have to put the bomb down.
Shit. Wait. Wait. Can I magnetize the banana? There's radiation in those fucking things.
I definitely can't. Oh my god there's another banana right there. He's gonna see this.
Try this again. I'm looking at mod chat. One of the mods said this is the port of the game
where I left and never came back. Baby rage. Baby rage. I'm glad there's no face cam on
because that looked weird. I almost snapped my controller at this part. I had to take a break.
Oh no. I have an idea. Let's just be. I just got like a hundred bananas. Why would I not do this?
Is anybody even over there? Shit. Oh dude this just there's no safe place to go. Please don't
turn around. Please don't turn around. Please don't turn around. Okay I'm okay right here.
Now I'm gonna throw a bunch of bananas over here. Sit down. You can't hold that here.
What are you talking about dude? Which way is he gonna go? Which way is he gonna go?
Is he going this way? Is somebody over here? Why? It's okay. I'm all right. I'm gonna get to
the ladder. If he doesn't go for one of those bananas I'm gonna scream. I don't even. I don't.
That could be a legendary item. The master sword could be in that chest. I don't care.
I don't want it. I'm kind of concerned right now though. Okay please tell me I did it right.
I'm going. I'm going. Oh no. Oh my god. Are they here? Nobody comes in here right?
Just happened. Whoa. What the hell was that? Tapaz. What's a tapaz? Thank god. Like in Diablo
2. Diablo. What's Diablo? Diablo? Who the heck are you and what are you doing in my napping spot?
Wait a minute. A thing on your hip. Is that a sheikah slate? If that's a sheikah slate then that means
that means it's you. You're that link guy I've been looking for. What luck. My scouts are out in the
field looking high and low but you just wander into my hideout. Oh excuse me. I haven't introduced
myself yet. I'm the leader. I'm strong. I'm burly. The one. The only. Master Koga. Prepare yourself.
Okay bye. I was gonna see you again. No. No. No. Better. Come on. I gotta get better than that.
That's good. Oh look at all the crystals around him. No. No. Keep the old picture.
Oh my fucking god damn it. Get me out of this. I'm sure I use this as a weapon.
Freezing frost blade. I can't turn that into ice. What just happened? He dropped it on his head.
Uh oh. Double. Where do they go? Just fly at you.
Hmm. Oh no. No. No. No. No. No. No. I know. I know. I know. I know. Close. Yeah.
Same deal right? A little late. Phase three. It's a big one. When does he drop it?
Okay so it's tethered to him. Ha ha ha ha. Hmm. Again? That's pretty easy. Just fun though.
You think I'm just gonna let this stand? Do you?
You? I almost lost my temper there. What a pain. I can't go out this way. What to do? What to do?
He hates this game. Why didn't you just use the bow? What do you mean?
I need my serious moves. This is the end. That was infuriating. You're gonna be alright.
You'll be alright. You're gonna be fine. Pretty soon you'll be gone and not just from my light
of sight. Only the leader of the Yiga clan can use this secret technique. It is the- Oh no.
His own creation? Killing him in the end? All the hubris? All the arrogance? Who could have seen
that coming? If only he had temperance and patience. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Yes. Yes. Yes.
What's in it? Yes. I can't wait to open this. Yes. What's in here? God. Okay. Calm down. What's in
here? Freshest Gerudo heirloom. Reclaimed from the Yiga. Hooray. Yeah. No, I didn't. Alright. Now we
can go all the way back here. Right? We have to bring this back. Let's go save it. Yeah. Jeremy,
you can just stop playing. It's okay. What did I say? A full letter- I said it was an 11 so a full
letter grade down would be a 10. I'm also saying that to all the Nintendo fans. Don't, uh, don't
murder me. I'll bring this shit down a full letter grade. I just heard- I heard like the
pitchforks get grabbed. Like off the fucking castle wall. Okay. Do you think it's a B?
I think it's better than a B. I think this is definitely an A. I don't know what kind of A.
It could be an A minus. It could be an A just regular A. Am I not allowed in here? It feels
like a B game with you playing. Oh, okay. This is 100%. This is 100% at least a 90%. We'll see.
Have the heirloom. I would give it an 80, but I'm not Mr. Streamer. No, this is a great game.
Anytime I think a game is great, it go- it's a 90 at least. He hates it. No, I just hated that
section. I just hate stealth. Even in the game that's built around a stealth game, every time
I played Hitman, I sneak past the first guard and then just throw bricks, vases, and fucking
briefcases at people. I just can't- I just don't like them. I hate stealth games. I do. You can say
he hates- I hate stealth games. I hate them. I do? Fine. You got it out of me. I don't like them.
Fine. I don't like them. That's kind of good. Oh, I've been holding that in for like 10 years.
That feels good. What- I'm gonna get some more takes. How about- you know how I feel about this?
Just go off on just- how about this take? I don't give takes. No. No, thank you.
Your arrival in the midst of all this must be the work of Lady Urbosa. Please give me the helm.
Jerma, you only take you never give. You've got me fucked up today.
Boy, have the two of you been getting along all right?
It's okay, I know. Your silence speaks volumes. She gets frustrated every time she looks up and
sees you carrying that sword on your back. It makes her feel like a failure when it comes to
her own destiny. Don't worry, it's not like you carry blame in any of this. I didn't have
breakfast this morning. I can relax. Stomach's grumbling.
You be sure to protect her with your life.
The game's quiet, sorry. You guys are fucking crazy, I love it.
The night brings a chill. It's probably time we take her in.
Hmm. Or...
And I just turned it up! Oh my god!
Hey dude, the game's quiet. Did you say that so I would turn it up during the fucking lightning
part, dude? Oh my god, I'm so s- that scared the shit out of me. That was kind of weird.
I can't get this thing off.
I must find some way to stop that thing before it threatens my people. Of course I'll help.
Hearing a simple, confident pledge of support from you would be what puts me at ease.
You guys having a good time? You guys- one in the chat, you having a good time?
I'm seeing- I'm seeing way too many ones. I'm seeing way too many yeses.
That's a lot of yeses. I'm not all right with that.
You guys having a good time right now? I'm not into that.
I'm so fucked up right now, I don't know why. Something's in the water today.
I need to get the sand seal. The lookout post isn't too far from town,
but you should take a sand seal there and get some practice in that way.
Okay, get a sand seal. I like that water.
Oh, another thing about Puss in Boots. Did anybody else feel this way? I know
Holly and I talked about it, but I- so much stuff in that movie just looked so delicious.
This looks like a popsicle. Like a glowing popsicle.
This dude's on another planet right now.
I promise I didn't just do a bong rip, but it's pretty suspicious considering the next thing I
said. I wanted to eat a majority of the Puss in Boots movie. That's very- I understand that that
sounded a little- a little suspicious. I need to cook. I need to- where can I cook?
I have a lot of ingredients. I'm not going to the divine beast until I cook. Where can I cook?
There's gotta be a stove around here somewhere, right? Why is it- there's gotta be a stove.
Every town has a stove. Is it near the stairs? Ow! That hurt a lot. I hope that wasn't too bad.
I don't know. Where is it? Near the stairs, you said? I scratched my nose and I scraped
the microphone accidentally. Sorry about that. What? Phrasing. Very poor choice of words.
What? This fucking bong fell over. I can't drink this, so. Can I cook here? You mean these stairs?
Left. I got it. Okay. What do I have for ingredients? And I kind of have- I forget how
this whole system works. Because you can make potions, but you can make food too. You don't
want to combine both of them. So, I can do a mushroom. I can do banana. What if I cook a
banana? Okay, there we go. What does cooking a banana do? Attack power boost? Okay, so that's
what that does. So, attack power. So you can only do one buff, so don't combine buffs. That's gonna
be pretty sick. There we go. Replenishes your stamina when cooked into a dish. So, this is a
stamina replenish. This is attack power. Banana is also attack power. Just go all in. Sort your
inventory. Any other attack power? I think this is all right. Yeah, I'll cook these. Maybe this
will be a big one. Whoa. High level attack power boost for four minutes. Good. One truffle. Maybe
a steak. Just one truffle. One truffle only. Ah, that's right. It's a full recovery. So,
I'm just gonna make a few of these. What about truffle and salt? Do I have salt? It's gonna be
a salty truffle. Why was that one worse? Too much salt. Okay, withstand cold. Probably four of these
and then something else too. Something like this. Yeah, it's gonna be a lot. 10 minutes of low level
cold. Not anymore. Electricity. Bitter cold. And then, how about a nutty seasoning? That's almost 11
minutes of mid-level cold. Okay. Electricity protection. Some salt. Another one of those.
And seasoning. Why do you sound like a wow streamer? I don't know. Oh, that's a huge raid.
Big raid. Massive raid. Welcome, everybody. That is a conner. That is a sea dog raid. Welcome,
everybody. Playing some Breath of the Wild. Thanks for the raid. Yeah, I turn the face cam on to say
hello. Sometimes. They get face cam and not us. You got it. I did it like three times already.
Oh, the moderation settings. Right. You can't say the. You can't say is. You can't say smelly.
You can't say sucks. You can't say he sucks. There's a lot of weird shit today. Just to let
you know. So be aware of that. There are some, there are a lot of things you just can't say today.
The mods are just having a chuckle. There's a hair on that. But anyways, hi. Thanks, conner.
If you don't follow Sea Dog, please do it. He's a gentleman. Scholar. Wonderful, wonderful man. Go
follow. You got nice hair. Hey, thanks. Temperance and chastity. We don't talk about that when new
people show up. This is stamina. Stamina. Is there any more stamina stuff? Oh, that is electricity.
I didn't, I didn't, I didn't see it as food. Defense. More hearts. All right, we're doing stamina.
Give me double meat and two salts. Let's go. This is attack power and then just salt. Whatever. Why
not? Yeah, for all conner, for all your viewers, we were talking about how all the seven deadly
sins get a ton of screen time, but the seven virtues do not. We went over it. Humility. Chastity.
Temperance. Patience. Diligence. What are the other two? Charity. Sin. Dude, they're all gone by now.
No! Who banned that person for fucking 10 minutes? Mid-level electricity. Very good. I think I'm
going to need those, so good. Kind of out of ingredients. What? I would love to hear your
opinion on macaroni and cheese. This person's name is macaroni and cheese or something.
Um, what do you mean? Do I like it? I mean, I love macaroni and cheese. It's great. All right,
I'm good for now. My opinion's on macaroni and cheese. It depends on who's making it.
I've had some runny ass macaroni and cheese before. That was awful. I've had some really,
really good macaroni and cheese. That was creamy. Delicious. Do you want me to tell you what my,
you want to know my absolute number one mac and cheese? Is that what it is?
Um, okay. My favorite mac and cheese. You're not going to say Velveeta, are you? No.
What's happening to me? Is it cold or? It's cold. Okay. Too cold? How cold is it? I'm still this
cold? Can I just make some shit? I could have eaten that stealth food. Um, these are all too
valuable. This is too valuable. All right. Hold the fire sword. Holy shit, that actually works.
I thought you were lying. Um, yeah, macaroni and cheese is great. I'm a big fan of a multiple
cheese macaroni and cheese. I'm, I don't know if I would put breadcrumbs on the top, although I
have to be in the mood for it. I do not like mac and cheese that is runny. If it's runny,
get it away from me. The cheese needs to be sticking to the noodles. I don't want it running
off. And they also, I don't want that much cheese. Some people load it up with, oh, gooey, gooey,
cheesy, right? No, no, no. It's like too much. It's kind of gross. Don't overdo it with cheese.
It's a little too much. I like it light. I don't want to have a heart attack after I take a bite.
Oh damn. Golden bow. Is this yours? What do I get rid of? I don't know what to get rid of.
One of the duplex bows. What cheeses though? Uh, cheddar, maybe Havarti. Swiss cheese can work
there. Pepper Jack works there. Honestly, you could just do whatever you want. Most cheeses
go pretty well together, except no goat cheese. Disgusting. I'll put a lookup post. Okay. What
about cottage cheese? Cottage cheese is fine. Ooh, that's really cool looking. Um, cottage cheese
with a little bit of cracked, just pepper all over it is pretty good. Gouda is really good.
I actually am not a big fan of brie. I don't like soft cheeses really. Cottage cheese and pepper.
Try it one day, then come back and report. All right, we're doing another divine beast. Let's go.
The sand seals to get in really close to that thing. I'll take the lead. I like feta, but feta
is not goat cheese. Shoot at its feet with bomb arrows. Not. It can be. I know the difference.
Staying close to not get shocked. Retreat. Not. She said, wait, here's not many. You gave me 20.
Feta is sheep. So I'm sorry, everybody. Feta is not goat. It is sheep. All right. Stop asking me
my opinions of cheeses. You're trying to derail the whole day. I need bomb arrows. I should
probably put the other bow on. I built a computer one time like 10 years ago and it made that sound
when I turned it on and I turned it off, unplugged it from the wall and cried. It's a true story.
It was a little longer than 10. It was probably, I don't know how long ago, maybe 15,
more than 15 years ago. I don't remember. Why would you cry? Because I don't know,
I like saved up a bunch of money and I'm going to build a computer and I put it all together
and it was just like, and it took like all day. It just was like overwhelming fucking sadness.
I couldn't help it. I was just like, this sucks. I'm fucking so sad. Yeah. Who wouldn't cry for
that? Are you kidding me? That's what a disaster of a day. I want to take out a different bow
because this shoots multiple arrows. What's going on? What's going on? Wait, there's a shrine. Why
am I having so much trouble controlling this? It only shoots. Oh, okay. Is that what I want though?
How do I put this down? Okay. You play games like a Midwestern mother. Okay. Let's go. That was
really fast. Wow. That was really good. So good. Midwestern mother, huh? But why don't you just go
upstairs and go to bed? Don't you know? I will not be hearing any more of that. I will not be hearing
any more of that. Fortunately, no choice but to entrust the rest to you. It's Canadian. Oh boy.
Yeah, you betcha. That's not Canadian. It's not, it's not Canadian. That's mid, it's Midwest.
I'm having trouble because all I can hear is the audio. That's Minnesota, Wisconsin. That's
Northern Midwest. It's still the Midwest. Minnesota. It's Northern Midwestern. I can't say
Northern Midwestern and say it's not Midwestern. Soda. What happened? Oh no, this looks tricky.
Somebody said this is the hardest divine beast. Okay. I think I held on to this. I need more
weapons. So badly. I need more weapon slots. Get rid of this torch. Don't you have to destroy
this stuff? Shoot the eye or something, right? Okay. So where are we going? This level is going
to make me puke. Oh man. I don't like that. The background moving like that. Okay. Electricity
field. Maybe. No, you guys have been good. Put it on. One. I need a map. What's with the horror
music? It's like scary music. Ancient battle acts. I'll take it. What was that? This brightness is
so bright. Well, they want me to have 50 of these for some reason. So I guess I'll hold on to it.
Wait, can I shoot through here? I don't think so. Nope. Whoa. I climbed this. Go down there.
Let's check the other side. I lost the weapon, but whatever. All right. What about here?
Can you stop mashing the piano, please? Stop going like this on the piano where you just take all
your fingers and just smoosh down. That gets you thrown out. That gets you thrown out, by the way.
I don't care where you are. I don't know if you're in a house. If you do that, you're getting thrown
out. This is going to happen. Just don't do that. You could be having a very, very normal conversation
hanging out. Oh, hey. Oh, you got a piano? Oh, cool. We open it up.
Someone's coming in that room and going, get out. Get out. I don't, I don't want you here anymore.
Get out. No, it's time for you to go home. All right. The thing obviously spins, but how do I spin
it? I had to get up there, up there. Oh, I can go that way. No, I can't. I think I can make it from
here. Let's try it. Okay. Dude, what the hell is going on here? I got to get over there.
Oh, fuck. I went the wrong way. Did I? Oh, okay. Good to know. Ancient spring. I can't believe bald
coin is still an emo. I never deleted it. I could have gone out that way, but whatever. No, no.
The most that emo has been used in five years. Oh, now I get the map. Okay. Oh, I have to,
I can rotate it. So the middle is a cylinder that spins. Good work getting the map of the divine.
The terminals that control are noted by a series of glowing points on your map.
Take no borders back by activating all of the terminal. You're ready for this. Who's talking
to me? Okay. Rotate 90 degrees. Execute. Right. I can do this one. All right. Do I have to do all
before this one? I can do this one now. Now this is the last one. Okay. So this one, um,
eh, shit. Whoa. This actually, wait a minute. Okay. Where is this one? It's right there. Okay.
Here we go. All right. Let's go. There are four terminals remaining. I'm counting on you.
I probably get this one right now. What about this one? Can I pull it?
Shit. Should have froze it. Freeze time. God damn it. All right. This is like fucked up out here.
I forgot I got that one already. It's blue. How do I spin that around?
Okay. How do I spin this? There's electricity up here, which I'm imagining
if the government make it go across the whole thing. I don't know. What are you doing all like
this for? What did that do? I, you know what happened. I don't even need to tell you what
happened. Okay. So I want to go up there or maybe down. Maybe I tried this way. I'm just going to,
okay. I got to, I got to explore now that I know that I can do that. Damn it. How do I get in here?
There's a hole in the top. All right. All right. All right. All right. I know what to do.
There's a hole at the top. I'm going to get up and through the hole. Maybe I should go this way.
What does this do? This needs to be electrified. All right. Okay. Well, at least I figured out what
it wants me to do. Electrify this to get the last one. I'm up here, but this is all the way up.
Can I climb from here? I have no idea. I have no freaking idea. The only thing I can think of
is to be in that hole. What happens if I do it again? Where does this hole go?
Can I stand on top of it or something? All right. I got to get out there.
Where's the hole? I'm going to do something really stupid. Give me a second.
That was stupid. It was really stupid. I just heard that right here.
Are there any moving parts? Can I stand on that or something? Hold on. No, I can't. Can I climb up?
Where does this other hole go? This thing is powered right now. Okay. I think my chat just
crashed. And my chat crashed. Am I still live? I'm just going to act like I am. Wait, the stream
turned off? That's weird. I don't have any drop frames or anything. Now I can see you. Maybe I
can't. My Twitch is fucked up. My internet's fine. I have no access to chat. Well, come on.
Come on. Come on. Where are you? We heard you make a puke sound and then it stopped.
Yeah, I got no drop frames. That's weird. What are you doing? What are you doing? What's going on?
What the hell? Did I- I fucking bumped it. Give me the elevator. What? Oh, no. My chat's back.
Okay. Everyone's saying not like this. Did I do it in the wrong order? I got it. It's right here.
We're good. Jump right now to prove you have free will. Time that person up for 20 minutes. Wait,
the stream crashed again. Maybe Twitch is having problems. All right. There are- All right. I got
to get up there. All right. That's that. Whoa. Should we pin a message saying refresh? Maybe
for a few minutes. Yeah. I think they see it now. All right. Good. All right. Only two more. The
last two are up. One is across that way. Let me see. So on the other side, on the same level
that I'm at right now. What the hell is this? I need electricity in there. Oh shit. Really?
What had happened? What just happened? Wait, what? I- Oh, I spun it accidentally. We're good.
We are good. We need to power it again. Anything over here? Get rid of that. Okay. I need to get
power there. Radishes? Sounds good. Okay. There's a bunch of shit this way. I did that. All right.
What about over here? I gotta be very careful. Fuck. Did you just hear what I said? I said be
careful and you just didn't do it correctly. Now what? I just slipped right off. It was- I don't
think you can walk on that. Where's the eye? Is there no eye on this one? I'm kind of screwed,
aren't I? Shit. What is going on? What is this? Is electricity here? What? This shit's all blocked
up now. Okay. I need to go up. Where am I looking right now? It's up there. I think I fucked
everything up. I was on the right track. I think I screwed it all up though. Damn it. Now I gotta
remember how to do this all again. I gotta turn the power back on, right? I don't know. I don't
know. That. Look at that. How do I get over there? Come on. How do I get in here? Come on, dude.
Really? I gotta drop from there. Hurry up. You can do them at the same time. Do I do them at
the same time or something? I wonder if that works. Okay. Power is back on. I can go that way
again. This shit is right next to me. Right here. How do I get up there? I'm gonna go back around.
I'm gonna go up and see if I can figure out how to get down there. Maybe I should go up there
through that hole. Where would that take me? Oh my god. Damn it, dude. I'm about to put a
fucking hole through my monitor. Sorry, I'm playing Breath of the Wild. Okay. Get out of the way. I
want to look. If I go up, I got an idea. I'm just gonna look. I just want to look. Don't press it.
I wish I could just rebind the keys because B is just A and A is B. Just let me rebind the
keys for the love of god. It's like three lines of code and I'm making that up because I'm
frustrated but I'm just saying it could be. I'm going all the way up. I'm going through that
fucking hole. No, I'm not. I don't know. I'm afraid to jump over here because I don't think
I'll make it. Look at that shit right there. What does this want to power? How do I get that to be
turned on? I turned that on. Can I pull it out? Can I throw a bomb at it? It needs to be powered
by something. I just don't know. I just don't get it. I mean, I kind of get it but how do I get on
the other side of this? I need to go from this direction to blow up the shit that's over there
and then power that somehow. Okay. This one is the grate that you have to fall into but I have to get
over there first. I have to get on this side of the beast. I'm fucking going for it. There's no eye.
Damn it. There's a hole there. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. How do I get? Okay, that's now- this
is now powered. Nobody move. Where is that? That's below- that's below me. Where is that elevator?
Where's that elevator? Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Am I- can I- am I in trouble here?
All right, that elevator is working and then down here and then- I don't know. So I just have to go
to the main room? Just go back to the main room and is there an elevator there now? I can't get out
this way. I'm seeing a lot of no's. Fuck. Up here first maybe? Up here through the thingy and then
down. Holy shit, it says to blame the stream for 20 minutes. The stream really did go down. Okay,
now how do I get this to go up? I just accidentally stepped off it. I didn't know- I didn't know there
was another lever. Another layer. I did not know this went up twice. That wasn't telegraphed
properly. That wasn't telegraphed properly. It was improperly telegraphed for sure. If I had known
this went up a second time I would have been fine. I should be close now. All right, what is that for?
I'm terrified to leave this area without knowing what that is. What does this do? So what? What the
hell does that even help me with? So I just- maybe I should just drop down. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let me go back and look at this. I think I can get the one in the crate because isn't it right
down here? What the hell is that? It's like a green ball. What on earth? What are you doing to
me here? Okay, what should I do with the ball? This is the back. Maybe there's something down
here. Can I do this? Then this way? I don't want to screw this up because I don't think this is
right. I think I need to get the ball. Do I need to bring the ball with me? I'm terrified to go
anywhere. That's what I was thinking. Give me this. Give me this. I fucking want it. I'll take it.
Dude, come on. Like, you know what I'm fucking aiming at. Like, fucking wet sock.
Yet, what is going on with- what is happening right now? I feel like I'm playing in quicksand.
All right, now where the hell do I bring this fucking thing? Down here, right?
No? This is wrong? That's wrong. Why did I pick this up? Bring it back up to the top, maybe?
What needed power that I couldn't- was the only thing I can think of.
What- what do I need to do with this up top? Is there actually something out here? I have no
fucking idea. This place is fucking crazy. Um, I don't- I don't remember what I'm- what I'm
supposed to be powering with this. I'm about to let you out so you can help. Let him out. Let him
out. Let him out. Let him out. What the hell do I do with this thing? You're so close. I know, but
one little mistake puts me back to the beginning. And I don't want to do that. You can rebind your
keys. That's the first thing everyone's screaming. Go rebind your keys. April fools. Do I take this-
I'm just going to carry this with me everywhere I go for now, for a minute. What- there's another
one right here. Why do they- why are there two of these fucking cube balls? Why are they two of- I
just brought it up to hang out with his fucking sibling. Should I take them both? I'm bringing
them both downstairs. They're both coming with me. No help. Just help me. Two balls of Bradley.
Can I take it off of this? Oh wait, okay. So it doesn't need to stay on there. I did it finally.
Need to go back and beat Lou three times at the Fox and Geese game. This one was fucked. I don't
like this one. This one was fucked up. I don't like this one at all. I don't like this one at all.
How do I get this out of the way? Power this and then open it. How do I open this? Don't crush me.
How do I drop down here? You can't get in from here? No bro, you gotta get swished.
Oh dude, I have to go out the side holes. I feel like I tried that and I couldn't get it to work.
So I'll just just go right down to the bottom, like of the actual level. Just get out of here
and go to the- you don't need the balls anymore? Okay, so it's over here. Side holes. Maybe- can
I go up? I have no freaking idea and I just said a bad word. Okay, so if I go out there I can get it.
I got it. I got it. Hold on, let me spin the whole entire video game like three more times.
Get me out of here. Get me out of here.
I know where it is. System settings, controller settings, change button mapping.
I'll take a break and do it. All right, now I'm just gonna get to the front.
How's temperance going? We're going full wrath. This is the hardest boss you have fucked. There's
too many buttons in this game. There are too many buttons in this game. There are like 60 different
inputs in Breath of the Wild. There are too many buttons. There are far too many buttons. There's
so many fucking buttons. Relax. That's not what I wanted to do. I wanted to jump. This might be
the most inputs of any game I've ever played. There's like every button has a second context
rule button. There's like 40 inputs in Breath of the Wild. Good luck.
Good thing. Good thing I just used the divine strength on shooting myself with a bomb arrow.
Okay. Where the hell am I? Where the hell am I? Why did it put me all the way down here?
Excuse me. How do I get back up there? I gotta redo the whole thing. No, I don't. It was right
there. I'm about to eat my controller about how much I hate this part of the game. This
whole Gerudo Valley. If I do a second playthrough, I'm not coming over here ever again.
Where? Oh my god. What just happened? No, we're good. How come you don't drink beer on stream?
What are you talking about? Ah, let me get like a nice, like a nice cold beer. Oh, it goes up.
Okay, what? Should I use for weapon? Wait, my fucking album is full. God damn it, man.
Is this electricity? What kind of damage is he doing? Electricity? Oh, I do have- wait,
do I have the- why am I not wearing a helmet? What the hell happened? It's fire. Thunderblight.
I didn't read his name. He just fell off the whole game. This world was so long. All right,
do the- okay, so it's one, two, three, bang. So it's one, two, three, back. One, two, three,
back. Okay, faster than I thought. How did I not dodge that? Parry? What? I don't- it's been four
months, guys. What's the parry button? It's A with the shield out. A? I just did it. God. I'm
doing it my way. My shield's not out anymore. Jesus. All right, let's go. Oh shit, I need to
have a- it's gonna be a one-hander weapon. Do I have another one-hander?
Royal Claymore. Why not? Can I take my shield out without- I don't know how to do that. Do I
have to have a one-hander? Or can I pull the shield out somehow? No, okay. I'm gonna have to
backflip over it then. Phase two. I don't even know where he is. Where is he? Put this fucking
camera down. Oh my god. Hold left bumper and then up and then hold left and then A and then right
bumper. Oh my goodness. Look what I have. What do I do with this? Do I just stick it in his face?
What do I do with it? Did I get him? You're reading chat? Sometimes. Very rarely. Um,
oh heck. I can't be on the ground. Yeah, rarely. Like when I'm fighting a boss. I just freaked out.
I thought he was jumping at me. Bro, you should get a ring light. I don't want- I have it. It's
just not turned on. All right, leave me alone. What? I can freeze him? Oh my god, dude. Oh my god.
Why would that help though? This doesn't hurt him. Put the ring light around your neck.
It does? What do you mean that one was a dud? I have to do it before he strikes it?
I don't even know where the hell this guy is. Fuck you. Dude, how many times does he swing?
Fuck. What the hell? I don't care about the low level stealth boost. I need the fucking hearts.
Where's my weapon? No, I'm- why don't you fucking strike some lightning down here?
Lady, I don't know who you're talking about. What direction is he swinging? You drop the
fucking weapon every time he hits you? Stop attacking. That shit is broken. Oh my god,
the damage is unreal. I just have to eat everything. Die. Yeah. That was really hard.
That was crazy. My eyes hurt. Yeah, that was cleric beast. What did I say? Delete this whole
part of the game. Heart container. It was genuinely a skill issue. That's all a skill issue. Two more
to the master sword. I'm looking forward to that. I was wearing metal armor. I lost so many points
believing tonight. I'm sorry.
Please accept this gift, which has come to be known as herbosa's fury. It will no doubt be of
use to you. That like, you don't hear that ever. Both you and the princess. I know you have suffered
much regarding what happened to us champions, but this is how things had to happen. No one need
carry blame. So please make it clear. So she understands that. Tell her to shed any worries
and let her know. You take good care of the princess. Oh, and also take good care of him.
Yeah. Bro, you're not even wearing. I was wearing metal armor and dying in like two hits.
I feel like every single thing that I could have done wrong, I did wrong during the last hour,
like everything to the things, the items I was wearing. So the strategy I had, I feel like I
was just doing every single possible thing incorrect for like 45 straight minutes. You did
it your way. Yeah. We'll take a break. Don't worry. It's still a 90. It's still an A. Don't worry.
I love people concerned. End of the stream. No, no, no. We'll go for like another hour.
Legend of the Gerudo celebrated over ages and you who were named to honor you are a legend as well.
Isn't that right? Yeah. Stream crashed halfway through defeat from a century.
It was written that calamity Gannon once adopted the form and that will make this victory all the
more satisfying. How much harder is the game if you just go right again? It's just like impossible.
We'll be up to link to keep Ganon occupied and is going to be so delicious.
Yes. You would cry on master mode. I cry on normal difficulty. I would probably agree with you.
I cried when I fried my PC. I cried at everything.
I cried in the end of Puss in Boots. I didn't even read what that said.
That was incredibly important and I have no idea what it was.
I cried at the end of Ghostbusters Afterlife. Guys, I cry at everything, okay?
Hold Y. Whoa. Hold it for longer.
And what scenario would you ever be able to hold it for this long?
Damn. Oh, okay. Hold on. It does 500 damage. Damn. Make sure it starts to recharge.
It's a good idea. Very cool. Oh, I can do that. It's gone forever. No, they recharge.
I'm going to take a quick break. Let's complete this quest and then I'm going to take a break.
We'll go for like another hour or two. Naboris is no longer a threat to the town.
I'm still worried about the larger threat to Hyrule, but at least my people won't be
troubled by Naboris anymore. Ooh. Two trinkets? Priceless treasures of the Gerudo people.
Only right that you should have them. Okay. Cool weapon. Wow. Simitar of the Seven. Nice.
Daybreaker. Very cool. Whoa. What can I get rid of? Why do I even have that?
Very cool. All right. So now where do I go now? Up here? Can I take that helmet?
Can I have it? Yeah, I want it. Yes. Lend it to me. Oh, I have to do side quests. So what's
going on here? Legendary rabbit trial. Look at the side stuff. Okay. So I could go up here.
I think I'm going to go here and go up, but I'll be right back. I'm going to take a first break.
I'll be back in maybe five minutes. See you in a sec. He was crying off camera.
Yeah. Remember, do you like Big Chungus? Big Chungus was in the Space Jam movie
for a half a second. Somebody told me that and then I thought they made it up.
I was like, there's no way that Big Chungus is in the movie. And Big Chungus is in the movie.
Did you cry when Big Chungus showed up? Yeah, I was so fucking moved. Like they had,
you know, it was very moving. What's this? Oh, it's this thing. Okay. I need my horse back.
Where is Frank too? Where are you Frank too? Over here. I need to go get Frank too. Thanks
for your opinion on Big Chungus. You're welcome. Put some armor on. All right. Let's actually go.
Where you at? What do you got? Okay. I'll take three of these. These are cheap. 10 rupees. That's
it? This is really cheap. Pretty cool. Okay. Can I teleport with the horse? Come on. We can't go
together. Well, looks like we're walking. Go to any stable and get it from there. I don't want
to walk all the way. Let's try this again. There's a saddle that lets you call your horse from
anywhere. Pretty good. Okay. I'll get it eventually. Wait, we can't go over here anyways. Wait,
am I going the wrong way? Why was that turned around? That was weird. I thought I was going
the right way. No horse in the desert. Yeah, that's right.
Vinny beats Jerma's time. Vinny beats Jerma's time. What is this? Vinny beats Jerma's time.
Playing Resident Evil 4. Dude, my connection to Twitch is like awful for some reason. Okay. Let's
see it. Bro, come on. What? Dude, how? How would you do that in two turns? No way. Wow.
You can actually do it in two spins. Hey, I ain't the only one that has trouble with this. I know
for a fact that there are a shitload of other people that just kind of, it's like, it's one
of those scenarios where if you do it wrong, yeah, you can do it in two turns. But if you don't do
it immediately correct, you fuck the whole thing up for like 10 minutes. Yeah. It's a shitload of
us. It's a shitload of us. And that's fine. That's so funny though. I did it in two turns by accident.
That's so funny. Chat told him you took forever. It's all right. That's so funny though.
Two turns. You would have taken forever. I did take forever. That already happened.
It's a reading chat. I'm not gonna buy this. Get this out of the way. Get the fuck away from me
and my horse. All right. Let's go. Made it. All bending. It's really pretty. I'm glad you're doing
no cam chill streams again. Yeah. I don't know if I would, I don't know if I would qualify this one
as that though. I feel like this got a little unhinged in the last couple hours I want to say,
but I agree with you. I do agree with you.
Nice. Deep freeze. What's up here? I think I already, yeah, I already was here. Oh, we good.
Imagine seeing that. If you're like, whoa, shit, that person almost just fell off.
That person's drunk up here. Not this girl. I'm talking about me.
He thinks I'm going to forgive him for this. He's got another thing coming.
I think I did most of everything here. Unless like, I don't know what's up there.
Play all the Final Fantasies. Nah, I'm really not into those games. Try to go up there.
Honestly, the only turn-based RPGs I really ever liked were the Chrono series. Chrono Trigger,
Mario RPG, Grenade. You okay? Oh, lift. By the goddess, I'm grateful.
Should I go back to that stable? Maybe I can collect a reward or something.
Just threw a barrel at me.
Play Roblox. April 5th, we're having a birthday party for, I don't even know who it is. I just
know we're having one. Are you coming to the birthday party? You're invited. It's on twitch.tv
slash germa985. That's what I heard. What the fuck? Oh my God. Don't do that. I thought there
was somebody in the room with me or something. I don't know. I just felt like somebody was in
my house or something. You know what I mean? Like someone's in my room. It's just jarring.
I'm just sitting here hanging out playing. She's like, hey, just want to let you know.
I'll stick with this. It's a long way. Oh my God. It was so scary. Hey, can I have a Minecraft
themed birthday party? It's May 13th. No, sorry. We're going to get through everybody's birthday
on the 5th. That's a chest. What about Splatoon birthday? No, we'll do a Roblox birthday on the
5th. So what was in here? A lot of work for five fire arrows. I don't want to go too far.
Oh my God. What am I doing? What is going on right now? I didn't want to use my weapons
because I've been breaking them. I broke like three in the last 10 minutes and I was afraid
to use them. What is going on with my brain at the moment? I don't want to break all my cool
weapons. So I'm like, I'll pick up the rock. And then that's all I remembered. I just woke
up a second ago. That's all I remember. How do they not see me? What? They didn't see me.
What just happened? I had an ice arrow. What? Okay. That was so confusing. Oh,
all right. Get the, get the bow out. Hold left, press right. Let go. I wish I could put arrows
on without having to be zoom the fucking. It's annoying. Let's go. I want to put a weapon on.
What the hell? I got a lot of health. Jesus. What do I get for this? Ooh.
Something like that came from a bathroom.
Give me my trinket. Change the bow. Did I not kill everything? Usually you kill everything and
something spawns, right? Hmm. Somebody still alive? No chest. Okay. Let's go. All right.
Just need to go this way. Hey, who are you? Okay. My partner, that's to say my horse ran off. And
hey, since I've been stranded here, I'll need a horse to continue my travels. I need a, if I
just had a horse. Does he want my horse? No. I don't, the brightness I don't think is the,
nothing on OBS. I don't have any filters on or anything. It's a radiant glow. This is not normal.
This is what I see through my screen too. HDR on. I don't think so.
It's like I just went through the windshield of a car.
Oh, where? Holy shit. I can't see anything. Oh my God. Is it over here? This is kind of ridiculous.
Is it in your game settings? I don't think so guys. No, I don't think so. There it is.
Oh my God. What about your, you need to buy a new switch. Hold on. What? Let me look at my,
you tell me go to my switch settings. Hold on a second. Screen brightness. Screen brightness
cannot be set while connected to a TV. Look, I can't change it. That's kind of weird. I don't
think I can do anything else with this. That's the switch. That's the actual switch brightness.
The screen on handheld mode. That's funny. No, it's not OBS because I have to capture the
console. Let me go to like my actual property properties. Let me see. Hold on. What if I do this?
That fix it? Is it better? Maybe a little. Yeah, I dropped my, I went into the actual capture card
and I dropped the brightness. It still is kind of, still is kind of crazy though. 13k versus 17k
earlier. Oh, my stream crashed. A lot of times people just don't come back. How much did I get
it? All right. What do we do here? On the move. We'll turn this on for now.
Am I, you're going to want to see my reactions when I fuck it up. Oh, wait, wait, wait, time.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Are we doing another one of these?
10 minutes? Are we doing a bet here? Okay. Well, I beat this in 10 minutes. By the way, I will,
when you say go, I will wait 10 seconds. I think that's fair. Ready? Three, two, one. Oh,
I'm deaf. There's no way I don't do this. All the doubters. I'm sorry, but you're about to get
wiped out. Let's get going. Fuck. Son of a gun. What are you? Wait, that actually worked.
Whoa. Whoa. That's coming from this side. It's coming from this side.
What do I have for time? Time check? I have five minutes. I'm just going to get up and just start
Fortnite dancing. Hey, all the believers from earlier that lost everything. Hope you got it
all back. Sorry doubters. The way it is. These are my favorite part about the whole game.
I have six orbs now, which lost everything. Why do you look so fucked up? Just chilling, man.
Very cool. So let's keep going over here. Oh, there's a little dungeon over here.
These need to explode. Get out of the way. Somebody move. I thought I was going to drop
the lantern. Get out of here. Oh, holy shit. What is hurting me so much right now?
I'm taking like times five damage. How am I getting hurt so bad? Out of food almost. Fire
burning you. How about now? Yes. The chest. Let's replace this one. Or is it time to get rid of one
of these? What do you think? Maybe get rid of the lizard shield. This thing just seems way better.
Oh, let's light this thing up. Jerma TWT thinks you look handsome today.
Oh, Twitter. T. I was like, what is T? I thought that was like some like imposter channel or
something like, oh, hey, Jerma TWT streaming right now. And I said, you look pretty good today.
What? Oh, my God. I'm so sorry. Come back. Come back. Come back. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
I'm so sorry. Going through his bones. Guys, he's going through his bones. That hurt so bad.
That was I need to relax. Geez, man. And spoils. No. I have something hidden in here.
Can you just admit that you hate this game? I don't think that's accurate.
How can you use lawyer talk? I think I'm just 40. I need to get some food now. I don't want
to waste all this good shit I have. A lot of this is high level, high level, mid level.
I need a town or something. Hmm. What should I eat? Whatever. I can cook more food. It's fine.
Canyon. Shrine. Which way? In the water? Jerma, do you have anything to say to your haters?
No. Oh, don't do this to us. No one's under any obligation to like this channel.
If you don't like this channel, then all right. It's on you. It's up to you.
And this is it. I'm so glad I had that. That's weird. I mean, if you go, hey,
this guy's a dickhead and then leave, then all right. Whatever. Oh dear. Hold on. Where's the shrine?
Under the bridge? There it is. Oh no. Wait, I think I'm okay.
Okay. Oh, pretty good cartoon laugh. That was a pretty good cartoon car.
I'm just running around with a bowl of cereal in my hands. It's like just children running after
me and I have a bowl of cereal running around. You guys want to bet? How are you guys doing on
the betting? No, it's a test of strength. Never mind. I'll do this pretty quickly.
They're magically delicious. Yeah. I don't even give them a chance.
I have some junk that I can get rid of, don't I? This is crap. It's in here. I should probably go
upgrade the slate, right? Can people still not write the word the? We cannot. Oh, well, you guys
have had to communicate in symbols all day anyways. This is a really funny prank. It's so funny. I'm
laughing. All right. You can take it off. Give them their freedom back. Give them all the words
back. Very nice. All right. I need to get back up. I could probably just go from here and just
jump off. What was the point of that? Because it's the funny day and I wanted to make chatting
unbearable, I guess, for some reason. I don't know. Okay. So how do I get back there quickly
I think that's just you being a prick. Is it really though? It's for like four hours one day
in April. Where's the horse? Yeah, but you were a prick for four hours. I guess that doesn't change
the fact that I was a dick for a few hours. That's right. Yeah, that's true. I don't think I want to
fight this. I'll be honest. I didn't even know it was still on. I was too busy being angry at Zelda.
Holy shit. Oh my goodness. I just annihilated this guy. This theme song didn't even get to play.
Can't hear any more of these. Ooh, wait a minute.
Wait, what was the bow? I don't know if I want to drop. Should I drop the golden bow?
I don't think anything I want to drop here. Soldier's bow. Nah. Nah, we're good.
I'm not picking up the signal anymore. Where is it? I need a tower.
The tower over there. That's really close to Ganon though. Ooh, a stable.
No, I want Frank too to be teleported here. Yeah, I'll get food too. But first I want to do this
shrine because then I will have the right amount of hearts to get the master sword. That's correct,
right? There it is. Yellow hearts don't count. How many do I have? 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10,
11, 12. I'll have 13 because I have eight orbs. I'll have 13 after this. Make it look like a rave
is going on in your cam. I don't have any lights in here that could do that. I'm sorry to say.
Are we voting? 10 minutes. Let's see if I can do it. I'll pause it so I'm not looking. Timer is
ready. In three, two, one. All right. First of all, something to do with this, I bet. Okay.
Ball up there. Hmm. What is this? Oh, shit. Hold on. Ball. Ball goes over here. Could have worked.
Why would I be able to do that though? Should I climb? Wait, can I get up here? I thought it was
too shallow. Okay. I know what to do. Fuck. It goes the other way. It goes the other way.
I need arrows, dude. How am I supposed to do this without arrows? How do I get that back?
Flip it again. So now I throw it in here. Fuck you. God damn it. I wasn't close enough.
How was I not close enough? Now how am I going to get this out of the water?
There. Okay. Sorry. It wasn't. Oh my God. This game. Let me out of here. Okay. So what? Me, me.
Are you sure this is like a bomb or something? How do I get that to move?
I can't select it or I can't do anything with it. Magnetism doesn't do anything.
Stasis doesn't do anything. Whatever it is. I keep forgetting I own these things. I really do.
Does that not do anything? That doesn't do it. Right here. Dude, I'm stumped. I don't get it.
What? What does it want me to do? What? What just happened? Wait, it turns the whole thing.
Wait a minute. Hold on. What? What? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Turn it back around.
I'm so confused right now. I don't have any arrows. I don't want to shoot an ancient arrow.
What if I get arrows? This thing's an ancient arrow. It's worth a lot.
Okay. Well then, can I? There's nothing at the end of this. I'm dead. I'm dead. GG doubters. I
physically can't get over there again because I don't have any arrows. Are you kidding me?
That can't be right. That can't be right. It actually can't be. All right. Now what?
Open. I have to. Oh, oh, oh, oh my God. I didn't even know that was a keyhole, guys.
I didn't know that was a keyhole. I didn't know that was a keyhole. Oh my God. I didn't. I
honestly just did not. That was not a keyhole to me. Oh my goodness. You got to be kidding me.
Okay. I picked up so many keys in Resident Evil 4 that they just became like,
oh, whatever. You got a key. Who cares? I still don't know what to do. I jump from here over.
Okay. I have to jump over. Okay. All right. That's fun. DJ, congratulations doubters.
You definitely won. GG doubters. Because I still can't piece together what the hell I do here.
Why am I hitting the ceiling, by the way? I shouldn't be. It's not that simple, right?
Where am I going? Where's the goal? I actually don't know where the goal of this shrine is.
It's not up top, right? Oh my God. It's over there. What is the point of that fucking thing?
What is the point of that square? Why is that there? It doesn't even help me at all. I'm done
with this fucking place. It didn't work. It doesn't even help me though. I don't fucking
understand this. I don't get it. It only launches you so far. Oh, I don't get it. How do I go higher
up over the edge? Wait, does this move everything? Yeah, but I don't have any arrows. How am I
supposed to do this without arrows? Throw a bomb over there? Can I even reach it? Come on, man.
That's just like that's so particular. That's so particular. That's particular. That was a 7x
payout. You just made a doubter out of me. Yeah, but next time you're going to bet against me and
I'm going to win and you're going to feel just as bad. All right, let's go upgrade and then I'm
going to pull that sword out of the ground. Is there one of those little shrines in here? What's
going on? No, the arrow would have made it easier. You can't probably drop because the words if and
though were banned. No, they were banned for hours before the stream crashed.
I'm sorry. I think that's just so stupid. What a strict community. Oh, hey, I'm just I'm a new
viewer. Do you think that I could I'm trying to think of a sense of the Oh, this is this is the
game for the switch that I like band. Oh, what did I say? Oh, fuck this guy. If you go up there,
I think deleted what this guy sucks. It wasn't timing anybody out. All right. Where is this
thing? It's in here, isn't it? Timed out for saying if frame rate forest was the to go inside
of this thing was the entrance. And it's right here. So I need health twice. My voice sucks.
We should do a secret word of the day. If you say it, you get a 24 hour timeout.
OK. Well, I like you just you just win. Yeah. All right. So if you get timed out for saying this
word, then you know, you just win. You don't win anything. You just win. And everyone goes,
wow, you did it. All right. I got to think of a word that people are just going to spam
words and then get it immediately. And it has to be a word in the dictionary. It's not going to be
a made up word. So in the mod chat, I'm going to type a word, put that on the list that times
you out, whatever. And whoever gets actually timed out for saying it wins the game. Who the
fuck is going to write this? No one's going to write that word. There's no way that's literally
not fucking going to happen. Tell me if somebody wins. Why would it be Peter Griffin? Wait,
we won't see it because it'll just get blocked. Yeah. Yeah, that's what I mean. Your chat is just
going to look like bots. I'll give you some hints because there's no you have to say every word in
the dictionary. I gave you a hint. The hint is, oh, it's not enabled yet. In the meantime,
I'm ready to pull this out. Your master will come for you until then. You shall rest safely here.
Although the slumber of restoration will most certainly deprive him of his memories.
Please trust me when I say that I know he will arrive before you yet again.
If I may be so bold, what is it that you are planning to do next, Princess?
Does thing talk? Oh, no, it doesn't. The Master Sword. I heard it speak to me.
It seems that my role is unfinished. There is still something I must do.
I sense there is great strength in your dedication.
I ask of you when he returns. Can you please relay this message?
Tell him I know the word as there was no word words intended for him. What sound much better
in the tones of your than if it was a word. Don't you think? Yes. All right. Here's the hint.
Steam. Steam. Nobody got it. Yes. Steam. Hot. Forceful. Magnificent. Somebody got it. Somebody
got it. Somebody got it. Somebody got it. Who got it? Somebody got it. It was Geyser. Nice job.
What you just saw, you stabbed years ago. It was Joshi. Hey, Joshi. Congratulations, Joshi.
Princess thought to bring it here where she knew that it would be safe under my watch.
She continues to fight. That's a dumbass word for real. It's a hard one. You never would have
guessed that. Heart cascades with faith that you will return. She has a smile like the sun.
I will do much to feel its warmth upon me once again. Want to do another one? Okay, let's do
another one. Okay, I got another one. This thing only does 30 damage. Okay, so don't use it till
the end of the game. All right. I did this stupid thing. How do I make it so I don't throw it?
It doesn't break. Oh, it doesn't break. You can throw it. Really? Whoa.
Oh, it does that at full health, right? That's really cool. Okay. The game is on. There's a new
word. Good luck. I'll give you a good hint. The hint is food. Food. It's delicious. Hot. Steam.
Forceful. Steam. Hot. You could even call it geyser-like. Somebody got it, Fajito.
Nice job. That was by Daisy. Nice job, Daisy. You're now ready to test the limits of your
courage at the place where you reunited with the Master Sword. You're gonna wait till I leave to
tell me this. Very cool. So this thing never breaks. That's DLC. Okay. Well, I'll do it maybe
another time. All right, we'll do one more word. I'm gonna give to the mods. It runs out of charge
and you can't use it for 30 minutes. Okay, that's good to know. Okay, a new word. A hint for this
one. How do I do a hint for this one, though, given in a way? Forceful. That's true. I wonder
if somebody gets it without me even saying it. Wait, somebody already got it? Somebody got it.
Who got it? I didn't even say anything. A lot of you guys are getting fucking timed out.
Somebody get it? What was the word? Wait, I need to get it confirmed. Did anybody get it?
Oh, okay. Fast. Blade. Blade.
That's pretty much all I can say to you. Fast. Blade. Spin. Spin. Spin.
Nice. Everybody got it. That was EV sprinkle helicopter. This next one is a phrase. Oh my god,
I'm driving the horse off into the water. This next one's gonna be a phrase. This is four words.
It's four words. It has to do with what you are seeing right now. Somebody already won it? All
right. Well, I don't know what the hell I did here, but I'm gonna have to call the horse at
a different stable. Just go back to this. Just get it. Go back and get it. No one got it yet?
All right. Here's the hint. Well, okay. All right. You got it, but you haven't said the right exact
phrase yet. It's all right. I'll do it. The stream is over. It's the end of the stream.
Oh, somebody got it. Gabe bud. But it's not quite over. Not yet. Give me another few minutes.
I want to get up to the next town. A right. What was the phrase? The phrase was the stream is over.
I'm ending the stream in about 10 minutes. 15 minutes. So, I've got one more divine beast and
then calamity Ganon, right? And then a bunch of side content, obviously.
That was fun. You're gonna do more side quests? Yeah. Oh, yeah. How did I turn around? I'm so
confused. How did I turn around in a circle? Let's do the secret word game next time.
I gotta think of some good twist for it. Okay. What is this? Or a tower. I'll get a tower in the
end. I don't see a tower anywhere. Kind of weird to be all the way out here and not have a single
tower or anything. There's one over there. Oh, I'll get this one.
Sing, please. My whole family is here. Your whole family is in the room. Like even like
grandparents, cousins, aunts, uncles, your whole family's in the room.
Yeah. All right. Yeah. Of course. I'll sing to your whole family. Hey, everybody. Welcome to
the stream. See, right now, you just fucking panicked and stumbled around desperately trying
to grab the remote to turn me down. Because you're like, no, no, no, no, no, no. It's so
embarrassing that you just had to show that to your whole family. Don't ever ask me for anything
like that again. You watch the sky. It was annoying. I fucking hated that.
Look at grandma. You pissed off grandma. Oh, that's probably easier to get.
It's been a wacky day today. Oh, you actually got me.
What the hell is happening? Why is there more than one? Oh, just because there's a tree.
Just because there's a tree. What happened to the horse?
Seriously, how do I revive the horse? No, I didn't, dude. He's fine. How do I revive the horse?
God damn it. Will you leave me alone with this? Do a fairy revive? Do I have one of those?
There is a way to revive. OK, thank God. Oh, no. Carry the laser, you'll be fine.
Will the next stream be chill? Yes. I feel like there's too many goofy things happening today
for it to be a proper chill stream. Too many goofy things happened. There we are. OK.
Yeah, Grotto Beast, it should be shipping really soon here. I've seen people talking about it out
there. Keep an eye on your tracking if you have one. We're incredibly excited to see
what people have to say. Yeah, we'll do a real chill stream. I'm going to slow it down a little
bit next time. I don't know. There was something in the water tonight. I was just all over the
place. It was fun, though. It was really fun. I will revive Frank 2. The next time you see me
stream, I'm going to play this again. I'm going to try to beat Breath of the Wild over the next
few days. So I will see you all on Monday. Monday at 6 p.m. Happy April Fools. I didn't really do
very much besides make it so you can't talk that much, which, oops. No, it was fun. I had a good
time. Hopefully it was fun to watch because it's fun to play. Good or as bad as I am at the game,
that's fine. We will slow it down. I will. We'll chill out next stream, but that's going to be it.
See you guys on Monday. Take care of yourselves. And also, Sea Dog had a massive raid. If you're
still here from Connor's stream. Yeah, we'll do some proper exploring. I'm not just going to run
to the next Divine Beast. There's a whole area that I want to go take a look at. So we're not
just going to sprint through the game. I'm thinking I'll try to get it done in the next
two or three streams. Maybe another two or three streams of this will probably do it.
Like another 15 hours or so. That's probably seems like accurate amount of time. We'll see.
What about April 5th? Well, that was that's the Roblox birthday party.
And take a pause on this for a little bit. Yeah. Have a great night. Have a good rest of your
weekend. I'm sorry. I was a little unhinged today, but I had fun. I still can't believe
people could not write the for the first four hours of the stream.
How do you guys were super, super creative with though? I didn't even notice. I did not even
notice as there was a lot of th threes is that's why they were writing that. Everybody was writing
that. That's right. I was wondering for a second after the first like 20 minutes, it's like, oh,
that's a funny joke. I just never, we just never turned it off. I was like, why are people doing
like th three? Still like what's going on? Adapt and overcome. All right. I'll see you guys
a day after tomorrow. Tomorrow for some of you, but take care of yourselves. Call your mother.
Thanks for watching. It's a good time to stop to midnight. I don't want to go too much longer.
More breath of the wild. Good night.