Hello. How you doing? Doing pretty good. On time. It's funny that I can be four or five
minutes late and still be considered on time. I appreciate that. Thanks for giving me the uh,
the extra leeway. Oh it's 6.05! He's on time! Not really. But better. Better. Okay. So hello.
I'm gonna play some mercenaries today. Came out today. I remember playing this on the old Resident
Evil 4. I got very addicted to this. A very long time ago. Dude the Roblox stream was funny as fuck.
I mean, I just had a good time. I appreciate that you think that though. It was a lot of fun.
And that's all that matters at the end of the day. Do I know who Hunk is? I do. Don't spoil it.
Oh I forgot to tweet. There we go. You're gonna have to be a full-time Roblox streamer. I feel
like Roblox is kind of a... I feel like that's a really easy way to be able to hit up other
streamers and just go, hey do you want to just do this for a few hours? Because one of the things
that's actually kind of difficult streaming is that there's so many people to reach out to or
talk to or whatever and it's like, oh what about you? Do you want to do something? Maybe I'll do
something with you. And it's like, oh what do you want to do? And it's like, oh fuck. What do we want
to do? I think that's a very simple thing just to be like, let's go ride roller coasters and Roblox
for an hour. I think that's just easy. It's just easy to like put that line out, right? Good title?
Well I didn't make it so don't give me the credit. It's simple and fun. I mean it's,
it is whatever you decide to make it I guess. There's a lot of stuff on Roblox from what I've
been told and I don't know a lot of it is probably not very good. There's probably a ton of really
just, there's a lot of really really good things. There's probably a lot of really bad things too.
I don't know anything about it. Why are you a hater? I don't know. I'm just saying. I don't
know. There could be a lot of things that aren't very good. Is that why people have opinions on it?
I don't know. I don't know anything about it. Nice centrist take. That's how you walk it back
real quick. No I genuinely don't know. My only experience with Roblox was two and a half hours
two days ago. I don't know anything about the platform at all but I had a lot of fun. I thought
it was, I thought it was a really enjoyable experience so I'm probably gonna do more.
Play with Ludwig. I gotta hit Ludwig up. We wanted to do something like weeks ago.
Just kind of fell off the plate. See what he's up to over the next couple weeks.
Nobody said more with a bunch of question marks. I don't know. We'll see. Who knows what's gonna
happen. You would like Ludwig? Hmm. Maybe I'll check him out. But yeah I was gonna chill tonight.
It's gonna be one of those of many more slowed down just kind of chill relaxed streams that I
talked about back in January. Just gonna play Mercenaries. Hang out. Chill. And that's all
there is to it. Chill on a horror game? Mercenaries is not really a horror game. Mercenaries is more
of a shooter game. Mercenaries is a wave shooting game mode that they put into Resident Evil 4.
So it's not really scary. It's just kind of fun. But let's do it. It's all jump scares over and
over again. Oh by the way I put like a I put a warning on the VOD. On the last VOD. I was
considering like doing a highlight to remove that really bad jump scare part but hopefully a warning
in the VOD is enough. Hopefully people saw it. It was a good warning. Okay. No no I'm not gonna
remove that. No no I was just making sure it was enough that people saw it. I'm not gonna remove
the VOD. I was gonna highlight the part of that out. But then it was gonna be kind of jarring. I
figured I figured a warning's probably enough. Don't you dare. The whole point of a jump scare
is that there's no warning. Uh I think a jump scare when you know a jump scare is possible
is different than when it just like attacks you out of nowhere for no reason. All right.
You guys ready? How did stir do that? That was my favorite part of the entire stream
a couple days ago was the incredible detective work that I did in one second
to accuse stir of doing that. There's so many layers as to how that happened. It's just
if you watch that whole segment that whole five minutes before that segment
that whole thing and like a minute or two after that it's just everything in my brain was you
could even see I'm like oh you you you did that you piece of shit it was it was just the way that
like the turn turn up the volume on stir's uh stir's discord to hey dude he's quiet he's quiet
dude stir even screams right before I turn him up he go I'm like oh stir's quiet he goes
and then it goes so it's like holy shit there's no way you didn't do that
and then he laughs he like laughs at it is so unbelievable just how much I could have
I thought it was him it's so so funny like just how I thought that I mean the jumps get sucked
and obviously I hope that that's not something I ever want to have to show anybody
unprompted but the whole thing leading up to that and after that of my accusal
of stir I think is my favorite part so far wrap it up Albertson hey you need to apologize
I did all right you guys ready let's just play here it is so I think you have to unlock stuff
yeah okay so you gotta unlock stuff so I'm gonna do village first obviously we have four characters
there's Leon I wonder who else is even in this because I know that I don't want to say anything
what if you've never seen this is this battle royale it is not they they give you more stuff
this time don't they okay well I know who these are this is uh Lewis what's this guy's name
so there's the um
Lewis this is hunk what I what I can't I can't think of this guy's name why not Kramer
Krauser yeah Krauser Krauser Lewis all right let's go so how this works is you just kind of
shoot run around and pick up stuff you get a time limit defeat as many enemies as possible
within the time limit taking them out in quick stitch mode from a combo they'll earn you points
yeah you want to keep a combo together so we're just gonna get the swing of it again
it's been a while you get seconds added all right you also want to make sure you keep combos don't
kill everybody because you might run out of people to kill oops where are they I remember back in the
day getting a I think it was like more it was an insane combo I forget what I used to be able to
get what is mayhem mode what is going on you can go it's like extra fast attack speed and more time
so you build up the mayhem meter oh wait add this power up still I think no don't lose the
combo no good okay we're good I don't even think about it where's the barrel there's a barrel here
somewhere right here all right get some people to come through here and I'm gonna blow this up
shoot the barrel we're good we're good oh all right mayhem mode go oh I'm kind of lagging
oh shit I'm out of bullets all right big enemy coming oh my god I didn't see him oh my god
how do I heal like of course I know how to heal shit okay go go go go get off me
all right I'm fine mayhem mode shotgun I gotta get a 50 combo right oh what's this
open open open open open open open open open the door oh my goodness all right wait I'll be happy
I'll be happy with 50 somebody said is this really in roblox no it's not no it's I it's not
okay careful all right go go go go this way this way I got to 50 oh we're doing actually doing
fantastic on the first run here I'm actually impressed with myself this has got to be going
pretty well watch out what does mayhem mode with the sniper like oh shit all right don't
don't die here I got a pretty good can I get to a hundred all right let me heal what do I got for
ammo I'm kind of running out of bullets I do have a good grenades okay let's make this happen here
shit get away from the fire oh yes I gotta get some more power ups I think blow that up
I didn't kill anybody how did that not kill anybody reload it quick come on it's mayhem
oh my god stop all right collect just run I'm among I might lose the uh I might lose the
combo but I need to survive this if I plan on oh I got it they're throwing all these bombs shit
am I not hitting them okay oh no no no I'm so close I'm so close I need heals oh my goodness
that person's got a oh my god oh my god I gotta get out of here no the combo forget about the
combo I might be dead what did I just do what is going on okay I think I'm all right I just put
the ladder back up I got 300 that's not bad for first run oh my god do the ladder strat see if
I can get any more okay whatever 340,000 is pretty good for first one 91 damn it the coveted 100
hit combo okay here we go I got uh oh no it's embarrassing all right so I got three I won't
try to get at least a what is um at the castle hold on everybody has different weapons as well
you already beat the game yep you got an s bro oh well I looked over and somebody said they got
600,000 in their first playthrough so I was like oh I won't register bro if it wasn't if it hadn't
have been for cotton eyed joe I'd been married a long time ago bro I'm just gonna I'm gonna
purge that comment personally I just did it and that's like kind of like it was kind of funny
in fact they put long in all capitals I would I would have been very long time ago okay let's uh
so this is mainly rifle that leon has like everything I will did lose oh it's the I might
have to change some settings because I feel like I'm not that efficient right now I'm not trying
to be that efficient though I just want to play the game mode I got to save the rifles for much
later what the what's going on it's weird that was very strange the person stood back up all right
I'm gonna do stairs rat what's that I have a big pipe use your ability I will once I get enough
people here now whoa what what just happened oh that's dynamite I didn't know okay I didn't know
that's what he that's what he did that's cool wait I can do it this is not in the other one this is
new I can just keep placing them all right that's good to know yeah he's I don't remember him being
in the at all you know what I mean the words I was just trying to say oh shit go oh I died
you know I gotta change everything I silently have been struggling selecting weapons the whole time
I played the game I'm gonna try to get some platerals let me get this stuff here all right
get off bomb them yeah like uh like hitting three and then four I gotta I gotta memorize where these
are seven is seven is so hard to hit on your keyboard it really is it's not it's not a simple
button to press with your left hand I gotta get down whatever it is to do um the other stuff
a lot harder you know let's do that just put this shit everywhere when can I put another one down
okay do it so you can do about three it looks like shit oh come on I didn't get it I gotta get in a
better spot I only have nine bullets in this thing okay I gotta get to a spot where I know
those are grenades there we go it's three what did I just okay well trying to get at least gold
right at least an a stop I'm gonna die goodbye oh you dropped that's all you dropped you guys
didn't drop shit did I kill him oh shit oh my god that was so lucky that was so unbelievably lucky
watch out behind me all right we're doing fine I gotta kill that guy down there with this sniper
rifle oh sorry dude you stood up at the worst possible time oh I gotta kill that guy shit
hold on god please can I just put them on yeah I can don't do that that should be a pretty good
place to do this come on blow blow blow blow blow blow blow blow blow yes okay get out get out get
out get out yes that was so that was huge give me this give me this shoot no no no no no I'm
doing it again collect collect collect collect collect somebody is just dropping okay I'm in
trouble if I don't I already know what I don't know where I am on the screen my screen is just
bloomed back fuck you nice all right I'm gonna stay right here somebody is it one it's somebody
on the uh you understand the catapult right oh shit I'm running out nobody died from that
oh yeah all right come on let's go come on shoot it oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy
oh boy oh boy oh boy all right I gotta hide all right who is shooting that shit where are you
where are they ow oh no no no no no no no no don't even think about it I got a golden egg too I'm
fine I'm gonna lose the combo I think come on dude get it oh that's it I gotta move lucky oh my god
he's right there I can't jump down oh my god I can't jump down I'm so dead I just like it I
think it's lost I don't have any more heals left oh I need heals is that a heal no it's a flash
grenade shit heals no heals I got the egg you're right holy shit thank you everybody
so I have a question if the time runs out versus dying if I die it's over right
or do I still get the point it's the same thing all right I'm actually not as concerned though
those guys gotta die and I don't even know where they are nice I gotta run where are they where's
it coming from right there oh shit that's bad throwing up throw throw throw throw yeah I think
I'm going I'm going nuts today I'm gonna lose the combo sorry kill the catapults yep move move
move where is it where's the barrel this shit's not even heated I don't even know where it is
all right I'm gonna try to go up go use the cannon oh wait more heals good I'm going for the one
million here I'm definitely going for one million I guess we're good spot all right there's the
cannon I killed everybody everybody's just dead where is that what wait oh I killed everybody
I killed everybody what holy shit I'm running around looking for to get to the next position
but I killed every single enemy damn oh I got Krauser and the island where's your score
yeah let's go that's pretty good all right what is um let's Krauser oh Krauser has the oh that's
right I want a bunch of oh and a machine gun I feel like I'm not going to be very good with
this character that's right he's got the uh the Las Plagas arm right okay during mayhem mode he
mutates and can deal close quarters attacks with left with rust with both that seems amazing I
think this one so far is my favorite all right let's try this I feel like I'm going to do pretty
bad here let's see so this is explosive arrows I only get three shots with that I don't think
I want to do that okay let's go I'm really not a big submachine gun fan in any of these games
as you've seen through through the first playthrough you saw here
use the knife where is it on the bar wait just regular melee swinging oh okay I thought it was
like something all right all right okay that's kind of amazing I need to reload my weapons that
would be great I'm gonna save it that's not a knife what oh die already die already I missed
every how they hit every single spot around his head I think I'm gonna lose the
I'm gonna lose the combo combo is I did that just to keep the combo I thought he was dead
I'm not doing it yet all right I'll do it now holy shit all right stinger is both left trigger
and right oh okay hold on we're good there it is that's really cool I like it no kill him
yes we're good get out of here I'm running out of ammo I need to do an ammo collection sprint
here I need ammo collection please all right so I go left or right need to use your knife use
your knife is it on what do you mean just use the knife okay I got full mayhem what is that
who's got something weird you do don't lose that combo dude oh okay okay we gotta go okay we gotta
go okay we gotta go we gotta go right now okay we're good keep that combo up black black oh my
god hurry no yes oh man all right we're good constant conflict that's right all right we
got two big guys coming through the big bowls did they come okay run run run run run run run run
go get off me shit oh I got clotheslined this is gonna be insane
nice that's like everybody that was here okay go die oh my god he didn't die what the hell why
is this guy made out of fucking steel what I shot him a thousand times okay I gotta run
we're gonna have to get into a new position start a new combo that's all there is to it dude
get the fuck away from me come on I just want to collect items wow there's a machine gun right
there oh my head that hurt my head in real life you should spacebar to knife aim oh I see what
you're saying got him did I get him oh shit oh shit oh shit that's gonna be good oh is he dead
he's dead oh my god yes all right collect and run the hell out of here man
oh my goodness it's there's too many people there's too many people there but I have to
kill them all collect every item all right now get the hell out of here I'm going up
Jeremy you should eat a smoked brisket on stream that sounds delicious but I don't know if I'm
gonna be doing that I got them both grouped up right here oh man all right this is gonna be
another s what is it 500k for s probably but I don't what did I eat for breakfast this morning
because I'm gonna eat it every single day whatever it was I gotta run give it a heal
what did I eat for dinner last night because I'm gonna eat it every single fucking day
what if my routine was over the last 12 hours 24 hours I need to go scientifically write this
all down nice I got hunk hand cannon can now be purchased in the extra content shop what
what does that mean the power of roblox extra where is it
bonuses oh okay here oh
thousand what do you think about dr dr ochers paninis dr dr ochers does paninis
since when okay I got an idea I think I want to take hunk to the village I think what does hunk
got hunk not only has a high performance sub machine gun but also a unique melee attack that
can kill instantly during mayhem mode he gains unlimited ammo damn kill instantly with melee
try so is every is it the cool melee weapon melee item that's um um it started here well route
there's everybody sub optimal route sub optimal route andy all right wait the melee is instant
I want to get it we're not gonna see it okay all right looks good you just snapped their neck
well why would you do anything else is there a reason to press any other buttons with this
character I'm about to get a unlimited ammo okay there's a first big bad guy oh hold on
that's not good I'm gonna try it what to do damn all right that's I should not have used that I
didn't even know all right this is so cool I wasted that so bad though I gotta build that
back up I need that like right now because the big enemies just probably spawned right now
what the hell is going on with you I hear somebody yep and I should have
Jesus collect I gotta get that built up and not use it till the double chainsaw
the next snap will instantly kill a chainsaw too really all right that's good to know
I gotta get up top lost items over there I gotta get and then I'm gonna run up the ladder
I'm almost out of time I need time right now I haven't been paying any attention
gotta get I'm gonna lose the combo but I don't care I need time we're good okay let's go all
right more combo what the fuck just hit me oh shit is there another guy I think so okay go go go go
all right I gotta get up here somebody's got to spawn please all right I want to go up
uh oops oh okay we're good this oh why did you take so long to reload do you supposed to be a
professional I need time time time time time time time time time building have I not gone in
this one here nice okay good we're good somebody needs to die right now yes who's left oh shit
I would really like to oh boy oh no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
I'm good I'm fine relax good oh my god you're still alive no did she breathe she killed me
no she didn't run I thought she was dead dead dead long ago I lost the combo but I thought
damn it sorry anymore any more time that I didn't get 150 enemies right shit I don't think I have
one more heal I think actually I'm okay I lost the combo kind of panicking here for no reason
I hear it I hear them I hear them I hear them where are they holy shit they're right here
I'm in trouble now very more bombs or anything oh we're so close
I'm so dead seven I need seven I don't care if it hurts me oh that's all right fuck oh I was so
close I just freaked out shit sorry if I had to do that I thought okay I thought the chainsaw person
was right behind me swinging so I just tried to get as many kills as possible in the last second
I thought I was dead you threw two grenades at your feet well because if I threw if I threw it
any further I thought I was gonna just overshoot everybody so right there I knew I in my mind
I'm dead I was just going for points because I was like I'm dead here no matter what
that was fun though cool hey I'm happy with every single attempt has been an S
I'm happy or S plus I'm okay with that I want to take hunk to let me try that again what happens
if you S plus everything I don't know I've never done it I don't think I even S'd every level in
the last time I played this like in the original game where do I go to kind of remember where the
layout is here how do I go up there's a very specific ladder to go up all right let me get
all the let me try a new strategy here S plus plus is the highest dude really I don't think
you should even shoot anything until you get all the bonuses try that strategy just hide somewhere
where where are all the greens I'm kind of wasting time uh restart it where are the greens I guess
it's good to kind of memorize that this is a uh this is a who cares run there's one in here
oh they it's random uh okay they move around well never mind let's just play you may lay a
crouch down staggered enemy with hunk oh I'm always so afraid to get in close to do a melee
on the big scary enemies I always feel like I'm gonna screw it up and they're gonna kill me in
one hit try to go let's see if I hold on I'm gonna try this um you grabbed me instead of whatever
so that's a big aoe okay cool dude that was somebody's grandma oh that is pretty good
I love how he does jazz hands after he does it don't be stupid here that grenade not kill
anybody that grenade didn't kill anyone it was a dud oh shit I didn't look at my
ammo that I had left I need I gotta get bonus time time time time time time over here
even more than that all right go go go go go go go go is that an instant kill
all right it's not an instant kill versus the big people let's go up I don't want to lose the
shit oh it has to be the next snap okay what's this every grenade good I just have to help no
why what do you how why would it have done that it sat right on the lip of the ladder dude what
are you talking about I gotta get up there okay there's one over there too I'm gonna get this one
on the ground first shit that's not how I get it there throw it he's doing it on purpose now
come on I have to get it and then somebody has to die okay we're all right get over there quick so
I can do it go go go go go go go yes all right collect all right there's one more over here I
gotta get up that building oh fuck you okay go I have an egg I need to do it I had to I had to
oh shit there's no more do I need that hundred fucking combo what the hell are you doing up here
I'm out of I'm out of stuff no reload the gun you fucking dope what are you doing
I need that okay we're fine oh shit I'm not gonna get a hundred
where is everybody where all the oh my god you all ran the other way they all ran the other way
and that's why they're not they all went the long way to get over here they all ran around
that's so funny whatever it's humorous just kill 100 more uh I don't think there are in left 100
on the level I'm gonna lose this combo but I'm going upstairs oh shit oh shit oh shit oh shit
get out of the way come on reloaded all right now I just want to survive I think there's only
there's not very many people left to kill I'm saving mayhem mode but when the last big scary
monster comes out I need to I need to use it now throw it somebody's on me all right they're
coming they're coming I need stuff I need ammo or something oh my god they're gonna come up for a
second oh my god there she is oh my god there he is I'm gonna I don't care if I lose the
it's okay to lose that I'm trying to stay alive break his neck yes and I got mayhem
don't even know I'm shooting break our neck break our neck oh I have no bullets oh my god
this is so scary I have to do it come here yes oh my god that was so fucking crazy thank god I
did it is s plus a million it's crazy that's so sad 98 damn it's okay that's one million
do I have an s plus with every character I don't have an s plus with Leon where's a good place for
Leon is it gonna take all of your energy I think I'm all right this is this is really fun maybe the
island or island or castle I'll try with Leon kill stream oh I mean it kind of is I'm just
kind of playing the game so I used to playing with hunk it's like a different video game
okay go I got lucky and got these really early so that's good all right let's go I'm bad
heck I was standing there watching me do that I'm not gonna use that yet no reason to that gives
you more points too okay all right here we go where did he spawn all right they come wait
give me the rifle give me the rifle whoa I'm wasting ammo yeah I am this is actually not a
bad start it's not gonna go in way worse I gotta just spam E shit I made a decision it was to make
sure I could keep the combo going I gotta make my way across now I might lose the combo here
don't be so they're not dead what what no way I was gonna say what are you talking about video
game what's wrong with you okay we gotta kill it's going still all right I gotta take out
the people on the thingies all right we just spawn come on swing do it run run run run run
shit oh dead all right run away and get some uh load back up all right reload reload reload
just throw a grenade back because that's good I gotta get some kills here
okay another one spawned this is gonna be bad if I I gotta do this now
shit I didn't get it off in time whoa oh my goodness uh-huh he's back there
that piece of shit oh my god I gotta run he's dead um oh we're good give me that hundred
all right I need it I need it I need it oh my god the fucking flop the panic I flopped I'm good
got it yes a hundred kills hell yeah all right I thought I just blew it so bad
oh shit okay run but for 150 oh that's gonna be tricky isn't it somebody die
oh I'm out of ammo on almost everything oh my god this is I think this ends here
I have no fucking bullets shoot oh I'm so dead stop I'm dead dude
wait where's my bonus wait what I didn't get a bonus
no bonus for all the the combo no if you die it doesn't count what oh I thought that meant
like oh you have 110 combo going when you die it'll add it you have to actually be alive still
oh well at least I got it hmm I have a lot of trouble with the uh what are they the blind guys
they're really hard to deal with I have to get s plus with Leon somewhere
I try here you're doing really good I mean the there's gonna be people that do this
I look forward to watching people destroy this good place to start the thing about mercenaries
mode you will play this you will go back to the regular game and it'll be like the easiest game
you've ever played in your life you're like training yourself to be really good at the game
in here um it's kind of a waste but sorry oh that's right like professional is the thing
that's true need to kill somebody can you play the peanut butter song again um no not tonight
sad no peanut butter song sad I want to get that time that's fine okay that's not bad
that wasn't bad all right let's go I gotta get all those items right now oh you just ruined
everything dude and how I didn't even how did I see that guy come on all of you come on group
around it please go up I gotta keep the combo where did you even come from give me that extra
mayhem I got plenty of time oh shit don't kill me I'll be so pissed you little shits get out of here
oh my god I have to use it who's on me dude get a fucking away from me how are these guys still
alive I've shot them a hundred times I shot you a hundred times I'm out of everything I need
ammo so bad get off of me you fucking asshole oh my god they're all doing the same stupid
wrestling move from like wwe get the fuck off of me oh my god it's so annoying oh my what I
I was in them dude I was in the menu and I pre- I super mario jumped a second time
let me just grab you from behind and like hold your arms back let me grab you from behind hold
your arms back hey let me get let me sneak back behind you grab your arms from behind
get the fuck out of here okay we're good oh hey did somebody just do that yeah don't worry
dude I'm gonna do that too did somebody just do that to you hey watch out I'm doing it now on you
hey can I can I speak back behind here that was going so well too three random dickheads have to
just do the whole nelson move it two or three times in a row fuck you guys fuck you guys that
move is stupid get out of here oh hold on let me grab I fucking hate these things
he just all right wait I need I gotta restart okay fell off the bridge all right we're good
they did a what full nelson you don't know the full nelson is a is a wrestling move
full nelson is a wrestling hold in which one arm is passed under the opponent's arm from behind
and then well they didn't grab my neck but you get the idea god damn it I'm so salty over that
everything was going so smoothly I was doing so well I gotta use the the pitcher's mentality
the major leagues major league baseball if you throw a pitch it gets destroyed out of the park
home run you have to forget it just happened otherwise you just you're gonna get all messed
up you gotta get back on the mound and just act like it never happened that's what pitchers do
all right let's go everybody's gonna be behind me in a second somebody right here okay hi guys
I did not hit all I didn't hit everybody there oh god where are you this level's actually kind of
difficult where's everybody what are you all doing over here remember you're my fourth favorite
funny man oh thanks that's cool I'm honored to be in your top five it means a lot thank you
good good good all right everything's fine get some reloads all right I gotta get this boom
right here shoot the barrel like why it buys me an extra second or two got all the shotgun shells
okay I can't believe I missed that stupidly all right we're fine though everyone relax okay go
oh my god I thought I thought he killed me instantly holy shit look at this thing
do it that's oh my god it's like playing tomb raider sometimes dude I thought you little
bug fuckers get away from me did I ammo oh shit it is flashbang the bugs thank you for reminding
me all right we're moving now we're on the run here yes all right sick all right we're on the
run can't uh oh wowie oh my god I'm out of everything you have to die right now give me
that s plus I can taste it I can I can taste it give me that s plus I can fucking I can smell it
I have to get rid of some of the shit 100 all right we're good oh all right I gotta I gotta
oh my god run that guy's gonna rocket goodbye reload it please oh my goodness
oh my god how am I still I don't care I don't care it's okay we're okay we're okay we're okay
everyone relax that was just a that was a little fucked up that guy's gonna fall
now sit me and I'm gonna scream why are you reloading this gun who told you to do something
so stupid oh I gotta I gotta fucking use I gotta do scopes here I'm so stressed out right now
this is I know I'm supposed to be chilling out but like goddamn don't even think about it
dude get me out of here I can't move I can't move help holy shit I'm so fucking dead here guys
I can't combine these wait what I can't do one red that's kind of annoying all right I
gotta go this and I got a flashbang immediately no you gotta be kidding me dude give me a fucking
break so I got it oh that would have been so awesome if I had got it damn it I got it though
it's okay it's so addicting this is a lot of fun I got s plus with every character at least once
I want to take Krauser to the village the time bonuses I think are doing it to you yeah probably
it's true oh I know I know knife knife knife use the knife I know I should only be using the knife
for the first like two or three minutes at least he's fun honestly maybe I should just avoid the
bonuses until I really actually until like maybe a minute yeah where's Ada wasn't Ada in this
and Wesker are they just not in it did they replace them damn Krauser is insane they're in
the game files there probably be DLC I wonder time to let's go so that ends the combo it's good
to know whoa it's not good okay come on there's a series of unfortunate events right there I like
have not had control of my character in like 12 straight seconds it's bad wait what they're on
the roof I know what why did I explode what the hell is that oh I got tunnel vision there
let's try it again it was a RPG yeah I tunnel visual tunnel visioned there for an extra
second or two that I shouldn't have how many can I fit in one room you know what I mean I want to
do an experiment maybe they don't spawn fighting each other they can't get to me so did I think
you have to kill people to have it's fun mom and dad are fighting all right try this I'll get this
one because it's close this should be plenty of time come here don't lose the combo all right I
need to kill somebody okay first big guy coming up in a minute there is a mayhem thing right there
use it now I can kill these last few guys over here all right that was pretty good all right
I gotta get killed now I guess I'm dead all right here comes big guy where is he where is he there
you are oh that was bad but it was okay okay a lot of people coming all right I gotta select
items up on the roof thank you yep oh okay here they come where are they oh no no no no no no yes
oh shit okay let's go how did I miss such an easy whatever this would be a pretty this is
gonna be a good bonus I'm gonna start I'm gonna lose the bonus eventually here and then I need
to get into one of the buildings nice roblox player accuracy I'm doing all right all right
next spawn I think is coming in a second I have tons of time too that's good all right let's go
when's the next spawn okay I gotta throw this oh that's not good I have to use them with these
right now no somebody died from that yes thank you for killing that person I appreciate it
I'm just gonna use it that's you're gonna hurt me not really all right here's the uh they come
got it it's one more I think she's right behind me got her no she's still alive oh she's still
alive what are you made out of okay dead all right we got it I gotta run well this is such
a bad place to go I don't even know why I decided to go up here I don't know why I did this that
may have just saved everything go hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry let's go come on I'm saving
this at the very end I'm not going to use it I don't care about the combo anymore I just care
about making it all the way watch out okay go come on it's all right all right this is where we
this is where we actually have to kill everybody oh my goodness I just gotta activate it now all
right just one more where are they wow they're behind me I did it all clean we're good all right
whoo too bad I didn't get 130 combo 129 oh so close damn it oh close very cool I wonder
what happens if you get s with every character s not s plus plus is basically an f it's probably
not even on the leaderboard if it's not s plus plus probably not uh I'm curious can you show
hunk again yeah I'll do it after this I have achieved what I wanted to achieve now we're
just playing for fun I got s plus with every character that's all I wanted to do this can
anybody confirm if there actually is anything for um getting everything on s or s plus I move
actually is really good no you just get the hand cannon still pretty cool cool cool oh I want to
use the I felt bad for that one guy I don't know if that guy was actually attacking me
time to item collect I already unlocked the hand cannon yeah I thought I did it just cost
a thousand points to actually use it all right where is the where are they there okay somebody's
behind me you can shoot the dynamite oh my god that's how you finish it that's like that's how
you finish oh I'm gonna lose it no I'm not um this is really kind of sloppy but I think we're
all right no my character is definitely uh Krauser for sure Krauser's probably everybody's character
considering he's hunk is really good but I like the special on Krauser better we can't have you
all be swarming me like that okay I let's go ahead and just activate it now he spawns over here
doesn't he oh jeez right there oh boy whoa too many people oh he's behind me no please
I can't shoot it they're all dead yes okay reload come on come on come on come on come on
oh that's not what I wanted what fucking full nelson of course dynamite does not hurt you he made
me to tell me I've been messing that up this whole time I gotta get out of this area I'm gonna
reset the combo go get a time and run away okay timer up here you hear them coming let's go ahead
and just preemptively do this because I'm afraid thank you for hitting me appreciate it I think
this is a full minute and a half this is gonna get ugly here in a sec holy shit
it why does he keep doing that why does he keep throwing grenades at himself why is he doing that
so much dude yeah where's the there's so much health everywhere holy shit look at all this
where are they oh I hear it oh my god I'm freaking out I'm freaking out oh I thought you said it
didn't hurt me I thought you said it didn't hurt that hurt a lot that was incredibly painful
it hurts me they were lying to me get out of my way oh I'm so dead here I'm not making out of
this one no way I have to it's no oh my god no way dude it's not gonna happen oh my goodness
it actually yeah I don't even know what just happened but I'm alive all right yeah I gotta
get out of here I'm stuck up here come on man let's go all right here they all come where are
they I'm going up top grenade grenade grenade grenade no why did that happen what are you
talking about oh shit oh my god she's over here get down get down get down run run run run run run
no what do I have for stuff I don't I need to reload this oh shit
I have to get out of here get out of my way please I have to get out of here
wait there's an explosive barrel right here
there's one down there's only one left only one left only one left this dude is just turning
I'm all right I'm okay I'm all right oh there's gotta be a fucking grenade in here
is there a grenade in here yes oh thank god oh my god that was so fucking scary I gotta ask
boss we're good oh my goodness gracious oh my goodness gracious nice yeah I mean I got a little
scared it's supposed to be a chill stream yeah no it is I'm that laugh was legit psycho you turned
into the joker he said beavis and butthead maniacal laugh I'm just gaming man I don't know
what you guys are even talking about hold on let me see let's hear it oh shit
I mean I would I would say it's more like bail from Diablo 2 you just put all right put some
filters on that put some echo on it and some kind of grunge on it and that will be when you stand
still in the uh the what the world sanctuary wherever it is and it goes like right that's
what I would have said my brothers will not die in vain vain vain yeah here's bail's laugh okay
let's let's see let's compare it my brothers will not have died in vain uh you know I always thought
I was a bail you know I was gonna pick what Diablo character enough I gotta s with everybody on here
I know everyone's saying dude um excuse me Leon's not my character somebody wanted to see hunk again
uh we'll play hunk here what am I gonna do after this um I don't know I kind of just
planned on playing whatever I didn't this wasn't gonna be like a super duper long long stream or
anything I just was I'll pivot to something else maybe uh probably not breath of the wild I was
thinking about that but my switch is not um not set up right now I played um I don't know I just
took the switch into bed because it was well breath of the wild I was playing it that's cool
and I kind of just started playing random switch games and one of those random games I was playing
the Wario where uh for Game Boy Advance didn't I stream that game a while ago vampire survivors
I played a lot of the DLC off camera so I have seen it already play some n64 games
I'm down for that I'm gonna lose the combo do the hitman freelancer I would I promise you I would
I just don't have hitman installed right now and that game is like 700 million gigabytes and I don't
really I think I can really install it on stream I probably could but it would take like 20 minutes
or so 30 minutes that one down I wonder can you turn off the power or do you just store it
crew crew um maybe hmm maybe someone's probably gonna drop behind me
oh we're good nobody spawned I need to break some more necks okay let me get this actually
let's just do it again why not come on what's with the stun lock there we go all right I got
plenty of time I don't need time anymore oh shit just deal with that what about dos
hmm after uh after I do this one we'll take a look what we have for options
there's something else like an hour or two where are you there you are break his neck I actually
don't mind being down here easy don't even fall Nelson right now please collect and then I'm
gonna go out this way no I gotta get the hundred combo yes I'm gonna use a couple grenades oh
shit those things kill you instantly yes they do I may have just blown it I completely forgot
those things kill you instantly I'm good all right crisis absolutely averted right there I'm
gonna lose the combo or am I nope I'm not that guy just annihilated me okay getting there 100
where are the others where are the others I didn't want to use this for no reason okay
it's done it's the last one there's one more person I don't know oh they did it did it
shit oops good all right I think I'm gonna stick right here till the end I'll have mayhem mode
I might be able to actually get 150 this is actually a big deal hold on I got really scared
there that's my own fault all right here we go oh shit oh this is the one this is the one this is
the one come on I did it where's the last enemy where's the last enemy oh oh my god yes holy
shit oh I did it oh that's thank god oh my god I thought I was gonna miss it big time right there
at the end there it is nice youtuber reaction that was real that made it may have sounded fake
that was genuine I was about to get really really sad
can I register my name yeah it's thinking 1.1 mil 1.1 mil 1.1 million does anybody know what
the maximum score is check the leaderboards dude I'm the 10,611th best gamer in the world
on island with hunk in Resident Evil 4 remake why am I on there twice that's funny 10
you know what's really kind of wild about this that was hard that was like really challenging
really hard there are so many people that are so good at this shit it's unbelievable
well I don't know if I'm gonna do much better than that look at number one
a village how do I go by ranking how do I sort it tab so 2.5 million is the highest you can
possibly get that's probably everywhere 2.5 million 2.5 million 2.5 million it's all leons too
probably because the point multiplier for leon it's crazy what s plus plus does so all of my
s pluses are like oh I think I think I did a pretty good job 46,000 but if you get an s plus plus you
almost instantly teleport up to like the top 10,000 that's kind of interesting so what's the
next layer then I guess let's see looks like 1.1 seems to be the highest to get out of here I wonder
let's go here let's do start at one so at what point does this become like most people are not
doing more than 2 million 2.1 seems to be a pretty hard cut off because then you got half a million
points that are only like seven slots that looks like two millions doable somewhere between 1.5 to
two is pretty doable it seems and these aren't even with full combos yeah seems like 1.5 1.5
is where all the the god gamers live that's definitely the case cool all right I'm going
to take a quick break that was really fun this was resident evil 4 remakes mercenaries mode
I heavily enjoyed it uh well I'll play something else for a little bit we'll figure it out when I
get back I'll take a look I'm gonna go pee I'm gonna get a drink and I'll see you guys in like
a few minutes five minutes maybe see you in a minute
oh my mic is still on you I'm just looking at my steam hot bike hot bike you know what's funny
anytime I go brb even if I know the mic is muted I don't do I don't talk until I'm out of the room
like if I have to burp or fart or something really bad I even if I mute it over here
I'm doing I'm not doing that till I'm out of the room I just don't sometimes I just don't trust it
I don't know but I'll uh all right I'm looking at my steam we heard it paranoid Perry well
let me tell you something if I'm not paranoid Perry and for some reason I'm sitting here
and I've ripped ass really really loud with a brb screen up you that you want to talk about a
clip that will be shared a hundred thousand times forever you guys you guys will link that to me
and hide it like oh hey dude um oh Diablo four is getting some uh some updates click this and it's
gonna be me farting with the brb screen you know I know what you guys are capable of all right I'll
be right back