I scare you. Alright, let's begin a wind down here. I'm gonna play a few pick-cross levels,
we'll just chill. Gonna close out of Sekiro though. What's the total in-game time? Let's see,
I'm curious. Because I saw articles, reviewers, other streamers talk about their game time,
I'm just curious what the actual in-game time was. Let's see, how long did it take me to beat
Sekiro? Let's see, the last hour, the last two hours or so was not finishing the game.
Just wandering around, right? Let's see. I have 42 hours in Sekiro, so the last two hours or so
were spent kind of walking around doing optional stuff. So 40 hours. It took just about 40 hours
to beat the game. That sounds about right. And that's pretty much, most people have said, between
35 to 55 hours. 30 to 40 is average, yeah. Damn, it was fun. And that's the end of that.
Just finished my second playthrough at 45 hours. That sounds about right. Any thoughts on Borderlands
3? No, I'm not really a Borderlands fan, I never was. Dude, there's a PictoPix update from like a
week ago. Hello everybody, I'm very excited to announce that a new free update is available for
PictoPix. This update adds new content. We got new content, boys and girls. He hates Borderlands. I
just don't really like it. I don't hate it, but I don't really, I never really was a fan. Not that
I don't like the idea. Let's get it open here. It's not his cup of tea. Yeah, yeah. I watched
your first PictoPix stream and now I have 21 hours in the game. It's great. I'm so happy if you never
even knew what PictoPix was, if you're into it now. PictoPix, there it is. There we go. Play.
Let's go classic. This is where we're at here. This is, is it linked to Twitch again? So you guys
can guess. Should be. Maybe not. Let me make sure it's, oops. Enable to, ah there we go. Let's turn
it on. Should be on now. There we go. Now you guys can guess what it is. So this is 15 by 15.
So we start off here. We got 10, 11. Can't really do much there. 8, 9, 10. I could get the 8,
but I just go like this and pretend. So that's 1. We got how many? 1. That's 14, 13. So 1, 2,
3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. I can probably go like this. So 8. So 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7. Maybe not,
because that would mean I'd have to go like kind of halfway through here. Let's see. 8,
8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14. I guess maybe like a couple of these could be between here. 9, 2,
4, 6. Why is it telling like dad jokes? Why are there cat facts going on with Nightbot?
What? Let's see. 3, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, not 15. Not a whole lot to start with here.
I mean I guess you go 1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3. We know that. As long as this is correct, which it kind
of has to be. Now does that help anything else? Not really. I mean I guess here. Harder than Ishin.
Oh yeah, I can see 3. This has to be 1, 2, 3. It has to be here somewhere so there's no way it can
be any of these. This might be the 2. I can't really tell. The hardest decisions require the
strongest wills. I'm surprised I don't have anything here like at the bottom or down here.
Let me see. So that's 14, 13. Let me see here. 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
So actually I don't know that info. I do not know that info. This makes it kind of worse though.
Where am I getting the two x's on the bottom? Well with the larger, you've got to look for
large numbers because you can fill them in because it has to be somewhere in the middle. But the
reason why I'm doing the bottom x's here is because there has to be a 1 in a space.
So there has to be at least two spaces before 8 is here. You know what I mean? So it can help
sometimes. This one's kind of tricky because there's really not much to go on right now.
Because this is 14. So it's not 15 down. 7, 8, 9. I'm kind of stuck here. There's no way to tell
this is the 1 or the 2. What down here? Let's see. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. Let's just say 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
Now there's too many. It's too much. Too much of a space. See this one on the other hand,
you could mean, let's just look at it. Two spaces. It could be anywhere. It could be like this,
right? It's too hard to tell. Because hold on. 3, 2, 2. This is part of the 8. Let's see. 1,
2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. This is not enough to go on. Because this could be here, right? 1, 2, 3, 2,
2, 3, or this could be 3, or this could be 2. I need more info. Fuck. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
There's too many spaces. You've got five full spaces of space here that,
like, let's just say the overlap would have to be. That's too many. 4, 4, 3. It's just,
you really would have to just go like this. Yeah, I'm gonna have to go like this. So
this is probably close enough. So it's probably gonna be something like this.
At least these two. At least these two at least probably have to be filled in. Because if you do
1, 2, 3, 4, 4, 3. I don't know. Because it could be like this then, right? The outlier here is this
one's always filled in. So this one has to be filled in. Therefore 1, 2, 3. This is 1, 2, 3.
All right. A little bit more info. Which leaves... Let's go like that. Let's just clear these.
All right. Where the fuck are we now? 1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3. If it was 4, I could fill in both of these.
It's not though. Oh, my brain is kind of on... I'm pretty slow right now. I'm not gonna lie.
I'm in like the post-securo fucking... I'm like about to fall asleep.
Uh, well there's no music playing right here. Let's put the jazz music on. There we go.
This is definitely part of the three at this point. Go to sleep. I'm all right for now.
I might just call it here in like 20 minutes. Uh, I gotta have something better than that.
Fuck this one. 11, 12, 13, 14, 15. 11, 12, 13, 14, 15. Oh, fuck that one.
Okay, that's it for this. He died to Picross. We got 9, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9. Look at that.
Perfect. 13. Done. And so this is 1, 2, 3. Uh-huh. 1, 2, 3. Good. This... Let's see. Let's say it was
2 here. Let's just take a look. So we got 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7. Let's just say it's either here or here.
No way for me to do to get that. Let's just do it from here. So this is 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8,
9, 10, 11, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11. 4 on each side. That works. Died to gridwheel. So this is 3, 1, 2. That
means this is done. Nothing else underneath it. There's the 1. And 1, 2, 3 has to be up here somewhere
like that. Speaking of 11s. 12, 13, 14, 15. 12, 13, 14, 15. All right. What do we got up here? 2, 1, 2.
That's a lot there. Let's see. What about down here? 2, 1. So there's the 2, 1, 2. This might be the
same thing. This is... Yeah, that's probably... That's the 2. So then look down here. 2, 3, 4.
It's blocking itself out. This is probably the 3 right here. Also 4. 1, 2, 3, 4. 1, 2, 3, 4.
That makes this a little easier. There's your 1. 3. There's your 1 and your 2. This is 3.
3 in the middle, right? There you go. Bingo. There's your 2. There's your other 2. Part of the 7.
3, 3, 3. Looking good. 1, 1, 3. This is also that 1. It has to be a 3 here. So it could be
1, 2, 3. It could be 3 here. Either this side or this side. Can't really tell right now.
What about... What's going on over here? 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14. This is... This
might be already done here. Let's see. And then 1, 2, 3. 1, 2, 3. Not quite. 3 is definitely right
here in the middle though. Has to be. Same thing with the other one. That leaves us with... Let's
just take a second here. This is the... These are both... These are all 4s down here. So because
there's only 5 options, it's got to be all the ones in the bottom there. I would say the same
thing here. Unless we... Hold on. 1, 2, 3. Now it could be... It's possible. Although improbable,
but still... It is still possible. Because up here is also a 3. But it could be there.
Somebody came in and said, what is happening?
What are you doing? What is happening? 1, 2, 3. 1, 2, 3. Same deal. Does that help us over this way?
2, 1. Here is the 4. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6. We know it's the two middle ones. Now is that the 2? This is
the 1. This is also part of a 4. 2, 4. So it's got to be these ones. That's a 1. A 1, 2, 3, 4 again.
What about here? 2, 1. I've got nothing here. 1, 2. There it is. Simple. Absolute simple. Making a
picture. Yeah. The way that Picross works is you build out with these logic puzzles a picture.
If you do exclamation point guess, you can guess to see what it is. 1, 1, 3. It could be this.
1, 3, 2. No, this might be the 3. If that's the case. What about up top? 2. Somewhere in here.
1, 2, 3, 4. 1, 2, 3, 4. I mean, it has to be the middle ones. This is definitely the 1.
There's 2. And there's the other 2. This is harder than Sekiro. Some of that can be really,
really just challenging. That's the last one. I couldn't even. Sometimes you just sit there
and look at it and it doesn't click. Nothing clicks on it. You just skip and go to another one. There's
like hundreds of them. Hmm. Plane. Yeah, that was a plane rumor. Crashing by. Just flying by.
1, 2, 3, 4. Nothing there. All right, so hold on. Wait, wait. This has to be 3.
So if that's the case, then it can't be any of these. Oh, shit. So this is definitely the 3.
I'm thinking the 3s. There's still one up here. So is that enough info to figure that out? This,
let's see. 1. Yeah, that has to be there. Unless I made a mistake, which I don't think I did.
And that's it for the 4. All three 4s. Somebody let me out of here. I'm in hell.
You're okay. Now let's see. Yeah, this is it. 1, 1, 1, 2, 3. 1, 2, 3, 4. 2, 1. Close. Close.
Could be either one. Still don't know about this side. Are they meant to be all white? Yeah,
you'll see when it's complete, it turns into a colored picture. Is the 1 here or is the 1 here?
Probably here. This is a 5 here. This is, okay, hold on. Let's just say 2, 1. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
No, the 5 is right here. There's the 2 and the 5. Here's the 1. Okay. These are all 1s, except
this one's a 2. Done. There's your 1. There's your 2. Oh, it feels good. Then we got 1. This is a 2.
And this is also a 2. That's part of the 11. 11's done. I think I can get some more of these in here.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12. No, I can't.
And it's just happening so quickly now. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7. Middle can go.
It's on its way. All right. What is it? I don't know. 2. Let's say 2, 1. It's apparently a building.
Where is this 4? Oh, there's a 5. Here it is. So 1, 1, 3, 1, 1, 1, 3, 1, 1, 1, 1, 3, 1, 1, 1.
This is 11. Done. 3. Got it. That is done. This row's done. And then 7 here. So 7.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10. Bingo. Done. The 1 has to be right there. 1, 2, 3, 11.
And that's it. It is a house. A hut. Who got it? 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10. Have you got it?
A hut. Nice work. So this is 15 by 15, but that's a lie. It's actually, that's 10.
This should be fairly easy to get a lot of these, because 8, 9, 10. The middle one's here.
6 is 4 on the sides. So 1, 2, 3, 4, 1, 2, 3, 4. 7, 3. Okay. What about 5? 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5. Sorry, sir. You can't do that. 11, though, is 4 on the sides.
We have to count up to 15. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
I can't really do anything else. All right. What we got to work with here? Anything else? We got
6, 8, 4, 7. 1, 2, 3, 4. X that one. 1, 2, 3, 4. It has to be up somewhere here. It's 11. All right.
So 3, 8, 5, 1, 3. I wonder if this is the 5, probably. And then if that's the 1,
we got 1, 2, 3, maybe. Could go here. If this is 1, 2, 3, that has to be the same. This is definitely
the second 3, because there's not enough room for it there. So 1, 2, 3. 1, 2, 3. 3 is in here
somewhere. Yeah, this just kind of has to be the 5. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. Let's just clean it up.
Any combinations here that I can do? I'm so mad that Jeremy plays this. This was my secret game.
Why are you mad that I enjoy a great, interesting, relaxing, fun game? Why does that make you mad?
I'm so mad that Jeremy likes this. This is my thing. This is my secret game.
I could get the 8 here. Let's see. Okay, so let's just say 1, 2, 3. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
That's definitely the 4. I mean, that would be very odd. That would be really odd if it was
like this. You know what I mean? 1, 2, 3, 4, 1. I don't believe that for a second. This is definitely
the 4. If I'm wrong, that's fine. I'll be wrong. The 1 is up here somewhere. So if this is the 8,
3 is 1. Let's just say 1, 2, 3. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It could be that. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7,
8. But even if it's this, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It has to be right here. Right? You mean it's
right? That's wrong. Wait, hold on. If this is the 4, then 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7. Hold on a second.
I hope this is correct. Otherwise, this whole thing's fucked up. This is probably a 1. 1, 2,
3, 4. 1, 2, 3, 4. It could be over here. I need to get rid of this shit first. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
Got more info to fill that. All right. Well, that's interesting because now 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
You have to assume here now this is the 1 and there's a 3. There's 5. Let's just make it.
Let's make it nice and simple on ourselves here. I either blew it or I didn't. It's pretty simple.
You know what I mean? This is probably wrong. But who knows? 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
I'm committing to have this being fucked up. We'll see. Yeah, it's all jacked up already.
Shit. No, I committed to it. I committed an initiative. Damn it. See how I screwed myself
here? This is the outlier right there. If that's the case, then this can't...
That's not the 5. No, the 5, man. 1, 2, 3, 4. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. It's got to be a 1.
I blew it. It's all right. Sometimes you blow it. Damn it. I thought I had that one too.
Well, this is 13. I like when they give you a nice easy one. 2, 4, 7. Yeah, not enough spaces.
1, 2, 3. 1, 2, 3. 2 somewhere up here. It all makes sense now. Thank you.
Now, wait a minute. This is... I can fill in a lot here because that's 15, 14, 13, 12.
Can I get at least... Let's just start with that. 10 is also... I can do a lot of these.
10, 10. Anything that's 10 can be filled in down to here and more than that. That was not a 10.
So this is a 10. Let's see. 6. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6. 1, 2, 3. Yoink. 1, 2, 3. Let's see. 9, 10, 11, 12.
Guess. Kim's Cookies. They're delicious. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9. 7, 8, 9. This is also part of the
9. Then 9. Speaking of 9. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10. Okay. This is 6, 8. A lot of just big numbers
here. Well, there has to be a 2, so. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6. Space 2. There's the 2.
And then there it is. Let's hope that's correct. The 9. Part of the 2. There's the 2 again.
There's another 2. There's all the 3's. 1, 2, 3. Eh. Meh. 2, 3, 4, 5. That's gotta be
right there. What about down here? 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7. Can't do anything with this.
Anyone know if I read the recommendations channel on Discord? I do. I do all the time.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. I do read it frequently. How many more left here? 1, 2, 3,
4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10. I can do this. This is done now. 1, 2, 3. Get it out of here.
Ah. 3. 1, 2, 3, 9. That's it. 5. I think I know what this is. What do I? It's weird that this
is here. It looks like a heart. 7. Done. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. This is done. Close that up.
I mean, there's no way it's there. That's like symmetrical, right? It has to be there.
That's it for that 10. Yeah, this is pretty much a done deal right now. So we've got that done.
I think I can just fill these both in. Yeah. There's the 6. Yeah. Yeah. Well, what?
What kind of heart is this though? Is it just a heart? What's with the top left?
Just a heart. Guess. Elephant. I feel nice and slowed down. I do like another a couple more.
Let's do like a few more. This is another one of those slightly harder ones, I think. 13, 14, 15.
Right down the middle there. Breathe, breathe. Let's see. Is this probably 1411 anymore?
5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10. 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10. A few more hours? No, I'm probably going to skedaddle here
in a little bit. I just wanted to wind down a little. Let's see. 8. You're already guessing
animals? How are you already guessing this? 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10. Nothing that's close to 15.
That's the only thing I can do is this one here. I think I can do that, right? Yeah, I can. 3,
2. No, this is definitely part of the 3. This is the 2, right? Yeah. Which then that makes this
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7. This is a 1. Part of the 8. Interesting. This game makes me irrationally angry.
I don't think that should be happening. I don't think that should be happening. I think you need
to calm down a little. I could probably pull this tooth out if I tried hard enough. Don't pull your
teeth out. Do not pull out your teeth, please. 2, 1. This is part of 3. This might be a 1.
If this is 1. Let's see. 1, 2, 3, 4. Let's see. 1, 2, 3, 4. 1, 2, 3, 4. 1, 1, 2. Okay. 1, 2,
3, 4. 1, 1. This could be the 4 here, although it's unlikely what it could be.
I'm gonna do it. Give me the pliers. No, sit down. Stop it. Give me the pliers.
Shit. I'm stuck. I'm stuck. I don't know. I'm stuck. 7, 8, 9, 10. I'm stuck right now. 1, 2.
1, 2. Help me out here, guys. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
I think I can get this. All right. I can get that. 2, 3. This is 3. 3, 3. 1, 2, 3. 1, 2, 3.
1, 2, 3. 1, 2, 3. This could be the 1. 1, and then 1, 2, 3. No, 1. 1, 2. 1, 2, 3. No,
it's not. This is definitely the 2. That one may cry 5 waiting room. We're not doing that tonight.
It sounds like I'm trying to count to 10, but I can't do it. 1, 2. 1, 2, 3. 1, 2, 3. I don't know.
Well, I can do something here. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7. Something on the other side. 1, 2, 3, 4. 6, 7.
Holy shit, this is part of the 4. Really? 1, 2, 3, 4. Oh, I don't know. It could be any one of
those numbers after 8. This changes this up a little. So 6 is now able to be done a little
bit here. It's 8. Something like that. 1, 2, 3. 1, 2, 3, 4. This is just counting. Yeah,
that freed up some space with 8 because look at this. 1, 2. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9. Look at
this. Okay, I'm just going to do it. I'm going to punch myself as hard as I can in the face.
Okay, this is meant to calm you down. That's right. It's supposed to just be chilling and
just shutting up and playing. I forgot. 1, 2, 3. Okay, I can get rid of this.
Doesn't help me for anything else though. Okay, that helps this though because if this is 3, then
I just figured that out. Smart guy. The question is, is this the 3? I don't know.
If this might be the 3, I think it is. I'm just going to say this. Now I can do the 4. 1, 2, 3.
Space. This has to be the 3 going up. Boing, boing. Please be right. I think it is.
It's a head scratcher at this point. 5, 2, 5, 6, 7. Can't do anything with that.
This 8 though. No. Remember to go to church this Sunday? If that's what you do, then yeah.
This is definitely part of that. That's it. Let's close that out of here. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7,
8. Can I get 3 on both sides? I can. Nice. Yes. Oh, it feels great. 5, 3. This is awkward here.
So 1, 4, right? It's not 1, 2, 3, 4, 1. That's part of the 4. So that's the first
1. Okay, that looks good. There's the second 2. Okay, what else we got here?
Done. And then that makes... He's guessing? No, I don't know. That 4 had to be right there,
and then the ones had to place this way, and that gave me the 2, and that gave me the 4.
I'm not guessing on this one. 2, 1. That's definitely 1. That's also 1. Oh, fuck. Wait. Oh,
no. 3, 3. Whoa. I blew it. Oh, it was going so well. Oh, what did I do? I really wasn't
guessing though. This is not correct here. No. This is correct. I'm certain of that, but not here.
But there's no way this is correct. That's the 8, right? This is the 3. That's the only 3.
On this side at least, right? All right. Got it. Just uninstall it. No, wait. What do you mean? No.
No? Are you sure? Because that looks pretty close. That would make complete sense. Because before
I had it back here. Oh, wait. No, but what the fuck is going on here? Oh, no. Oh, this is the
worst when you... Oh, god damn it. No. The right 3 crosses, I guess? No, I didn't. I just... Because
this was empty. And I figured it had to be the 4. And it... Shit. No. No, this is supposed to
be making me happy. Let me see if I can fix this shit. How can I sleep with this pick-ross fail?
Well, there's no way it's these. Because this 4 can't fit in here. No, it's not down here either.
I might be too tired for this. And I do this while I'm tired. Oh, no. No, I had it too.
It's the same shit I was saying when I played Sekiro. No, no, I had it. I gotta restart. I gotta
redo it again from the beginning. Oh, fuck. I had it. This is correct. It is. Don't tell me it's
not. I know it is. It's wrong. Is this... This whole row can't... This can't be incorrect.
And looks like is... Is that what was just fucking me this whole time? No, but this is fucking wrong
though. You see, like 4, 1, 1 can't be here. It's... Something else is wrong. See what I'm saying?
Like, I think this whole thing is fucked up. Because this is supposed to be 2, 1, which...
Like, that's 2, 1, but... But then this 6, right? Like, there's no... How am I gonna get the 6 in
here? You know what I'm saying? There's no way. The 6 is not gonna fit in here. This whole thing is...
What is this? What nice animal. 3... Because look, see? Nope. Nope. This is 1. This is the only place
where it can start. 5 and then 2. 2 is already done here. This one's done. Or no, at least like
this part is. That's the 3, 5, 2. Where's the 1 go? 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6. See what's going on here?
This is all messed up. Look at this. We're gonna get a bigger problem down here. No. No.
Fuck. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. I need one more. 6. But then this is fucking wrong. All these 5, these 2, 2,
2, 2. I got... This is all... I screwed up something like a couple times and it's just over.
Is it... I don't think there's something I can replace here to make this right.
Because the 13 has to... The 13 has to be here. You understand? The 5 is wrong then.
Because this has to be here. And then all this shit is wrong.
Get me out of here. Fuck it. Harder than Sekiro. I fucked it up. God damn it. I'm going to bed.
God damn it. I had it too. I was gonna relax. Yeah, this is relaxing me. My 40% capacity
brainpower right now is doing great. 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14. Not enough to get a whole row.
I need to calm down from this stressful de-stress. Yeah. Hey, calm down and go play some Sekiro.
I actually probably should have just gone... I should have probably just ended the stream
an hour ago when I was already tired enough to go to bed. All right, let's see. 5 and then 1, 2,
3. That's... This is 6. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 4. No, 1. 1, 2, 3, 4. Okay, that would... That makes sense.
He doesn't know how to count again. He's losing his mind. He beats Sekiro. Can't beat Picross.
No, I can. I can do it. I'm gonna like just go hold my head under water and then the bath
and like the bathtub that... No, no, no. Listen, listen. Like I'm talking about like
go take a bath. Go take a bath. Listen. I'm gonna go take a bath and just like relax and like put
my head under and then get the warmth and then come back out. You didn't let me finish.
That's not how you bathe. Yes, you do. You go back and like go under just for like two seconds
and then come out and you're... You baptize yourself. All right, we've got 8. So obviously
8 has to be here. So we got 1, 2, 3. Let's see. 1, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. Pretty good.
That would make sense here. And then the 2 is down here somewhere because that's correct. Yeah,
it is. I know what I'm doing. I know what I'm doing. 5, 5. Let's see. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
I can... It's probably the same thing. It's baptized. Yeah, I'm gonna go baptize myself
in like the warm cooling waters of the bathtub. Yeah, it's the cooling waters of the bath.
This is 4. In fact, I might just fucking flip the table over here in Monopoly and just go do it now.
I went into like the 15 by 15 P-Cross. Should have just did like the 10 by 10. Let me see.
3, 1. Do a 50 by 51 in a bath. I think... I honestly think Ishin might have dropped my IQ by like
8 points. I mean that permanently. To beat Sekiro, I had to drop my IQ by 10 points.
I used it all. You know how you have like... Okay, I used some life consumables.
Take 10 years or 10 points of IQ off life but gain 30 straight seconds of utter complete focus.
I used it. Perishables. He's activated checks too many times. Again, you guys know
in like fucking time travel movies and tv shows where they like their nose is bleeding and they
keep using the time travel and eventually they like they they go fucking like wacky. They've
lost their mind because they've done it too many times. I think I may have activated checks too
many times. This happens in click. Have fun. I'm gonna just relax. I use my back and time powers
too much. If you guys do this, I'll do another Minecraft VR stream. You have uh you have five
minutes. I don't know why that's making me laugh so hard. You have until uh 11 um you can't cheat
either. Yeah, I'm sorry. I've I got no brain power left. It's gone. I'm gonna admit when I,
you know, when I'm just gonna admit defeat when I have to. All of it's gone. Jeremy lied about
Minecraft VR. Five more community subs. You've been insane tonight with these community subs.
Thank you. You guys have to let's see eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen. I'll give you guys
until 15 minutes. No cheating. You have until the clock on the top right strikes 15. Restart the
board. That's not part of the deal. We ain't got no damn idea. No, some of you guys know what's
going on. Restart the board, fucker. Fine. Fine. I'll give that to you. But you just consumed uh
two of your brain cell minutes. So now you have five minutes to do it. You used your power.
Don't use it too many times. Alright, fine. You got until seven minutes. I'll give it back.
I cleared the board. You have seven minutes and then the stream's over. I gotta go take a break.
I gotta go take a shower. Eat some food. Good luck though guys. I really hope you hope you get it.
I promised Minecraft. Yeah, if you guys if you guys do this by the time it's seven minutes,
I will do another episode of Germacraft VR. I said seven minutes. I did make it six minutes.
I just gave you an extra minute. I'm not lying. Do it. Keep me honest. That's the thing. The 15
by 15s are like some some of them are very difficult. Most pit cross puzzles top out
at around 15 by 20, 20 by 20, 25 by 25 is really kind of pushing it for difficulty.
There are a lot, there are some pit cross puzzles that go more than 25 by 25 or 20 by 20 but they're
it's like doing a thousand piece jigsaw puzzle. At some point you're just like,
eh, I kind of wanted to do a quick one. 30 by 30s, yeah. They take a while though. They can take
upwards of like an hour. Especially some of the ones that are more than 30 to 40 or 40 by 40.
What are you all even trying to do? They're trying to make a full square and they do it every time.
40 by 40 is 1600 pieces. It's a lot, yeah. Takes a while. Is it 1600? No, it's not. Is it? How many
are here in 15 by 15? You guys have plenty of time to get this fixed but for those of you that are
sticking around, that's the end of the stream. Sekiro was really the only thing I wanted to
finish tonight. Yeah, it is 1600, yeah. You will see me again. We're gonna play Monster Rancher.
We're gonna start with Monster Rancher 4 and if it sucks we're gonna go back to Monster Rancher 2.
All the Sekiro people already left, yeah. I know. Thanks for sticking around, you guys.
Just sticking around in pit cross and watching me have another meltdown. Meltdown 2. Give us until
you finish reading bits. Okay, that's not like a fair assessment here. Let's see, how many bits
do we have? Okay, no, that's fair. I wish you luck. So, my journal lied about Minecraft VR. Five more
community subs. My god, thank you so much. So many community subs. Super seal, thanks for the 250.
Just letting you know there's going to be a temporary TF2 man versus machine update.
What do you mean temporary? Operation memes versus machines. Oh, nah.
All right, just the title alone is kind of like,
I don't know about that. That's on the official Team Fortress post, yeah. Memes versus machines.
Might be interesting, but maybe not. Who knows. But thank you super seal for the heads up there.
Sad Vega, thanks for the 250. Oh my god, Jeremy, you missed so much shit. No joke, you're gonna
have to play the whole game again. You should do as much as you can before you get to Junichiro
and fight him. Also, could you kill those poor castle grandmas? I did that parent
and didn't hurt a single one. I did that parent and didn't hurt a single one. They just cry
and curl into a ball if you look at them. You horrible monster. I feel like I did,
I missed a lot of shit, but yeah, but aren't there two or three different ways you can go through
the game? I was under the assumption that some of the choices I was making changed the whole game.
And you can't really go back and redo them, right? There's four, there's four endings.
And on a first playthrough, it's, you know, kind of just need to do it, you know. But thank you,
Sad Vega. Hole of one zombie, thanks for the five dolls. Kind of odd, but just wanted to say thanks
for reading my dumb comments. Before I watched your streams, I used to think up stupid shit to
make my friend laugh, but he passed from cancer. Your streams helped me laugh again and want to
make you laugh too, if that makes sense. Kind of depressing, but keep making people laugh.
I'm really, really fucking sorry to hear that. Making people laugh, telling jokes, and enjoying
experiences with people is one of my favorite things in the world. Having fun together is
my favorite thing on earth. I'm really, really terribly sorry to hear about that hole of one
zombie. I'm happy that you can hang out here and make jokes and give some joy to other people.
Thank you so much for the five dolls. How are you guys doing? Yeah, actually, I'm really doing
that bad. You're starting to get it. A Frodeon weapon, thanks to the five dolls, Frodeon. Superb
shinobi execution, term of checks. I think that was for the demon of hatred, but thank you,
Frodeon. And then say 250 from Frodeon again. You're doing a great job.
I'm trying, I'm trying. Sekiro was fun. Did you beat the final boss? Yes, I completed Sekiro.
It is done. Something or other, thanks to the 250. Hey Jerm, saw you at the bowling alley the
other day trying to get the bowling shoes over your regular clown shoes. I noticed that you
wouldn't, I noticed that you would let out a high-pitched scream whenever someone tried to
help, so I figured I'd offer a piece of advice now that I'm not with an earshot. Why not put the
bowling shoes on first, then put the clown shoes on over them, since the clown shoes are bigger?
Smiley face. That's a good tip. That's a really good tip. I'll probably check, I'll probably do
that next time in this imaginary scenario that you made up. $50, I missed this earlier. I was
really, really focused and intense and I missed a $50 donation. I don't know if you still hear fudge
44. It was 5,000 bits. I'm really sorry I didn't catch this when it first came through,
but I'm not sure if you still hear. Maybe not. I suppose it was about four hours ago, so
thank you regardless. They say, hey Jerm, I stumbled across your channel years ago when
you were playing Battlefield 3 with Pwnstar and have been a fan since. Now that is a long time ago.
Just want to say thanks for getting me into TF2 and volunteering at an elementary school.
Got inspired by your video on working at an animal shelter. About to finish university
and recently got my first job, so finally have the money to show my appreciation for all the
entertainment advice. Sorry it's taken so long for me to give something back. You already gave
something back by watching. The amount of people that watch these streams, collectively all of you,
have given me more than anything I could ever ask for in my life. Everything I've ever dreamed of.
Doing entertainment. Doing jokes and comedy and bits. That's the number one thing I've wanted in
my entire life and you've given it to me. That's worth way more than money. Thank you.
You guys just filled row A. Well you got a little bit more time. Hanging out and doing
broadcasting and doing videos and shit. Something I've always wanted to do. Thank you for letting
me fulfill my the goal of my whole entire existence. It's worth way more than a dollar.
Thank you. And when I say dollar I don't mean a dollar that you get 50. I'm talking about just
like the dollar. Thank you so much. Penguin thanks for the five dollars penguin. I would help you
Jerma but I have... this is like a thing with the streamer says the thing right? No is this? I don't
know. Lumbago? What is that? I've heard it. I would help you Jerma but I have Lumbago. Who says that?
Somebody says that. Oh it's from Red Dead. Right. I thought it was like the the other one.
Flank tank. Thanks for the three bucks flank tank. Are there going to be new emotes anytime
soon if you have any open slots or maybe a community emote vote part two? Yeah,
Sakura really has just taken up 100% of my time here. I haven't really had an opportunity and
I'm sick too. I spent a couple days last week sick so I haven't really been focusing on it
but yes there's gonna be a lot of new shit soon. Soon soon soon. But thank you flank tank.
D Jack thanks for the 250. Well done Sekiro. Well done. I got through it. Tingy thanks for the 250.
Is this the guy who beat Sekiro on stream? It is not. As of the end of this broadcast, yes it is.
It is not. We get to say that now. Thank you Tingy. Thank you Have Gun for the 250. I was there when
Jerma defeated grandpa and became his own man. You guys again with the A. Some people just want
to watch the world burn. That's the scenario there. Smelly Boy thanks for the 250. I hate that clip
it. I wonder what you were referring to. But thank you Iron Dude for the five dollars. Congrats Jerma.
Thank you. Thank you so much for the five dollars Iron Dude. Clueless Sniper thanks for 250. Hey
Jerma now that you've beaten Sekiro what are your favorite from bosses? Ludwig is number one
always. I don't think any boss in this game topped how I felt when I played Ludwig for the first time.
The fountainhead dragon was really really awesome. Scale wise probably the biggest boss they've done
which was just awesome to see. Really really interesting design. That's probably the up there
for like coolest looking and most interesting art direction wise. I'm trying to think if I would put
any I'm trying to think of before. It's hard to remember like every boss from the whole this
like 150 bosses across this whole company's lineup here. Who's my favorite? Let me just think about
my favorite bosses from the whole series in general. Dark Souls one. My favorite boss from
Dark Souls or my favorite boss from Demon's Souls was probably the last fight. That was a lot of fun.
Fighting against the guy with the sword that dashed around and he was really really cool.
I forget what his name was. I think in Sekiro the first fight against Genichiro was maybe my
favorite. Now that I have a chance to sit here and think about it. No no no not the not the
tutorial one. I'm talking about like the first when you beat him then he like falls over the
balcony. Just that fight was just really really fun. It felt very fluid. Old King Alant is that
boss from Demon's Souls. Yeah that was definitely one of my favorites. Dark Souls two. I feel like
there was a boss every 30 minutes in Dark Souls two so it's hard to remember. Who was my favorite
boss from Dark Souls two? I don't know. Maybe not necessarily favorite fight but the guy that the
two people that were back to back that were connected that would fold on top of each other
and you'd fight one and then they would do like a little cartwheel. I don't know if I liked that
fight but I liked that how that boss looked. They had the two scimitars. The sentry yeah.
That was just a really interesting mechanic in regards to just how it looks and how cool it was.
Dark Souls three is uh honestly probably Pontiff. I just love his animations. They're so cool.
He was just so fun to watch. His the two blades that he has were just and oh no Gale. Gale was
unbelievable. That oh man that's tricky. That might be one of my favorite. That's my favorite
fight like ever huh. Gale yeah Gale Ludwig I think are still higher than anything from Sekiro for me.
Sekiro was more about fighting other people for the most part. There wasn't there was a couple of
extravagant ridiculous enemies but for the most part the major enemies in Sekiro are
I'm also a guy and I've got a sword too. So it's hard to make the comparison between like Gale
or Ludwig versus something like Owl. It's kind of just your dad. Fight wise they were brilliant
but I guess it's it's hard to overcome the way that I felt when when you get to phase three of
Gale. It's just it's so everything it just clicks everything looks so interesting.
He has a really really cool move set. I don't know it would be tough between Gale and uh
and Ludwig. They're all good. Most of the Sekiro bosses were dudes with swords. Kind of had to be
like that though because in a game that's based around parrying deflecting and you know posture
and sword play you did they really then they tried you know they came like the ape the giant
ape was sword and he was stabbing and they did do a good job with that but you kind of have to
have it be a game about sword play and then you move on to Bloodborne and Bloodborne is just
is a perfect video game. There's so many bosses. I have such fond memories of a shitload of those
bosses. The research facility is one of my favorite zones in any video game. Drip drop drip drop like
that place was fucking crazy. I loved that place. I wish I could just play Bloodborne 2.
The DLC in Bloodborne was the best DLC that From Software has ever made. Regardless of a copy and
paste couple of boss fights the DLC was the best they've done ever. It was perfect. Well not perfect
because I just told you that they you know this they copy pasted a boss or two. We'll see if they
come up with some DLC for this game because they've been pretty on point with it so far the last like
five years. Lady Maria was just absolutely phenomenal. Ludwig absolutely fucking phenomenal.
Yeah I want to like go back and play it again. Orphan was next level almost like the yeah what
a great game. I still hold it to a higher regard than Sekiro. Sekiro is pretty close though. I
think Sekiro is better than Dark Souls 3 just as an entire the whole package. It's tough.
Ah the memories. But hopefully that answers your question.
Sad Vega thanks for the 250. Congratulations on getting the bad end. I hope you do better next
time. Oh man wait till you see the actual final boss. Congratulations on the bad end. Nioh is
better than all of them. I just okay I'm gonna be here's a confession here. Yes I play oh dude
go back to Nioh. You know you were just like shitfaced. You would like it. Offstream I like
a year ago or so I did try to just play Nioh off stream. I just I didn't like it. I was I just
didn't it didn't click. I don't know what it was about it. The gameplay is fun. The environment's
interesting. I just something about it was not clicking with me. Nioh looks lame compared to
Sekiro. They had a really uh the way your character moved around is I think what I had the biggest
problem with in Nioh. Like the way that the dodges worked and it was just it felt very
um it's hard to describe. You guys did it. Look you made a bow and arrow. But thank you sad
mega. Thank you Dubski dude for the 250. You are a gaming god. My heart was pounding during that
last stretch. Didn't think you were gonna make it. Neither did I. This game wasn't made for human
beings but you beat it. Have my bit so I can finally say that I gave a sweaty internet goblin
a hundred dollars in total. You deserve it. Thank you. Thank you Dubski dude. I didn't think I was
gonna make it either. I had so much self-doubt going into half of those attempts. 52 attempts.
Dear god. I guarantee I can tell you how like 38 of them went. Oh my god.
Fuck no. Just redo it. Ready? Let's let's turn let's turn the audio off. I want you to like
maybe somebody like just super they can pose me over. Ready? Here is absolutely at least
15 to 20 of those attempts. Now I'm just gonna go. I'm gonna try it. Okay. Fucking god damn it.
It's just fucking insane. It's it's just insane. I don't want to do this part. Oh my fucking god.
Jesus christ. Always hits me with that bullshit. Yeah that's a good one. Always hits me with that
bullshit. I forgot about that one. What a stupid fucking mechanic. Honestly why? Why? I'm so close
to the wall. There's nothing I could even do. Someone just said I came I just came back. What?
But impose me. Ready? Oh my god. No. No. No. Fucking my god. Oh my fucking god.
Give me a fucking break. I probably said that four or five hundred times in the last three hours of
the stream. He's raging at stuff that doesn't exist in Picross. Is this guy like on fucking drugs?
Hey PikaBanana thanks for 30 bucks. 30 dollars from PikaBanana. Congrats Jerma. I'm so glad I
could watch you beat the game live. It was so much fun to watch. Thanks for sticking around. Thanks
for hanging out. I know some of these new games that have a lot of hype behind them. A lot of
people maybe don't want to see just because they're playing on planet themselves. So those of you that
have really stuck around the whole time. I hope you enjoyed it. Thanks for hanging out the whole
time. Well for you know however long you were here. Thank you for the 30 dollars PikaBanana.
Appreciate it. Zero giblets thanks for three bucks. You did great Jerma. Thanks for the stream. I have
to ask what is your new scale of favorites for from games? You mentioned favorite bosses. Thanks
again. You ready? Here we go. Dark Souls 2 at the bottom. But this is going up right? I would say
Dark Souls 2. I'm not gonna make a lot of people upset about with this but Dark Souls 2. Dark
Souls 1. No no no no. Dark Souls 2. Dark Souls 3. Dark Souls 1. Sekiro. Demon's Souls. Bloodborne.
There you go. Done. In that like order going up. I loved that. I love Demon's Souls. Yeah Demon's
Souls is that high. I just I loved it. Do it again but this time coherent. Okay Dark Souls 2.
Then Dark Souls 3. Dark Souls 1. Sekiro. Demon's Souls. Bloodborne. The thing about
you could probably. Sekiro could probably overtake Demon's Souls. I mean I just did play
Demon's Souls. I mean I did. Well actually I did like last year. Here look. Oh here you go. I'll
write it out. Here we go. I'll hear you. Official. I would probably say Demon's Souls and Sekiro
probably equal for me right now. What am I lagging for? Okay here we go. Ready? He's typing really
slow. You guys didn't even come close. Let me see. 29 minutes and this is shit you guys have.
There you go. I fixed it. 30 minutes are gone. That's it. Guess what? I'll give you a consolation
prize. I'll play Minecraft VR again. Not as long this time. Oh no you know I'll watch a Minecraft
video. I'll watch a Minecraft related video. Today? No not today. Thank you Tingy for the 250.
Congrats on beating the game. Now it's time for your death count. Drum roll please. German95 you
had 221 deaths throughout all the streams. Jess you got it and I've kept count. And there you go.
Look at this. Let's see how. Wow what happened on March 26th? Honest to god look at that. I was on
point on the 26th apparently. I must have had my fucking vitamins. What was what what bosses what
areas were the 26th? Was it the ape? I would expect that would be way less. I mean way more.
That's cool though. 63 52 of them were the final boss. German lied about Minecraft VR. Another
five community subs. You are uh what are you at now? 115 total in the channel. You've given 115
community subs. Thank you German lied about Minecraft VR. That's a lot. But thank you Tingy
for the 250 and for keeping track. You and Jess you got it. It's cool to see it. D Jack thanks for
the 250. So quick first impression. The game's not even fun. It's like the least amount of fun
I've ever had. Thank you though. Thank you Wavelet for the four dollars and 20 cents. Congrats on
beating the game. German the last boss fight. Stage three with no healing pots or Rez's left was
intense. Pog. Yeah oh I'm just I'm just remembering that fight. It's a lot. It's a lot of fun. Thank
you snooze and copter for the 250. Uh have I seen this video? This video. Yeah this is this is the
German Defoe one with the painting. You know some people say it looks like me. Yeah I watched it on
stream before here. We have seen this one. And then they said uh I was curious how you and Kim met.
How did you get to know each other? Uh we met at a Christmas party and then I we just started
texting. We like we hooked up at the Christmas party right. So it was already kind of like oh
okay like I will talk again. We started texting back and forth and then it was like hey come over
you want to come over? Yeah we watched like fucking Iron Chef for three hours and that was it. Boring
lore. What do you mean boring lore? Yeah you got everyone. Jeremiah I got like what you got any like
tips like relationship tips or you know how do I know what what what give me some tips give me
some secrets on how to get food network shows. Iron Chef. Hell's Kitchen. Kitchen Nightmares.
There is no better thing to watch when you're on a date. You want to know why? Because it never
fucking ends and you don't you don't have to think of the awkward moment where oh let's watch this
movie. An hour and 30 minutes went by it's over. Oh fuck now what the hell am I gonna do? What the
hell are we gonna talk about? There's like 6,000 episodes of Iron Chef across regions of the earth.
There's like 2,000 Japanese episodes and then they ported it to America and there's like 3,000
American episodes. You can just leave it on and just figure out what you're gonna how you're gonna
what you're gonna do. Well then she'll go I gotta go now it's getting late. Yeah but like you you
had you have so many opportunities to like talk and it's not just like the the movie ends or the
tv show ends. Everybody expects when you look when you go into it you turn on Iron Chef you're not
just gonna watch one episode. That's not how it works. You're gonna watch at least eight otherwise
you're not gonna watch it at all. So you know you know what you're getting into. Nobody goes
hey yeah like Iron Chef oh yeah that sounds like a cool idea one episode done. That's I'm done. No
it would be weird if you were to turn that off after two episodes telling you Iron Chef. And
there's plenty to talk about there's so many interesting things and food and and wow he
burnt the chicken oh my god he burnt hey Kim he burnt the chicken can you believe it? No I can't
he burnt I know it's unbelievable. He's gonna get points deducted from that you can't do that during
a movie. Try doing that during a movie. He just got shot in the chest Kim he got shot in the chest
Kim yeah he got shot yeah oh he just like John Wick just punched that guy did you see John Wick
yeah John Wick just like threw him across the bridge yeah. No you're gonna sit there quiet
awkward and silent. You can do full-on commentary during a Food Network show. This is an NPC
conversation. That's my biggest relationship tip Iron Chef that's all I gotta say. Hey we've got
your earlier rigid parallel thanks for the five dolls yeah the one that has 21 hours in
PictoPix is a fantastic little game there's so many different versions. Jerma goes on dates and
talks like an oblivion NPC. No I'll just give an example and look my brain is tired so they're
gonna be very very basic simple examples. All right we're almost done. Thank you to Garfield
the Monday Killer for the 250. Been a while since I've made a comic for you. Let's get this on here
There's more stuff. Been a while since I made a comic for you Jerma the Worm. I had a dream the
mammoth from Ice Age was trying to kill me inside an insane asylum. First of all don't eat before
you go to bed because that's why that happened. The only way out was to grab an egg spinning on
a metal saw blade. Have you ever had a dream like that? Ever had deja vu before? Hey I'm Garf I'm
not so Garf and where are the game Garfs? Yeah Jerma you said that yesterday you're losing your
marbles man. Odie called the doctor I don't think Jerma's feeling. Stop you violated the law you
burnt the chicken. I burnt the chicken you burnt the chicken. God damn it. Yeah don't eat like
fucking three slices of pepperoni pizza before you go to bed that's why you're having weird dreams.
I'm serious look it up. I just did that. Don't. I'm gonna do that now why? No don't eat eating
right before bed fucks with you. It does. Yes somebody just said it. But thank you Garfield
for the 250. Thank you Garfield the Monday killer. Bingo Sunshine thanks for the five bucks. The AI
the AL is a boring mess this year. Do you think the Brewers can win the most competitive division
in baseball and take it all? Fuck the Pats lol. Red Sox are gonna win again. The Red Sox are gonna
win 154 games. Hey Mast Herman thanks for the 10 dollars. Thank you so much. I've been hoping to
show you the movie I made inspired by Rat Movie. Oh it's Mast Hero Man not Mast Herman like the
Pee Wee Herman superhero. I'm sorry. There's no capitals on Streamlabs. I've tried to explain
this before but there are no capitals on Streamlabs so you M the H and the M they're
they're not capitalized so it's Mast Herman. I'm sorry. Yeah by the way why the fuck is there are
there no capitals on Streamlabs? I have no idea why that is. Why have I botched so many names?
That's so odd. I'm just thinking about this now. How odd that is. Mast Herman. But for real thank
you so much Hero Man for the 10 bucks. You made a rat movie and a movie inspired by a rat movie.
When you got it done give it a link. Why do I support Boston teams? It's I think it's this
weird scenario where I grew up on the east coast and grew up in Boston in the 30 years of my life.
Something like that. I don't know. It's weird how that you you know you rip the team that's closest
to you somehow. I'm I don't know. It's weird. How does that how that works? Vegas gets a baseball
team. I'll be a Vegas baseball fan and they win. That's what are you talking about? You're from
Massachusetts. You spent 30 plus years in Massachusetts and the Massachusetts based teams win all the
fucking time. Why are you a fan of the Boston area teams? Why wouldn't I be? You have to admit that
Boston fans are the worst in the country. Why would I do that? Red Sox Nation. Red Sox Nation
representing here. Duncan. Red Sox. Duncan. Red Sox. Duncan. Red Sox. I just had that's pretty
much five out of ten conversations you'll have in downtown Boston. Hey Duncan. Yeah yeah it's a
launch. Red Sox. Yeah. Hey Duncan. Duncan Sox. You got it. That's how fucking like deals are made
over here. When they're building buildings in Boston that's how they that's what they do. They
oops. Oh yeah I'm from out of town. I'm from Wisconsin. I'm here on a contract duty.
I was just wondering how tall we're going to be making the floors here. I heard maybe 15 or 16
stories high. Which one is it? Sox. 17. Okay. Now what about the uh how many doors are we going to
have? I heard we're going to have two doors double doors on the front and then single doors in the
back. Red Sox Nation. Okay so we're going to have two uh thank you for the clarification. Two double
doors in the front and one in the back. That's how it works. Hey Jack. Thank you Jack for the 250.
What's your favorite game you played in 2019? Resident Evil 2. Probably. We're talking about
games that released in 2019. Sekiro is definitely up there but Resident Evil 2 probably. It'd be
close because Sekiro was great. Hey have gone thanks for the 250. Hey Jeremy. It was fun
watching you play Sekiro but I was disappointed that you didn't take the Japanese voices
a spin. I saw Kraken play with the Japanese voices and it made the game feel like a Kurosawa film.
Plus the Japanese voice actors have more consistent pronunciations of the names.
My favorite boss fight to watch was Isshin. What was your favorite boss battle?
The first fight with Genichiro or the fight with Owl? Probably my favorites. Um I was supposed to
turn on the Japanese voice acting after the first like 40 minutes of the game. I'm just realizing
this now. Whoops. This. All right it's all right. The owl fight was pretty boring looking. I just
liked the the flow of that fight. The horse guy was fun too. The Genichiro fight was the best I
think. That second phase was just so interesting for the first time seeing that with the lightning.
Like that's he's the first person that you understand that with you know. And it's a really
interesting mechanic. Doesn't feel bad. It feels fun to do. But thank you have gone. Thank you
Gondor Lane for the 250. A few days ago Jerma I actually had a dream of you. More dreams about
hopefully this is not about like people like putting you in like a torture room or something
like the other one was. In the dream I was just browsing Twitch and I just saw you streaming and
saw that it said you were playing Sam and Max. I got so unbelievably excited then I woke up
and my heart sank. You were playing my favorite game. It's suggested often in the discord too.
Make us happy Jerma. It's a perfect wind down puzzle game although it's lengthy so you might
want to save it for a good weekend. All right I gotta I can tell you every time somebody brings
up Sam and Max at least a handful of people at least go don't do it. What's going on here?
What's going on here? You just said you don't Gondor Lane just said don't do it. You just told
me that you had a dream about me playing it. What do you and you want what? Why did you say don't do
it? Don't you want me to do this? It is on a list. It is just one of those games that's probably
gonna be chill on his hangout. It was his nightmare. Oh I see right but I can't give you any
reason why it's gonna start or what it would happen or when. Just know that it is it is on a list.
It's on a notepad. It's just the stars need to align but love of god don't do it. But thank you
I appreciate the enthusiasm and appreciate the dream. Why I mean you hated that dream. You got
like upset about that dream. I shouldn't be happy about that dream but thank you. George McCaw thanks
for the 250. You're really good at these games but it's still fun to make fun of you losing.
I love everything you do bud. Nice RP here by the way. What? Nice RP? Oh I gotta get like
PictoPix out of here. The PictoPix was playing over. All right this is nice RP. Let's see what
they mean by this. Where is it? Where is it? Come on say it. Say it. I didn't even. Here we go.
I didn't even have it. No he was gonna say it. He was gonna say it. He was gonna do it.
You are so dramatic. He was gonna say I wouldn't even ready or I didn't even have the right thing
equipped or I should have the hitbox was so big you're gonna hear at least one of them.
Fuck this guy. I'm gonna go watch German at A5. There's dirt in my controller. Yeah this is
disgusting. It really is. Get a list of all the things I've said and how many times I've said
them. It'd be embarrassing for me to see it. You want to like embarrass me on stream? Pick out all
the times that I said something like that and count them. It would probably be the same audio
clip like fucking 50 times and it would be an embarrassment. Hey Tingy thanks for the 250.
This is the best Iron Chef icebreaker. It's called beer.
This guy like does like flips and shit.
You gotta okay give give him credit to do a big elaborate like this is the thing that I'm revealing
right beer is one syllable beer beer it's got to be longer beer that's how I would do it I would
go beer today's secret ingredient is beer I do you know the line uh thank you masked hero man for
the ten dollars just a few minutes ago here's a link straight from Herman's mind Herman's mind
what the hell is this oh this is a 3d movie maker
I'm surprised people can even get this to run this up you guys there's a 21 minute video holy
shit how long did this take you to make I remember when I went through 3d movie maker
I would have to restart and do different clips and do and pull it different segments because after
like five minutes of actually in the editor the thing would break down you just don't need to
stream yourself making rat movie three oh no that would be no it just takes too long it takes me so
long to do that shit I don't think anyone would want to really see that but thank you masked hero
man it took four days that it all on stream well that would be fucking I can't imagine how crazy
that would be and do I have trans parents of my planets I don't I really don't it's just the
emotes it's the emotes that are just blown up I don't have like high quality uh trans parents of
them that would be your most popular stream what a bad practice but it's more authentic that way
when Ashley did the shirt she actually like re-drew it and used the emotes too as references and tried
to copy them and stuff there was like a couple of different versions she's very talented let's just
put it that way uh let's get the credits up here these are all the subs tonight there were a lot of
gifted subs thank you everybody for sticking around we got two or three more bits to get
through not much more let's see how fast is it gonna go pretty fast pretty fast thank you so
much everybody you will see me again I'm gonna take the next two days off so I'll see you guys
on the 31st I'm gonna do monster ranch at four it's also uh it's Kim's birthday very soon here
so we're gonna probably celebrate it over this uh weekend here so happy birthday to Kim preemptively
so I'll see you guys on the 31st and we'll figure out what we're gonna do from there monster ranch
or four is the plan we'll see if it's any good but we're not done yet Jess you got it thanks for
the 250 I was just watching kitchen nightmares today and I realized I have a new respect for
Gordon because he just shoves his hand in the grossest food and kitchen grime and just says
what the fuck is this while his hand is coated in two-week-old oil and rotten chicken wild stuff
yeah that is kind of yeah that's crazy he eats this food too in kitchen nightmares he'll just
sit there at the beginning and be like oh like yeah what yeah give me the crab cakes and he'll
eat them even if he knows that the place is about to shut down because it's disgusting
didn't he quit kitchen nightmares because he kept getting sick from the food that would be crazy if
that was true I don't know if that's true that's ridiculous but thank you for the 250 Jess Garfield
the monday killer coming in right here 250 German what do you think you're doing man you skipped my
comic you know how much time I spend in the writing room developing this don't you remember my links
don't stink when Garf has ever when has Garf ever led you astray now read the comic where I'm unsubbing
can you even unsub on twitch I don't know let's take a look hey German if I were to die today how
would you feel he's dead we finally killed him I can live in peace reality is often disappointing
though is it can't get rid of me that easy that emote is so bad do you see what that looks like
up close can I at least change the name of this emote why did you guys vote for mustard no it
doesn't make any sense at all not even a remote smidge of sense you guys voted for this name
people come in here and they think that I made this emote called germa mustard and they're like
what the fuck are you talking about some weird meta inside joke no chat had 10 or 15 different
options Jeremy why but thank you Garfield for your comic thank you we'll let you change it if you can
beat a pit cross level in under five minutes no I'm done with embarrassing myself at least for one
night vr josh right at the end thank you for the 250 hey German for one of your future vr streams
I highly suggest looking into a free program called live it's free and on steam it lets you
composite yourself into the vr games really easily and looks awesome works best with a green screen
but they also have tools to composite other backgrounds too I've actually seen this yeah I
have seen you just I feel like I would want a bigger room for this though that I unfortunately
this room is not big enough for this to work because I just have barely enough room for you
guys to even have a face cam pointing at me and for me to do a room skill this is really really
cool though don't you mean your office yeah well every time I say that word it triggers this
this automatic response and I look over and see l u l's you guys have like a script ready when I
say the word office rent the green screen and bring the vr now if I'm gonna go to the green
screen that I'm gonna do like the vape fortnight joke and if those of you that don't know what I'm
talking about then good because I still might do it where the room just fills with like fucking fog
and I'm dressed like a dick I I love this okay even if it's gonna fall flat on my face
I still want to do it no not like an actual dick just dressed like a dick dressed like a dickhead
but that's gonna be it I'll see you guys in let's see Friday Saturday I'll see you guys on Sunday
Sunday 31st same time same place around 3 to 4 p.m pacific Sekiro is done thank you for joining
me for the one of the best games probably that's come out in 2019 hard as shit frustrating as hell
but it was great hope you enjoyed it I'll see you guys real soon thank you so much everybody
see you when I see you next time in a few days oh right right right right hold on
the guild the guild members I think keep always remind me about this because I know a lot of
people think it's fun so it's a free loot if you scroll all the way to the bottom of page there's
like a little idle game it's called stream legends just a little fun free little idle game and I can
give loot every so often so let's do it all right you ready here it comes three two one bingo
enjoy the free shit all right guys take care see you soon have a great rest of your night