Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight I'm gonna be playing as the Demoman with the Loose Cannon, the Sticky Bomb Launcher, and the Eyelander.
Don't know why the Eyelander was equipped. It didn't really help me out in this situation at all.
But before I start talking about the video, very quick video by the way, less than 4 minutes I think it is.
But I don't know if you can tell, but I'm pretty sick right now. If you can hear my voice, I sound like an old lady that like went through the dry cleaning machine.
Like she was on the dry cleaning machine, it was spinning around, and she was on it, and she came off talking like this.
But no, I've got the flu. I don't know how. I don't know where it came from.
I tell you right now, I haven't had a fever in over 10 years, and I woke up the other day with like a 101 or a 102 or something.
I was really damn sick, and you know when you get really sick and you're just sweating?
It's not even like, it's not like you stink or anything like that, but you just wake up in your bed and you're just, the bed is wet.
Like as if somebody dumped water on you when you were sleeping. That has been happening to me for at least the last couple of days.
And sorry for sharing those grotesque details with you guys, but I like to keep you guys in the loop, let you know what's going on with the channel, with me, etc. etc.
So we're going to talk about the video very briefly right now. This was a super overtime video.
This is on Hoodoo, by the way. We're on defense.
And this game, it just got down to the wire right here, and I was just cracking up laughing this entire freaking time.
Like it was just nonsense. If you want to talk about just like total chaos, this is total chaos.
They actually get the cart inside the door, almost to the point where it's touching.
Like I don't know if you could get any closer with the cart on any point as close as it gets right here.
And it goes to like a minute long overtime. I'm not going to spoil anything, but just going to let it play out in the background.
You can watch it. It's pretty funny, pretty chaotic, like I said.
But we are going to move on from that. There is something I do want to bring up in this video, something I do want to talk about.
And what I want to talk about is the grandpa face cam video or the grandpa face reveal video.
A lot of you guys are wondering where it is, and because I've been out of commission for a few days,
I haven't been able to really respond to many of these inquiries. Inquiries. There we go.
So the grandpa face cam is coming along very, very nicely. I'm going to tell you, it will be worth the wait.
And this is not going to be just as simple as, oh, grandpa has like a face cam in the corner of the screen,
and he's playing like Happy Wheels or something. No, no, no. This is going to be an entire production.
I want to make sure this video is done right. I want to make sure it is funny.
I want to make sure that things go well with the creation of the video and so on and so forth.
So if you're waiting for it, I'm sorry, but you're going to have to wait a little, little bit longer.
And I was trying to get it up by this weekend, but because I was like sweating with a fever in my bed for the last three or four days,
that's just not going to happen. So I'm not going to give a date. I don't want to give like a concrete date on this video
because it's too important of a video for me to just be like, yeah, it's going to go up on January 6th.
I'd rather get it done when it's done and upload it when it's ready. So I'm going to go on valve time right now, guys.
A lot of you are probably not going to want to hear that, but trust me, it will be worth the wait.
So I'm going to say my goodbyes now. Thank you so much for watching, guys. I really do appreciate it.
I'm going to hop back in bed and drink some more Pedialyte and eat some more soup with my hands.
So I'll see you guys all next time. Happy New Year, by the way. I don't think I actually said that.
I think I said it on Twitter back when it first happened, right when it got to like 11 o'clock or something.
I said it on Twitter, but Happy New Year, everybody. Let's hope for a good 2013 for all of you.
And of course, take care, everybody.