I'm enjoying rap. Yeah, I didn't have time to make a title, guys. I just found out eight
minutes ago that I can't play Tony Hawk right now. That is a quick, very fast title. I just
found out I can't play Tony Hawk until I get an original Xbox hard drive. Imagine my face
when it's 1.47 p.m. Oh, sorry, 12.47 p.m. Pacific. And I put in Tony Hawk's Underground. Oh,
it's backwards. It's backwards compatible. Close. Here it comes. You need an Xbox, an
original Xbox hard drive to play this game. That's like a bite my finger. Okay. Now what
do I do? Because I don't have one of those. I don't own one of those. So I have to get some
third party. But I'm not going to put that on here. How do you attach an original Xbox hard
drive to an Xbox 360? I don't understand. It's a 360 hard drive. That's not what it said. It said
I need an original Xbox hard drive. Play it on PC. It's probably very hard to get that game to run
on PC. I'm scared to buy it on and try to get it on PC because it probably doesn't work. The 360
hard drive can do. But this doesn't have a hard drive in it. Whatever. All right. I'll figure that
out over the next couple of days. I want to play Tony Hawk too. Buy it on PC. I gotta find it too.
All right. So we're doing a pivot here. We're doing a hard pivot. And this is a game that I
have that I bought that I know I was going to play it eventually and knew during an Xbox stream.
This was very, very highly requested. This is Asura's wrath. I heard it's crazy. So I'm like,
all right, I'll get it. The arcade slim 360 doesn't have one. Holy shit. This shit is nuts.
All right. Yeah, let's go. This is a hard pivot and I got plenty of hard pivots. This game fucking
sucks compared to Tony Hawk. But don't worry. I have it behind me. I just need like an Xbox
hard drive. I didn't know that. I wasn't personally contacted by Phil. Let me tweet this out. We'll
start in a minute. I'll be back in like two minutes. All right. What is this? What is this
game? Not even an HD? What? Are you serious? Look at this game. Look at this. What is this game? Not
That's some crazy music going on in the background here. Look at this. Quick apologize. I don't have
to apologize for anything. There are no, I, I'm going to, I'm going to seem to make a statement
here. I am not going to apologize once on this screen. Okay. I don't need to apologize for
anything. I actually saw somebody talk about this recently. They said he doesn't have to fucking
apologize. He'd do whatever he wants. And I was like, thank you. Thank you for saying that. I
do whatever I want. That being said, I'm very sorry if you happen to find something in this
game that you know, just kidding. The sir is rat. Here we go. Can we just play on fucking David?
Does it really matter? No, I need to be able to like, no, I'm going on my shitty account. Oh, come
on. Let me just, a 620 fucking K update. What is it? Did you change a background image there?
What do you even possibly update with a 600 K update? That this text was changed. Get it together.
By the way, this is from Capcom. One of the best fucking video game companies currently right now.
They're really killing it. It's an HD now. Ooh, that'd be cool if it was. All right. Cool. Is it
an HD? Wait, does it? Is it an HD now? Why does it look different? A new episode has arrived. Lost
episode two. The new episode has arrived. Lost episode one. The show lost. All right.
Oh, why only the first two episodes? I don't understand. JJ Abrams. A new episode has arrived.
Episode pack part four. A new episode has arrived. Episode 11.5. A new episode of TV has arrived.
Episode 15.5. There's a lot of random TV shows. I just opened up a sir's wrath's torrent folder.
New game. It's like the difficulty. All right. This is a hard game. Players who want to enjoy
the story. Players who want to seek revenge on those who betrayed them. Players who want to
unleash their wrath. Hard. No, no. Be real. Be real. This is like, this game's like 10 years old.
Is hard too hard? Do it. Is it too hard? Normal please. All right. Hold on. Is VR Josh here right
now? Because VR Josh was one of the people that recommended this game. VR Josh, are you here?
Help me. I need to know. I trust you. I only saw cutscenes. What? What do you mean you only saw
cutscenes? You've, this is like a direct recommendation. You only, what, you watched
the cutscene on YouTube? The cutscene movie? You never even played the game? I hope this wasn't a
fucking mistake. This game is almost entirely cutscenes. Is it? The ending of this game is
locked behind DLC. Oh, great. Paramount pictures? What? Oh, what? I thought that was spelling
paramount. I was like, holy shit, that's kind of cool.
Developed by Capcom. Pretty good extensive use of the Unreal Engine 3 lighting effects.
I like that bright yellow light is in every game and from 2012 to like 2016. Wait, didn't I already
press start? I already pressed start. What? Okay. Press start again. Oh shit. Lock on fire.
What am I firing at? Is this like Star Fox?
What the fuck is that? What is going on? Did I kill it? I would like it if there was not text all of
the screen. Whoa. Rapid fire X. Am I dead? It's cinematic. Oh. All right, for a second I didn't
know what those buttons were. I was like, what is GS? It was right stick. I was fucked it up.
Is your Xbox running in 1080? It's rough on the eyes. Yeah. Yeah, it is. This game,
what's on the back of the box? Does this game even have 1080p as an option?
A 720p 1080i 1080p. It should be. No, it's not. Hold on. How do I check? Check your Xbox settings.
Settings. Preferences. What's it under? Preferences. System settings.
As you'll end your current session. Let me get to like a save point first. Sorry. No, no, no.
It's fine. I think it just looks like this, guys. No, it's definitely 1080. Because it wouldn't be
fucked up looking on my other screen. This is 1080. Guys, this is 2012 1080.
It's beat. Brightness on 200%. You know what? You know what? It might be. Let's check. All right,
coming to the QT. Is that better? It's better, right? Yeah, that's better. All right. Yeah,
the brightness was up for some reason. Good job catching that. I wouldn't have thought that.
Hold on. I got to go back.
I'm back.
The impure have defiled and scorched our land, but it is we who shall live to see tomorrow's light.
Legion of demigods, heed your priestess's words and purify your lamps and for all.
That sounds like one of the dragons in Warcraft. Let us offer Gaia the greatest blessing.
I'm sorry. Let me rephrase that. Any dragon in Warcraft.
This is actually kind of cool. Big, cool enemies. When do I get to play the game?
Oh, look at that. I want to be that demigod. This is the game. No, it's not. This is not the game.
This is like the first little tutorial cinematic part of the game. This is not the full game.
I remember the health bar. This is not the game. It's the opening cut scene.
What do you mean he seriously doesn't know? This is not the game. This is the opening cut scene.
That was a pretty sick Derva Raptor. That was the exact noise. Let's go. You're halfway done with
the game. The whole game is just an E3 demo. No, the eight guardian generals.
There he is. The eight guardian generals. Asura.
I know this is not the actual game because games aren't hard. This is not hard. This is
not a game at all, actually. So how could it be hard?
The game won't register how fast I can do it. Sorry, guys. What is going on?
Apologize.
Nice. Oh, nice. You're at level two. Nice. Level two. Here I come.
Go.
Why are we just all sitting in a Google Hangout? Don't we have Earth to save? I don't understand.
Okay, there's supposed to be eight generals. I think that's like 12.
The music's too loud. I can't even hear what he's saying.
They made the music too loud. Remember, you just triggered my Google Home.
Get your Google Home away from the speakers of your computer.
Can you hear that sometimes? Dude, what the fuck? Alexa just started responding to me.
Is Alexa in your headset? No, put Alexa in your fucking living room and turn the volume down.
Not in your office. No, office in quotes.
It shows how serious we are about winning.
This game looks fucking dumb. Okay, this game was $60 when it came out. I have no idea how much it
is now. I really don't know how much this was. It might still be $60. I have no idea. All right,
we made it to the impurity level. Holy shit, wait, did the Earth just turn into a monster?
Well, we were not prepared for this. Okay, we're getting a commercial break.
Yes, this is actually the anime has the commercial break. All we needed right there was a voiceover.
Here we go. Am I going to float around and shoot things out of my eyes or whatever it is?
Oh, metal. Full metal alchemist.
The worst part about those is it says it twice. You don't need to say it on the return,
especially when you're watching a repeat of it for a DVD or on Netflix, whatever. And it goes
full metal alchemist, full metal alchemist. It's like you don't just cut that second one out.
Like where's the quality control? This is the longest opening ever.
What's your business?
Are there levels? This is a third person action game? I think, no, it is, right? How long is this
game? Wait, wait, wait. No, this is not it. This is like a third person Bayonetta kind of game,
right? Like devil may cry. Yeah. No, he really believes that. No, I do.
No, this is. Oh shit. In 16 years of playing games, I've never seen anything like Asura's
wrath is the quote from IGN. That doesn't mean good. That doesn't say this is very fun to play.
It means it means it's it's different dot dot dot dot. Interesting. It's interesting.
And all the stuff in the back of the box. Yeah, there's no, I don't know what I did.
I'm going to give it a chance. No, I'm not going to. This is what we're doing.
16 years of playing games. What? Am I dead? All right. You can take that quote in 16 years
of playing games. I've never seen anything like this. It was so bad. It's the worst game I played
in 16 years. That quote could be like, in all my years, I've never seen anything so bad.
This game is good. I know it is.
What troubles you? Wait, Asura is a street fighter character.
I could not kill it. No one can kill Vlytra. You should be grateful you were able to subdue it.
We have suffered more casualties than ever, but it will not be back for a while.
You should rest. Asura. Due to General Asura's efforts, Vlytra has subsided.
No, he's Asura's in-street fighter. Confused.
The costume.
Soon you will get to play a video game. Episode one.
I got an A. I'm good. New concept art has been added. War of creation.
A new video has been added. Episode one. All right. All right. Let's go.
Episode one of Germacraft has been unlocked. Episode one. Coming of a new dream.
Short interludes in between the episodes are displayed to further explain the story.
All right. Let's go. Congratulations, Commander. We have once again succeeded in suppressing.
That means nothing, and time will be back and pose an even greater threat than today.
That vile beast destroying will be more troublesome than I had anticipated, and
who would have thought that Helion Asura would be the one to quell-
That was only possible because we have a comic book in- all right, so the first part of the
game was an interactive movie, and now the second part of the game here is a comic book.
The third part of the game will be playing a video game. It was only possible because
they had aid of the priestess. Okay. Yes, his daughter Mithra. We might very well owe our
victory solely to her. The priestess proves to be more useful than Emperor Strata himself.
Okay, perhaps I said too much. No. Well, yes. Yes, you have. Just a little bit.
Okay. All right. Can I have like an earpiece while I fight that, like, you can tell me the
rest in my earpiece? Hmm, arcing the power. Her power will be a vital step in acknowledging our-
Indeed, her ability to amplify mantra is quite remarkable. You would never guess that mindless
brute to be her father. I suggest we intervene for the priestess's sake. He is a potential
danger to our plans. Not just yet, he can still be useful to us. Haven't had any new info from
For now, we must concentrate on completing the karma fortress as well as finding more efficient.
Give it a chance. Hold on. Just give it a chance. This game's only like four and a half hours long.
Just give it a moment. Just wait a minute. Without that, first assured commander, I have
already devised a plan for it all, including the priestess. Just skip the filler episodes.
This is not- Okay, episode one is not a filler episode. If episode one is a filler episode of
your TV show, holy fuck, you did it wrong. Very well. Perceive his plan. Failure is not an option.
Priestess Mithra lent her power to the Shinkoku army and all of Gaia rejoiced at the victory over
Vlytra. But this time- What happened in episode one? For in the shadows of victory, the wheels of
betrayal had already been set in motion. One that would shake the very foundation- Is this a preview?
Did this game come out? No, it didn't. It's the- I didn't skip anything.
Go to the next episode. It was an episode one recap? Skip the previews. It's going to spoil things, okay?
The day after the defeat of V- whatever. How do I get QTEs to walk and like,
shake hands and wave and shit? See, no one's ever went full fucking absolute QTE. I want a QTE where
every button is me. I have to press A every time I take a step. Like, I have to do QTEs right now.
And if I fail, I have to start the whole thing over. Asura! Oh, that's- that's- that's wife.
Father! All right, easy. It's like tripped three times. You're safe. I am.
She failed the QTE. Asura, the emperor summons you. He awaits your presence in the throne room.
I wonder if he's going to present you with a medal for defeating Vlytra. She's right. You
mustn't keep the emperor waiting. All right. This is like an android or something?
These fucking frames. It's 2012 1080p, don't you know? They cared so much about having a huge
resolution. Games- the Xbox 360 couldn't run this shit at like more than 20 frames a second,
but it was like 1080p. Having a game at 720 or like 480 was like, no, no, no, no, no, no,
excuse me. Don't do that. Ugly. Oh shit, it said press A. I pressed B. Oh fuck. These are hard.
What'd you do? Everybody's failing QTEs.
Uh, all right, so they think I did it. It's the- it's the classic I didn't do it,
but I have- I have blood all over my hands, so it has to be me. That's classic.
Understand what's happening. Still, part one. What episode is this? Wait, episode two,
part one. Episode two, betrayal and vengeance of part one of episode two.
It wasn't me. Why do you have to have anything named after me? Episode two, part one of episode two.
Episode two, part one of episode three. Here we go. Gameplay. Press B attack.
That was pretty fun. Just do heavy attack. It's easy.
The FPS. Yeah, don't you know? In stunning 1080p. Graphics absolutely stunning.
Basura's wrath. Basura's wrath. I think the rule- the moral of the story here is don't ever,
like, touch anyone. That's- you know what I mean? Like, what- what are they- what are they- what are
they dead? Do they have your blood on your hands? She just came up behind and, like, put her hand on
her back. What if she was dead and you had blood all over your hands? Don't fucking ever. Always
make sure the person's alive first. That is- kill this guy? Oh, that's kind of cool. Oh, well, I
thought- I thought A was dead. Do I have a health bar? Can you die in this game? Oh, perfect. Perfect
QTE. I won. Dude, he got one. That's one of the eight. You know what the best part about
full sprint close-up run is in any form of video? Your- the suspension of disbelief is if they cut
to, like, he- he's, like, in another country, it's like, oh, okay, that makes sense. Oh, don't touch
her! Don't go- don't- no, no, no, get away! No, no, you idiot! Didn't you just learn anything?
You! Who did this? Oh, shit, it wasn't me! This- I swear! Have you learned nothing? QTE her back to
life. I don't think that's how this works. Who's that? Hold on. Isn't this, like, the exact story
of God of War? The exact story. Didn't this- didn't this happen in God of War? Kind of.
Awesome. Yes, play that. But wha- why are you in there? You can't see with that on. Why would you
put that on? Yeah, necessary for civilization. Uh, not that concerned about the guy that can't see
right now. I can't see anything. I could throw a rock at that guy's head and it would probably
knock him out and I could beat that guy. Not even eye holes. I don't know why I'm thinking-
I'm looking way too much into that one. But really, that's just a big piece of metal covering your
eyes. I didn't fail with my QTE. I'm going over the edge. Next Smash Brothers character?
Oh, he's already in season three fighter. He's getting zapped back to level one.
What? Can't I fly? Wasn't I just flying? Just fly. You know how to fly.
I know how to fly. Well, all right, well, she's got turned into an N64 character.
You've just degraded her graphics quality. Uh-oh, that's not good. I kind of turned her into a cake.
She just turned into a cake. All right, to be continued.
Did I even have to do anything? Oh, I had to fight a little bit. Yeah.
Look, I got S. This one's hard too. Imagine playing this one. Easy.
A new video has been added so you can just watch them. All right, let's go.
You're gonna end up with zero viewers. No, I'm not. Relax.
So this is like fake about me.
Yes, this is like fake. This has been made up about me, right?
Yeah, like they scapegoated me, right?
Under the command of the great deus, they fought heroically against their brother who betrayed them
and avenged their emperor's death by sending Asura to his own. Henceforth, they became known as the
seven deities and they watch over the humans from the heavens, but they don't have a great marketing
team because pretty boring. We were the eight, now we're the seven. That's it. This is minus one.
All he has left is his wrath. Refusing to die, Asura awakens in a strange world.
Oh, it's Asura. There, a small mysterious spider. All right, all right. You skip, skip. Yeah,
we're watching the preview for the next episode, right? I don't know. I didn't... All right,
whatever. Does it really matter? Doesn't matter. Oh my god, there was a spider there. You know what
that means. Don't skip Dan's game. We're still getting opening cutscenes credits. Oh, thank god
he grabbed onto that edge. How long are you even doing that for? Episode three, hell on Nogaya.
The golden, the golden friendly spider.
I hope you guys just started to like the game.
Five thousand bits just came in from phylactery. Five thousand bits. Fifty dollars. Please play
this whole game. The boss fights are a huge, such a huge spectacle to see. I mean, we're here, so
I didn't fail this. You can't fail this. What if I press down? I cannot fail that.
Up you go. Yes, there is a reason why you must continue to climb. But thanks for the
50 dollars phylactery. We're here. I got no other plan. Man, I was gonna play Tony Hawk, but I need
a fucking hard drive, but I didn't know that because I'm stupid. That's it. Keep going. I'm
not even that stupid. I'm actually pretty smart. I'm pretty... I would say I'm like average
intelligence. I am. I am. We make jokes on this channel, but I'm... I know what I'm doing.
These are our enemies. Tutorial. The impure goma. Let's see what you make of them. Wait, isn't this
one of the seven? I already... I already know how to do this. This is tutorial two. This is tutorial
two, part two, episode two, part one. Every heavy attack causes Asura to overheat for a period of
time. Heavy attacks cannot be used while overheating. This is cool. This game is so hype. I love it.
Yeah, I see everyone is relaxed. That's because the first hour of the game is a TV show.
But while you're overheating, you can't... Yeah, you can't. Hold B to perform a dash attack.
Dude, this is just like DMC, man. This is just like DMC.
Wow, I love this game. It's just like fucking DMC 2. After pressing A, hold B to... DMC 2 was the shitty
one. Oh, sorry. I have not played one second of any of the Devil May Cry games. Not one second.
Press Y to execute a special attack when your enemy is down. Especially... Yeah, I know how to do that.
Good. I thought people loved those games. What are you talking about? You're a fake Capcom fan.
I never claimed to be a real Capcom fan. What? People love them all except DMC 2.
No. No, you're telling me I picked the one that... the one that everybody hates?
Uh-oh. Big boy. Asura can recover directly after being hit by pressing A. Recovering reduces damage
and allows Asura to quickly get back into a fighting stance. So I get knocked down
after immediately after getting hit. They have to hit the ground first. So... Oh, we missed. Come on.
Let's go. Oh, finally an evade. Now this is my game. Oh, yeah. Dodge roll.
Like, there's no way I lose now. You guys know me in a dodge roll. It's... I'm so good with a dodge
roll. Four buttons. Dodge roll. I will not have a single problem in this game.
Press the correct on-screen prompt right before an enemy attacks to execute a counter-attack.
Dodge roll, baby. Yup. Again? Here again. This game is the equivalent of somebody saying,
trust me, this show is good. You just have to get past three episodes.
Yeah, kind of. And then by the time you get to pass the third episode and you're on the
couch and they look over at you and they can tell that you're not into it, they know that they've
failed. And they're just sitting there going, god damn it, they're not into this at all. And
they should be at this point and they're not. So I'm just gonna give them an out. And you give
them an out simply by saying something like this. All right, that's three episodes in. I mean,
that's a lot of TV. Yeah, it's a pretty cool show. We can do something else. I'm gonna take the DVD
out. I'll take it out. And then they either go, yeah, yeah, that's a lot of TV. Three episodes
before. That's a lot of TV. You're right. That's pretty cool, though. That's when you know,
take the fucking DVD out and do something else. They don't want to watch the show and they never
will. Hold X for rapid fire. Oh, I actually have to aim this thing. Why can't I just do that
normally? Why would I ever punch with my fist? And then you never watch it or bring it up ever
again. And then you feel terrible because you love this show. And you're like, fuck, man, I just
watched three episodes of this show. I'm gonna keep going. And then you get like 25 episodes in
because this is like the fourth time you've watched the show. And they might come up to you at some
point in the future and be like, hey, dude, you want to watch like episode four? And you're like,
fuck, I don't want to watch the show again from the beginning again. We had a chance and now I
already went like two seasons ahead of this. Now I have to watch it again. I know. I've been there
before. Trust me, guys. You can use rapid fire to shoot it in analog aiming. Why is he teaching me
this? I didn't start. I haven't stopped. What is he shooting from? Spines on his back. That's what I
gather from this. This is a flashback. You idiot. Sorry. Sorry. I wasn't aware we were in episode
three part one of the second part of the second tutorial. Apologizing. You already said that joke.
I'm gonna say it again because it's very relevant right now. Don't apologize. I'm not apologizing.
No, I'm not sorry. All right. Inflicting and receiving damage increases the unlimited gauge.
Once it's full unlimited mode can be activated by pressing LT. Automatically activated in easy mode.
Okay. Fill up the unlimited gauge by attacking. Where am I? I wish there was a block.
Oh, why can I not lock on? Isn't LB lock on? How do you fill it if it's unlimited?
I don't know. Your guess is as good as mine. That's a lot of bar to fill up.
That's full. Now use it by left trigger. In unlimited mode, Asura's strength is increased
and he cannot overheat. But I just can keep. Inflicting damage upon enemies increases the burst
gauge. Once it's full, burst can be activated by pressing RT and unleashing a devastating attack.
Okay. I have two gauges. Higher DPS. Do you level up in this game? No wonder. I'm gonna try this.
There you go. Why the exact moment of impact increases your
synchronic rate with Asura? Do you have a high enough synchronic rate and get?
What? Get what? That's a cool sword. Is that a machine gun? That was like distant machine gun fire.
What was that?
This spider is probably worth a lot of money. I mean that is coming in jewels and shit.
Solid gold spider covered in sapphires.
Where are we now? Where am I? Where am I?
All right. All right. I get it. Not bad. It's pretty fucking fun. Yeah, it's pretty fucking
fun. I imagine that that I'm saying that while I have a crying face. It's pretty fun guys.
Play Hulk Ultimate Destruction Resonance Leaper. Well, I recommend it then. You can't just come to
the screen and be like, hey dude, why is this called Hulk Ultimate Destruction for the fucking
weed? I don't have that game. Let's go. That guy has a point. I don't have that game. Should
I get it? Is that game fun? The ultimate in Unreal 3 lighting.
You know, I could do this with the OBS sliders. In fact, I feel like I've done it already.
Do it. Unregistered Hypercam. No, it will be unregistered weed. I don't know why and I'm
going to probably make a lot of people angry with this, but I feel like that's how Twilight
Princess looks the whole time. Did I just make anybody angry? I may have.
It's not a bad game. I'm still angry though.
It's at this point where I go, all right, listen, buddy. You tell me exactly what's going on or I'm
breaking a leg off and making a million. I mean, I'm just going to stop. I'm taking a fall. I'm
taking a leg. Tell me what's going on. The next time you talk in a riddle, I'm
melting you down into a necklace. It'll be that easy. He's very angry. Did you get the DLC for
this? No. I did not.
I can't get the ending without it. Who's this? How you save the world? This place looks like hell.
This is you after Simpsons hit and run. How many episodes are there in the, I almost said show and
I would have been right, but how many episodes are in there? Part one, episode three. How many
parts and how many episodes? 13 episodes? 15 parts? All right. I was told skip the next part
because I don't, we don't want spoilers. It's 12 parts total, seven episodes. 12 parts in seven,
two episodes per part? A barren land somewhere on Gaia, the golden spider. What do you think?
It's become a tad desolate since you were here last. I can hear thunder in the distance. Can
you see the lightning? It is as red as blood. So you remember, yes, the threat of the Goma still
remains even now. Curious as to what your former comrades have been doing. Over there, have a look.
They looked at Goma. Not quite. This was the work of your own race, the demigods.
What? They now have control over the world as they do please as much as they want to.
Paraphrasing, actors do that. Changing the few words around. That can't be. A lot can change
in 12,000 years. If you don't believe me, why don't you go see for yourself? Shut up.
There's that famous Asura anger. Well then, this world shall be your playground.
After a long slumber, Asura. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. No, there's a bell in this one.
Fuck. I'm done. Somebody hits a bell and shit and it's probably very important.
All right, next episode. Bell spoiled. I'm so fucking mad right now. Fucking stupid fucking
thing. I just want to be spoiler free. Like what the fuck? Mr. God. I haven't seen like
Star Wars episode three yet. Like no, not the sequel. I'm talking about like the actual like
the prequel trilogy. Don't fucking talk about it. What's wrong with me? I'm angry. All right,
I used all my anger powers and now I'm a little slowed down. This is post anger. Oh, I have to
go this way. Don't talk to me. I'm angry. Yeah, this really is like the don't. Kids playing down
here. I remember when it used to be quiet.
They added a 5G tower too. I knew that was gonna happen. Fucking angry. God damn it. I knew that
was gonna happen. I'm so mad that we saw that.
This really is just he's very angry walking around.
That's the face that a little kid makes when they don't get to ride the ride at Disney.
Do you want some lunch? No. Do you want to insert your favorite thing that I know you love?
No, but they do get reversed. I do have a health bar. It's just Batman. It's just Batman.
It's Batman with a much, much larger window to actually walk in. This is Batman,
but the game freezes and tells you the button to press for five seconds.
Well, purification for private joji. I'll have the same line.
Destruction, destruction, destruction, destruction.
Okay, who made this? I know Capcom, but what's Capcom? Which Capcom?
What Capcom studio?
Almost dead. Why is he fighting these things?
Cyber what? Capcom Canada. Is that a real company? CyberConnect. CyberConnect 2.
Unregistered HyperCam 2. Unregistered CyberConnect 2.
All ships, prepare for purification. Didn't we already beat this guy?
All ships, release. Wait, back to back bosses. What a lucky turn to find the traitor.
All right. Whoa.
Not quite. He's on the ground though. Get him. Get up. Get the combo up.
All right. That hurts a lot. I'm actually going to die.
I'm going to build up my QTE meter. I hope I don't have to do hard.
Oh, it's all right. I'll be all right. Everything's going to be fine. Don't worry.
He's almost dead. I don't want to use my QTE thing. I almost got him.
He's on. Okay. Bonehug Crusher. Impurity level 680. It's now I have to fight a giant
elephant. Just keep getting more and more logical. What did he just do? I was eating their souls.
Did they get to go back into the bodies? Nope. Right now he's sitting there going.
Is it dead? Is this fucking thing dead? I hope so. What did I be doing?
There's always a bigger fish. We go. We do it again. Let's go. No. Next episode, we'll do that.
I'm going to be completely honest. What the fuck is the point of that?
This game's interesting. I like this game. It's actually interesting, but what is the point of
that? It's not TV. Why is it there? Pacing commercial, but there's no commercial.
It'd be funny if there was commercials, like made up products. The Seven Deities. Wisen.
What? I can do that? Shut him up.
Your wrath too? Let's go. All right. Does it dash? I can't lock on. Come on. He's on the ground. I
can't. Can I get away from that? Does it blow up or something? Does it explode?
What's that? What's that? Throw it back. Yep. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here.
Omega well, tuber voice. What? Am I doing a tuber voice? When? When did I do a tuber voice?
This guy's fucking dead. No, he is. Oh shit. He's going to come back up.
Wisen fucking sucks laughing my ass off. No, he doesn't. It's not over.
All right. I didn't think he was going to be this huge. Jesus. Okay.
I feel like it should be a lot deeper and a lot more echo.
His voice should be a little deeper.
Press B again. Do I have time to go, go let Otto in here?
Otto wants to come in here. I don't think I have enough time. Hold on. Let me pause the game.
Otto wants to come in and hang out.
And then on the next episode, they replay the last five minutes that just happened
until we get to that point again. All right. I'll be right back. All right.
This is going to introduce Terma to Jojo. Jojo's Jojo's Bizarre Adventure. New video episode four.
Old friends, new enemies. I feel like it's not long enough to have it be an episode.
Each episode is four and a half minutes. Jo, Otto, I can't. I cannot. I do not have any clothes on.
I have no clothing on. I can't turn the webcam on today. I'm sorry.
All right. Here we go. Uh, it seems Asura has returned to this world. You don't say.
Apostress, that's impossible. Nothing is impossible. It actually sounds like fun.
Oh, fuck. Redeem a wink.
I, all right. I, I'm going to have to put on clothes.
Nobody redeemed a wink. No, they did not. Oh, hold on. This is bad. I gotta,
do I really have to go? Oh, did somebody actually do that?
No, they didn't. I'm looking right now. I don't see anything. Yeah, they fucking, it's fake.
Let's say they faked it. I haven't done anything to see it. No, they did not. There's no wink.
They didn't. Oh my fucking God. What, what do I have? What do I do? I don't know what to do about
this. I'm, I can't turn away. I have to go put on a shirt. Fucking God damn it. I need to make sure
this is. You see it? This is the fucking thing you plugged in. Right one. God. Ah, my black
key is not even plugged in. Wait. Get some USB slots. No, my motherboard sucks and it's fucked
up and I have to get a new computer. Okay. All right. Here you go. You ready? Motherfuckers.
I got a haircut too. There you go. That's the only thing I have. What do you wear? This is,
this is like a suit, a suit top. I don't have anything clean right now.
I just did it. You look nervous because I don't have to. Okay. I'm going to keep this on
just in case something happens. I got to like button it up. Professional streamer.
What is this link? All right. I'm trying to watch my favorite animated television show. Okay.
What does fucking naked mean? What? What? What? What? I know. Yes. Yeah. I don't,
it doesn't matter. It's fine. Uh, I know. I'm not showing this on stream, but that's fine.
Here we go. I'm going back to the game. Yeah. I know my audio wasn't synced
because I'm playing an Xbox game. Joe Otto. No, I can't. Is nothing but a speck of dust
of the past. Indeed. Our power was nothing compared to what we are capable of now.
Joe Otto. I cannot sh- Okay. I'm going to be completely and totally transparent with you guys.
The reason why I can't show Otto is for very specifically. I don't have a shirt on. I have
a suit fucking jacket on and I have a pair of shorts on that. That's it. I can't, I cannot
do webcam right now. So I can't do that. I'm not prepared for this. Put on a shirt. I don't have,
I don't have any shirts. They're all being in the laundry room. This is bullshit. No,
I can't even prove this because I'll get banned. No. Well, all right. All right. That's it. That's
it. Who cares? I'm just going to play the game. That's what you're here for, right?
No, no, no. This game sucks. I don't like this game. Where is this ultimate Shrek Hulk game?
Okay. I think there was a time when we had to actually exert effort to purify one large goma.
Oh, how pitiful we all once were. How shall we proceed, my lord? If it pleases you,
I can depart immediately to purify him. I've already sent Weizen. Let him take care of our
old friend. I already beat Weizen. That's if you don't know. I can imagine the look on
Asura's face now. He hasn't the slightest idea how powerless he is right now.
We like Fortnite. Well, good. I'm glad you do. You'll never see that channel on this. You'll
never see that channel. You'll never see that game on this channel. Whatever.
I think you'd be surprised to explain. There are no guarantees in battle. Nothing is impossible.
Ha ha ha ha ha. We like Fortnite. Play it, old man. You play it. You have 11,000 subscriptions
and can't afford a shirt. What? You want me to go buy a bunch of fucking expensive shirts?
Why? Go buy a bunch of expensive shirts. No. What? Why would I do that? I have like eight Star
Wars shirts and like two blazers and two and like four shorts. They're fine. And I have like a
couple of nice shirts. I have some nice jeans. You want to go spend like 600 bucks on like a nice
button up that I'll wear once a year? No, I can wear my 12 dollar Star Wars shirts every day and
not have to spend a thousand dollars. All right, here we go. Do I have to hold up? Oh, this is
use left stick to drag the reticle over enemies to lock on press wide release all the blasts
at once. The more lock-ons you have, the more powerful the blast will be. Is that it? I actually
like this game. It's fun. Just go. It's easy. I was reading chat. Sorry, not going to get a perfect
now. You can fail. This is just shadow of the Colossus, but far less buttons. All right. I'm
getting hit. All right. Yeah, I'm getting hit. Nick Donald's of the Colossus. Oh, dude. The
best part about that is I was a little too deep down in the dirt and he didn't even,
he didn't depress it down any further. So I was fine. I was too deep down in the rock. This was
loud. She suffers and to bring about like a shitty DJ, get like four buttons to the DJ pauses
all the music that does that. And then turns the music back on where it left off six arm.
Oh, I can actually hit. Wait. Oh, he's attacking. Okay. I thought he was wicked far away. I thought
he was like a thousand meters away. I thought that was him. Go super damage. I'm not going to
chat right now. Let's wait and do this. I throw it back. There we go. There we go. Throw it back.
First, we demand attention. Streamer goes on coke and loses all clothes.
This still exists. Can we end this? Oh, I thought I was, I jumped. Oh my God. Oh, fuck. I'm going to
die. Okay. I can't, I can't get hit anymore. How do I dodge this shit? I'm dead. I got disconnected
from Xbox. Why? What the hell did I do? Throw it back. Throw it back.
All right. First. So burst is just go into a cut scene and continue. Spin it around.
Come on by his fingers. Throw. Here we go. Ooh, that was quick. That was weird. That slowed down.
Okay. We're good. I can't hit it that fast. It's not registering when I do it too fast. See,
I'm pressing it a million miles per hour. You guys know how far I can do that.
It doesn't know. It doesn't register some of them. Please explode. Explode. I got this laser on.
This thing is so hot. I was waiting for him to do a big breathe in like, and you think you can beat
a god? And that asteroid like sucks into his throat. That's probably what would happen.
That, I mean think about how powerful that breath is. You have a phase three. It's even bigger.
I am an absolute unit. Hey, we'll see you on the next episode. He never stops growing.
What do you, what do I do about this now? The guy's as big as the three or four planets.
Gongenweisen. Holy shit. He set up like a pull shot.
Oh, that's a pretty big finger. That big, that finger is the size of like New Hampshire. We've
got to be careful. Stop. Stop. Let's go. Oh God. And it's hot too.
Holy shit. All right. This game just increased the full letter grade.
It wasn't me. I have decided to save. Nice bit rate. Great rebirth. Why do I have,
why is my memory in like 1200 up? Bro, come on. I can do it faster, but it won't register a lot
of them if I do it too fast. I'm doing it so fast. What? Oh my God. Which way, which way do I go?
I was going the other way. Oh, the sad part is we lost the entire Western hemisphere because of
that. Hey, look, there's your cool explosion. Did I just destroy earth? Why are you here?
Is this a spider? Do you even know what you want? You have already failed once at living.
You are a fool. Next time. Do not come back. Who is going to repair my auto mail?
Total rank C. Oh, sorry. I got a B. Sixth armed Azra Asura.
Concept art. New video. New achievements. Cool. Next episode. Let's go.
Robin Atkin Downs. Yeah, he is in this game. Episode five. Hello, victory. Impossible. How
could Wyzen have lost to him? He has brought shame to the seven deities. In all honesty,
I'm not surprised Wyzen was the weakest among us after all. He lost the moment he believed that
size equals strength. So we're going to have to do the thing that Asura did to him. We just have
to shrink to like one thousandth his size. There's going to be like a tiny ant boss, right? I would
assume. In any case, the real problem is the fact that fat idiot wasted a significant amount of the
mantra, an amount that took us so long to accumulate. That fool. Our cause will not waver because of
something as trivial as this. Who cares about the cause? I'll kill him for fun. Not so fast. A large
coma has appeared on the surface with Wyzen gone. I need someone to handle it.
And have someone handle it. I only follow what my blade thirsts for.
Everybody in the room, their eyes just all rolled to the back of their fucking head.
Oops. While you two were arguing, Yasha went after Asura himself. He, he, he.
That could be fun to watch. After the defeat of war. No. We're just going to get boss, boss, boss,
boss, boss. End of the game. That's so funny. They're all just going to come one by one and die.
In extravagant fashion. This one's got to take a few steps and like walk into a sign.
Next time. His head just rocks back. Just like, ba-boom. It hits him like in the mouth a little
bit too. It's like really bad. You know when somebody like really actually walks into something
and it fucks them up. Like they hit someone like the face, the mouth. What? Asura, why have you come
back? Okay. This is my brother. We were, we were, we were at a mall. Hold on. This is like funny.
We were at a mall and we were, I don't know why I'm thinking about this right now,
but we were walking together and I don't know what happened, but there was a sign,
you know, like in the mall, those signs that the little stand up signs with, it's like a
rectangle that's in this little metal frame and it's just on a single stand.
Do you guys know what I'm talking about while they have those? It's just a single stand sign
that's up at about like four or five feet tall. All right. So we're walking around and there was
a poster for a Goldie Hawn movie. Goldie Hawn movie. I don't know which one it was. And it was,
it was like, Goldie Hawn was in the middle and there was other two other people next to her.
And she was like just sitting there and he was like, hey, look, we should go see that movie.
And he was just making like a joke, let's go see that movie. But he wasn't paying attention
in front of him. He just, boom, like rocked into this sign. It was fucking crazy. I have this
memory burned in my brain forever. It was like, it was just, I haven't thought about this in like
25 years, but he was pointing and going, hey, let's go see that movie. And then right when
he got to the V in movie, he just like, his head just rocked. He was fine. The thing didn't weigh
that much. It was just kind of, it was just, it was just like ridiculous. Oh, it's not like a joke
or anything. Like it was just, I have that burned into my brain forever. And I'm like seeing it
again. He failed the QTE. No, he didn't fail the QTE. He was reading chat and wasn't paying
attention. That's a silent film joke. No, I'm just, now I keep seeing it. It was like a cartoon.
All right. I'm not going to pay attention. I don't have any arms.
Avenge your wife's death. I can't even fight this guy. It is pointless to resist.
She's the Travis voice. Am I supposed to lose? Just dodge? This guy just sounded fair.
Fuckhead. Stop making me laugh. I keep seeing my brother walk into the sign.
Avenge your wife's death. Take back your daughter.
Watch it. All right, he's got to dodge. I just think he's walking off.
Dodge and then go at him. I'm going to fucking attack him.
Wait, should I dive kick him? I'm going to dive kick him. That's worse. Wait, I can do that.
Avenge your wife's death. Take back your daughter. You got a big Buddha.
It is pointless 12,000 years ago. That was your fate. Leave it at that.
Thanks for you in this world. What? I can't do it. All right, almost good. I got it. I got it.
Do I dodge?
Don't kill me. Don't kill me. Oh, there it is. Get out of here. Did I miss? You can miss.
You can miss that. I thought it was just press RT and watch a movie.
What do you mean it was two? No, it wasn't. Let's go. I get it. I got it now. I got it. I got it.
Avenge your wife's death. Take back your daughter. Come on. Do the swing. Two swings.
Nice. Good combo. It's pre-recorded. No, it's not. Stop saying that. Don't say that.
Yes, I am. I used to be one of you. Wasn't I like number eight?
Oh, shit. All right, here we go.
Burst. Come here. Come here. Come here. Oh, shit. I got it. I think I missed.
Look at you. You cannot hide. Oh, then I won't be able to see.
Whoa. I mean, that's a pretty, that's pretty, come on. That's like a, that's a boss move.
I'm not even worth avoiding because they don't hurt you. Damn. Oh, boy.
Oh, fuck. Did I get it? Pretty sick T-pose. Oh, no. I got to be careful.
Run. I can avoid that. Oh, fuck. What's he doing? Run. Quick hit him with a visceral attack.
Oh, I got greedy.
Can I fire? Oh, what's happening? Yeah, I keep trying to do it, but I can't. I'm not getting it
right. All right. Don't fuck this up. No. Sorry. I got it. Shit. Please don't. All right. Don't use
it. Not yet. It's not a, no choke. Here we go. I said, all right, hopefully this guy didn't
raise to be 5,000 times the size. There is nothing you can do as priestess. Mithra has
dedicated herself to the salvation of our world. You should be proud. What did you say?
Hey, be proud. Oh, he's making me angry. He's devoted to the cause in order to save the world.
I'm going to say the thing that makes you angry again. You motherfucker.
Boy. Lava. Did I put it on? Can I just like worm my body over there and slide it on my face? Does
it do anything to me? Is it like putting the mask on in the Jim Carrey movie?
As is your temper, but he's ugly before the cause.
He did the, am I cut in half? Do not return again.
Still getting credits for this game. I think I know who wrote the game by now.
Witness the salvation of the world from the depths of Naraka.
Bad ending. Yeah. I mean, I could say that thing that everybody says, but
does this turn into kingdom hearts? Where's the goofy? Where's Donald Duck? Where's Mickey?
Presented by Capcom. Coming up next on the next episode of Asura's Wrath. That was part one.
Part one is its own season of TV. What's going to happen is it's going to open up the next one and
it's going to be like, I'm going to start slow and you're going to hear, oh, you're kidding me.
We're going to get a full recap of what happened in the first part of part two. We're talking like
potentially 10 hours of gameplay shown in about four minutes. And they do that in kingdom hearts
too. They, they like showed, they just like skipped the whole portion of the game, right?
Clip that one. Why? Is that bad? I mean, probably. We're singing 2020. Don't bookmark it then.
All right. This will be the second time we've taken your father from you. Won't it?
When is the half life stream? I've never said I was going to play half. All right.
Why do you put words in my mouth? I said, I wasn't going to play halfway. I was.
What your most used dance on playing halfway. I don't think I'm going to play. I'm not going
to be playing half life on this stream. Hey, so when's half life? I, this will be the second
time we've taken your father from you. Won't it be? He didn't even know what a Lambda was.
When this is all over, you'll have the right to take my life and I will accept death. Gladly.
It's going to be tomorrow. No, it's not. I guess I've played half life like six times.
I'm not playing half life. No, I don't want to play half life. I'm not playing half life
too. It makes me want to puke. It makes the boat level makes me sick. It's a really good game.
But for now, you will have to wait. Just watch this episode with me. It's the only way we need
your power. The world needs it. Alitra is constantly unleashing Goma upon the world.
If we do not have mantra to fight against them, there is no hope for civilization.
Your power to amplify mantra is our sword and shield. We cannot bring salvation to Gaia
without you. Half life, half life, half life, half life. Let's go. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Sura, why do you choose not to listen to reason? Mithra's power is essential to the cause. Once we
defeat the Alitra, Mithra and the world will be saved. Stubborn fool. 500 years later, 12,000.
1000. It's a long time. Part two. Rebirth. Stubborn fool won't play half life.
God damn it. Wait, we did this? We're doing this again?
We meet again. You are a demigod just as they are, you know. If you can accept their actions,
perhaps you should let go and allow your soul to become one with Gaia again.
Hey, can you, can you, can you bite me? Do you choose to move forward?
I feel like that would be beneficial to me. Just bite me right in the neck.
This is exactly why your soul will never belong to the Goma nor the seven deities.
There is a great power hidden in you. No, not even Spider-Man. Just, I feel like this thing's
powerful. Just like, bite me. And like, inject venom into my bloodstream.
Remember. If we're two hours into the game and I get another
part two tutorial, it's gonna be tutorial two. They're gonna introduce a mechanic or something.
Or maybe not. What's the point of this? Kill, kill, kill, kill, kill. This is the beginning.
It's elephant fall. This should be fun. What happened to the first hour?
I got framed for something I didn't do and then they made lore based around how bad of a person
I was and how evil I was. Those people have since taken over the world and now I need to
come back and take it over and tell everybody that they're bad people, I think. I don't know.
I think there's a telegraph system.
Merrick, Merrick, Merrick, Merrick, Merrick. Got it. Why am I fighting the elephant? Oh, why not?
Which leg? What? Yeah, this is some entity. This is an entity. These are entities.
They're called gomas. They're apparently, I don't know, evil or something or they're part of the
world, the inside the world, inside the crust, to the earth's crust, the core. There's like lava
enemies and I don't know. We'll find out. They're demons. Yeah, the demons that live inside the
planet or something and we're trying to stop them from coming out and killing everybody.
How am I gonna get hit by that? I'm so pissed off about that one. Let's end this.
This time, shoot it. Wait, you mean shoot it? Can I just shoot it? Oh, what a good idea that is.
No, look, I can't shoot it anymore. No, it's it. Here we go. Let's do the worst. One tusk down.
All right, now what? Part two. What's that? Holy shit. Okay, well, that happens very quickly.
It goes up and then, okay, here it comes. It goes up and then, no,
it does it two times in a row. Oh, fuck. Oh, my God. I don't know the timing on it. I'm gonna die.
Oh, damn it. I think it doesn't. This one's easy to avoid.
Can you just pick a side and just get away from that side? Oh, my fucking God. Yeah,
you just have to get away from the side that it's on.
All right, that's not building. That doesn't build any pressure. What the hell am I trying to do?
What's that? Oh, God. What the fuck? Oh, it's a dodge through it.
This game had an anime, did it? I just lost 50% of my HP.
This is what happens when you read a chat room when you're supposed to be playing a game.
God damn it. What am I streaming right now?
Oh, my God. I'm gonna die again. Come here. Does this do extra damage? No.
Press LT. Yeah, I can't like hit him or anything. Do you want me just to punch him? No, I mean,
I can't. Where's he going? Oh, my fucking God. Jump? It's hard to tell which side he's gonna pick.
Oh, God. Here we go. He's gonna do the stupid beam. Do it twice? Stay in the middle?
I can't get hit. I can't get hit. I can't get hit. I can't get hit. I can't get hit. I can't get hit.
Don't get hit. Don't get hit. Don't get hit. Don't get hit. Don't get hit. Don't get hit. How long is
it gonna be for? How long are you gonna do this for? What's this? New move? All right, come on.
Just don't get hit. Stop. I'm fine. Which side is he gonna do? I don't know.
What's this? Oh, come on. Shoot him? I can't. I can't. Come on. All right, dash. Dash at me.
Burst. What the fuck just happened? Oh, yeah, this cut. It's too nerve-wracking.
Forgot they were QTEs. No, I didn't forget. I just wanted to see what you guys were saying.
Why do I miss those? Because I look to the left and there's a chat room over here.
And I go, what did somebody say? Whoops. Missed the QTE.
Control yourself. Where did this guy even come from? Immersing oneself in battle like that.
Well done, Asura. Now that you have something to protect, why are you so full of rage?
Perhaps. Just a massive hand. That is exactly why. Something to protect? Nonsense.
The only reason one needs to fight is the fight itself. That is so like you, master.
They all have big hands. We have cleared this area of Goma. Let us return to Shinkoku.
Right. Oh, why are they all elephants? Is there something in the lore as to why they're elephants?
Your father has returned. Welcome home, dear. Thanks. Giant enemy baby.
So that is what he must protect? Yes, though you may not understand why.
Easy. Whoa. I'm sorry, I'm just so angry. Please take it. Oh, and he just turns around and just
fucking punches a wall. Brother. Looks scared of her. Then he should pacify her. Him? That's
an abrupt cut. Not bad, Asura. That uncontrollable rage of yours suits you well. See what I mean?
And I didn't do anything. You just told everybody to move.
And I said move, but they didn't. Asura, join us. Should we work together? We could more effectively
exterminate the Goma. Test me. You are aware of Mithra is the only suitable vessel to become
priestess. Praise her with care. Incompetent as you may be. Well, now I know. You certainly are
incompetent. I wager that is one of your more charming features. At least we know now the
source of the flame that burns in your soul. In other words, you... Stop. What was that?
I can't kill the spider. Hey, Lois, remember that time I fought the Goma?
What do you mean? That was kind of funny. Hey, Lois. Minus two family guy jokes. No,
come on. That's like kind of funny. That's kind of funny. That's kind of funny. You got it.
That was humorous.
I just grab the end of his web and like slurp and like suck it up like spaghetti.
Every time we're down here, I talk about killing this thing. I don't know why.
That's kind of fucked up. You were in the lava. Yeah. I mean, you can just leave me like that.
Father's duty, episode seven. Is that part of the elephant or what? Yeah, maybe it was.
Here we go.
We continued Omega Lo. Omega Lo.
Usher is residents thousands of years earlier. Seems that you made quite an impression in the
last battle. Is that so? Pithra was praying for you the whole time. You hear my prayers, father?
I did. I felt your presence with me and thought of you the whole time.
So you didn't think about me at all? Hmm. No, I meant, oh, father, hee hee hee.
General Osura, the next priestess has been chosen. What? General Osura's daughter Mithra is to be
priestess. Congratulations, General. I can do better than that. I will not allow it. Father,
but why? I will not have you become a tool for war. If it will give me the power to protect you,
I will gladly become priestess. But Pithra is gifted with the power to save the world.
She could be the key in eradicating the Goma. Shut up. Osura, wait. Where are you going?
Can't see that. Can't have that be spoiled. Animation and touch up. Cyber Connect 2.
I just want to see Cyber Connect 3, 4, 5, 6, 7 to all different episodes.
No, I can do it too. You know I can. You know I can do that exact thing that's happening right
now. You know it. I know I can do it. You know I can. You know I'm capable of it. I'm having,
I am using a lot of control right now to not do that. I want to do it so bad. If it was me alone,
I'd be doing it over and over again for the next hour. If I wasn't on stream, I would seriously be
sitting here just going, and it would do it for an hour. And then Kim would come in here and be
like, what the fuck are you doing? His arms are back. Oh, don't be such a baby. Oh, I'm a squirrel
back. No, they don't. That's one of my favorite lines from any video game cut scene. It's delivered
so perfectly. Wait, what? Oh, now look what you did. Now you woke up the baby. And how long it
took. You know how long it took to get them to go to sleep. Wait, wait. All right, bye.
Is that supposed to be a laugh? I think that was a laugh.
Oh, we have forward progress in this level. This is an arena.
There's somebody behind me too. Get, get. This is the Sonic Unleashed Werewolf levels.
God damn it. Why did you have to say that? That is so accurate. Why did you have to
ruin this whole game for me? Don't hit the baby. Watch out. Watch out for the Mario.
Get up quick. I know a lot of you thought I was going to fail that on purpose to see what happens,
but no, I want the good grade.
Jesus. Goma Squasher. Hey, you go first. He's like a turtle. Here we go. Goma Squasher.
Uh, does it run? Kind of. Pistols? Yeah. Can I fire? Can I shoot? In the head? Yep.
Oh, it's uh, Contra. Contra for the Super Nintendo. Contra for the Super Nintendo.
The turtle, when you hit the head and the head goes like quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack,
quack, quack, quack. Holy shit, it's the same thing. Yep. We're working as a bunch of them.
The stomach? All right. Yeah. Turn into the stomach.
Back it up. Oh, that was probably exceptionally painful. Oh, does it keep going around? No,
we're good. Right in the head. Out, out, out. I don't know what that means. What's that? Adds?
Yep. I just summoned him, man. Just summoned him. Charge. Let's kill your own friends.
Oh, fuck. Take his ass. Sorry, he's doing spin. No, he just double tapped. Don't triple tap me.
All right, I'm good. What are you gonna do? Charge? Nope. All right. Settle down.
LT is immunity? Is it really? Can you do a tail whip? Oh my fucking god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
Oh my god. What the fuck happened? What have I done? I almost got instantly killed.
This. Wish I knew that. I'm scared of doing anything.
Oh, tap, tap, tap, tap. Oh my god, my nose is so itchy.
Do a charge. The frames. Yeah, they're not very, they're not very good, are they?
The console, this is on Xbox 360.
But what language are they speaking?
Stop praying. This is pathetic.
English? Septentrion.
So this is the reason for the unusual mantra concentration in these parts.
Guys on a single wheel? Oh, okay. The magical wheel. Of course it is.
I wonder what that guy's fight's gonna be like.
Oh, it's happening right now. I don't have to wonder anymore. Boss? No? No boss?
Uh, why'd you kill that guy? What? What?
This guy's playing black and white.
That's his, that's his creature. He turns around and he's like, stop doing that!
No! Puts a leash on him. I had that, oh god damn it, I had the destruction leash on!
The hologram really. He even pointed too, he was like, point. This little baby. Rock music.
There's the fucking machine gun sound.
Some battle going on somewhere with guns.
I know what it is. There are no guns in this game, it just sounds like it.
Can you please switch to the Japanese voiceover? It's better.
He's already become invested in the characters while they speak up.
I dodged it.
Base.
Oh, I hit him with that too. Oh, what?
Oh shit. Where is he? Sonic unleashed.
Can't get over it. Why did that person have to say that?
Oh fuck, that hurt. Oh wait, there's another, there's like another mini-boss here.
Oh shit. Sorry. Oh boy. What the hell's going on? I'm invincible though.
What is it? What is he saying? What is he doing?
You go tell who's responsible for this. That I'm coming for him.
All right. Can I not do it? What if I don't want to? Can I not do it?
Now what? Uh oh. She's learning. That's not good. I'm not putting a good example out.
She's gonna rock in her hand. Holy shit. She's learning from you. You're the god.
You're the reason humans are like this. No, I'm not. Stop, stop, stop. Enough. Use two hands.
Take more leverage that way. Black and white too sure is weird. Where's the baby? Yeah, where's the
baby? You, you let me. Baby got League of Legends ganked. I don't, I kind of, I kind of know what
you mean by that, but I don't at the same time. I don't know what that means. Sort of. I don't know
what that means. I mean, I kind of do. Not really. Villager B. Episode 8, willing sacrifices. All
right. Let's go. Village on the outskirts of Shinkoku. Here within this stone lies remains
of the fallen demigod who defied the seven deities long ago. He succeeded in killing one of them,
but at the cost of his own. Following the divine battle, the remaining deities
abandoned this land declared a curse for all eternity. It is believed the fallen demigod
continues to watch over this land, but the Goma rarely appear in these parts. For this reason,
the villagers enshrined his remains and worship from afar, who do not dare approach the shrine
out of fear. There was one little girl, however, who regularly came to the shrine and offered
flowers to the fallen demigod. Long ago, when she and her father went off to a nearby village,
they were attacked by the Goma. Just when they thought their lives were over, the seven deities
came from the heavens and purified the Goma. The little girl was deeply relieved that the deities
have saved them. However, the deities did not only purify the Goma and thus many humans were
caught in the fires of their purification. The girl's father was one of those who perished,
but rather than defy the deities for their tyranny, the villagers saw it as an honor.
They rejoiced that the deities would lead their souls to heaven and gladly gave their lives.
The girl walked hopeless and full of despair until she stumbled upon the shrine of the
fallen demigod. As the old tale said, the stone had an aura of anger that the girl was not afraid.
Somewhere in the fallen demigod's face, she saw a resemblance to her late father.
Since then, the girl has been visiting the shrine to offer flowers.
Everyone did nothing but pray, but he took action.
But oh, this is not a narrator. Wait for me, I'm coming with you.
Jerma, are you the CEO of Jerma, Incorporated? No, I mean, I guess you could say like, sure,
yes, I guess. You're doing the infomercial voice. Yeah, because it's the narrator.
You, you let me handle them. Let's do the CEO. The best laid plans, episode nine.
That was pretty, that was full. God, I'm really hating skip sections. You can't skip them either.
They're getting angry. It's pretty nice to be able to get Chip and Dale to get angry.
They just had to press a button and skip the sequence. Actually not that bad. Six arms,
no? Minus two, nobody likes Kingdom Hearts. I just, I just made fun of Kingdom Hearts.
Roger, all ships commence exorcism. I like Kingdom Hearts one and two a little,
I guess. I like Kingdom Hearts one. I don't really remember to. I'm in the ship. Let's go.
I'm not the one who started this fire. It's always burning as the world's been turned.
Now, but it will burn you to ash. It's pretty much the same thing I said.
Roger, all ships commence purification.
I have to do some firing the sky.
Oh, come on. What am I aiming at here? What am I aiming at? This, these things.
Those, these ships, these ships, everything. I'm gonna watch the right side of my screen.
Aim, forehead. No, it's yeah, you're right.
Oh, no, you cannot take the full brunt of a star. That's the worst line ever.
Only if it kills me.
That's what, oh, that's what a, that was a fun movie. Who else liked that movie? Raise your hand.
Did you like that movie? Who liked that movie?
I cannot allow fear any further. He will ruin everything.
You haven't watched it yet? What?
Roger, destroy the traitor.
Marvel fanboy. It was a good movie. It was fun. It was, it was cool.
Sometimes I forget. Don't ever like anything in 2020.
Don't like anything. Oh, what a fucking consumer.
You can't like anything. You can like anything else, just not Marvel. What movie?
What movie? Some of us don't watch movies, but superheroes are lame.
No, I knew we were going to get here eventually. I just didn't know when.
Enough people liked Marvel for it now to be, ah, stupid lame.
Enough people started to watch like Captain America had happened.
Stupid, stupid, stupid. I only drank the finest of movie wine.
Reddit has ruined everything. Oh my God. I'm instantly dead.
Oh, I didn't time it correctly. Oh shit. It starts all the way back here.
All right. That's the thing with the nature of like the internet. All right. So,
back in the day it used to be, if you had a group of maybe like eight people you ever
communicated with back like 20 years ago, you had to call somebody on a landline to like
talk to them. And no, no one was going to call your landline to be like, hey,
Marvel movies are stupid. But now, there's so many opinions.
But you didn't get random prank calls. People dialing random numbers going, hey,
by the way, Spider-Man's dumb. You'd be like, who the fuck is this?
You talk to like eight people ever. Your mom, your dad, the person who lived across the street from
you and like two people you went to school with. And if one of them didn't like Spider-Man, well,
okay. Well, yeah, like simply. Now you can, you can hear from anybody on earth,
any of their opinions instantly right now. Like right now this 5,000 people here. You guys can
give your opinions on anything. And we could just have a huge, just disgusting bubble of the world
and like movies. And half of you would hate the other half because they don't like Spider-Man.
I hate the other half. All right. I can't die here. This is important.
Come on. You're a nerd. Yeah. So what?
Come here. Come here. Come here. Kill it. Kill it. Ah, still alive. How are you still alive? Okay.
All right. Now it's just you. I don't like Spider-Man on pizza. Now neither do I.
Can I build up shit with this? Are they going to keep blocking? Oh my God. He just gave me a free
kill. Are you kidding me? Oh, come on. I'm all right. Watch out. Watch out. He's coming.
Thank God. I like this. I like this. I like this. I like this.
Cookie dough is tasty. Yeah, it is. I think that's redemption troop. Colonel
Eisen. You don't. Oh, that was quick. That was really quick. I hope it's right there. Don't be
all the way back. Thank goodness. All right. It comes quick. Laser. It's a very slow laser.
He's trying to let me win. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Oh, his name is mouth. Here comes boss. Intruder detected in the mantra chamber.
All right. Is it weird that I want to eat his hair? That's weird. All right.
Those are the mortal souls that have been harvested into mantra.
These ships, send them to heaven. You son of a bitch.
What? I knew that was going to happen. How do you like your hair? Oh, I don't.
Where did these guys come from? Where did. Oh, I don't have any. It's walking on.
Come here. Come on. Come on. Come on. Don't kill me. Come on. He's dead. He is dead. Shit.
What the fuck are these things doing? I just think it's freaking me out. I think through the
explode. Holy shit. I need to hit one person. Come on. Why? What? I can't do. Why not? Jesus.
Walk to the door. What? What do you mean walk to the door? No, I have to kill this guy.
I have a preemptive burst. Oh, now I have to use burst on door.
Throw it back. Of course it's an elevator sequence. We have to have an elevator sequence.
Elevator sequences are universal. There's no health now. There's no health in this game either.
There's a spider. Yeah. Not dead. Oh, come on. I actually just get killed in one hit there.
I thought he was dead. I have to do the whole elevator again.
Skip to the boss. Not impossible. Play the game first. Who's next? Here comes one, two,
three. Are these guys stuck in the corner?
Dead? Yep. This is where I fucked up last time. I'm ready. One, two, three, drop.
Okay. I'm going to hold the super. No, I'll just use it.
Do it again. Again? How many fucking times do I have to do this?
I have to RT this guy. Turn off the game, please. Okay, yeah, sure. But I'm done.
It's the stock alarm. All right, let's go. Are you done yet? No, not yet. Is that another hologram?
Come on. Do I have the DLC? I don't have the DLC. I didn't know I needed the DLC to beat the game.
Okay, this fight's probably going to be me ripping him out and just snap his neck.
I don't think this is going to be a big epic boss fight, guys. I think I'm just going to
break this guy's neck. Oh, I'm crushing him.
Garnet him into paste. That's the plan. Oh, I actually knew that wasn't going to be a big fight.
Yeah, I just crushed his head. Wait, am I going to be broken apart again?
Finally, a use for a shitty emote. I know who this guy is at this point. You don't have to keep
telling me. Who is this guy? August? August, yeah. August? Episode nine. In the books. D.
Hey, how do I get D on top? Because I restarted, right? But didn't somebody say there were 13
episodes? I'm almost done. Let's go. 18 episodes. Well, all right, let's fucking go. We're at number
10. Number nine.
That wasn't as cool as the first one. Now, now let's not get hasty. It's in such bad taste. I'm
sure August would be more than happy to take our little care of our problem. Fine. Where is he?
What could he be doing? All right, we're going to fight August. Where do you think he is?
This next one is really, really good. Okay. This fight is amazing. This is the best part.
Well, let's go. This next one is my favorite. Oh, well, you're setting this up here. There we go.
Words of wisdom. What? Why is he? Oh yeah, I have these arms. I forgot. It's like a baby
realizing he has fingers and hands.
Then eat good food. You fight, then drink fine wine. You fight, then sleep with beautiful women.
Hell, beautiful women. That's what it means to live. It's hobbit music.
I am not like you. It kind of was. I didn't say anything about it because it's a Lord of the
Rings reference and people might be angry at me, but it kind of does. This is rated. Where's that
box? This is T for team. We're fine. What? Why? Wait, let's go. I don't fuck around. Flash? Flash
who? That's a dick move. Okay. So look around. Well, what's he doing? Who the fuck is that? Hey.
All right. What's he doing? Hey, I'll do that too. Okay. Now what are you doing?
That's pretty good cat puke. All right. What about just regular drink?
Hell, there's a different one here. What does stand up do? To show how big I am?
All right. I filled my meter. Why splash? I don't know. That's an option.
No, I'm not ready yet. I'm not ready yet. Does it keep going? This is getting worse.
I have another. I can't even move. All right. First stand up. It's burst time.
What? This was T. This is T for team. God damn it. What? Why is he naked? This just says T on the box
and it's team. Don't be a soccer mom. I didn't do anything.
They're all to depend on. That's why weisen and cow row were so weak. Don't be a soccer mom.
They are unsatisfying. Things were different before. Yes, we used to fight side by side.
Those were the days. You remember when we did this? Let's go back and find out.
Viewers went up by about 200 or 300 viewers during that segment, by the way.
Your minds are just in the gutter. Come on. What do you mean the thumbnail? That's fine.
Thumbnail's fine. The guy looking at the moon. It's not the guy. I just looked at it. I just
looked. It's not there. It's not there. No, it's definitely not. Recommended live channels. Yeah,
but you is that that's it might not be real though. He's left. Let's go this way.
Goma charger. All right, let's do it. We're in Goma with Rhino. Two of them.
Fuck. I'm gonna dodge and then do a dab punch instead. All right, good. Good.
Dude, Nintendo in chat. Hey, welcome back. All right, I have to stop paying attention to what
you guys are doing. You're losing viewers. You have to do something about that. Well,
they were here for one reason and I don't that whatever. Oh, shit. Well, I really should have
used that now. Jesus. Oh, my God. No help. Oh, here it comes. Go to kill him. What was that weird?
Okay, that was you see that turn. That was like an instant turn. Instant turn. Hopefully,
it's right there. Why is chat focused on everything but the game? Well, I think it's because
that sometimes like to do its own thing and just
they go off on their own. Hence, tends to happen because we're bored.
I'll get some like Nickelodeon gag and fucking play with it. Oh, don't you fucking dare screw
this up. Please be dead. Please be dead. Please be dead. It's not dead. It's not dead.
I almost have enough. There it is. Invincible. Burst him. You saw boobs. It's over.
You didn't. You saw somebody in a bath. A big one. That's it. Another turtle. Oh,
we've already seen the turtle. This is not a new enemy.
I got hit by it. I got hit by the end of it.
I want to get killed. Get hit in the back. Get hit in the head. It's not doing anything.
Giant enemy turtle. That's right. Dude, how the fuck am I supposed to avoid that? That seems
unavoidable. Run? He just run away. I can't dodge it.
Can I leave? Can you do something? Oh, you're not. Just jump. You gotta jump.
Invincible. Just spam. Spam. Spam. Spam. Spam. Spam. Spam. Spam. Spam. Spam. Spam. Spam. Spam.
Just keep doing that. Invincible. Watch out.
He's learning. Yes. Very slowly, but I am.
If I get hit once, I'm dead. So that'd be very, very, very sad. What are you gonna do?
Eh. Shoot him. I can't.
You can build your meter. It doesn't work. It's not doing anything. That's not doing shit.
Your other meter. Oh, the other meter. Right. Right. The LT meter. Well, in that case, let's do it.
Whoa. He just spawned a fucking rhino. Why didn't he spawn a rhino? It's all right. I have some
invincible. I'll get it. Come on. Stop spinning. Stop spinning. Holy shit. Oh my God. Oh my God.
Oh my God. Oh my God. Fuck. I need to watch the. Did I fail them both? I think I failed them both.
I keep forgetting this. Whatever. Every time there's a cutscene, I go like, yeah, I got a
minute. Let's look over here. What are you guys saying about this thing? I have to focus the
whole time I'm playing against the enemy and I look over. Hey, what are you guys doing?
How have you been, guys? It's in QTEs. It's just less points. Oh, that's all right.
All right. At least this is different. What is this? Fish. Not fair. We're fighting over who
gets to kill the giant fish monster. To be continued. Episode 11. Wow. That was a pretty
long dream. I'm going to go now. You're fighting rhinos and elephants and shit in your dreams,
man. You got to stop. You got to stop eating hamburgers at 11 o'clock. It's a boomer joke.
Will I turn 35 this year? Get over it. It's going to be more and more of that. I'm going to fucking
on. I'm trying to turn 35 in like three days. Episode 11. We actually get to fight this guy.
They say Lord August has gone off to find the fallen one. The traitor
was Lord August's pupil, was he not? Yep. You think Lord August sympathizes with the fallen one?
No. Lord August is one of the most merciless of the seven. I believe he's gone to finish the
traitor off. Where did Lord August go? Kanazuki spring. Lord August always goes there to bathe
before a battle. You guys see squidbillies, right? Who's the lady that lies down like this
in squidbillies? Earl's like wife. It's the same stance. What's his name? Hurly? Hurly. Yeah.
I wouldn't be so sure Lord Wyzen and Lord Calro were defeated. Who is to say that Lord August will
fare any better? We've obviously never seen Lord August in battle. You would not say such things
if you had. I know because I was a soldier thousands of years ago during the War of Creation.
No one can defeat Lord August. He's very well made. He's stronger than
Lord Deus. Now enough of your babble. Move it. Yes, sir. Awesome. I'm turning 21 in a couple weeks.
Do you have any good drink recommendations? Yeah. Do you like wine? Well, you don't know
because you can't drink yet. You might. Wine's good. This will do. A good red wine. It has some
good fruity deep flavors to it. Malbec is my favorite wine. Absolutely.
Vodka pineapple is also just perfect. What's this song? All right. This is awesome.
I'm fighting on the moon. Let's go. This is a great setting for a fight.
Because there ain't shit on the moon. So there's plenty of room. Okay. Well, he just destroyed me.
Oh my god. If I get hit, I'm dead. I took all of my damage at the very beginning of the fight.
That's great. What's this? Get it. Put perfect fight music. Oh, fuck. I just walked into it.
All right. Now I know what's going on. Two, three, four.
There it is. Yes, this is the hardest. Is it on hard? Is there a difficulty after hard?
Harder. Wow. This isn't too bad. It's really nice. You die in like three hits, but
it's not too bad. This probably would have been too easy on normal.
Do I lack critical information? Somehow. Why? What that means?
Okay. That's a good sign. Get it. Get it. Come on. Yes.
Again? What the fuck? What's going on? Okay. Again. Again? Dragon ball fight is kind of ridiculous.
Again?
Here comes the sword.
On the next episode. Is it going to do that to us?
As deity, the only other person August has ever drawn his sword against is you, my Lord.
Is he that powerful? Oh, interesting.
You guys. Deus means God, by the way. All right. Cool. That's my favorite comedy. I love that.
Great. They caught it. Jesus. And whoa. Jump. All right. It's time to make it all the way to him.
Yeah. Definitely. What the fuck is that? Whoa. All right. No, we're not good. We're not good.
He does it twice. Just two swings. Fuck. Oh my God. Holy shit, man. What the hell is this?
All right. Now the music's distracting. How did we see the opportunity to hit him?
Thank God. It's not the whole fight. Shoot him. Breathe. All right. Yeah. He does three.
Holy shit. What's happening? Give me that meter. Let's do it. Two, three. More, more, more, more,
more. Get in, in, in, in, in, in. All right. Fine. Just get it. All right. Don't. Don't blow this.
Don't use it. Wait till he does it before he comes over to you. There we go.
What? Oh shit. He didn't do the thing I thought he was going to do.
Don't. Don't. Don't. I just need to. He's going to dash. There it goes. To use it. No. I used to
miss the four. This is an extra long sword.
Is it going to be this big for the rest of the fight? That should be pretty cool. He's got this
huge hole. Oh God. I'm losing my arms again. What the fuck is going on? How can they still
hear each other? There's a hole on either end of that sword. They're just putting their morphoboots
in. Don't rip your blind eyes out. Then he puts his ear up to it in your
flashback. Oh, another meteor. Must be Monday.
If you can hang on for this long, just lift your body up and make it settle this forward motion.
What the hell is he going to do then? He's going to tip over and fall.
Look forward. You made it. Did I get it?
Harmless again for the second time today.
It's been 12,000 years since you've lost the arm. Oh. Yeah, that's right.
Yet you continue to fight. Anybody want a water or something?
You no longer need my training. One who stands in the end is righteous.
Can I get you guys anything? You know, I just love a black coffee.
You guys have that here? Ew, black coffee minus two.
What? If you drink coffee at a diner, I always get a question.
Why is that? Why is that? Why is it minus two? I drink black coffee at a diner.
Bad show. That's a big, that's a huge snake stegosaurus.
We lose frames here. What's going on? We're good. I think we're good.
Give it a refresh. Maybe it looks like we dropped something. I'm just walking like this.
I'm running away from her?
Should be good now. A little all over the place, but it'll be all right.
Well, turn and run the other way. This is when you turn and run the other way.
Part two, rebirth episode two. But what epi- oh no. No, no, no. That's- it's not part 11.
Part 11, rebirth episode 11. That's not correct. They got the Roman numerals there.
Viewers just jumped up like crazy. Oh, I- did we get front page?
That's a lot of people that just came in. Hi guys. This has been no raid or anything.
Is it a host from somewhere? Now they're all gone.
That's the equivalent of, um, like you called an elevator and there's like fucking a shitload
of people on the elevator when it opens. And then you just, you're just like, nah,
no one's getting off and just keep going. Just keep going. Like, oh, is this, is this our,
is this our floor? No, no, no. Someone pressed the button and there's not enough room.
Ah, whatever. Bye dickhead. A village on the outskirts of Shinkoku in the plaza.
No, why am I still alive? If I, if I had only prayed more, perhaps then they would have
accepted my soul. Why is my voice high pitched? What? My voice is high pitched? Returnable.
What? You're freaking me out. It's high? What? No, it's not. Look, look. Actually on
the front page. Oh, well, yeah, that's cool. No, that's not the right, whatever. This was
our chance to be guided to heaven. Oh, what are we to do now? We must pray. If we continue praying,
they will surely guide our souls as well. What's wrong with all of you? Why do you do nothing but
pray for death? This isn't right. I feel like I'm going to be sick. A high pitched thing is
an audio glitch. Refresh. You literally sound like a chipmunk. What are you talking about?
I sound, I'm high pitched? Just refresh your page. I need to leave this place. I don't want
to be here anywhere but here. Episode 11, Zenora on episode 12. A little while later, Baron Field.
What is that? Ah, that must be him. He's fighting in the heavens again. It can't be Agoma. Agoma
unborn from the heavens. It has to be him. I won't just wait here and pray. I have to make it there.
I have to get to his battle. A village. It's a mobile app bug though. Oh, whatever.
Few days after the mysterious explosion, I turned to stone. I just keep dying, huh?
Well, gods of death. I wink. How do you know my name? Okay, has she only seen me with no arms?
I think this is the only impression I've ever had on this person. You're so blue.
Because I didn't, I just plugged the mic in. I mean, I plugged the webcam in just to be able
to do that. I'm not wearing, you know how much I'd be sweating if I had that on the whole time?
Can I run faster? Can I trade my wink for Otto's feet? No. It very clearly says
wink in camera. It's currently 61 in Las Vegas. Yeah, but I'm indoors wearing a suit jacket.
Like, you know, I'm indoors in this one room wearing a suit jacket just sitting here.
No, I'm not doing it now. I'm doing it because it's the only clothes that people that just
came here have no idea. Why am I in a suit jacket? I just know. What a weirdo.
I'm not wearing it right now. No. All right. I have to explain this to a bunch of people
probably are here that weren't here like two hours ago. I don't have any clothes right now.
They're being washed. They're being, I don't have anything. I don't have any,
I'm literally naked right now. So I had to grab something real quick. So I have a suit jacket top
that if somebody has to redeem a fucking wink, I have to put on my suit jacket and
wink into the camera. It's a long story. That was a great image looking right. I feel like
that's how I look if somebody has like a camera. I went to their house and you bring their door
up. It's like, okay, I'm ready. And then you just look up and you're like, oh, hi.
Hi. I'm on camera up there. Hi.
Okay. That audio was full three seconds before it happened. What? I'm still out here.
I know I'm putting on my jacket. Just wait a second.
Wait, I've been live for four hours. I didn't stop in the middle of the stream to
change my laundry over. What? Oh, excuse me, guys. Yeah. Two hours ago, I had to,
I took my laundry out of the dryer. Let's see another quality content. There was not
another one. I can look. I'm going to do this. How am I going to do this? Impossible. This is
fucking impossible. How is he? How is it impossible to do this? Like, this is impossible.
Seriously. Fucking not even possible. See? Impossible. Two winks for deemed.
Hold on. Currently dealing with a fucking impossible thing here.
Okay. Thank you for that. Another wink. I'll hold on.
Hey, I know it's fake. It was real. I can smell your bullshit from a mile away.
There's been at least two real ones and I've done two. What's one of my lips? Oh, why am I a corpse?
Is this what girls do? I know it's blue, but my, why am I lips like that?
There is no need. That's that only take our gods are dead.
He's freezing. He had some food. He looked like violet from Willy Wonka. Why is he freezing?
Someone help him. God. Crack stream part two.
Who defied the seven deities.
I thought we didn't get the, I was really hoping we were going to get the
Oh, if only I had arms, why does today after 12,000 years have to be the day that I don't have
fucking arms? No, you mouth. That's not going to work. Blink was fake. Let me say something.
I've upgraded. I got my arms back. Now they have eyes on. Oh, I'm a skull girl.
Oh geez.
Okay. That was a lot. That was like just dead instantly. How many people are on this ship?
I don't have enough time to scream about anything. It's just like, oh my, no, no, no.
Are these these people in part of fight playing trauma center? I remember that game. That game
was crazy. Okay. What's the, what's the over under that? This is another head's wish.
Do it. Bullets are coming from every single missile at that.
They're half-assed until you can't count it. Yes. Good. I'm kind of getting into
bat boy territory here. It's getting there. Hey, by the way, in case you haven't figured it out yet,
Capcom made this game and cyber connect to also did this stuff in case every single we just,
let's remind you every 20 minutes. They even was a full on credit sequence where he was
floating around in the credits of going scrolling down the screen. I think it's a little late for
credits. It's animated. Okay. No, no, no. I'm sorry. You can't, you can't. And what do you say now?
What are you saying now about that? Okay. Those are the pre credits to the real credits
season two ending, please be floating. It's DLC time. No, it's not.
No, this is part two rebirth end. Oh, no, we got like, we got like five more episodes.
It's time to kill Diablo. What? I'm not even, I'm not done with this game. What are you talking
about? All right, man. Oh yeah. You got, you got to the end. All right, let's go. It's time to kill
Diablo on hardcore. Let's go. No, we have the, we're not done. Guys, I'm streaming for five
days in a row. There's plenty of time to kill Diablo. Yeah, we're good. This is part three.
Make sure to pace yourself. No, I'll be all right. We got plenty of stuff to play. So it's not like,
you know, I hope we can. I need stuff to do. Drink water. I've been hooked up to a saline
IV this whole stream guys. I'm fine. Golden spider rise and shine. Asura. I lost myself again.
No, you haven't lost anything. You've gained the power to save the world.
I could not even save a little girl with this power.
Oh, no, that's not, that's sorry. That's not him. Let me fix that. Oh, wait, you have a destiny.
I got cut off there. Somebody turned the stream off right when I got in the middle of that one.
You have a destiny to fulfill. I was going to scream really loud when it was like, I don't want
my voice to hurt. I'm streaming for five days in a row. Oh, I'm not going to do it. I'm sorry.
Oh, oh, testing. Overwhelming power surging through. What are you guys linking me here?
Kind of showing me something important. That's creepy. Freaky. What even is that part three?
Karma. Frogger for the Gameboy. You play as a frog. Dumbass. Even August could not defeat you.
Why does that make me a dumbass? Why do you keep coming back? What is it that you are fighting for?
And this power of yours? How can it surpass the power that took us 12,000 years to attain?
Needed no more heroes this week? Maybe. We'll see. We'll see. He is too much of a threat.
He must be stopped here and now. Ready the Bromastra. What was the Bromastra?
Hey, it sounds like my microphone. What was that? It's the Death Star, but this time it's made out
of a human in the shape of a human. This is the giant human Death Star. This is a cosmic entity.
You cannot do this with that one blast. Do you realize how much mantra will be lost?
All the souls that have been given for the cause. Do you not realize that this will hinder the coming
of the Great Rebirth? Then we will just get more mantra. With the mortals under our control,
our supply is endless. You guys never like put a crack in your iPad and don't get it fixed?
If we do not finish him now, there will be no Great Rebirth. Wait. I will finish Asura.
Like you did before. If we finish him now, once and for all, he can never come back.
This is made for the eradication of the Goma. This conversation is over. You will not interfere.
Bad guy, good guy, bad guy becomes good guy, good guy. I will not let you do this. He's drawn on
muscles. This dude's, he's a fat guy, but he drew on the muscles. I guess he's around all these
demigods all the time. I guess he needs to keep up, I guess. The mantra finishes loading.
I'm not going to stop this injustice.
Do I get to play as a new character now? I do.
That sound is, where is it from? It's from something. It's like a lasso or something.
From everything. Yeah.
Come here. That's a cool move. I need somebody to fight. Let's go.
Come here. Flip him down. I don't even know what I'm doing. I'm doing cool shit though.
Bad, bad, bad. Did I grab it? I didn't. Did I?
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Fake Link? I know. I think it's even a real one. Come on. What? He's not falling for it. No.
I need to play Ninja Gaiden. Ninja Gaiden, Ninja Gaiden, Ninja Gaiden, Ninja Gaiden.
Even gods are not important. Ninja Gaiden. Not Ninja Gaiden.
Whatever. Ninja Gaiden. The Brahmastra has entered the final preparation phase.
Commencing mantra charge. Mantra charge completion in T minus five minutes.
It's begun. I must hurry. I have Black here. Shooter, Black. That's a classic.
I can't hit them? Well, just take a deep breath. Go outside. Get some air. Come back.
All right, that's pretty cool. That's a cool vehicle. Where are they? Right here? To the right?
To the right? I'm going to run into them.
Watch it.
Just use it. Kill, kill. Oh, fuck. Oh, that hurt. Oh, please.
Is this a mobile game? Why are you just saying that?
You're getting me going. I think saying that because I've been playing this game for like
four and a half hours, so I think that saying that's going to make me be like,
what the fuck, dude? Mobile? Come on, dude. Give me a break.
All the break. Good. Just good. This would be a pretty cool iPad game, honestly. That's cool.
We're going to see. We're going to see it coming up in the horizon. Where is he?
Well, we got to see it and then now it's not here anymore. Come on.
I thought we were going to get a cool sequence where I ran down into his mouth or something.
Jesus. I can't even fucking see what's going on. How do I dodge that? Oh,
I'm just going to use this. Use it. Use it. Use it. Don't die. Am I using it? Going in. My health.
Well, final sequence. Am I invisible? Does this count as your anime for the year?
This is not a television show. I'm not watching this on TV. I'm playing this on my Xbox 360 console.
Not. This is a video game. Where am I going? That's a lot of people.
Am I going to get it? I didn't make it. All that for nothing. I didn't even make it.
I couldn't. I couldn't stop the migraine beam. Okay. Oh, well, he's going to. He can't do it.
Let's rewind 12,000 years and learn about why we lost. I feel like this is you guys in chat right
now. This is me and this is you guys about how you feel about this game. You're just like,
oh no. The motion. Oh, Yasha's interference has diverted the beam. Damage report. Unable to fire.
Damn you, Yasha. That was a big beam. Hey, some protagonists just are unstoppable. It's good to
see that this protagonist dies all the time and loses every fight. Cause I support it. This has
always turned into stone, burnt to death. I've died three times in the course of four and a half hours.
And one of those was 12,000 years ago. So not bad. His power of molding is infinite. He's just so
angry. He keeps coming back. It's a 13 causing him. I gotta take my jacket off. I'm starting
to sweat in this thing. I was scared that there was going to be a wink. Somewhere on Gaia. To
maintain my beauty, a little exercise is necessary once in a while. Consider it an honor to be purified
by someone with such grace. That's what I would say if any of you impure had any brains.
This is the only chance for you filth to shine. After dashing through the horde of Goma,
Serjei bows gracefully at the same moment. The Goma are ripped to shreds in the background.
At least you can die beautifully. Lord Serjei, I have a report. During our attempt to fire the
Brahmastra upon Asura, Lord Yasha interfered in deflective blast. God, guys. All right,
I'm just going to keep it on. How do you have this many points? How do you have like a million
points? Where did you get a million points? A typical of him. I knew he would show his true
colors one day. And what does he look in his face? Yes, sir. Lord Deus has summoned you regarding
the incident. Tell him I'll be right there. I got fooled? That wasn't the right thing?
I was at 14. Actually, my internet died for hours and you're still playing this.
Yeah, I'm going to play. I'm going to beat this game.
How is it such a foreign concept everybody? I'm going to play. I'm going to play this game today.
That's cool. You're still playing this? But this is what we do. Yeah, that's what I'm doing.
That's what I'm doing today. I know you're busy, but can I get a high five? Yeah, you can.
That just like scared me. Well, well, here they come. I don't know. For some reason,
people think that I'm going to get like halfway through the game and be like, oh, yeah, I'll keep
going. No, no, no. I'm going to hit the power bugs and then spike the Xbox into the ground
and watch it explode and then press a button and here's Jump King. Dude, why are you still
playing this? Get out, rip the power cord up and then press button. Here we go. Jump King.
Dude, how have you not spiked your Xbox into the ground already?
This is pretty cool. Disney ride. And they said,
you're getting the true ending DLC, right? This is not a joke. Here's money for it.
I don't know. Are you sure you don't want me to smash my Xbox? Here's $300 for a new Xbox.
Xbox 360 is not $300. It's like 60. It's like less than 80 bucks. What is this fish doing?
Does anyone have any idea of what this is actually doing? Why is it doing this?
Like, get the fuck away from me. No, he's just like, get out of here. Like, you're just in a way.
I'm trying.
Now, are you winning some? Yeah.
And because of it, three fourths of the karma fortresses mantra consumed.
Two hours earlier. That is everything I witnessed. My body's just hot right now.
Just heat is coming out of my body. But yes, I, why do you hesitate? Speak. All these years,
I have believed in the cause. But asura's mantra has proven powerful enough to rival that of our own,
that of the Brahmastra. After the blast, we lost track of his whereabouts.
We did not know when he might attack again. Lord deus.
Lord deus, I have a report to make. I used the Brahmastra on Asura. Yes, I already know.
You're dismissed. But my lord, Yasha tried to-
Dismissed!
Must I repeat myself a third time?
Who's this thing's snoked motherfucker?
Lord, forgive me.
He just sits in a chair and just goes, but you can't see, he's not any closer.
Yasha. Sir.
Power without a purpose is meaningless and worthless.
A purpose that is firm can change the impossible.
Wait, this is a boss fight right now? Stories bouncing around all over the place.
Here comes the boss battle music.
It was quite entertaining. So dedicated tennis in our fight. There is nothing more to discuss.
An absolute shitload of community subs just came in. About 32 nixums.
Sir, I want you to bring Yasha with excellent determination.
Thank you for the 20 community subs.
That's a storm.
Thank you. Thank you, Richard Nixon.
He has merely forgotten.
That's a lot of subs.
As you wish.
20 community subs. Goddamn, thank you.
Report. Large mass of Goma confirmed. They are headed for a city in the vicinity of Shinto.
These are just- these are the toads of this universe. We just figured it out.
Requesting permission for immediate purification.
Ah, a purification.
Holy shit.
How beautiful.
Uh, Snarabossus just gave 20 community subs.
That's 40 subs. 20 back to back. Thanks, guys. Snarabossus.
Can they be evolved? You can just buy a new Xbox.
Break something. I own one already. Why would I do that?
Because it's funny. It's funny.
Well, that was different.
All right, it's another elephant.
Ah, now here's the real filler episode.
We already did elephant before.
Elephant and turtle will both filler episodes.
This is elephant episode. Turtle episode.
Meter, meter, meter.
Come on. Meter.
There it is.
Oh, well, good time to use it is with two fucking rhinos.
Just focus on him.
Focus on the elephant.
I'm invincible.
Am I still invincible?
Doesn't matter.
It was so laggy. I couldn't even.
Offline. He's lagging offline.
Nice lie. Nice lie. Lagging offline.
Because that was a good, uh, small clip from the movie.
Brute ninja.
I feel bad about that.
Anybody else feel bad after watching that?
Who did that?
Septentrion, Mizar.
See how they're summoned to please their gods.
Oh, he's tossing it aside.
You're gonna throw it at me?
I thought he gave it the finger.
I thought he just flipped off the town.
What's this for again?
Before the mortals are devoured by the goma,
we purify their souls and turn them into our power.
This is nothing new.
It's the same thing you've been doing for the past 12,000 years.
You've just fought a meaningless battle.
Oh, where's their weapons?
Bastards.
One way or another, their swords muster up.
One's behavior has been more resting for them.
You ever think about just breaking fucking decap?
Gods must dirty their hands.
And then he goes to spit in his face,
but he forgets he has the mask on right there,
and it just hits him right in the bottom of the mask.
It was me.
Dead, but well, there goes another boss.
That's not a boss.
He's getting more and more Lord of the Rings golem.
Every time we see him, he's going full hollow at this point.
Hey, D, roll B, I'll take it.
It's time to roll credits.
Play an ad.
I can't even run ads on my channel, guys.
Every time I've tried, it doesn't work.
OmegaLul, no ad Andy.
Report of Asura's movements.
Search troop Captain Upala's log.
This mission to find traces of Asura's movements has proven very challenging.
The blast from the Brahmastra has set the land ablaze,
which still continues erasing any tracks Asura left behind.
Despite this, we carried on with our mission in the search of
whatever we could find.
Fortunately, we were able to find some footprints on a snow field quite far.
We followed them immediately.
After a while in the distance, we discovered one of our fleets in mid-battle with the Impure.
That is when it appeared.
A scorched black soot-covered body with the rage glowing in its eyes.
By the time we realized it was the fallen one, the battle had already begun.
Watching from afar, neither our fellow soldiers nor the Goma were any match for him.
Terrified by what was happening before our eyes, we could do nothing but hide and shiver with fear.
After the fallen had annihilated them all,
he roared out towards the heavens as if he were calling out to someone.
After that, I continued to pursue Asura.
My men were horrified and ran away, but by that time I did not care.
Asura ran onward and encountered more Shinkoku soldiers and Goma,
which he ripped to shreds in an instant.
Interestingly enough, he had no eyes for civilian demigods or humans,
and left them alone.
At that moment, Asura is headed toward the area
where Lord Serjay and Lord Yasha are conducting a purification.
What is he? What is he trying to do?
Sound of his ferocious cry still rings in my ears.
I must know what it all means.
Okay.
He's doing Obama.
Was I?
Loss.
Now what?
So this guy, this guy turned out to be kind of a chump, huh?
Wait, am I making, am I doing it right?
I thought it was like puppeting him.
Is this a Gatorade commercial?
Just let him like stand on the ground?
This is weird.
His feet are just dangling.
This is odd.
God.
Joker audition?
Kill Jester.
Why am I holding his head?
Can't they just talk?
Ah, this is weird.
I'm just Venom.
Head Squish.
We're gonna get another one.
I knew we were gonna get another one.
I knew it.
This was a matter of time.
If we get the hat trick on Head Squish's, you owe me a soda.
What's, okay, what's with this in anime?
Somebody help me here.
Everyone always does this.
They lean, they lean forward like this.
And they like lean forward and they go like this and their arm is up like this.
The game started so I have to, oh I have to, I'm playing games myself?
See, look, he's doing the, he's doing the like I've gone crazy anime stance.
That happens in every anime.
Watch.
Because I've, because I've seen like 10 of them.
Give me a second.
What the fuck are you doing?
Stay with him, stay with him, stay with him, stay with him, stay with him.
Good, I got some good hits on that one.
Watch out!
By one hit, by one fucking hit move thing.
What?
Thousand miles per hour.
Got it.
Hi, everybody.
Sorry for doing the ayaya.
Apologize every day.
Now, it would be cool if we changed sides, right?
If they flipped it and now I control, that would be really cool.
Shit, I missed it.
That's supposed to happen.
I think that's supposed to happen.
I forgot.
It's supposed to happen.
Still the same Asura.
Listen to anyone.
All right, there's the real.
Did it work?
I just ran an ad, I just ran ads.
It didn't work.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No one's gonna get any.
I swear to God, my ad profile is ShadowBand on Twitch.
I really think it is.
Hold on, let's see.
15 seconds.
Okay, hold on, here they come.
Asura's Wrath.
How's, did you guys see it?
You guys gonna have, how's the ad break?
I got an ad on my phone.
Oh.
Is this game vegan?
Yeah.
Okay.
Dude, I don't even know if it's fucking moving.
Whoa.
He just fell down.
He failed the QTE.
Good.
Good for us.
Ah, shit.
How did I miss that?
He didn't even put, you see, he put his hand down.
He didn't even swing.
He, he swung after I died.
His build meter.
Who the hell am I?
What the fuck is going on?
I'm moving too fast.
I can't even see what I'm doing.
Who the hell am I?
What?
Hello?
Moving too fast.
I was moving way too fast.
Oh, man.
He fucking killed me.
Okay.
I was going too fast.
I gotta, that's just all super speed.
All right, let's go.
I thought, for some reason,
I thought they could walk around it somehow.
Get this jacket off.
I'm getting a goddamn wedding over here.
Come here.
Jesus, too fast did I go.
You move so fast.
God damn, this is gonna be hard.
This is the hardest fight so far.
God, sometimes he doesn't do it.
Just kill me.
Kill me.
We have a pee break?
I need to pee.
After this mission, we'll do a pee break.
Finally, he falls down and dash.
Same deal.
Getting close.
Back up.
Come on.
Do it.
Dash.
Here goes.
Damn it.
I thought he was dashing.
All right.
Didn't take much damage.
Fuck.
I thought he was...
That's so annoying.
Fuck.
I thought he was doing the whole thing.
All right.
Don't use the speed unless I need it.
Only one more.
That should be it.
More good one.
This should be it.
Come on.
Ah.
Needs like one more.
Good.
I'm losing frames here.
It doesn't count.
We're at like 14 frames a second.
All right.
Did I win?
Is the QTE the same button?
It's usually Y.
Yeah.
I hope he keeps devolving.
Okay.
Are we going to get another form?
Can he just be like a puddle of mud or something with like two fingers?
I should dispose of him where he stands.
My soul tells me different.
Screams to me.
He's too angry to die.
Let him die.
For a reason.
Then listen to my fists.
How many times are we going to do that?
You'd think you'd punch with the other hand by now.
Civil War.
That really was Civil War.
I have business in Shinto.
Why is it normal now?
Wait for my return.
Dead for the fourth time.
Number four.
Hope we appear back on that pillar to climb.
I am Yasha of the Seven Deities.
Corvette.
There's a 15.
Two more episodes remain until we get the final story.
Comes episode 16.
Oh look.
It's Jerma's grade in college.
I don't remember that.
It said P-break.
Yeah.
No, don't worry.
We will.
Thousands of years ago in Deus's office.
Yasha, we decided.
Why are you so hesitant?
It's the only way we can save this accursed planet.
But to kill a few to save the many, I do not feel that would be just.
This has nothing to do with justice.
It is our cause.
What do you mean saving our way of life?
I would gladly accept becoming a demon.
That's what it takes to attain an eternity of peace and prosperity for our people.
A village with no name.
Great guardian.
Why do the Goma exist?
Why do they come and take everything from us?
Well, my lord, my son's death was not in vain, was it?
No, it was not.
We would have been powerless without his prayers.
I see.
Thank goodness, son, your death was not in vain.
But I wish you could have lived to see a world of peace.
Let us meet again one day when you are reborn in a different life.
It is his office.
Well, I've seen so much pain and suffering of our people throughout this internal war.
If you say we can stop this, then I am at your command.
I too shall become a demon.
You made the right choice.
I'm confident you will make me very proud.
From this day forth, I shall live only for the cause.
Until I fly away in a corvette.
All right, pee break.
And then we'll get into the end here.
All right.
I don't know if this is gonna sound weird, Mike, but my room smells like chocolate.
For some reason.
It smells like chocolate in here.
Will we be back here again?
We the seven deities have finally brought stability and all this anger inside of me.
I don't fight for good.
And I don't fight for evil.
I just fight.
I will say it once more.
I am you and you are me.
I'm leaning back in my chair right now.
Take a look at this.
This is a new new mic sound, right?
Yes.
The source of your power is your fan.
If you're so powerful, it could scorch your very body.
Unleash your rage and let your arm do the rest.
Yes.
Give in to the fear.
Spider.
I will lose myself again.
You have extraordinary power, sir.
It's the power that cannot protect anything.
He's giving birth.
Yes, it can.
It can save the world.
Save the world.
This power is ridiculous.
Oh.
All right.
Okay.
You just have to go over there.
Exact same thing happens in the Fall Metal Alchemist intro.
I will let you take any more lives.
Exact same thing.
How would you know?
Because I've seen it.
I swear to God, watching anime for some of you guys is the equivalent
of me like snorting coke before I scream.
But you...
Did you get that?
Should you have done that?
Snorting anime before the stream turns on.
Snap, I've seen a couple, but it's not a big deal.
Look, they'll scream.
Oh, that was right in the face.
Come on.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Walk onto him.
Why would you walk onto that guy?
Why would you walk onto the guy back here?
What do you think of him?
Why would you do something like that?
More?
Ooh, that daggers it up.
I actually have to sit up.
Come on again.
Thanks for the help.
Oh, this area sucks.
Ah, yai.
This place sucks.
I'm not even going to walk onto him.
Stop telling me in the story I was going right at the beginning of the stream.
It just rips around.
Now I walk onto him.
No.
What the fuck are you doing?
Hey, you know the guy that's in front of me?
Just kill me.
Just fucking kill me.
This has to last like five waves.
Because that guy can't believe he just got a kill.
Oh my god, I actually did it.
I shot my little fucking peepee gun at him.
Whoa, he died from that.
That's unbelievable.
Never happened before, ever to me.
How do- you gotta be fucking kidding me.
You gotta be kidding me.
Get out of here.
I'm gonna fucking smash the Xbox.
I'm gonna hit him in the ear.
I'm fucking dead.
This is unbelievable.
All right, here comes the worst part.
This is gonna be the worst part.
Use burst?
I don't have it.
Burst is the way to beat the level.
All right, I gotta clear out the little guys first.
Hi.
Hey, let's fight now, please.
I'd love to-
Stop pretending.
Dude, I gotta fucking pretend for views, man.
Come on.
What are you doing?
Get it?
I've got to.
How are people gonna watch if I don't get hit three times and die by 10 people surrounding me
without a block?
Imagine blocking in an action game.
It's just stuff with 10 people on the screen around you in a circle and the lock-on sucks.
All right, just do it again, do it again, do it again.
The best part about playing an action game,
when you fucking stand still and nobody will touch you,
it's like they know that you're not moving around.
No one's even trying to hurt me right now.
Why does this happen?
Well, I've decided I will attack you now.
I waited 15 full seconds to do anything.
When you actually are trying to beat the game,
I've turned it on times a thousand.
Jack isn't doing anything, like this is on target.
Just fucking kill me.
I was gonna say you almost missed.
He's mauling at a cutscene game.
All right, this is the one, this is the one,
this is the one, this is the one.
But I didn't even have time to react.
I'm stupid, I'm stupid.
What the fuck are you doing?
What the fuck?
I'm not walking onto anybody, I can't.
No, that's not the guy I wanted to walk onto.
What, who do you think I was trying to target?
It's not the person I was trying to target.
I'm glad he's dead anyways.
Fuck man, these guys still behind me.
Where did he even come from?
All right, I can make this count.
What the fuck is happening right now?
I can't, these people are fucking freaking me out.
Jesus Christ.
No, don't.
Do something, do something, do something, do something.
Thank God.
Back up, back up, back up, back up, back up, back up.
I got a fucking idea.
Here's my idea, this is it.
I'm fine.
Dead?
That was horrible.
That was painful.
That hurt.
It was a quality tuber noises.
Yeah, I know, dude.
Imagine that in a fucking compilation.
No, it's probably gonna get harder.
All right.
Good, get me out, get me out.
How do I get out?
What's going on?
This guy's fucking up the door.
Okay, let's go.
This just got, this game just got like 5,000 times harder.
It's a good grab.
Great, he's getting angry again.
Last time he did was he turned into a goblin.
I don't get it, but he's connected to the girl so I can't kill him.
It's one of those slime hands you get as a kid.
From like the 50 cent machine, the little gumball machine.
That was a sick stock electricity sound.
I can probably find that right now.
What's that for?
It's mine.
Stay out of my way.
You want to fight?
No, I got it.
It's required to save the world.
Are we gonna do two on one here?
I will show you how useless that cure is.
Let's go.
But blinded by your own bringing salvation to guide.
It becomes a triple threat match.
I'm gonna save the world.
This hell will finally end.
I'm powering up too close.
How many arms do I get?
Do I get more than six?
Watch out for the electricity.
Shitload of electricity.
Drive iframes.
Go, go, go, double team.
Ow, fuck.
Nice.
Hey, I'm walking far away.
That's what I like to see, the good double.
We will shoot at the same time.
Oh, shit.
I don't have any power.
All right, I gotta be careful here.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, hurry, hurry.
Hey, hey, huh?
What was that?
Okay, wait a minute.
That didn't, I didn't even get a tenth of a second to do that last one.
Bullshit.
All right, get in there, let's go.
Start attacking them.
Get in there.
All right, what was there?
Shit.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
Oh, I just had it off timing.
Ah, I had it off timed.
All right, I know what he does now.
When you get close enough,
you're gonna be fucking careful.
He does that shit.
Oh, come on.
I thought I was out of the range.
Give me a break, game.
Get in here.
This dude isn't doing anything.
He usually helps.
Not this time, apparently.
The other dude didn't do shit this time.
He just, he's supposed to help me.
He just has to act to every sound.
My god, Jesus.
Good job.
Good job, you keep missing.
He has to do the big stomp thing.
What the fuck?
Why do the cameras grip around like that?
Okay.
This camera's giving me a headache.
I'm not even locked onto him.
We're just like ripping around
when he dashes forward.
Yeah, it's two guys versus a fucking hacker.
He goes that far?
I thought it didn't go that far.
I can't even, man.
Please.
He's giving me fucking diarrhea.
All right, I think I got it for free.
This is too much stimulation right now.
Fuck this guy.
It's just flashing lights.
Get out of here, please.
Just kill him.
Help me fight him.
Thanks a lot, idiot.
He just ruined it.
I was doing my move here.
As he just squints the boss fight.
I jumped.
What happened?
What?
I jumped over that.
And this guy has a run of fucking mana.
This is bullshit.
Where is he?
Come on.
We're almost there.
You and me.
We call him again.
Not you.
Get him.
More.
Get in.
Go.
Get him.
He's on the ground.
No.
Get him.
I don't know what he's doing.
What?
Did I beat him?
I lost.
Oh my fucking God.
Stop rushing.
I can't attack him unless I get in close
because the only way I can attack him.
I have to get in close.
Otherwise, he just keeps doing the hurt your eyes move.
He's gonna do this forever.
The only way I can attack him is if I get in close.
I had it there, but instead of dodging,
I tried that before I get in close.
I can only jump over that one.
I can dodge through the...
I can only jump over the circle on the ground.
See?
Look.
Three people telling me to jump.
I had like 30% health.
I'm not gonna just...
I need full health.
It wasn't paying attention.
Idiot.
It was three people that told me to jump.
It's faster than dodging.
Thanks, guys.
No, really.
Thanks.
Like, I wouldn't...
I would have been like,
what the fuck are they talking about?
What the fuck?
Are they fucking stupid?
That was like $6,000.
What's the point of a dodge roll?
Why is there a dodge roll?
I just parked him.
What the...
Oops.
It's over.
Wait.
That's not part of the video.
Not that I don't even care.
I seem to like to do this to people.
I like to lift them up and let them talk.
Or their neck.
Behold.
This is that very power.
Wait, is this supposed to be him?
We have to fight the galaxy brain guy?
I don't know why that's making me laugh.
Galaxy brain.
I'm stupid.
Sakura Geninam Indra Deus.
Destiny, it is me.
Okay.
It doesn't matter how big you get.
You can just see that.
Well, we finally agree.
That doesn't make us friends.
Of course not.
Still, Deus.
So, this is your decision.
But this is...
Now stop talking to yourself.
Asura, you...
With a target that big, we can't miss.
Always dwelling on the fight.
Very well.
What is he doing?
Oh, he's...
Right, he's hauling his car.
Who said you could board?
You and I will settle this later.
But how was I going to get there?
You'll fly.
Do not blame me if you fall off.
How was I going to get there?
Oh, we're going to have to deal with...
We're going to have to do the...
Walk on and shoot enemies for an episode.
It is a little bit 18 up to date.
Are we about to beat the...
Are we about to fight the final boss?
Of course.
Whatever.
Grenade up his nose or something.
Or whatever I'm going to do here.
Still going?
Or get too full of moves?
I mean, this is cool.
It's cool.
But I'm not really doing it.
Good.
Dumbass is wasting your wing points.
More?
Tilted?
A thousand years for a gigantic toy.
That's definitely better than a toy.
It's like the king of all cosmos.
He's clapping us.
He's going to squish us together in his palms.
Why not?
Pray?
Did he get us?
Nope.
Maybe.
You'll see.
Design?
Yeah, that big guy is pretty cool.
Pretty cool.
I will say.
Here goes 17.
Aliyoth on the bridge.
Ah, sakra, davanam, indra, deus.
I cannot believe I'm seeing it with my own eyes.
It's magnificent.
Not even the colossi compared to its power.
By merging with the karma fortress,
it has become the most powerful being in existence.
It'll purify Goma Viltra.
With the use of the priestess's power
and the seven trillion souls we have accumulated.
There's a lot of people on Earth.
That's a lot.
That's...
Seems like too many people on Earth.
But would that not also destroy the planet as well?
Seven trillion people?
Perhaps it was just the brahmastra.
Now that lord deus is merged with the karma fortress,
he can concentrate blast with great precision.
Sakra, davanam, indra, deus is invincible.
Lots of fun.
Laugh.
They've been farming the planet for 12,000 years.
Yeah, but haven't we been...
Aren't we under the knowledge that they've been using it?
Like cast spells and throw parties and stuff
and have power and do stuff and destroy things, right?
They've been using it, haven't they?
Episode 17, fleet of play.
We crashed!
We gotta kill his heart now!
Why is it...
I don't know why that's making me laugh tonight.
Why is that doing that?
I don't know why I think that's funny today.
Sorry.
No, who cares?
Fuck that.
I'm not sorry.
I'm sorry!
It's probably Mr. Apology now because of the ayaya.
Now I think if I eat like peanut butter and jelly
with like the peanut butter on the top instead of the bottom,
I gotta have to apologize to you guys for that.
Oh, dance game?
You don't do jelly on top?
I'm sorry.
Open it!
Sonic Adventure 2.
Tails mechanic.
I actually have to control this shit.
This is the reactor that turns the souls into mantra.
If we destroy it, it will cut off Deus's energy supply.
Wait, should I be breaking these?
I can't break them.
I'm just trying to talk.
I can't not hear anything you say.
Sorry, I can't hear you.
I'm destroying all the capsules.
What?
That's not fair.
There's no opening.
I'm getting it.
Great.
I'm going through it.
Okay, you know there's a problem when Aladdin the Super Nintendo
didn't do that.
There's an issue here.
Fire now.
These lasers are terrible.
Look at how bad these lasers are.
You don't have a laser that can shoot forward.
It's just arched up and down left and right while you just shoot it.
I'm getting real sick of the zooming on the face
and then hit Y.
It's happened a hundred times.
Hurry.
Jerma hates the game.
Feels bad, man.
No, I'm fine.
This game would be so much better if his other four hands
turned into mouths and talked.
They'll like, they'll be fun.
They talk to each other and shit and turned and it was like the mouth hand.
That'd be awesome.
I do understand.
I must do what I think is right.
I am the god that carries the fate of civilization on his shoulders.
I'm talking about like his puppet.
His hands are puppets.
And they talk and they have different personalities and shit.
You are a danger to my words.
Consider your lies, puppet.
What?
He's actually crazy.
What do you mean?
What?
Back up, back up, back up.
What's he doing?
Oh!
Is it the same boss?
I think so.
I'm distracting him.
Hit him.
Hit him, hit him.
Nice job.
All right, get in.
That's what we call teamwork.
Get in.
Oh shit.
No, get in.
Get in.
One of us can distract him.
Wait, don't get it.
Just call, just call, get in.
Get in, good.
Oh, now it's just one v one.
God damn it.
We can't co-op him anymore.
Jesus.
See what to do here.
I don't know what to do.
I can't get this.
It was slow.
Man, that move sucks.
So I don't know what he's going to do with it.
Jesus, man.
Give me an opportunity.
Don't die.
What?
What happened?
We were doing a, we were about to do a
TTE.
It didn't.
Okay, let's go.
I know what someone was moving up.
I'll get him.
Done.
Stupid.
Damn it.
I thought he was doing the jump thing.
We haven't grabbed for that long.
It's hard to tell what he's going to do.
All right, this is a bust.
This is a shit run.
Are they cheating this game?
Probably.
I'm not going to use them though.
Really?
I don't like this LOL.
Yeah.
Yep.
Yep, yep, yep.
Man.
Move, do it.
Oh, that's not the move I wanted you to do.
Shit.
Oh, that's so bad to fuck up.
That was almost 80% of my whole health for the fuck me.
It's just when you get in close and you're fighting and it's just like cutting.
Oh, nope.
You pressed B because you were pressing B to attack the guy.
When you get in close again, it doesn't seem it's just like you're pressing B because you're hitting and you're attacking.
And this shit got buried in hell in 2000 fucking 15.
Like nobody wants this back.
Might as well just die again, Jeremy.
Did I just play it on normal?
I was like the second last boss in the game and I can't change it back now.
I'm gonna beat this motherfucker as well.
How many have left?
I don't even know how many deities have left.
We've time traveled like three times.
Fuck.
He stays on the ground.
I keep forgetting it.
It didn't.
My hand's sweating.
Did he hit me with something?
I wanted to fight the electricity man again.
For all the people I have to fight again.
They're just killing me.
Did I start making bite marks?
Can't go in.
All right.
Here we go.
This is the one.
It's only I'm gonna say it.
Hold on.
I love how Jeremy's too stupid to recover health.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean to recover health?
What do you wait?
What?
You're a liar.
I would laugh so hard if I was able to recover health the whole game.
That would be an embarrassment.
I'm gonna stop doing that.
I'll go in.
You have to jump if you're getting hit.
I haven't gotten hit yet.
This whole time I've been playing.
My health has been dropping.
I have like a debuff.
I don't know what the fuck's wrong.
This is the one right here.
This is the one.
Patience.
Just have patience.
Come on.
Come at me.
This is the one right here.
All right.
Now we have to do.
Now we have to trade with Asura.
And do the same thing again.
I'm ready for it.
What the fuck are you doing, Jeremy?
What are you doing?
What are you doing, Jeremy?
I'm doing too fast.
It's a problem.
It's too fast.
I don't like this.
Get him.
Okay, we're good.
I'm gonna get the fucking stuff.
Fucking stuff.
Exactly.
I thought he was just gonna go on, so.
I'm curious.
Do it.
Just do it already.
Do we have to do phase three with this guy?
I'll be okay.
I'll just look up and.
Now all my teeth are gone.
I'll be all right.
I didn't even say it this time.
She cries because she knows of the world's suffering.
Once my world is liberated from the gold mine, I shall cease all the cries.
I'm crying right now.
They killed this dude.
Oh, no.
I knew I had to do it again.
Die.
Yeah.
I was out of that fucking range.
What the fuck?
What is that?
What is happening?
I tried to fucking dodge.
I'm fucked.
Now I'm gonna do this shit again.
He got me with a reverse counter.
Press B.
Yeah, I know.
So easy.
Just press the B button, like.
And then sometimes press A.
Why is it so hard for you?
All right.
That's what happens.
Holy fuck.
That's recovered.
Hold on.
I've done that move before, though.
I need to test this.
It's back to getting hit.
Yeah.
That was not working.
I see.
I didn't recover health.
It's recovering a little bit of health.
You take less damage.
Right.
It's worded weirdly.
It's you take less damage, not recover health.
You take less damage.
Are they?
Why do they word that so strangely?
I remember reading that.
It was like, oh, you take less damage.
But, like, after, like, I thought it was, like,
for, like, a few seconds after the recover damage, you salvage HP.
Why can't it just say you recover health?
Well, my back is wicked itchy right now.
I have, like, the itchiest back.
I have to, like, scratch my back with, like, a whip or something.
Hold on.
Imagine being so good you beat the game without healing.
See, that's a great way to look at it.
Thank you.
Is it always going to be B?
I'm scared to press it more than once.
That's why.
Is it going to be B every time?
Did you just counter it?
Why did you?
What?
Oh, really?
I got countered.
How'd he counter that?
In the circle.
I'm scared to try to go in the circle, I'll be honest.
All right.
Now punch it a million times.
It's always B.
Hold on.
Don't fuck it up.
I'm not going to get this fast.
Oh, god damn it.
All right.
Ammos.
Eat my ass.
Kill him.
You just beat this guy already.
I'm trying to do that.
Nobody even said that.
I'm just making that up.
Somebody probably did.
Not so fast.
I'm still alive.
Let's do this again.
You and me, two on two again.
Oh, that's it.
I got it.
Oh, wait.
He's not going to say, like, a funny line, like the goblin thing King does?
You're not going to, like, ruin a scene?
That's not how gravity works.
She's like a god.
She is weightless.
So you have power.
What do you think?
Charging at whatever is in front of you can save the world?
Yeah, that scared me a little bit, too.
That really was random loud noise in a YouTube video to fuck with you.
What do you mean?
You were the good guys.
This is, is this, he was the good guy?
You've lost your spirits.
Glitter is the will of the planet itself.
It will devour all the souls on Gaia.
Its power is limitless.
All the more reason we must defeat it.
Wait, Asura.
You didn't pay for it yet.
That cost $1,199.
I shouldn't.
Empty your pockets.
You never change.
Asura, how could I have been defeated?
Doesn't matter.
I see.
So not even you know.
And then there is no hope.
Just turn and just soccer kick this guy's head.
Mithra.
Just a full running start.
I do not deserve to be called your uncle.
That's your mom's brother.
It is all right.
The hell are you talking about?
Mithra.
There's father.
He is there.
He fought to save you.
There is still something left we must do.
We will end all of this.
Am I crying?
Come on.
You can hear that?
All Jerma is crying.
I thought I could be emotional but I happen to be caught on camera.
So what are we supposed to do about this?
At what point do we just leave?
At what point do we just turn the fucking ship around and be like well
this 500 quadrillion other planets.
We just leave.
Go somewhere else.
You take a look at that and you kind of go yeah that's probably it.
That's probably it for Earth.
Defeat of Plague.
And the Imperial Hall.
My liege there's little time before Lytra's next revival.
We do not start preparing preemptive measures soon.
It will be too late.
Cruising to do nothing is also an option.
Change comes opposition.
Jinkoku would not respond well.
Well this is the kind of beginning that we fake killed.
Would you have our people take up arms and wait for Viltra's return
after we finally obtained a moment of peace?
With each awakening Viltra grows more powerful than the last.
Next time our forces may not be enough to subdue it.
The rate at which our civilization is growing far surpasses
that of the impure.
Furthermore the eight guardian generals have never been stronger
especially with such a powerful priestess.
Oh my liege enough I've given you my answer.
You are dismissed in Deus's office.
Commander Deus the emperor did not grant us permission.
Regrettably no the emperor is only interested in protecting himself.
He must be disposed of and you shall rise to the throne.
Brilliant do not misunderstand I have no intention of becoming emperor.
Mander was my destiny to purge this planet of the impure
and if I must be the one to guide our people in doing so then so be it.
I'll always be a warrior once we have accomplished our goal I shall reign.
Resign my post not not reign supreme not like reign all over everybody resign
but you'll just be sacrificing yourself for the cause.
My purpose has always been for the cause I have no desire to sit on a throne for all eternity.
The source of all gold.
Episode 18 this is it right.
I'm not doing the DLC tonight.
DLC is like five minutes.
Throw this game in the trash.
Holy shit it's two hours or so yeah I'm not doing a 10 hour stream.
What oh I thought we for a second I thought this was the DLC.
Let's go kill the snake inside the planet.
Can I still buy the DLC?
Microsoft points yeah it's a pain in the ass.
Oh I wasn't even looking.
I was just looking I was just talking to you guys I wasn't even watching.
They kind of have to deal with this shit every day.
Snake that's right this is snake snake number one there's one this is cool this is cool
yeah this is super interesting yeah I'm kind of just like
eat a sandwich and go to bed and take a bath are we gonna fuse please fuse do a fusion
why are there two bees you're playing too the body we're gonna go in here and there's gonna be
decrepit little monster in there that's like slimy and slugged we're just gonna have to
stab it once the whole thing dies well someone was asking what would people be doing right now
there you go I would take out my cell phone and videotape and then fucking throw as hard
as I could in the space of the cell phone somebody would find it one day
just turn around and just whip it as hard as I can into space
I'm eventually come across and be like holy shit this is crazy its power is overwhelming are you
you never change that is why I cannot give up either fight you there's a face oh here comes
the big brother I feel like I'm fucking hallucinating right now no this is real okay
we're good this game is so weird it's pretty cool technology I guess that it can simulate
bugs all over my room and shit spiders everywhere that's weird but it can do that
I don't know the tech existed to do this
what that's a lot that's a lot of arms
I fucking ruined that one that was the end of the game the only thing I could think of is
all right I want every time I hit him I want that sound effect to play that old like beat
him up sound effect you guys don't have somebody else that I'm talking about it goes like
I need to find it somebody find it for me I know somebody knows what it is
in the simpsons beat-em-up game he's like crap no somebody knows
oh no it's the first boss in the simpsons beat-em-up game in the arcade
what it's like the second boss baby how does he do it this is it this is it I need to know
that is this it I need to know seriously please tell me you got it no no no no no no no wrong
no no no I fucking thought you guys seriously had it I was about to be so happy
no no that was street fighter this one please I know someone's gonna get it it's one person
stop linking the fucking gnome stop linking the gnome there's a clip of me please I know
someone's gonna get it so I don't look like a psycho one of them's gonna be right this is all
bosses nice okay I'm not insane thank you for proving my point
all right what the hell am I alive all right now imagine that sound you know
how much of this game is just yelling a lot this is what this game is
ah ow ow that just fucked me up let's fuck anybody else up it's like core
oh is it over Asura how are you still playing this I used to play remember why are you playing
I have to actually fight a final boss but he's just like me but better
he has extra arms he's angry he's red
who is that letra core all right so I hope this whole game is in QTEs I hope this is just a QTE fight
there's a lot of walking yes it should be
let's go fight attack attack oh all right get it get away it's a huge explosion
we good I'm gonna save the LT big bomb big bomb uh I don't know what just happened I think we did it
whoa another one what I need a good chance anybody anyone have any idea what's going on
I think I'm doing okay I think where are we I tried to do the jump okay
ah I tried to jump again and I couldn't get it what the fuck I don't even have an indicator
oh please
yeah right I gotta dodge through it after jumping twice probably ah shit it's going
don't tell him I have to go to bed soon yeah shit I didn't get it what I where's the indicator
what the fuck I I'm gonna lose like probably six or seven more times
why didn't you know I get knocked down
you regret setting this to hard yes because I I'm assuming the only difference is
you just die in three hits I don't think the game's any harder
that's okay it's it's not very long get in get don't get it
give me give me give me give me give me give me give me give me give me give me give me give me
give me give me all right dodge through it I'll screw it no what I have to light my house on fire
what hey Jeremy I have to go to bed come on like let's go let's end this dude I gotta go to work
tomorrow you'll have to light my house on fire soon so like come on let's go let's hurry the fuck
up just kill me I'm missing the birth of my child well you shouldn't be here then I'm missing the
birth of my child I'm gonna watch this fucking dumb internet e-clown asshole greet this dumb
shine a flashlight in your eyes boss on hard I gotta stay here I just want to hold on
it's not now we go get it save the LT dodge attack fight get it all right get it
you saw me jump what's with that fucking stupid one dodge jump easy
I just beat this boss and I don't have the game called so I don't spoil the screen for myself
already that's right let's do it now I tried to jump but it didn't fucking do anything
okay do you that is like point that's like not even a tenth of a second that's not even a tenth
of a second to do that eat the blt jeremie eat the blt I'm gonna die no this doesn't even need
cheers to you it's just it's just extra damage I'm gonna put it on normal if I can't do this in
like 15 minutes oh careful look I'm not gonna lose very much sleep if I can't beat the final
boss in the sewer graph I'll be able to go to bed tonight and be like disease don't matter
just keep coming
get in there he dives in
he's so far away okay oh my goodness gracious that sucks
we didn't get hit because I was invisible
no okay I gotta get him get in quick while I have power all right get the fuck out get the
fuck out get the fuck out get the fuck out what's he doing hey hey sorry you can take a few hits
it's okay it's okay I got a fucking another lip which teleports he's gonna jump there he goes
get in there oh he almost jumped I win I win I win I win I win I win all right we're done
loser get out of this let me get out of this I am mother guy are you two fucking idiots
no I can't believe I just let these two dumps
yay we saved earth we've rescued it look at how good it's doing right now flat what the
it's the first time you're seeing that the first time you're seeing this dude what the fuck I
I thought I thought it was flat this is crazy to me I died for the fifth time I was laughing at
everything today because everything's funny to me today is it really you guys have been on point
with like the weird comments is your wrath guys said I don't know but I see let us go Mithra is
waiting please my credit's number four Mithra who made this game well I'm surprised somebody's
saying that considering that let's say let's say the average viewer is here for let's say
30 minutes 20 30 minutes average time somebody spends on a stream maybe
Capcom's logo has popped up probably every 25 to 30 minutes so I'm actually surprised
that anyone would even ask that so this is the third running credit real wink all right fine
all right see you guys tomorrow I'm not doing DLC right now I'm the same being I'm not making
this a total fuckface stream no I'm going five days in a row here I'm not going to be let's do
11 and a half hours and let me fucking burn my eyes out no I'm not doing the DLC tomorrow
we're gonna do something else there you are in the freezer do the DLC we'll see what we got going
on this week I might throw it in here somewhere because there's a couple there's a bunch of other
I have like two other Xbox 360 games got NBA Street over here that I want to play
I just want to get the hard drive so I can actually play Tony Hawk
I want to do Outer Wilds this week too I've been putting that off for a long time
Noble Heroes 2 yeah we'll see I got a lot of games but I don't know who knows Black and White 2 is
also something I want to do I still have not the chibi robo I really really badly want to play it
I'm just gonna get it I'm just gonna get it but that was a Asura's Wrath it was pretty fun it was
over the top I enjoyed it it's not over well I mean it is but not it might not be I skipped this
I can't even skip it what are your impressions my impressions are uh all right the boss fights
were really cool just wish I didn't have to press Y as many times as I did like you even you take
away even half the times that I had to press the button Y and I would have probably thought this
is a very game the DLC is no I know about the DLC don't worry see if we can fit it in somewhere
because what is it like an hour or two couple hours
yeah all right well yeah we'll do it probably this week we'll throw it in somewhere
that's fine all right is it like after credit scene or something
with the Diablo yeah we could do Diablo 2 hardcore and then whatever happens with that
throw this at the end do the DLC now no I'm not doing a 10-hour stream
please yeah all right now I'm in I still play Return of the King and I'm kind of concerned
to play it just because you know how the last one went I can I skip this oh breaking point
total rank B B A C we're good to see them all C for crap oh there is another thing after this
my hello there it's been a while do you remember me seems you have vested Vlietra I suppose I
ought to congratulate you the time has finally come I'm going to enjoy this oh how rude of me
I was just talking to myself pretend I never said a thing maybe there's lots of work to be done
in Naraka so I'll be on my way ta-ta that's the actual final boss I have to fight the
giants spider boss that's why everybody wants me to do it the hidden episode can be unlocked
by achieving an S rank in five or more episodes or complete 50 or more episodes on any difficulty
I thought you guys said this is DLC true episode a turn of events look at all these C's
A B B A B no S's this is actually what my report card looked like when I was in high school
just get an S on easy another day another day all right guys we're gonna we're gonna call it a night
here I'll see you guys tomorrow tomorrow we are going to start uh not at one probably start
somewhere around like two-ish tomorrow start a little bit early today we'll start around
two tomorrow somewhere around one two two-ish the S grade is a real thing in Japan
it means like super that was fun though it was worth doing it got really hard at the end I was
here on 2 p.m pacific tomorrow good night guys let's do the outro let's get to the end of the
actual stream here uh that was fun I had a good time let's get some music on here while we just
relax people in chat are mean just got it did he beat Diablo uh you're a little late we I started
farming him I think we beat him like 15 or 16 times still no uniques though which sucks
all right let's do the end I didn't want to go too much longer than this I want to be up and ready
to go tomorrow easy and the next day in the next day the next day in the next day bullshit you got
a gold wrap great actually all right let's go crack head gaming yeah kind of but uh circ
whack thanks for the 500 bits I'm so happy you're playing this it's amazing it's literally a pog
simulator first hour is slow but it gets fantastic it did start off a little slow but we did give it
a chance and then I beat the base game I thought it was good I just wish it was a little less
QTE just just enough for me to not you know think my nose at it was that phrase something like that
it was crazy though the fat boss yeah the the big fat boss that puts his finger down
the game was made during the end of the QTE yeah the era of QTE unfortunately still a fun game
though I did enjoy it otherwise I would not have played it I wouldn't have streamed the game for
almost eight hours if I didn't think it was fun it was definitely worth playing but thank you
appreciate the 500 bits thank you son of genova for the 250 hydra please check the uh the carnivore
saga someday especially carnivores too or ice age they are great they're old as fuck though
I do remember those games those games were those games are crazy he plays the dinos don't even
run around as a dinosaur in that game I need to see if I can get a hold of some of those
though you hunt no yeah you hunt you hunt them they're attacking you and shit
let's check them out add them on the list we're gonna do Tony Hawk's underground today but I
didn't have an xbox hard drive or something it was embarrassing but it's all good we'll get that this
week I'm gonna play Tony Hawk's underground this week I really do so I'm gonna probably tomorrow
morning I'm gonna get up and we might even just do it tomorrow try to get up early and go get one
I wanted to do that today so we're gonna have to do that tomorrow
Vilemi gave 5 000 bits I missed this one they say German we tricked you into watching an anime on
stream the best part about this is talking to VR Josh about how much he recommended it he's like
don't play you gotta play Serious Wrath on stream it's awesome it's really good I'm like hey so what
why and he's like oh I didn't play it I watched like a few of the cutscenes I'm just I did not
say what did you say you said something like that you said something like what did you say
you said something like that read my recommendation what does it what does it say
he said it was like his favorite game ever made let's get recommendations let's go search VR Josh
he's deleting I've been recommending this a while but Serious Wrath for xbox c2 would be
worth experiencing on stream at least once a very flawed game but worth experiencing just for the
absurd cutscenes and boss battles the boss battles consist of mostly QTEs but the sheer
scale and anime nature of them make it worthwhile oh shit you did say that you didn't like it no you
said you liked it see yeah but but when I said hey what's what's makes the game so good you
didn't you say I don't know I didn't play it that long you said what did you say in the beginning
of the stream you said something in the beginning of the stream that's what I'm referring to he's
like oh I don't I didn't I didn't play it show us the corpse face again no all right you know
what I'm just gonna purge you get out of here stop uh but anyways thank you for letting me for the
50 thanks to the I hope we can giggly today too fuck I was wicked giggly today I was just like
laughing today but thank you for letting me for the 5 000 bits 50 dollars phylactery gave 50
dollars as well we did do the whole game and I'm glad it did fairy with a pan thanks for 500 bits
germy you should play the lost episode the dlc on hard we're gonna try to throw it in at some
point this week I don't know it depends on I'm doing I'm gonna try to do Tony Hawk Underground
tomorrow so it's sitting on the same console so maybe I mean if I get really into Tony Hawk
Underground tomorrow and I play it for like six seven eight hours then of course I'm not gonna do
the dlc but if for some reason I only play Tony Hawk for a few hours or something then I'll just
stick it on top of that whatever we'll see I will do it gnarly thanks to the 250 here's a short
germa dream I dreamed I was in chat during a stream and I typed germa venus twice a mod saw it and
instantly perma banned me I'm sorry that happened to you uh sweaty man thanks for the five community
sub sweaty men Pugles thanks for the 400 bits auto is a speck of dust or auto no I can't
what is nothing but a can't is nothing but a speck of dust in the past that's pretty
anyways let's keep going uh thank you Pugles for the 400 bits doc thanks for the 250 doc
3660 hey germ I'm thinking of buying you a birthday present but I'm not sure what color I
should get just walkers uh walkers.com well why is one of the most expensive ones the shittiest
reviewed one the one that's 60 dollars is apparently like the best one with 22 reviews
this one's 135 dollars and it's it's got three and a half stars uh the green one thank you
appreciate it thank you doc we had a huge community subs come in from snar bosses
and about 32 nixons 40 community subs uh among the both of you thank you guys seriously
thanks for dumping a shitload of subs speaking of those subs why don't we show them
let's switch over to here thanks all of you hopefully we see you again tomorrow
hopefully the tony hawks underground well I played the credits actually jumped what the
scare but I don't believe any noise underground 2 is more fun uh we're gonna have that's actually
a really really good question I have both of them I have both I was kind of unsure of what I wanted
to do I could just do both thug 2 is a baby game thug 1 is best thug 2 is better thug 1 is classic
yeah I don't I mean this I knew this was gonna happen so I got both so we can just do both
eventually we're probably gonna start with the first one it seems like right idea but here comes
up thanks a lot guys for your extreme support of this channel thank you the short games anyways
yeah oh right soundtrack am I gonna have that host the stream tomorrow is gonna be muted
the stream tomorrow is gonna be muted so if you're planning on watching the vod
sorry but I don't know I mean I could turn the soundtrack off and put on like
yoshi's island or something but I don't know I'll figure that out anti-poison thanks for the 1500 bits
hey germo I was thinking about getting a germa rat tattoo and was wondering if you would be
okay with that that's not about me being okay with that it's about you being okay with that
uh in 10 years are you gonna think that that's all right still if you want a germa rat tattoo
that's a you thing that you have to decide I can't decide that for you I would give that a good
think um just don't put it on your face you know put it like I don't know somewhere you're gonna
hide it because in 30 years you might be like I don't know germa rat tattoo germa he disapproved
it never get don't know I didn't say don't get a tat don't I said don't put a rat tattoo a germa
rat tattoo on your face in 10 years the term is going to get cancelled for saying something
fucked up okay why are you planning on for this I don't like that you're planning for that
oh long story short if you're gonna get a tattoo make sure something that you really want um if
you come back to me in like three years and say hey this tattoo sucks why did you tell me to do
that I'm gonna say I didn't I'm gonna say I told you don't if you feed I have nothing to do with
this five years are gonna be 40 yeah don't remind me that hurts that comment I don't want to see
that I just vomited everywhere bye germa I'll go to the doctor hope you have a safe next day
you don't sick anymore whatever it's me drink some fluids have some soup goku thank you goku
green for the 550 here my I would I had your stream up tonight while I was doing my uh my
testosterone injection when I pulled the needle out there was a lot of blood it was not anything
to worry about because it can happen but I yelled at the same time as sura did wait a lot of blood
why did I read that I don't know like I don't know everyone's gonna be streaming at 90 I don't
think I've ever had any injection I've ever had I don't think there's any blood blood from a needle
does it happen oh be careful why would you tell people this what me I I bet that I've never had
blood I bet having six arms would help I once got a flu shot and I'm not going to read the
rest of that because it's fucking horrifying so I'm not don't get a tattoo on your face of my face
okay don't do that it'll look really strange I'm sorry to hear that uh goku hopefully you're all
right plug boy thanks to the 500 bits what's up germa was wondering if back in the day you
were ever into any hardcore shooters like arma and such I've always been into been like escape
from tarkov has been stealing my heart recently not a recommendation though because considering
how you reacted while playing pub g you would hate it just not really into the br thing
no I never really got into armor no armor wasn't necessarily br but escape from tarkov kind of is
not really into the br thing though escape from tarkov isn't the battle royale
not what is it it isn't br what is it is it oh you just it's just an fps it's just a realistic
fps don't they like drop everybody in a spot and people have to like extract and shit it's
a rogue like fps multiplayer stalker without the anomalies arena huh that's all right that's cool
I thought it was br I stand corrected all right hey mark melzer uh thanks for the 250 hey germa
I've always loved your stream especially the rhythm ones as of late speaking of which would
you consider playing the path upon remaster on ps4 yes it's on the list glad to see a streamer
willing to play older pc games rather than what's hot at the moment this hidden cult classics out
there let me do the reason why I play so many old games is because I'm just not really into any of
the new ones you mentioned br br's are really really hot right now and some of the multiplayer
shooters are really really hot right now I'm just not really into them anymore I just not the last
two big gaming trends have been genres I don't really don't really care about the big moba
explosion five years ago or so I don't didn't really care besides I played smite but a little
bit not really so I didn't really jump on that too much and then this newest kind of
fps third person br it's been a big big explosion the last few years I haven't really been into that
either I made 15 videos on smite yeah but that was also back in like 2013 that's not very much
considering how big that genre was at the time the people still place my smile still a big thing
I still think it's good I haven't played in a long time 25 Dr Pepper thanks for the 250
Super Bowl prediction I'm from Kansas City so I'm a little biased um I just it's just gonna be a
fun game it's gonna be a fun game right chiefs I'm okay I'm gonna have to say I'm gonna have to say
the chiefs for one reason because of that old Snickers commercial where the guy paints the
end zone wrong he's the whole commercial is a guy painting the end zone for the chiefs he's doing
he's going up and down he's sweating he's wiping his brow and he's doing a really really good job
they don't show what he's writing and then one of the players comes up and he's like hey man
that's a really good job but who are the chefs it pans up and it's just the chefs he didn't put the
eye he's like oh Jesus so I'm gonna say the Kansas City Chief what a great commercial yeah there you
go this is my Super Bowl prediction all right chiefs Kansas City Chiefs 19 to 6 Kansas City
Chiefs 19 to 6 gonna be a fucked up game hey jerma put sun chips in f-tier yes it did thanks
to the 250 jerma I'm here to tell you that you're still dreaming after you got naked on stream one
guy saw your penis you passed out from embarrassment every stream from that moment has been in your head
only way you can wake up is to peek your mic also you should do it because it's my birthday
what a wonderful comment this is you this ticks this you checked every box happy birthday by the
way all right I'll see happy birthday seriously jerma put sun chips in f-tier have a good one hope
you had a lot of sun chips right we can't leave yet let's go one more just got one more vlog boy
thanks in 250 dropping some more bits for you tonight before I sign off I think a game you
would really severely enjoy possibly off-stream is disco-alsium I was gonna stream disco-alsium
but I decided not to some people told me it was way too long
and that I would get bored you got to remember if I cannot complete a game within two to four streams
it gradually drops I mean it gradually drops like a rock after that if I'm gonna play it again also
I'll be the big 21 next week and be upset there won't be a stream yes I will not be around next
week I got a lot of friends coming in but I don't have any plans on streaming it anymore
does look fun though but I'm not gonna catch you next week happy birthday plug boy preemptively
why am I uncommitted to playing games I mean I'm not uncommitted it's just okay here hear me out
if if a game is more than 40 hours to get through the main game off-stream I wouldn't really play it
also I wouldn't play it off-stream really Red Dead Redemption 2 is the only exception
in probably the last couple of years at least so if you're talking about like this stream is
eight hours a typical stream is somewhere around six and a half to like seven and a half hours
it's like a typical average stream on this channel so if I can't beat a game in like
40 to 50 hours I really don't want to walk in and play a game for like 100 hours
Dark Souls Dark Souls well I look there is an exception for some of that's like my one of my
favorite gaming franchises I love Dark Souls and I love all the Dark Souls games and all the
from software games so that's not really a fair comparison because you're talking about one of my
favorite game studio franchises ever Darkwood I beat Darkwood in three streams Darkwood was
three streams my game was crazy but yeah if if I can't do it in like under five full streams
it's something I'm probably not going to stream I'll just do it on my own time
unless it's something I'm so insanely into like for instance Elden Ring is going to come out
I'm going to stream every second of me playing that game just because I I can't wait and I'm
going to play it as long as it takes you guys know that's happening but that's something that I
kind of do should be fun but hopefully that gives you your answer thank you near shoe for
the 300 bits a German doing college assignments to stream is the best longtime fan from Canada
keep bringing in you I wish you luck on your assignments hopefully you get a decent grade
a plus it's just don't even don't worry about that nobody you don't nobody cares about that
when you get out of college nobody knows if you got an a plus on your fucking paper
you know don't worry about that just do your best to do good enough you know like they're
not going to see you oh wait you got a b plus on that fucking paper they're not going to know
you got a degree in your hand we know it's fine god knows that's all right
how do you work listening to this psychopath yeah pretty good point actually
all right I'll see you guys tomorrow or hopefully Tony Hawk's underground if not then we're going to
do okay if I cannot get an xbox hard drive then we are going to do out of wilds okay all right
sounds good take your mic for that guy's birthday I'm not going to peek my mic for somebody's
birthday see you guys tomorrow good bye goodbye goodbye please don't go I'll be back I will be
back in less than nine and eleven twelve one two three four five six seven I'm gonna be back in
like 16 hours or something it's gonna be 24 hours you'll see me again where we go we got one more
we got one more one more donation from snoozing copter drink filtered water I will uh thanks
to the 250 snoozing all right Jeremy you need to shut the fuck up for a second sorry I'm riled up
I love you but seriously uh chat's gonna back me up on this nobody cares if you beat disco lcm on
stream but you have to play it on stream have to remember how fun the sorcery streams were
you have to do it I mean when you say when you say can you bring sorcery to this I mean
you're kind of comparing you I mean I don't know I you're comparing like Mozart to something
is this is this is as good as Mozart I that's tricky this do you tell me disco lcm is the
equivalent of being as good as sorcery which is the Mozart of these games you have to look into
that it's a bold statement you're gonna put Sean sunships in f-tier thanks to 250 everyone keep
giving him bits to force him to stay well that only works until I press the button that turns
off right now good night guys see you tomorrow what time uh somewhere around 2 p.m pacific
2 p.m pacific looking for Tony Hawk's pro skater underground or outer wilds
thanks near shoe for the 300 bits I did it he did thank you