What's up? How's it going? What's happening? I'm at the beach right now. Oh, that sounds actually kind of fun.
At the beach? I'm at the North Pole. What? Where are you guys? No, good to see you. Today we're going to play
Halls of Torment. It's a vampire survivor's lake. I've had my eye on it for a little while and
unfortunately I'm playing this game one day too early because I believe the beta launches
in like a day or two. So that's my fault. I'm playing it literally like 24 hours too early,
but that's too bad because I want to play it bad. So even if it beta comes out the next day or two,
whatever, it looks really fun. I'm a huge vampire survivors fan. I'm going to play it. I'm ready.
I'm here for five minutes to laugh at how lame this is. All right, we'll see you later.
Thanks for stopping by. Bye. Okay. Anyways, let's go. I'm fresh save file. Hey, can you wait?
My boyfriend's in the bathroom. Yeah. What do you think? Like another 100 or two? Two minutes?
It's, yeah, it's a fresh save file. I love these games with a fresh save file because I'm going to
be terrible. I'm going to have no items. I'm going to be dog shit at the game. I love it. I can't wait.
What about Hilux too? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Your dog shit at all games.
Clearly think you forgot about the, the one to two headshots in a row. I got with the Huntsman last
week. I mean, I, I, I don't know if you knew that. I'm not sure you saw that footage. Yeah,
it was gonna chill out, chill stream. And I mean it this time. I just want to play this game and
hang out and I'll go on one or two rants. We'll find for all time's sake. Why not? Oh shit. It's
a chill stream today. You know what I should start doing? Anytime. I just want to sit,
just kind of relax and play and hang out. I'm just going to tell you, it's going to be the most
fucked up stream ever. I'm going to tell you, man, it's going to be so exciting. There's going to be
all kinds of crazy shit's going to happen today. So then when it's the complete opposite, then we're
good. It's, it's, that's how it's going to be, right? False advertising. That's all right.
You're still a streamer? I mean, yeah, I guess. Kind of. Yeah. What, what am I doing right now?
Dude, you're still, I streamed like four or five days ago. I haven't been gone for like six months.
But all right, you guys ready? Take a look at this. All right. So like I said, this is like
vampire survivors. I know nothing about the game. I've been told this is unbelievably fun.
I am so ready to play it. All I know is that there's this quest thing and this is chapter one.
I cannot wait to play this. I've been sitting on this for a long time. There are 200 quests.
And the game's not even out yet. There's 201 quests. The game's not even out yet.
All right. So what do I want to do? Survive until there are only 26 minutes left. So that's easy.
Well, no, I mean, it's just an easy mission. Defeat the imp chieftain. Okay. I imagine it's
just the gigantic. Okay. It's the gigantic door. All right. Move, aim, attack, toggle,
auto attack and toggle auto aim. Ooh. Okay. Should I hold the button down? All right. Level up.
All right. So I think you can get items in the game too. The gameplay is it has control support.
I'll do just keyboard and mouse for now. I'm into it though. It's he's going to be playing on food
mode. Did you know what actually is food mode? Diablo 2 summoning classes. It's that's like the
best food mode. I thought about this a lot. Summoning necromancer and summoning druid is
the ultimate food mode. You can play with one hand. All right. Hold on. Plus 8% area cone size.
That's pretty cool. Diablo is in one. Health regen crit damage and movement speed. Hey chat,
which one? Hey chat, which one should I do? Chat's complaining about the graphics. They don't know
what the absolute. I almost just said fuck, right? They don't know what the heck they're talking
about. I'm going to say moving speed. All right. There's something down here. Monster crits. I love
graphics. Gameplay. I have to pick up the things, but wait, I actually am moving kind of slow,
aren't I? You need to get the little guys. I think I'm doing okay. All right. Defense, range,
attack speed. I'm going to go with cone size. Is that stupid? We'll find out. Yeah. I love these
games. Vampire survivors was my game of the year last year. These are like, I love these. I'm so
glad this is getting the treatment where a ton of people just make these. I will say though,
a lot of them, I haven't really thought were that great. I thought they were okay, but I mean,
when you're talking about the vampire survivors is the king, but I've heard this one is quite good.
Oh, probably this one crit damage. I can't wait just to start absolutely mowing down monsters.
Really going to get that feeling of just absolutely mowing down monsters. What's the plot? I don't know.
I just like to click on the skeletons. That's all I care about. I should probably go pick up the
items though, make up some lore right now. Okay. You guys ever think that skeleton is like a really
strange thing that we just like, Oh look, Oh yeah, it was skeleton. This is because this is somebody's
bones. Isn't like the concept of a skeleton kind of like weird in a way that's like somebody's
bones. That's your entire skeleton. Like that is weird. We all just look like that. Pickup range.
No, probably this one 10% range, 10% cone. I'm way too high for that. Uh, it's all right. Don't
worry. We're not going to, we're not going to stay on it for that long. I don't think about that
shit, dude. I think about taxes, man. You know, what I was really thinking about the other day,
man, man, like we all have a skeleton in the inside of us. Like, yeah, dude, you know,
there's way more pressing shit to worry about than like the fact that we all have skeletons
in our bodies. Yeah, man. Really think about it, man. There's like, you got, you got like bones in
you. New enemy type. That's a huge great, by the way, it was like two or three times.
Jeremy, did you see the aliens are real? Yeah. Take me with you. Take me with you. Okay. Uh,
I'm just taking this straight away. Damage or attack speed. Can I get some math? Andy's in here
to help is 10% more damage better than more DPS. I'm curious. Attack speed means you will always
be doing more damage because you were swinging more often. I'm not so sure.
Now tax fees, but I would go for tax fees for sure. Damage, damage, damage. I think I'll go speed.
Speed sounds good. How have you guys been? How's it going? What's new? I'm gonna die. Oh, I got,
I just realized I have 500 health. I think it is healed. You should talk about aliens. Yeah,
I don't know. Guys, if the, if aliens are real, like nothing we say is really like, they might
be pissed off that we like eat each other. You know what I mean? Well, not each other, but like
think about like, what if, what if an alien species was like, wait a minute, you guys like,
you guys like kill and eat stuff. What do you mean? You, you eat, you eat things. You don't just take
in like energy from the air. I don't know. They might be like annoyed that we like eat stuff.
Who knows what the fuck is going to happen. I want the range actually deranged. I'm just,
we don't even know what, what it even could be. We don't even know if it's like a carbon based
life form. Nobody knows what anything, anything was going on. What is it? What would the alien
national anthem be? Ladies and gentlemen, we have landed on earth and we are going to play you
our national anthem first of all, to make sure you understand what we are all about. And it's just
just a midi version of our national anthem. And then we play them the orchestral version
and they give us all their technology area. Ooh, I did it. This is exactly what you did last time.
Yeah. Well, if you go to like a comedy show, they're going to tell like the same jokes all
year. You understand? Like if you go to like a standup show, they have like a bunch of material
that they wrote for like a year or two. And then they come up with more material, like two years
later, you need to be better than that. I'm just hanging out mowing down monsters, man. This is
really your material. No, not really. Not really. All right. It's starting to get a little harder.
Uh, I think this can't go wrong with crit chance. Oh, how much is in the non beta?
I look like there was a pretty good amount of content in this game. Are they unique?
That's the only thing I care about in every video game. It's like 20 hours worth of content. Oh my
God. OK, this boss is almost dead. Oh, a squill. All of your jokes are bad. Um, I don't think all
of them are. I think like maybe if I were to actually tell you what I really think, I think
that probably, probably like 20% of the jokes that I tell are bad. Maybe like 30, maybe,
maybe a little more. No, no, no, no. Wait, what is this? 30%? Hey, that means I'm batting 700.
Even if I'm, OK, even if it's 50%, that means I'm batting 500. Do you know that you can hit,
you can strike out seven out of 10 times and be one of the best baseball players ever. You
could literally go up there and swing and miss seven times in a row and then hit three home runs
and you're one of the best players ever. So let's translate that completely to, to, to my life.
And, uh, a complete false equivalence that it means absolutely nothing next to each other.
But I'm going to use these two points to tell you why I think that I'm doing just fine.
All right, what do I want? Astronomers Orb? Metal orbs that circle around the player and
damage enemies. Orbs are indestructible and permanent. All right, so this is build movement
speed. Short range projectiles in a vertical spread pattern. Projectiles remain for a short
while. That's OK. Lighting's my favorite type of damage. This one seems to be interesting.
How do I use it? Oh, it just happens. I always love a good roguelike. What is that? Uh, well,
I'm doing the movement speed because this thing, this guy's fast. Jesus. Ow. Is there a block?
All right, I have to, I have to win. This is literally this, this is the tutorial boss.
I can't lose to this. Whoa. Oh my goodness. OK. Um, get rid of the adds. I need to level up.
Give me that scroll down there. What's up here? Give me the potion potion potion potion. That's
what that is for sure. Is this a damage buff? There it is. All right. Movement speed or just
straight up damage? Probably just damage right now. Trying to get him hit by the. Oh, I'm fine.
I got him. I got him. I got him. I got him. All right. All right. Things are getting a lot harder
to kill. It's in the chest. I need more attack speed. A hundred percent. Give me that shit.
Give it to me. I can't. I'm just like swirling a drain right now. Oh, there's items. OK. This
just got way fucking cooler. This just got way cooler. 20% attack speed, 10% crit chance,
10% health. I mean, it's definitely this. Cool. Oh, I feel the speed bat chest. You can bat
chest all you want. You are totally in your right to bat chest whenever you want to bat chest.
But I'm going to disagree with your bat chest. Idiot. Sorry. I put that last part in there.
Probably the health. Yeah, just get the orbs up. I'm going to I'm going to go up the scroll.
I did two quests already. What the hell is bat chest? It means I don't I think this thing is
cringe and it's like lame. So I'm going to that's what that's supposed to mean. Right.
It's supposed to be like, oh, my God, I'm so excited for this thing. And like, it's cringy.
How excited I am. Right. Is that how it is? I'm just going to run down here. Oh, my God,
Jerma. Oh, my God, Jerma bat chest. Come on. This is getting crazy right now. I'm going to
try to wrap around this dude. Is this the Jerma stream? Oh, taking the health because I will die
if I don't click this. I like the sound effects at the very beginning of the intro, like right
when the thing loads up and you press start to play, it should go. Welcome to the halls of
men. They can just use that if they want. No, they can't. Never mind. What am I talking about?
Oh, health and movement speed. That helps. I miss that. I miss when games used to just yell their
title card. That was cool. Why do we get away from that? We replaced having an interesting
voice acting at the beginning that just yells the title of your game to like, I don't know,
climb up the tower and activate the radio as like every game now. Bring back the fucking
yelling the intro speed. Yeah. Dance Dance Revolution. Does it do it? Dragon Ball Z does
that too. Well, there's a lot of shit on the ground. I mean, these are all good, but which
one is the most good? Does Mario Kart still do it? Yeah. Does he still go Mario Kart? In Mario Kart,
they even go a step forward. Like another step beyond that. It's select your player.
Choose your character. Street Fighter does it right. Street Fighter six. Yeah. And of course,
you understand why Capcom is just absolutely killing it lately. They just they say all the
names of their games in their intro. I know a lot of you didn't think I was going to get this far
on my first run, but you have no idea how much I loved Vampire Survivors. It's like my favorite
video game. I'm going to say, well, let's go with the 70 health. Do you get to keep the items?
All right. This is the end here for sure. Yeah. Yep. OK. All right. Character level 18. Survival
12 minutes. You suck. You're supposed to die. They don't understand these games. All right.
What did I get? I unlocked the Archer. I unlocked under the stage. I got a new ability,
Ring Blades. And then I got a Shrine of Blessings. The next quest is to enter Ember Grounds and
rescue the Wellkeeper. Cool. I got a thousand bucks. I thought you did good. I thought I did
good, too. Let's do Archer. What's this? Oh, and there's a shitload of upgrades. OK,
this is probably permanent. Yeah, permanent. Probably this one. Attack range, pick up range,
movement speed. Oh, yeah. Let's go movement speed twice. Movement speed is just so important.
Register of Halls. Choose your destination in the Halls of Torment. Oh, OK. The next quest was here.
I don't think I'm going to do it yet. Let me look at that. Let me look at the missions. OK. Kill
five thousand enemies in one run. Deal seven hundred and fifty thousand damage with the orbs.
Deal seven hundred and fifty thousand damage with Phantom Needles. All right. So kill five
thousand enemies in one run. Sounds easy. Can you please comment on Quiznos? I like Quiznos.
I haven't had it in a long time, but I love it. I'll do. Yeah, let's go for it. Let's just do it
again. Can I have a turn now? No, it's my Xbox. This character seems very, very good. I'm telling
You got a PlayStation. I have the Xbox. Go play Demon's Souls or whatever is on that fucking
console. I'm on the Xbox. More speed. Is this game even on Xbox? No, it's not. I'm on PC.
Is it on Game Pass? I have all three. Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha. Hey, come on. I'm going to go just
all damage on this one. You can probably increase the projectiles. I hope so. I'm going to go pick
that parchment up, whatever that is. How do people play this with a mouse? If I was going
to play with controller, I would do auto aim. These are all kind of weak block strength. What
if you don't have a shield? I'll go defense. Aiming with the mouse is going to be always be
a thousand times easier than aiming with an analog. So I will probably play with the mouse
forever. All right. Let me go down this way. This is in VR. I'm the character down there.
I just don't know. I don't have the webcam on today. Oh, that's really good. Yeah. I'm just
I rented out a warehouse. I have like 50 or 60 thousand square feet here. So it's really
roomy here. That's why I can move around this much. I can't decide if I like this joke.
We have an undecided joke voter here. What do we do? What do we do to convince them?
Is there a map? You're doing your make shit up voice. It's so funny. We talked about this before,
but this is just the way I normally talk. Dude, why is he doing the bit voice? Oh,
it's just like the way the dude actually just like kind of talks normally.
Everything is a bit. I don't know if I'd say that. I just like having fun laughing my ass off the
other day. Do you remember when that guy did that zoom call thing where he got like beat up in an
octagon? Oh, yeah. You know, when you you okay, you know, when you see somebody do something and
you wish you made that joke. Let's do a text. You guys have never seen that video of the guys
that link in a zoom call and he's like a green screen behind him, like attached to a backpack
on him. And he's in like an octagon. He's getting like beat up in his zoom meeting.
You've never seen this. It's it's fucking insane. Show it. I don't even know how to look for it.
I just I just remember seeing it. Bro picked eight over 20 percent. Oh, shit. Hold on.
This is really good. I do want to get down to the parchment, though. It was during Covid.
It's so funny. What is this? Oh, it was a thing to get a quest for this. Fires needles at random
nearby enemies in quick succession. Multi hit increases the attack speed. I'll do it. I'm going
to need it right now. OK, multi hit. Go 10 percent damage. I need more piercing movement speed.
No, I need more. Yeah, let's keep going. Attack speed. One more level up and I'm going down to get
the ability or chance. You just made me buy this game. I mean, the game is fun. I mean, did you
open the stream and see this thing that may have been speaking to you and your gameplay preferences?
That's what that's what just happened. All right. I'm being stupid, but I want the experience.
I'm doing it for a reason. All right. These are all good. I don't know what to do.
You're a really good salesman. Um, I don't I do not think so. Uh, 20 percent crit damage seems
amazing, but so does attack speed. That's just this game sounds like I'm sorting through a Lego bin.
Kind of does. Like, where is that fucking little square with the two pegs on it?
And it needs to be green. This is why I keep saying I need to organize these fucking things.
I just throw them in here. How am I ever going to be able to finish the Millennium Falcon now?
Um, more health. Pick up range. I know it's lame, but I need it. Uh, give me the crits. Yep.
It's day 34. Can you wear a nun cosplay? Uh, this is day 34 of me telling you once on day 34,
the answer is no. So the next 6000 days of you asking this are going to be a waste of your time.
There's so much over here. I don't want to miss it. There's so many little crunchies over here.
Guard the middle. There we go. All right. Five percent crit, 20 percent crit damage. That's
amazing. I'm so good on health. This first boss seems really fun and challenging, but fair enough.
I like the first boss. What's this? Is this me reading?
All right. Do I get this or something? Do I have to do anything with that or is it just lore?
Somebody said not looking great, bro. What do you mean? Me playing? I'm doing fine.
I haven't gotten hit for three minutes. You're telling me it's not looking good for me?
It's been three minutes. I've taken a point of damage. That's got achievement for it.
Yes. All right. Give me that loot crit chance. 80 percent pick up range. It's definitely this one.
I mean, 10 percent crit. That's nothing can compare to that. Give me a speed. There we go.
One attack per second. One, two, three, four. There's even more than one per second.
All right. I'm getting too cocky. Don't be stupid. Go collect. All right. Now go down.
Wait, there's like trinkets here. Come on, level up. What am I lacking in right now? More attack
speed. That actually is kind of getting ugly. You're right. I'm going to turn on auto attack
while I collect. That's definitely the time to do it. Oh, wait a minute. It's auto attack, not auto
aim. That I'm really glad I figured that out. So I don't have to hold down left click. Oh,
that's a huge deal. That is a monumental deal. There's so much stuff over here, but
whatever. Just go for it. Give me, give me everything. Is it health or is it just more crit?
It's over believers. It might not be. I don't know if it's over yet. I'm going to take the health.
I know it's a lame upgrade, but it's effectively drinking a health potion
and it's gone already. I would have been dead. I need damage. I need piercing and I need damage
right now. I mean, that's good enough. Damage is damage. All right. I'm now I'm finally going to
leave. Uh, more damage. All right. Now I'm running. They're starting to need multiple hits with my
main weapon to die. Oh shit. Okay. Hold on. He never picks up the regen lamp. What's the
region lamp? Is that a cool game feature that I haven't been interacting with? Don't tell him
that. What do you mean? Don't tell me that. He doesn't know about the regen lamp stand. Oh,
I thought that was a lamp. Walk over the fire. A lot of money. I'm missing out on a lot of
experience, but I don't care. I'm getting the other ability. Who knows how far away this is,
but whatever. Where's your movement speed to eight, eight milliseconds a second.
I'm going to hang on here for just a second. More damage. These guys drop a lot of experience.
This dude has an NA education. All right. Cause I'm just doing damage only. What do you mean?
This is where I lost last time. Already made more progress. Oh, give me, come on. Come on.
Yeah. Uh, I'm doing movement speed. These things are fast. I'm going to wrap around. There's a lot
of experience here. I don't even care if I die. When are you going to do the auto treat review
stream? Um, I don't know. I don't want to give auto too many treats. These are all kind of bad,
but I think I'll take this one. What's this? Ooh, he wants all the treats to himself.
You ever look at the back of a thing of dog treats or a thing of dog food and you go,
I could survive on this in the apocalypse. I'll be fine. You look at the ingredients list and
you're like, damn, okay. These like, these like really good treats for dogs. The,
I could probably eat these in the apocalypse. I'm going to run. Why did you not get damaged?
Cause I want to be running very fast because these things are fast and it's kind of freaking
me out. Remember avoiding damage means you can live longer to deal more damage. Defense
is directly translated to offense in a lot of these games that are in this genre. If you stay
alive for 10 minutes, you'll do more damage than if you stayed alive for eight, thus increasing
your score. All right. This big skeleton has to go. All right. 30% more 5% crit. Yep. Are you
guys doing the longer the enemy lives, the more damage it does to you. But if you don't get hit
and get good, as they say, all right, there goes the, Oh, that was just his shield.
His shield is the only thing I killed. Oh, that's not funny. Uh, this might be the end.
That's at some point I'm going to be at like, I'm pretty much at like 60, 50% crit or something.
Aren't I? Something kind of crazy. He needs a better gaming chair. No, I, I actually really
don't. I'm doing just fine. What do you mean? I'm doing fine. I gotta get rid of this thing.
Come on. All right. There we go. Can't get it yet. Uh, moving speed and help. What about, yeah, no
moving speed and help. That second boss has to die. Give me the other ability.
Ring blades throws blades left and right and alternation blades act like boomerangs passing
the character and then flying off screen. Multi-hit increases the frequency of throwing blades.
Lightning strike is random. I imagine it's just like in vampire survivors, stuns enemies for a
brief period. Stun enemies can't move, right? Electricity electrified deals damage. 100 each
tick based on the amount of stacks. Ooh, that was a big, that was a bad one. Each stack decreases
the tick time. When electrified ticks, it is reduced by one stack. I didn't read that. I
didn't comprehend any of that. I'm going to go with ring blades. No lightning. He's so drunk.
Yeah, that was like a, Hey, I just, um, can somebody read this for me?
Like the drunk Looney Tunes character. Uh, I'm getting close to dying and I would have died
right there. If, what is this? It comes with a negative. I mean, we're just going with this.
It's 30% more damage. Are you kidding me? All right. I can stay alive. I'm going to be quiet.
I actually don't want to die. All right. I unlocked a new wind crown, piercing wind.
They get 500 bucks. Cool. All right. I, what do I, what do I, let's try sword again.
I got, I killed 3,600 enemies in one run. Not quite there. Now it's just, uh, I'm going to do
the other stage. I think that unlocks more stuff. Yeah. Rescue the wellkeeper. All right. Go for it.
Auto aim is toggleable too. That's really cool. All right. Let's go for it. Ooh, this is harder.
They have a lot more health. I just break them out. I love this avatar.
See what I can do. You can't die, right? He must be nearby. I have to level up a few times.
Everybody does not believe right now. Um, I mean, this is a new level. This is harder than the first
one. And this is a rogue like with permanent upgrades. I'm going to say, I don't know if I
would be betting on the yes right now, maybe a few runs, but who knows? What if I do really good and
you make a huge amount of channel points? I'm going to go tank. Ooh, key. They're manageable.
Oh, I didn't upgrade last time. It's all right. Try to hit as many as possible damage. Yeah.
You don't have any precision, dude. Um, I don't, you don't need precision in a game like this.
It's about surviving waves and mowing down. I don't know why I keep saying that. It's because
it's cause that's like the thing that kind of looks like the Diablo thing, like mowing down
waves of enemies, mowing down monsters. And I sit here and ask myself, when did I,
have I ever cared about that in Diablo? Like I've never have ever. Um, okay. Back speed. Remember,
these are people. Well, they're well, we're in hell. So, okay. What do you want to say?
Uh, cone size. Yep. It's devil spawn. These are not people. These are devil spawn. What are you
talking about? No, this is the, this is the non completely nondescript bad guy character.
So you never have to feel anything about like, oh, what am I killing here? Because they're like,
yes, murder and torture and killing. Like this, you don't feel bad. You can't feel bad about
killing like demon imps. They've, we've specifically been told this for like the last a hundred years
of any like media and video games and anything. It's just, oh, these things are just evil creatures
that hurt stuff. And we're also led to believe that they can just be kind of created, just like
snap. Oh, there's like another 2000 of them. I didn't even read that last part. Hey dude,
can you find Ben Franklin and that person for an hour? This, I have not hurt this guy yet. Uh,
more cone. You actually ban him. What are your thoughts on POE? I mean, I'm excited to play it.
The, okay. So POE, let me go over this. So I've played a little bit of lost dark. I played a
little bit of POE. I've played obviously a lot of Diablo, but my concern with something like POE,
and this is what I've talked to stir about this a few times. Uh, my concern was always,
it's not that it's overwhelming. It's that there is just such an unbelievable amount of content
that I'm going to accidentally open up one of the menus for said content and have, and gets
freaked out. It's kind of like when you open up one of these MMO type games or these like kind of
live service games after a while of not playing. And the game is just like, Hey, you've missed,
um, literally like seven years of patches and updates and changes. Uh, here's like 10 pop-up
windows to explain to you every massive, monumental fucking ridiculous change we've made over the last
five years. It's just, I don't even know where to start. I want to start. And it's not an excuse
because there's plenty of, you know, if you really care, you'll do it. But I think it was just the
prospect of not ever paid paying attention and having to, and even the stuff they were
talking about at exile con was like, Holy shit, this is so cool. You can make a rogue like dungeon
and trade it. And wait, this is, they're bringing this back. Oh, by the way, like stir was telling
me there's like, there's like 15 different end game, like whole zones to like care about and
like make a character around. Oh, by the way, there's like 7,000 uniques in the game. Oh,
it's like, Holy shit. That sounds like the, that sounds like my favorite game ever made.
My favorite game ever made is D2. It's just a fact. It just is what I liked about D2. That's
not in a lot of the ARPGs now is it's incredible simplicity. It was very simple. It was very easy
to understand, but like I could be an item fine barbarian if I wanted to. I think that's what I
liked the most about it is there's like 30 moves. This character has, do you want to be a Raven
Druid? I mean, is that stupid? Maybe, but who cares? Put 20 points into it and have fun. I'm,
that's what I'm looking for. D2 was the worst Diablo game. I mean, you're literally talking about
like my, like my entire identity is based around this game. So like you're, that's a personal
attack, not doom too. That was a, that was a personal, no, not destiny to Diablo too. What
D2 Diablo to not destiny to, I played a little bit of destiny too. It was fun. It was all right. I
didn't, I didn't really get into it, but I could understand why people played it. But I thought
about this the other day. What is it about seeing the beige kind of beige golden letters on the
ground? It's the fact that I kind of don't even know what it is. And even if it sucks, who cares?
It's got like cool artwork and I can give that to like my level three Amazon. It's like a level
five unique. And the thing's a piece of shit. The thing sucks, but who cares? It's like a fun
little thing to collect and it's got a custom art for each little piece. I can, I can keep it
in a little inventory. Everything feels like handmade. It all feels handmade. What don't you
like about D4's uniques? First of all, there's like, when I played D, I played a lot of D4 off
stream. I really did. I'll give you my real, I'm going to give you the real take cause I know I've
been, you know, I haven't been given you the real one. I just don't like the aspects. I just,
I just really don't like that system. I haven't liked the legendary system since D3
and they leaned even more heavily into it. I would rather instead of legendaries with legendary
powers, just get rid of that entire system and just have like three fucking hundred uniques in
the game and have them all fun and interesting and have them unique and have them have cool artwork
and let me collect them. That's it. That's what I want. That's what I want. That's all I wanted.
And then somebody would just say, just play D2. Yeah, that's true. D2 got remastered and the
remaster is very, very good. Yeah. You're right. You're right. You're absolutely right. But I've
kind of been waiting for a D2 sequel for like 30 years. Do you know what I mean? It's just like,
God damn it. I just want, I want D2 more. I want like D2 too. Does that make me an old boomer?
Probably, but that's just how I feel. That's Diablo 3. Diablo 3 is not Diablo 2 too. Diablo 3
is the base for Diablo 4, which is why I prefer Diablo 2. The Diablo 2 item system, I think,
and plus I think about gems. I like to just collect them and you could make them and it's like,
oh wow, I've got like five perfect topazes. Throw that shit into a five, six socket chest,
give yourself some magic fine and go have a goddamn fucking fun time killing Mephisto
four times in a row. Who cares? POE has gems. I'm going to play POE. I'm going to play it.
German, none of those words are in the Bible. No, they're not. Are they? Is the word gem? It
might be. In my honest opinion, Diablo 4 kind of, they kind of just made this game where it was
just, it wasn't about the fact that they made the game. It was the fact that they wanted you to just
play it. It wasn't about making the game. It was about making sure you play it. Do you understand
what I mean by that? Does anybody get that? Like, do you, does anybody understand what I mean by
that? It's not about the game being good. It's about making sure you play it. And let me be very,
very clear. I do think that the Diablo 4 devs really do want to have a good game. I think they
really want to make a great experience. And you know what? Over the next few years, they probably
will. They'll probably make a pretty fleshed out end game system. But the core of Diablo 4, the very
fundamentals of that game, I do not like. So I, I don't, Diablo 2, I don't think I'm, I don't think
I'm ever going to get the sequel that I ever really wanted. And that's all right. Oh my God, gone are
the days of centrist Andy. No, but that's just how I feel. That's just the truth of how I feel.
There are a lot of people that really, really liked D4. I'm not going to tell you that you are
stupid or wrong for liking D4 a lot. I'm not going to say that to you because if you like it, then
you like it. I'm not going to tell you that you can't like it. I'm just going to tell you that I
don't. Okay. You already said that. That I, wait, when did I say that? I'm going to die. But nothing
will ever hit the same as finding, you know, and I want to identify items. I want to identify items.
Do you know what I mean? I don't want to just pick up a bunch of shit and just have it be like
just a mess in my inventory. And it's just green and red letters. And which one is green letters?
Which has red letters? How many, what, what, how many percent? Everything has a percentage on it.
Everything's a percentage percentage to percentage of a percentage to this percentage. So I don't
want to see, I just, I want real numbers. I don't want percentages. Give me a number.
I'm going off. I don't want it like the 20% chance to do 10% more vulnerability damage. If you have
10% more, no, I just give me, I want 25 dexterity on that item. And I want the art to look really
cool. Cause there's a lot of talented artists and shit. And I want it to have beige letters. And I
want to have a big collection box where I can put these items and I want to trade them. I want to
be able to fucking, I want to be able to, I lost, but whatever. He's still going. Okay.
Nobody talks shit about Diablo more than somebody that says Diablo is my favorite game. Yeah,
you got, okay. You've got me here. You do got me, but let me tell you, let me just try to make it
as clear as I can. Diablo two was just such a, was such an unbelievable genre defining experience.
Like nothing really was ever really like that. There was a couple things kind of, but it just,
they just paved the whole road for every action RPG that came after it. And it's hard to play
a game that's supposed to be a Diablo sequel, Diablo two, Diablo three, a numbered sequel.
And have, in my opinion, they go so far away from what made me like Diablo so much that it's not
really even a numbered sequel for me anymore. PoE is better than D2. I think PoE has had a lot more
time of to be developed. Diablo two was, was done by Blizzard North. They just kind of made the game
and it released. There wasn't like a bunch. I mean, they did patches and they added stuff and that
like ladder and everything and D2, the expansion, everything. But PoE has been continuously developed
for about 10 years. Who is he talking to? Um, you. I'm talking to you. How can you call yourself a
Diablo fan when you dislike 75% of Diablo games? I don't, I don't dislike Diablo one. I think Diablo
one was almost like an experiment. I think Diablo two was the first like Diablo is a big game that
everybody cares about now. I think Diablo one was more of like an awesome experiment. All right,
I'm going for it. I want to do the first mission. I feel like I was doing pretty good in that one.
Diablo one's a good time. Yeah. All right. I'm going for it this time. I'm going to go right to
the scroll. I like random. I just don't like everything is random and everything is random
to an extent. Let me give you an example. I know, I know this is like, finally he like took, he like
is, he's finally giving his Diablo four take. I know, but it's been a while. It's been a long
time coming. Uh, what was I, what was I just going to say? I actually just forgot everything. What
was the last sentence I said? What was the last sentence I said? I'm, I was like looking at reading
the, um, the thing up there. What was the last thing I said? Random. Okay. Random. Yeah. I like
random, but I don't like when things are too random, but they're random in a box. Let me give you an
example. For instance, in D four, if I wanted to make like a charged bolt, a charged bolt sorcerer
sorceress, right there, there are items in the game that completely change charge bolts, right?
There's also, you can get us to charge bolts on a pair of gloves or I think it's legs, whatever it
is, but that can only appear on a certain couple pieces of gear. Why can't it roll on everything
else? Why can't plus to charge bolts roll on anything? Why does it have to roll on like one
item only in one specific slot? Why? What if I want to try to get like a bunch of points into
charge bolts? Why can't I just put it on a bunch of shit? And every item seems to like, I don't know,
just feels like when I do a bunch of runs, like, oh, I'm going to do some nightmare dungeons and
then I'm going to do the hell tide or whatever. All right, cool. I have a full inventory of shit
of like a bunch of legendaries and rares and, and now you go, you scroll over to me like,
I don't even know what the fuck half of this shit even is saying to me. Like, what, what,
what even is better? I don't just salvage the whole inventory. This is like, I guess, I mean,
I found the distant enemies are stunned like eight times and I guess I'm just going to keep one of
them. I had a full inventory. I had a full stash of aspects that I was just like, these are all,
I don't even know what the fuck to do with these. Dude, stop being a nerd. People are leaving. Hey,
I've been pressed to give my Diablo four take for like two months and I haven't given it and I'm
giving it to you now. TLDR in Diablo two, even when a piece of shit unique drops, you just see
the beige letters and you go, Ooh, when like a legendary ring drops in D four, I don't even
fucking care. I just don't, I don't even care. It's just like, Oh, that's just going to be a
bunch of random stats and a random aspect. I don't even care. And you pick it up and she's like,
okay, is this like 1% better than the one aspect of this that I already have? I don't know. I guess
throw it away. I guess your TLDR is way too long. Is beige really a deal breaker? Yeah,
it kind of is. And because to me asked that it matters a lot to me. I want to be able to like
pick that item up. Like what was that big mall in D two bone snap, right? It was, it was in,
when you identify it, it like, well, there's the artwork, right? Remember that shit. Remember that
shit. Hey, remember that shit. Remember when you, you, you've, you actually identified it
and the artwork showed up. Give me, give me, I want the items to be, have like, wait, I want
them to fucking have visuals. I don't want them just to be like a bunch of fucking rolled stats.
I don't give a shit about any of that. I don't care about any of that. Go get the scroll. Oh yeah,
I will do the D four ramp, but do it in a quagmire voice now. Hey, so I mean,
Hey, Hey, Peter, so Diablo four. Oh, right. It's, it's actually kind of a, I'm not a big fan of it.
That hurt me physically worse than the Deadpool routine. I, you know, I, I will stand by the
Deadpool routine. I thought that was a good time. I think some of you are hating on the Deadpool
routine and you don't even, you don't even, you didn't get it. I don't think you got it. You didn't
get it. I just don't think you got it. I, you know what I mean? I really think you just didn't
get it. Yeah. Some of you got it, but a lot of you didn't. And a lot of you like hate my Deadpool.
Let me get it. I was reeling in pain. Yeah, it's all right. All right. I'm going to get the scroll.
I'm not, wait, let's read this. Let us into the darkness. Brines awaited with a sacrifice in
exchange for a fragment of the token trade its old master to finally end his atrocious reign.
Go get the scroll, Madge. I'm going, I'll get it. I am 100% going to play POE 2. I will. POE 1,
when the new league comes out. I'll definitely check it out. I already played a little bit of
Path of Exile just because, you know, obviously stir plays a lot and he's like, this is my
favorite game. Please. I know you like D2. Please for the love of God play it. Why do you keep not
playing this? You keep saying D2 is your favorite game ever. Why won't you play the game that is
supposed to be a successor to that game you love so much? Why there's like 70, there's like 10
years worth of content. You'll never get to the end of it. And I go, I'm maybe with a D Diablo 4
might patch in and some more uniques. It's not, it's not going to happen. It's not going to happen.
When I heard that Diablo 4 was bringing uniques back, I rejoiced. I was like, we are going back
to the old Diablo 2 style. It's going to be uniques. It's going to be so, oh, our aspects are back.
And they just, you can pull them off and you have to stick them on a rare. And then like everything's
kind of like, there's no value on anything. And you can't even trade with somebody in your own
fucking party. And trading doesn't matter anyways, cause you get the same piece of gear over and over
again. Cause it's like the smart loot with the class and then everything's scaled and which is
one of the good ones here. I just want crafted items back. You're always complaining, dude.
Enjoy yourself once. I don't think I'm complaining a lot. I'm always, what? No, I'm not. I give a
lot of benefit of the doubt to a lot of games. I'll try. Yeah. I'll do ring blades. All right.
Now I actually, I'm going to level up one more time and I'm going to go get the thing down there.
It's so funny because you remember when I played the default beta on stream, I was going into that
with woo. Uh, yeah. I remember saying very, very clearly, it was like, this feels kind of fun.
The first five to 10 levels of D four, I was like, holy shit, this is going to be the best game I've
ever played in my entire life. I didn't want to say it on stream because I don't, I didn't want
to be like, you know, jumping the gun, right? Turns out it was not the case at all. It was
almost the complete opposite. And I remember saying on stream, hold on. I love this, but I don't,
I got to be really careful. I don't, what if I, let me give it some more time. I'm so glad I said
that. All I remember from that was grip gate. You know, that's like part of that makes me kind of
happy because well, like the weird dumb shit that we talk about on these streams, the fact that the
one thing that you remembered from that whole thing was not the fact that of like my opinion
of Diablo, it was the fact that we talked about like somebody's grip and nothing else mattered on
that stream. Right? So like, we go over a lot on these streams and it's kind of almost refreshing
to know that the only thing that you particularly care about is like me talking about somebody's
grip. You wanted to say Cyclops drip. Yeah. And my compressor cut it off. All right. Now I'm
actually officially going to go get the archment. I know people like bring back room words. I don't,
I don't really necessarily care too much about room words. I just want the, I want the socketable
items to feel good. It didn't feel bad putting a shitty ass chipped ass gem in some piece of
shit gear that you knew you were going to use for like five levels. That was actually useful.
I almost feel like the whole gem system in D4 is completely fucking meaningless.
It is 100% meaningless. Maybe one of them are like, I'm giving you my D4 take. I feel like your rant
is meaningless. I mean, I guess it kind of is. But don't you think my rant about like what kind
of peanut butter is my favorite is also pretty meaningless? I mean, I guess this has a little
bit of substance. Okay. Definitely the orbs. These things are awesome. That would be more entertaining.
Yeah. I'm telling you how I feel. That's what I'm doing. All right. Give me something good.
1% attack speed for five seconds for each killed enemy.
That feels great. It's that one, right? It has to be. Yeah, that thing's amazing. Every time you
kill something for five seconds, up to 50%. Is there an indicator where I can see it? Oh, it's
up here on the right. Oh, I need more damage because I'm not killing things fast enough.
Attack speed. Will you ever do a second run of choose your own Diablo in Diablo? Sorry,
hold on. That was pretty fun. Hardcore where you guys pick there at every point I put in
with D2 remastered. That's much, much easier to do now. Boy, this might be bad. Oh, come on.
Damn it. It's all right. It's all right. It's all right. I never got the key to that cage. Okay.
I got money. How much do I have? I got, oh my God, I have tons of money. I have 4,300 gold.
Maybe defense. Max health defense. Try to get it to last a little longer. Pack range.
I'm going to say this one. Let's do area and projectile speed. That's not what that said.
24% bigger projectile. I think that's pretty good. All right, let's go. All right. I'm going to go
rescue that guy in the cage. Don't skip plus one piercing. Yeah, we were talking about Diablo. That's
my bad. Oh yeah. We were talking about gems. We were talking about gems, gems, gems. Let's talk
about gems. I remember when you start D2, it's just you're going to use your gems. You're going
to put the flawed topaz in this busted up piece of shit, one-handed acts you found and you're going
to get a little bit of lightning damage and you're going to notice it. Here we go again.
Oh, okay. All right. Give me another topic. Give me another topic. Give me another topic. Geez,
man. You're still on. It's been like an hour. What do you want to talk about? Talk about Wendy's?
I like their nuggets. What's the best jam for peanut butter? That would be grape jelly or
grape jam. In fact, I haven't had it in a long time, but they make this product
where it's this weird spiral of 50-50 peanut butter and grape jam inside the same container.
And there was a point when I was eating that shit out of the jar. I was eating it out of the jar
for like 30 straight minutes and I realized what was going on and I had to stop it.
Goobers. Yeah. N.A. food. N.A. food. All right. Yeah. Well, hey, how can you take your crisps and
get the fuck out of here? All right. I'm going to eat Goobers out of the jar. Okay.
He's really patriotic today. Uh, I've ran. I've just we've I've just discussed Diablo
two's item system and I eat peanut butter out of the jar. Does that make me an American?
Is that an American thing? Is that patriotism? Is that patriotic?
Let me tell you something about Diablo. Hey, give me that jar of peanut butter while I go over this.
What's some good British food? Beans, right? Nothing. The only thing I think of when I think
of British food is just like two big fucking sausages on a plate with a bunch of plain beans
on it. And like, that's it. That's like what I think of. But I would eat that. That sounds
pretty damn good. Like, that's fine. I would be okay with that. That's this is not an insult to
an entire country of people's food. No, I'm just I'm that's what I think of. I think of like two big
sausages and like plain beans and I think a toast plain toast that that that sounds pretty good to
me. Remember the cage. Right. Right. Right. I get it. I get it. I get it. Scones. All right. Who has
the best desserts? Who has the best desserts? France. France has the best desserts. I would say
I would say Italy. No, no, no, no. America and Mexico. Yeah. I mean, I I'm trying to think of
what my like really favorite desserts are. And they are kind of American. Unless like where did
like banana cream pie, for instance, who made that up? Where did who made the first banana
cream pie? Who did that? Who? What country did it originate from? That's your go to dessert. I love
banana banana cream pie and banana pudding are two of my top desserts ever. And those of you that oh
my god, are you 80? Oh, yeah. Slurp up the banana pudding, right? Oh, man. No, you you've never
eaten it. You've seen a bunch of old people eat it and you laugh at them. But go eat it. Eat it next
time. And then you then you come back and talk. I know I walked by the guy in the cage, but I really
want I want the abilities first. I believe to have originated in the Midwest of the United States.
OK, so that's American. It's great, too. Oh, what else? I mean, like ice cream. I love ice cream.
Who doesn't, though? And who even made up ice cream? Anybody even know what ice cream be?
Where was where was ice cream invented? China, ancient Chinese planted the first seeds of
modern day ice cream. OK, 600 A.D. in China. I love ice cream. All right, let's go collect and
then I'll get this archman and then we'll go get I have 28 health. What happened? Ice cream. What
else? What else is like another thing up there in a cream pie? Just like a good chocolate ice cream.
All right, I'm going to go this way here. Tiramisu Tiramisu is really good, but I don't know if I
would say Tiramisu is my is my favorite dessert. OK, that's like the thing in vampire survivors.
Oh, speed. What is this gigantic pickup range? This is ridiculous. Oh, my God. I want region.
Oh, that sucks. Oh, that sucks. That sucks. That's hard. Oh, I got a blessing. Health. OK,
all right. Now I'm going to open. I'll open that cage now. I'm going to go with melee.
You suck at this. That's fine. That's fine. I don't care. Defense. Health regen. Wait, I want
much more of that. All right, let's go. Area size is really good. Yeah, I need to do cone size.
First of all, let me go talk to the guy. Let me do the actual mission.
What instrument is that? The thing that goes. What is that thing? I want more regen. I want to be.
I want to be regening like one health, two health a second.
We're going to work on that first while it's easy.
OK, let's get this done immediately. Don't free him. Keep him there. What's with you? What's with
you? I think having more than four or five slots for gems in Diablo three and Diablo two is like
probably the best part about having the gem system. And I'm kidding. I'm not. I got you.
Got you. Got you. Got you. But no, seriously, like I'll seriously the one to two slots per
it's just you've designed it in a way to make it so it can never be interesting.
It has to be this this this calculated thing that you've done where you can have one thing put in
this very specific box of randomness. I want to be able to throw six perfect fucking topazes
into a weapon and waste it and be an idiot. I want six perfect emeralds and a shitty sword
with 600 poison damage over fucking 12 seconds. And I want my friends to make fun of me because
I did that. When I got it, I got the six gems in that thing. Rattle, rattle, rattle. No one cares.
Yeah, they do. I think a lot of people care. I think a very large amount of people care.
Hey, and it's my stream. So I'm going to talk about Diablo 2 gems. OK, so
will he just be at the town? Dude, will you please read the nice comments? I'm a streamer.
I'm immune to those. I only read the ones that say like, hey, dude, like, when are you going to
put a baseball of your ass? God damn it. I had so much help there, too. All right. Cone size.
There it is. Finally. There's a lot. There's like two or three levels right here. Come on.
There we go. I leveled up twice. Range and crit. Yep. Damage and attack speed, probably. Yeah.
Banana ripeness chart. What do you like your banana? All right, hold on. I let me actually
get it like a decent run and then we'll go over the banana ripeness because it's very specific
for me because it depends on what you're doing with it. Is this is this going into a smoothie?
Are you eating this? Is this being put on cereal? It's very important that we go over that. I want
more defense and health. What keeps killing me every time? Crit damage. It barely hurt this guy.
We try to burn him. Oh, that was an unbelievable amount of damage. All right. So ripeness or a
smoothie. I want that shit right before it's rotten. I want an overripe banana to be a good
sweetener or a smoothie. How do you think about that? Yeah, I've got hold on. I've currently got
Tom Hanks voice. Let me hold on. If I want it really sweet, I would say like a little bit before
being overripe is the best place to put it in a smoothie. But sometimes you really want it to
have that really like sugary sugariness. That's disgusting. Whatever. You don't have to eat it,
but not okay. Is there peanut butter in it? If it's a peanut butter banana smoothie,
then I don't want the bananas to be very ripe because I don't want them to overpower the
peanut butter flavor. But then I don't want to use too much peanut butter because I don't actually
want to overpower the banana flavor with the peanut butter. It's a very, very, very hard
balance to get. I'm going all health. That was a really bad idea. I'll be all right. But all
seriously though. Yeah. I like a ripe banana for a smoothie. I like a non-ripe, just kind of right
in the middle. I'm just going to eat it. I do like bananas. I don't know what I just got, but I think
I can. Okay. I don't know what I'm, I don't know what's going on. Oh, it's like super speed. I just
can't kill anything. All right. Damage is a damage is immediate. I need it right now.
This guy's been walking around for 10 straight minutes. Shit. Shit. Cone size. All right. You
have to die. I have to get at least this one boss down, right? Or can I really say I'm a video game
player? There we go. Okay. I hope I'm not instantly dead, but I'm going to do arcane splinters because
we haven't seen it. What are your thoughts on Twitter being called X? I don't care. I use that
app like once a month. Uh, okay. What about this one here? I don't like the projectile size
reduction. I'll take it. All right. What does it do? They stay. Ooh, they, I think they, yeah,
they're still doing damage when they stay. All right. I don't want to lose this because
this has, I have an opportunity here to do pretty good. Let's regen a little. Don't get hurt.
Go get the other parchment. This is where it always goes to shit. I'd like the, okay. I'm dead.
Oh, that was fun. All right. I got the wellkeeper now. What does he do?
All right. What's up with you? Wellkeeper. You've earned my deepest gratitude for the rescue,
of course. And since we've made such a great team down there, I have a proposition for you.
Okay. I had a dream where you made fun of my chat message and literally made chat bully me.
Well, has dried up a long time ago. Now it leads to the very halls. You helped me escape.
Are you waiting to fall breakfast? Make sure you eat a full breakfast in the morning.
All right. I need to pay attention. What does this say?
This well has dried up long time ago. Now it leads to the very halls. You helped me escape.
But if you ever happened to find the other end, you might want to drop a trinket into the bucket.
Oh, whoa. I can just put these on. I have an entire stash of items that I just wasn't wearing.
Do I have to buy these? Wait, 10% health, free defense, 15% movement speed, 20% attack speed,
a shitload. Okay. Well, it says you own them. Attack speed, 10% more health and defense.
All right. This is really cool. Are there rarities? Are there uniques in this game?
Jeremy, your webcam is on and your balls are out. Whatever. I don't care. You have a ring too. Do I?
Oh, it's actually on the character too. Or am I making that up? I don't think I
got out with it. You can buy new items from the well keep it once you've retrieved them
through the well. So there's something down there where I can put items up there.
There are kids here. What are you doing? They really shouldn't be. It just shouldn't be.
It really shouldn't be at all. Okay. Here we go. I'm going to try to get a full run Haunted Caverns.
Adults only. I mean, you know, I've had the mature audience filter on this stream for like
eight years. I just never turned it off because I mean we talk about kind of weird shit on this
stream. All right. Right off the bat. Huge deal. It's not working clearly. It's not working.
It's not working. Bananas are adult content only. Yeah. You guys missed it. We just talked about.
We just talked about bananas for at least 10 straight minutes. Damage. Damage. Damage. Damage.
Damage. I it took me 10 minutes to get to 104 last time. I want to be doing 200 damage before
that first boss shows up. More. Here we go. This is the one. It actually might be because
I've leveled up like three times in 25 seconds. All right. Attack speed. We're going for damage
only. Already at 228 crits. Might as well just might as well just sign the paperwork now.
This is this was this is a done deal. Good. Look at that. Already got a cone with already. But wait
cone or crit? Which one? Cat ages in dog years. Cone omega lol. Everybody said cone. I was going
to pick cone too. So that's what I've decided. I'm getting a lot better at actually physically
clearing, which is what I really should be doing. 10 percent damage. Yep. I have to go. I got to go
for it. These guys take two hits and I try to get them down to take like one. I already took
damage. You might as well just fucking uninstall the fucking goddamn game. Dude, chill. I'm fine.
Range or health? Let's go. No, we're going damage. All right, let's get let's kill this guy quick.
Don't let him just walk around for 15 minutes. There's the well. You can tell he's mad. I'm
really not. I'm just messing around already. OK, already got the first item. Phantom needles. Let's
go. That's a good thing for May Lake because it just kind of randomly hits stuff around me.
Yeah. All right, give me an item so I can drop it in the well. When are you when are you going to
play POE on stream? I don't know. I don't think I might not. I mean, maybe me and stir would play
it just to mess around for like an afternoon or something. But that's an off stream game for me.
I mean, I mean, no, not necessarily. I mean, with the kind of direction that I was telling you guys
about with the channel and everything and more of these streams where I'm just kind of hanging
around, nothing too crazy going on, just chilling. Maybe I would just play POE and just do runs or
something. There it is. Is the cone size thing a joke or doesn't actually kind of doesn't feel
like it because I'm killing things a lot faster now. A slime rancher. No, you silly Billy. You
play more roadblocks. I think I'm trying to set up a MVM. I've got five people that are
willing to do MVM. I think that'd be really fun. Also, I want to open some crates too.
I just have a bunch of different cases from the last six or seven years just sitting in my backpack
and I just don't really know what to do with them. I don't want to do something like an egregious
amount, right? But I'll be like 20 open up like 10 to 25 cases or something. Open a case after
every death. That would get a little ridiculous, I think. Attack speed or crit or maybe pickup
range. Attack speed. Yeah, I was thinking movement speed, but it's just low. Six percent's not very
much. All right, I'm doing a lot better now. Decision time. That's big. This is also big.
They're all big. I really actually don't know. They're all good. Cone width or speed and damage.
Always damage. Yeah, that's true. First boss should be coming any second now. Did you get
the well guy? Yes. I don't have any items to put into the well though. So if I put items into the
well do they go away for this run? I feel like you just immediately deposit any item you find
regardless of if it's better. Yeah, defense and crit damage. I'm killing this guy so much faster
than the last like five attempts. Oh, that's the well. Okay, I just like walked into it.
Well, we might be depositing something right now. Oh, shit. What is it? Ooh. Ooh.
Critical strike damage by 40 percent. We're dropping that into the well. Uh-huh. What is
the thing in the top right? What is that? Is that the kind of attract thing? Cone size. That's my
health. That's a magnet. Should I make my way up there or should I get the... No, I'll get the
parchment first. I have to buy that item from the vendor. My pickup range is so bad. Let's get an
ability. I don't have one yet and it's been like eight minutes plus 10% additional attacks. Oh,
yeah. Double hits. Sing, bro. Bro, sing. I want everyone to just relax for a sec because I've got
something to tell you. We have officially confirmed, officially, that that hit sound,
the needles that are going out. Officially confirmed. That is the plants versus zombies
pellet hitting a zombie that has a bucket on their head. Sound effect. That has been officially not
confirmed by anybody but me. The projectiles are absolutely killer. It's killer. Damage again.
All right. I don't want to get... Hold on. There's so much EXP here. Damage. There's so much EXP. I
have to just leave it. I'll wrap around. Oh, my goodness. I think this is invulnerability.
Give me this. Shit. Shit. Are you an archer or kind of a barbarian kind of guy? I am more of a
ranged damage kind of fan but I do like melee characters. All right. I'm leaving. Another
centrist take. Add it to the list. Another centrist take from German985. Fucking Sag.
Ooh. Is that good? I don't know if that's even good on this character. I mean, I already pierced
with my weapon, right? Or does that work for the ability too? It's only for the ability. Ooh.
Maybe it is good. It is going through them now. Cool. What did this guy do to piss off so many
skeletons? You know, I thought about this the other day. Have we talked about this? The prospect of
the bandits. Look out, adventurer. Make sure to kill the bandits that are surrounding us.
There are like 70,000 fucking bandits in every video game and like 12 people that live in the
town. What's going on here? There are more bandits than people that live in any of these towns like
times a hundred. At some point, are they bandits or is that just the entire human population outside?
Oh, a pack of bandits. It's around our camp. It's me. You. That lady over there. In a healing well.
Adventurer, go out and stop the encroaching bandits. It's about as big as a small country's
worth of people out there. They definitely could have taken that over 100%. Like in D2, if they
just like rushed the rogue encampment, we're all dead. They just they've never tried. Do you wear
a wig? No. Yeah, there's a lot of skeletons too. A lot of demons. I think this is an automatic. I
mean, but this one's good too, though. 10% damage and 10% attack speed is you can't pick anything
else if it's here. You just can't. All right. I think a boss is incoming here. Yep. Remember this
part. Not so tough now, are you? Speed. All right. I don't get cocky because this is the furthest I've
ever gotten. Geez. Lightning strike here. Maybe orbs. I have piercing. I don't think this is. I
should do the blades if I have piercing, right? Always orb. Really? Even with piercing. I'm going
with blades. I think the piercing is going to be good. I need to pick up this shit so bad.
There's so much on the ground. Let me pull everybody over here. OK, health and defense. Whoa.
I'm fine. I need that thing. That thing that sucks everything to me. I would level up like five times.
God damn it. Come on. I was really, really stupid, but I got a bunch of experience. Additional
attacks or health. I had to do it. Point one additional attacks or the movement speed
or health. What the fuck is he doing? I had to go through there because I had to get the item.
Bro, this is boring. Play Persona 4. You're not going to start an account where every day you're
going to say, hey, please, Jerma, please. This is day 50 of Persona 4. Let me help you again.
I probably won't play that ever. So don't make one of those. Persona 4 is good. I know. I'm going
with the health. It might be stupid, but I don't care. I want to live. Did I tell you guys that I
it was like, oh, man, Persona. Persona is such an awesome series. Just try it. And I like I don't
know. I downloaded one of them. It was like Persona 5, but not the actual fucking Persona 5 video game,
I guess. It was like, hey, this is like not Persona 5, but it's like Persona 5, but it's not that game.
I don't know what I did. Additional attacks. You need to focus. Yes, I do. Thank you. There it is.
Yay. There's so much over here. I got it. Low 30 damage. Go on. Let me kill the second boss.
I got him. Block strength, health or probably this one, right? And then deposit this immediately.
Go get the magnet now. I don't have any helmets. He's a terrible. I mean, I don't have any helmets
though, do I? Defense, block strength. Yeah, I'm going with health. I already have this one.
A magnet just dropped nearby. Really? Oh my goodness. It did. You're right. You're right.
Let me go get it. You can only use the well once per run. Oh, all right. Well, let's level up like
15 times more cone size, uh, attack speed, uh, piercing and okay. This is a way. There's a,
there's a lot of shit up here. Hold on. Okay. All right. All right. Now I'm going to give me
the scroll. Oh shit. It's getting hairy. I'm about, I'm hitting the limit here of my character's
strength versus the difficulty of the level. I have a lot of money though. Get the scroll.
I know I'm going, I'm going. Look at all that XP. I'm going to make my way back up to get it all.
I'm going to sneeze. I think I apologize in advance. I cannot hit the mute button because
well, actually I could pause it, but I don't want to lose the rhythm.
Oh, well, geez, there it is. 5,000 in one run. Just do it already. Come on. Damage.
Ooh. I maxed out the strength thing. This would be great if I, if I could win right now,
that'd be awesome. Oh, you're a guardian of the parchment. I can get two of these.
Well, might as well get all three of them. I get the orbs. Oh, this is the end. Yep. Maybe not.
Jesus. Oh, that's yeah. I don't think so. I don't think so, but I'll try.
It's not too bad. I had to tank it for that money. 6K. Can I get to 10K?
Give me the pickup range because I'm definitely going to die soon. Hey, how's the bit rate over
there in a streamer video on demand land? How was it over there guys? How do you feel? How's it going?
It's pretty good. Really? No, no, no. That's it. Let me get one more level. Nice. Okay. Phantom
Rift again. Yeah. Wait, what did that do? Oh, I can't have two. I don't know what I just did.
Why do you hate Persona 4? I don't. It's a really fun game. I just feel like that game takes a long
time to play. Correct choice, but read it next time. Oh, it adds one projectile. Okay, cool.
I'm just going with health and defense now to try to live because I'm actually might be able to do
it. Maybe not. Weird pattern. Okay. Health, right? That's ridiculous. I'm just going to try to get the
magnet thing. If I get health along the way, that's great. No, no, no, no, no. This is bad.
I got a turkey though. That's okay. Come on. Give me another level so I can get health. Health? Shit.
Movement speed. Is there going to be health in here? Good. I only got eight minutes left
and that's a full run done. Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Bad. Oh,
boy. Oh, boy. Oh, I made a lot of, look at all this. I unlocked a lot of stuff. I unlocked an
upgrade. Necromancer. Cool. I got to do blessing for. Oh, I'm unlocking things to upgrade.
Interesting. Wait, didn't I have 6,000 gold? Didn't I have 6,000? Where's this 3,000 come from?
That was kills though. 2,500 gold? What? That's my entire bank account. I think I'm going to get
the pickup range. That's pretty good. Completed quest, increase XP gain. I'll try ranged.
Attention streamer, please play Pikmin 4. Um, I don't know. Maybe. Maybe one day. What's the
goal now? What am I trying to do? Defeat the lich. That's probably the last boss that I just saw.
Uh, deal 750,000 damage. This is not in one run, so just total. Kill 50,000 slimes. All right,
so we need to do astronomer's orb. All right, I want to do astronomer's orb. Let's do it. Okay,
cool. Ever considered disco, uh, elcium? I've considered it, but I have not played it. All right,
where's the strength? Did I unlock one of these damage? All right, that's a big deal. That's a
big deal. 10%, 20%. Wait, let me get rid of some of the... I'm not getting diminishing returns for
this, right? Just like vampire sparrers, because give me the 20% damage. Give me the 20% damage in
the health regen. This is going to be fun. Let me take a sip. Max out health regen. That's a good
idea. Actually a good idea. Maybe I'll do that now. Oh, that's some good cider. I came pretty
close with the melee character. Let's see if I can do it with the ranged character, especially
with that 20% damage. Look at that. I'm killing skeletons in one hit. That wasn't happening
before. Well is right here. Already level one. Health regen. Let's go. Let's do it.
Look at this piercing damage. Attack speed already. Good start. Get the scrolls early, man. Yeah,
that's a good call. That's a good call. I'm gonna go get it right now. You always should be making
your way down that way in the first minute or so, right? What are your theories of the lore of the
game? I don't know. There's just a lot of dead people. These skeletons were once a person.
That was 9% movement speed. It's worth it. Probably more than one person died. Yeah,
probably. I need to wash my eyes. You need to wash your eyes. It's apparently estimated that
about 117 billion people have ever been born. So is that why they're all outside the Rogan
cabin? Yep. Shit, I didn't want to knock that over. I want to leave those. Get an item right now.
Oh, I've got 20% more damage to close enemies. You know that more than one person has been born
today. It's kind of wild. All right. I said orbs, but there's no orbs here. So we're gonna have to
go with the needles. I feel like I've written something down that I really wanted to go over
today. I forget what it was. I was like, I have to talk about this someday. What was it? Okay.
All right. All right. So you know, like the fart sound effects sounds, you know, we all know the
ones like that. A fart sound effect. Don't you think it's kind of ridiculous that those may
have been recorded like 20 or 30 years ago? Somebody farted into a mic and it's been used
for 30 fucking years. Imagine being that guy or being that guy's kids. And it's like, yeah,
that's that's me up there. I'm I farted into a mic 25 years ago and it's just it's everywhere.
How would you feel about that? Imagine like you're just like watching a movie or something and you
hear your fart. You farted. Is it embarrassing or is it like, yep, I get a lot of those residuals
for the fart sounds I did. Yeah, I recorded 20 of them and they're all used and they use the same
ones from like the same library for the last 30 years. But how does how does that guy feel
now that he's like 60? I don't know. That's a lot of damage. A thousand people just left.
They're obviously not strong enough. Fart royalties. Yeah, that me and Holly were
just sitting there and it's just like, yeah, like we just heard that fart sound. That guy
did somebody had to have done that. You think that somebody I saw somebody say that they
think it was a mouth somebody could do. I don't think so. Some of those are very, very real.
I don't know why I just picture and I don't know. You can think I'm looking stupid for this. I just
see some guy just like, hey, yeah, Bill, we need like we need a fart sound. I guess
I'm just imagining the guy taking this and it's like a standard microphone,
the type of microphone that it's got a long cable connected long. It's about at least 10 to 15 feet
long and it's plugged in somewhere and it's got that metal top like a stand up routine.
And the guy just puts it like right between his cheeks and just parts right into it.
These things, he like presses it up there. That's what I see. 18 plus stream. It's been there for
seven or eight years. Okay. That warning has been here for no way. Get the kids out of here.
Get the kids out of here. They never should have been here. They shouldn't be here. Get the kids
out of here. Kids. This is no longer a kid friendly discussion. Your viewers are increasing. Carry on.
I'll take that. And don't you think that the audio engineer after bill like
put the mic right up to where his ass is and did it and it ripped it. It was just awful.
Do you think he's like, Hey Bill, that was fucking rancid. We should do another one,
but this time don't put the microphone like up to your asshole. You should probably do it
a little further away because that was fucking disgusting. I imagine just having two headphones
on just sitting there and it's like, yeah, I don't know if we can, I don't think we should
put that one in. You know what I'm talking about though. All you, all that matters is at least 10
of you get it. You know what I mean? There's like, there's like 13, 14,000 people here right now.
As long as 10 of you understand what I mean by this and like, you get it, then I'm good.
Then we're good. I'm okay with getting the question marks from like 10 plus thousand people. As long
as I know, like six of you are like, yup, I see it. I know what he's, I know what's going on here.
I get it. Lower the bar. Yeah. Well, that's how I make myself feel better, right? I don't care what
the 14,000 people said. I care about what five of you have to say. The five of you that I made up
that agree with everything I ever say. And there's nobody ever disagrees. And it's the five of you.
I have Avengers in this chat right now and you think it's you, you know what I mean?
Just sitting there like, yeah, it's me. I'm the one. It's probably a lot. How many of you just did
that? Oh, let's talk about TF2 cases. I'm curious. So they did a thing where damage, yup. What's the
next among us stream? Uh, it was a one night only. Okay. So cases in TF2. I remember the last time I
really played, it was you opened up weapons cases, but those are no longer a thing. It's now paint
cases that you can put on most anything. And the paint has quality. Is that, that's what's,
that's what's going on, right? Uh, or so this, yeah, there's cosmetic cases and then there's
the paint cases and the paint cases are the old weapons cases, but the paint can now go on most
main, um, like number one in your loadout. So what is considered a really rare case or a really good
case? That sounds kind of good. When you do not use your main attack for two seconds, your abilities
become stronger over time up to winter, winter 2017. I'm not sure which one of these to take.
I feel like this, the range character really needs to shoot the bow. 30 or 40 is pretty special.
Yeah. Holly just reminded me. So let's just take a, let's take a little bit of break and go over
this because you got, some of you guys are going to really, really, you're going to like this one.
Okay. Take the ring. All right. Well, take the ring. But I let, while I have a second to give you a
quick little story, if you had any indication at all of what kind of player is playing the game
of team fortress. So in spawn, when you see that flog pyro in spawn and it's like, what the
fuck is that guy doing? It might be AFK. I, uh, got really high and just ate like almost a whole
bag of chocolates and AFK'd in the spawn as a flog pyro for an entire round. If you're wondering
who is behind the flog pyro, that's, that's what we do. That's what we do. And it, it got me thinking
about, holy shit. I just, I just did that. I lost that match because of you. Yeah. I just,
I had the flog out and I was just sitting there just eating chocolate. And I was sitting there
going, ah, I haven't really done anything this round. I think I walked out of the spawn and died
once. And I think I fell asleep too. I think I fell asleep and woke up at the second round.
So that, if you're curious, that you're, you're right. You're correct. I am that flog pyro. I just
wanted to make sure you were aware. It really happened that I, all right. Which one of these
am I taking? Bro, you're like 45. Not quite. Not quite. Take the ring. TF2's greatest soldiers.
Thank you. Yeah. And then I walk out of spawn and I get the, the, the, the flog up the, with the,
the meter, whatever it's called. And then sniper. It's like, dude, you, you, he's way too far away
and just holding down the crit fire. You're not going to make it. You're not going to make it.
Flog pyros, listen to me. I'm telling you, we have to be better. We have to be better. I know
we can be. Okay. I'll take the, uh, I'll take the ring. I really did just eat chocolate for
the whole round. It was fucked. Don't ever use a Liberty launcher again. Hey, I'm going to use
whatever item I feel like using. This one's really good too though. Well, they were little chocolates.
They were the little tiny ones. So I, realistically, I probably ate like a bar and a half of chocolate.
It was just the little, the little Hershey's mini ones, which you're never ready to eat.
Just one of those. I might as well just buy the Hershey's bars, the full bars,
because I always eat a full bar worth of them. Anyways, what's the point of getting the little
ones? I think 10% tax. What about Hershey kisses? Hershey kisses are good. And I know I look,
dude. Hey, wait a minute. Hershey's tastes like puke. Hershey's tastes like somebody puked in your
face. Yeah. It's, I still don't, I like it. Yeah. And if you smell the inside of a bag of M&M's
after there's no M&M's in it, it smells like somebody's shit in your bathroom an hour ago.
We all know this. Uh, it's this one. It's always the damage. Uh, I need to go deposit this ring
because it's really good. German. Nobody knows this. Try it next time. 10% movement speed. Yeah.
Need to get to that well. Hershey's is a terrible chocolate. Yeah, but it's hard to beat taking a
graham cracker, having a graham. I've taken a nice warm marshmallow, squishing it with the two or
three blocks of Hershey's and making a little more. It's just, it hits so different. I don't
care how gross you think Hershey's is. That hits differently. It just does. It's very, very good.
However many fit. It's sometimes it's too, too little squares. Whatever fits on the graham cracker.
After you eat European chocolate, you'll never want American chocolate ever again.
I trust me. I've had a lot of chocolate. I've had it from all over the world. I've had chocolate.
I've had tons of it, but okay. I've had a lot of like Kraft cheeseburgers and like I've had like
a bunch of stakes before. That doesn't mean I'm never going to eat McDonald's ever again.
Sometimes it's just you, you're looking for a different,
you're looking for a different feel today. A McDonald's cheeseburger is arguably not even
remotely close, not even close to a burger you'd get at a nice restaurant, but I'm still going to
get it sometimes. Should I just go full movement speed piercing? Yeah. All right. Where's the well?
All right. I'm at the 10 minute mark. Where's the boss? I need more attack speed.
Grandpa's on the food podcast rant again. I'm telling you, do not be surprised. Don't be
surprised. I'm just saying don't be surprised if when I am retired, there is a food podcast.
That's like once every few weeks. Don't be surprised. I'm just, I'm telling you what is
probably happening. Do not be surprised. This one hopes are skyrocketing for the food podcast.
You better call it food mode enabled. How one gamer saw his love for food turn into a second
hobby. By the way, we don't talk about food at all on this podcast at all. It's an, and when it's
getting, when it gets brought up, I get annoyed at the guest. Oh my God. That's a lot. This actually
could be the one. So I'm going to pay attention now. So let's put the gamer trying hands on damage.
Let me pause it for one second. Somebody has an explanation. There's a reason American chocolate
has that flavor because back in the early days of Hershey's when transporting the milk got timed
out. Nevermind. Uh, I'm not doing so well. I need more health. Yeah, I have to take it and then
hopefully you drop an item. Come on, come on, come on. You did lightning strike. I like splinters.
They seems like pretty good. I like the area denial movement speed again. You might think
that that's not a smart play, but in about one to two minutes it will be. All right. Uh,
this is the one I want to deposit. That kind of nerves me a lot right now though. So I probably
won't beat it. Who's he talking to? My grandma though. She's right here. Hey, thanks. Thanks
grandma. The fuck do you think I was talking to? Damn. That's a lot. Let's try to collect as many
things as possible. Speed or damage? Yeah. Damn it. I need more attack speed. If I see it,
I have to grab it. It doesn't matter what the other options are. What is that? Anybody know what that
is? 100% damage. Nice. Okay. I want the health and the movement speed. Whoa, there's a lot of shit
over here. Big damage. 8% duration projectiles. Yep. I think I got most of it. Nice. More projectiles.
I got three arrows now. That's awesome. Okay. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Damage.
Where's the boss? Here. Kill. Kill. Kill. Okay. I don't have any of these. When you do not use
your main attack for two seconds, your abilities become stronger. All right. Plus 0.07% damage for
each missing health point. So 0.07 times 589. What is that? 10% crit? That's not very much.
Like 14% right now. I mean, I guess it's okay. I'll do it. I'll try it. I'm doing more damage
right now. So I shouldn't want to get any more health. Oh, that's doing actually a lot. That's
a lot more than I thought it was going to be. Attack speed. Where's the boss? All right. Killed
it. Oops. All right. This actually might be the one as long as I can actually do it.
Not talk about it because I am actually mowing down monsters right now. Attack speed is really
killing me though. I need it. Damn it. That's probably just the orb. Cheese. Two hits to the
shields. All right. Now I'm going up to pick up this thing and I'm going to collect everything.
I just, you know what I'm saying? Carrot only three health. What's the point of even picking
it up? That was three health. There it is. Finally get to five health for max damage. Yeah. But
five health means I'm dead. Didn't one hit. If I'm careful, I could probably do it. There's one more
boss. All right. This is where it gets really, really bad, but I should be fine. Carve a path
out. That's all it is. Forget about any of the items. I'll get them all with the magnet. Okay.
Shit. All right. All right. All right. All right. Okay. Okay. All right. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm
fine. Piercing. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Come on. Just give me it. It's right here.
I'm getting so much health. I need this. I'll level up like three times if I pick this up.
Let's go. Okay. More attack speed. Now we walk all the way back down here.
Damage. Damage. Duration. I don't know. It could be bebecrit damage. All right. This is it. Attack
speed is priority if I find it and just try to stay alive. Nice. Electrified orbs. Orbs deal
additional lightning damage based on their movement speed. What's my movement speed right now? I mean,
that sounds kind of amazing. My movement speed is pretty high. All right. There's another magnet
down here. Get down there. Jesus. Okay. 50% crit damage. I can't go anywhere. Don't freak out.
Don't freak out. Just get out of here. Just get out. Get out of this stupid thing I'm in.
Then I'm going to I'm going to heal. Nice. Nice. Attack speed. I need it. I'm going to stay over
here because yeah, this is where it gets. There's the boss. Play it smart. Oh, there's too many.
Shit. Oh, I was so close. Damn it. Spawning behind me. That sucked. I got a lot of stuff,
though. Ability expert. Elven slippers. Arcane splitter. My next main quest. Cool. All right.
How much does it cost for this? Okay. No, never mind. That's that's ludicrous. Equip the ring.
Ah, pick up range or attack speed. I think I need more defense. Should I keep watching or should I
go shit? I'll be back. I'll be here when you get back. Or maybe you do something else today.
Attack speed. Kind of feels mandatory, doesn't it? And the health. Do I need a shield for block
strength? How does that work? Can do defense or pick up range. No, I want movement speed is so
important. Let me refund to all. I got 11,000. What do I damage? 30% more damage. 18% more attack
speed and movement speed and pick up range. And I got my items on. So what's the next quest?
I haven't been here in a while. What's this place? Okay. Kill 15,000 enemies in one visit.
Kill 50,000 imps. Defeat the flame dancer. Survive the ember grounds until there are 12 minutes left.
I can do that. Kill a thousand enemies in one visit. I can do that right now. Let's do it right
now. It's 12 minutes. That's it. Wait, that's actually kind of a long time. I'll try. We have
a stretch break. Um, yeah, it's been like three hours. I'm going to go get some water. I'll be
right back. Hey guys, I just stood up to go get some water and there are orcs outside of my room.
That's the orcs are coming music. Be right back. How is the uh, how's the fight against all the
orcs going in my absence? We are losing. Uh oh. Let me get in here. Hey, let me get in here and
get this all sorted out for you. All right. What I just have to live until there's 12 minutes left.
All right. I got it more. Look at I'm already doing a ton of damage. There's that progression
system. Speed. Speed again if it's there. Crits. I'm building attack speed first as fast as I can
so I don't have to worry about it later because I kind of got all caught up before
because I didn't have, I wasn't doing enough dps. All right. Range. Pick up range. We're going with
a utility build. We're going to go with some utility. Wow. That's great to get right now.
Sometimes I do block. I'm curious how that system works. Is it just straight up a percent to block?
Chance. Get more defense. Read the thing. Kind of good but damage. Don't listen to that person.
Ban them. I don't even know who you're referring to. There's a lot of people here.
Hey ban that. Ban that guy in chat. Don't listen to them. I've actually been at like a stadium
and I just hear from like row eight. Seat number like fucking 400. You're going to ban that guy.
Ban that guy. Ban him. He's a piece of shit. And I'm just looking. I don't know who. Who?
He's like that guy. That guy right there. That guy. He's pointing. It's like dude there's like
600 people where you're pointing. I don't know that this one. This guy here. No you fucking idiot.
No you're so stupid. You're way off. This guy. This guy right here. No. Ban that. Ban that guy.
Always attack speed. Am I at the cap? Why do I feel like I'm at the attack speed cap? It feels
like it. Is there a cap? I don't think there would be. Damage again. I gotta get this to 200
really quickly. More crit chance. Crit damage is great but you actually have to be critting.
So let's get that situated first. Now we can get it. I mean we. Why do you keep saying we? I don't
know. How close am I to? No not even close. Never mind. Wells right here. If he dropped something
good. Get these little shell fucking things out of here. God that just took half my health.
Okay it's not an item but it's archment. I'm already almost dead. Oh thank god it's saving us. Okay
now slow it down and get some health. I can't even get in there. That little shit has like a thousand
health. All right. Uh splinters. Attack speed. Am I at a cap? I feel like I'm not swinging faster
for the last like three times I've done this. You are? No cap. No cap. No cap. Are you sure? 1.8.
No cap. No cap. Um I guess there is no cap. I feel like I haven't seen a 20% increase. I'm
gonna piss people off for that. There it is. 25% critical damage main weapon and then a 10% cone
with with the main weapon. Okay collect the part that sucks. I haven't seen this guy before. Oh
no wait we have. Very briefly. Oh yeah I remember this. It is this guy. And goodbye. I got further
than I did before. That was hard. I did that at least. Character exterminator. I unlocked a new
character. It's the exterminator. Cool. It's a ranged character. Movement speed. Attack speed.
Yeah I'll keep other. I'll keep the rest of this one. This is the worst character. Um let's find out.
I got one of these done. Beat the lich. One run. Geez. All right I'm gonna try to get to the end.
Haunted caverns. It's a flamethrower guy. What do we do? Attack speed. I'm imagining it's probably
just spray. All attack speed. Don't touch that. Not yet. Seems kind of fun. Blog gaming. Oh yeah.
Where are my chocolates? The auto attack is funny because it just holds the button down.
Useful whatever. Getting some kind of shit rolls here. Should I turn on auto aim too? Yeah. All
right I'm playing just with I'm playing with my left hand. 10% burn chance. I guess that's good.
Attack speed and burn chance. This doesn't do very much damage but I guess it stacks. This sounds
like shaking a bunch of colored pencils. It that might even be more accurate than the lego comment.
Yeah it's grabbing a bunch and I mean at least 30 colored pencils and when you do that you get a you
pick up as many as you can and then like six or seven drop on the ground. Yep oh I know. Speed.
Follow the blood. I was gonna say who is that my blood? Whose blood is this? Uh what is that?
Uh oh. 100? 100 what? What does that mean? 199. Why is it counting down? Don't leave the area.
Kill 99 things inside of it. This character. Probably lightning strike because I don't have
to do anything. It just does it automatically. I'm gonna do lightning strike. So kill things inside
of here okay. That hurt a lot. Definitely more range. All right three two one zero. What is that?
Was that a super item? Like a piece of something? Okay I actually want to aim now because it's
aiming erratically in random directions. Oh shit. You know I have area. Rejectile area
is I think what you need to put on with this guy. All right follow the blood back but don't die.
10% is not very much when it's 28. Like one or two damage. Oh wait where's the blood? I forgot
about the blood trail. Where'd it go? Where's that blood trail? There it is. Okay now give me
something else. I kind of like this character. Am I going to keep saying that in another five
minutes when I can't hurt anything? Probably not. I know. Yes safe safe. I'm trying to be safe.
Safe Andy. That's me. I want help. I could. That scared me a lot. I just did not expect
it to be there right there. Sorry I know I'm like kind of chilled out tonight and that was a very
loud sound. I do apologize. It's actually kind of good against bosses though. What do we got?
Base crit, defense and block, spike boots. When hit drop 10 spikes to the ground that deal 100
damage and stun the enemy on contact. Takes four seconds to recharge. I mean just the crit. Yeah
those are cool. What does it say? And so it came to pass that the countess who once bathed into
rejuvenating blood. I think I have that. I have that area. I want to deposit the
item that I got because I'm afraid of my death. Will this work with fire? It does. Oh
then I want it. I'm gonna pick this up first because I think I can collect a lot of things.
What was that? 10,000. I know I didn't forget about the blood. I just want to get this because
I can level up probably two three times. 10% burn chance. Yep that's a 20. Is that it?
There's gotta be more than that. Well stream from a library computer. No range. Yeah.
Okay all the bone rattling. Yeah it just kind of sounds like this colored pencils all over
the ground. They're just a bunch of rats running in circles. Does this mean that they'll come out
faster? I think so. All right where's this other piece? Any more range? I picked it up a couple
times. About the last few times though. All right here it comes. I gotta kill 90 people in here.
That's not too bad actually. As long as there's no time limit that's fine. Area yep. Oh there's so
many in there. All right only one more. I got it. I got the whole thing. So now I go back to that
podium. All right I'm gonna kill this elite. It's gonna give me a bunch of stuff. Fuck I'm gonna die.
How many elites are there? I'll just run. There's so much bullshit everywhere.
I need health. I just did I actually just lose it right when I picked it up? Come on.
That's a big stinker right there. All right orbs. Some health regen and defense. More damage.
So far so good. Ah shit. This one. You're gonna play portal 2 ever? I played through portal 2.
I think like two or three times so I don't think I would ever stream portal 2. I mean
maybe to go back and be like hey remember how good this game was? I guess I'm just gonna play it.
Oh my god. Okay that was just a I was like a blessed more range. Oh yeah okay more attack speed.
All right don't blow this now. I need to get healed. Blood trail up. I'm afraid if I deposit
this thing I'm gonna get killed by whatever comes out of it. Oh whatever. I guess we'll see it.
People are calling you the pirate of twitch because you don't brush your teeth. Is that true?
Yeah that's why they call me that. Ah my teeth are fucking black and gray.
They don't brush me teeth. I never have it. I never will. That's my whole stick. I look
out and doesn't brush his fucking teeth ever. And I look into the camera and I go like ah.
I do that every every like five minutes. No I don't want to die please. I want to at least
deposit this thing. No. Where is it? Where is it? Somebody said a stupid pirate joke and now I've
I forgot where I am. Where is it? It's right there. I'm just gonna kill this fucking guy right now.
He's gonna keep just messing with me. Hurry up and die. Did that just save my life? It may have.
Oh my god damn it dude. I don't. All right all right all right all right. I gotta I just got
the first time I ever played with that character. That's the first time I've ever played with that
character okay. Fire damage is now a blessing. I got a new ability. A dragon's breath or something.
Like I had you have to play to unlock stuff. Fire damage. I'm just gonna go all in. Fire damage and
damage. Bow and attack speed and projectile size. Can you please say please? Go wide not ah that's
actually true. So this is wide and a shitload of fire damage. I'll try it. I could afford this.
Let's do it again. This is fun. I like this game. All right so what do we what do we got?
I have to kill the lich. Kill a bunch of slimes. How do you do 750,000 in one run?
This is not in one run so I'm gonna try to take lightning strike again. Stop dying.
Play for 333 minutes. How long has that been? Kill 100,000 enemies. Crit enemies 50,000 times.
Deal 10 million damage in total. It's almost there. Collect 20,000. Apply damage effects.
Kill a total of 10 bosses. Almost there. Apply debuffs 50,000 times. Story. Wait there's a story.
Reach level 60. Ah it's individual character stuff. Destroy objects. All right reach level 30 with
the exterminator and then burn. Can chat have a lala? Um in like another six or seven hours.
I like that each class has their own individual trees kind of go through.
Hold on let me put this up here. Did it work? Did not. No teeth. Hold on. You guys are linking
like pirate faces. This is just this is the okay this is the weird magician one right where I was
like I drank the chaos potion. This is the chaos potion one but this one's a little bit different.
Okay this is I drank the chaos potion but have since kind of learned to to to be okay with the
chaos potion enabled. Yeah this is 10 years later after I drank the chaos potion. That's
that's a good one. That's a really good one. Somebody said dude that looks like a heroes of
might and magic portrait. It yeah that's perfect. That's an actual good one. Yeah we'll we'll let
them hang out down here for a little while. Okay face cam. Oh yeah face cam. Look face cam tonight.
All right so I did burn damage. I need to do I just have to kill I just I just have to survive
to level 30. I should be able to do that simp very simply. Burn damage is way higher. My
the other stuff that I did should be good. All right I'm going attack speed. Speed and burn.
Speed and burn. Speed and burn. I need to I don't care about any of the items. I'm not doing
anything weird. I just want to get to level 30 on this character. Regen. I want I want to get to
like two to three health a second. Germa nine matey five. Nice uh hold on this is the character
I'm playing as. That's like my portrait. I feel like that is gonna just start moving around
like a full motion video game. When I die that guy over there on the screen is gonna just start
saying things and then he's it's gonna cut and it's gonna be back to the regular place like
right there. So he's gonna be like oh almost had me that time and then he's gonna just cut back
to being a static health regen. I'm going for it now. I know I should have gotten the other thing
but let me try to get to like one health a second. It'd be so fun to make an FMV game.
You know I've thought about that over the years. It's just I it'd be so fun to make one of those
like an old like an old shooter. Get the stunt people make a whole thing over. I think it'd be
so fun to just like do that. Speed. You officially lost your marbles. I don't think so. I think I'm
okay. I think I'm doing fine. Are you still making that video? That video was put on hiatus and I
just never opened it up. So yes I still I do still think about it very frequently. It is in my brain
very frequently. One day you will see. One day you'll see. It's not really a big deal. I I've
been talking about this video but I'm trying to set expectations to zero. It's literally one thing
I think is funny for about eight to ten minutes straight. Oh this is new. Dragon's breath. Damage.
Yeah what does it do? Ah it just shoots it out like a big wave. Sorry so it's just double fire.
Oh point 15 additional flame walls and 10% area. Yeah just keep this still as your face cam for the
rest of the streams. If I actually looked like that I would probably have face cam on every day
and I would just I would move my face around and be like yeah I would be it would be so fun. It'd
be so fun to have just like a full head of hair and a gigantic beard like that. I would make all
kinds of face movements. I would be unbearable. I would be unbearable. Do a vtuber thing.
What happened? Yeah there's all there's lots of things that I've said I wanted to do but just
never did it. We talked about the idea. I don't know. Yeah we did. I wanted to make a disgusting
slime avatar and just have a big cigar hanging out of the mouth and just be awful on stream
and start at zero and don't tell anybody and just be fucking awful and toxic and mean and shit to
everybody. Just like talk shit to people in chat like if somebody even asks like a very basic
question just tell them to like to fuck off and just like make fun of them and stuff.
This character would be unbearable. All right if that account gets banned do I get banned
or can I go no it wasn't me it was it was the goblin it was the goblin. That's burn damage is
doing a lot more. 50. I feel a lot stronger in this one. Definitely going to improve even more.
Ah which one? Burn chance or additional attacks? I feel like burn chance is probably what to do.
Is multi hit just best in slot for every character? It probably is. WM1. Sometimes it works. I'm going
to make my way down to that. Level up one more time. I always damage. All right let's get rid
of this guy quick. Let's try not to get hit once. All right that was that was clean. That was really
clean. It was very clean. Feels very good. I think it's this it's this one plus 10 to base attack
damage that just it's definitely the ring. Look at that. That's amazing. All right now don't mess it
up because this could be the one at least to get to level 30. What am I missing right now? What
what could I what could I use? What could I really need? What do I need? Besides the scroll more burn
more attack speed more movement speed more regen. I am very slow that's true. You need a lot of
really more movement speed than this. Okay I definitely feel very slow so good idea. This
fucking pirate picture is so weird. Yes 10 million damage total. What do I get for that? I kind of
look like somebody cosplaying as a pirate that takes it dead seriously and at a convention you
see the guy that looks like this and you're like holy shit that guy take this guy that guy means
business. That guy means business. That's huge. You guys are you guys are fucking crazy. All right
I gotta get this scroll. Are there two of them now? Wait why are there two of these? No though okay
the one the that one is I leveled up five times and I think I'm the fucking man even though I'm
essentially the same character. I'm just like level six instead of level one. All right I gotta
get back to pay attention. This shoe is through people especially the ability power I think is
great. Um health regen yeah I need it I want it. I can't just do offense only it's the only reason
why I keep losing. Wow that's so good that was very good holy shit. I just I actually want to
say this but it is the title but I just mowed down an entire wave. What is this? I hate this.
I hate this. Okay I'm gonna use it. What is going on in the world man? What is going on in the world?
Hold on. What is happening in the world? We've gone too far. How come it's not moving? It's not moving.
This one's supposed to be moving. This is a gif. I can't get it. Can you make it a video source?
I don't think so. Hold on. How come this is not playing as a gif? He got he got closer.
Yeah I just I just leaned in like five feet. Save it as a gif. Okay it's very weird. Okay I I have
like so many of these saved to my desktop now. No that was a wrong one. I didn't want to put
that one on. I have so many versions of this now. Okay there it is. Did it work? Why not? Why not?
This is just this is a different guy. This is not even me. All right I'll leave it for five minutes.
Uh movement speed. I need it. More regen if I can get it. Yep I want it. Okay I'm almost at one
per second which is a big deal. I think this is the one. This is a great great great great great
great great start. What should I actually get with this character? Because I really don't know. Orbs?
I don't know. Orbs kind of feel not I don't know feel like orbs aren't really doing very much.
This is creeping us out. Needles? Give me another dragon breath. Raid coming in. Vine sauce raid.
Vinny. What's up Vinny? Welcome raiders. Welcome ein sauce viewers. Oh and my face cam was just
off. Let me turn it back on. Throwing the beard out a little. Thanks for the raid Vinny. Hope you had
a good stream. I hope you guys had a good time watching. We're playing halls of torment. Games
fucking lit. See I can talk. I'm I'm with it. I'm hip. You have to see Austin powers.
I'm cool. I'm with it. I'm hip. Oh that one. Austin powers is so good. It really is. Yeah.
All right so I'm gonna turn this off to not scare all of the vine sauce viewers. This thing is
gonna be disgusting now. Look at that. Look at that wave. Look at that wave of death. Sorry
I got a little uh a little overzealous there. Which one would you pick? I'm not sure which one.
I'm leaning towards attack speed or defense. Any of them? Yeah this is like vampire survivors
but it's a little different and I'll tell you this is very good. I've played a lot of the vampire
survivor likes. I think this one is probably it's it's definitely not probably the most fun I've had
in a vampire survivor's like that was not vampire survivors. I think that with time with a ton of
additions because the game's not even in beta yet uh I think it seems pretty good. This seems
pretty fun. It's a good baseline. Depends on how much they add. Have you tried bro tato? I have. I
have played bro tato but this to me feels the most like vampire survivors. The same kind of
aesthetic. Remember what we said. I'm all about aesthetic. It sucks that I have to choose this
but I'm going to. Ah yep. I think I'm all right now. I don't think I need movement speed anymore.
All right go get the parchment. Have you tried to hollow cure? I have not. I have not. I don't know.
I don't know. Is it good? Is it like a vampire survivor's game?
I got it level 30. Nice damage with the yeah 20% more damage. I don't get caught up here.
This is a good one. I got a good run going. I'm melting these things. Remember how horrible these
were an hour ago? Not even like 40 minutes ago. I just did a million fire damage. Dragon's Breath
knocks back enemies. Yep. Damage. Nice. Oh I'm gonna unlock the whole tree for the exterminator.
Crit chance. Health. Um have I haven't deposited an item. Have I take the boots? I think I want
to take this and deposit this one. This thing is just uh yeah I'll switch the room. I want to
deposit this. Yeah I'll take the hood and deposit the drink. All right this is where I have to
snowball big time because even though I'm doing a lot of damage and I'm fine that changes very
quickly in four and a half minutes. I'm going to go I'm not going to do the well yet but I'm going
to do the um might as well. I'm going to go grab that magnet because I wonder how far away it is.
Crit chance now. If it shows up yeah. Pick up range is a big deal too. Yeah I have completely
completely neglected pick up range. I do kill things very quickly though.
Oh this is like god mode. No it's not just invincibility but just take the opportunity
to run fast. Geez that hurt. Pick up range or let's just do it. I'm safe right now. Plus I'm
going to level up a ton of times in about 10 seconds. Rotato doesn't have a good art style.
Rotato was very fun. Rotato does this thing where they say hey do you like this game. Oh you do like
this game. Well okay well now you're going to play it for a thousand hours because there's like 200
characters and there's seven difficulties. Like oh okay and each character needs to beat each
difficulty. Have fun. Okay well now that's that's awesome. Yeah I played a lot of Rotato on the
iPad. I know. I didn't want to tell you. Crit uh more regen whatever. Offense is not a problem
right now. Always going to be moving forward. That's uh oh. How far away is this thing? There
it is. Mow it down. Mow it down. All right go. There's your crit damage bonus. Should I just get
more health? Yeah. Uh more area. Oh yep. Come on. Additional flame wall and more area. This is maxed
out. 20% more range and more area. That's maxed out. Movement speed. Holy shit. Trans-transfiction?
Transfiction? Virus projectile is in the direction you're facing. Damage is reduced for every enemy
hit. What's that? Is this good? Damage is reduced for every enemy hit. Just get orbs instead. Well
what about lightning? It's archer as an ability. Do not pick it. Pick this. Pick lightning. Orbs.
Orbs I think is lightning is the safest because I don't have to think about it. It just will hit
stuff. Uh crit chance. There's so much shit everywhere. Uh piercing? Does that work for fire?
I think I'm just going crit. Yeah. All right get it all. This pickup range is such dog shit. All
right. I'm about to fight the boss. I've not I've not killed this yet. Oh wait. This actually
will be great against these enemies because these things are so annoying. They just like kind of
cycle on you. Oops. Oh shit. Oh my god. I'm freaking out. I'm freaking out. I'm all right.
Everything's fine. Everyone relax. Shit. Oh I'm just I'm just barely barely. I'm okay. Everything's
all right. I am taking a lot more damage than I should be though. Uh god. Well worst thing that
happens is. All right. All right. Holy shit. Oh my god. It's just too many. Die you piece of shit.
Yes. Oh elven slippers. I gotta deposit something. Increases block strength while moving. Builds up
by moved distance. Block strength is limited to 10. Movement speed buffs increase the cap. Standing
still remove. I I have to read that like five more times. Increases block strength while moving.
So I can build up to 10 block by moving around. If I have movement speed buffs that goes over 10.
But if I stop moving it's all gone. Uh how why would I not have take this. 4% additional damage
for each burning enemy. That's unbelievable. I hope I don't die instantly after taking this.
Um I guess just put it in my backpack. Okay here we go. I'm already at the cap. No don't lose it
right now. Come on. I have to go deposit this. Wish me luck. Shit. Okay. Uh range. I'm gonna do
range. I have to keep that helmet. It's imperative. Oh fuck. Put it in. Okay. All right.
I'm good. I'm good. This thing is amazing. It's gonna kill the run but it's okay. Don't. I want
to put this up. No. I want to put this up here. How do I put that up there? Okay. Geez. All right.
This is gonna be the end here. Got to keep finding spots to move. Five more minutes of this. I don't
know about that. We'll see. If there's health I'm just gonna take it. I'm going for healing only at
this point. There we go. Oh this is not good. Health. Block strength right? Quick. Don't think
of a pink elephant. Why did you do that? There's a magnet right above you. Pick up range. There is
a magnet right here. All right. Here we go. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Holy shit. Um even more dragon's breath.
Oh. Uh. I'm dead. I'm dead. Uh. I'm okay. There's cheese right here. I'll give me a healing potion.
Yikes. Avoid the slimes. They're the worst. They turn into like five enemies. Huge. I thought the
pirate image was still up doing the animation. I was about to be like oh shit. How do I take that
off? Healing. Jesus. There's so many. This way. This way. There's a gap. There's a gap. There's a gap.
This way. How much time is left? Like a minute right? I don't want to look. 20 seconds. All
right. I got it. I got it. I got it. Just don't get cocky. Yes. Oh shit. It's a real boss.
Okay. Well you do that. Oh this is hard. This is hard. Oh man. Damn it. I took a lot of damage
early. Just learning the move set. That was the downfall. I unlocked a lot of stuff. It's a lot.
Trait. Stance. Proficiency. Four. I got a lot of money. Ring of fire. This character is good.
Trait type. Flammability and recovery. Firewalker boots. Sparking tips. Cleric. Oh new character.
Unlocks upgrades stream of fire. All right. I probably have like five or six grand. Ten grand.
Cleric. That's so much money. It's so good but I think. What's the cleric? Wooden ring is the best.
It just. Yeah. It's just great. I'll just get. I want to buy upgrades though. I don't want to buy
all these items. I want the pickup. Attack speed's great but I feel like I'm lacking. End of the
stream. No. I'll play. I'll do a couple more. It's a chill stream. The whole stream is end of the
stream voice. I think this is good for now. I want to do some upgrades. Okay. What did I unlock?
Health capacity. Did I have that? I think I had that before. Turn on auto aim. It's efficient. I
had it on for like at the end of the boss fight there. Just trying to focus on dodging the circles
but I got hit too many times. I don't know what this character is so I'm just going to do some
basic stuff. I think that's. I mean you can't go wrong with damage and you can't go wrong with
attack speed. So I guess that's what we're doing before we figure out what this character does.
You feeling beachy today? Yeah. Whoa. Okay. What kind of damage is that?
Dun dun. That's a lot of 500. All right. This is if you want to do damage on this
and attack speed. I'll try the auto aim. Should I plug the controller in? Let me try it with
the controller. I'm curious. How does it work with controller? How fun is it with controller?
Because I just have auto aim is on and it moves in my d-pad. It's actually recommended. Much better.
I do prefer analog moving around with a character like this. Auto and use your thumb stick when you
want to clear in front of you. Whoa. That's a million times better than what I was just
doing for the last five, four and a half hours. Well, that's for those of you that want to be
precise. Uh, then no, but you can be precise. I I'm holding the analog and I'm aiming.
Is it on game pass? Is it like vampire survivors? I would say it is heavily influenced by vampire
survivors. Heavily. I will tell you this is probably my this is I'm enjoying this a lot.
This is I played every vampire survivors DLC. I feel like I'm starting vampire survivors over
at zero again. And that's something that you just can't do. You can. But I mean, after you have
hundreds of hours in vampire survivors, I get to start over it on a whole new one. Now that's fun.
So I can just aim here. Wow. Okay. That's disgusting. I wonder if it's good to do it
with this character. Let me just see what it does. It shoots out. It's pretty frequent.
I thought it was going to be a lot slower than that. Clerics cannot crit. That's why they are
doing so much damage. I see. But I just did. And I just crit. I just crit right there. Wait,
do you mean the the move there, the actual auto attack that I have? Because I have not seen that
crit. I got one guide. I don't I have not seen my regular attack crit though. I think they're
correct. I think they got it right. The abilities can create but my this cannot. I don't think.
Technically they're correct. More projectiles. Yes. You just start with zero crit. Okay, base
zero percent. But it's improvable. This is the kind of character I really like to play. I like
massive damage. But first, I think it's fun. 20% more damage and more range. Yeah. Look at that.
It's doing less damage. Wait, it's doing more damage based on the distance. Is that correct?
Am I wrong? I'm trying to figure this out. Splits between the AOE. This is a boss killer.
It's divided on who's hit. That's a boss killer then. It's doing 400 damage. 600.
Yeah, that's crazy. So then I should start building crit because then now I have five percent.
A crit with a thousand damage on a boss would be ridiculous.
Area. Somebody's first time chatter. I think I'm I think I'm turning into mush. I'm gonna help you
here. Let me help you out here. Get a glass of water. Drink a glass of water. Sit down. Stretch
for a little bit. Stretch both your arms up in the air. Stretch up. Kind of puff your chest out a
little. Stand up. Kind of move around. Let that water really just get into your muscles and into
your muscle fibers. Make sure you're going outside and you're getting at least five minutes of
sunshine a day. I don't care what you do out there. Just go out there. Let the sun hit you in the face
for five minutes a day. At least. If it's really really hot where you are. The sun is just beaming.
Put on a little bit of sunscreen. Put on a little bit of SPF. You'll be all right. You gotta turn
that vitamin D into you got you have to synthesize the vitamin D in your body. Let that sun just hit
you right in the face for a few minutes. Synthesize the vitamin D in your bloodstream. But you can
take a supplement. You cannot. You cannot supplement our mother earth. Well, our son.
Is that what he goes? Okay dude. Okay dude. This is. Look at how much damage this does.
Thousand? I gotta get him alone. Wow. Okay this character is filthy. An iron mouse raid.
What's up? Thank you iron mouse. Welcome everybody. Thanks for the raid. We're just chilling out
playing some halls of torment. Thank you iron mouse. Hope you had a good stream. Raid song?
We did get two raids but it's. No. But thank you. Welcome. This game is sick. It's very good. And I
believe. Tell me if I'm wrong. I believe the beta comes out tomorrow. The beta for this game I think
is tomorrow. They're adding a bunch of stuff tomorrow. That's pretty. That's pretty cool.
Iron mouse loves it. It's great. Yeah. Iron mouse you got great taste. Uh it's it's a wind crown.
Remind me to deposit this because I'll forget. Show your your your vtuber model.
Oh you mean this. I mean this old thing. This is. Fuck. Stop it. Stop it. It's allowed to be up there
for 10 to 15 seconds. It's been way longer than that but it's okay. That's what it looked like
in real life by the way. I just want everyone to know that. Funny sometimes I'll look in the
mirrors. I've tried to grow a beard before and it's just it's very it's very hard to do. More attacks.
Yep. Okay. That's all we needed that for. Any tips on growing a mustache. No my facial hair is
like I'm like the scarecrow. It's it's like straw coming out of my face. I can't do it.
It's funny the last like couple of months I've tried but a month will go by and then we have a
string of 110 115 degree days and I go I can't I gotta get this off. It's it's driving me crazy
and then another month will go by and I'll be like you know I'm gonna try to grow the beard again
and then and it's another string of 115 degree days and like get this off me. What's the name
of your pirate vtuber model. Oh that's easy. Arthur. Everybody that came from Iron Mouse's
channel you can leave now like that. I get it. I get it. If you're you know that was so all I
yeah I get it. Like if you want to just take off. I get it. I'm really sorry. If you're here for if
you're in my community that's here now you can you can leave too. You can leave too. That was
that was that was a that was a lever. That was a lever. You can that was like you're hovering
over the X. Yeah it's time to go. I got like dinner to eat and shit. No stay stay stay stay please.
What was Iron Mouse playing? What was Iron Mouse doing? Wrist Drain. That's another one that I
really want to. I feel like me and Italics played that for a day or two or me at least stir as well.
I feel like we played that really really really early in the early access years ago and just
never played it ever again. Early adopter abandoning Andy. I feel like that happens a lot
whenever I play an early access game. I play it and I go oh whoa this sounds this looks so much fun.
This is cool. Oh it's not going to be done for like four years. Oh okay I guess I'll come back
later and then I just don't come back. I don't know if that's entirely true because I feel like
there's some early access games I really got into and kept playing later. Yeah name ten.
Coin game. Was that game in early access? It might it may not have ever been. Oh that's one.
Vampire Survivors. That was another big one. Yeah I played that pretty much all the way through.
Ultra Kill. I've played pretty much every Ultra Kill update. There's three. I played the Gloomwood
demo. I didn't play the early access. Technically you went back to Diablo 4. Oh wait is this a
Diablo 4 is an early access joke? Oh I see. Let me tell you about Jam. You played the beta?
Yeah I played the beta. Hey how do you how do you guys feel about Diablo 2?
Crippling cuts add shots in a backwards direction. I mean I want to see it. Plus 166 base damage.
I'm not sure which one of these is the one to take. Probably the fourth one. What about Dark
and Darker? Yeah but Dark and Darker sits in a weird place right now. I'm not sure if that
game is ever going to release. I mean I don't know the story. I kind of caught up on the first part
when it was kind of came off steam and everything. Which isn't that's unfortunate because I really
did I really liked that game. So I don't know what the deal is with that but I I mean me and
Holly were sitting around talking about it. It's like oh man Dark and Darker I think this is going
to be the game. This is going to be the game that I play a lot and I'm going to put a bunch of time
into it. I love it and it just gets fucking delisted from steam. The one game that I talk
about how much like oh man I'm super excited about it has been delisted from steam and there's like a
lawsuit now. Oh well I was excited about that one. I think you just like the dark fantasy setting.
Oh yeah absolutely. Dark medieval fantasy is probably my favorite setting. Have we decided
which one I'm taking? It's supposed to still be coming out. Well I hope whatever happens I hope
it gets resolved and I hope we get to see a cool product but yeah we'll see. Take one. One is more
yeah that's I don't know. I was never a big Tarkov fan but the concept of Tarkov was really
interesting. That you need to take items with you and if you don't take them with you they're gone
but you do have a stash. That it was a lot of I don't know it's cool that's cool that you just
kind of I'm gonna put on all my good stuff and really try this time and then you get killed in
one hit in the head and you throw your hands up and go well congratulations you just opened up a
fucking loot pinata and then that we make that person's whole week. I never thought I'd hear you
talk about Tarkov. I just wish and this is just me being a selfish selfish person maybe it's not.
I just wish they would stop making shooting games and spend more time making games that
could work in that world in that sort of shooter br kind of world and I just want I wish we got more
stuff that wasn't a shooter. Dark and Darker was not a shooter but it followed the same rules as
a lot of those games that are shooters. Does it hurt being so correct? I don't even know if it's
a correct or incorrect thing it's just what I want. That's why I said it was selfish. That's
what I want. A lot of shooters have come out that a lot of people play you know like Valorant, Apex,
Tarkov. What's that other one? There's another like you know Counter-Strike. I don't I don't
put Counter-Strike in this category because I think Counter-Strike has been around for so long
that it just is it to me Counter-Strike just is the shooter. It's just the shooter. It's just the
shooter to me. Everything else is sort of in a weird kind of cloud above it for me. Overwatch?
Yeah it was a different it was it was different but I liked Overwatch when it came out the first
like year or two. I played it all I streamed it all the time. Some of the people that are new to
this channel might not know back in like 2016-2017 I played Overwatch on stream like once a week.
I played it a lot. That was a game I played. I enjoyed it. It just kind of started to get a
little out of hand for me and then Overwatch 2 was just like I don't really I don't see a reason
to play it. I just didn't really I mean I played Overwatch. I missed this pew. Is your favorite
Overwatch character? I really liked Zenyatta and Lucio. I thought they were great. He's shit faced.
I'm not. I liked how they did support in Overwatch. It was fun. It was. Zenyatta was fun to play. It
was a really fun take on a healer in a shooting game. It was really cool putting that orb on
people. The healing orb. It was a really well designed character. They made support really fun
to play in Overwatch but the rest of the game I was not like a massive huge fan of after the
first year or two. 2016-2018 Overwatch was a time to be alive. It was fun. It was very fun. I sort
of microbalanced it to hell. I'm not sure if this character is just really good or if I just turned
my brain off and started playing very well. I think it's probably a combination of both.
All right. We've not seen this yet. Every 15 seconds you summon a skeleton to fight for you.
They will perish after a set time but their life force can be extended. I don't know if I can take
this off. Is 50% attack speed worse than having a skeleton walk around? Oh wait it's a ring. I
thought it was a helmet. I thought that was a mouth and two eyes. It's a ring. Okay. What should I
I'm probably gonna say. I just froze for a second. This character doesn't do very many crits so let's
put this away and put this on. All right let's see what the skeletons look like. One of five
skeletons. All right there he is. Remind me to deposit this because which one should I deposit?
Duration? The duration abilities and or summonings. Oh yeah you should put throw a wind crown in
there for sure. But look at how cool this item is. You mean I could have five skeletons at the
beginning of the game? That's kind of fun. They're kind of doing work. They take aggro. It's hard to
tell but they're doing almost 90 damage a hit. I think these things are pretty good. They fight
off screen. Oh that's a big deal. Look at how huge that is. You know what else I think has made me
improve? The controller. WASD versus the two analogues. Yeah this is just much easier to play
I think. Wait is that a skeleton mage? That's cool you can spawn those. You might as well go skeleton
build. I've got like a 13 minutes left. This has been going very well. Uh movement speed. Especially
if I'm gonna fight the last boss again. There's no way I'll die in three four seconds. I should
have enough damage. That'll be what like two or three thousand a hit. Uh oh I gotta just power
through it. Hey dude your hot pocket is ready. Oh that took a while. How long has it been? Five
hours? I don't think that it's edible anymore. More duration. I just max it out. It's cold in
the middle. That was always the worst. I remember I haven't had hot pockets in a while. A long time
but I do remember you'd get one bite that was burning hot that burnt your mouth and then the
one right after that sometimes would be lukewarm. But when you got it perfect. When it was when it
heated up just right. We're talking Goldilocks situation. It is perfect. Perfect temperature
all the way through. The meatball hot pocket was my absolute gem. I probably lived off of those
for a significant period of time. I could have if I needed to. You know what else I lived off of?
Corned beef hash out of the can. I used to eat that stuff all the time. It's like one of my
favorite foods. Oh shit. All right give me that. Dragon's breath is really good but I don't know
if it's got all the bonuses. You're not supposed to admit that. What? That I like corned beef hash?
The canned corned beef hash? Yeah you cook. No not raw. All right how come every time I say a food
I like you guys assume it is raw out of the box. Oh man I'm you know I really just love a nice
salmon. Why are you eating raw salmon? What? You said out of the can. Yeah corned beef hash out of
the can. Because you can get corned beef hash from a ton of breakfast places. You can make corned
beef hash. It's just corned beef and potatoes and onions. I'm talking about like the Hormel
corned beef hash out of the can. Not straight out of the can with a spoon. Like no. You put
an over medium egg on top of a serving of corned beef hash Hormel and then you
with Tabasco. Get out of here. That's like one of the best things to eat. That's some real
that's some real good eating. That's good eat. One fried egg on a nice portion of corned beef hash.
A couple of dupe dupes of Tabasco and maybe some you know what let's get fucking freaky.
How about a couple of heirloom tomatoes on the side from the oven. Like four or five of them.
Oof. Get the scroll. All right I'm going. And a whole roast beef? No. Get the scroll dude. I'm
going. I only got 10 minutes. I'm gonna beat this one. Where'd everybody go? Oh that was weird.
That was kind of weird. But I do think that D4 is gonna be. All right I'll stop. I am unstoppable.
Great damage. You've been talking about Diablo for four hours. I've talked about Diablo for
maybe like 38 minutes total across four hours. It's not been four straight hours. It's been across
trickled in over four hours. Five minutes here. Two minutes there. Seven minutes there. Six minutes
here. It's not been the whole time. It's been a portion of the time. What's the best salad dressing?
Olive oil. Any more questions? I'm just reading chat and just walked through a whole group of
enemies. Look at that health regen. Tick tick tick tick. That's my health going up. Why do you talk
about food so much? I think food is one of the most important things that humanity has ever
created. I think that like food and culture around food I think is probably our greatest
achievement as a species. People think it's going to the moon. People think it's like no no it's
the guy that made a pizza for the first time. The first person that's like you know what I'm
the person that invented baklava. That's kind of remarkable. Look at what we've created with food.
Look what we've created with food. Welcome to episode two of food for thought. Me,
grandpile which you know I was thinking the other day who made uh wait this is important.
Firewalker boots? While you move you produce a trail of fire that damages your enemies.
Uh I have so many items that I want to deposit but I don't know which one is the cool one.
This seems incredible to put on the fire character. This one is cool. This one is just
the best one arguably but this one might be really fun. I can't wait until that's your real voice.
Well you're gonna have to wait about 40 years. Is your favorite Trader Joe's item still the
the chicken tikka masala? Yes. Butter chicken does fill it in. They have this new bowl. They
have these bowls there that are really good now. If you try to move something with your mind. Let
me try the thing on your desk. Let me try the uh the the matchbox. The the box of matches on
your desk. Let me try to move them right now. The red ones. The red. Ready? Did it work? Did
somebody just say holy shit dude stop you moved my house. I'm gonna move the matchbox on your desk.
I've ripped your house's foundation off and just goes into the air. Uh I'm gonna I'm gonna take
him because it's fun and whatever. Seven more minutes and I'm good. I'm putting them on. Okay
so the trail does not last very long but it is cool looking. Are you the reason why the earth
rotates on an axis? Nah. They're okay. You should play Psychonauts. I was never a fan of just action
platform games like that. I don't know why. Roughness. Games like Ratchet and Clank I put
in that same category. Is it wrong for me to say that I put Jack and Jackster, Ratchet and Clank,
and Psychonauts is in that category? Is that accurate? Because that's as a genre I don't
usually play. I'm weird. The game I play needs to have weird stakes. It has to be stakes with
whatever game I'm playing. You really break it down. To me Jack and Jack and Dexter does not have
stakes. It's just like a fun cool game to play which is fine but I want I needed to be stakes.
What are the stakes in House Flipper? They're there because in House Flipper without cheating
you're you're trying to make money to buy the better houses to sell to flip to get more money
to buy the bigger houses to flip there are stakes there you need to like spend the money you need
to make money and spend it there's like these negotiations yeah what are the stakes in Elden
Ring you holding on to souls for too long and losing them that is like the stakes game what
are you come on gwen come on gwen what are you talking about that's a reach how is it okay wait
Elden Ring you tell me Elden Ring does not have stakes like something you you have to put it up
right you got to level up you got to hold on to your souls you got to find items you got to get
good you could lose shit if you don't if you're not careful where's the next bonfire I don't know be
careful up that cliff yeah and you goofied off the edge motherfucker what are you doing
what have you done now you lost everything I didn't mean to call you up and a mother effort
by the way slipped out you were a cartoon no I just act like one on TV I'm kind of this is going
pretty well defense I feel like the defense play is what's gonna work here because even if I get
hit it won't kill me see what happens people said you act like one in real life too oh I mean I
mess around a lot I mean I think everybody you know when you're around like your friends and
stuff you kind of just you act like goofy and shit just for fun the magnet oh are you comfortable
here I think that's why I act the way that I act on stream because it is just like I I feel fine
I'm feeling cool here well the well the well ooh but what do I deposit I'm coming I guys I just
I you can't shut me up I'm I just keep I'll talk as long as I'm allowed to don't ever give me
have I ever go to like a parent teacher conference I will just sit up there with the microphone and
talk about Diablo 2 items as the parent or the teacher I mean just like in general like that as
like the parent like oh I'm here to just we're here to because uh the school assemblies we're
going to hear what they're going to be this year and here's here's the conference where we're going
to go over like what the students have been doing recently and no I'll I'll just I'll I'll I'll fake
an illness to not go to them you're going to be dead in a minute um I got two minutes whose dad
is this yeah we're really excited for the next season of the of the school baseball team uh I
really was curious this year are we going to be able to have uh are the gloves going to be provided
or we're going to have to get that as parents hey by the way gloves speaking of gloves I think
that you should be able to put charge bolt on something besides glove I think you should be
able to put them on uh let's say for instance cleats uh boots I think that would be it would
be interesting I think where's my kid your kid's not here this is the parent teacher conference
oh right anyways Diablo 4 is not good Diablo 2 is the real game and then and then you hear somebody
somebody starts clapping because one person cares about this well oh shit the well okay okay okay
okay I'm good I'm good I'm sure I have a cartoon character remember oh shit oh shit what am I
depositing probably the I don't know the boots seems not that great well that was exactly what
I wanted to get badly how far away is this I'm not even gonna be able to get there oh
shit I'm in trouble okay what am I putting in wind crown is just useful for a ton of people
it just is this is really fun but this is useful this is the one those defense points really did
come in handy damn all right I got uh-oh that's not what I wanted to do what's he doing why is
he being so weird what's he doing he's like trying to grab he's trying to grab me I got it
collect a total of 20 000 golds gradually survive the halls of torment and I picked up something
so what did I get ability radiant aura money money activity and accuracy money painful incision
upgrade money false blessing trait money revives that's a great thing to unlock money gold gets
brewed in barrels and then there's the wraith warlord and grand well this character is amazing
what does it let me see revives yeah five grand cool these are all very expensive that I unlock
a new zone all right there's a boss here too but I don't know if I'm gonna get there today actually
buy the wind crown yeah do I buy the wind crown or do I buy this and have the fire character be
very good this is good for everybody though yeah everybody can use that there's only one character
that really can use this 500 000 damage with a lightning strike 500 000 in one go a lot of
unlockables this is I like this game reach level 100 I feel like you have to have pretty much
everything unlocked we could probably call it here too it's been like five and a half hours I think
that's a good place to stop this is great the beta is tomorrow I think and they're adding a bunch of
stuff so maybe I'll do another killout stream in the next couple days I do want to I want to open
some tf2 crates too probably maybe Wednesday this week middle of the week Wednesday around
probably on the same time like five or six keep it at six pacific because I can always pull it back
like 30 40 minutes if I need to on Wednesday might play some more of this might play a little tf2
open up some tf2 boxes see you on Sunday no no I'll be live on Wednesday I'll see you Wednesday
more team fortress Wednesday 6 p.m pacific d2 remastered if I play d2 remastered and I start a
new character and you guys pick the build that's actually going to end up being a like seven to
eight o'clock pacific we just we turn it down and just hang out and just play show off your characters
uh we'll look at this exterminator swordsman archer what about yakuza I want to I want to get my fill
of this especially if they're going to update it tomorrow so we'll probably this sounds so
outrageous to say but I'm gonna say it we're gonna open tf2 boxes for like a half an hour
I might play like a round or two maybe I'll hang out and play some tf2 for like an hour
and then I'm gonna play this so I'm gonna open up boxes for the first part of the stream that
feels odd to say that sounds outrageous not too many I just have a ton of crates and cases over
the last 10 years that I never opened and I just kind of want to open them I've given my tf2 backpack
away like three or four times maybe I'll get something cool probably like 20 boxes maybe like
15 to 25 I don't want to go overboard but just enough to you know have a little bit of fun 100
no 250 I don't even know if I have 50 boxes to open I think I have like 30 or 40 and I don't
think I want to open some of them some of them are some old crates that I don't even know what's
really in them all right is series 90 91 and 92 crates any good I have a lot of 89 90 and 91
are those any good don't open crates open cases there are no good tf2 crates not anymore really
you said you once said that you would rather have every hair on your body removed with tweezers
rather than open crates on stream I did well no I said that that's not how long ago how long ago
though more was it more than five years was it like 10 years ago link the clip I've been I've
been doing this for too long you guys just have every audio every piece of audio I've said for
13 years you just have it I don't remember what I said 11 years ago all right so I saw so 10
years ago I said I would remove every hair in my body with tweezers if I did it or I whatever you
said it an hour ago I don't remember you saying that you can't seriously expect my client to
perjure himself over a conversation from 12 years ago that's right do it now or we unfollow
I'm doing it on Wednesday hey relax it was on the streamer simulator stream from about two years ago
well things have changed I've changed right things have changed a little I've changed
I'm willing to open up 15 to 20 crates in team fortress without removing all of the hair on my
body it's changed it's been two years has it really only been two years yeah I okay post 35
I can't be like ah you know I was yeah I was like 20s I said that I didn't that was literally like
I was I was over 35 when I said that but we're still doing it so you've massively mellowed out
I think that's just kind of natural though I told you guys this the beginning of the year
I mean it's that I've gotten I've when I started doing YouTube videos I was 25 26 that's when I
started that's like the the team fortress to YouTube videos I've gone through my 20s
into my late 30s it's just natural you're just going through the uh the natural order of you
know dialing it back a little that doesn't mean I still can't have a bunch of fun I can still move
how about that one oh my arm uh-oh oh boy that's uh that's a blown out elbow that's a blown out
elbow yeah I'll see you guys on Wednesday thanks for watching thanks for hanging out
you should have played a loud bone cracking sound do it again what about the la la la la there you
go I'm not doing that ever again unless somebody says it as a one guy and I read it I do it
immediately following reading it so I'm never doing that again yeah that this is fun I like
kind of adding to that it is nice to just kind of relax a little bit I know a lot of people are
really used to this channel being kind of like crazy I think it really is for the best to do more
of this yeah I definitely don't want to just only have it be just wacky crazy shit that's very
unsustainable if you want me to be completely realistic this one was still kind of wacky it
can be wacky but dialed down a few notches you know what I mean do you prefer this or vampire
survivors they're both very very good uh vampire survivors has way more content we like the chill
streams I do too I like them both you can eat pizza but then you can also eat steak and cheese
sandwiches too they both exist what's something that's too wacky um I don't know it's just the
vibes when the vibes are wacky it's fun it's also nice to kind of just not do that just relax and
chill and play games and just talk about stuff it's the vibes with the bat chest exactly you know
exactly what I'm talking about thank you for watching to see you all on Wednesday thanks a lot
take care of yourselves uh it's probably pretty late for some of you guys get some rest drink some
water call your mother you know you know the deal see you later take care it's 4 p.m. oh yeah
these late night streams there's a lot of people from the other side of the world that watch
Australia yeah senior citizen it's 2034 here why are you still alive well you're in a time machine
all right see you Wednesday take care have a good one see you later