Why can't I tweet this? What's going on?
Hello, how are you? Hi. Oh, ads.
No, no ads today.
Is it Echo? Yeah, I'm in a different room.
It's probably really loud. Yeah, I'm streaming from my bathroom.
It was literally an ad. Well, I can't control that.
I'll talk quieter. There we go. Is that better? Bye from the hospital.
What a wild week it's been.
I will say it's been very stressful, but I'm very excited.
Toilet cam. What if I do that?
Hold on. Does this help at all? Does that change anything?
There's not much I can really do about it. It's probably going to be very Echo-y.
Did that help? Oh, shit, it did. Oh, I'll just do this then.
Just put the mic in your mouth. Let me change a bit there.
I can't tweet this for some reason. I don't know why.
Yeah, we're going to talk about the dollhouse. This frame is going to be very short.
I envision this will be live for about 20-30 minutes.
There's a lot of work going on behind the scenes.
I will tell you that this is literally the coolest fucking thing I've ever seen
in the 10 plus years I've been doing Twitch and YouTube.
I am incredibly excited. I couldn't be more excited.
So, it's going to be insane.
Let me see. Reverb. Let me see what it sounds like. I have these headphones here.
Well, yeah, it is pretty...
Well, actually, it's not that bad. You can handle it, can't you?
Yeah, I'm okay. I want to make that really clear first and foremost.
Streaming from... Yeah, I'm in my office right now.
Old Jerma. Do I look old?
Why can't I... Hold on. We're going back to the start screen.
You look like a podcaster. I was thinking about just eating the microphone, but I don't know.
This is not my mic, so I don't think I want to do that.
I'm trying to send a tweet. I'll go over very quickly. Sorry about the echo.
Not in my usual setup, as you can probably tell.
This stream, I really want to just kind of reiterate the dollhouse stream.
I announced it, then I went on Ludwig's stream and we talked about some stuff.
Then I had a fucking immediate medical concern that was an annoying process that I just barely finished.
Literally, like yesterday.
I'm still kind of dealing with it. I won't give you any details because I don't want anybody to be concerned about this or anything.
But I had a little bit of a medical problem that's completely unrelated to the other stuff.
Of course it happens, like a week before a big show like this.
It sounds like a Zoom court meeting.
Yeah, I guess.
Young man, this is not a joke.
Yeah, whatever. Fuck you.
And by the way, get some fucking padding on these walls. This is unbearable.
It's bugleberry.
Let me try to tweet. If I can't tweet it, I can't. I don't know why.
Talking stream. Come on, tweet.
There we go. That took long enough.
I'll come back on. Look, I'm here.
That's not what I wanted to click. I didn't want to click that.
But anyways, hello, how are you?
I love how there's stream start, there's face cam, there's desktop capture, there's desktop with face.
And then BRB. And then stream it.
So I probably look tired, because I kind of am.
Why am I in the void? Handsome?
Yeah, well, probably not today.
I'll be honest with you.
The mic sucks? Yeah, it does.
Here, let me hold onto it.
I feel like the price is right.
Does it have one of these mics?
Look at how fucking big this is. Hold on, ready?
No, that looks like I'm on a podium.
Yes, I'm here to accept the award for a small but cool streamer.
What the fuck do I care?
A spelling bee.
Okay, so let's talk about a few things. This is going to be very quick.
Still going through some medical shit.
I'm trying to get it just completely gone by this coming week,
because obviously a lot of shit going on here that I can't really be ill for.
And it's not like a cough-cough like I'm sick.
It's something completely different than how I'm dealing with.
And it's annoying, so we'll see how that plays out.
I feel pretty good now. I feel okay.
Maybe after the streams are over,
I will give a more in-depth detail of what I'm talking about here.
But it's nothing to be majorly concerned about, so don't worry.
The show must go on. We're going to continue.
And the show is going to be crazy.
I want to reiterate something I didn't really talk about too much,
is that we have special guests.
Ludwig is one of them.
We also have Kit Boga is going to be on the stream too,
which I only really barely leaked for 14 seconds on Ludwig's stream last week.
So Kit Boga is going to be there.
And I can't wait to do that.
I can't wait to just have Kit, can't wait to have Ludwig on the streams.
It's going to be the funnest thing I've ever done in my entire life.
So having a new medical problem is fucking annoying.
It was a testicular tortusion.
Does that mean that I got like a testicular contusion?
Yeah, I don't want to talk about it, guys.
I slammed my balls in a car door getting out to come to the dollhouse.
Anyways, Kit Boga is going to be there.
Ludwig is going to be there.
We also, I can say today, I can say this today too.
I want to make sure that you guys are aware of this.
We have a sponsor that is now going to be completely baked into the stream.
And it's really good because it can help pay for a shitload of stuff that's really expensive.
So not only Twitch, but Coinbase is also going to be helping pay for the stream.
They're going to be presenting the stream as well.
So now we got all the money we need.
And that's probably really, really, really loud.
But now we got literally all the money we need.
I can't fucking wait to do this show.
You're a stock user?
Bitcoin Andy.
Those of you that have followed this stream for a fairly long time, though, will know that I have been into cryptocurrency since like 2015.
So you've heard me talk about, I mean, we literally have a fucking crypto fake bald coin emote.
So it's cool that they wanted to actually come in and help sponsor the stream because we needed it for sure.
And at this stage, I wish I could just yell all these insane things that you're going to see in the next like four or five days,
but I can't. I can't do that.
I want to make this really clear again, too.
All of the money that's coming in from Twitch, all the money that's coming in from potentially Coinbase,
anything that's coming in, I'm not taking any money from.
It's only to make sure that we can pay for the stream and all the production staff, all the people, everybody that's coming together to do this.
I can't take any money. It would be impossible.
If I took any money from this stream, the stream wouldn't happen.
It just would be impossible.
So I want to make that really clear that this isn't like, yeah, Coinbase is coming in.
I'm getting a fucking bunch of money for doing it.
So no, that's that's not happening.
It's just to I'm fucking grateful, actually, because for them to kind of come in here and give us the remaining kind of funding that that we need is a huge fucking deal.
So this microphone is fucking freaking me out.
But I want to reiterate a couple of things about the extension.
We'll talk about that really briefly.
Am I in jail?
No, I'm wearing a Red Sox shirt.
I'm not like in a prison outfit.
Zoom call.
I know this looks like I'm like a fucking professor.
Oh, that was a that was a really weird face.
I'm annoyed that it was an HD prison break.
Yeah, I didn't do shit.
Let me out.
You're in the courthouse.
All Boston prisons have Red Sox jumpsuits.
Yeah, they let us all watch the games on TV.
Convicted Andy.
Well, it's a further back away.
I go the worst it is.
Let's see.
Yeah, I'll just give you like a couple of clips just for fun.
Ready?
Like, I didn't fucking do anything.
I didn't I didn't do anything.
Yep.
No, I'm not going to give you like no, we're not doing that anymore.
Mini green screen.
No, I don't want people to fuck with that.
Never mind.
We're not doing that anymore.
Life sentence Larry.
I can see your pores.
Don't don't look at me.
This is why I never stream with the camera.
This is good because like people can like see my fucking like my nose goes this way.
Like one of my eyes has a like red line in it.
And my hair is like I'm getting a little gray up here.
I don't want people to know this shit.
I'm 25 to a half of you.
I can't be like pushing 40 to add to you guys.
I have to be able to keep up the appearance of being of I have to keep up the appearance of being a 25 year old.
I have to pick up the appearance being a 25 year old boy.
It's a school assembly.
What a weird school assembly this would be if this is what the person was doing.
You kids don't understand as the principal.
I have to keep up appearances.
I have to be a 26 year old.
Are you guys don't you understand?
I know I can't be old to you pushing 40.
Yeah, I know.
Your face has too many colors.
No, it doesn't.
I mean, if you have a few extra nose hairs, but I don't think that's out of the ordinary.
What are you saying?
You're not 20.
No, your head is huge.
My head is tiny.
OK.
Here's a bit more perspective.
My I don't have my head is small.
It's because I was leaning in.
Do you know perspectives?
Come on, man.
OK.
Take your mug shot.
I just imagine people editing that and being like, dude, I found his fucking arrest records.
He's wearing the same shirt he was wearing when he streamed that time.
Do a side profile.
OK.
No.
What the fuck is the stream?
I don't want to do.
We're supposed to be talking about the dollhouse.
I don't want to give you guys like fucking every avenue.
Look what I've done to myself.
I gave myself like fucking a rash.
I just gave myself a rash on camera.
OK.
So the dollhouse is coming up on the 18th, the 20th and 20th.
It's three streams.
Not just one.
We're doing three streams.
Yes.
I'm going to throw up.
Why?
The extension is going to be baked into Twitch.
A lot of people have been asking this question.
I want to make sure this is very much taken care of.
You're in a porn mansion.
Just listen for a second.
We can get back to that in a second.
So the extension is baked.
It's actually a Twitch extension.
There's not going to be anything in the chat room.
So you're not going to be chatting and doing commands or anything.
No.
It's an extension, an elaborate extension that's baked in through Twitch.
So people were sick.
Do you want me to put something back here so people stop freaking out?
Like, hold on.
Should I have a picture of like a painting or something?
I don't know.
So we can't see chat.
No.
Chat will be available.
You can chat in the chat room.
It's just none of the actions or anything will be in the chat.
You'll be actually physically clicking on the screen on an extension
that is baked in through Twitch.
You need a louder mic?
I thought people told me to lower it because it was so annoying.
How's that?
All right.
Is that better?
I think it's going to work.
I believe a portion of the extension does work on mobile.
I think mobile does work.
So I don't know if every single feature is going to work on mobile,
but I think I probably would have to get that corrected,
but I believe mobile works for at least some of it.
The mic sucks.
I know.
There's nothing I can do about it.
Are you...
What are you...
Is this supposed to...
Oh, also really important.
I want to make sure people are very clear on what you are going to be able to do
on this stream.
I've seen comments like, oh, so we can make them just like sit and zerk off
for like fucking two hours.
That's...
That's not...
No.
Why...
This is a game.
This is a game where you have to play by the rules of the game, essentially, right?
You guys are going to have a lot of things to be able to do,
as if you were playing some kind of like type of simulation type games, right?
This is not a scenario where somebody just like tells me to go like zerk off
into the fridge for an hour.
So that's not how this is going to work.
You'll have a lot of shit to do, but that's not one of them.
I heard people say like, oh, can we...
Oh, okay.
So ladies and gentlemen, it has just been confirmed by Community Jake.
All features work on mobile.
Somebody was like coming in here.
I was like, shit, what happened?
So all features do work on mobile.
No pants?
Right.
Somebody just asked something.
What was it?
You're on record calling...
No, I'm not going to be on record in front of like with this like court mic.
What do you got?
You said you wanted something on the mic.
What is that?
It's just a...
That looks worse.
That looks way worse.
It's not...
That looks like...
That looks like I'm streaming from like the bottom of a dumpster.
There's this trash all down here.
And like that's like stuck on the lid.
Didn't Oscar the Grouch have like a fucking entire like civilization of the trash can, right?
You need more garbage back there.
Do a dumpster stream.
Okay.
Let's...
One thing at a time, please.
One thing at a time.
Because this stream that you're going to see in the next week, right?
We were just in chat and somebody was like, oh, hey, man, like, this would be cool.
And like, yeah, it would be cool, wouldn't it?
Oh, imagine if I like if I was in a dollhouse and you guys like controlled what I was doing
and we did like a real life like life simulator.
Ha ha ha.
Oh dear.
Literally.
Big, big shit later and here we are.
So can we do one at a time?
Like I don't want to go now like contact a bunch of people and be like, okay, I'm going
to do a dumpster stream and it's going to cost this amount of money and I need to have
like a fucking whole civilization in the dumpster.
Like, you know, one thing at a time.
Are there any breaks?
Yeah.
So you guys are going to be able to buy stuff.
I want to make that clear too.
So people think, oh, we're just going to make you like be able to like take a shit like
a thousand times.
You are going to have a buy menu.
Yes.
With lots and lots and lots of options.
You will have money.
You're going to have a currency to have to deal with there.
This is not just me walking around a room without any interaction from you guys or just
simply telling me where to go.
You're going to be able to put furniture wherever the fuck you want.
It's baked into the extension.
So it's, it's not, it's not, it's not real money.
Will there be gambling?
I don't, I don't know.
I don't think so.
Not off the top of my head.
It's going to be bonkers.
I can at least say it'll be, it'll be interesting to watch.
Buy a slot machine.
I wonder, I wonder if there's anything.
I don't know.
We'll see.
Is it channel points?
No.
It is its own currency in the extension baked into the game.
Not channel points.
Is it going to be a shit pants button?
You guys are going to have to take care of me.
Let me make that clear as well.
You're going to have things that you're going to have to manage.
It's not just me walking around and like pooping.
I have quite a few needs that you're going to have to attend to.
Can you cook?
Yes.
I don't want to give too much shit away.
I really don't.
But yes, you're going to be able to do things.
He's a maniac.
Debatable.
Is there a mana bar?
No, but there's something.
There are things that need to be managed that could be potentially bar related.
How many things will be baked?
I don't know.
That's not like a fire alarm.
Can you guys hear that?
Yeah, just leave it over there for now.
There's a fucking lift over here.
I told you I'm in the dumpster.
There may or may not be a lift for some reason over here.
I don't know.
Do a recap.
Okay.
Quick recap.
Extension works on mobile.
It works on desktop.
You don't have to be nothing special.
You just have to be on Twitch.
Kitboga's going to be there.
Ludwig's going to be there.
There may even be a few others that you may or may not know.
How do we control you?
Through the extension.
The extension is going to have a menu.
We're doing this for three days, so this is something important to remember, too.
The first stream that we're doing on, I believe it's Wednesday the 18th, right?
Yeah.
The first stream is a tutorial.
It really is.
Because I want to make sure that everything works, that people know how the thing, how
the extension works, how well did it work, does anything need to be changed, tweaked.
The first stream is a tutorial.
I'm just going to say it because that's the way it is.
What are you saying?
Am I saying Joe Biden?
No.
No, Joe.
He's not here.
I was like, why are they saying that?
It doesn't make any sense.
But anyways, the first stream is a tutorial for everyone to learn how the extension works.
That doesn't mean it's not going to be a fun experiment, a fun stream.
It's just that's why we did three of them.
Because we want you guys to have the ability to kind of learn how it works and keep going.
Because one stream is just not going to do it.
If we did one stream or even two streams, by the time you guys figured out even how it worked,
it's like, oh, that's it.
See you later.
No, we wanted time for you guys to play around and have fun.
So there will be plenty of instructions.
There will be plenty of ways for you guys to figure out what's going on.
And we'll be doing it for three days.
How many hours?
That's a really good question.
It really depends on a few factors.
But it will be at least, each stream will be probably at least, the first stream is a tutorial.
Because remember, it's the 18th, the 20th, and 21st.
So that day, that first stream is probably going to be pretty short just to make sure things go off.
People know what they're doing.
The tutorial goes well.
We do some fun stuff.
And then we have a day to get other stuff prepared and make sure we can get it all ready.
And then day two and three are like, here we go.
And I would assume it's probably going to be at least three to six hours a day.
At least.
Probably four to six hours each stream.
So it's not going to be a two-hour stream for each one.
There will be at least four, five, six hours each.
What else is he saying here?
Is it a tutorial?
Yeah.
It's a very elaborate extension.
So it's, like I said, it's not just simply writing.
Because remember, the carnival stream had people just kind of doing inputs into the stream.
You know, like up, down, fire, up, down, left, right, like forward, forward, back, back, back, right?
This is multiple menus, multiple things to click on, multiple things to look at.
So you're going to need the time to figure out how to use it.
Ken, is it?
No.
What are you saying?
Snob Andy?
What?
Why did you call me Snob Andy?
Is that what you said?
I didn't even see it.
How many NPCs were there be?
Do I need to just confirm that there are NPCs?
I don't know.
It could be fucking...
You'll see.
It'll be enough.
Fuck it.
I don't know.
Fuck around and find out.
Wake me up when he plays Sly Cooper.
And I'm here to announce, ladies and gentlemen, that after the Dollhouse streams, I will...
I'm not playing Sly Cooper.
I tried to play it.
It ran like shit and I couldn't get it to work.
But I'll play it on the remastered ones.
Why am I even fucking responding to this person?
Why am I responding to this?
This has nothing to do with the stream.
Let me tell you when I'm going to play Sly Cooper.
Why am I even responding?
That person just wrote...
Why did I even reply to that person?
What am I doing?
It was like...
I don't know.
Small words work on me.
Like, sly.
That's easy.
That's an easy word.
I know that.
One, two, three.
Small words.
I see them.
And I go, okay.
What's this stream about anyways?
In offline chat four and a half years ago, we made a couple of offhand comments about
being in a simulator.
And like, what if I was in a dollhouse and you guys could control me and funny things
happened, in quotes.
And I was like, oh, that sounds like a pretty funny idea.
And then four years later, we decided to do it.
Aaron.
Fuck.
God.
Oh, my pinky.
Why don't you use that for the court session?
Uh, Mr. Albertson, are you aware of the charges?
I fucking lock him up.
Like, I guess he did it.
Comic Con panel.
All right.
Yeah.
I'll do Comic Con.
Why do they all sit like this?
What's up?
Hey, hey.
What's going on?
Is there a reason?
Does this make you look more relatable or something?
It's always like, yeah, that was a pretty sick project that we did.
We worked on it.
It was pretty cool.
Yeah, I got a couple of funny fucking stories for you.
It's like, what's this doing up here?
Why is this up here?
Put it down here and sit like this.
I don't get it.
That's not relatable.
It's because they're waiting to leave.
Well, let me put these on.
No, I'm not going to play around with any toys over here.
This is not toys.
What's the bag behind you?
It's part of a dollhouse.
Arg.
Community Jake just put it back here.
There's no arg.
I just want to make that clear.
Eat the mic.
No.
Do you have any pets that we can pet for there?
There are no pets.
I want to make that clear.
He's unaware.
There's no auto DLC.
No, unfortunately, no auto DLC.
He doesn't know.
Don't say anything.
Is someone in my face?
Someone in my nose?
What's wrong with me?
What?
What the heck was wrong?
I'm going to burp and I can't turn the camera off because I don't know how.
I don't know what this is.
This is not my usual setup.
I'm going to have to lean back for a second.
Don't tell him.
Well, whatever.
I'm sure I'll read it on fucking Reddit tomorrow.
He had boogers all over his hair.
Oh, whatever.
What are the times again?
Okay, let's make that clear as well.
I just got stuck up here.
Did you see that?
So I'm going to say, no, this is in August.
So Wednesday the 18th, we're starting at 12 p.m. Pacific.
And then Friday the 20th, we are starting at 12 p.m. Pacific.
And then Saturday, we're starting at 9 a.m. Pacific because we want to be able to have
as much time as we can.
So 12, 12, 9 Pacific.
You have a wig on?
Rip it off.
Okay, I have a question for you.
What would you guys say is my good side?
This one or this one?
What's my good side?
I would say this is the bad side because my nose goes like that way.
Front-facing?
This side?
This side.
Who cares?
Like, really, who gives a shit?
What are we talking about?
You're not talking about it.
It's me talking about it.
I don't know why I am.
I didn't.
I missed.
I was looking at the preview and I was going to try to pretend to snort the mic and I went
the wrong way.
So I just looked like a fucking maniac because that would have been like, oh, he's like
sniffing the mic.
But instead, I just went like, is the Minecraft server still being developed?
Yes, it's just this was such a big project that everything else had to go on hold.
But as of next week, we'll be ready to focus on some more stuff.
How do you eat peanut butter?
50% of the time, out of the jar with a spoon with some fluff next to me.
So I do one big spoon of peanut butter and then one big spoon of fluff and let it just
mess around in my mouth and swallow it.
And then the other half is on like a piece of toast, just like spread it on toast.
And if you've never done the first one, then I don't even know how I could even explain
that to you.
It's unbelievably good.
And I'm going to die.
Guys, this is not a thing I do every day.
I don't eat like a jar of peanut butter every day.
Although I have Googled before, do you die if you eat a whole jar of peanut butter?
I've Googled that.
I actually have Googled that.
And the answer is no.
But be careful.
So yeah, I love peanut butter, though.
I think it's awesome.
Cholesterol.
Now, you don't eat a whole jar of anything.
The Google result should be, Google, what happens if you eat a whole jar of pickles?
I don't know, but don't do it.
Just eat like four.
Google, what happens if you eat a whole jar of peanut butter?
I don't know.
Probably nothing good.
Don't do it.
Just have like three or four servings.
Have like a serving.
You could say that for anything.
Literally any food product.
Just don't eat the whole thing.
Eat like one or two servings.
That's it.
Do I like cantaloupe?
No.
Sorry.
A whole, what about moderation?
Yeah.
Just do moderation.
Moderate.
Do you like bananas?
Yes.
AMA stream.
Yeah.
That's what this is.
Do you have more than one food product in your house?
Yeah.
Of course I do.
What do you think I am, dumb?
Can you guys ask dollhouse related questions?
Like what my favorite peanut butter brand is is not relevant to the dollhouse stream.
What happens if we take good care of you?
Well, then I will have probably be a more happy existence.
I mean, I'm going to have to make money somehow, right?
I'm going to have to make sure that I'm taken care of so I can perform, right?
What's my favorite Sonic character?
That's a really hard question.
Who's my favorite Sonic character?
I don't want to say Tails.
That's easy, right?
Robotnik is easy too.
Can I just say Jim Carrey?
That's my answer.
When you speak in, no, it's going to be in English.
So not going to be doing any other dialect or any language that's not English.
It's going to be in English.
We fought for a long time about if I should talk in like kind of non-existent language,
but that turned out to be something that I did not want to do for like more than 12 to 18 fucking hours.
You know what I mean?
Like if each one of these streams is like four, five, six hours long,
I'm not, I don't want to talk in like fake, not just a fake language for that long.
It would be unbearable.
So no.
What was he saying?
Are you going to do a funny accent?
Probably not.
It's just me.
I'm not going to answer specific questions about specific things that you want to see there,
or if certain objects are there, you're just going to have to see.
You're just going to have to play the game.
Hold on.
Somebody had like an interesting question.
What was it?
What did you say?
Do we get to do a character customizer?
I just keep touching my fucking mouth.
Is there a character customizer?
I really am at like a court session.
I'm not going to answer that question, Your Honor.
Okay.
All right.
So that means you did it.
I'm just not going to answer that question.
I don't think I need to answer that question.
If there will or will not be character customization.
I don't think I have to answer that, Your Honor.
I keep fucking touching this thing with my mouth.
The stream is so fucking vague.
It kind of has to be though, because there's a lot of surprises.
There's a lot of things that I think people don't know are going to happen.
And I'd rather not just sit here three or four days before the stream
and just tell you all the fun potential things you can do.
I'd rather you figure that out on your own.
Yes, there's a fucking, yes, there's a character creator.
Okay.
There you go.
Yes.
Yes, there is a character creator.
That's all you're getting.
That is literally the only thing you're getting.
Can we adjust your height?
And I specifically made sure that that was something we weren't going to do.
What are the dates and times of the streams?
18th, the 18th, the 20th, and the 21st.
The 18th and the 20th, the streams will be at 12 p.m. Pacific.
The 21st stream will be at 9 a.m. Pacific.
Each stream is scheduled to go for approximately three to six hours,
depending on chat interaction and scenario play-outs.
How's your body feeling?
I'm feeling okay.
I'm still dealing with it.
I'm powering through a handful of problems right now.
I don't know what Greek god I angered in the last two or three weeks,
but a few things have just piled on here.
The last 48 hours, too.
I'm powering through as hard as I can,
and I'm on some medication to help with stuff that's happening,
and I should be good to go.
This stream is so interesting to me.
There's tons of people involved.
Tons of awesome people have worked on this,
and maybe eventually we'll do something.
Maybe after the stream is over,
we'll probably get people together to talk about it,
because it's not just me that had anything to do with this.
Yes, I was like, this is what I want,
this is what I think would be funny,
and this is what I think would be fun.
But it took a monumental amount of people
and a monumental amount of financial support
from different organizations.
I couldn't be happier with how this is turning out.
I really hope it's a lot of fun for everybody.
I'm really excited.
I hope it's as interesting and as fun as I hope it is.
And if it is, great.
If it isn't, then we tried to do something interesting, right?
But I can't see a scenario where this is not at least worth
at least watching for a little while.
Yeah, I've seen a lot of things the last few days
that I'm just so...
I'm very proud and very grateful for the people
that have been working on this project.
It's fucking unbelievable.
So I can't wait for you to see it.
I really can't.
He's going to cry.
Show your feet.
Okay, let's show our bare feet.
What are you doing here?
What?
Okay, worst phase 2021.
Who else is in the room?
Your honor.
What's happening?
Booger.
Is the echo...
I'm just in a big room, a big empty room.
Blink if you're in trouble.
I have to blink normally as a human.
I'm fine.
Nothing's wrong.
I'm blinking now because I'm literally a human that blinks.
That's how we like secrete liquid into our eyelids
to keep our eyes moisturized.
I have to blink.
I'm fine.
I am fine right now, okay?
I'm going to clip these weird images of me with an HD camera
and be like, what's wrong with him?
You're going to take that, and you're going to get like this,
and people are going to be like, is he all right?
What happened to him?
I'm fine.
So there's a lot of work still to be done.
I wanted to come in and make sure that I talk to you guys
one-on-one before the stream happened
because I wasn't able to the last week,
and I wanted to play The Sims 3,
and I have a shitload of mods on The Sims 3,
and that game is an absolute clown show ready to happen.
I'll probably do that after the Dollhouse stuff,
but I wanted to at least say hello
and explain a little more detail on stuff
and give you some more insight on it.
So I'm glad I was at least able to do this
for the period I have here.
So there's still a lot of shit to be done.
I'm going to get back to it,
and I can't wait for you to see the finished product.
Hopefully it's as interesting as I hope it is.
How much power does one person have?
One person has not power over anybody else.
It's going to be a system based off of a democracy-type system,
and there is...
Why? What?
It's baked in through Twitch.
That's pretty much how it works.
Do we get money for watching the stream?
So there's going to be a monetary system
that you guys will have to manage,
and whether that's sending me to work, right?
Whether that's managing what kind of thing you want to buy.
Where do you want to put it?
You're going to have a lot of things to worry about,
and hopefully you can work together
to have a good outcome.
Otherwise, I'm going to be in trouble.
Where will you work?
These are all things that you will be shown very shortly.
And then microtransactions.
The entire game is a microtransaction,
if you think about it.
You're going to be spending money on all kinds of stuff.
So the whole thing is a microtransaction.
But you don't have to pay for anything.
You just have to watch.
Chat's going very fast. Let me see.
Will the extension work on every web navigator?
I believe all through desktop and mobile
it's been confirmed that it will work.
What if we kill you in the tutorial?
I don't want to give you guys any ways
to make this any different than it could be.
Like, take care of me.
Take care of me.
I'm a growing boy. I'm pushing for it.
But I'm a growing boy still.
How much interaction with the outside world?
I think you mean how much interaction with other people
or things that come to the dollhouse?
Is that what you mean?
Because with you guys, I will be communicating with you
as well as potential NPCs
and people that will arrive or not arrive, right?
So there will be lots of interactions
with other people.
Will I go outside?
You fucking answered. You're my lawyer.
Stop acting like a teen. You're 35, dude.
I'm not acting like...
Me getting angry and loud is like a teen.
Like, that's not what I'm doing, Mom!
I'll be an adult.
How is it going to work with people in the chat?
The chat room is just going to be the chat room.
So you are free to just chat like you normally would.
Everything is going to be baked in through Twitch
as an extension.
So the chat's going to be free for you guys just to talk.
Will there be action?
You want to take that one?
How much bacon? I stopped touching this.
How much bacon are you allowed to eat?
Is there even a limit of how much bacon you should have?
Will there be QuickTime events?
Hey, you want some bacon, lawyer?
You want some bacon?
How will the camera work?
Just wait.
Will there be pyrotechnics?
Yeah.
I don't know.
You guys can hear the explosions, right?
Fireworks?
Good.
I am going to go.
There's a lot to do.
Will there be ragdoll physics?
What the fuck was that?
I don't want to tell you guys everything.
You're just going to have to watch.
That was such a smug asshole.
Oh, is there ragdoll physics?
Can we make you eat a jar of fluff?
Just wait.
Baked in through Twitch.
That's been the motto.
What am I trying to say?
The motto of this stream
is
it's baked in through Twitch.
But yeah, we have
Coinbase is now a presenting
sponsor on the stream.
We're able to do a lot of stuff.
I am fucking insanely
excited. I'm going to power through
some of these issues that I have
because I think it's going to be really fun.
It's going to be at least fun to do.
The next time you see this stream
live, it will be on the 18th
at 12 p.m. Pacific.
We're going to go for it.
It'll be a tutorial.
Hopefully you'll learn how to play it.
We'll see how it goes.
I'm really, really excited.
I can't wait.
I'm just going to go
and just turn the stream off.
Let me make sure this is correct.
My brain is...
I'm slowing down here.
I will see you guys Wednesday the 18th.
That's only a few days from now.
That's 12 p.m. Pacific.
It's the next time this stream is going to be live.
The extension will be there
and you can learn how to play.
See you soon. I'm very excited.
One more for the road, right?
Look at this.