Hold on, hold on a second. Do you see him sliding? No. He is sliding like no animation on my screen.
Is he dead? Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. I was gonna like beat him up, but... He's dead.
Yo, Jarvan, look at this guy. He's dead. He's bleeding. There's a puddle of... Hold on, what happened?
He tripped on this little triangle over here. He ran so fast. He hit this and he died.
Look how far... Look at his neck from over here. It kind of looks like it's broken, doesn't it?
Dude, he must have smashed his face so hard to instantly die.
We're still riding the wheelie. Wow, you can hold this for a long time. Whoa! Oh my god.
That was cool. Oh, we just... Oh, fine, I got this. You wanna see my skills? Oh, here's a sick jump.
Why is that jump there? That whole chain of events just didn't make any sense.
And then I hit my face on a wall. That was awesome. What is this giant boat? Oh, I thought that was a boat.
Here, let me do a wheelie onto this lady. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. You gotta...
What is happening? How did we get down here? No! You see that. I do. I'm not gonna freak out.
Can you snipe it? Can you snipe the guy out of it? No, I don't know. Don't shoot him. You don't want to risk it?
No, because he'll step on the gas like sometimes they do. What is he doing? He already knows we're after him.
He's bullying this guy off the road from... Yeah, if I shoot this guy right now, he's going to step on the gas.
Wouldn't you, if you're in this car? Well, shoot him in the head. Go. Nice. I'm driving this.
Not nice, because now... Where is he? Did he get you? He got you, Jerma. He was completely stopped.
The ghost of the guy in the GT. His otherworldly soul needed revenge on me. I can't believe that happened. Why did that happen?
We got out. Is he dead? Yeah, I got him out of the car somehow. I think this car is cursed now, though.
No, it's getting away. Get in the car, get in the car, get in the car, get in the car. Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick.
I'm trying. That lady is like... Oh my god, do you see this lady?
Hold on, did I... I got in the car? How did I get in the car?
No question. Just go, go, go, go. Keep going straight. Fast, fast.
I don't understand what just happened. Let's see if you can do it. My whole life is riding on this moment.
Your entire life is riding on if you can make this GTA jump. I will die if I don't do it.
I'm dead. How does that happen?
We hit the first step. Hold on, let's think about this in reality right now.
That's probably what would happen if you tried to do that in the big... What the hell is going on?
I thought you were going to drive right into that guy. Keep going, keep going, keep going, keep going.
Not going in the tunnel. Go to the left of the tunnel. We're going to turn right again.
I don't think that's going to... We're fine, we're fine. We're fine, we're fine.
Go fast, fast. Hit this guy. 10 points. Don't get hit by these cars. Oh my god. You did, didn't you?
I hit my face on the lamppost. I've never seen that before.
Okay, get on your bike. Meet me.
Hold on. I'm recovering from this laugh.
Sick burnout, bro. Did you see the guy I hit behind you? Oh my god.
This is so... I can't... Oh, good thing, good.
We wanted to do as much car damage to this as humanly possible.
Yes, before it blows up. You know what, Jerma? I say we get it to the point where it's going to blow up.
It's on fire. Yep. Yep.
All right, what do you want to do with it? Just keep driving.
Just pretend like, you know, you want to go to 7-Eleven and get some late night snacks.
Yeah, they have drinks at 7-Eleven, right? Of course they do.
Yeah, that's usually all I get at 7-Eleven. I don't know if, like, you want, um, like, Funyuns or something weird.
I was pretty close, but I, like, bumped something.
We're going over the bridge. I'm sick of this place.
Oh, no, this tire... This tire's not having it.
Yeah, you just ran... I did that. I did that.
Yep. You gonna kill me, Jerma? You gonna keep killing me? Or can we actually, like, have some fun with this?
I'm sitting in the front seat. How would I have been able to do that, GTA?
He killed it. He ran himself over. I didn't do anything.