This next game is going to be fairly interesting to some of you. It's going to be a nice surprise.
I'm actually going to, I'm going to mute. I know there's at least 5500ish people here right now.
I guarantee at least 200 of you just like absolutely clog your pants.
I'm going to shave your pants. Let's turn it off so you can't hear what it is.
I don't want you to know. You say that for every game. Of course I do.
Okay. I'm calling it right now. It's Pikmin. No it's not. No it is not. Something else.
Okay I don't want you to hear this. Oh man it's a really crunchy loud one.
Holy shit. Hopefully this doesn't do this through the whole game.
Okay hold on. You ready? I'm going to give you a hint.
Ladies and gentlemen please if you would hold on to your seats for...
A game by Sega. We're talking of course about...
That's not the title of the game. Not Edge of Reality.
That's not the game also. Talking about Hulk Ultimate Destruction.
Am I sure this is not the sound clips that I was playing yesterday?
It's wicked loud is it? Let's go. Story mode.
The werewolf? This is not The Bachelor. Should I just keep it on The Bachelor?
Welcome to The Bachelor. I didn't get the rose.
That's illegal. That's twitch illegal.
I'm trying to stop a monster. Edward Norton or pretend somebody is doing an Edward Norton voice.
Which one? What is it? The Incredible Hulk. The Incredible Hulk Ultimate Destruction.
The Incredible Hulk. The Pantheon Saga. Hulk Hogan's main event.
The Incredible Hulk.
Should I have a missile in here?
Alright let's go. This is so fucking loud too. Hold on.
I'm going to turn this shit down.
What the fuck was that? Press B or Z to punch?
I don't even know whether it was B or Z.
Get through the door. Alright!
Hey! What's going on everybody?
Jerma here with a live broadcast stream. Welcome to the stream everybody.
Playing The Incredible Hulk action.
I can just walk into shit.
Take and take care everybody.
Alright this is Hulk Ultimate Destruction.
Think about it. When am I going to throw my first car?
It's actually kind of fun.
Can I get rid of the helicopter?
I can Q up a punch. Hold on I can do a running punch.
Why am I not playing the good Hulk game?
This is not the right video game.
This is the wrong video game.
Look, it's Hulk Break Shit the game.
Is it really that big of a difference?
Yes? You tell me there's a difference?
What is this one called?
This is an extremely big difference.
It's not Madden.
This is not Hulk Ultimate Destruction.
Oh, it's the movie tie-in game.
It's the movie tie-in licensed movie game.
The one for the GameCube was just a game that was made for the GameCube.
Not a licensed. It's the movie.
That's why Edward Norton's in this movie.
But we're playing it anyways.
But you can do this in this one.
Hulk's health is dangerously low. Heal.
Press left or right to select Hulk's healing factor.
Then shake the nunchuck and press B.
That was dumb.
Can I pick up weapons?
Beats our challenge as Hulk completes to earn new powers and enhancements.
When he completes a feat, the upgrade indicator appears.
Press 1 to access the upgrade screen and see the newly completed feat and associated upgrade.
Healing factor. Hulk has innate ability to heal.
Oh, there's like a Street Fighter menu.
Punching bag is BBBB. Body toss is Z.
How do you grab?
ZZZZZZZZZB.
Grab is down.
Alright, cool. Let's go back.
That's grab. Alright, I'm ready.
What's the deal with the Hulk?
Pick up an object.
And you guys all thought this was going to be like a boring game.
But now I can throw shit at people.
Hold down C to target.
That's C.
Wait, that's not C?
Hold down C to target.
Alright, I've got somebody's...
I was going to make an internal organ joke.
C.
Hold down C to target.
That's C, right?
I did it.
Who's this?
Defeat Blonsky.
Alright, I just embarrassed this guy.
Just keep going.
Into the wall.
It's a gorilla.
Wait, what is it? Hold down...what is it?
Oh, this.
Watch me do this.
Keep playing. I'm going to keep playing.
Just wait until I get out and I can jump around in cars.
Oh, and then you're going to ask.
This is literally the movie.
It's just the movie.
NSA listening post.
Undisclosed location.
That's Ed Norton.
It is.
That's a good Ed Norton.
At the bottom of the screen is the minimap showing
Hulk and the surrounding area.
I didn't even do that one.
I didn't do that one either.
I didn't do that.
He just drove into the wall and
exploded.
Hey, easy.
Why can you do that?
In the Spider-Man game you couldn't do that.
You couldn't do
this shit in the Spider-Man game?
You go like, oh, have a good day.
I'm Spider-Man in the Hulk.
Why can I just fucking
blast that lady?
Why?
He's eating a candy stick.
Baby Hulk is upset.
Why?
It's so funny.
It's fucking hilarious.
In a building?
Wait, I can't
battlefield this building.
Can I?
And all you motherfuckers wanted me to change
the game.
Can I?
I lost my pole.
What do I have to go?
I'm going to go this way.
Pick somebody up.
Help him.
I'm the reason why he needed
to be helped.
It's fucking unbelievable.
I don't care if I don't even play
this game for another 20 fucking minutes.
Who gives a shit if it's worth it?
The other Hulk game is better.
Those don't look like army forces.
They're attacking the city.
It looks strong, but Hulk is stronger.
Show them just how strong he is.
Holy shit.
It's just this
but better?
Is it?
Alright, I'll get it.
I'll get it immediately. It'll be here in fucking two days.
It'll be here in
two days. Guaranteed.
Wait, this is not a bad guy?
This is not a bad guy.
This it was? Look,
it was on the minimap.
That guy was already dead.
I can't wait. You're telling me it's just a better version of the
other one? Oh man, I can't wait.
I can't pick this shit up?
It looks like broke the guy's neck.
Why did it explode?
Oh shit.
Stand next to buildings and jump by pressing
to cling to the side of a building.
Wait, I can jump up here too?
Okay, I can't wait to play the new one.
I get to experience the new one.
Fuck your AC.
It's actually older.
It is older.
It's seen us.
Jump higher or farther, hold down A.
I fucking love this.
It's Mario Sunshine all over again.
How durable is this guy?
Uh, pretty durable.
No, they're playing laser tag.
I don't think he's...
He had a health bar.
Dude, you're telling me to do like a charge.
I don't even need to do that. Alright, where are they at?
I'm ready for them.
How do you move the camera?
Holy fuck, that move is so ridiculous.
Climb!
Okay, we're good. Probably lose to the helicopter.
Oh, we're good. No, I did it.
This looks like a mobile game.
Oh, plot armor.
That makes sense.
I've never even seen this movie.
Dude, they're like baseball swing
with the telephone pole.
So unnecessary.
They use Manhattan as a giant test site.
The jokesters on the roof?
Specialists in artificial intelligence
that's morphed into mind control.
I came across some stuff that I shouldn't have.
I know these guys have to be stopped.
Whatever you were about to say.
Full on face scan.
It isn't on anyone's side.
He helped me, right?
I guarantee you there is a video that you unlock
where it's Ed Norton
getting his face scanned.
Put this transmitter in your ear.
Hopefully it'll survive your transformation.
Where'd you get this?
You'd be amazed at what you can find in places you shouldn't be looking.
Watch your back, by the way.
There's a large military presence in town.
It's gonna be like a Viggo Mortensen
Lord of the Rings interview.
What's the first thing you do in GTA?
I see all the D faces.
The first thing you do when you open up GTA
is you turn and you punch the closest person
in the face next to you.
That's the tutorial in GTA.
And when you do it, you go,
Oh, shit!
Oh, I gotta go this way.
Are there any other cars besides taxis and trucks?
Leon Clavin, Rick Jones, part 2.
Why am I just walking around like this?
Don't people know who the Hulk is?
Oh, no, this is the movie
licensed standalone movie.
This is pre-
stop frowning. I can't help it. I have a huge problem.
Fight the army.
I always
swing with it.
Give me one of the trees. I'm gonna get a tree.
Give me a tree.
I know those soldiers are bugging you, but
I just got a lead on an Enclave lab
hidden in a building. Thinking you'd knock
that sucker down. Giant toothpick.
The icon fades. The farther Hulk is from
the object, it indicates. As Hulk gets close
to the icon, it becomes more solid.
Hulk can't do
this.
By breaking an ATM? This is an
Enclave base. The Paragon Corporation
sign is a giveaway. Paragon
is the front company for the Enclave
and they leave buildings all over the city.
Open it. Hulk can destroy
buildings all around the city, but not without attracting
attention.
What are you doing?
Why are you driving directly?
I have no power
on this.
The ambulance isn't gonna do it, right? Of course, at least
the ambulance is smart. What is that?
What does the woman do over there?
What am I trying to grab? What is that thing?
Was this a person?
I still want to pick up a fucking rock.
Hulk can now perform combo attacks
with a shield. Okay.
Why would the Hulk need a shield?
I just bounced him. Let's go.
Down. Down. Swing down.
Swing down. Swing down.
This game being on the Wii,
was this game on PlayStation 2?
I feel like it probably was.
Yes, it was. I charged it up.
I can fly with this thing?
What am I supposed to be doing?
Boss has more men down here than you could believe.
This is the kill of these guys.
I think you're gonna be able to stop a strike team once it's activated.
Your only option is to lie low and wait
for things to blow over. Wait, there's like a
getaway from the cops? Get to the subway.
You should be able to lose the army in the tunnel.
Holy shit.
Hulk can use the subway to move around the city faster.
The yellow circle S
on the menu have the subway locations.
They get a new shield at any time.
Press A, B while unarmed.
And on the ground.
Get out of here. I gotta move. I gotta go.
You can also fly.
Hulk GTA on mobile.
This does look like one of those reskins.
Where the guy
made 10
GTA clones and they all have
licensed characters.
Did I make it? Wait.
I just had to walk in it.
Okay.
Mission complete.
Subway is open.
Oh shit. It costs
$5 on the app store.
Travel the New York subway system.
The map is kind of big.
It's kind of a big map.
How does Hulk ride the bus?
How does Hulk get on the train?
He walks in the tunnels.
Oh.
I didn't mean to do that.
Let's get as high as we can and we gotta get to the top
of the Empire State Building and look down like you do in
Spider-Man.
No fall damage.
The four enclave sectors have hidden their bases at key locations
in the city. Occasionally they will send out an assault group
to test the destructive power of their weapons.
Warning.
An enclave assault group is active.
Oh shit. I went too far.
This game came out before
prototype.
This game is actually kind of cool.
Is the stark tower
here? Where's stark
tower? Wait. What's this?
What was it? Did you see that? What was that?
It was like a little ring up here.
How do I move the camera?
Click the YouTube link.
Click the link. Wait, wait, wait.
What is it? What is it? This needs music.
Oh, I see.
Ground pound.
Skip.
Is it me talking?
We have to hurry. Can you
carry me? I'm carrying
this person?
You don't want to be here.
I'm wearing this. This guy's a human backpack.
Hulk found his first
fury canister.
There are another 99 hidden
throughout New York City. Collect more to increase
Hulk's rage.
Ugh.
Ultimate destruction.
Did somebody just fly?
Alright, get over here.
Oh, we're out of time, time, time, time, time, time, time, time, time, time.
Oh, it felt good.
This character is just like
I'm not, yeah.
Give me that.
Give me, give me, give me, give me,
give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me.
He just got squashed.
Are they down below?
Done?
Alright, alright, alright, alright, alright, alright, alright.
My sources, these bombs came from
a specific research facility.
Hmm.
Go on the top right.
Nice throw.
Ooh, it's stuck in the building.
You move with the game? Yes, I do.
I'm one of those fucking psychos.
Come here, come here, come here, come here,
come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here.
You!
Hey, you!
This, this more?
That's it.
Defeat the remaining fuck.
Shit, canisters, a fanabase.
Punch him!
How many more are left?
Oh, this guy here.
See ya.
Top right, be like, what?
What are you talking about? Top right, what the fuck?
What? It's you.
I'm bringing a truck with me this time.
Alright, did he fall? Alright.
Don't forget about me, I won't.
Alright, here we go, down the bowl.
Get it all with the truck. Didn't work.
Top right of the screen is me.
I know, I know!
It's not though, it's this guy.
I always remember looking at the chat and the game at the same time.
You were right here!
Good throw.
Nice. Look at me, look at me.
Jervis Grumpy.
What? I'm not Grumpy, what are you talking about?
He's pissed, I'm not pissed, I'm happy.
Playing hold, ultimate destruction for the week.
How could I not be happy?
You know, give me, give me one of these.
Hit him in the fucking skull.
How could you not like it?
This isn't ultimate destruction, I know.
Alright, on a scale of one to ten, how much better of a game is ultimate destruction than licensed Hulk video games?
Ten.
Oh wait, this one came out, this is the newer one.
Why is this one not as good?
Watch the trailer, nope.
I want to go in blind, completely blind.
I don't want to see a single thing.
This was a cash grab.
This is bootleg tie-in.
Bootleg license tie-in.
What else is over here?
Oh, I have to break the door?
Is it the door?
Or is it just break the building?
This looks like a Minecraft creative level.
It does not look like that.
It actually kind of does.
How come I can't do anything?
Oh.
Cause I destroyed it.
Ultimate destruction even looks better.
Really?
That scared the shit out of me.
I thought that was like somebody outside my window for a second.
Like I just heard it down here.
Like listen, like
Like somebody here in the house.
What's the next mission?
That sounds like Woody from Toy Story.
Help! Buzz!
How do you put somebody down?
I want to hear that. You're violating!
That actually does sound like Woody.
That could be like a Buzz Lightyear.
It sounds like Buzz Lightyear more than Woody.
How do I put people down?
I think they're going to be okay.
They're okay.
Holy shit.
That was like a super choke slam.
Alright, I'm going to do one more mission
in a Hulk tie-in movie game.
And then I'm going to
play the actual one
cause this is the wrong game.
But I feel like
we got some value from this.
I'm happy that I got to play this.
I'm very happy about this.
Alright, last mission.
How much did I pay?
I don't think this is more than like five dollars.
This is probably like six and a half dollars.
Maybe.
Choke slam somebody from the tallest building.
I can't. I don't think I can do that.
I have to jump there.
Choke slam from the highest possible place.
Cause I can't climb.
Alright, I can go from here to here.
Right here.
There.
We can jump up here.
And then I can go over this way.
Up to that building.
Okay.
Up here.
Any other buildings I can do?
Can I get up on this one?
Over there?
Might be too far.
I think it's too far to get over there.
It's not. Let's see.
No, over there.
Over here.
Rotate the camera a little bit.
How about this way?
I think this is as good as it's going to get.
Okay, we need a good spot.
That I can go all the way to the ground.
That was an elbow drop.
That was a full on landing with the elbow in his chest.
I broke his arm.
Still alive? Wow.
Didn't kill him. He's still alive.
Line up. This will kill him.
Holy shit.
Did I gamma ray this guy from the top rope?
He's invincible.
He's actually unkillable.
I knocked him over.
What if I run him over with a car?
That was brutal.
Stay right here for a second.
The cops?
He's still alive. He's still good.
How do I kill him?
That's it.
Here, punch this guy.
You can't do it either.
Throw him into the ocean.
You want me to throw him in the ocean?
I'm going to throw him in the ocean.
I was supposed to do a mission.
Ocean.
You're not coming back from this one.
Not a chance at health.
Definitely dead.
The game automatically does this to you.
He's dead.
Last mission.
He will return.
It's the same model.
Let's go.
Final mission.
It was a GMod map.
GM city.
I took a shower and you're being psycho.
What did I do?
It really is big city.
Big city in GMod.
I can stand on them?
I can stand on cars.
This is important.
I can stand on shit.
I'm trying to get you to...
I need to make a traffic jam.
I want you to bump into each other.
Very gently and explode.
It's possible.
Let me save you here.
Get on the bus.
Just throw this and get on him.
I'm the Hulk. Of course it's going to break.
The Bachelor.
Quit streaming.
Nice flip phone, Bruce.
This is like 2003.
I'm right here, dude.
You're in a tank?
You need backup and you're in a tank.
Watch out for the cabs.
Whatever his name is.
Why was this a 3D movie?
Nice.
Perfect.
A railroad spike. Whatever it is.
A railroad stick.
Not that powerful, actually.
No!
I needed that bus.
Any more buses?
These things are so fragile.
They're blowing up in my hands.
They made it a paper mache.
I didn't do anything.
They made it a thin glass.
That one's still driving.
Alright, look for a bus.
That's all I care about.
Throw a truck in the air and then shoot it in the air with a car.
No!
You can't get these guys away from me.
Oh, my head.
That was like waking up
really early when you're on the top bunk
and you smash your head on the ceiling.
You guys have that problem?
Alright, I'm jumping.
Fox, get these guys off me.
I'm coming, Slippy.
I didn't even want to pick you up.
Everybody's Elmo.
Every character is Elmo.
Every single character is Elmo.
Don't you guys know that by now?
Bus. I need a bus.
I need a bus.
Good.
I'm coming.
What do you think I'm doing?
It's over. We win.
My eyes flashed.
Okay, bus.
Still alive.
Alright, let's move.
Go into the subway.
Go into the subway
is probably the idea.
My ear is itchy.
Try to break the game.
Well, I care about throwing a bus
into the ocean, so
I mean, that's a given.
This mission is long.
That's not a bad guy.
Die!
All the way down here. Get out of here.
Where the fuck are these super mutants
even coming from?
That guy just fucked himself up.
He's dead. He's dead.
Why did he turn into
seven other smaller
cars? That guy was driving
backwards faster than you could
drive forwards.
There's so many cabs.
Now we can fucking stop.
What do we got? Six hours?
Not sure when I could start right now
that wouldn't take at least four hours.
Yeah, I'll see you tomorrow.
I'll see you tomorrow. And then I'll see you Sunday too.
What are we doing tomorrow?
That's a really good...I kind of need to look at what
I need to...I have to look at what I have.
Wait, this is a new big thing to grab.
I need to look at what I got.
A real wink? It's been a while since we had one.
Community content night is Sunday.
We'll be live tomorrow.
And then...I want to do
something I can do in one stream.
I don't know if I want to do...I think I want to move away from like the
GUI in the GameCube for a little while.
I have a lot of stuff. So I gotta figure out
what I want to do. Hulk.
Well, the good one
won't be here for at least a couple days.
Yeah, we'll figure it out.
We'll do something. And then
the community content night is Sunday.
Also the last day for winks. We're gonna do
a wink apocalypse.
So, we'll see you tomorrow.
Putting the Wiimote down.
Wink. I got it.
Putting down the Wiimote. And we're gonna end
the stream here. I'm gonna stick around. We'll do the bits
and everything. We'll hang out. But
reliably, it's
not very much I think I would want to start that
would take less than 30 to 40 minutes.
And if we're gonna do that anyways, if I'm just gonna
stream for like 31 minutes, might as well just do
the 30 to 40 minute end of the stream.
And start fresh tomorrow
I'm gonna do something that can take
6 plus hours to do.
Did I finish Mario Sunshine?
I did. Play Mario Odyssey.
I probably will.
I probably will. Well, thanks for joining me.
I'll see you tomorrow. Take care guys.
Get the music going.
Turn it up a little bit.
Do a Frogger stream.
Remember, if you just sit there
motionless for 16 hours, why don't you
just keep the cam on?
Yeah, just keep the camera on.
Stream 24x7.
But let's go back to earlier.
We had 5 community subs from Never
Trust Nanners. I think that was before the stream even
started. So thanks for that.
Bulbaswag, thanks for the 500 bits.
I'm so happy I got to derail with
this neat glitch.
Yeah, that was at least
30 to 40 minutes
of stream time. Was that
whole scenario.
And I didn't even use it. Just did it the regular way.
I'm going to buy Hulk Ultimate
Destruction and get it here as soon as
possible. Don't worry.
If I bought the wrong game, I'd make mistakes.
It's okay.
Jaxx with a bunch of X's thanks for the 500
bits. Jeremy, long time listener, first time caller.
Hope I did this right. Thanks for doing the Mario.
It was really fun.
Glad I finally got to experience
the
mainline Mario game
for the Gamecube. I didn't play it.
Thanks a lot. Cold Warhol
gave $20, 2000 bits
from Cold Warhol. Thanks for the 20 bucks.
Appreciate it. Howdy, Jeremy. Hope you're doing
well. Today's my 21st birthday, which means I'm
finally legally old enough to watch your streams.
Here's some of that birthday
card money for your own, for
your e-clown services.
Our rated movie is 17, isn't it?
What is PG-13?
What if PG-13 was 16 or something?
That would make no sense. It would just be PG-16.
But happy birthday,
Cold Warhol. Thanks for the 20 bucks.
Appreciate it. Peaceful
Haley. Thanks for the 250, Jeremy. Hope you liked
the game so far. I was wondering, which are your favorite
worlds, so far at least?
Mine is Serena Beach.
My least favorite is probably Noki Bay
because it gets annoying. Also, yeah, the only
complaint I have on this game is the camera.
The best world
in Mario Sunshine was
I think I like that
first world. Either the first
world or
yeah, probably the first world.
That first introduction world I think is really
nice. I like the
lake. I like the big windmill.
That's probably where I would like the most.
Bianco Hills, yeah.
That one reminded me the most of
Mario 64.
It was a very Mario 64-esque
level.
Are you excited for Resident Evil 3? Yep. I mean, Resident Evil 2
I thought was the best game that came out last year, so I
definitely can't wait for the next in
the series to be remade. What about
the Chalksters? Oh, that wasn't a world.
That was a secret level.
Thanks a lot, Haley. I thought it was
great. We had five
community subs from Oath Horse and
2,000 bits
from Oath Horse as well.
So thank you, Oath Horse, for your $20 and
five community subs. Back
to back. And they say awesome Mario
streams when my daughter had introduced
me to you and your content was a baby.
She watched her cousin playing
this game and when he collected a shine
she threw up her
fat baby arms and yelled
Woo Cha Chao.
It's a family
meme to this day.
Woo Cha Chao. If you get a
chance, our family would love to hear one from
you. Woo Cha Chao.
Did I do it right?
This is a sitcom plot line.
Nobody does better
gaming-related improv and sketch comedy
than you do. That's very nice of you.
Huge fans and love your content.
I told you there was kids watching. That's why
I had to be careful today.
I tried to not swear as much, but I
think I've removed
two or three swears today.
If I typically swear four to five thousand
times a stream, I took
maybe
0.2%. I'm not a kid.
You're not a kid, but
kids probably watching. There were kids potentially
in the audience.
But thanks for the
big drop and the community subs.
Appreciate that. Thank you.
Captain Sharkbait gave five community
subs, but the difference between these five
community subs and
standard community subs is these five
were tier three. They gave
five tier three community
subs, which are $25
each. Aren't they?
How much are they? $24.99, right?
Wait, how much are they?
Okay, that's expensive.
Five tier three subs.
That's $125 in subs.
So that's insane.
Thank you, Captain Sharkbait.
There's not even a tier three emote.
Do I still have 10k subs? No, I do
not. Hitting it and crossing it
was a fucking crazy thing.
I could never expect
to keep 10,000
fucking subs on this channel.
That is an unbelievable
number.
That's alright.
That does not bother me.
But thank you, Captain Sharkbait, for your
ridiculous tier three subs.
Hoj, fast thanks for the 500 bits. They just
say hype. I must have done something
cool. Thank you, HojFest.
SticksRenegade250
HeyiiGerma, I'm five.
What's a 69?
It's
a 69 is
the way to write out
how a battery connects.
How some of your devices work.
That's what they mean. That's why they think it's a cool number.
Thanks for the 250, just in case you're curious.
BraptonB
Thanks for the five community subs, Brapton.
Earlier today.
WembleyTTV
Hey, Germa, I took into account
what you said.
I did dream about you and Spongebob crossing swords.
You made it even worse.
I still got you naked with
Defoe while you and Spongebob
you know, nevermind that. Thanks for the help.
What? I still got
naked?
Why are we naked? Wait.
PeacefulHailey, thanks for the 250. Germa, please let
me simp you.
What does that mean?
What does that mean? Turn the stream
off now.
Thank you. I don't
know what that is. KeithKingKrimz
Thanks for the 250. Hey, Germa, this is Keith.
The NPC from The Bachelor. I deserved
that rose, not you, fucker.
Well, you didn't get enough hearts.
I did.
YharnamTouristShop, thanks for the
300 bits.
Germa, how much do I have to pay you to stop playing
this bachelor game and come beat
Orphan of Kos
with me? Name your price.
Oh, there is
none. Price is
n-slash-a, not applicable.
Hey, many rabbits, thanks for the 300
bits. In the span of about three weeks, I lost my job
and now I'm losing my home. That's
terrible. Sorry to hear
that. Meanwhile, I'm watching your
JumpKingBots and there's something kind of therapeutic
about watching you fail so intensely
over and over again while I'm dealing with this.
Love you, 5ever.
I don't know your exact scenario, but that's
that sounds fucking horrible.
Hopefully you get that figured out.
I cannot imagine something like that happening.
Yeah, hope everything turns out
okay. Thanks for the $3
and good luck.
We also had TheManWithTheBabyHands
for 1000 bits
$10 teddy bear streamer
No, I'm not a teddy bear. I'm not a teddy bear.
Let me tell you, I'm a bull.
What's the world's sleepiest animal?
Okay, for like one hour a day
I'm a bull.
And then for 23 more hours I'm a koala.
That's like
two to three hours I'm a bull.
For 22 to 21 hours a day
I'm a koala. What does that make me?
An idiot.
Hey
Lazy Luke, thanks for the 250.
Last stream we talked about something like this.
So I made a page which randomly
picks a moment out of about
3200 hours of archived streams
and main channeled videos.
Are you kidding me? You did this in one day?
Click the button at the top
center to play a random moment out of
3200 hours of Jerma videos
and streams.
You fucking legend.
You are legendary. Are you serious?
You actually did this?
Oh my god.
Unfucking believable.
It works. This is
unbelievable. This is amazing.
Holy shit.
Well, okay.
So for those that have need context here
talked about how funny it would be
on a stream if
we took every
stream I've ever done.
Or at least the ones that are available.
The archive channel has 80
to 90% or so of every
stream I've ever done. And every
10 minutes we change
to a random stream
at a random time. And watch
for 10 minutes and see what happens.
That would be pretty fun.
Compact duration.
Do that tomorrow.
I mean, it's
ready to use.
That's unbelievable. I did not think
this was going to be ready to use as of now.
Easy content.
Hold on. Let me think about this.
Do it now. No, no, no, no, no.
We have to sit there. We have to be ready for this.
I don't want to do one right now.
I don't want to give that away.
Lazy Luke. Holy shit.
Lazy Luke, what's your Discord name? What's your name on Discord?
Are you using Lazy Luke
on Discord?
Do I have you on Discord?
Alright, somebody get a hold of that guy.
One of the mods. Get a hold of Lazy Luke.
I want to talk to Lazy Luke.
One on one.
What? No, I...
No! And I'll tell you a couple of reasons
why. First,
very importantly,
Lazy Luke has made
a better stream dashboard
than all the ones
that are currently available.
It's five times better than Streamlabs.
And they've also
got a couple of the little website things.
I want to have a couple
of words with Lazy Luke
about some stuff. Yeah, I mean,
we're doing this too.
This sounds ominous.
Ominous.
What's their exact username?
They sent their info. Okay, cool.
There we go.
The newest VIP of the channel is Lazy Luke.
I mean, this is so good.
We talked about this
just off the cuff.
Randomly. Yesterday.
And it's already done and ready to be used?
That's unfucking believable.
Talk to me on Discord. We've got some stuff to talk about.
I'll put you up in the next day or two.
Anyways, we have...
Where are we?
We have Leroy Brown for $5.
Jerma, this stream has been amazing.
I love this stream so much that I made a JPG
to remember it by.
Wait, why am I green?
Why am I green in this picture?
Can you see it? Wait, what's going on?
Oh, sorry.
Oh, cause the Hulk.
Alright. What am I thinking of the
slide level?
He thought I was a Teletubby.
Thank you
for the $5 Leroy. Appreciate it.
Zaru, thanks for the 300 bits.
My friends and I occasionally play Happy Rock.
And reminds you...
Reminds me of your hilarious
Grab That Auto 5 video and many more.
Thanks for being a hilarious entertainer
and genuine human being.
Oh, thank you.
Happy Rock. Thank you, Zaru.
Zaru. For the $5.
Re dollars.
The nibs. Thanks for the $5.
Can you wish my friend Justin
a happy birthday? Sure.
Happy birthday, Justin.
From me, Jerma985.
I hope you have
a healthy day
and things look great.
And I hope that you get cool.
Don't overdo it. Don't overdo it.
Yeah, this is turning into
a cameo.com video.
Yeah, sorry about that. Happy birthday, Justin.
Thanks for the $5.
Hunter Johnson.
Thanks for the $5. Can't wait for you to see my video
for Community Content Night.
Neither can I. 500 bits.
Jay Bong. Thanks for the $2.50.
Hey man, is your body ready for VR yet?
Or are you going to have to wear your boomer brace for a few more weeks?
I can't wait for you to play Boneworks
and Half-Life Alex.
Maybe invest in those index controllers.
Yeah, we talked about this in
pre-stream chat a little bit today, but
anything that requires
tilting, rotating,
and moving around and jumping
around, I could do it for
20 minutes or 30 minutes
or so, but it's really the
tilting and the leaning and the move
with that thing on my head
adding weight
to kind of my
cervical, whatever it is, spine,
whatever it is, the top part of your spine,
it might not be a great
idea. And
I kind of have to just try to
take care of this
and do it as best as I can.
But, cervical spine.
The cervical spine is where your
neck, that's the part, that's the spine where
your neck is, it's your neck bones.
What are you guys talking about?
What did you think I was talking about?
Cerebral? No, it's your
cervical spine.
You guys, what are you on about?
But, uh, Grain Screen
Part 2 is just
on indefinite hold.
Doing extensive VR is on
hold. I still have Connect
Games to play that, but I'm like, I can't
like run around my room and shit like I
just can't right now. That's the unfortunate
truth, they all have to be on indefinite hold
until
I have a real good permanent
solution for what's going on.
Right now it's physical therapy, and if
physical therapy doesn't work over the next
month or two, then I
have to go get an intercostal nerve block
injection into my body.
So, I'm sure
I'll probably be fine after that,
but that has to happen, but I don't want to do it yet.
That was a big word,
yeah, it was a very big word.
So, can't really do a whole lot of movement.
I'm not
hopefully not making a sound like a
I can't move like oil, oil
like
No, no, it's not like that,
but I don't want to aggravate anything.
Sudden movements can be like
ooh, ow, and
obviously if I'm doing physical therapy, I don't want to go to
my physical therapist and be like, oh hey, yeah
my like chest and back hurt really
bad today. I did a bunch of VR shit
and was like spinning around in circles.
Oh, are we starting at zero again
with physical therapy? Whoops.
I'm just concerned about it.
There you go.
Oylixes
or oylixes, thanks for the
thousand bits. Ten dollars.
Appreciate it. Hey, Jeremy,
I just wanted to say that after seeing
taxi after taxi drive into a building and
explode on contact, that was some of the
funny you should have seen in a long time.
And my diaphragm and cheeks still hurt from laughing.
I really needed to pick me up like that.
You're a perfect antidepressant.
Thank you for all you do, and I wish you the absolute
best on your road to recovery.
I can speak for everyone present when I say that we're all here to support
you as you've supported us.
There were a couple things
today that really got me going.
And yesterday too.
Now that
it wasn't even, it was the cars was funny.
The first like I hit the guy in the face
with polos, like I just didn't think he would even do that in
these games. They,
I don't think I want like the Marvel super heroes
to be the good guys.
That's what I'm saying in Spider-Man. You just walk up
and wave to people. You can't like blast
people in the face as hard as you can.
It's the Hulk. Yeah, I know.
But the Hulk doesn't like fucking hit people
with wrenches and shit.
Hulk does bad stuff.
I guess, but
I really appreciate that. And thanks for the $10.
The man with the baby hands thanks for
500 bits. Remember when Jerma One Guy
was the tier 3 emote?
Yep. But then we
found a really really good use for it.
So it had to become baseline.
I can't hide that behind
a $25 a month, are you serious?
That's one of the most important
ways for chat to communicate
with me. It's really
easy for you guys to spam that and I know
that I got one guide.
That's incredible communication
tool. But yeah, I do
remember that. Uh, Hallulu.
Hallulu. Thanks for the
350. Hi Jerma, the last time
I gave you bits I asked you for streaming advice and I
watched the VOD the next day
and watched stunned to find that this led
to you eating baby food on camera.
It was a little extra weird
because earlier that week I was in the market
and was eyeing the flavors they had
and wished they made adult versions
of some of them. You get it.
Sweet potato, carrot, and mango
why wouldn't I eat that?
Anyway, thanks and much love to you and chat.
It's a tip. It's a
real tip.
The whole gang is here.
It's real. I do that.
Alright, let's get the credits to roll. We have
only a few more bits to do. Let's actually
change the scenery here.
Watch your head.
Here we go. Oh wait, am I
am I not
logged in?
I'm not logged in.
I got de-logged out.
Gotta log back in.
Hold on.
Nobody subbed. Imagine.
Why do I feel like one of these days you guys are gonna coordinate
to make it so nobody does so that it just scrolls by
and just like thanks for subbing
and there's just no names. There's one or two.
There they come. All of you, thank you
again. I will see you tomorrow.
For...I don't know.
There are a few
very good options now.
We'll see which one we do. Thanks for all the subs.
You guys fucking rock.
We have a few more bits. We have Keith King Crimson
for 250. By the way,
to simp someone is like to
white knight them or like do
anything for them. It's a meme.
No, that was Peaceful Hayley.
It skipped up on me.
Peaceful, that was Peaceful Hayley. Did I say Peaceful
Hayley? Am I losing my mind?
It's just a meme. It's just a
meme. Hey, you said
it. You said it.
Thanks for the 250.
Thanks for the 250. I saw someone bring this up
and all the memories came back.
Remember clown in the town.
Now that you're a millionaire, this
project becomes much more reasonable, doesn't
it? Now gather star and MLC
Stealth and make it reality. Looking forward
to it. That's
one of the best ideas.
And we have that
conversation stamped.
It's like ours, you know what I mean?
If somebody does clown in the town, it's like, no, no, excuse
me. You took that from us.
That whole explanation of how
that would work is just, that would be
an amazing TV show. It'd be
fucking incredible. Keith King Crimson
thanks for the 250. Look, Jerma, I may
not be good at catching feathers or oysters
or tracing zodiac signs, but at least
I have to get
back to you on that one. What's clown
in the town? Clown in the town is one of those
things that it would take 45
minutes for me to explain it to you.
I think there are a couple of YouTube videos
that have the full thing
and it is the full explanation
of clown in the town. I have
it on my Soundcloud. Let me. Really?
Thank you, Keith King Crimson.
Anson is a copter.
I don't know.
I like doing things,
but I don't know if that thing is possible.
I don't know.
Hey, Tar Alecran, thanks for the 250. Just use the random Jerma
moment feature from that website and got one of those
10 minute stretches where you didn't talk
from rhythm heaven.
Alright, don't tell me
these things. Don't tell me these things.
This is like 3500 hours
of videos and streams. I wonder
what the algorithm, where it can pull
from? Is it possible to get pull from all of it?
I can't wait.
This is going to be so much fun.
I got one. It was a sim getting hit by a car.
Oh man, that's going to be so
funny. How does it determine
a moment? It just picks a random
timestamp on a random
stream.
And there are
uploaded and documented
about 3500 hours, which is probably
it's probably 70
to 80% of every stream I've ever done.
I think this is probably like streams
that have been lost that have not been uploaded
or that have got deleted somehow
over the last four or five years.
But I look forward to this.
This is going to be fun. There are
133 days.
That's a lot of content
to randomly generate.
I'm excited for this.
We're going to go channel surfing
from every stream I've ever done.
It'll be fun.
Garfield the Monday Killer, thanks for the 250.
It's a time for new beginnings.
Garfield's full animated Sonic film
just premiered.
I'm sure there were a few delays, but it's out.
This is some drawn out joke about how I directed
the Sonic movie.
There's currently an hour long reanimated
Sonic film called Sonic Rebuilt for free
on YouTube. I know I can't
send links anymore, but it'd mean the world to me
if you checked some of it out.
Big shout out to all the animators who helped
directed it for you in chat.
This thing's an hour long? Link banned.
Hey, sorry, I'm fucking
Link banned.
That's cool that you
that's done. I didn't know it was going to be
that long. I thought this was like a
10 minute project.
Like a full hour long feature.
Holy shit. When's the rat movie
reanimated thing coming out?
Oh, I've heard about that.
Can we get a link? Yeah, check it out.
I can't really watch that right now.
But I will definitely
click it and I will watch it.
I don't think I
don't even watch TV shows for an hour.
I'll be honest with you. You know how long it's
taken for people to try to get me to watch Joel's
3D movie, Baker movie, that's like 26
minutes long?
Ah, fuck, I don't have
I'll watch it, I will.
But yeah, he still wants
you to watch it. I know, I know, I know,
I know. I have watched it. I've got a lot of
things to watch. Just watch it two minutes
at a time. No,
you can't just watch it one minute at a time.
Watch Joel's movie. Do it
on community content night. But it's not community
content night because Joel didn't make that
for community content night.
That's why you have to watch it two minutes.
Rip the Band-Aid off. He watches
your movies and you won't watch his?
Who cares? Watch it anyway. Yeah,
he did. It's not how it worked.
It's still content from the
community. Alright, well
we're gonna watch Joel's movie
not on Sunday. Not on Sunday.
We're gonna watch
Joel's 3D movie maker movie.
I'm gonna give you a date.
Thursday the
Hold on. Thursday the 12th.
On the shoe eating stream.
I'm gonna watch
Joel's movie maker movie
while I eat a shoe.
In fact, that's gonna be the first
stream after
coming back from
being off for a few days.
We're streaming tomorrow,
we're doing Sunday community content night, and
then I'm gonna be off for a few days.
When I come back on Thursday the 12th,
I'm gonna eat a fucking shoe.
And we're gonna watch that movie.
It's too much candy?
Don't worry. He needs a few days
to make an edible shoe.
I didn't say what kind
of shoe it had to be. It's just
a shoe or a
shoe-like substance.
What was that laugh?
I hated that.
That was a horrible laugh.
But we had 250 from
Goo Berry Juice.
If you want to find out if you're a bull or a koala,
try this quiz. It's not bad, I promise.
I think it'd be interesting to do it on stream.
Also, can I know which animal
to photoshop your face onto?
A lion.
Animalinu.com
Somebody remember that? Because we're doing that
on Thursday the 12th.
Thursday the 12th is gonna be
an absolute dog shit stream.
Thursday the 12th is gonna be the worst stream
of the year.
It's the fulfilled promise stream.
Okay, so look.
Let's be real.
I'm gonna watch a 3D movie maker movie
that's 30 minutes long, eat a
shoe on camera, and
do an animal quiz.
That's what's planned for the 12th.
So, sounds fun.
It sounds bad when you say it
like that. You mean saying it
out loud?
Wow, well thanks for the 400 bits.
Jerma Grinch.
With some snowmen emotes.
Don't eat a shoe. If you think I'm
gonna eat, like, a
Skechers shoe.
I don't know what to tell you.
I'm gonna eat a
shoe.
Shooo
on camera. Yes.
Awfutz.
Thanks for the 500 bits, Awfutz.
Five dollars, thanks a lot. Haven't been able to watch
the streams lately because of school, and I feel
incredibly behind, and I'm like missing out on all the
fun. The other day I started calling
you King, and you noticed that
three streams in a row, and kind of
seemed Monka-esque out.
It's just a reminder that you're
King. Thanks for the lulz.
Wait, so when I've been saying
You know, I've been seeing somebody
I've been seeing a lot of King. What's a King?
It was the same person.
And I just caught it three
times in a row. It's literally
just me.
Wow.
I thought it was if people write in it.
It's only been one person.
No one else has been doing it.
It's literally just
me. I thought it was a shit load
of people.
That's fucking funny.
Thanks for the five dollars, dude.
Opster Narwhal, again, thanks
for 253. Have you heard of the PlayStation
2 classic Muppets Party Cruise?
It's a true hidden gem, and must
be played on stream. So do it.
That or RollerCoaster Tycoon 3.
Also, people be paying
75,000 channel points for
Winx when I have an infinite amount
of German Wink, German Wink,
German Wink, German Wink. What does that mean?
Muppets Party Cruise.
Garfield the Monday Killer,
thanks for the 250. You don't have to watch the whole
thing on stream. Just skip around.
I just wanted some raw German commentary.
I don't know.
We'll do it on Sunday.
That's like a community piece of content
that qualifies.
I'll skip through and watch a couple of
pieces of it on Sunday.
What are you going to do? Don't starve together.
I don't think I am.
Winx are going to be half off on Sunday?
They might even be lower than that.
FutureGamer, thanks for 250. How is FTK
coming along? Any time frame yet?
Um, not
before German
Rumble charity.
There's going to be a charity German Rumble stream
that happens over the next few weeks.
A buddy of mine is running
in the Boston Marathon
and we are going to do a charity stream
to sponsor
his run.
And all the money that,
every cent that
comes into that stream
is going to be a couple of places to make it easy.
We'll go directly to
the foundation
that is going to sponsor
his run.
A lot of people were talking about charity
stuff and charity streams
and I've never really done one
on my own, on my own
channel.
I've been a part of a lot of other
great projects
and great charity events, right?
The Blind Saw stuff
the last couple of years has been
somewhat involved with some of it.
Obviously the Tip of the Hat stuff
in years past.
I've never done one, I've never
done one. I'm always on somebody
else's thing and I think it just,
it's time to try to do one. I just want to
try it and see if we can do some.
So there will be,
there will be a lot more information on that
a week or two before it
happens because I'm not just going to like do
a, hey here it, German Rumble,
here it is. At least two
or three weeks before that stream happens, which it has
to happen before
the, when's the Boston Marathon?
April like 10th? April 20th or something?
April 20th.
So before April 20th
it will be a stream.
And it's going to be the German Rumble.
I know it's a little late
but it'll be there.
It should be good.
But that is the end.
I will see you guys later.
I'll see you tomorrow.
We got some options and I'll be in
pre-stream chat before the stream turns on.
So we can kind of discuss it,
talk about it. I am going to go, I am
very hungry. So I'm going to get out of here.
Have a good night, take care,
and goodbye. See you soon.
Right at the buzzer we had 250
from GooBerryJuice. Hey
King985, remember that game I talked about a few
streams ago? AlphaChimp, who is only
available on Xbox Live. Turns out it's free
on PC now. Please play it, it's so good.
Please God.
Thanks. Uh, maybe.
Not tomorrow and not the next day.
I'm
begging.
Please God in all
capitals. That means
never. No it doesn't. It means not immediately,
which means never.
But never on this channel doesn't actually mean never.
It means maybe a
year. You might just see it,
I don't think I was going to ever play Super Mario
Sunshine on this stream. I think like
two years ago, people
were like, hey dude, you should,
you're thinking about doing GameCube streams.
You're doing like PlayStation 1, PlayStation 2 stuff.
You would love the GameCube stuff.
And I'm like, yeah, I don't know, maybe like in a few months.
You should play Mario Sunshine.
Yeah, I don't know. Probably not.
Here we are. It's been two years.
Never doesn't mean never on
this channel. It means like
probably not. For a long time.
But I did
not say that I was never going to play
AlphaChimp.
So don't worry. Don't worry.
Uh, then finally I have Obstinawal
for five dollars. So I'm going to ask this and I thought it
should be answered. Will the rumble be pushed
back if the marathon gets canceled due
to Corona? Or will we just
do it to get it out of the way?
Um, I, that's a
really, really, really good question.
Because I don't really have an answer for that.
Because I, I don't know
what, if that would happen or if it's
possible or what would
probably end up happening
is, hmm.
If something like that
does happen, which
God forbid, hopefully not, right?
I mean, hopefully this can be contained
and it's not, doesn't turn into
anything super serious.
Uh, but
in the event for some reason it does
turn into something like that.
Um, we'll probably
if it gets moved
we'll probably just do the same and move it.
And I might do a
sort of like a pre
not like a full rumble. Maybe I'll do
like a little like wrestling card
that's not the rumble but just maybe
introduces some of the new characters maybe.
Just for fun for like maybe like an hour or two.
We'll see.
There's no way that that's gonna happen.
I mean, what the probability
maybe, but I mean there's always a
chance that something bad could happen, right? There's always
a chance that something like this
is not contained and
for some reason it gets out of control
and it has to be lots of closings
and stuff. I mean it's, it's possible.
Is it probable? No.
But it's possible.
A lot of huge things have been cancelled recently.
Yeah, it's, I mean
some of them, yeah. Twitchcon
Amsterdam, ECCC.
Yeah.
I don't know. I guess that's kind of have to be
gonna have to be a wait and see scenario to see what actually
happens. It's
not a bad thing to think about though.
SXSW was cancelled, yeah.
That's true.
FutureGamer for 250, thanks a lot dude for the 250.
My school shut down
a
school shut down, a Rome travel study
and everyone was sent home and told to
self quarantine for 14 days. Jesus.
Yeah, this shit's no joke.
But we'll cross that bridge if we have to.
And I'll figure it out from there.
I'm gonna go. Before I
go, I'm going to
I'm gonna turn on
the voice
changer to low and echoey
and make a bunch of noises.
How you feel about that? Do you guys feel pretty good about that I think?
Right, that's
what I'm going for. And I'll see you tomorrow.
Have a good night.
Bye!