Comedy Central TV time. Aye yi yi. God damn it. You guys have no idea. I'll wait a little bit for
people to come in for me to tell this story. Because to understand the end of the story,
you have to understand the beginning. What is Guitar-O-Man? Oh, you're in for a treat,
and so am I. Because I ain't ever played it either. And this is the original Guitar-O-Man.
That's supposed to be the title. The original Guitar-O-Man. This ain't no hacked copy.
This ain't the remake that was on PlayStation Portable. This is the original Guitar-O-Man for
PlayStation 2. Am I gonna do a stream on Rhythm Heaven? Maybe. But I wanted to break it up a
little bit today. We've been doing horror games. Scary scream-in-your-face games. For the last like
two weeks. So I'm like, you know, it's time to break it up and do something a little more
light-hearted. So today, we are gonna do Guitar-O-Man. And then tomorrow, we're going to do
the new Trine with Star and Ashley. I believe that's what's happening tomorrow. So we're gonna
light it up a little bit. And then after that, we're gonna go to the thing. We've got a whole
plan for this next week or two straight. Yes, the thing. What thing? The thing. The thing.
But anyways, let's have a little discussion on what happened earlier today. The Three Triners.
That's right. Okay, so like I said, to understand the end of the story, you have to understand the
beginning. So as a lot of you know, I've been having some issues lately. Stomach issues.
I've been having stomach pain. I've been having abdominal pain, abdominal cramps, and back pain
for the last probably eight months. I've had a colonoscopy. We've gone through like all kinds
of stuff. We've gone, I've had a colonoscopy. I'm going in for like another endoscopy of my
stomach. I have to get a liver scan. We're trying to find out what the fuck is wrong with me, right?
Because it's, I don't, we don't think it's related to colitis. Whatever it is, we're trying to figure
it out. So I'm on a couple of new medications, right? And these medications, let's just lay it
out there because you have to understand. Let's lay it out there. I don't care. I right now,
which we're trying to do a few things, and one of them is to do with my intestines and my stomach.
Right now, I am on a prescription grade laxative. Let's get it out there. Like out of what the fuck
do I care? One of the reasons why I've had to say, wait, our streams are going to be like
four or five hours, four hours this week is because I'm actually on a literal prescription
grade laxative. So that's one of the, that's one of the medications I'm on. We're trying something
to do. It's, I don't even, I don't even tell you why I just am. Anyways, so I know I'm on all this
new medication and I know that I have a liver scan coming up. So I have a liver scan coming up
in a couple of weeks actually. And I woke up this morning. Seemed like a pretty normal morning,
right? Yeah, everything's normal. What's, what's, what's going on here? Just going to get my coffee
and have some fun and just stream. That sounds like, yeah, we're going to stream today too.
So those of you that know anything about liver problems, there is a certain condition that can
come that can arise when you have a pretty, a liver issue. One of those things is yellowing
of the skin. It's called jaundice. So I woke up this morning and I didn't look in the mirror.
I hadn't taken like a shower yet. I was making coffee. It was up and down the stairs. So about
like an hour and a half or so before I was going to start the stream, I look in the mirror and I
noticed that my skin is yellow, like under my arms was bright Crayola yellow. And I'm going,
no, this is, that's, that's jaundice, right? I'm on this new medication. Is it the new medicine?
Oh, okay. I'm, I got to figure this out. What the fuck is happening? So I called Kim and I'm like,
Kim, I just want to let you know, I'm probably, I got to go to the doctor. I'm not sure if this
is something to do maybe with the liver thing that we were talking about, me and the doctor.
So I, I, I got to go get like something done. I got to get my blood work or something.
Okay. So that's what's going to happen. Just want to make sure I'm okay. Everything's fine.
And I'm about to literally go to the, to the ER. Like I was going to go to the ER because the
doctor's office, all the doctor's office is closed on the weekends. By the way, why the fuck is that
a thing? Why are doctor's offices closed on the weekend? What if you have a problem? But anyways,
so I'm like getting re ready to go with my, my yellow skin and I stopped for a second and I,
I take a wet wipe and I start to wipe hard on the places that are yellow and it's coming off.
My skin was dyed yellow from a bath I took yesterday. I took a bath last night and,
and put in some like a, like, like an oil essential oil thing and it was green. It's
from a bath bomb. It was turmeric oil, but you have to understand something. I've been told
we need to check your liver. Um, your abdominal pain could be because you, you might have an,
you know, you might have an enlarged liver and liver jaundice and my brain, I'm just going,
this is the, this is the, this has to be it. So I dyed my skin yellow accidentally last night,
taken a bath bomb bath and I, but it wasn't there. It was not, it was not there.
I didn't get out of the bath and I wasn't like yellow. I woke up yellow. I didn't go to bed
yellow. Oh, but I, I, I, I, can you imagine if I had gone to the doctor? Yes. What is it? Mr.
Hamilton? You've got, unless I see you've got some jaundice there. Yeah. Yeah. I don't know. And I
would give him the whole story. Yeah. We're trying to figure it out. I mean, my regular doctor,
we're trying to figure out like I'm getting a liver exam, a liver, a scan. We think my liver
might be have some problems with it. Um, I've been having abdominal pain and this is all real.
And he's like, Oh, come here for a second. Let me take a look at you. Yeah. Let's go,
let's put you through a bunch of more tests. And he finds out that I've just like have like
yellow food coloring on me. What is that doctor going to say to me?
He's medical grade wet wipes. He's going to be like, uh, Jeremy, did you, are you, uh,
did you, did you do this? Why are you have yellow food coloring on you coming to the doctor?
Cause if I didn't do that, it would be just as much of a surprise to me as it is to him
or them, whatever. Right. It'd be like, I don't know. I don't know what that is. Is that what's
going on? I'm confused too. Did, uh, did somebody paint me? Somebody paint my body? I don't know.
Doctor, I don't know what's going on. Imagine having to have that conversation of like, this
is you have that's okay. You know, when GameStop employees, uh, tell you about the crazy customer
that comes in and like, Oh, it's a GameStop stories dot Reddit, whatever. Right. I would be on the
like doctor, like crazy stories subreddit. So I have the guy that came in with, with like the
yellow paint on his body telling the doctor he had jaundiced. God damn it. So that was my, uh,
that was my afternoon. I canceled the stream. I came in here before the stream started and I
canceled it. I was like, guys, I've, I've got like an issue I've got to figure out.
But the reason why this sucks so bad is, and I know that's like funny,
but like at the same time I'm sitting there going, all right, so we still got to figure out what's
wrong with me. I still have to go for those exams. You know what I mean? I still am on a prescription
grade laxative. You know, that doesn't go away. But anyways, uh, so today we're going to play
guitar. Oh man, that's, that was the story. He's fooling his chat live. Like I can't imagine
how embarrassing that would be if I, if I actually went to the doctor,
he would just take a wet, like a, like a medical grade wet wipe and just go like that and be like,
sir, what are you doing here? Like the cost, it would cost so much like money too.
Imagine you go to the ER and it's just, you have to wipe your skin with a wet wipe.
Oh man. Anyways, we can move on now. I just figured I would let you guys know.
That's why the stream is starting 40 minutes late. Uh, we had some huge, uh, donations coming here.
We had Freddy dread gave 10,000 bits, $100, 10,000 bits. Uh, Frig, I can't watch the stream today,
but game hard boss. Oh, this is a hard game. Okay. Thank you for the 10,000 bits. Freddy
dread. I'll do my best. It's going to be a relaxing stream. It's all right. And then another thing
I've like come to, like, I've come to terms with the fact that shit like that just kind of happens
to me. You know, it's just like, and whatever, it's just another one. He's telling you the
game's hard and it's all right. What's this? Somebody's got an image. That's not even what
I said. What it's got an amazing man. I misread it. They say, no, it says, uh, Frig, I can't watch
the stream today, but game hard boss, like game hard, like game sucks. And they're calling me boss.
Is this like a game hard? This game is hard or go for it. You game hard today.
I don't know. I woke up yellow today. Okay. I'm still getting over this. It was like very
stressful. I was like, I was like, we're going to call my mother and shit. Like it was, this was
daughter, like a very good morning. That's a sentence. Oh, okay. But anyways, thank you,
Freddy dread. And then thank you to, uh, zip. So for the 10 community subs, appreciate that. Thank
you. Uh, I cannot do face cam today because, um, it's not plugged in. That's it. I've been
doing a lot of face cam. We're going to, this is, this is, we don't need face cam. This is a,
this is a music stream. Speaking of music streams. Why don't we take a look at it?
And here it is, or at least it should be there. It's our old man. Hey, yeah. I don't even know
what it sounds like. What does it sound like? Why can I not hear this? Did it just stop?
All right. First things first, like we do with every old console game, we need to test to make
sure that you can, that this is synced up. Okay. Here we go. You ready? One, two, three, four,
one, two, three, four, one, two, three, four. We good. All right. So, uh, guitar,
old man is a game where you play the guitar and it's a rhythm game. And apparently it's a hard
game. What I've been told from, uh, some of the members of this community, let's give it a try.
We got a full motion video cut scene in the beginning. That's good.
Hmm. It's Snoopy.
You know, you want, cause he been pecking on you again. You're really like totally useless.
Aren't you? Oh, shut up. But you want, there's something you can do about it. I think.
Come on, let's go. Give it a shot. Oh, it's going to teach me how to play the guitar on a tennis
racket. Me when I'm on prescription grade laxatives. All right. I tell you, I, I, I'm,
I'm all right. I'll be completely transparent with it. All right. Guitar.
There's one, two. I don't have one. Head forward. Head. Yeah. Like give yourself a nerd neck.
How's that? Feel good. Okay. Lean forward. Same thing with the left stick.
Tilt it in any direction and spin around and tilt your head forward. Relax your shoulders.
Have bad airflow. It's called the trace line. Okay. Wait, I just have to use the analog.
Look, rotate the left analog to follow the trace. Oh shit. Oh man. This isn't going to be hard.
This is a hard game boss. When do I get to go like,
so you hold it and let it go. Oh Jesus. Okay. I'm ready. I'll try. Oh, this way. Oh shit.
Come on. That's better than okay. Wait, that wasn't me doing that. I thought that was me doing that.
Nice. It's Cheeto.
I just spilled coffee literally all over my whole body. Give me a break. What a disaster.
So how do you use a guitar to fight?
First, the charge. The charge is the phase where you gain power. I have like a street fighter meter.
If your timing's off or if the trace line goes out of the blue zone, you won't gain.
Next, the battle phase. There's the attack mode in the car. You alternate between them.
What?
Okay. Oh no.
Thank God this is on PlayStation controller.
Here we go. I don't need him to say push.
I mean, you're adorable, but I don't need you to say it. I don't like how they're not colored
correctly. Oh, I guess they are. What am I talking about? Red is uh, or yeah, pink is square.
I'll be all right.
So wait, do I get to like just strum random stuff?
Okay, so don't make mistakes. Easy.
Yeah, I just won't make any mistakes. Tutorial boss incoming.
Good. Don't make any mistakes. What? Here we go. Defense. It's just about timing. It's just
right when the beat happens. I'll be really good. Now it's my turn. Oh shit. What did I do?
Oh, that's fucking hard when you go around in a circle. What's wrong? What's wrong? What's wrong?
Why are these stuff? I'm big. This is too much. I can't do this.
Dude, you know it's getting real when their mouth turns into a square. That's how you know
shit's hitting the fucking fan. This is real. This is an issue. This is a little issue that I
have here. I have an old, I have a, hold on, somebody's coming in the room. Could you just
open this jar real quick? Sorry. I'm getting like, I'm getting like jump scared from behind.
Open this jar? How come every time? This is just what I do. Look at that. Thank you. I still got
it. Thank you. I still got it. I just opened jars on stream. Sorry about that. The last, okay. I
think the last three Kim appearances on stream have been open the jar. Here comes the dog.
Open the jar. I'm fairly certain about that. All right. Here we go. Retry. No, try again. I lost
already? All right. I'm ready. Why do you get full power? What I'm going to say is I have a,
I don't have an official PlayStation 2 controller. I can already, I can see an issue here already.
Okay. Excuse me. Let's go. It's very jagged. Yeah. I got it. I got it. I got that right. What
happened? Why do I feel like I'm doing that wrong? Get out of here. Oops. This is actually
really fun. I'll tell you one thing though. This takes every single ounce of my concentration.
I don't have room in my brain to speak. Not today. It's taking up every spot in my mind.
The final, here we go. Oh, got it. What? No. You win. Who's the dinosaur?
The game is way too fast. I got a B. I'll take a B. How many misses? Only 4%.
I got mostly good. That's a B. I'll take a B. Replay this game. What? What are you talking
about? Replay this game. Collection get. Save current game. Yes. Put it in slot one.
Which bank will you save game data in? Toothbrush lizard? All right. Sounds good. What? Wouldn't
you be more injured? I feel like first try I could do a better job dubbing that. I mean,
maybe not like the quality of the voice, but like the quality of the singing.
My dog can talk. That's a real quick way to get everyone to pay attention.
No, but then it's like every television show that's ever had a talking animal in it.
They'll come over and the dog won't talk. It'll just like pee on a hydrant or something. It won't
speak. What the fuck is this? Remember the Warner Brothers frog? The guy that found the frog.
They're hello my baby. Hello my dog. And nobody did. He didn't do it in front of anybody else.
And the guy went nuts as a boomer reference. That's a classic piece of animation history.
Flying. Oh, you're stopping the UFO invasion. This sounds pretty good. I got to get both
headphones into this one. Nice. Pretty good. 100% this one. What do you say?
That was hard. It was hard. That was hard. What do you mean killing? I'm not killing anybody.
I'm still winning. Slot machine. I love it. Damn it. This controller sucks. What brand is this?
It's unbranded. That's the problem. I have an unbranded controller right now.
That's bad. It's not even a mad cat. I'm still winning. All right. You're going to pay attention.
Fuck. Come on. I was doing it. I haven't taken very much damage. That's all right. Okay. Be ready.
Oh, come on. This thing's unbranded. It's unbranded. It has a turbo, though.
Watch out, little lady.
I fucked up. Not the last note.
That's the last note again. You absolutely fucked the ending.
You win.
I still did okay. Me. I'll take it. Why do I not have an official PS2 controller? What was I
thinking? I mean, yes. This is a purchase from like three years ago. Go get one. I don't need one.
I'll deal with it. It's an excuse. Can you imagine? Okay. So I don't want to leave right now. Like,
no, I can't. I don't want to leave. I just started the stream. Imagine like Uber Eatsing,
a PlayStation 2 controller, like Postmatesing, an Uber Eats controller. You can't buy these guys.
There's no buying these. A PlayStation 2 controller, you can't buy them anywhere. You
have to like special get them on like Amazon. Do Amazon same day prime. Yeah. It'll be here in
like 12 hours. Same day delivery. Yeah, it's three o'clock Pacific. Okay, let's go. Get out,
get out, get out, get out, get out. No, don't. I already did it, didn't I? Yes. No.
Get Amazon ultra delivery.
Do not fail me. Send Moto King B into the forest.
Okay, listen, you one, you're of the guitar man bloodline, inheritor of the legendary guitar.
Of course. If you can collect all the guitars, you'll gain great powers and boom,
huh? I have other plans. I'm going to practice my skateboarding and Pico's going to be like,
wow, you're so cool. Look, only you can use this guitar that's been passed down for generations
by the ancestors. The ancestors, meaning my ancestors, meaning what? By the way, Puma,
since when exactly have you been living at my place? I don't know exactly when I was born,
so I'm not exactly the, look out. Are you sure that that dog's okay? It's got like a crushed head.
All right, here we go. I didn't even see the intro here. Frog King B.
Let's do it. All right. That was definitely the best song so far.
Yeah, that's all the commentary you're going to get. That's the only thing I'm going to say
this whole stream. I guarantee it. Yeah. Yeah. Just cap that and just play it over and over again.
I'm not doing that bad this one. I'm not. Yeah. Oh, sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I was trying to think of what to say.
I had to get, I got to come up with my bread and butter.
Holy shit. I have the whole thing screwed up. Okay. Did I win? It's pretty, it's pretty close.
Come on. Get rid of them. Yes. Here comes the finale. Oh my God. Kim Post makes me a
PlayStation 2 controller. What? What do you mean try again? No. What? I can't press start? Hold on.
If I pause the game, that's, that's immediate retry. Oh, and what? Oh, that's not good.
There's no breaks. You actually can't. I guess I understand because it's cheating.
There was like 30 seconds left in this song. Hold on a second. Here we go. It's the PS2 version of
this game, not the controller. The controls are poopy. What's wrong? Why do I have to have help?
All right. I'm going to, this is the one. Here we go. Can you pause real quick? I need to pee.
No, we're going to turn it up. That's what we're going to do. You got pee? Oh, that's too bad.
And you know what? I'm fine. This is, I, I like the song. The song is good. Here we go.
It's all right. Fucked up is going on here. Did this shit get harder because I retried it?
Never been as hard. Going from down to up or left to right is like,
shit didn't happen the last time I did this. Look, look, I'm not doing anything.
I'm not doing, I wasn't doing anything. I was holding it in the same spot. That's just DDR.
I never even played DDR in my entire life. I've never played DDR. I'm serious. Not one time.
DDR was the only exercise I ever got. No, that's what I had Wii Sports for.
Banging on the door? Getting close. All right. Finale. This is it. Pause games. I'm not pausing.
I can't. Come on. It's too, you don't get it. Look at the change. Look at the change. You saw it.
Let's see. I didn't fuck that up. All right. So if I look, look, see what happened. So I'm moving
from like, I'm moving one degree. Sometimes you move one degree and it goes to like four o'clock.
If you start at 12 and you want to move it to one, it will go to like four o'clock sometimes.
I'm telling you. Hold on a second. It's not possible. You can't, you can't,
I can't get a PS2 controller right now. I've exercised those options. Okay. Looks good.
It's Miranda the elder. Quite impressive. Defeating such a powerful gravillian agent.
Gravillian? Oh, we've prayed and waited for this moment.
It's one of Stewie's grand, like, steam costumes.
He just wants to learn how to skateboard.
Everything in life is the consequence of your own acts. Master the waves.
All right. Here we are. Two moons.
It's a hammerhead shark that plays music.
Here we go. It's a weird beat. It's a little bit of a weird beat.
It's hard to keep up with because it's off beats. Not that hard. It was. I'm not going to diminish
the fact that it was very hard. Oh shit. Oh, I gotta pause the game. I gotta pause it.
Oh my God. When can I fight him? Can I do damage? Is that just phase one? That's probably phase one.
You made it. No, that's it. I did it. All right. That was pretty tricky.
The issue was the do-do-do. So it goes do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
And you have to press the do-do-do. It can get tricky. Overwrite it. Save it.
Okay. Is this first playthrough? Yes. I have never played this game before.
Oh, would you look at that? Now he's a giant robot. What do we do, robot?
He transformed it into a deep turntable? All right. That's pretty crazy. That's pretty crazy.
The music for this level sucks. Does it? No. It's a good start.
Damn. I love it. All right. Let's do it. Mech battle. Follow me.
These fucking controls, man. Give me a break. Like, look at that. How am I...
No, there's no way. What the fuck did I do wrong here? No, no, no. Look at... It's not...
Do you see what happens here? No way. Uh-uh. It's not me. Look. It's not me. Look what happens.
Look at this. Oh, why? No, stop. I have to tilt my neck. My god. I don't know if I'm going to be
able to do this. Oh, my god, guys. I can't postmate the controller. Kim already looked.
Sorry. I can still win. Don't push the stick. So, when you see it spaz out, that is probably
one degree change. I can still win.
That might become a real problem later on, though.
What the fuck? I'm not touching anything. I've heard better reggae. Well, it doesn't help that
half of the song is not being played. I'm still going to win. I mean, my defense is just absolutely
impenetrable.
No! No!
I almost paused the game for that one.
I actually did it. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. No!
Anytime there's a change of direction is where it becomes, like, impossible.
Finale incoming.
Okay. No, that's it. That was the finale. Use the d-pad? I don't think you can.
This one's probably going to be a C. I can't guarantee a B for this one. Yes, I can.
Save, please. Save, please. What am I doing wrong?
Save. Previously saved game data exists. Overwrite saved data. Yes. Hold on a second.
Wouldn't the highlighted one be the one that's... Okay.
Huh? What's that? We got it.
It's just Rick and Morty voice acting.
Yeah, that's the demeanor that Justin Roiland does for every character that's
a character that you're not supposed to care about.
Hey, it's me, this character. The one that talks like this. I'm doing this. I'm in the bathtub.
It's me. Bathtub. I'm the bathtub guy.
I didn't know. Okay. I thought I had Jaundice.
Like I said, there's a whole... All right. I'm not going to talk over Cousin.
I just came out for a walk to see the moon, but then I heard that.
Oh, this. Yeah. Somehow I seem to be okay with this thing.
You're good. I tried once, but I could never play like that.
Is there a reason why every like anime young boy character is an old lady straining their voice?
That's... Isn't that strange? It's weird, right? Wait, this is like a... Hold on.
I wrote this song for you. No, hold on. I've been practicing.
Don't get up. Don't get up. Hold on. Oh, no. Sorry. I have to go home now.
That's fucking funny. All right. Let's do it for real.
I wrote this kid's day. Let's see what happens after a few weeks of practice.
Actually, probably like more like eight years of practice. 10,000 hours of practice.
He's going to play Wonderwall. No, he's not.
She looks over like, okay, come on. Come on. You fucked that one up.
Why does she have a life bar? Why am I like killing her? I guess
I kind of would be like in this situation, right? I just gotta listen to this.
All right. He's got half the notes. Okay. Nice job. That's the abrupt changes. I'm trying.
Don't make me laugh. Don't make me laugh, please. It's almost over. I did it. Oh, yeah.
I got another V. That's too generous. No, it's not. It's fine. Just in case everyone's curious,
I have to press the down button on the D-pad. That's not left. It's not right. It's down on the
D-pad. I'm sorry. And it was fucking completely silent too. The singer's voice was honey love.
What? Where's Puma? Puma. Puma. Where'd you go? Why'd you leave me? What am I going to do about
myself? No, not again. That's expensive. I have you now, Gitaru man. Puma, what's happened? Where
could you have gone? I want those shoes. So lonely, Puma. Those things are awesome. We've been together
so long. That's why I said I didn't want to come to this stupid place. What? It's moving.
I probably can get those at a mall kiosk. You know, like the big goofy
sneaker slippers. Welcome to our planet, Gitaru man. Hey, it's you. How does it feel to know
you've been had? Zoe, I'm going to. By the way, your friend has been waiting for you.
Don't say it. I know what they look like. So you dognapped him. It was too easy. You're both
so cute. Gitaru man, without this mutt, you can't fight. You creep, give Puma back to me. Go son
Montreal. This is going to be fun. All right. Is this, how's this one? Anybody know the songs?
Is this one good? All of a sudden it's like, I'd be like, holy shit. It's, it's the bone song.
Holy shit. Bone song. I don't have a guitar. Let's go. This is the best song.
Come on, you're the guitar. Get it. Here we go.
I didn't even see this mobile combat theme. Oh shit. Oh my God.
Thank God somebody has a trumpet behind me.
Holy shit. Hard game boss.
From here to here is an issue.
And then from here to here is an issue.
God damn it. You win.
B. Not a C. Come on. Let's go. I'm going to get it. I have to get a B. Come on. It's all about
defense. That was just doing it on. Why's it not telling me how I did? Gitaru! What the fuck is
going on right now? What? Was that just, that was, that's a replay. Like a replay of the,
like it records the game. What? Replay this game? Like replay the left, like redo it, like do it.
This is like 2000, this is like 1999 or something. It records your game for you.
That would be retry. I don't know. It's a Japanese game, isn't it? Like replay this game.
I don't know. I thought it was like redo it, like do it again. I don't know that the game
records everything you do. And by the way, manga S. Damn it. What the fuck? I just want to retry
the level. Replay this level. You're all so grateful. Grateful to me? Gosh, we have been
freed. But the real battle is just beginning. To save this planet, you must get back all
the Gitarus the enemy has taken. There are just two left. When they're all collected,
a great power will shake the sky. You can't allow Zoe to possess that power.
Gitaruman, go now! Let's do it. We gotta go, you one. We gotta get out of here.
Don't lose now. Okay, here we go. Just two more. That's it? I'm about to beat this fucking game.
Gregorio. That's either the third or that is a scroll. Like a magic scroll. Or it's a
like a sand time thing that you turn upside down. This just sounds pretty good.
Replay it. But these last two might be very hard. Maybe can I turn like sensitivity down? Definitely
not. It's so small. It's such a tiny increase. It's stuck. There's no fucking
way you can do this. Possible, I don't think. I'm trying so hard right now. Got it.
Winning. Here comes the defense. What did you do that? Sorry, I had to do that.
Why did somebody just say omega lol? For what reason? For what reason did you say that?
Oh, I'm gonna win. Oh my god, it's so hard. I'm doing it wrong. I don't know what I'm
doing wrong. It's okay. Come on. Come on. Kill him. Please. I don't want to do it again. Oh no.
No! What? You lose. Mama, I've done it again. It's so hard to control. It's so hard.
This is the analog. Please. I'm telling you. Don't think I'm bad. It's not me. It's not me.
Don't think that I'm not good. It's not me. This isn't me. It's not me.
All right. Focus.
It was the controller. All right. Come on. I didn't do anything.
All right. Let's go. It just ripped to the side. Come on. Good.
All right. Get ready. I fucked it up last time. Bad. Not this time.
What happened there? What was the problem?
I don't get it. Fuck out of here. All right. This is where it gets hard.
All right. He's dead. Come on. I know I can do it.
Mama, I've done it again. That was a lot of screaming.
I was like a bat just came in my room and flew in and went right in my face like a pigeon got in here.
It's like da-da, da-da, da-da. But I said, God damn it, I have to emulate. Somebody told me the emulator
doesn't have this problem. Well, this is the original. We have to deal with how much it sucks.
I'm going to beat him this time. All right. I'm ready. Here we go. Here we go.
I'm not. Here we go. This is it. Here we go. I'm not doing it this time. I've done it twice already.
Imagine I did it. Pretend I did it. Here we go. Fuck. Don't fuck it up. Don't fuck it up.
It's hard, but don't screw it up. I got to have both hands with control here.
Here it is.
Da-da, da-da, da-da, da-da. Please. The finale. Don't screw it up.
I did it. I win. My goodness. You win. And that's not even the last one. There's one more after this.
I missed a lot. It's okay. The final boss is even worse. Shit. No, I don't want to replay this game.
Oh, man. We're going to be here for a while.
I'm impressed. It seems the legends are true, but I've prepared the stage for the ultimate test.
Who's the true ruler of planet Gitaru? It will be decided once and for all here in Gitaru Arena.
No, it ain't just you wait. You're finished. You're the one who's finished,
Gitaru man. This time you will relinquish your Gitaru to me. Greatest Gravillian warrior, enter.
Wait, what? What? What the fuck? What? Lost your nerve? This girl has been
bred since birth to be our mightiest warrior. No. But I played the guitar.
Oh, it's you. You're the Gitaru man. Well, when I listen to you at the tree,
this is going to be real easy. No, I can't do it. Puma. She's the one person that I refuse to fight.
All right. I'm going to get this on first try. Controller sucks. The mechanics suck. The game
sucks. No. I mean, some of that's true, but no, we're not going to say that right now. We're going
to do it. All right. Good. We're doing country versus rock. I don't know which one. Hey, hey.
If I block it, I can't block it. What's he doing to me? Control split. What the? No. Come on.
Oh, I refuse to fight. Right.
No, get up.
No. That thing's not even a guitar. What is that thing?
Oh, getting called out. Wait, that's the song that I played at the tree.
And I sing now. Yeah. Nevermind. I'm just going to play.
My finger's falling off the fucking analog. We're playing it together.
It's my fingers up. My finger. What the fuck are you doing?
The people watching in the stands. This is kind of embarrassing. Oh, boy. I really,
really shouldn't have drank like that full pint of vodka before playing.
It was a mistake. It's a big deal for me right now. Did anybody notice? I got them all. You know
what happens now? You are the true guitar man. You are the true guitar man. What about the bad guy?
All right. Back to B. Good. B tier.
Incredible powers. Powers like what? Awesome powers that only the almighty,
well, anyway, it's the best guitar whoever. Well done, you won. The same clothes, too.
This last guitar was truly meant for you. The clothes? These small? We got them all, you won.
Nobody really did it. I didn't? Me? Maybe I'm not so pathetic after all. Here comes the not so fast.
Pathetic? No, you're not. There is nothing to fear, but here it's so.
Akira, you betrayed me. No, Zoe. I just finally realized that my music is not for fighting.
That's right. Go, Zoe. I hate you. Curse you, guitar man. I'll fight you myself.
My arm and guitar will blast you to smithereens. Eat this. No. You can do what you want. You can,
indeed. Silence. Silence yourself, Zoe. Go home. Go home? No, I won't go home. I'm going to rule
the universe with the last guitar. There's no future in your dreams, Zoe. All your goons are
gone. It's just you. What did you say, punk? You think I can't beat you by myself? You're just a
pathetic loser. You couldn't beat me in all of Neverending Eternity. Why you? Can't you do it?
So tell me, what do you do? I can do it. What, defeat me? I can't. No, not you. Can't you?
You're a loser. Am not. Always made fun of. No way. Always stuck. Never. Always running. No.
Always failing. No. Failing all things. No. Can't do anything. Yes, I can. This is the Venom movie.
I can do it. What can you do? I can do it. What? What can you do? Show me now. Sure, I can.
You miserable scrub. Show me all you've got. I can do it. I can. No, you can't. I can. There's no
way you can. You can't. You can't. Because I can. Because what? Because. Say it. Because what? I
can do it. Because. Because. Because I'm guitarist. Oh, the true power. The light. The light.
Did my voice change? This is going to be fun. What's the song though? That's important. What's
like the final battle song? It's actually Wonderwall. That joke was made a long time ago.
It's a... Today is going to be a day. Okay. I can't do that. I have to restart it.
Fuck. Why? What? What? Come on, quick. I skipped over the radio station a few times.
The bad reception. Yeah. I'm going to win. All right. This is where I'm going to do the damage.
All right. Come on. Look at his health. Like a full health. He ain't got nothing.
Nobody's just at the volume control. Putting it from 10 to zero over and over again.
I think I won. I lost here for a second. The legendary guitarist.
I was choking. I was choking there really hard at the end. But I did it. That's okay. Damn.
That was a lot. 32%. Great. 36% good. This is going to be an A.
Okay. What? Oh, because B is purple. Okay. I get it. It's all right. Whatever.
That song was wild. That was a good one. I did it. Hooray. It doesn't take much to turn impossible
into I'm possible. What? I've taken the leap. It's your turn. This is a bad ending.
Hey, you won. Why don't you give it up? You're starting to get on my nerves.
Here we go. Epilogue song. Come on. Epilogue song. Come on.
Do you know my name?
What does that mean?
You hard bone. I mean, I know there's more.
Do you play the game?
You can't hear me. Somebody said the game's only three hours. Perfect for someone with chronic
intestinal problems. You're right. What the fuck are you talking about? All right. Skip. Skip it.
The game is in. It's not open. And it was great. It's not open. The game must have even refunded
on steam. This is a collector's item. Why would I refund the collector's item?
PS2 steam game. Master's play. Oh no. Theater? What's theater? Oh, it's just the cut scenes.
Master's play. I just want to... There's more. Oh man. What is this? I don't know what that
would even mean. This is too much. I can't do this. I don't understand. This is Master's...
This is hard mode. What does it add? Just more timings? More beats and everything? What do you
think it does? It starts you at like no health. Spinning. Spinning. Spinning. No, it's not. I'm
doing fine. This guy. Is this guy the original? Come on. Come on. That was so close.
Got it. That was easy. No, not really. You win. This would be fun to play high as fuck.
I mean, or not. It could just be... It doesn't matter. It could be normal. We're going to hit
a wall. Probably the next song, I would say. I'm going to watch the cut scene.
All right. This one's going to be tricky. Don't skip lore. We already saw it.
I'm one of these I'm going to do sincerely tired Leon. It's going to be an embarrassment.
See if I can do it. I feel like I've improved a bit.
I'm not. No, I'm not. I did it. I did it. Fine. It fell down.
The PlayStation 2 is hooked up. I have a couple of secret PlayStation 2 games back here. Secret
ones that I have never played on this stream. Or I put in Um Jam and Lammy and we continue the
rhythm games. Probably Um Jam and Lammy requires... I have to switch out the PS2 and the PS1.
I actually do need to take a small break for reasons. I'm going to leave it up to you.
We'll do another couple hours. So let's do that. Let's be right back. I'll put a poll in here.
Either secret PlayStation 2 games, or game, or Um Jam and Lammy. That requires me to switch out
the PS1. Guitar Man is actually pretty fun. I might actually try to do like one or two more
levels in Guitar Man. It's fun. It's hard to control, but it's fun. Okay. Which one? Um Jammer,
Lammy, or secret PS2 game. Guess what? I don't even know what it is.
It could be anything because I don't even fucking know. All right. I'll be right back. I'm going to
be a couple minutes. So go grab a snack if you want to. I'll be right back. The PS2 is backwards
compatible. Are you fucking kidding me? Why would I do that? I almost just unhooked everything.
I forgot. Wow. Okay. All right. I'll be right back though anyways.