Hello. Hi. Hey. Hey. Hello. Hello. Ster. How are you? Welcome back to the stream. We had a stream a couple days ago. Hello. Hi. Would you wait? Hold on. Play that again. Hello. Hello. Why do you still have this shit like fucking four years later? Hello. Uh, cause I had no need to replace it. Why would you still have a recording of me from like four years ago? I, it's one of the most valuable things I own. All right. Can I get an invite please? I got, I got to launch the game.
Okay. So do you want to, uh, do you want to be the one to tell everybody that what, what we did? Because you sounded so paranoid that I'm surprised you would even say anything has been done at all. You don't think that when we open up our menus and show our skill points on stream, people will be like, what the fuck is going on here? You know how you guys, you have the please do not remove this under federal law things on your mattresses. Like we pulled it off. Not only did we, we didn't pull the whole thing off. So there's like still little,
a little bit there. So there's evidence and people can clearly see that we've been hampered with the device.
I'm just saying we're going to have to address it.
You don't open up your menu and see that we have like 20 extra skill points to be like, wait, what? You're in the same zone. You were just in. No one, no one remembers from last time. No one watched from beginning to end, except for my mom.
Is your mom still a big fan? Yeah. She told me all about, she was watching and catching up on the pod and she really, yeah, that's so cool.
All right. You want to invite me?
I'm hold on. I'm going to continue. Okay, chat. This game takes so long to level up. We just love, we just, we ripped the mattress tag off and now we have the cool skill points and we can drop kick zombies. Send me to jail. Send me to jail. Fair enough.
I'm going to change my stream title. Hold on. Cause I'm not doing GeoGuessr anymore. Did you know that GeoGuessr is like an updated thing and now you have to pay for it? You don't have to.
I have never used GeoGuessr.
What?
I have, I don't, I wouldn't know any of this.
You've never played GeoGuessr?
No.
You should. I feel like you'd probably like it. What's a good title? Just literally the next sentence you say will be my title.
Came in pants, still gaming.
It's not going to be that. It's not anything else. Say something normal.
Something normal.
Anything else besides what you just said. Another sentence, please.
Uh, you're putting me on the spot.
Why would you fucking say that?
I mean, like, I,
You were always the title guy when, when, when,
I was the title guy?
You were always like, you had the funniest titles. Your titles were always so funny.
Well, you just denied my first one.
Because your title that you just gave me is like, I feel like I would get in trouble for writing that in my title.
Um, you could just write, no, that's lame.
What was it?
You'd write Sterma, perma, and then like six hearts. Like a bunch of emojis.
Uh, okay. Sterma, perma?
Yeah.
And then hearts?
Don't do like, don't do like the less than threes. Like actually go to Google and copy a heart emoji.
I don't want to do that shit. That's too much work.
Wait, perma means like permanent, right?
Yeah.
Okay. It's not something weird thing that you're like making me, right?
What else would it mean?
I don't know.
I don't know. You, you just, the last thing you just told me to do was say that I like did something into my fucking pants.
And I'm not going to just put whatever the next thing you say with a little bit of scrutiny.
I want it.
I just wanted you to have the greatest clickbait title you could have.
I wanted you to succeed.
All right. Can I get an invite?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay. I guess we cheated. I'm sorry.
We cheated and, and, and I don't want to get in trouble for it.
He, it was his idea. It had nothing to do with me.
I actually fought against it.
Sterma, temp.
Are you in the game yet?
Yeah. I just invited you.
No, you didn't.
Uh, my whole, um, the whole world just saw me invite you.
So.
Oh, okay. I got it.
Should I do the thing again where I just like.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I got it.
Okay.
It's your screen.
I know.
I'm not in the game yet.
Yeah.
The BRB screen is still there because I'm not technically back.
Okay.
I've loaded in.
I am now technically in the game as of right.
I'd say right now.
Have you ever had a naked on stream?
Like dream?
A naked, a naked on stream dream.
Like you had a dream that like, oh my God, I'm naked.
A connection to the game.
Your session is, could not be established.
You have to invite me again.
No, I've never had a, a naked in.
I just have a lot of school dreams.
Like I'm back in school.
I had one last night.
It's always just like, fuck school again.
Really?
How, like, how much school does one person need?
All right.
I'm in, is that you?
Where are you?
You got my box.
Let me get my screen correct here.
Okay.
Should be dying light too.
There it is.
I mean, like I have nothing to hide.
Like if I walked on camera nude.
If you walked on camera nude, then you don't think that you would
like to get in trouble for that.
I think I would get banned for three days, but I think on all the
websites where they like post nude people, like, uh, the drama streamer
stuff, I think that would probably be the best thing that could happen to me.
All right.
So what are we, where are we going?
The last thing we did, we, um, we unlocked like the actual
video game last time, right?
Um, yes, I think maybe.
Yeah.
And we also unlocked all these moves that you guys don't remember.
And we, we, we got like 50,000 points of experience.
Um, if you don't remember the last, uh, mission we completed.
Yeah.
They, they just like, they said, wow, you unlock the new area.
You're also going to need all of these experience points for it.
All right.
Let's go find Barney's place.
We got to go to Barney.
Face cam?
No, I don't, I don't want face cam.
I have a headache.
It wasn't face cam on last time.
I have to, it has to be consistent.
Why, why do you have a headache?
I don't know.
Cause I had a dream.
Every time I have a dream that I remember, I have a headache.
Does that work for you too?
Whoa.
No.
Really?
Is that something?
That's not, that's not at all related to the content of the
dream being you nude on stream.
No, no.
Every time I have a dream that I can remember, I have a migraine for the whole day.
It's been like that since I was like 16, 15.
I don't know why.
Yeah.
I think your, your brain's broke.
I mean, I've had an MRI of my brain like twice and they just say,
Oh, it looks okay.
There's a quest giver here.
Inside?
No, like, like, like this Bush is a quest giver, apparently.
I think they're in the building.
No, we're, we're not doing that.
By the way, we're going to the yellow.
We're going to find Barney's house, whether you like it or not.
Cause Barney's going to show us to the new area and he's going to give us like,
Oh, what was that?
There's a flare.
We're going to the foot.
You see the flare.
Oh my God.
Yes.
Let's go.
Somebody needs help over here.
Help him get them up.
Help him.
All right.
200 experience.
That's pretty good.
Do you understand that for the rest of the whole game, we're not going to be able to
put points in because of the fact that we cheated.
Yeah, I know.
Exp means nothing right now because we're like 20 hours ahead and experience points.
Yeah, but they gatekeep being able to do a power attack.
It's a power attack is the third tier of ability where you just hold down your
mouse button.
I will agree that having that hidden was the flare.
This was the guy shooting it.
It was.
Yeah, you just ruined the dying light to experience.
Well, I mean, that's not necessarily true because this is the last time either one of
us is going to play this game.
I kind of have a knack for ruining games for Jerma.
So, I mean, we've been playing for just about, well, like eight to 10 hours with
including the single player stuff we had to do.
Yeah.
I'm completely happy with getting to this point and we're at like 13, 15 hours of
like gameplay.
I'm all right.
That's okay.
What was the last time you finished a single player game that wasn't a from
a software game?
Finished a game.
So the place should be empty now, but I don't know when they'll be back.
That's a good question.
Literally.
I got to tell you this.
Oh, oh, shit.
I got goop.
I got goop to bad.
Why is my immunity critical?
Because we walked through the group.
You're going to have to mushroom.
What do I do?
That was this one.
Press two and you switch to your things and you got your mushrooms, your power ups
or your users.
I got it, dad.
Okay.
Thank you.
Uh, where's Barney's up in this building up there.
Let's get up there.
They're going to say they do a lot of talking in this game about how nighttime
is super dangerous.
I like, you know, I kind of like this, like do like more than one thing on
stream thing.
That's kind of cool.
I like that.
Have you never done more than one thing before?
I mean, not really.
Maybe like once or twice.
It's like, instead of just one thing for like five to seven hours, it's like two
things for like two to three hours each.
I feel like you would realize that earlier, considering you like, like super
ADD.
Excuse me?
It's not a bad thing.
Hold on.
Excuse me?
I'm unlocked.
Okay.
I'm just going to like, pretend like you didn't say that.
Like, what the fuck?
Okay, dude.
Um, Oh, yeah, you already took this one.
Yeah.
This was the same mission from before when, oh, right.
With the things and the stuff and there was people here.
And where's Barry?
Barry is in here somewhere.
Barry season three over here.
Like you said, Barry, it's just about us being friends.
It's just like you said, I don't think there's anything I need to do about that.
Barry.
It's like you said, how come you're not laughing at that?
I'm doing the guy from Barry.
Um, thank you.
That wasn't Mr.
Satan.
I don't, I don't remember that part.
And I feel like of all the things you don't remember that part from, that is
like the best character in Barry.
Which one?
It's been so long, like four years.
Actually has been a long time.
Yeah.
Search Barney's hideout for evidence.
Everyone's always hiding stuff behind these really heavy planks.
Three voices, Andy.
Oh, there's no evidence.
There's something right here.
Oh, there is something right here.
I wonder what she says.
What's that?
I found the tattoo they cut out of Lucas.
It cut his tattoo off.
Throw up.
We did a little piece of Lucas to remember him.
Just sicko.
That ain't mine yet.
Lucas's you shitter.
Wait, didn't he just swing?
Yeah.
Where are you?
I'm right here.
All right.
Let's both hit him with a charged up swing at the same time.
One, two, three.
Did you even hit him?
We kill.
Wait, did you just stomp his head?
Yeah.
I jumped on his head.
She's next.
We still have level one weapons.
Yeah.
You cut the tattoo from commander Lucas's.
Oh, shit.
It was her.
Okay.
Now we've got to fight him.
I'll kill you.
We need to know.
Where did this piece of skin come from?
Sophie could have been planted to set us up.
Who's planting skin in your head?
I'm going to plant a cut somebody's skin off and plant it in
their drywall.
And when somebody finds it, I don't think it was them.
How do you come in here and demo this house and put that in there
and then hide it with a plywood plank?
I'm going to say, okay, if I came home and I went up into my
bedroom and there was a huge piece of fucking plywood against the
wall, would you know it must always be there?
He's only looking for a reason to raid the bizarre.
Someone you'd be like, why is that there?
Well, we didn't have to fight them.
Lame.
Where did they go?
This is the apocalypse German.
Nobody is demoing omega low, but you wouldn't notice that this was here.
This is something you don't notice because there's a piece of huge
piece of plywood in front of it.
That's what I'm saying.
It must always be that way.
Why are you expecting like they'd live in this luxury home in the
apocalypse, like they don't have holes in their wall?
All right.
What's our quest?
We got to go get this guy a permit.
Very important question for Easter.
Three, two, one.
Do you call them quests or missions?
Go.
Quests.
Loser.
Why am I a loser?
It's a mission.
That's a very important question.
Like this isn't magical fucking 1400 Europe.
Hey, well, I think this game calls them quests.
And based on what you said in the previous session of them being
called community gifts, subs, I think you have to concede to what
the game is describing them as.
I'm having a little bit of trouble here.
Trying to see, uh, do you see the elves anywhere?
Uh, not seeing any elves though.
Okay.
I am definitely seeing some, uh, more to how chivalry style medieval gameplay.
Uh, do we, we don't have a quest.
Fuck.
That was bad.
That was really bad.
That was so bad that it was made up for a joke, but it wasn't.
Wow.
Unbelievable.
I'm going to take that loss.
That's a big problem.
I can't fucking believe that just happened.
That had to be fake.
Hold on.
I'm looking up the missions.
Cancel the throw.
What does it want from me?
It's a massive L.
It really was Jesus.
I have a headache.
All right.
It's like hard to concentrate.
Our quest is wait for Sophie's call.
So we just have to walk around.
Yeah.
I think we just like, let's just go like hop around.
I'm following you.
You're the one that knows where you're going.
I don't know where Sophie's call is.
I think it's a pay phone.
Yeah.
We do have level one weapons because look at how long it takes to hurt anybody.
Yeah, we do.
How do you level up your weapon?
Well, we're still fighting level two enemies.
Like some of my weapons are level two.
Oh my, what happened?
How'd you do that?
Drop kick.
You jump and you mash E or kick.
Kick, kick F.
Oh, holy shit.
That's crazy.
Who needs the weapon when you got a drop kick?
All right.
Let's keep going.
Wait for that call.
Watch out.
There's a boomer over there.
Boomer.
L plus ratio plus headache.
Plus you fell out.
Watch out.
We got Zeds coming.
Uh, I'm going to sneeze and I can't mute because it's too far.
What do I do?
Give me a word to say.
I come in pants.
Nope, I'm not saying that.
What the fuck?
Oh, the chase is on.
I jumped off a zombie's head and went, you go like three stories.
Do you see this?
What?
I'm trying to run a look at this zombie parkour.
Holy shit.
How did you do that?
I don't know.
Oh, I'm my, I'm my immunity is, is, is in critical condition.
We're at chase level one, dude.
No, you.
I'm going for this UV light.
Is that my foot?
It's the only safe place for miles.
They can't get me here.
In the tomatoes.
You think zombies would eat these tomatoes?
Yeah.
See, this is like, this is more what I was talking about.
Instead of having like one tomato vine, you got like 10.
Is he going to?
Yes.
I think they put the UV lights here because the zombies would be taking
potatoes, put the tomatoes.
He said potatoes.
I said wrong.
I'm going to say it.
Can this lady call us?
No.
Oh, wait.
I think we have an actual marker now.
Oh, we do.
Yeah.
We got to go to the place.
He's bringing out these, bringing out the spie voice, but we didn't get a call though.
Is that a problem that we were waiting for a call?
Can you just go to the fucking quest diamond?
Are you going to play Elden Ring?
Uh, yeah.
Are you going to beat Elden Ring?
Like you didn't beat Sekiro?
I mean, I saw the last boss in Sekiro.
That's pretty much beating it.
That's true.
And like, what else is there?
You remember you and me, both of us, desperately co-opping orphan.
And we just couldn't do it.
I do actually.
And we both just gave up.
We did.
We co-opped orphan and gave up.
And I mean, this wasn't, we didn't just try for like 10 minutes.
This was like two plus hours of us just co-opping orphan and not being able to do it.
And I think we both said the same thing that you just said, which was, I mean, like we, we pretty much, we got them down to like 30%.
We saw it.
I mean, we pretty much beat it.
We, we like, we know there's nothing else after them.
Are we on?
We got, I think you're going the wrong way.
What do you mean I'm going the wrong way?
I'm going the right way.
I'm going towards the diamond.
I'm running across the rooftops.
I'm using my injected hyper serum to be able to do incredible jumps.
How do you do that?
Fantastic maneuvers.
I don't know.
We just cheated and I didn't even know what we did.
So like, how do you do that move?
I had it before we cheated where you, you press space to climb over something.
And as you're doing it, you press kick and then you look, look at me, look at me.
Yes.
Look at me behind you.
Look, practice.
Okay.
So is that F?
You, you, you press your jump button to go over the thing and then your kick
button as you're doing it and then you go to space.
Oh, I got a new skill point.
Oh, I bet you cheated for that one too.
All right.
I'm just going to put it in here.
20.
Here we are.
Who am I playing with?
This is stir twitch.tv slash stir.
S T E R.
Twitch.tv slash stir youtube.com slash stir.
What are we going to play borderlands?
What?
I'm going to ask if we were going to play borderlands too.
And I, oh, did they ask you that like a year and a half ago?
And you just replied now.
This thing is insane.
73 damage.
This guy's got level six weapons, probably because we're level probably
because, uh, don't, don't buy these.
Don't buy them.
I already did.
I don't buy it.
Wow.
Well, okay.
Someone's cheating.
I need all the players up here.
Hey, stir, who are you playing with?
Oh, this is German nine eight five.
The guy that used to do a little gem.
This is madness.
Oh, peacekeepers have more.
Yeah, that's me.
They will crush us like worms.
Nobody gets that reference, but the people that do really thought that was
funny because it was remote C four.
Let's go blow someone up.
Okay.
I think they just, they just, I think we just got a mission.
I think we do have a mission.
Yeah.
Remote decoy.
No, I thought there was C four.
I need more scraps because I want to make more molotovs.
Okay.
Well, this guy wants to talk to us.
Is this the guy from the servers?
They're making fun of me.
Oh, okay.
My chat is too.
Very mean.
Okay.
Let's do it.
All right.
I was my new weapon.
This thing here.
Okay.
Go to the water tower for the explosives.
Oh, can I tell you that I was laughing at the Sopranos punch, the propane tank
thing, the rest of the night.
And even, and even until like two, like a day ago, I thought that was
the funniest goddamn thing.
I'm surprised that was, that was the thing.
It was just so perfect.
It was so stupid.
That's the other way.
You started a chase, man.
How do you get to chase level four?
What's that mean?
I mean, do you want to try?
No, I don't.
We just need, okay.
He doesn't actually care.
Probably just intensifies how many zombies are fighting you.
I feel like dying light one.
Here's my review.
I'm, I'm 1000 experience points in.
You are.
Okay.
I am.
I feel like dying one was a better game.
Oh my goodness.
Okay.
Almost every way other than like graphical fidelity.
Now I'm ready.
I'm ready to make that assertion.
Okay.
So the, you think dying light one was a better game.
Is there any specific reason as to why you feel that way?
Um, I feel like I'm not threatened at all by these nighttime chases.
It's actually really fucking bright out the whole nighttime.
The zombies, it feels like there's a lot less of them.
Like before, when you'd throw firecrackers in the street, it was like
the entire street was full of them.
Um, and they felt a little bit more, you know, a little bit more dynamic,
a little bit more cream cheesy, a little bit more, um, a little bit more squishy.
The propane tanks feel like they, they blow up and like, it's a one foot square
in this, just, just, everything's a little bit, a little bit diminished.
This chase level one, like I'm not, don't you remember like hiding in the
dark and being scared of zombies?
I'm muted.
Aren't I?
No, you're not.
No, no, no.
I remember, I remember hiding in the dark, hiding in the dark.
It's always, yeah.
I don't, I think dying light one, where are they?
Like the weird super.
Also, it had guns.
I miss guns.
I'm going to say it.
Where are the guns?
Wait, I don't, were there guns in dying light one?
Yeah.
You would, uh, you would, um, that's why I wanted to get in the police trunks.
Cause sometimes they'd have like handguns in them.
Yeah, we're, I don't remember the being guns.
There were, was a dying light one.
Yes.
I mean, there was also cars in the DLC.
We never, yeah, but that's, I don't think that's a fair, uh, assumption there
because, well, you know, you know what, actually I played dying light like a year
ago, I think, I don't know why, but I returned to it randomly and played it for
like a day and had some mods on it.
And, uh, I wonder overall good game, but like, it feels like, I don't know.
I wonder what's going to, okay.
When do you think we're going to see like innovation in the like video
game, like AAA world is that I feel like we've been in this kind of, kind of
like quest marker over somebody's head.
And like pick stuff up scavenge and craft in the crafting menu.
I feel like we've been playing like the same far cry game for the last like 10 years.
They have been making the same far cry game.
So what would, like, is this going to, do we just keep doing this?
Yeah, why not?
It's not a problem, right?
Like it's until, until like a modern invents auto chess and then every
company tries to make auto chess.
It's kind of weird because like fallout, right?
All that was the, oh, I can pick up plates.
That's kind of interesting.
I can pick up like cigarettes on the ground and plates and stuff.
And then every company decided that that was like not cool anymore.
So instead of picking up like plates, it's like, just pick up like med
pack craftable kit one and med pack craftable kit to scrap metal.
Like, it's not like I can break the plates down and just, it's just, they kind
of like oversimplified it in a way.
Yeah.
Can you look up?
I'll be in touch.
Oh my God.
What perfect right up the butt.
That's how I want to go.
Shoot the plates.
I don't know.
I just, I feel like we, a lot of people have been doing this.
Wait, wait, wait, this is, oh my God, same tuber joke over and over again.
And there's casualties everywhere.
Look at all these YouTubers.
You scared the shit out of me.
I guess if you were like tabbed out and you just hear me go, Oh my God.
Oh my God.
Like somebody's like, I just got like strangled.
So he just like attacked me in my room.
Hey, you remember dying light.
Here's the real comparison.
They even do this in the tutorial where you like walk through the subway and it's
like all in the subway in the dark.
There's like a whole bunch of them.
I remember there being so many zombies.
You like, couldn't move.
If you got off the top of a truck, it was like you were surrounded by six
layers of dudes and now it's like, uh, there's like five, you know, there's a
few guys in here, but is it, okay.
Is it just easier to kind of develop a game like that?
That's just, Hey, there's, we have like these few, these like five or six, like
crafting items to make stuff.
And then there's like all these markers that are in the game for you to go like
get experience points to touch them.
Yeah.
Well, here's the other question, right?
Let's be fair.
Let's be fair to, to be fair.
What else, what, uh, what's the next step, right?
Like, how do you make a video game like this better?
What do you do?
Like, oh, we have this monster zombies and this system and it's like a city
street and there's cars and what, what's the, what's it left to do?
What's in the details.
Do you see that video?
The probe account man always does like comparison videos and did one for left
or dead versus back for blood.
Yeah.
But it's a little things.
So I don't think it's, we need more stuff.
We need just more passion.
I know.
I think I've always said this that after half life one, everyone should have
collectively said, this is so realistic.
These graphics I can see Gordon Freeman and they should have just stopped
improving graphics, but at the same time though, right?
Think about this.
Like golden eye.
Do you really need more than like one square for a person's face?
Let's be realistic.
Not really, I guess.
No, but there's a lot of indie companies and indie devs that are doing exactly
that and they're doing just fine.
Right.
I mean, have you played a lot of the first brain too?
I have not played it a long time ago, but it's still good.
Oh, okay.
Let me, let's be honest.
Let it be, be, be, but give don't negative, negative, negative.
Everything's negative like this stuff here.
I go prevent infection like this, like artwork and like crafting, like a
scene and this like building, right?
The wanted, but this is somebody put a lot of time into this and this is
actually like a very interesting, um, like piece of architecture and stuff.
Like that, that the pieces by themselves are actually really, really interesting.
Yeah.
It's almost like when they all come together and like the game is turned on.
It's like, you have to sacrifice a lot for all of those pieces to look that good.
Yeah.
And you gotta put a little budget in that.
And why does it matter when your game is sold based on how it looks in a
commercial rather than how it plays?
Cause once they're playing it, they already bought it.
But also too, every game does not need to be, I mean, look, it's some, some
piece, some people just kind of want to jump in a game and run around and
collect stuff and kills on pieces.
Is that a problem?
I'm saying for me, dying light, here's the analysis.
Dying light one for me was like a nine out of 10 game.
I really enjoyed it.
Yeah.
It was a little bit flawed, you know, can't give it the 10 and you know,
I'm not going crazy.
It's no bloodborne out here.
This game I'll knock like two points off.
It's a seven.
It's a totally like, yeah, good game.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't know.
We're still fine.
It's tough because, uh, wait, are we supposed to kill these people?
Apparently.
Why am I sliding down here?
Uh, I don't, I, I, I don't know.
It feels like we've been in the same video game since like 2014, 2013.
Okay.
If you were to take a screenshot right now, I wonder if somebody would like do an
experiment like this.
I get rid of the HUD and just take a screenshot and like a ton of games that
have come out that are open world games like this and see if somebody can guess
the game or guess the date.
Yeah.
Depends how generic of a scenery it is with trees and whatnot.
I would actually have a lot of trouble.
Can we get some fucking zone too?
No, this is, this is the podcast.
This is the, the stirring German talking about games.
Well, to talk about the game, I want to like see area too.
Cause the tutorial area where you start in the mountains was like ridiculously
beautiful.
If you're talking about take a screenshot of this and see where it's from.
Like, is this, is this Spider-Man?
Hope I can grab that.
Am I Spider-Man?
Open world games are overdone.
Yeah, but I feel like people are afraid to not to make something that's not open
world because it's not enough and people expect it to be like a GTA five level
map.
You know what you're experiencing is the games that are formulaic are the ones
that are marketed and you see them more often because they are built to be
financial successes.
So they get marketed super hard and the ones that are a little bit more
experimental don't have a budget for that kind of thing.
And they don't know how to market it.
So you're like, Oh, all these games don't exist, but you're just not seeing
them as much.
Interesting take interesting take.
That's a, that's a little bit of my take.
Very interesting take here.
I killed them.
Can we open this door?
They're still there.
And another thing that makes a problem is, I mean, I feel like this is kind of
shitty to say, but I'm gonna say it.
Oh shit.
I feel like a lot of newer games in the last five, 10 years.
What happened?
Whoa, use the medicine, use the medicine.
Why can't I open this?
It's made out of straw.
All right.
How do I throw a grenade?
I'm really mean to say this, but you were going to say what?
Okay.
What I was going to say is I feel like games nowadays don't want you to play
the game for more than five minutes before they start talking to you.
I think, you know what?
Like dark souls nowadays.
Well, no, just like, like, I mean, the last like 10 years, like recently, like,
I think people love dark souls because the game doesn't like talk to you every
fucking five minutes.
Yeah.
New AAA games, the last five, 10 years.
It's like, go do this.
And now let's talk about it for like an hour.
I kind of just want to play the game, right?
Like, it's more play it and like story and like, we've got to have like an
elaborate story of a guy trying to find his daughter.
It's like, do we really need to have all that?
Like, can I just play the game?
No, I feel like this is all stuff I said to you like eight years ago.
And you're like, oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I just want to like skip this.
Don't you?
No, I, okay.
Go watch dying light one.
Right.
There is a part of that game where we are skipping every single cut scene and
going skip, skip, skip, skip.
Yeah.
So I was on board.
I was on board.
Okay.
Well, this is, this is, how did you feel about the new doom?
I didn't, I didn't play it.
I don't think he's references.
Did you get one before that?
I played 2016.
Yeah.
Okay.
So I'm going to start here.
Everyone really liked that game because it starts the game and it makes the joke
of like you talking to the intercom and you're just like, no, I'm doom guy.
Fuck this.
And then you go play the game.
Right.
And everyone's like, Oh dude, it's just like, you know, action.
We like playing this game and it's a really fun game.
And we weren't like bogged down by story.
And like they do have the intercom guy come in, but it doesn't really
interrupt the pace of the game.
Doom eternal starts with a fucking cut scene of characters.
You have no idea who they are and all this weird shit.
And it keeps slowing you down and giving you all these bizarre cut scenes.
And it's like they, they did it right.
And I'm curious what made them go the complete opposite
direction on the next game.
Do game companies do focus groups and stuff and ask people how they feel about
things now, or did that happen now?
Or I wonder if there's like focus groups that are like, you know what?
I really want to know what happened to this guy's daughter.
I, okay.
Imagine, imagine this.
You're in a focus group.
They're asking you like, Oh, what's your opinion on how to improve this?
But you enjoyed the thing, but they're really, really want to know how to improve it.
Do you just make up like, Oh, I mean, I guess I like, don't know his motivation.
I mean, I guess like if there was, you know, like I don't understand why I was there.
And then they get that feedback and they're like, Oh shit, we need to fix that.
Even though you're just like, you only made it up because they
really want it feedback.
I don't know.
Do you read into that?
You do.
Okay.
But actually you started Valley, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Started Valley started Valley had like a story about like your grandfather's farm.
And there was like this corporation that it was okay.
By the way, I just got to cut you off.
This is exactly what I mean about this game.
What did I do that?
I'm seriously jumping and hopping around in circles while these guys, these guys
do not feel threatening at all.
We're just like having a conversation.
I don't know what's going on.
I, we have to collect items from the thing, the box, but there's these big guys.
Are we just like kind of weirdos and talking about how we don't want cut
scenes in our video games anymore?
I mean, calling you weirdos.
Are they question marking you?
No, no.
I think about this is, I don't think this is that unpopular of an opinion.
Okay.
Well they all grew up on like Tik TOK and Twitter.
They're like already on the next video.
They like click next already.
No, they didn't.
They're still there.
Well, I mean, that's a new, that's, they're not, that's a new person that just showed
up, but I hate to kind of sit here and be like, everything is bad and I'm smart
enough to see it, right?
Like, but I kind of feel like I've been playing the same game for 10 years, but
was it like that back in like the eighties and nineties too?
Like, right?
Are we just like in a cycle?
I don't know.
It definitely was.
Can you start opening these boxes so I can, I don't know.
There's like these big guys with these, these hammer.
I don't think we're supposed to fight these guys.
What's this?
We have to click kill at least one of these guys.
And why was that?
Why did that even hit me?
I got everything we needed.
I need to craft some heels bad.
Is this health?
I don't know.
I think so.
Yeah.
I can't people understand the potential of the medium instead of trying
to make interactive movies.
Um, I don't know.
How did you do that?
I probably have like wall running.
You don't.
I think I have that though.
I just ran at the wall.
Oh, we're going to go.
All right.
We're going to go this way.
Okay.
Follow me.
It's because of money, but do these games sell that well?
I don't know.
I guess they kind of do.
They have to sell a certain amount of well, so you can only make a
certain amount of risk.
And if you're putting a certain amount of marketing into it, you can expect
to sell a certain amount of copies.
And it's a very, like, if you deviate from that formula, how much of your
own money are you investing to put into it to be like, well, this weird thing
might work, but I feel like if you did something also keeping in mind that
you're like a dude that doesn't play games and you're the one who's
like bankrolling the company.
Video game boomer podcast residence sleeper.
No, we have to turn our compressors up to a hundred.
You have a go XLR, right?
Yeah, I do.
Can you guys hear me?
Turn your compressor up to a hundred percent.
Oh, we doing this?
Yes, we are.
Okay.
So, I mean, the thing is it's like, you don't sound any different.
I don't sound any different at all.
Maybe a little, maybe a little bit.
You think I don't sound different at all.
Do I?
I think I sound a little bit different.
Yeah.
I don't think I sound different.
Oh my, oh God.
Yeah.
You can turn it up a little bit.
Turn it up.
My like threshold.
Okay.
Just turn, turn compressor to a hundred percent.
I mean, that's the thing though.
I think that as we get older, I mean, you're getting older too.
We're getting to a point where we're getting older.
You, we're starting to see maybe what we don't like in the industry.
I'm not getting old.
Yes, you are.
How am I getting older?
Yeah.
Do you not want to say your age on stream?
How old are you?
31.
Well, that's not super old, but that's still older.
But aren't you like, like 53 now?
Getting there.
I feel like when you say old, it's a very different reality of what I'm living.
But I think that the issue at hand is we grew up in the eighties and nineties
surrounded by these games.
I did not grow up in the eighties.
You, you grew up in the, okay, you grew up in the nineties and get, get a
little closer to the microphone by the way.
I'm not picking up the, uh, okay.
So we grew up in the nineties and honestly, we have a different perspective.
We have a perspective.
That's a lot different than a lot of the younger generation here.
And I think that we need to use all of our perspectives across old and young
to be able to come up with solutions for these problems.
What's the problem?
The problem is these video game companies that might be, oh my God, you
just kicked that lady in the face.
Don't go overboard.
I'm still doing my radio voice.
You kick that lady directly in the face.
And I found it to be something that was a, that was a problem.
And let's talk about why that was a problem.
Yeah.
Innocent people.
You don't, you don't just drop kick in the face.
And I think that that speaks to something about our current world.
And the game incentivizes it through experience gain.
You know, you're correct there.
Let's do, let's, let's, let's deep dive that.
So you got experience for hitting that innocent person, for instance, like
I'm going to get experience for hitting this innocent person.
Oh, these guys, this one gives a quest.
Okay.
Let's deep dive them.
All right.
I'm turning my compressor off.
It really doesn't sound that different.
You're just talking.
Who's this guy?
What?
Who is that guy?
Random NPC.
Now I can laugh because I'm not doing a little funny routine.
You drop kick that lady off the building.
Yeah.
What the fuck?
I skipped a nighttime so we could do the night mission that we just
accepted from these people we just talked to.
And I don't know what it is.
It's 169 meters away.
Whatever it is, you talk, say something.
It's boring stream.
Um, I was doing something dead air, dead air, the podcasters nightmare.
Here, come over here.
Come over here.
Yes, I am here.
What do you want me to do?
Wait, I, can I not do it to these people?
I don't think I can do it to him.
Nevermind trying to break this guy's neck.
No, I wasn't.
That didn't make any sense.
We're on a quest.
I've doesn't have to make sense.
We're in the game.
Just, just throwing some dead air out there until the conversation changed.
Oh, we got flares.
Well, all right.
All right.
Here comes content.
That was well, he got it first aid.
Here, hold on.
I got this guy.
I got, I wonder if you're going to kill him.
I wonder if you can kill him.
I just took something out of his pocket.
It's not falling over.
No, he's not falling over.
That's the thing that's really funny in these open world games.
You make him fall.
Fucking bye.
I'm, I'm bored now.
Come on, do it.
I can't, that guy won't fall over.
He's immune.
No, he's going to fall and we're going to like slap high fives.
Oh, the quest is right here.
He's talking shit to somebody.
He's talking shit to you.
He's like, yeah, what the fuck are you going to do about it?
You want to do a quest?
You interested in this quest down here?
Yep.
Hey, gas can.
Inhibitor container is nearby.
Oh my fucking God.
I didn't grab it.
Oh shit.
We got a goober.
Is that health?
These inhalers.
I don't know which one is healing.
Watch out.
We're getting goobered.
The quest is right here.
We're going to go in.
Oh shit.
It's right there.
You don't need to run.
All right.
Where, where, where, where is it?
Search the ground floor of the dark hollow for Theodore.
Theodore.
He's in here somewhere.
This chemicals in here.
We're going to be quick.
Oh shit.
There's chemis.
It or.
I'll use your game with our vision.
There's some vodka.
You can't use enemies nearby.
What?
Watch out for the chems.
Okay.
You can only be in here for like another minute, by the way.
Well, if you walk right here, you kind of reset.
Are we sure that they're in here?
It says look on the ground floor.
They're going upstairs.
Sounds wrong.
Um, can't use enemies nearby.
What?
Yeah.
The inhibitors in that room.
We have to get rid of the chase.
Oh, we have to get rid of the chase.
Well, chase will go away if we stand in the light.
Will it?
Or are they not going to stop?
Chase ended.
Right.
You're today.
Send it.
I believe it's ended.
Okay.
Be stealthy.
Is the ground floor up or down?
Are you sure?
Go fuck yourself, dude.
Okay.
That's going to be a, that's going to be a, maybe not talk to you for a while.
Closer to kill Monica sent me.
Weren't you talking shit about how like in-game cutscenes annoyed you?
Yeah.
Would you rather have in-game cutscenes or mass effect dialogue choice?
When it, for the, for no reason.
I'd rather, I'd rather have neither.
Who of these have mattered?
I'm a gamer and I love gameplay.
I love true authentic video gameplay.
I love the classics.
I'm talking like Assassin's Creed two.
That was a, someone was like, we're serious?
Wasn't the Assassin's Creed the first one, a couple, weren't they pretty good?
Uh, I hated the first one.
I know that I am.
I'm morally opposed to the first Assassin's Creed game.
I hate, you know,
Hold on.
If you hate story, I'm at the pearly gates and they're like, you got to
like Assassin's Creed one, I'm going to hell.
That's the criteria.
You're at the St.
Peter's is sitting there.
He's wearing, he's wearing like an Ubisoft t-shirt.
Yep.
It would be.
How did you feel about Assassin's Creed one and two?
Okay.
You are saved.
You're so, Jay started.
One was trash.
Run, run, dude.
I'm running.
I'm, they're getting me.
Okay.
You, you want to continue being negative, negative?
No, we're not being negative.
I'm, you want to be like a more negative?
You do this to me.
You want to know what I hate?
You know what I really dislike?
No.
Why not?
All right.
What is it?
Is it video game related?
It's the health bars on enemies.
Health bar that you can turn them off.
Well, no, like specifically like Assassin's Creed, the new Assassin's
Creed Odyssey, where you can stealth assassinate people and kill them in one
shot, but if you accidentally walk to a level 50 zone where they have their big
health bars above their head and you're like, I can't assassinate this guy anymore.
And it's like, the fuck is this game then?
What was the whole like Assassin's Creed?
Like I'm a stealth.
I can't stealth kill him because he's, he's too higher level than the, do you
know who I am?
Why don't you try making a game?
My name is Ezio, Ezio, Edziri Beneficio or something.
Oh no, you try making a game.
It's too hard.
I'm not going to fucking do that.
That's a waste of time.
Just have nerds like this sitting around all day, critiquing it.
Need all players.
I'm cooming.
Upgrade.
I upgraded my health booster and upgrade the immunity booster.
All right.
But anyways, yeah, I think, I think that we're, what'd you do?
Where's your father?
They would do in New York.
Wait, wait, wait.
I have a question before you go forward.
We have skipped every dialogue.
Yes.
Like we, we don't know what's going on.
I mean, we have an idea, but, um, have, I don't know how to put this.
Hasn't each mission kind of still felt like, like the same, like it doesn't
matter what they had said to each mission is kind of like the same.
I mean, by that, you could say that about a lot of things, but yeah.
People saying Mario RPG has dialogue.
Why do you care?
Because Mario RPG was kind of an interesting story.
Mario RPG was interesting.
You can't say that.
You just know, you're not allowed to say that because I'm sorry.
This is, if this game's fun, it is, but like zombie apocalypse, find your daughter.
We've, I've seen this movie a hundred fucking times.
It's not your daughter.
But you know what?
It doesn't matter.
Replace daughter with any other person.
Where's the vaccine though?
That's what I mean.
Like we, I've, I've seen this movie.
Mario RPG is a movie that I haven't seen since.
What about, um, in fact, they deleted half the characters from the fucking universe.
So how dare you compare that to this?
Considering that like Mallow is dead.
They killed him.
How dare you say the shit you're saying.
What I'm pretty sure the last of us two won like best writing ever.
And it's also a zombie game.
Don't be zoomed.
Well, everyone we know is dying.
Let's be, let's be real.
Cause people can critique us on our dumb shitty opinions.
Okay.
What do you think was the last triple a game?
Watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out.
Exploded him.
What was the last triple a major release video game that you played that you said
that was actually a really cool story.
Like I'm, and I'm very invested in this and I'm really, I want to know
what happens.
Um, dude, I'm, I'm, I have such a small brain.
I would need a list of the games I've played.
It's probably God of War, right?
Like, but isn't God of War the same thing?
Like, Oh, where's my boy?
Yes, it is.
Disco Elysium.
Yeah, it's not your play.
You played Disco Elysium?
No, I heard it's good.
You, you're going to keep complaining.
You know, games that don't have good stories.
I'm just going to skip all the ones with good stories.
But it was okay.
God of War was cool though.
It was, it was cool.
I think we just hate zombie games.
I, what are you talking about?
I said this game has been fun.
No, I'm talking about story, story, story, story.
I said story.
Zombies, zombies are like who gives a shit.
Just beat them up, put as many on screen as you possibly can.
And that's why I'm saying dying late one was better because they put more
zombies on my screen and that's all I care about.
What, what, okay, is it, you mentioned the last of us.
Isn't the last of us considered like really, really good gameplay?
Like it's a very good game.
I've never played any of them.
I just assumed that comment would rile someone up.
Not the gameplay is not good.
Oh, the last of us is only well-regarded for the story.
All I know is that occasionally people complain that there's like women in
the last of us or some shit.
Was Bioshock Infinite really good?
I like feel like enough time's gone by.
I liked that game.
Does that make me like a weird, like normie or something?
Wait, that Bioshock Infinite was what?
I bought Bioshock Infinite was good.
Like it was an interesting concept.
Like the Bioshock series might be the last time that I was like, holy shit,
that was fucking actually phenomenal.
Like the story.
I was shocked one, like Bioshock Infinite.
I feel like it was like phenomenal.
That's exactly what I'm afraid of.
Flare, save that guy.
Save that guy.
Oh fuck, save me instead.
What about Red Dead?
Red Dead was, okay.
Yep.
Red Dead Redemption 2 was, I liked what they did in Red Dead 2.
This is what I mean.
When we can sit here and be reminded of games, it's easy to forget how many good
things there are and you just sit around and like, just, I don't even remember.
And then someone will go, what about this game?
You go, oh yeah.
And what about this?
Oh yeah.
What about this?
Yeah, that was good too.
Just laser focused on like the one zombie apocalypse genre and forgetting every
other phenomenal game that's come out.
Yeah.
Every game is a zombie game and I don't like it.
I fucking swear to God, you have to save me.
I'm just jumping around and dying.
Negativity for the sake of negativity.
Well, I don't know, but I, this game's not bad.
It's like, it's, this is fun.
You to be in a discord call with somebody that's like one of your, I mean, a friend
of yours, I wouldn't call them a good friend.
I'd call them like a pretty decent friend.
Like, you know, like an acquaintance level up.
Like I would say, like then you could like a hang out with that person.
Hang out, kill some zombies, just talk and hang out.
It's just a fun time.
Like this is that, is there's nothing wrong with that.
We're just hopping around.
I'm the markers over here.
Oh, you just, this is your coworker.
And he said, just fucking go outside, dude.
That's what I'm saying.
Video games.
Have you guys tried in real life sports games?
No, but forget about zombies.
I played Far Cry four, Far Cry five, Far Cry six, whatever.
I feel like I'm in that game right now.
I feel like I'm in the game now and there's no cars.
There's doors right here.
You are in the game right now.
You're dying like one that was like it was a good game and then Ubisoft
in between dying like one and two released about 50 of the same game.
And they're like, wow, that model is successful.
Let's do that.
And then they did it.
Oh, of course, I'm sure.
I don't know something.
All right, we have to move on because I think we've been talking about
like the video game podcast routine.
Dying light zombie games are boring since like an hour and 12 minutes ago.
Yes. Like, ask me a stupid question about McDonald's.
All right. All right. All right.
So, dude, what's your order at Wendy's, would you say?
I think mine is chicken nuggets and Asiago ranch.
Asiago cheese.
You have unused inhibitors.
I do. Oh, shit, I do.
Oh, I got something for you.
Why is Asiago cheese only ever sprinkled on baked bread?
How come it's never on anything else?
It's only like, oh, and by the way, the bread, it's got Asiago cheese
baked on top of it.
Well, I want to eat it normally.
Why the fuck do they always do that?
I'm not a cheese expert.
I I don't know.
It tastes so good.
Why is it only like the little little like bacon bits
that are sprinkled on the edge of like a pizza crust?
My chat says it is. He's narrow minded.
Oh, OK.
Oops. I got to plant the bombs over here.
That's actually kind of cool looking.
This is like once the last time you really sat down and had a triple A sandwich
that didn't just put Asiago on it.
Yeah, like these double A sandwich developers,
they I think they're doing a much better job.
Yeah. Every time I've had an indie sandwich and come away
with like a really unique experience, I've always remembered it more
and always wanted more.
I mean, like the triple A sandwich devs putting like a slice of avocado
on everything, I mean, like I'm kind of getting sick of that.
The avocado shit.
And these guys are level six.
Are they? Oh, no.
He almost one shot me.
I swear to God, I wouldn't be surprised if like a meatball sub had avocado.
It's always like an extra dollar.
Yep, we have avocado as an extra dollar 50.
Oh, what does this do?
He's not even being ironic anymore.
And he's a triple A sandwich devs.
I love. Oh, my God.
You guys are kicking our ass.
We're going to use the environment to our advantage, bro.
There's all this swamp water they conveniently live by.
I love avocado.
Avocado is delicious.
I just I just don't want it on like number one through four
out of the 10 things on the menu.
We got to blow this up.
Do you want to do it? Help me.
I wonder if these guys drop anything sick.
Yeah, I bet their loot tables are insane.
You missed.
I didn't. He just took it
like that game with a great story.
Boy, take it.
Whoa.
Avocados, avocado and everything.
God, can you imagine put like millennials avocado?
Thanks for the points. I got Internet points.
I like avocados. So do I.
They're delicious. They have a ton of good fats.
They're really good for you.
And like, sure, put it on a bunch of stuff because you get if you put
avocado like smear on like a ham sandwich
and like the motherfucker doesn't even know it's on there.
That's just healthy. And they're going to feel better.
They gave up vitamins.
Why am I complaining about this? Who cares?
They go bad kind of quickly, though.
But I think that just might be their
replying to obsolescence now.
What's your favorite condiment on a sandwich?
It'd be pretty much anything.
Like when I say condiment, what's your favorite addition to a sandwich?
We talk like we're talking.
What kind of sandwich?
Just in general, like like a cold cut.
Hmm. Hmm. Hmm.
You lost me like 6000 viewers, by the way.
Thanks a lot. Did I?
Yeah, because I didn't instantly answer your fucking stupid
question sandwich question.
No, you started talking like video game politics.
And you started that whole conversation.
I was like, I'm surprised.
Germa's going here. Germa's usually not this negative.
This is usually me. This is why I have no viewers.
And then you just kept going.
But honestly, God, what do you minds?
Well, I want to hear yours first.
Um, I don't know what it is.
I don't know what the full combo is.
But as a as a a young lad who grew up in New Jersey,
I got to say Jersey Mike's the like
there's some like classic Jersey put this on a cold sub.
That is like, yeah, that's Jersey.
I'm going to go down the shore and say weird things to other people at the shore.
Oh, are you talking about oregano Mike's?
Yeah, oregano Mike's oregano Mike's.
OK, well, it's not it's not like any one thing.
It's like there's this salt and vinegar and oregano Mike's and and something else.
Last few times I ordered Jersey Mike's.
It was like an oregano sandwich.
So you like oregano?
I mean, oregano is pretty good.
You didn't say a condiment.
You just said, I like Jersey Mike's.
No, it's the thing that because that's what people would understand now.
Growing up in New Jersey, there was this place I lived.
It was called Big Wally's.
It was a local local.
All right. You know, you know, for local business.
And they put like the same shit on it.
So apparently it's like a New Jersey thing.
And I didn't know until like they called their place Jersey Mike's.
I was like, you know what? I did have these back in Jersey.
OK, but where it all began.
What's on it?
It's like salt and vinegar.
And what the fuck is this?
What is the mixture?
I don't know. That was my question.
My question was, what do you like on a sandwich?
And you said, I like this sandwich place.
No, I'm not saying I like this sandwich place.
I'm saying Jersey Mike's.
They typically put that mixture of Jersey things on their Jersey sandwiches.
OK, but I never really knew exactly what it was.
OK, hold on. He's got me going to the menu.
I literally typed German into my like food delivery menu.
No, you don't want to order the German.
Trust me, you'll puke.
It's like it's like four tablespoons of mayonnaise, turkey, lettuce
and like a bunch of honey mustard.
You'd probably throw up if you ate it.
Olive oil blend, red wine, vinegar, oregano salt.
I think that's like the classic.
We're going to drench this shit in some sort of like sewage water.
But it's going to taste good.
I'm a big fan of mayo on turkey sandwiches.
And now, obviously, when I said three tablespoons, that was a joke.
OK. Oh, I changed my answer.
You did. Yeah, I changed it.
Lettuce, mayo, turkey and cheddar is like
it's probably my all time favorite, just cold cut sandwich.
Turkey and mayo is in general just like a like a Thanksgiving sandwich to turkey
cranberry, like stuffing thick cut turkey.
Oh, my God.
Turkey mayonnaise is unfucking believable.
It's the best combination.
Some Chipotle aioli.
Sure. I think the whole thing blew up Chipotle.
What? Chipotle aioli.
I don't know. I thought you said Chipotle bologna.
And I was like, wait, that's actually kind of sounds kind of good.
Wait, am I wrong? Am I?
Is my is my brain melting?
I haven't I haven't been talking to German for too long.
Why? What happened?
Is that what it's called?
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm lost. We have to.
I think I think you got to talk to him.
I just I did.
I did you and I did the mission and then I climbed on the roof.
People hate Mayo because they're just like, oh, it's oh, you like Mayo.
It's all gross.
You know that Mayo is like a thick, creamy white substance.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Please kind of bland.
That's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying aioli out here.
That's just aioli.
Do you know what? Yeah, I was going to say aioli is mayonnaise.
Yeah, but it's like flavored with something.
It's like mayonnaise is the water.
The creamy, gross water of sandwiches.
No, but it Mayo pulls out a lot of flavors.
That's why it's in a ton of aiolis.
It's why it's the base of a ton of shit.
Yeah, but it's it's a base.
It's not like with Mayo and turkey and cranberry sauce mixed together.
It makes an incredible combination.
OK, but is it the cranberry sauce or the Mayo that you're
like really wooed by here?
It's both combined.
I like cranberry sauce, but if it's like a cranberry Mayo,
it's just it's 10 times better.
Oh, we're being timed.
Yes, we are.
Oh, this thing.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Was I not supposed to do that?
On my screen, you're holding onto nothing.
You're just floating.
How long am I supposed to hold this for?
A while.
Oh, I'm I'm going to run out of here.
I'm going to run out of grip.
Hold on. Oh, oh, what?
Oh, shit.
You just went by the right side.
You were right in my peripheral.
Are you OK?
Did you make it? Oh, God.
I went to go get you and it just it took me up again.
I'm sure I can do this in 30 seconds.
How come I this is going to explode?
I don't know.
Why won't anyone tell us what's going on?
How come I can't just force kill?
Oh, no, Tony Soprano is about to walk over here with a propane tank.
He's going to be setting up his grill and see, he's going to be pissed
that it doesn't work and he's going to punch it.
You know, shows over. OK.
This is important, dude.
Two minutes and 30 seconds.
Your street cred on the line.
You're a parkour master.
And we said Sopranos reference.
You may have missed the last stream.
Yeah, that's all we talk about now.
We're huge Sopranos fans.
We love Jersey Mike because it's from Jersey.
We love everything about just sandwiches and like TV show references.
It's the only thing.
Yeah. What the fuck is what do you go from here?
I think you need to jump to the other.
Yeah, there you go. OK.
They do it here for long. This is really thin from here.
I don't know.
Yeah. Wait, we have to wait for this to OK.
I got it. Oh, fuck.
OK. Now from here, it's this way.
Oh, wait.
You fall, you fell, didn't you?
You did. I'm going to make it up.
It's up to you. I'll do it.
Thank God I made it.
Do you need me to be there to plant it?
No. OK. OK.
I was going to say that would be bad.
Yeah, this is why I play games with you.
You're so good at them.
That's what I did. But you died down here.
I didn't die. I landed in the water.
You know what I mean? That was like three hundred
and forty five thousand dollars to do that.
Yeah. Why did we have only two minutes to blow it up?
Was the C4 already timed?
Who maybe like what did this guy have to say?
Why did you skip?
That costs probably so much to have money to do that.
Oh, my God, dude.
Is my phone Uber eats on my phone.
Jersey Mike subs on your mind.
You're one tap away.
Shut the fuck up.
Well, didn't they know I'm here?
Weren't you typing it into that app?
I was. So now they're trying to get me.
I totally like my brain forgot that I was already doing it.
And I thought that they tapped into my
because I'm I'm already under surveillance for that other thing.
But this is this is not like, oh, no.
The iPhone's listening to me.
This is you typed in Jersey Mike's into that app.
Yeah. They're recommending it.
Yes. But now it's targeted ads.
And we don't like those because we don't want anything to be advertised.
I don't want people listening to me.
I do. That's why I'm streaming.
You did. I don't know if you saw that one time
I was browsing YouTube and I got an ad for this place
and it was just popped up a banner ad.
It's like, I don't know, five or six videos in.
And this thing said, oh, luxury apartments starting at twenty one thousand dollars.
And that I think that was a month.
I was sitting there just freaking out
because everybody was saying that was a targeted ad.
But that would be fucking crazy.
You're not you're not paying twenty one thousand dollars a month for your apartment.
Oh, wait, what do we do?
Do we lie to Alberto and not show up on time?
Yeah, let's get to the center.
OK, I'll show you the way.
I don't remember what I said to him, so it's like I never did.
Twenty thousand dollars a month in like a home cost is what is that a year?
But to was it to turn like fifty thousand dollars a year?
A lot of a lot of money.
That's like buying a house every year.
What the fuck, man?
I'm done matter.
You help me. That's buying a house.
That's almost buying a house every single year of your life.
But such a great neighborhood.
I accidentally did cocaine.
I just imagine you put a line on your desk
and you like sneeze and you smash your head as hard as you can onto the desk
and like hurt your head and.
Oh, fuck, I didn't mean to do that.
No, no, I feel weird.
Yep. Yep.
Yeah, it's not dead air.
Oh, come on dead.
It's not dead air. It's been five seconds.
You can't just talk for an infinite amount of time forever.
We need time for our brains to think about something like it.
We can't just speak forever, constantly like we need ten seconds sometimes
to be like, OK, this is the next sentence I'm going to say.
I think I'm going to say that now stalling.
I actually might be stupid.
It's starting to become clear.
No, I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine.
Why can I not grab this? But you can.
Oh, what?
On my screen, you jumped and grab that.
I did grab something.
I'm buying some medicine. 72 damage.
It's insane. Yeah, I need some medicine from this guy.
He's selling some drugs.
I want this helmet and I want these gloves to also booster.
You're going to want that muscle booster.
Unity, endurance.
I want health.
This guy, honey.
I haven't crafted anything since the tutorial.
What kind of a customer feels like kind of kind of be feeling like
this is totally my face when oh, yeah, I can craft 13 medicines.
And you've been saying you've been saying the whole time
how much you don't have health or healing.
You know, you have been saying that.
Yeah, it's been a problem.
Well, just get on it.
How are streamers simultaneously supposed to be the ones who talk
to people endlessly without good air, but also are always in their chair
so they never leave and have life experience?
Are you running out of stuff to talk about?
Like, have we ran out of stuff to talk about?
I mean, it's been a long time since we've started.
I mean, you like the last episode of Game of Thrones.
Why are you giving me all your health packs?
You were hurt.
Yeah, but I've helped.
I'm a support.
Oh, OK.
What's this one do for damage?
I think 73 now.
That's way better.
All right, so now we have to go this way.
Hey, what's up with the Olympics?
I don't I didn't even know they were on.
Exactly.
They're doing the Olympics right now.
And then I brought that up and Ashley's mom was like, you're crazy
because they had the Olympics during the summer.
Yeah.
The winner and the but they're doing the Winter Olympics now.
But usually they're doing they usually there's a two year gap, right?
I'm not crazy.
It's been two years since the Summer Olympics.
No, it hasn't, because I remember watching the Summer Olympics
while I was at a gamer's house and that was in August ish.
That was in July.
Oh, no, no. Yeah, that's because of covid.
They delayed it because of that.
You don't know what covid-19 is.
Yes, you do.
Stop it.
Stop faking for content because we have no more life experience to talk about.
What is that?
All right.
I want to grab this and go down.
And if we stop doing like a weird Looney Tunes,
a coyote way to grab this.
So wait, because because of covid, they're doing more Olympics.
The Olympics and usually delayed.
Yeah.
So they did it.
So now they're just they're doing the winter one on schedule.
I don't know. I have no idea.
I'm not I don't know anything about the Olympics.
OK, you didn't tell them to like wait a year and be like, hey,
how about we just like chill for a bit?
I think that's what happened.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's what happened.
But then how are there two Olympics in one year?
Because they delayed the summer Olympics a year because of covid.
So then they did the summer Olympics and then they were already
scheduled to do the winter Olympics.
So they're doing winter Olympics on time.
Isn't there a bigger gap than that usually?
You're throwing for content.
I'm serious.
I thought there's at least a two year gap minimum between summer and winter,
but they cycle it.
See, this is why we don't want to have conversations.
This I this is what I'm not bringing up.
This is what I'm saving everyone from.
They push the summer back.
Yeah. Well, this is kind of crazy.
But the dates, they don't they still don't add up to me.
I mean, there was a delay and that's it.
Hey, you got to run, run, run, run.
He's coming. He's coming. He's coming.
He's going to do something. Run, run.
He's here. I tried to warn you.
I have never been able to do like the slide under this.
Oh, there. Oh, you got to hold it.
Will you hold C? Yeah.
You one of those are you one of those like useless people who binds
crouch to see because it starts with crouching?
What does that mean?
It's like drinking a Gatorade.
You're just ready for a fight.
A couple of zeds.
Should we check like some of these buildings or materials?
Do you need materials?
Why is there a waypoint?
Did you put a waypoint there?
I might have by accident a long time ago.
I want to get to the new zone.
It's not going to happen.
This has to be soon.
We just blew this zone up.
Can we please go to the objective?
We cheated and put a bunch of XP points in and we're not going to get there.
We got soldiers.
Break his neck, break his neck, break his neck, break his neck.
This is what I'm talking about with the health bars, where you throw molotovs
on people and they act like these are near them.
So stupid.
That should not.
Oh, it should not kill somebody.
Getting hit in the head by an axe doesn't kill you.
But getting drop kicked WWE style does.
Yeah.
Do you not respect wrestlers?
Do you think they're not putting their lives on the line every time a drop
kick comes out?
Triple H. You know what I'm saying?
Random mission here.
No, we're going to the main quest.
I don't want to hear anything from you.
You so badly want to get us to the other island, but I don't think it's going to happen, man.
I don't think so.
How are we not right there when this island just got blown up?
All the loose ends are dealt with.
Every person has betrayed us.
We've killed everyone.
I need a player here.
Oh, I'm right there.
Hack on betrayed us.
You'll find it here.
Let's go.
See, we're going.
We still have some coffee left.
That's kind of Pog.
That's kind of Pog, dude.
I was just about to say this guy's going to die in this scene.
I should have said it. What a stupid idiot.
I was going to say it.
I promise I was.
Calm down. Let me see.
Everyone's dead.
Now we can go to the next area.
Show me. I can't believe I didn't say it.
It would have been perfect.
I'm dying my arms.
You say you killed Lucas.
If not for those brass knuckles, it would only be a few seconds to do the job.
I thought it was a better fighter.
I think so.
No point denying it with this one.
I'm born.
Well, wait, don't skip.
Let him talk.
Oh, you don't get it, kid.
You like watching people in pain?
This is the first cut, you know, like
grab your attention.
Is it because he kind of looks like me a little bit?
Does he have black hair?
He kind of does kind of look like you.
He does have black hair.
So he's like he does look like me.
He's got like scars all across his face and he's like 40 years old.
Kind of looks like me.
This guy was double crossing us.
Yeah.
We have to make a choice.
Leave him to die or help him.
He did betray us.
He did. He did.
But he did give us our wristwatch.
And he put us through that long fucking tutorial.
He did make us do a tutorial.
You're right. He is the reason why the tutorial happened.
But if it wouldn't, if it wasn't going to be Hakan, it would have been somebody else.
I'm going to let him die.
I'm going to help him.
I heard an impasse here.
I should leave you to die for what you did.
Why wouldn't you?
I'm going to find that sniper first.
Well, now he's guaranteed to die because.
Yeah, yeah, really.
You do that for me after that.
We're fucking done.
And I was bad.
Didn't hit any major organs.
So I think it's OK.
Yeah. You have to push the arrow in.
No, you don't.
Everybody pretends to know what to do in that scenario.
I don't think anybody really does.
You you you force some like acid on it, right, to just dissolve the thing.
Are we going down the tube?
Yeah, we'd actually get to go down.
Let me see.
I want to how are you going to put this tube here?
And I can't go down this way.
You can't go down the tube.
Yes. Oh, you can. Why?
What? Nice.
Watch out for the chemical waste.
I got eyes, Hakan.
They're shooting us with a sniper rifle, bow and arrow.
All right. Yeah.
Did the arrow stick out of you?
No. Oh, I was going to say, let's sit here and just heal and get like a thousand arrows in us.
You take that guy over here.
How? No, we don't have we don't have range weapons or guns.
I just threw an explosive coin.
Aiden, you all right?
Got him with the grenade.
Did you? I think so.
What the? Wait, this is not how shoots and ladders works.
Hold on. I see him, Aiden.
Sticking to the roof. How do I get up there?
He's running.
Uh, it's going to hurt me.
Make sure you use your healing kit.
I mean, I have mushrooms.
One second until I'm dead.
OK. Remember, the floor is lava, dude.
That makes sense.
Now we got to go. Oh, we got to get up this way.
We do. We're not going to let this guy get away with shooting Hakan,
the guy who betrayed us that we're going to save.
This is I mean, who makes it like this?
Like, why don't you make an elevator?
They took the time to, like, outline it in yellow and all that.
Hold on. I'm picking flowers.
I mean, this is really important, but.
Actually, kind of is because we need help.
I don't see. I don't.
What? Don't question it.
You even need to grab onto that.
Yeah, you do. Maybe. Yeah, maybe.
All right, let's go get that sniper.
Why wouldn't you just shoot us while we're climbing up
when we're really vulnerable?
Because he's using a bow and arrow to snipe people.
Oh, it's very challenging.
And he doesn't know we're here because we've been very stealthy.
Oh, shit. Now we.
Every character in this game has betrayed us.
Literally, every NPC introduced is our enemy.
Everybody's an enemy.
Oh, you got to pick your friends better.
OK, now she gets a choice.
Leave him or help him.
And then she decides to help us and she pulls the arrow out.
It's in the ground. What?
It went through the wall.
She's going to smash into the wall.
Can you imagine if she just went wily coyote style
directly into the side of the building?
Why don't they do that shit?
Do that. Have her just mess up and smash into the wall and explode into blood.
That would be like kind of funny.
I feel like they'd be like, holy shit, that's crazy what just happened.
I'm chasing after her.
I'm going to get her. Borderlands.
Yeah. And then after and then after it happens, you hear
that there ain't no rest for the wicked.
Money don't grow on trees.
I got bills to pay. I got to do it.
There ain't nothing in this life for free.
And then that guy goes,
oh, stranger,
the guy who was supposed to get me there.
You don't think that I was going to leave you on the side of the road.
Don't hit me. I jumped on the building.
I'm dead.
How are you dead?
The fucking immunity stuff down here.
Oh, fuck. It's two seconds.
You might be able to.
Oh, no.
And you're telling me this just now.
Sorry. Oh, but most of all, I have to.
What the fuck? I'm immune.
All this sludge on the floor, dude.
We need to get out of here.
This sludge won't let us.
Oh, we're going to the next area.
We're doing it.
Oh, oh, oh.
Here, watch this jump.
Watch this jump.
360.
What am I watching?
You're watching two, two bros playing a game together,
having a good time and messing around.
We talk about all kinds of things here.
We talk about the state of the industry.
We talk about the state of gaming.
We talk about all kinds of fun stuff.
We talk about McDonald's orders.
So what's your McDonald's order?
Double cheeseburger, two of them.
Ten piece nugget.
You think you really need to?
Are we actually going to the new area?
Yeah.
What just?
I swear to God, if that hurt me, I'd be mad.
Do we have to get up this bridge?
I don't know.
Looking at my map, we may have to get up to.
Yeah, we may have to be getting up to the top of this bridge somehow.
I see. I see where to go.
You got to use your wits a little bit when you're doing some hardcore parkour.
Yeah, I order French fries.
That's part of the nugget meal.
You get a 10 piece nugget meal and then two double cheeseburgers.
It's pretty much it.
What's your opinion on fries that are not sweet potato fries?
I think sweet potato fries are disgusting.
Oh, that's.
Well, let me because every place does them
and they're always like mushy and like kind of weird and gross.
Are you and their normal fries aren't mushy from that same place?
No, they are.
But I would rather have mushy regular fries than mushy sweet potato fries.
Sweet potato fries need to be good or I don't want them.
But like normal fries are so bad that you're just used to them being a little gross.
Well, because normal fries are an applicator for some type of condiment,
whether that's ketchup or like a mushy normal fry, you can do ketchup.
You can do like mustard, mayo, cheese.
It doesn't matter what it is.
Sweet potato fries, I don't that doesn't taste right with like
honey mustard or like ketchup or I don't like it.
It just tastes kind of different.
So you're faulting you there.
Sweet potato fries for being delicious on their own without any added.
Yeah, but that's the problem is they have to be really good for me to want to eat
them on their own because I don't dip like sweet potato fries and ketchup mushy
regular shitty fries taste good because you put them into like ketchup or mustard
or whatever, anything.
I like sweet potato fries if they're good on their own.
I don't want to talk about this anymore.
I'm getting too upset.
The G.R.E.
tunnel is like a dangerous thing, like in the tunnels.
All the zombies are in the tunnels.
This is like real dangerous.
It's level six.
Not anymore.
Talking about sweet potato fries.
No, they're good.
I mean, I like sweet potatoes, but they have to be good on their own.
All right. I don't really want.
Yeah. Yeah.
You don't like sweet potato fries because bad sweet potato fries are bad
and can't be fixed with ketchup or mustard.
They can't be fixed.
Yes.
Why don't you just get good sweet potato fries?
I don't know. How am I supposed to know that if I've never eaten there before?
What's the last meal you cooked?
Oh, tough guy.
Oh, look, tough guy.
Orange chicken, an orange chicken with a vegetable stir fry.
Tough guy.
OK, so like, why don't you just like make your own sweet potato fries?
Because they kind of make your own fries is already kind of hard to do anyways.
You need to like cut them into like the potato strips and then fry them up.
And I know that's kind of kind of an elaborate ordeal.
Or you can like put them in the. Oh, yeah.
But I don't know.
It seems like a lot of work to generate around here.
You have to hit the potato with a tennis racket.
It sounds like a Wii game.
I just I just boil boil sweet potatoes because they're delicious and amazing
by themselves and they don't need to be fried and they don't need an excess condiment.
So you just hold on a minute.
Hold on a minute.
You just recently, over the last couple of years, turned into like a healthy guy.
Dude, wait a minute.
No, don't start this.
You're a vegan potato fries and you're like healthy.
You're going to like the gym.
You're like working out and shit.
Uh-huh. OK, I get it.
Do you? Yeah, like all of a sudden, like sweet potato fries, man, they're like killer.
I don't think in the 10 years that we've known each other,
I don't think I've ever heard you say, do you?
Oh, man, sweet potato fries.
Mm hmm. This is new.
How many meals have we had together?
At least like 30.
We wouldn't normally talk about food for like six hours like this.
All right. Honest to God, like we have been talking about food or like video game
zombies for a long time.
It's time to change subject.
Apparently, this is just like what gets you going.
Because you know what the big tip off was to me was when was the last time you cooked?
That's how I knew this was a tip off.
Well, this was like, OK, stir is cooking and healthy meals.
And no, you're talking about sweet potato fries being bad,
because when they're delivered, they're all soggy and you don't know if they're good or not.
I didn't say to order.
The only way they're going to be soggy is the delivery package.
No. Oh, he fucked it up.
I'll get it first try.
Excuse me, sir.
But an emotional state right now.
OK, well, here we go.
Are you ready?
What was the last meal that you cooked at home?
Tell me.
Really?
It was. What else was on it?
I know I had eggs this morning.
Eggs. Nice, healthy eggs.
Wait, do you eat the yolk?
Yeah, I just I put like a bunch of eggs in the pan with green peppers and cheese.
And I was going to say, like some slices of ham.
If you were removing the yolks and having egg whites and sweet potato, like I would,
you would automatically I would win.
Well, how do you win?
How is like me being healthy, you winning?
No, because like if you're taking the yolks out, that's what I was looking for.
But you're not doing that. OK.
Yeah, Ashley, my wife, she eats egg whites.
Got a problem?
No, I don't. I've got a problem with you.
Why?
Yolk is the best part.
Yolk is where all the vitamins are.
That don't eat the egg yolk is like propaganda.
But how does how do you win this conversation?
Because eating it because that's a really super healthy, like no cholesterol
and like super like, you know, superfoods and yes.
But like how is anyone winning this discussion?
Because I'm a gamer and all things are, you know, got to be tied back to gaming.
Whenever I get in a weird mood whenever you're around.
I have too much fun when you are in a call.
So we better just like not play anything together for like another year.
Yeah.
But honest to God, though, egg yolks.
Look, this is obviously if you're trying to do low cholesterol, then egg yolks.
But don't eggs have good cholesterol?
Not the bad, bad one.
Be a little bit of that. What, LD?
OK. Hold on. They're doing this fucking Ginyu Force pose.
They're all mad at me. They're betraying us.
We did missions for them, and now they want to betray us.
So I'm so sick of hearing, oh, like cholesterol is bad for you,
but eggs are the good cholesterol.
And there's a whole bunch of things like I think it's all propaganda
where if you talk about coconuts and you look online like, are coconuts good for you?
Oh, it has a lot of fat, but it's like the good fat.
Like, when when does the cholesterol from the eggs become good?
The unsaturated fat is not.
It's like a building block for everything in your whole life.
Like like fat isn't inherently bad.
No, it's not saying like when I get my blood tested,
my doctors are like, oh, you're looking good, but your cholesterol is a little bit high.
And I'm like, OK, so like, is that eggs?
Is that the good cholesterol?
Is that the bad cholesterol? Is too much cholesterol in general a bad?
Am I going to die soon? It's they combine it, right?
It's a combined. So here's the thing.
A cholesterol is you have to understand something about cholesterol.
If your cholesterol is over, I believe, 200, which is the it's combined
with your HDL and LDL, right?
Your HDMI, your HDMI is too high.
That like HTML cholesterol comes from like battered fish,
like beer, battered French fries and and like full fat, saturated fat meats and stuff.
So good fat and like good cholesterol.
We're getting residents sleeper again.
Just to give me this is your fault.
Chat, whoever who is whoever is residents sleeper in Germany right now.
You guys are about to go eat some bad cholesterol and have an awful life.
This is the one to live an amazing, healthy life right now.
You know, when they interviewed like the 95 year old woman, they're like,
Oh, what did you do to live this long and live this healthy?
And then you just fucking residents sleeper and you don't even listen to her.
German's going to outlast all of you guys because the good ones always die first.
What someone was here.
Are you implying that I'm like a bad guy?
No, I'm just saying, like, you know, the health tips like you.
You're I wanted to hear this explanation.
I've been OK.
So when you have saturated fat, it means it cannot be your body uses it.
It can't be used. Your body uses fat as unsaturated fat.
This is poly saturated fat, right?
There's a bunch of different like kind of half saturated, full saturated fat.
Your body can does not use it.
It's just junk that has been completely saturated.
That's why it's called saturated.
Reason why people say to eat peanut butter and eat like avocados and eat
like olive oil is because it's an unsaturated fat.
OK, yeah. Well, what about the cholesterol?
What do you want to know about it?
It's it's it's all good.
OK, let me let me look this up.
LD LDL cholesterol.
Yeah. What about Hillary's cholesterol?
Low density cholesterol is one of the five major groups of lipoprotein,
which transport all fat molecules around the body in an extra terrestrial water.
Oh, the cosmic fluid.
So that's the stuff that flows your blood.
Look, you understand how fucked up our bodies are.
You know how complicated it is and how we even know any of this.
Our bodies are insane.
You have a thing in your body that pumps blood oxygen shit across your whole body.
Do you really need to know why this all works?
Yeah, I just want to know.
I guess at the end of the conversation, we have to go through this morning.
I made myself eggs this morning.
Does that count or like making eggs beneath you?
Do you make eggs? What do you have for breakfast?
I love eggs. Eggs are like one of my favorite breakfast foods.
Yes, I have no idea what we're doing.
Follow the traces.
They lead to the door.
And then the guys like this door is stupid underneath in the water.
Maybe the cholesterol is not necessarily a bad thing,
but too much of it fills up like plaque in your arteries.
Wait, we can go up here in the event.
Oh, the secret one of my favorite things is hard boiled eggs
because especially when I used to work out a lot,
don't really do it anymore. But, you know, whatever.
Hard boiled eggs were so easy because I would just make like a two dozen of them
and I would just take them out an hour or two.
What? Me? You?
So I would make like 12, buy a carton of eggs
and I would make a boil them up, hard boil eggs,
put them in a container and I would eat two or three of them every day.
And then I would go to the gym and I would utilize that fat and protein.
They were really, really easy.
You would eat eggs before you went to the gym.
Like maybe an hour, a couple of hours before, an hour before.
I also used to eat tuna out of the can like a cat.
OK, that's a little weirder.
Like I would just open the thing and just like drain the water and just eat it.
Like his cat food.
Who is this guy?
I don't know, but he's holding his hands in a really weird place.
He's got a knife back there.
He's hiding. But like his thumbs are like in front of his neck.
It's kind of weird. Yeah.
Why does his death? Sardines.
Yeah, sardines are really good, too.
You're not enjoying your new status, new challenges.
New possum. Don't I deserve it?
I was on a kick for a long time of eating
like a tin of sardines, like a couple of times a week.
Crap. Oh, shut up.
Now give back what you stole from me.
Give back the key, boy.
Oh, this is broke as a hand.
It's Wesker.
Nice clip. Nice.
Ooh, I was watching what you've done.
I hope this guy is a face turn, right?
Seven minutes, seven minutes is all I can spare for you.
You guys like that video?
The video was exactly seven minutes long.
I love that video.
It's honestly incredible.
The thought that goes into these things.
What about locks on a bagel?
I have to really be in the mood for a smoke salmon.
That person's a little different. Let's kill him.
So we fight. Yeah, we fight these people.
He's killing me.
What I'm in, I'm in goon vision.
Oh, my God, I hit that guy's torso off.
What the fuck?
The game crashed.
Oh, what the hell?
No, I had found it.
What's happening here?
You still there? Yeah.
OK, he's in the car factory.
OK, now we're going to hunt down Wesker.
Get back. OK, so now let's let's follow.
So I think we're going to get a major encounter here.
Major boss, maybe.
Yeah, the whole world's opening up.
We're out of the tutorial now.
So we have the same powers as him is what I'm getting here.
That seems to be the case that we were experimented on when we were children
and we were with our our our friend Mia and we want to find her again.
And she's going to be the key to we're all actually.
The new infested are the people that were together.
This is looks cool.
You tune it out of the can on stream.
I'm not going to do that.
It's it was just really easy and really fast,
especially if you were working out a lot.
Oh, my God. I almost fell through. Oh, God.
Oh, shit. I saw you do that and I freaked out.
And now I'm going to fall.
I thought that you did you fall. You said.
All right. I mean, I'll continue forward, I suppose.
I heard you say, oh, God.
And I saw you fall.
So I was like, wait, maybe I'm doing this wrong.
I'm coming.
Let's go, Borpo.
Yeah, I'm sorry that you falling was my fault.
Well, no, I you jumped in the air.
I heard, oh, God.
Yeah, because of me.
I'm not fucked up. I would do that to you.
So let me see here.
Hey, die lockpick.
We need some meds.
I actually do need a crafting med kit.
And these are these bandages are starting to not be enough for me anymore.
I've got so much.
I'm so vascular.
So much blood.
Oh, I'm through me.
What I've had, I didn't get the pick.
Oh, dude, what is it with this one?
I thought you were reacting to vascular men.
Right. You guys going to complete the entire game?
No. Yeah.
I think in the next hour or so.
Stirr definitely is at that point where he's like starting to get a little bored.
Oh, it's me. It's me again.
Bringing up like sweet potatoes and food and I got the Gundam.
He said something about Gundam's like a Gundam photo, whatever it was.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
And we just got to the big the big city out here.
And it's good. Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Wait. Oh, hey, we got heads.
Is it solar? Yeah.
Hmm. Oh, watch out heads.
I want to craft a bomb or something.
I think I got a bomb.
Oh, they've heard us. Our factory.
There it is. All right.
What do you got? Bomb.
Oh, no, you didn't jump and kick them.
Now he's dead.
You just you just put like shrapnel in his eyeballs, but you didn't kick him.
That's my bad. I jumped and kicked him.
Tahini paste.
No, but that was like I do not recommend that.
That's that's probably not that great for you, to be honest.
Oh, spear. Nice.
Is that thing going to blow?
Yeah, I speared right through the metal container
with my incredible strength.
Come on, come on, come on.
When does Elden Ring come out?
Like really soon, right?
Uh, hey, hey, hey, he's putting his hands up.
He wants us to stop.
I thought you were serious for saying.
I am. Don't Thursday of next week.
Damn. OK.
How come there are more suplexes in video games?
I agree. That's actually pretty not a bad point.
I think because you have to make the the models match up
and it depends on which character.
And it's a whole there was a there was a suplex
mod for like all the Skyrim games, the scrolls of Skyrim,
and it would always do you think weird and give you this crazy kill cam.
But that's what made it enjoyable.
He's in here somewhere. We go up.
I think we just keep going around.
Oh, wait. Are you still inside?
I'm out. No. Oh.
Yeah, maybe we did stop to be in there.
Little auto plant.
Let's go back in.
These doors feel like they would leave there, but they're fake doors.
I think we can we can climb over.
Oh, we can climb.
Or it looks like you can.
How do we climb?
Oh, I see. There we go.
This way. Oh, you just you just skipped it.
So you guys having fun?
No, not really.
Right. How did you get up there?
I jumped that. Oh, I got to go from here to here.
Oh, fuck off, please.
Come on. Just give it to him.
Game. I seriously got there.
I was so dumb.
I'm going to wait up for my blood.
Thanks, man. My sweet potato bud.
All right. Where's he at?
No, I'm kidding. We're having a good time. It's fun.
You're telling jokes.
Somebody asked if we were having a good time, and I said no.
What's the punch line?
There isn't. I was making I was just lying.
Yeah, a lie is the punch line.
OK, so down is this him?
I'm just swinging.
We should play Fart Simulator 2004.
Some reason I feel like I'm wasting my valuable time.
I mean, your time is pretty valuable, right?
Like if there's something else you could be doing, maybe.
All right. He accidentally just snorted some coke.
He's got like an Abraham Lincoln vibe.
It's very official.
And one of his experiments.
The chance witness something spectacular.
My God, his pants are coming off.
He's got everything comes full circle.
We return beginning.
Ethan. Hi, Ethan.
Now you will witness history in the making.
You don't understand anything, Ethan.
I'm going to kill you right now, Ethan.
Kids, you got a chance, Ethan.
You were part of something special, but as strong as me.
That's too red.
Last words from my sister, sister.
Red. What?
Oh, betrayed. Instantly betrayed.
Hey, we're friends. I got shot by an arrow.
It's dad. What?
The double, double cross.
Mother gas coin. Let's go.
No, we should have watched that.
That's the one time we should have paid attention.
Nope. Is he coming?
Is he chasing us?
I mean, I have one spend skill points, so.
Wait, that's not even him.
This is him. Where?
Oh, in the window.
It's just some random dude.
Oh, yeah, that's renegade.
We got to go. OK, let's go.
We got to go.
We're here.
I hope so bad that all of a sudden we here in the distance.
Here the cutscene ends.
Run across the street and we're going to start it again.
Why? What happened?
Oh, Tony Soprano was cooking over here.
He got angry at the grill.
Not starting.
OK, I think you skipped something really important.
I don't know.
Wait, what happened?
I have no idea.
Didn't we go in this door?
I think we're trying to catch her, but she was on my screen.
It's an indicator over here.
Escape from Waltz.
Wait, is this Waltz here?
We have to go.
You just locked us out of the room.
How do we go in that door last time?
My chance saying a soft lock.
I mean, we're here.
Maybe get the fuck out of there.
He did it.
OK, we here we are.
I can't get through this.
This got to be a way to get out.
Wait, it's just to go down here now.
I think we progressed it somehow.
We slide through here.
Yeah, try to jump out now.
OK, we can't get in there.
I think we have to die.
I'm in.
Wait, he's on the map now for me.
What is going on?
I'm at her.
OK, I'm going to do that.
I'm going to go backwards and try and get a trigger.
He was just on the screen.
OK, I got her.
I got her.
Something's happening.
We're going to go this way.
Wait, there she is.
I needed that.
Just grab it.
Grab the top.
You got to jump.
You grab it at the same time.
All right, finally, here we are.
Why did she stay here and then shut the door?
I think we got it.
Flashlights on.
Oh, that's him.
He's literally here.
We actually get to see him now.
Oh, he's right behind me.
Dude, you're about to get Western.
You have any grenades?
I got some coins.
You're just running in circles.
That guy had no idea where we went, by the way.
Not a clue.
What?
He's not behind us.
What is?
I can't swim.
What do you mean you can't swim?
Are you all right?
No, I can't swim.
Did you just drown?
I think he's supposed to be behind us constantly,
but he's not.
This is supposed to be very scary.
Oh, there he is.
There he is.
Wait, he doesn't know where we are.
Oh, shit, he found me.
He's right behind me.
Oh, shit, he's right behind me.
I don't know where did you go?
Where did you go?
He's behind me.
I'm dead.
I don't think you matter.
I don't?
I actually don't matter.
So why don't I just distract him?
Oh, you just have to get there.
It doesn't matter what happens to me.
Dude, you don't see what I'm seeing either.
This lady just keeps disappearing and teleporting.
And this whole thing has been a fever dream.
There he is again.
I got me.
He got you.
Wait, I can get you.
I can help you.
Oh, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up.
What the fuck?
What happened?
He died so that I could live.
I got to make it out of here for the both of us.
He was just looking at us.
The music.
I did not make the jump to this ladder, by the way.
I had to shoot you to keep up appearances.
What?
Nate, and you?
Show me your arm.
Come on, I won't bite.
See, I'm not infected.
We have something in common.
I was one of that crazy fucker's subjects too.
Well, hers does not light up.
Mia, did you know a girl named Mia?
Mia?
No.
Who's Mia?
She's my sister.
We were in a GRB place together.
I have to find her.
Well, if she's alive, she must be pouring herself with water
somewhere in the city.
What?
Not that I blame her.
Where did you go?
What are you saying?
Fuck you.
Whoa, Gaja.
I am you.
Time is what we live in.
Just saying.
I have to find her.
Well, first, let's fuck out of here.
Not sure we managed to ditch that cycle.
Right?
All right, so he's still chasing us.
OK, he's still on the map.
Oh, we got to follow the sniper.
She won't tell us her name, because her name's Mia.
Hell, she's fast.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun,
dun, dun.
Lube's not far away.
We'll be safe there.
Come on.
I'm coming.
Let's try to stay human.
You're here.
We're just a million miles away.
You have nightmares about what he did to us.
All the time.
That's why I want to kill the fucker.
Waltz is number three on my list.
So Wendy's number one.
You got a hit list.
Seriously.
Do I look like I'm kidding?
The city's got a lot of trash.
Yeah.
Who else is on it?
Besides Waltz, Butcher, Hackon, and.
Oh, wait.
Hackon.
There's a few.
She's the one who shot him, dude.
He got.
We got it.
When are they going to reveal that that's Mia?
They're not going to.
Aiden, you there?
Yeah.
I mean, the sniper is sort of weird, right?
Like, sniper is going to be a reveal.
I don't know if it's going to be Mia, though.
Why wouldn't it be?
Who else could it be that we know the name of,
that they would be hiding the name?
When otherwise, these Ubisoft style games are like,
we want you to know who our goofy zany characters are.
This is Zilpo, the fucking, the goofy, you know,
one time amount.
Zilpo.
Yeah, I see you on the list.
Because, you know, I like these blue puppets that be death.
I thought my dear is alone.
Let's just say everyone on that.
But where did you get that?
Don't worry, I can handle this.
Yeah, you know, don't he's dead.
Waltz, oh, so maybe we were meant to meet.
Okay, P.K., Commander Lucas, P.K., P.K., P.K., Pree.
Let's Waltz.
All right, bring lavender and metal parts to Nero, okay.
We got a bow.
Oh, dude.
Have to use it.
Oh, yeah, man.
How do we use it?
I'm gonna be an archer, like that show Archer.
Me and my ax in my bum, in my bum.
In my bum.
What?
That's not what I said.
Me and my ax in my bum.
In my, in my bum.
In my ax, stop saying this.
I'm trying to do a thing here.
In my ax, and I can't even.
Hey, you just walk by an inhibitor.
Wait, we're still following her?
Hey, bud, you just walk by an inhibitor, bud.
Hey, bud, down here there's an inhibitor, bud.
And there's a bed in here, too, bud.
Thanks, bud.
Hey, no problem, bud.
In my bum, in my bum, in my bum.
In my bum.
Silence.
What are you saying if it's not in my bum?
The Lord of the Rings, when they say,
and my ax, and my sword, and my bow,
when they say, like, at the fellowship of the ring,
yes, we're gonna work together.
And you made a song about this moment,
and you sing in my bum.
That's what I do.
I make songs.
I make little jingles.
That's what I do here.
I was sightseeing.
With some volume, but, with some volume, but.
I thought you did, like,
I thought you did nunchucks.
Oh, shit, look.
I do that, too.
You too?
Fuck.
I don't know, we're getting, like,
Nick Fury just walked in the room.
That's the same soundtrack.
See what?
What's going on?
I'm coming, Mia.
Yeah, I don't go by Mia anymore.
That was the name that they gave me.
I'm still holding on to it.
I think we've opened up the game.
I was wrong.
Can't see shit.
I'm gonna unlock the best part of the game, really.
Fucking d-
It's peaceful.
Soul.
Why am I just gonna push her?
I can't believe it.
Electricity.
Come on, you're seeing this.
This has happened, dark as hell for 50 years.
Chicken pie.
I don't know, no.
Yeah, I could go for some chicken pie.
Then drop by the canteen and let's eat.
While shotgunning beers and screwdrivers.
You know it.
You dumbass.
Hey, what happened?
You skipped too fast.
What the hell's going on?
So that's the fish eye.
Okay, how do we get there?
The fish eye's gotta be-
The power just went out again.
Somebody's like, but they didn't realize
is that they only had it on a few fuses.
Somebody just fucking microwaved a bag of popcorn
and just fucking turned the whole thing up.
She gave us the paraglider.
We're paragliders.
Hold Z to open the paraglider.
Hold Z, press S.
Oh baby, here we go.
What, are you gonna really do this to me?
You're leaving the mission area?
I won't go forward.
That wasn't a paraglider.
That was like a parachute.
Press S to stabilize.
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
How am I leaving the mission area?
As you're going too low, you gotta press S.
It's teaching you to press S.
It's like, hey, press S right now.
Oh, cool.
We unlocked it.
We got it.
Hey, meet me down here.
Oh, gas can.
What?
I'm down a little bit.
Why did you tell me to come down here?
Well, this is the objective, but you landed high
and I'm not good enough to do that.
The objective is up there.
You have to talk to Mia.
Yeah, I'm talking to Mia.
I just talked to her and getting the fuck out of this.
I fell.
I can teleport you.
I was, I was.
Come on.
Come on, dude.
That was almost bad.
How do you get up and get dressed in the morning?
I just rip open my closet and just grab
and just like, rip shit off the hangers
and rip the shirts and stuff
and smush it all over my face
and smush it and rub all of my face
until it gets on me.
He still has his mommy do it.
I've seen it.
Using air vents.
Yeah, okay, yeah.
The air vents are pumping so hard.
I just roll around on the ground
until it gets on one arm.
You fly into the vents.
You're not saying the thing that Mario does
when he jumps off the edge of a level you can't fall off of.
What does he say?
Come on, you know what he says.
Hello.
Holy shit.
Mario.
Wow, oh my God.
Are you kidding me?
Is that not what he says?
No.
That wasn't even close.
Hey, let me help you.
I'll do the sound effect.
Okay.
What?
What the fuck was that?
It was like in a horror movie
where like your phone starts going static
because the ghost is nearby.
Does she have one of these things?
Yeah, she goes first.
But you have to control the wind.
It controls you.
Okay.
Show us.
Show us what it means to fly.
Ah, good joke.
What did you do?
I'm coming.
I don't know how to control this.
You need to control the wind.
I'm out of stamina.
Oh no.
I was going to come save you.
Okay.
Here we go.
Oh, by the way, I just want to let you know,
your weapon's almost broken.
Well, where are we going?
Okay, now she's going.
Here we go.
Control the wind.
There.
Oh, you get stamina when you go over that shit.
If we could collide in the air,
that would be kind of funny.
Is there a break?
How do you get off?
Like what's break?
What's break?
I don't know what break is.
How do I just go?
Crouch, crouch, crouch.
Is it actually crouch?
Are you making that up?
Yeah, it's actually crouch.
All right, we'll just hit the button.
Oh, you're back soon.
I got here before you.
Well, you did super good on your hang glider,
but have you ever done it this way?
Okay, we're going somewhere to activate.
That's what she sounds like.
What?
I can make fun of her.
She's my sister.
Activate the electrical substation.
So you said C is break.
C is let go.
You said it was break.
You said how do you get to the ground?
I didn't say break.
You can't break something that is guided by the wind.
You can tilt it the other way so it fills the air.
You go backwards so it fills it up.
The air pushes into the big balloon shit.
You tilt it up so the air slows you down.
This is a video game.
I think you have to get enough speed
and when you have the owl hat with the tail,
then you jump with the cape.
Can I not climb this?
Dude, there's Zeds in here.
Is there an event right here?
There is right there.
There's events down here and yeah, there's Zeds up here.
So I could really use some help.
Oh my God, damn it.
Someone is crying for help.
I have to go around.
I haven't figured it out yet.
This isn't even where we're going.
It's not?
No, it's a building over this way.
Let me just turn.
Please, look, I've got to turn the right way.
It used to be a Knight Runner's favorite.
Me, Knight Runner?
Really something, Aiden.
We'll hear of it.
I'm holding S. Just relax.
The only thing I had in common, maybe.
Somebody's pressing that button.
Yeah, I hear him.
It's fine, I'm ignoring him.
I'm self-killing the zombies.
I'm something of an assassin.
Are you up higher?
I'm right here.
Oh, there you are.
Finally, level three enemies.
New crafting recipe.
Okay, where are we going?
You kind of feel like, so we've been waiting for this.
I feel like we just did,
we waited in line at Disney World for like three hours
to go on Soarin' and like the ride is now over.
It was like fucking two minutes, three minutes.
And I don't think I don't care anymore.
You don't care anymore?
Like we just rode the ride that we were waiting for.
Yeah.
You know, they like spray scents in your nose.
What?
You've never gone on Soarin' before?
That guy kind of looks like you.
Who's Soarin'?
Who are these guys?
I don't know, but apparently we're fighting them.
I'm gonna drop kick them.
I think the guy behind you is also mad at you.
They're all doing the stunt man in a movie from the nineties.
They have like eight articles of clothing on.
They're all like burnt.
This guy actually is not, we have to talk to him now.
Now they're not fighting anymore.
Wait, don't, they're not, don't, okay.
Over here.
The guy that's engulfed in flames
that's walking around like a toddler.
Cause he's wearing like five flame like suits on.
Can you come over here?
I'm trying to take the story seriously.
I got involved, I'm invested in the characters
now that Wesker's in the game.
My name's A.
Hey, you guys know this one?
What did the bullets say to the man that got shot?
What is it?
You're Swiss cheese, you're dead.
Just passing through, bang, bang.
Wait, what was it?
What did the bullets say to the man that got shot?
You got this right.
Just passing through.
Come on, man.
Yeah.
You severed his limbs with a machete knit-taff.
Technically speaking, that's a melee weapon
while bullets are reserved for-
I'm glad you're fine too.
Bullets?
You still want to climb up there, Aiden?
Not for free, of course.
We reward specialists if you need.
What are we looking at?
We're climbing up into the building.
And I think we're doing the unlock the front door
for the people.
Okay.
Well, let's get up there.
But we need to go around and figure out
how to get up there.
I think we can just run up here like this
and go, bup, bup, bup, bup, bup, bup, bup, bup, bup.
I don't think so.
Why is it telling me to press F?
I think you did it.
Yep.
How'd you do that?
I don't know.
Oh, hold on.
How's it look?
Somebody was in a big hurry when they took it offline.
Somebody went inside the building.
I would surmise the main circuit suffered a break.
Find a cable and connect the source of power
to the transmitter.
That should restore the circuit.
There's like a whole thing going on in here now.
Electrical station.
There's like a whole tutorial.
Report in.
Yep, I'm on top of the substation.
Trying to connect power to the transmitter.
And the piece of cake in here after all.
Always another tutorial.
Are you sure you're gonna make it?
I met a bunch of PKs who couldn't get
to the substation themselves.
So that's why you haven't called me yet.
Is it connected to you?
Yeah.
Okay, so what do you bring?
I got a release cable button.
All right, so now what we have to do
is we have to literally make a mess
and drag that across the whole game.
It's not a distance.
Oh.
It can only go, it can only go like 17 meters.
I thought we were in America.
But.
They have their own men.
The free folk.
Someone should be on their side.
Not people like us.
Now think about it.
Where are you supposed to bring it?
Just don't take too long, Gaja.
I can't go.
I'm stuck.
It's probably like right here though.
Oh, no, no, no.
I think it's right here.
It's right across the way.
It's the competition, huh?
Yeah, it's right here.
Bring it to me.
Wait, can we cast her up?
This one's over here.
I think we need a different cable for that one.
Different cable?
Yeah.
Now it's looking like it's gonna be
up on the roof there, chump.
All right, it's time to criticize video games again.
Who wants to do this?
Who cares?
Isn't this getting your brain juices going?
No, not really.
It's just thinking about it.
But who cares?
Well, you're only saying that
because I'm doing it for you.
Ooh, this looks cool.
101 damage, holy shit.
I don't, you know what?
I've brought this up before.
I truly do not understand how you are an impatient gamer
that hates all this dialogue and stuff
and you're like the least patient
and yet you love House Flipper and you love cleaning game
and you love like viscera cleanup detail.
Rebuttal time.
So if I opened up this game
and the game was called connect cables to each other
and I knew exactly what I was getting into,
I'm gonna connect cables to walls.
That's the game, it's a puzzle game.
It's a game where you connect cables.
If I'm into that shit, I will play that cable game.
Sounds awesome.
House Flipper is a game where you know
you're gonna go in there and clean and paint.
House Flipper is not a game that starts out
when you have like a machete in your hand
and it's like, oh, hey, welcome to House Flipper.
Go slaughter people.
If this game includes things from other games you do like,
like if you loved fishing games and you find out,
oh wait, this game also has fishing.
Okay, so.
You just hate that.
No, no, because look, there's a difference
between like a game having fishing
and a game having drag a cable across the room
to pad 10 minutes onto the game.
This is not a puzzle that people think is cool.
It's just, it's just here.
It's just here.
It's nothing, it doesn't do anything.
It's just like, this is just here now.
There's not a fishing mini game
where I get achievements for getting the big mouth baths.
Okay, so you want the big mouth.
I'm just saying like, if I go in a fishing game
and I'm doing brrrr and I pull it up
and it's like, this bath was 16 pounds.
That like has weight behind it to me.
We are just walking around this room
looking to drag a cable to the other thing to plug it in.
Okay, if there was like a, if there was mines,
if there was like little mineral deposits everywhere,
I would not, I would be happy about that.
Oh, cool, here's some, here's some ore, like ding, boom.
Why would you be happy about that?
I wouldn't be happy about it, but it's like,
it's not just like, hey, go walk around the building
and drag a cable around it.
Like, no, it's different.
Okay, well, we gotta drag one more cable.
There's one more thing I think here
that needs a cable in it.
And I think I'm gonna leave this one up to you.
No, don't.
I think it's right, oh no,
there's like an inhibitor above us.
Look, I'm sure that there's probably gonna be.
There'll be a thing in our inventory
that's like electrical boxes connected,
like two out of 58, right?
I'm, let's see if it's there.
Well, you haven't connected any,
so it's probably not in your inventory.
I mean, I've been, I've been connecting them.
There's lock picks needed up here.
Like, there's a whole bunch of things you could be doing.
You know, I'm looting stuff, I'm picking up shoes.
I can't grab those, why not?
Are they too big?
Oh, shit, just do it.
Do what?
Just do the mission.
I'm doing it, and for the record, I'm hating it.
But at least I'm doing it.
Okay, I just wanna make sure
we're very clear what you just said.
I know what I just said.
I'm just surprised that you, someone,
I see, I don't like visceral cleanup detail.
I think that house flipper is fucking boring.
I hated that.
No, what?
You hated visceral cleanup detail?
Yes, that was the whole premise
of why you wanted to play with me,
because you knew I would hate it.
But like that, it's like,
it scratches like a dopamine itch
to like clean up stuff and move stuff
and make things look nice.
Yeah, I bet you like kitchens real clean, right?
Actually, it is.
It's actually very clean.
I contribute a lot of cleaning, a lot, okay?
Yes.
I'm not buying it.
What do you mean you don't buy it?
You don't buy it that I like clean my own places?
The tone that you just took.
For a second I thought you were talking about the tub.
The tub, do you do the tub too?
Look, okay, we gotta get this to go somewhere.
And I opened this door
and I don't know where this goes.
I don't know where any of the things are.
There's no like objective markers
from where they're supposed to be.
There's like a sub,
oh, there's a substation basement down here.
Oh, there it is.
Where's this one going?
Up here to the two, right?
Oh, no, this one's gotta go to the three.
Oh, right.
That's the number three.
Gotta come over here.
Now I'm taking it through the vent.
Shit, watch out, zombies.
Yeah, dodge, dodge, watch out.
Grenade out, grenade great.
Watch out, whoa, parkour, got it.
What is the point of this?
I need help.
Okay, so from there, you need to walk.
If that's three, I don't think this is correct
because this is yellow.
You have something plugged into three.
That one is not correct.
Let me get that off.
And I need you to...
So this has to go to two.
Two is over here.
Honey.
Two goes to two, stop.
I think I gotta climb up here.
And then, one is wrong too, I think.
Really?
Where is three?
Can you go stand by three
so I at least know where the fuck I'm going?
One is connected to one, I think that's right.
I'm gonna scream.
Does one have to connect to two and then two to three?
Don't scream.
It won't even pick up and it won't be funny.
You're gonna hurt your voice.
How do I release?
Yes, you plugged three into three?
Yeah, now we got one more to go.
Okay, so I have this one here.
So where does this one go now?
This one goes to two.
And two is up there?
How do I let this go?
Hold F.
Okay, so if you grab two and put it into two,
does that do it?
I mean, I gotta go put it into two
because you're not doing it.
Yeah, well, I had to let it go
because it was all tangled up.
I don't know where two is, I forget where two is.
I think it's down there in that corner.
Two, wait, does it show up on the map?
What?
You holding onto it and using it to swing?
Yeah.
I'll go find two, hold on.
Do you remember if it was up or down?
I think it's over there in that corner.
I'm stuck.
The game just crashed.
Did it?
Yeah.
Oh, that was fun dying light session.
Are you done?
You know, I'm just saying
I don't think your game crashed.
I swear to God it did.