Hello. Tweet that there's a stream at 12 30. Hold on, I might be in the room. All right, I got it.
How are you? Jeremy, you never say hi when the person says hi, Jeremy Wormy.
Shit. Hey! But I, how do I respond to that? Yeah, I'm, should I say no? I was gonna say should I say
chatty waddy? That kind of hurts to say that. That's, no, that's like a, that's like a you're
dating somebody. That's, I don't know if I want that. Oh, hey, Jeremy Wormy. Oh, hey, chatty
waddy. No, no, no, no, no, no. I'm gonna just continue to say hi. That's like creepy.
That's a creepy thing. I'm not sure I'm okay with that. Anyways, let me just tweet this. Yeah,
early stream. Uh, there's a couple of reasons for it, but hold on. Early Mega Man. Early Mega Man.
He has to leave in two hours. No, that is not accurate. Please do not spread misinformation
about me needing to leave in two hours. I have to leave in three. Okay, come on, get it right.
Uh, I have another doctor's appointment today and this, that's all, this is all just fucked up.
You know what I mean? Like just this whole, you know, I don't, you know how it is. You know,
we've talked about it a bunch of times. It's just fucked up and I'm fucking annoyed by it,
but let's just, hey, I'm good. We should make a clip of like, what, what, what, what,
what's Jerma talking about? It's just fucked up and I'm fucking annoyed by it. Yeah, that's it.
That's all we need. But yeah, I got a doctor's appointment today. So I got to get back into the
doctor and I could be like, Hey doc, play Mega No. Am I wearing my boomer brace? No, I'm actually
not wearing it today because I ordered a new one and the new one is supposed to be a little bit
better because the one I have now really kind of tears into my armpits and I've tried to adjust
it, its length and everything. It was pretty cheap. So I got, I got a new boomer base boomer
brace 2.0. Oh, that should be here soon. Plus I only plan on sitting here for about three hours
or so. So I think I'll be fine. And my physical therapist did say that I really shouldn't rely
on a brace because it can become, he said it can become kind of a crutch.
So I really don't want to do that. You know, he's like, you'll start wearing it every single day
and then you're like, you can't do anything with that unless it's on. And I got to be careful with
that too, but it's only for sitting for long periods. Wait a wink. Did I, did my, did I even
tweet anything? Did I just press the tweet button? Where is it? I don't see it. Did I like accidentally
tweet under, like, did I like click on somebody that I'm following and tweet underneath them?
I didn't know. Why is it not on my feet? All right. All right, let's go. You remember this game?
You remember Mega Man? Let's actually turn it on. It was a real wink. I know. And guess what? I've
got clothes on. Oh, I've, I've got, I've got clothes on. I have to wear fucking clothes every day.
This is so rare for me to wear clothes every day. It's rare. All right. So the last thing we did,
uh, it looks all right. Is it fucked up? Hold on. Uh, no, it looks fine. Okay. Doctor waiting room.
I mean, you could say this is just a giant doctor waiting room. That's right. All right. So I just
got like one of the crystals, right? What was I doing? I remember I was tired and I was like
freaking out and I couldn't decide. I couldn't figure out where a door was. I have to go back
down there. Don't I? There's going to be an era that people like, like, let's say three or four
years from now. If somebody just finds this channel, they're like, oh, this guy, German985,
maybe I'll check up on his VODs. Is it going to be a Reddit thread complaining about this era?
Like, Hey, man, I just like was curious. I'm like going back and watching old VODs and like, why
did he like every like four and a half minutes winking to the camera? Like it was kind of annoying
and I'm going to have to sit there and be like, fuck, well there were these things called channel
points. They don't exist anymore. They got deleted. Twitch doesn't even use them anymore.
I'm already saved. What am I? All right. What do I do now? Let's talk to the, let's talk to the
monkey. Tell me what should I do now? Oh, the flutter might not be fully operational yet,
but at least we can get to the sub gate in the closer woods. Did I not finish up what I was
doing in there? I was here before the link error. Did I, did I not, was this something I didn't do
here? I remember I fought the three, uh, dog wolf monsters, right? Come on, let me see.
Do the auto voice where I'm leaving. This way, that way, this way, that way, this way, that way.
That's my favorite like comment of the whole year. All right. So was it something I didn't do down
here? Cause I killed the boss. Wasn't the boss, the, um, oh, the ID cards, the ID cards. Okay.
Yeah. So I do have to be here. Remember it's past your bedtime. Go to bed. I woke up like two hours
ago. I, what are you, what are you talking about? I'm not, I'm not going to bed. All right. These
guys. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. I time to pay attention. And remember
where the control room was? Cause I don't, it's, you know, it's something about this level in
particular. Like I cannot burn into memory this level. It's, uh, this level doesn't exist. I can,
okay. You know, like the, the, the first place we were like that factory level, I could, I could
go do that right now. It's not, I don't know what it is about this level in particular. I cannot put
this into long-term memory. It's like a block. All right. Drop some help please. I think it's
right in here. I have a shit load of money too. Did I remember about the holes? Don't forget about
the holes. Was it this way? This is right in the middle. I think is this correct? Is this right?
All right. It's in the first room. No. Yeah. Cause then you go up the elevator, right?
Oh, let me just kill this guy. Like if it's sub ended feels bad, man. It's all right. It's all
right. Wait, are we getting, are we getting, are we getting coxed? What? It's been a while since
that has happened. All right. Let's go back. You know, I think it's cause it's a big circle
and both the, yeah, both sides are identical. Minor cox. Oh, okay.
Well, did you get one near shoe? Just gave 10 community subs. Were you,
did you get another one back? Did you get one? I got it. Oh, sick. All right. And then we go up.
Wait, hold on. It's not over here. Is it? Okay. Now it's right over here. It's, it's like here,
right here somewhere. Isn't it? Well, this area hurts my brain so much. I was going to stand it.
I'm literally going to stand in the first room and you just tell me what room to go into.
I have no idea which way I have absolutely no idea where I'm going up that way, that way.
Oh, wait, what? I'm, I'm so confused. Why is this a memory block? Like it's this whole level is a
block. I can't even see in this level. It's like a full block. Wait, and here it's only this level.
It's only this one. Look, I'm like in this set. I'm like, I'm in the same room again in the,
right in the middle. It's, it's only this level. Well, I've played seven hours of this game and
this is the only time I've had a problem here. I don't know what it is about this place. Is it in
the center? It's cause there's like two circle rooms and no, it's definitely not the center.
I'm going to just draw a map on a fucking piece of paper. No, this is wrong.
It is this way. I can't do this place. Boomer struggles with a kid's game. No, it's just this
one area. It's the double circle rooms with like the three side rooms. I'm going this way.
I'm just going to keep, I'm just going to walk this way. See what happens. This is the generator
room. Go back up to the entrance. Why is it only this level that causes me so many problems?
Go back to the elev, go the first room. Okay. So I have to go over here and
it wasn't, I just in the first room. So many places look identical in this place. It's hard
to even remember. Okay. I should just die and walk in the fucking front door. They'll go in this hole.
Just kill me. I'd rather just die and restart the game and walk in and then, then try to figure out
the map in this game. What did I, what did I just in here? Hey, I found the computer.
Pick a man. I have trouble with it too. Don't worry. Game is quiet. I did. I don't know why
it's that quiet. I don't have that much like stream resources today. I just spent like
nine minutes walking around in circles, trying to find a computer room.
That's precious real estate today. Cause I can only be live for like three and a half hours.
Oh God, I have no health. Do I have a canteen? No. Fuck. Nope. Don't die. Don't die on the way out.
Please don't make me have to go through that again. I, I know, I know. Exit the map. I know.
But there's people here. Oh, no, there's not. Wait, you have to go up and then out, right?
I need, I want to be certain of this and I'm never going back here ever again, even if the
best weapon of the whole game is here. Up and leave. Yes. Up and out. Okay. You could tell me that
$500 would get deposited into my bank account. If I went back here and I'd be like, no, I don't want
to feel like somebody else will do it. And then I'll go, I'll get like my electric bill in the mail
and be like, how much is this for? $487. Hey guys, what's up? It's me, Jerma. I just want to say that
I had a change of heart and I would like to go back into that fun room. I was just kidding that
whole time. All right, let's see. I got a really bad feeling about this. Like we're getting into
something better left alone. Sonic. The tuber voice is Sonic the Hedgehog. I'm sure you could
probably take clips of all the time Sonic has talked and put it in the background over somebody's
Five Nights at Freddy's gameplay. And it would make sense. It would match. All right. Got the
game saved. So, uh, the thing opened. Let's talk to Grant. See, Grant. I'm slowing down in my old
age, Mega Man. Won't be able to help you like I used to. I guess I'll just stay here and watch TV.
Why don't you stay and watch TV with me? See, look there. It's Catalox Island. That's kind of sad.
I just want to sit here and watch TV. All right. So let's, um, correct me if I'm wrong, but that
thing that opened was the thing that was where I fought that boss. The tank boss, right? So I want
to go back there. No, that's incorrect. What just opened? You haven't even seen the thing that opened
yet. Oh, playing this fucking thing. He went back. No, no, no, no. I know. I don't have to be here.
I have to tell. No, my God. I thought I would. Why would I come out that way? What?
Game's not loading now because I can't believe that I just didn't. I just like fucked that up
somehow. It's like, wait, we didn't load the game because we like can't believe you turned around
and went back in the door and broke the fucking game. Is the CD broken? Like what's going? Did I
break the fucking CD because I turned around? I didn't do anything. Did I like, did I like record
scratch like, oh shit, we were loading the other area and you, oh fuck. Thank God I saved it right
there. It's dead. I don't know what's fucking wrong with me. I need some fucking Wheaties.
All right. Please take this back to the fucking forest. For the love of God, get me out of here.
I never want to see this part of the game again. You already saw it three times. You'll be back.
I hope not. Look at that side eye. Now that he's opened the main gate for us,
we don't need to keep him around any longer. Time to blow him and that ship of his to kingdom
come. All board cannons, prepare to fire.
Fire.
Cease fire.
They're trying to lose us in the clouds. After them. Why am I wrong? What even 50 degrees are
right now? A fly just like, that's the first fly I think I've seen in Vegas. It's trying to kill me.
Isn't that like a sign of something? What does a fly mean? What does a fly trying to kill you
mean in lore? Doesn't it mean something bad? It means you just stink.
Bees above the devil manifest as a fly in the real world. So if I killed this fly,
I'd kill the devil. That'd be weird. Well I got homing missiles though, so we should be good.
I mean it kind of is a problem. Final battle? What do you mean final battle with the with the
galestia shaft, galus shaft. Destroy the warcraft galus shaft while protecting the flutter from
attack. Mission start. Final battle? No it's not. Look at how small this area. All right let's just
do homing. Let's not save them. All right they're doing like synchronized swimming.
I'm just gonna stay in the squad and aim. Fire. God. It's getting closer. How close is it gonna get?
Did I just do it? That was a final battle? I can't believe I fucking almost broke this.
Oh god damn it. That's so bad. I'm so embarrassed. I can't get over it. I'm so sad.
They bought us enough time to catch up with blue boy there. There they go. They're gone.
Diesel they're underneath us. They're right below the ghastly shaft. Underneath? They couldn't have.
They must have discovered our weak spot. Battle stations. It looks like they're serious. They
want to go out fighting just like cornered rats. On your toes everyone. Radu.
It's not possible. They're flying the ship. It's our turn to talk. It's our scene.
Remember your lines Mega Man. It's our. The cameras are rolling. All right right the belly.
Engine. Aim for the underside of the engine on the wing. Shoot in the eye.
Are you sure you don't want me to shoot it in the eye? I got rid of that. That's it. Keep it up.
Don't give them any breathing room. Right there. That's what you want.
Come on get it. Get it. Whoa no no too much turn. Too much tilt.
Dude that was an epic fucking reference. That's what I'd like to do here on German 95 is make
references and talk about stuff and give wacky analytics to stuff too. That's what we do if
you're new to the channel. Hey how are you? Why is everybody that. Okay I got a question.
Why is everybody that has like a weird way of saying like hey or hello. Hey everybody. What's
up? Hey. They all do. They all say hey in like a weird way. I did it. I did it. Hey what's going
on everybody? Jerma here with a T-42 gameplay. Like why did I do that? What was the point of that?
Why do we all do that? Like 2012. It's like every every youtuber's first sentence they forget how to
talk. And then they're like oh wait hold on a second. I'm a human. I'm like a normal person.
I gotta talk normally. All right this one's dead. This one's dead. What are you doing?
Other side's not hurt. Game is loud. I'm sorry.
Yeah that's what I'm saying. Okay goodbye. Final battle. Yeah no the game was just way too loud.
I had it was like almost peaking. See you in fucking hell.
Imagine they took a really dark turn and Mega Man just goes like see you in hell. Wild. Right
before the ship explodes he goes that implies you're going to hell too. Boom. And then Mega Man goes
what? Oh right fuck.
Tuber joke. Yeah we do those sometimes. Well I already know the spoiler.
I mean this whole video game with the misadventures of Tron Bone.
Like I know this plug. How do you hold on? Wait wait wait. I'm like all right I'm in the middle
of taking. I'm in the middle of taking like a fucking multivitamin. Like you know I'm not
kidding. Like what am I doing? You know now's a good time to take a fucking multivitamin
right now. Can you drink coconut water? I need fucking potassium man. I'm low on potassium today.
I don't drink every day. All right where are you? Where are you?
Oh my god. This is not fair. Where? Oh my. There you are. How do I hit you?
Wait is this script? Is this a scripted scene? It sounds like I can hit. Lock on? I'm trying.
Lock on is not doing it. R2. Not locking on. R2. Nothing. R2. Nothing. It's scripted. Scripted.
Okay apparently not. Holy shit. Okay that went from the easiest fight to the hardest
fight. But I can't. Do I have to like get off them? So all right I'm not going to use my
homing missiles because they're very very much needed. Wait what? Where am I? Oh don't walk out.
Don't walk out and walk out the exit. Don't. No you have to do this. Don't do that again.
Back to the forest. Oh fuck we have to do this again. It's all right. I don't have a refill. No
I don't. I'm actually pretty fucked here to be honest. I don't have a refill and this is
just scripted fucking cutscene. All right here we go. I got this. I'm just going to save my
homing missiles till the next fight. Check this out. I'm not going to even use the homing. You
don't skip. Yes you do if you've seen it already. The buster fire is too short. Oh let's see. Should
I get rid of it? Let's see what I got. No I need range. I have range two. Range five. Yeah let's
do that one. Let's max out the range. Sniper scope. I'll keep the laser on and energy. What do I have?
Energy two. Attack one. Energy two. I lose the uh now this should be fine. Yeah this is fine. Now
this is these travel the whole. They go forever. Not as much rapid fire but I don't know rapid
fire is cool but I feel like you're moving and shooting. It's range is always better. All right
I'll get this now. If I don't do it this time then what I'm going to do is I'm going to upgrade
uh the homing missiles again. It's too slow. It's all right. It's okay. Let's go. I really
shouldn't get hit at all because this thing even fire. The cannon does but barely. Well it's not
the weak points aren't even activated yet. It's not active yet but this shit don't matter either.
I don't think this is not taking. It's not doing damage. It's just to prevent me from taking damage.
I don't want to use my special. All right that's fine. We'll get it all in the next go.
Oh my god look at that fucking range. Pretty good. That one. Gunners what do you think you're doing?
The sky. And there's that one. Another hit. Here we go. What kind of firepower. All right.
I just need to be careful. Dodge. Locking on doesn't work. Thank god I have homing missiles.
I'm already doing it. All right. Mission complete. Can I run in there and like talk to the monkey
real quick? Here we go. Three, two, one, go. Where are you? Where are you? Oh dude. Jesus
Christ. This is a mess. The camera. I can't even see what anything's shooting at me.
God. Dude what the fuck? Why can't I shoot these? I can't shoot the missiles. I'll get it. Just
watch out for the fucking fire. Oh my fucking god. I don't know where the fuck they are.
Jesus. Watch out. I don't have a heal. Oh my goodness. What a dirty wet sock this control is like.
I'm dead. There's not enough range.
Hi Mega Man. We can't see you. That camera needs to be like a hundred feet further out.
Skrifted. Dude. You gotta go back to that room to get the best weapon. Okay. So I'm gonna put it.
I'm gonna put every cent I own into that gun because this is annoying. What can I do?
Range. $60,000 range. Use the. I'm not gonna use the vacuum. Time to farm in the dungeon. No. I'm
not going back in there. Save it. All right. So I can't. I can't leave. Can I? I'm stuck here.
I can't go back to the market. I have to do this without a without a canteen. All right. Well,
I almost did it back there. I got upgraded damage on my gun. I'm ready. Let's go. Skip, skip, skip,
skip, skip, skip. The ship is called Gielishat. Society in German. That's pretty good tidbit.
You can't team. I physically cannot fill the canteen.
You can only fill the canteen in town. I cannot go back to town. This is me going back to town.
I cannot leave this location until I beat this guy. Also, softlock yourself. Kind of, actually.
But not really. Isn't I just I have look at the attack. I have this now. I just have to do this
again. This is the hardest boss in the game. I mean, I could see that considering it's a flying
boss that flies all over the whole screen. And this is what you have to do. Why can't you just
fly too? I know that's that's unfucking fair. Am I really Mega Man? Mega is more than super,
but yet Superman can fucking fly. Come on, Capcom. What the fuck are you thinking?
Man, it's working. Keep it up. Gunners, what do you think you're doing?
More like Mega Stupid. God, I could have one cycled that.
We don't criticize the streamer. We don't criticize the streamer. We don't criticize the streamer. We
don't criticize the streamer. Is it Mega Man's whole thing that he absorbs other people's power?
Yes, he's the engineering Kirby. He's Kirby, the engineering student. Who came first?
All right, no more fucking around. I'm getting this done. Go.
What? Oh, oh, what a good line. That's the face I was making. Was that so hard? No.
I had a really good line there.
Holy shit. Oh my god, that was fucking horrible. Oh. Jesus.
Maybe we should have taken it easier on them.
Kids game. We should have taken it easier, but they ejected, right? Nope. And now this song.
Looks like the main gate is opened at last. I'm certain the answers to all our questions can be
found inside. I bet you can't wait to get inside, eh? Are you going to check it out right away?
No. It's always a good idea to be cautious when getting into a situation you know nothing about.
Make sure you're fully prepared and equipped before you head out.
Yeah, because this is the last dungeon in the game. I'm not making that same mistake. All right,
let's go. What's a good grind spot? Hey, what do you think you're doing? What? Whoops. What?
Get out of here now. Haven't I been going in here to talk? Next time not before opening the door.
Sorry, roll. Okay. Where's the? Where's the monkey? I want to save. All right, I need a good grind.
I need a good grind spot. Do I have any items that you can use?
Sorry, I wasn't able to make anything out of what you have. Never mind. Why is this Bernie? Bernie?
Not. Why is it Bernie? All right, let's go back to town. I want to get some shit. I want to get some
money. I spent it. All right, let's go to. I want to go to downtown. He said sorry with an accent,
like sorry. Oh, chat is high as fuck. Why? So it's like 1 p.m. Pacific. What do you mean? What do you
guys? I'm going to go self. I will not confirm or deny this. You smoking weed? Are you smoking weed?
Tell me. I found this in your room. To me, this looks like a half-smoked joint. That's so expensive.
Oh, that's really good. Ah, but that's just a better version of what I have on right now.
I learned it from you, okay? Now you didn't. Sniper unit Omega. I don't have enough money.
I need the Kevlar jacket too. All right, I have to get. I have to make some money.
I have to make. I have to make some money. What do I have? Sell items. Ancient book. But I don't.
I can turn this shit into stuff. That's not enough money. I mean, I could sell the sniper scope,
but no. That's a ton of range. No, I'm just going to buy. I got to make some money.
Let's just go. You have a few dungeons to go still that will earn you money. Well, how come?
Why was grandpa like, this is it. Yeah, this is the end of the game. No turning back now. Like
they did all that they used to do. Usually when you get that piece of dialogue and you say yes,
it's like locked in. You can't go anywhere. I got like a, you're at the end of the game, say yes
from grandpa. Should I not be concerned about them? He's an old bastard. Oh, well, what does
that have to do with anything? You're thinking of new Vegas. What? Yeah, I got those walls to break
too. These cats. Wow. That was in the game. Cool. All right, grandpa, I'm ready. Are you sure you
have all the equipment you need? This will be it. Slowing down. What? Wait, so I just have to,
he's going to die. I just have to go to the main gate. Oh, okay. Well, okay. Spend time with him,
you ungrateful fuck. I, stop. All right, so I have to go to the main gate and the main gate was in
over here in like the closer woods, right? I need to put on the other piece of gear, don't I?
I also have to put on the grenade launcher because that will take out the walls. I need the grand
grenade launcher. Drill is better for walls. I don't have the drill. All right. Main gate.
See what this does. We're here. Cats. Why are the cats everywhere? Look at this. The main gates
opened up. There's a door here. Are you going to go inside? I am going to go inside after I bring
Otto upstairs because he wants to come up. I'll be right back. Hello. He also had to poop. He has
been pooped. Gross. It was you that pooped. No, it wasn't. All right. Are you ready? Let's go.
All right. New place to fucking forget where everything is. Check. Where do I go?
I was going to say what? Oh, I'm going to change my, uh, let's put on. I need the range right now.
Let's do rapid. Yeah, there we go. Are you inside of a birthday cake? Oh, I should have, no,
I should have put on the, uh, I should have put on the vacuum, right? This looks like a Kirby area.
Are you just saying that because we said Kirby and Mega Man are
distant relatives, why would you need to farm money in the final dungeon?
Is this the final dungeon? Well, there's 10,000 zenny. Well, we get Mario 64 here. We have to
get like a special item to go down. Take it off. Take the shield off. Yeah, I can go there or I
can keep going down. Let's just wrap around first and see what's over here. Another door.
Oh no, I'm going out of range. Shit. Pretty good. Pretty good wireless signal so far though.
Fuck you too. You're live? The birthday cake spiral. All right, let's, there's two doors up
there. Let's just go. No, there is no crazy into you foe show here. Every single song cannot be
crazy into you. Crazy into you foe show, foe show. All right, it works, but like still,
just because it's a beat doesn't mean you can do that. Wink? Was there? All right, this is the
bottom. I'm going to wrap up and check the other stuff. There's one huge door. I'm not going to go
in the huge door yet. We're going to go into one of, there's two doors up here. It's probably money
and shit. Oh yeah, I have skates. Whoops. What's in here? Monsters. There's a big room. I don't see
any holes or anything. Do you? This is like a doom level. Like a Wolfenstein level. All right,
what is this? Please enter commands. Operate central gate. Unlock subsidies. OS voice warning.
Unlocking the subsidy entrances may cause a breach of security protocols.
Do you still want to unlock the subsidies? Uh, sure. Command acknowledged. Unlocking subsidy
entrances. The switch I just pulled deviated the portals to the living quarters. They should have
appeared somewhere on the island. What? Guess it's time to start looking for them.
Get a look for portals? What was the other thing I could do? Please enter command.
Operate central gate. Warning. The central gate has been locked by Eden. Activation requires manual
override for use of the watcher, sleeper, and dreamer keys. Hey, I thought that was blood on
the ground. Who is it? Okay, one of these dogs. That hurt a lot. I'm just trying to like aim and fire.
Hey, if it works. If it works. That's a lot of money. All right, so this place is huge. There's
three ways to go here. How about let's go, let's go over here. Is it going out? Uh, where the hell
does this go? Okay, so this is, this goes up, but where does it put me out? Oh, this is that old
city with the dogs. This is how you get in there. Okay. Remember the dogs? How would I get in here?
I guess you can't. There is no getting in. I mean, I could, could I get, could I even get out from
here? Good to know. Is there a big door? What the hell is this? Hey, what? This is not a boss, right?
Uh oh. Don't turn on, don't turn on. Why did I think that was the machine talking?
Well, to be honest with you, Tron, I thought you did die.
I'm not ready for a boss fight right now.
No, it's not time. It's time for me to go talk to the monkey and save the game.
My masterpiece. You're welcome to try and stop us, but you won't stand a chance this time.
See you. Thanks for waiting, Teasel. Let's go. Shit. Okay. Everyone ready? We're monsters.
Ah, okay. Let's make, let's make this eat good. Just lock in and focus. Maybe it just leaves.
It's just, it's here and it's big and has lots of weapons, lots of cannons and I don't even have,
what do I have for a buster parts? All right. Okay. I need range. Bad. This is just not going
to happen. Fucking useless item to have on right now. Wow. Okay. I don't even have that upgrade
to my black jacket. Uh, shit. And I can't leave this either. I mean, I, I'm going to,
I'm going to try. I'm going to try. All about you. Stop. That's not even accurate. I'll get it.
Just take it slow. It's not a race. What is that lock on? Shield repair. Jesus. I'm barely
doing any damage really, to be honest. I might be able to still do it. This auto lock is really
not doing me any favors at all. All right. I have the worst possible fucking special weapon
onto this. I have to like jump up and shoot, I think. Head. I guess the torso. Look out. Look
out. Look out. Look out. Stake. God, what a pain in the ass it is to hit this guy. What the fuck are
you aiming at? Dude. Okay. This game has it up. I'm just going to turn it off. It's just like
left shoulder, right shoulder, mid ground. Come on. I have maximum range. Oh,
why is some of those not hurting them? Right in the center. All right. What? What? Oh fuck.
He walked into it. Okay. Shield repair. I don't have any more. Why are you not hitting it again?
Like it just locked onto his shoulder and then it's just like, oh, you know, I don't want to do that
anymore. I'm going to stand on another house. Standing on house is best strategy so far.
Make it on top of this one. Nope. I need the house to stand on. Right here? Okay. Right here.
Oh, come on. What? That's such absolute horse shit. Like dog shit. Great aiming. Great lock-on
mechanic. It's fantastic. What is it doing? I can't even control where these bullets are going. It
just picks where it wants to shoot. It's like Mega Man's just guessing. I can't aim up. The game
automatically shoots where it wants to. Ah, I turned it off. I turned the fucking thing off.
What the fuck? I just turned it off. Why is it doing it still? What are you doing? Stop.
Come for those fucking grenades. Game. Why are you doing this? Shoot the spine? It just picks
randomly where it wants to shoot. He's going to break this building. I gotta go. Oh fuck. Oh fuck.
Stop shooting. Come down. Shoot him in the foot. Good. Great job. Aim at his spine and shoot him
in the foot. No, aim at his spine and like four out of ten shots are going to aim at his foot.
Just because I feel like it. I feel like shooting straight. Look at how far back this shit is too.
The active buster makes that fight a joke. I sure would have loved to have put it on.
Ah, but I was putting, I put on like the put on the
grenade launcher because I got to go break walls. Whoops. Here's the fucking boss. Now I'm going to
go kill him in probably less than 10 seconds. Hopefully he has two phases. So do I. All right.
What do I got? I'm going to keep the range on. Thankfully this is just walking a circle.
Turn around. Do the turn.
All right. Turn.
Have to defeat all enemies. Well, I want to get the money. I need zenny otherwise I can't upgrade
anymore. Oh yeah. I'll do it. All right. It's time to win. I'm going to make this an absolute joke.
Wait. No, this is the first. Oh, double door. There's two doors. What's in this box? That's
not hitting you. This music sucks. All right. Yeah. This, this song sucks. I'll get that to you.
This is a, this is a sample of the same three seconds. Buster unit omega.
This, it's pretty bad.
That's it. This did the whole song. Buster unit omega. Attack in range plus three. Holy shit.
Take off the sniper unit then. We're gonna max attack in max range. No energy though. No,
we'll keep on the blizzard. Max range, max damage, but slow shooting. Is there an energy and range
one? Energy and rapid attack and energy. Energy and range sniper unit. It'll be fine. It'll be
fine. It's bad. That's who cares. Looks cool too. All right. We're good. All right. Let's get going.
I'm starting. All right. I'm going to kill this motherfucker now. I'm just going to get in a good
spot and spam hoeing missiles at his chest and win. The ultimate in auto lock on. Smoke meth.
Don't smoke meth. Don't like, do not do that. That's like the worst thing you could ever do.
Unlock the gate. All right. I have to get the three keys. The watcher, the sleeper and the dreamer.
Unlock all the subsidies. Someone's calling me but I can't answer it.
Open the gates. Yes. The music's driving me nuts. All right. Okay. How much money would it take for
you to have two headphones in and have this song play over and over and over again without stopping
in your ears? Not like super loud, but loud enough where it's the only thing you can really hear.
For like six straight hours. 100 bucks? 500 bucks? 1000 bucks? People saying 2k?
Seven dollars? Why would you accept it? That's not worth it. All right. Let's go. No more fucking
around. Wait. A little bit more fucking around. There's other stuff in here that might help me
on my journey. Maybe just a little bit more fucking around. Got me stuck. I take a lot of damage from
this. Mega Man, Mega Man, Mega Man, Mega Man, Mega Man, Mega Man, Mega Man. You're dancing with
us right now? Keep it up. Shiny red stone. Good thing you're an idiot. All right. Don't be greedy.
Eventually comes through. This is a good chunk of change. I'm not. Should I? I think I'm gonna
upgrade. Don't be an idiot. You know what I mean? Like, don't be stupid. That's what I would say.
Is go get the, go get the upgrade. Go get the actual damage reducer. Who's over here? You hear
that? Yeah. Okay. Who is it? Oh, it's just a little guy. Hole and chest. All right. Nice. So,
I've explored. Auto fire barrel. Yeah. I mean, we got stuff too. I can run right to the boss very
quickly. Blunted drill. Didn't somebody say get drill, get drill, drill best item in game?
Because that's it. Somebody came in here and was like, dude, does he have the drill? He doesn't
have the drill. What a, what an idiot. I said that. Oh, what do you think? Should I just like go kill
boss? I think I can do it. What do you think? Go kill boss. Go kill boss. Let's go. I'm just gonna
do it. I'm fucking, no, no, no excuses. I'm doing it. Generator part. Let me just check up here.
This is a secret. Of course it's too bad. I don't have the thing that I had on before,
so I can't do this shortcut. Get your omega lulz ready chat. No, no, no, no, no, no. You get your
like, wow, he killed that boss in like 30 seconds and didn't take one point of damage. And one of
his eyes was closed. This is a pretty good grind spot actually, because these guys respond.
People are gonna be like, wait, hold on. I've been a Mega Man Legends fan for two decades. I didn't
even know you could do that to this boss. Yeah, let's fucking go. Let's go. Fuck it. Let's go.
Let's go. I'm doing it. I'm doing it. No, no, save. No, no, no, no.
Check this out. You know what I'm saying? Like, fuck it. You know what I'm saying?
I'm doing it. Let's do it. One, two, three, begin. It turns out the homing missiles are absolute dog
shit. They're not even aiming at it. Like, they're homing missiles. Why are they just going straight?
What? I didn't feel the canteen. Why is the canteen not filled? What's going on? Why is
the canteen not filled? I say, what? No, I'm like being dead serious. Why is the canteen at zero?
Did I not? Um, range. Oh my god. Unbelievable. Oh no fucking way. I really thought it was
going to be fucking easy. Oh, no way. That's so bad. Oh, this sucks. Absolute asshole. Nice fucking
lock on. Oh my god. I'm so fucking sad right now. Like, oh my god. You can't be serious.
That's un-fucking-believeable. I thought because I had the homing thing on it was going to be real
and I just upgraded its damage. Did I even upgrade the damage or what? Oh my fucking god.
Oh, this sucks. I thought it was going to be so easy with the homing missile and the damage upgrade.
Oh my god. That's so sad. I'm so actually sad. Oh my god. No. I have to go through that again.
Oh man. Why? Why? It's because auto-aim's not on? What? It's a homing missile. It's on.
Am I even going to finish this game in the next like hour and a half because of this shit? I can't
believe this shit. And now I have to go back to fill the canteen. Why is the canteen not filled?
Didn't I save it? Didn't I save the game before? When I filled the canteen up, I didn't come back
and save the game. What? I bought other stuff too. It's easily like three plus hours after this boss.
What? I thought I had like an hour left in the game. Well, how is the canteen already full?
I didn't refill it. Oh, it's because I bought the upgrade. Yeah, I'm streaming again tonight.
I'm streaming again tonight. I'm coming back after all my doctor shit and I'm going to
finish this fucking game. I'll be back. Not yet, but you know, I don't want to play this tomorrow.
We're doing black and white tomorrow. We're uh, all right, back in there. He hates this game so
he's streaming it twice in one day. No, it just, it's going to screw up the whole schedule for the
week if I don't finish it today. Oh no, I have to redo all these fucking upgrades. This sucks.
Actually, I can't even do it, can I? No, I can't even do it again. No, I did already do it.
Okay, sir. Save my game. You don't have to finish it. I'm at like the last two to three hours of
the game. I've got to finish the game. He's thinking about giving up. No, I'm responding.
I'm just, what? I'm responding to somebody that says give up and I said no, I'm not giving up.
I said the complete opposite of what you just said. Okay, we're going to do this smart. We're
going to do this fucking smart. Smart but quick. Are you ready? Smart but quick. Smart and quick.
I've got to beat it in 30 seconds. Oh yeah, I don't need to save. What the fuck, man? Don't,
this is, this game is 20 years old. Don't ever underestimate like the amount of random dumb
shit that can happen in a 20 year old fucking game. Like this is not, this is not like fall
into order where if I jump off the cliff, I just reappear instantly right behind where I fell off.
You know what I mean? Like, what am I thinking? It's 20 years old. They didn't give a shit 20
years ago. Sometimes I forget. I have to get all the items though. Open, open, open, open, open,
open, open. Turn the music off. You want to hear it for very much longer, I promise.
5,000 bits. $50 just came in. I gave $50. Jaredon, thanks for the 5,000 bits, dude.
That's a $50 bit drop. I just picked it up. Oh, these really are bits. Holy shit.
Okay, that's weird. How have I not made that joke the whole time? They say the reason the weapons
keep auto locking through his speed is because he has bomb cannons on his feet. Destroy those first
with your mega buster before you use the homing missiles. You have to shoot them from the front
to hit them. Mega buster. Uh, good tip. Good tip. Thank you. And thanks for the huge amount of money.
All right, where is it? I want to take off. Uh, there it is. Oink. Max attack, max range.
You suck, omega low. Wait, did I get everything in that room? Was there a hole?
You stink. Can you guys start, instead of saying you suck, omega low, can you guys just start doing
you stink with auto? You stink. That's, I like that more. Can you do that, Noah? Can you do that
instead? Uh, I'm going back up. I just have to turn off the gates too. Let me do that first.
And I'm going to come back and save it. Don't worry. And now I don't, I don't have to worry
about, um, I don't have to worry about time constraints because I'm just going to come back
and fucking finish the damn game. Is this the first time I'm ever going to do a double stream
in the same day? There's like two streams, two separate streams. Have I done that before?
The switch I just pulled should have activated the portals to the living quarters. First one that's
not an internet issue, yeah. It should have appeared somewhere on the island.
Guess it's time to start looking for them. Let's fight this guy. Look, a lot of money too. I'm
preparing. There's like 20,000, $30,000 down here. I'm going to get it. And I'm going to, yeah, yeah,
be smart about this. I want the items. There's like two items down here. It's like a shiny stone.
Can a dog eat a lemon? I don't, I don't fucking know. Probably no. I'll probably not. Don't give
me a dog. Why are you giving a dog a lemon? Don't do that. What are you talking about?
I don't know. Why are you asking me?
Not a problem. I beat this game when I was six. No, you didn't.
If I was like sports betting on the fact if you beat this game and you were six,
I would put every cent I own on it. You rented this game from Blockbuster when you were six
and got past the first tutorial level and then went to bed. And then your mother returned it
two days later. That's what happened. That's what happened to all of us. So come on.
This is what happened. Don't go in that door. Did I miss anything else? All right. Well,
there was an item. Um, all right. Time to go back. Okay. Yes. That door, that door, left door,
left door. What, what, what? This door, left door, left door. VR Josh, I'm trusting you with my life
here. Why am I going in this door? Is this left door's items? All right. Liar? Liar. Did you lie
to me? No, you didn't. Thank God. What a trustworthy individual. VR Josh is a known liar.
No, no, he's not. I can't do that. All right. We're good. Save the fucking game.
Save the fucking game. VIP that guy. No, don't. Okay. Hold on. I have to get out of this.
Escape. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I think he's going to hit me with a flame
throw. She's crying. Jesus Christ. Somebody said it and it makes me laugh. All right. Saving games.
I don't care. Just get me out. Just give me the big ones. Fast and smart. Wait, isn't this going,
this is going down. I knew I was going to run into that guy.
Okay, here we go. Dumb and slow. Can I make any new items? Here you go Mega Man. The blunted drill
is used to make drill arm. You can't use it in combat unless you get right next to your opponent.
I don't know. Maybe you can think of another good use for it. Auto fire and generator part we use
to make the buster part auto battery. This part will increase the number of shots you can fire
once to the max. With this you can fire a constant stream of energy. Oh shit, really?
Wait, no, I don't want to do the Mega Man voice acting line thing. Let me check it out.
All right, so this is energy, attack and range, attack, attack and range. So could I, let's see,
where is it? Auto battery. I mean, that's, let's see. I can't even test it. I think I want to try
it. All right, the game has been saved. How much money do I have? 36. That's just enough. That is
just enough to get the flak jacket. $36,000, just enough. Save again after you buy the jacket. I will.
I won't forget. It reminds me of like a dentist drilling my teeth. I don't like that noise.
Here we go. Kevlar jacket. Done. There's another one. Kevlar jacket Omega.
Canteen is full. It's equipped, right? Toilet seat. Now he's broke. Yep. Take us back to the
runes, save the game. We'll take us back to the runes, then save again. And I'm going for it.
Take us to the main gate. Okay. It's time. It's time. Have I checked the museum? Some of that stuff
goes to the museum. I don't know where the museum is. Memory card. Let's go kill this boss. Let's
go kill this boss. I'm ready. I have the damage reducer. I'm just going to get over there. I opened
up these, those sub gates already, right? Real wink. Take wink. Whatever. All right, here we go.
Smart, quick, fast, and to the point. Quick, fast, and to the point. I'm ready. No more excuses.
It's time to like drink a Pacific Gatorade and do this. Remember, shoot the cannons on the boots
first. You got it. What's going on? Okay. This like, this fucking lip is, that's what's going on. The
lip there. I love how the camera does that too. Kill that boss in 30 seconds. This guy sucks. All
right. Am I even hitting the cannons on his feet? I'm still doing it. What am I doing? I'm listening
to the one person that said to destroy the cannons on his feet first. Did I not listen to the one
person who told me to do it? Here goes one. My God, why? Auto lock is turned off. Shoot the, what the
fuck, Mega Man? Shoot the thing on his foot. What are you fucking aiming at? Dude, shoot.
It's on his foot. Shoot his foot. What the fuck, Mega Man? It's just, what do you want me to tell
you? How do I, what do you want me to tell you? What do you want me to say? Sorry, but I'm going
to apologize for this. I told you it was going to take 30 seconds. No. Stupid. I told you it was
going to work. He was right. Nobody talked shit about the one guy. He was right. It was shooting
at the cannons on his feet and homing on them. Okay, Blue. You must know. What's your name?
Me? My name is Mega Man. Mega Man Volnut. Mega Man, is it? You know, I've been in this business
a long time, but this is the first time anyone's ever given me this much trouble. Yet it feels
good somehow being bliss, almost as though I've met my match. I can face the facts. I lost. You
won. I'm going to try to beat this guy before he stops saying this. To say that feels as clean as
the blue sky on a cloudless day. See you around. Which one's Tron and which one's Bon? Both?
I'll never see him again. Okay, that's Tron. Once he finds the treasure, we'll wait for our
chance and take it from him. What? I was going to just walk away, did you? It's a full name.
You bet it is. Old Teasel never gives up. So it's Teasel Bon, Tron Bon, and Bon Bon.
Did I get any money for that? I don't think I even got any money for that.
All right, so now, um, let's go. Let's go. What the fuck is this? No, no, no, no, no.
Security breach detected. Unauthorized exit not permitted.
What? I can't leave? Why? I just want to, I just opened the door. Oh no. What happened? Why?
What do you mean I can't leave? Oh, okay. Just play good. I'm going to be very careful.
It's not about the money right now. It's about surviving. It is about money. Who the fuck am I
kidding? Did I get it? Um, where am I? I would be taken though. In here, this building looks
different. So how do I get inside? I don't know. How do I get out and save the game?
I have to clear this dungeon to leave. No, I don't. Do I? No, I don't. I don't say that.
It would mean the whole thing. Or just here. All right, I'm going to, I'm going to be such
a coward this whole time. No risks, no mistakes. I'm going to be the ultimate coward. Do I still
have shield repair? I don't. I don't. But I do have, um, it's like four health bars to heal.
No. Yeah, that's fine. You can call me a mega coward if you want. I'm not relining like 45
minutes. Oh my God. All right, where do I want to go from here? I got to get in that building.
This one looks different than the other. It's probably the guy I jump in like the top or
something, right? Jump in the top. This building looks different. I can go in the top. Just say
it Mega Man. Help me. This one looks different than all the others.
Isn't there another enemy? There's one more guy. Where's this, where's this one guy?
Oh, I hit one guy. Spam it. Spam it. I can leave, right? Okay.
Shit, there's a dog blocking the door. All right, get me out of here. Get me out. I want to get out.
I need to go, uh, west. I missed weapons. Don't worry. I'll be back. I'm going back there anyways.
Can I go west from here? Go west from here. Mega Man has lilies on. Uh, sometimes.
Wait, is there a way to get out of here? All right, come pick me up and heal me and
fill up the canteen and go back there. Pick me up. Item dab. Got some new stuff. Nothing.
I hope you're ready to do that again because you, you didn't do the reward. That's fine. I mean, I,
the save point I have is before I fought the last boss. So that takes priority over anything.
Checking, saving. I'm all right. That, that didn't, that wasn't too bad. Do that again.
All right. What about, what do I, what do I have for money? 13,000. Not enough. We have to keep
going. So we're going to go east. Back where I was. Excuse me. Whoa, Mega Man in 3D. What the fuck?
Yep. I know. It's pretty spectacular. And then from here, we got to go,
where was it? North? Was it right here? No, it was over here, wasn't it?
Wasn't it, was it north or was it south? I think it was south. Oh, it was just right here. Oh,
it was just right here. Yeah. Some reason I thought there was another place to go.
All right, here we go. Stay up here. I have maximum range.
I don't care. It's fine. Everybody's my friend. Thank you. More money, more money, more money.
Hello. Real Wink? Liars. You idiots cried wolf too many times.
The boy, the boys who cried Wink. Guys, they made nursery rhymes about this shit. Like,
haven't you figured it out by now? Come on. There's one more tank. Where was that tank?
Is there somebody else on top of a building? No. I hear him. Where was he? I just heard him.
He's like hiding over here somewhere. Oh, there's one over there.
Controls this game look so funky. They are. It's, it's R1 and L1 to turn. And then obviously forward
and back, left and right. Now I can, I could have it left and right be turned, but I tried it and it
was, it just didn't feel right. Free analog controls. Yeah. All right. What's this last
thing? Yeah. It's really, it's, it's the, it's the turning that's the worst, but it's okay. It's not
like the worst thing in the world. The only, really the only time where it's bad is when that enemy
was flying around all over the place. It's like R1, L1, R1. Ooh. Your brain, like at this point
playing this many games without doing this, doesn't want to do it. Double wink. All right.
Where's his last person? All right. Anybody see anybody? You? Over here? Oh, there you are.
It's like hiding over here. Why are you not even moving around? A noise was just made. Something
happened. Ooh. You found the watcher key. Got it. To the surface. Oh, so that's what you mean when
you guys said you just have to go in and get it. But I thought it could have been another dungeon.
That's all it is. Okay. All right. I need two more of those. Tell the other side. This is,
there's another door here, right? Is this going this one? Did I go in here? This is where I was
before. Can I go down any further? I actually forget where the other subsidies are. Well,
it says that just around the world, like the town, right? Just join. This game sucks.
How would you know that if you just got here? Hey, just opened up the browser. Hey, this game sucks.
Really? You haven't even seen it. What did I just say? Load twitch.tv. The Samsung Galaxy Galaxy S1
2. Buy a 5 second, 15 second Twitch ad. This game sucks. No, you didn't even see it.
You never rebuilt the city? No, I don't have any money for that. Oh, look. Save it. You guys think
I have money to rebuild the city? I need to like take care of me so I can beat the monsters and
then I'll take care of the city. Put your oxygen mask on first before putting another oxygen mask
on to another passenger. If I'm going to, I take care of, there's people attacking the city still.
I have to do that. I'm going to come back and I'm going to rebuild. This monkey is punchable? Why?
What? It's the super monkey ball monkey. What are you talking about? All right. Let's go. Here we go.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Okay, I'm done. I'm just trying to like make it over exaggerated.
I did that anyways. I don't have to like pretend. Push. Okay. Pay attention. He's having fun again.
Bog. I was having fun the whole time. Just fucking stupid and can't pay attention to anything.
You're a pain in the ass. You're a pain in the ass. How much of a pain in the ass do you have to
be? I'm going to the building. Oh my god. That's max attack. Pain in the ass. Should I like over
react the fuck out of everything going on right now and like if somebody trickles into the screen,
they're going to think I'm like a fucking herd. All right. All right. All right. Fuck. Whoa, whoa,
whoa. Guy behind. Whoa. Oh my god. What the fuck? Okay. Oh, I got it. Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it.
Oh, he's coming out. Oh no. Come on. I got to get the items. This guy dropped. I didn't get any.
Oh, whoopsie. Fuck. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This is kind of normal though, isn't it? It's just like, isn't this like kind of normal?
It's like I do this. I like do this stuff. There's no difference. I do this shit. Not like that
ridiculous, but I've like done that before. Uh oh. No pretending anymore.
I thought it was normal. How do you like, how do I overreact more than me overreacting all the time?
Like, especially when it was like that. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I think I did that like
three days ago. All right. This guy's actually going to kill me. Well, nobody even joined the
stream. So, hey, there you go guys. I hope you thought that was interesting. Not one person
trickled into the stream. I didn't even do that for any reason. Wait, hold on. I can fix this.
Give me a second. I can fix this. Trust me. You're going to want to wait for this one.
Go like this. Hold on a second. I'll fix it. It has to be a little bit pixelated though.
Now I got to get this mapped in my stream deck. Important. Just trust me. I'll fix it. Okay.
Okay. All right. So, that's good. Okay. Dude, this guy is fucking stupid. Did it work? Okay.
Oh. Oh, shit. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Okay, guys. I've got to fight this guy.
No, no, no, no, no. No, no, no. Watch out. Watch out. He's behind me. Behind me. Behind me.
Yeah. Yeah. That's, now that's what I'm talking about. Get destroyed, idiot. Guys, guys. I don't
think that we have a chance at all here. Oh, I got him. Cool. Cool. Cool. Anymore? Are there any,
are there any more? Are there any more? I never understood that. Why? Why does every YouTube video
now with the face cam have to go like fucking this and zoom into their face? Like every five seconds.
Why? And it's not even like a zoom. It's actually like pulled and stretched webcam like this.
You just got plus 40 viewers. Like, why, why do we all do this? Wait, this is in my last video?
This is, wait, this is in my last video? Wait, hold on a second, guys. Whoa. This is in my last
video. Wait a minute. I got to, I got to have to speak to those editors. This is,
all right. Where's this last person? You need to react. No reactions. Anybody see anybody? Ah,
found you. Do something funny. Wait. No, no, I didn't. I know that that's real though. That's me.
Guys, I do that shit when I do the laundry. If like a sock drops, I go like, oh shit.
I have like ADHD, neurotic. Like that's just who I am. That's me. I'm not making that up.
He's an IRL tuber. Don't you have a doctor's appointment? Yeah, I'm all right. I got time.
One more. So where's this last hole? Are you prepared? Are you prepared? Oh, I love that.
Are you prepared? And sometimes it goes, are you like, they just cut off immediately. I love it.
Are you prepared? Are you prepared? We don't know what I'm talking about. I mean, I'm a little
neurotic. You know, that's what we do here. Fringe monkey, cringe monkey. What? Why is he's dancing?
Come on. Give me a break. What are you talking about? What's wrong with everybody? Let him dance.
He is dancing. He's fine. I'm fine. My appointment's not, I got plenty of time. Don't worry.
If I don't finish this in the next like 30 minutes, then whatever. I'll come back. I'll turn the
stream on in like a few hours. That's not a joke, by the way. That's actually going to happen.
All right. So is there one here? No, I'm not playing this tomorrow. So if I can't beat this
before my appointment, I'm just going to come back and finish it later. We're doing black and
white two tomorrow. The return of Murius. I don't see. Is it here? Somebody said the check report
out here. You know what shirt you have to wear tomorrow? No, I don't. Up here somewhere in
Uptown. But where? Let's skate around and find out. All right. If I get hit by a car while
searching, I will, I will give 500,000 community subs. All right. I'm like fucking scared.
I'm going to stop. All right. I just passed it. I just went fired. That's, that's like fucking
50 million dollars or something. No, I saw it. I knew where it was. Who's here is going to pop
in gamer. Did I save it? Yes. All right. Good. We have a boss battle. Oh, it's a giant centipede.
You're going to shoot it in the butt. Absolutely need to shoot it in the butt. I don't have this
singled out in my mind that you don't shoot it. They mean right there in the butt and it's back
or whatever it is. Yep. Easy. Oh, this little dinky guy over here got me.
This is grind city. I just take the vacuum. Just do this forever. Right? Right? It's free money.
There's not much money from these guys. Wait, not much money from these guys at all.
Game doesn't even hold up 20 years later. Unbelievable.
Easily getting overwhelmed here without being able to shoot at the thing.
I feel like I need a grenade launcher for this. That's not a terror. That's pretty good actually.
I didn't pick up any of it, but it was still pretty good. If I had the vacuum, I would just be like,
I'd just suck it all up right now. Oh, let's do something else. You're behind me. Oh, he is.
All right. Oh, come on. What's with those pixels? Don't kill it. Please. Whoa. All right.
They're still here. I really needed the vacuum for this. Those other people were okay. We've got
tuber DNA. I mean, I did YouTube videos for like six years.
And then I did Twitch for like five. I've been on that. That's 11 years. That's not real.
All right. I got all the keys. Now I go. Go back to that. I know where that is.
Am I going to finish this before I have to leave? Well, maybe if I play well.
This is the end game for your information. There's a lot to do if you want, but it's optional.
Well, I'll come back and we'll finish it all up and clean it up. That's fine.
I'm all right with that. This level is ugly. There's a mini game at the TV station. All right.
We've been waiting for you. You're one of the contestants for our hit show, Dangerous Games.
I'm not a contestant. Hey, you look like you're a pretty good runner. Do you want to try out for
my show? It's a race through the city streets. What do you say? Yeah, sure. Great. Come on then.
Let's go. Do you want to hear the rules? Yes. This game is a timed race through the city streets.
The object is to pass through the course marked by the red cones within the time limit.
Yellow cones are bonus cones. Knock them over as you're running and the clock will stop for a
short while. You win if you finish the course within the time limit. Okay. Three courses,
four ranks. I get it. I get it. I get it. Uh, straight course. I didn't even need to get the
other cone. A thousand zenny. Go to the left curve course. 15 seconds. Are you ready?
Okay. Yeah. Technical course. 25 seconds.
Fuck. Did I miss it? What? No, I didn't. Look at how tiny that is. I'm gonna lose. Oh, I did it.
No, I didn't. I'm gonna have to memorize this whole course. I didn't miss one, right?
Hey, what are you doing? Just walk. Okay. 3000. Now it's time to go back to the straight course.
10 seconds. I'm gonna do all. No, don't do them all in a row. I have to get them down.
Yes, it does. All right. This is a lot of money. Do it again. B, eight seconds. I have to get a
couple of the cones. Ooh, that was close. All right. Now I have to get all the cones. I gotta
get them all in one go. A, seven seconds. I gotta get both cones. Why don't I get them on the left
reliably? I think I'm live again. Oh, hi. Refresh. I'm sorry. I don't know what just happened. I think
we just dropped. Time for your appointment. No, no, no. We're fine. You'll know when it's
time for me to go. Whoa, that was close. Oh, I didn't get it. I didn't get it. This is the
second stream. Oh, yeah. He's live. He's live. He's live. This is not the second stream. Oh,
come on. I was trying to cut the corner. Got it perfect. Hold up. All right. I just did,
and I'm going left and right. I'm holding up as moving my character left and right.
That is a lie. Why did I even listen to that? For some reason I was like, maybe that's real.
Oh, how do I catch that? How am I supposed to catch this? I feel like I'm not even faster
to go through this straight. Damn, what? Holding should make you go faster. Yeah,
I have a D-pad. I was just doing. When I push up the character, he turns left and right.
Let me just, I need to take him. Let me see. Hold on a second. No, that doesn't do anything.
It actually doesn't do anything. Does holding down make me turn sharper? Let's find out.
Oh, not really. I mean, it should. If I do.
I just went slower. So why is up not working? I just cut the corner better.
We are Josh, the liar. What do I get? Music box. Please enter a name. Oh, okay. That's
I get it. I get it. Left curve. This is going to suck. Oh, come on. I got to get this done.
It's going to take me a little while. Nine seconds. So it's wrap around and then it's
bang bang. All right. Yeah. You got, you got to cut the corner a little higher
and then you have to go through here and then strafe. What's the A goal? Probably seven seconds.
Who cares? Duh. All right. I just did that. I did it in seven. I'm just eight. Let's do it again.
YouTuber. That was it. I do that shit when I do my laundry. I promise. What do I get? You win
Omni unit. Okay. Here we go. Technical course. This is going to be hard. It's going to be tighter
than that. Oh, it's going to be really tight. That one's going to be hard too. Oh, this one's
going to be fucking hard. I mean, we say this one is not what we do. I got, I got
really, really difficult and you got to get this one and now it's going to pull down to like 15
seconds to I'll give it a few more times and then I actually have to leave. That's so tight. I got
to hold. I don't even know what I have to hold down. I have to like actually cut that super hard.
All right. Last attempt. Yeah. I'm holding right and R1 when I turn so it's a tighter turn.
That's what I'm doing. All right. That's not bad. Oh, okay. So the end is really the problem now.
I might be a little, I might be all right. Try it again. It's that last
column that's going to be hard to hit. Oh, sorry. Sorry. Okay. What's A? 17 seconds. I can do this.
60. I can do this. Let's go. Oh, I fucked it up. It's okay. Sorry. I actually pushed in the left
stick. I screwed it up. Oh, fuck you. All right. Not you. This. Give it. I still get it. Oh, man.
Oh, if I had hit the cone, that would have been it. If I had hit that first cone, that would have
been it. No, no, no, no, no, no. Oh, you got to go like bang, bang. You got to like rip left,
rip right. That's the worst one. Nope. I kind of screwed it up. Sorry. I was late doc. I was
streaming Mega Man Legends. This is it. I'm going to complete this and I'm going to leave
and I'll come back later. Oh, that was almost perfect. I wish I could practice this
that part up here where you go like, no, as long as I leave here in about 15 minutes.
Damn it. Oh, fuck. It's so painful because if I hit it, I might hit the cone next to it too.
Really? This is your doctor. I believe you have an appointment with me in five minutes. All right.
Let's do it. Can we do it over the webcam? But I don't need to be there. Like, what's the
difference? It was a little sloppy near the end. At least I hit the cone. Nope. Already a failure.
If it is not pixel exact, you have to start over. All right. I'm actually doing spring more attempts
than I have to go to the doctor and I'll be back. I'll be back at like, probably like maybe six,
30 specific to finish. Oh, you mother fucker. Mother fucker. It was there. It was, that was the
one fucking frame. Perfect dog shit. All right. One more time. One more, one more, one more,
and I'll come back later. This one sucks. Oh, what? What was wrong with that? What was wrong
with that one? That was like perfect. What? Oh, is that not enough? It was right there.
No. Get out of here, John. Giant horn. What do these do? You're allowed to leave now. Yeah,
I'm allowed to leave. Tell the doctor. You should have seen it. I got 15.7 seconds
in the Mega Man Legends final tactical course. All right. Let me get out. Save the game. Okay.
So, uh, this is part one. I will see you guys. I'm not going to do the bits because technically
the stream's not over. It's just taking the pause. So, I will be back in a few hours and we'll
finish. But first, let me see what this is. Nothing. So, I will see you guys at around six, 30.
Let's say six, 30 Pacific. I'll be back. Don't be late to the doctor. I won't be. Don't worry.
Put up the BRB screen for three hours. No. No, that's so bad. No, I can't do that. No way.
No, that's weird. I don't like, I don't want a BRB screen up for three hours. That's so bad. No.
I don't think I even can do that. I think Twitch will turn the stream off.
I'm pretty sure like after like an hour or two, Twitch will turn, will turn me off.
I'm not sure I'm even allowed to do that. No, no, no, no, no, no. It's going to be too long.
It's going to be at least three hours from now. I'm not going to leave a BRB screen up.
No, I'm not doing that. You just need a timer that goes down. No, but what if I'm not back?
No, no. Goodbye. I'll see you guys in a couple hours. Goodbye. I'll be back. No, what if like,
what if I get stuck somewhere? What if I can't, what if there's a snowstorm and I can't leave
the doctor? All right. I'll see you guys in a couple hours. Part two incoming. How do I end
the stream? Just turn it off? Take it in a couple hours.