Everybody run. Run, run as fast as you can. Something about the gingerbread man. There's some line there.
Hey, but hi, welcome everybody. This is Cactus Canyon. This is the, uh, I guess improved Cactus Canyon.
If you remember the last time we played on this map, the, that is a spy, and he exploded, so we're okay.
But if you remember on Cactus Canyon last time, my last video, there was no way to conceivably, like, get through this choke point
unless, of course, you went straight through the choke point. So now they added a little thing to the top left here.
If I could, I don't want to pull, no, pull the shotgun out, you dipshit.
No! No! They added a little thing here. I can't even speak. Speak words, Jerma, speak words. Use your words.
Uh, they added a thing in the top left. There we go. That wasn't so hard, was it?
So now it's not just ridiculous people going through the choke. And there's a spy there. Who's on this cart? Oh, nobody, of course.
Nobody. Nobody. But I need to run. I need to get back in the water. Maybe get this medic to heal me. That would be fantastic.
You might be, yes, you are, in fact, a spy. No, you're not. I need my glasses checked.
You know, go see my local ophthalmologist. Go get a new prescription.
Sometimes your eyes aren't that good. My eyes are pretty bad, but that's a different story.
Hello, scout. Oh, medic, medic, medic, please. There we go. Surprise. That was a double.
Whoo. Whoo. More medic help. I love you. Be careful. Don't let them push.
We only, we only got eight and a half more minutes. Might sound like a lot, but watch out behind you.
Don't let them. Please, please let me get that shot. I almost messed that all up.
And yes, this is, hey, hey, just everybody chill. I got a pretty good streak going here.
I don't want to mess it up with any stupid moves, but we're going to get this demo man that went around this way.
And he doesn't even know we're chasing him. Oh, there's plenty of people over here.
Please, please. I just got that medic killed. That's a dead ringer for sure.
People are just everywhere. I'm in trouble. This is the end. This is the end for me. That's the end for me.
I died. Set up three seconds. What the fuck is going on here? Three sec. What?
Okay. I, there's a train. There's a train here now. What? And they just get to sit on the point.
All right. I'm pretty confused. Was there always a train here? I don't, was there?
This is cool if there wasn't. I don't remember a train. Damn it. Damn it.
They're going to cap the second point already. They're already going to get this second point.
And I, for one, am just all over the place with my shots. It's not going good right this second.
But at least we have that going for us. That is crazy. There's a, there's a legit train that comes down here.
Cool. Cool. I like it. And where am I even going? Yeah. Okay. So they come from over here.
I'm, for some reason, I am just totally confused at everything. I'm like a toddler right now.
I'm just seeing shapes and colors and going like, oh, look at those. They're cool.
Whoa. Crit Scree. That's a Crit Scree that I wasn't prepared for. That's a Crit Scree that I wasn't prepared for.
But it's okay. We'll get some money. We'll get some money out of it. We'll get the money's worth somehow.
And where are they spawning? Over here? Okay. I knew you were going to reflect that.
That's why I prepared for it. I trained for it. Don't notice me. Do not. How did you know I was here?
Everybody just move out of the way. Damn. I wonder what else they're going to add to this.
There must be a couple of other things that they're going to add. I'm not sure. Who knows?
Who knows what Valve has up their sleeve? They probably got like an ace or two.
When was the last time Valve used an ace? You know, I mean, we've seen some, we've seen some queens, we've seen some kings.
But when's, when's the next TF2 ace? I wonder. Please tell me you don't have a whole lot of health. You didn't.
There's like spies just like running around back here. Don't let, don't let him trick you.
He absolutely is not dead.
Man, we're going to hold this for a long time.
He said, damn man. Can we just, can we? Please. I knew you were going in that room, huh?
Just quit jumping around. It's not like time for cardio right now. Get, I'm making quite a few like exercise references here for some reason.
He just launched that back. He did, didn't he?
All right. Nobody, nobody do anything crazy. I need to refill myself.
I need to fill myself up with some delicious red beams.
There we go. Let's go. And let me get an overheal too.
Let me get an overheal. Just did damage to myself. Fantastic.
Well, you're real miraculously. You know what? I don't know what's over there.
I feel like there's a sentry right there, but you know, I don't know. I've been wrong many, many times before.
They're all up here. Okay. I got you.
Sorry. I'm being like silent right now. I just don't want to get smashed by something.
Can we open this? No, that's the train.
Hey, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't.
Oh, don't shoot that back. You know what? I'm going to be safe here.
Let's be safe here. Anybody else? Come on.
Somebody walk into that. Ah, somebody could have walked into that.
I'm sorry. I'm like never prepared for this guy's crit screes.
I'm always like in the middle of like a reload animation.
Where'd he go? Where'd he go?
Damn it. He didn't die from the fall damage.
And now I'm going to die from this pyro unless I can somehow keep myself healed with this.
And you are a lifesaver and you died for me.
And we both died, but at least I got the pyro.
We just cannot have that right in his face.
Stand back. Stand back. Stand back.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Uh, well, I did, I did get a couple of them.
I did do some work there. It wasn't all for nothing.
Maybe somebody's going to hear. I, I, can I just say I love maps with crazy hazards like this.
Because somebody always gets smashed by it. It's just like the saws in Sawmill.
It's just like the train that is in that train map.
I forget the name of it. I want to say freight, but I don't want to be like totally wrong.
Did I just, no, I thought I got a double kill there, but no, it was just a domination.
Get the health. You're safe.
There is a big sentry up there and that just is not going to happen.
We just cannot have that. We cannot have that right now, but what is that guy doing?
Come on. This is pyro. It's pyro mania.
It's pyro mania all over again.
They're going to call it. That cut is like landed on a pane of glass.
Oh, they're going to get it. I think we're going to lose.
I think we are going to lose this.
As much as I don't want to say it, I think it's possible.
It's like four people. Three people just get hit by the train.
How many people were on blue?
Hopefully more people on blue get hit by the train. I'm not even going to deal with you.
Get on top of the, I don't even know where I am right now.
I can't let you do that. I got backstabbed.
Swear.
I'm just going to scream a swear word right now.
Poop.
Watch out.
There's that. Where is this? Where does it go now?
Why do I not know this?
What is it doing?
I really can't believe I don't know what this is, what's happening right now.
Have I only played on one part of this game, of this mode or something?
Am I just crazy?
I wish that critscreek was here right now.
I'll tell you that.
It's no secret.
Oh, they're going to get it.
I didn't realize it was that close.
Didn't realize it was that close. Somebody, please.
We're going to lose. Game over.
He pushed him off.
What a hero.
Don't let this medic get it.
Come on.
Heroes.
You guys are heroes.
I love it.
I got to whip somebody. Let's go.
Quick, quick, quick, quick. Get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out.
Oh, there's no possible way.
We're going to keep this going for another six, seven minutes.
What is going on?
Is it going backwards?
Oh, what? It was going backwards, right?
What does a sentry up there?
Okay, that is...
I'm...
I don't have any words.
Words can't be expressed. Where does it cap?
Where's the actual cap point here?
Because like, seriously, I am...
Is it goes around a circle?
Okay. No, it stops right there.
And it just falls off.
Okay.
This whole video, I think I'm going to like... No, no, no.
Oh, it gets hit by the train.
It has to get hit by the train?
That's awesome.
Okay, now my confusion is over.
But that's really, really cool.
And yeah, that might be the end of the video.
I think it is.
Thanks everybody so much for watching. Really do appreciate it.
This has been Jerma is Confused at Everything
in the updated Cactus Canyon map.
Take care everybody. Have a nice day.
Goodbye.