Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here again with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
This time I'm gonna continue the series I started a while back called One Life, where I showcase One Life from One Class.
You guys know the deal. Show you something cool, show you a good kill streak.
As you can see on the screen, playing as the Engineer with the default Sentry Gun, the Frontier Justice and the Short Circuit.
And let me just tell you that I max out the Frontier Justice crits and I put them to very good use.
I'm pretty lucky that I was recording during this particular gameplay because sometimes I don't.
Sometimes I just kind of want to play for fun and I don't want to record.
Don't want to have to worry about the pressure of recording, but I'm glad I did because this is a great gameplay.
So let's get started. No more talking about nonsense. Here we go.
Level 3 Sentry is now built up to completion and let me just tell you quickly, this is a great spot to put a Sentry Gun on defense.
Only because it's the turning point of the cart and at least the first time that people come around this area here,
the first time they take this turn, they're not going to expect it because the point cap is right there.
They're thinking about capping the point. They're not thinking about turning around and having a Sentry Gun there.
That's a Spy. My Medic told me to turn around at the right time.
Thank you because that would have ended right there and this gameplay would not exist.
So props to good, aware Medics, huh?
Speaking of which, watch what happens here.
Sentry gets sapped and I try to go for the Spy for a second or two, but it doesn't matter.
That Medic gets the kill with the Ubersaw.
So fantastic job, Medic. You really saved my ass at least two times in this gameplay.
So thank you very much.
Putting a Teleporter up now, I don't really do anything with it.
I forgot when I came out of the gate to put a Teleporter up,
which is something I don't normally do because Engineer is my number one played class,
except maybe for Spy, but Engineer is my pretty much bread and butter class.
So me doing that, when I realized it, I said, Oh God, terrible Engineer. I don't even have a Teleporter.
People are going to yell at me, but it didn't even matter. We ended up crushing them anyways.
So just sitting here whacking the Sentry.
I turned the corner because there was really no action going on right now,
so I wanted to see where the enemy team was.
Turn the corner. They are coming up here pretty soon.
Coming back, just whacking the Sentry more and more, get another kill.
This is kind of what you do as an Engineer.
You kind of sit back and you let the enemies come to you while you play your guitar
and you watch your TV and you eat your TV dinners at the same time.
That was terrible, but watch this.
This is ridiculous. Look at how many Spies there were here.
I thought that was an eternal reward Spy on their team
because he backstabbed that Spy who looked like he was on our team
and turned into that Spy. It's just ridiculous.
And then there was another Spy that was just de-cloaking.
If you want to watch that back, I put it in slow motion so you can see it a little better and more clearly.
I don't think I'll ever see something like that ever again.
Just three Spies just stabbing each other and walking into each other at the same time.
So my Sentry is racking up a lot of kills.
Nine kills and two assists at the moment right now.
Me and this Medic are kind of just hanging back here alone.
So I told the Medic, I said, don't run out there, don't get yourself killed.
There's a Mini-Sentry, there's a bunch of people.
Because take a look over yonder, the rest of the team is back there.
So we're kind of down here by ourselves and finally a Pyro comes back here.
But look, pretty much no man's land back here.
And then a Demo Knight comes out of nowhere.
I thought he was going to kill the Medic and a Spy.
The Medic ubers me to save my life for like the third time in a row.
Coming out here just because I wanted to make something happen, try to cause some chaos.
The Sentry goes down unfortunately, but take a look at the lower right-hand corner.
29 crits, here we go.
Time to cause complete and total chaos.
She thought this was so funny.
This was a friend of mine, Lydia, that's the Medic by the way.
I was cracking up, she was cracking up.
It was a great time, just having fun.
29 crits.
I think the maximum is 29, I don't think you can get further than that.
Valve put a cap on it so you can't just sit there with like 400 crits for an entire round.
29's the cap, I think I only shoot 11 or 12 rounds just because I get myself killed.
After about 4 kills or 5 kills, I take my final shot on that Scout, but I die.
And that's the one life as the Engineer on Hoodoo guys.
Thank you so much for watching, I really appreciate everybody that views the videos.
Take care everybody, I'll see you all soon. See you later.