Asperdergo, no, that's not my name. My name is Captain Blackbeard. I can't fix it. I can't- what? I can't be Captain Blackbeard, I can be Captain Blackbear. That's not happening.
I've decided to change my name, ladies and gentlemen. For reasons unbeknownst to anybody, I'm now going to be Captain Humphreys.
His teeth are so white. That's not a pirate. Pirates don't have bright white crest commercial teeth. No, seriously, this guy's teeth are like perfect.
What about this guy's teeth? They're great. This is fucking up my immersion.
Okay. Are you ready for the pirate to attack with his dual blades?
Yeah, I mean, I guess I could attack you with these. Yeah, whatever. I don't know. I just kinda don't care.
Did I get you? Did I get you? I'll just keep walking.
See, these are like the redcoats. It's the British. The British are coming. Tell Paul Revere.
You British need to leave our lands at once.
What? He doesn't know I'm right here?
What are they doing to that poor guy? That guy's gonna get... What is happening right now?
Is that a chicken? What are these chickens? Dude, look at these giant chickens. Oh, that's a turtle.
I thought it was like a turkey. I thought it was a turkey. Hi, I'm Mr. Assassin Creed Man.
That's a nice big gun you got there.
Dude, that was sick.
Y'all know how it goes. I've been captain of this boat for long enough.
It's time to sing the pirate song that we've been learning since we were two years old.
And it starts a little something like this.
The wind at our backs and the sun at the sea. None have ever been good to me.
Feel the waves crush through the sky. Into the deep air, yonder sky.
Drink in my hand and a trickle of my sleeves.
Looting and prendering's all that I crave.
Cast on the sails, release the brave. Tonight we dive.
Oh, shit.
Anybody on this boat have insurance?
What's insurance?
Drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, go, go.
You're just a daydreaming office worker. That's like what this is.
Assassin's Creed IV is your daydreaming office worker.
Yeah, I may wear work socks, you know, but you know, I'm just gonna sit here at my cubicle, which is a cubicle.
I daydream about being a pirate and they like record my daydreams.
Got ourselves a fight here. Got ourselves a fight with the George Washingtons.
If you guys didn't know, the plot of this game of Assassin's Creed IV is George Washington cloned himself after the cherry tree incident.
And now he wants to try to take over the earth with his George Washington clones, but I ain't gonna let that happen.
Yeah, get the fuck out of here.
What about your buddy? Your buddy's a fucking gonna get his neck broken too.
What about this guy? Fuck you.
You're all gonna get your heads punched in.
You're gonna get your head busted, broken, your fucking neck.
Yo, get the ear clapped. What is this? Oh, you want to get a double tap?
What about you? Oh, what's this? Ooh, ooh.
What's that? Chin punch, bitch.
What you working on? Ah, sanding.
I used to sand. It was a really tough job. Really good, honest day's work.
Fuck yourself.
Be careful. This is a pretty big, this is this ledge.
I know you just want to dance. That's great. But you know, that's not a safe place to be.
I told you, now you're all wet.
And that wasn't my fault, that was your fault.
And now everyone's going for a swim. Let's go.
Everyone's going for a swim. Get in.
Did they actually follow you in?
This one died.
Oh, I gotta kill somebody.
I almost just shit my pants when I did that, by the way.
I seriously almost just shit my pants when I just sneezed.
Did you hear? You know he shit his pants last night?
He sneezed.
That's gross.
Take a look for yourself, man. Right here, five minutes, 45 seconds.
Bang, shits his pants right there. How do you pull that off?
I don't know, but it's disgusting. He seriously disgusts me on another level that I can't even explain.
I mean, I shit my pants at least once a week, but I've never played in Assassin's Creed.
So I got MLC Stealth in the call here now.
We're going to go over some tips and some secret strategies that he knows about the Assassin's Creed multiplayer.
Because I know nothing. All I know is that I'm the Joker.
I'm playing as the Joker right now, and I need some secret tips from MLC Stealth.
Which does the Joker look like? Does he have a nose on his face?
No, the Joker. We're all the Joker. Every single person on our team is the Joker.
You can tell who a player is if they're jumping on roofs. That's normally what they do.
If they're moving quickly, it's a player.
You've got to sit there and hope they don't find you.
There's a guy.
You can't move. You can't budge.
I don't know what this guy's doing. Is that a bad guy?
No! Jesus!
He just has to remain still.
How did he...?
Hiding in a bush.
That's the way you do it. You hide in the bush.
Okay. Do I arrest this guy? Do I jump out and attack this guy?
Stealth, what do I do?
He's coming over here. No, no, no, no, no, no. Oh my God.
I think I killed him.
You have stunned him. No, I ripped him out.
Stealth, how do I...? Do I arrest him? Do I kill him?
I'm like killing civilians right now. Stealth, what do I do?
Stealth!
Am I still on the Skype call?
Killed my brother!
We got a huge amount of waves coming.
Brace yourselves, crew!
Oh, we're going to crash directly into these people.
The boat's going to tip over.
Holy crap.
This one fateful day reminds me of a story.
Did I ever tell you the story about me old boys?