Just made it. Just barely made it. I got that window. Between 3 and 4 p.m. Pacific.
340. Last stream. 350. Stream before that. 315. 359. I'm here to do the work. Uh, back to VR.
Welcome everybody. Hope you had a good few days here. This last few days. Proud of you. Hey.
Thanks. Everybody was talking about politics and I said don't do that.
They're right. Don't do that. Some of you may be noticing. Hold on. We'll wait. Hold on a second.
Give me a second. Hold on. You find yourself unable to cast sus because the stream is live.
But yes. Back to VR. Sure you're noticing, like I said before, uh, did somebody install
a certain add-on for Twitch? It might be something here. Let's take a look.
BTTV. I got it. And I added a peepo dance. Uh, Sticks Renegade. Thanks for the 50 bucks. And
they say hey, tax return stream. Tax return stream. Hold on. Let me see. I can't even
hear this. Hold on. I'm not going to be able to play this because I have my Vive audio
going through the Vive. Hold on. Can I hear it like through the Vive? Let me see if I can
hear this through the Vive. Oh, I can. That's really low though. What the hell? That's so
strange. Yeah, let's try it again. You want to see my tax returns? All right. Remind me,
in 2019, we'll take a look at my tax returns and we'll see how much money I get paid.
It's zero. See? That's because everyone was giving me shit. I'm not going to show you
guys my fucking tax returns. That was like a jokey, funny little jokey thing about how
you're playing Octogeddon too much. Therefore, somebody had to pay you to do it. That wasn't
even true. Okay, remind me in like 2021 that I'll show you a receipt. I'll show you like a
business receipt. You can clip that if you want. All right, here we go. We're going to
start with Duck Season. I don't know what this is. I know this is like a scary game.
That's what I've been told. Why don't we like get on camera? Get that out of here.
Hey, would you look at that? There he is. He's back and he's got his workout gear. Yep.
The shirt's back. It actually feels pretty good when you have it on. We got a full 3D
motion here, right? Make sure you can see more than you could. Don't touch that thing,
though. Don't touch that. The whole thing will probably explode if I put my hands on that.
So, I'm going to get in. Hold on. Is my shit all together here?
I think it is. Can you guys hear this? Is this sound? No. Does this have sound?
That got sound, right? Okay, yeah. Good. All right, I got the chat too. I'm ready to go in.
Just give me a minute. My head in frame. Wait a minute. Hold on. Activate the clap
emote. And then they called me the B word. Well, that should help a little bit with
the helmet. All right, let's go. I didn't even get a sip of coffee. Don't you? Okay.
I know I stall when I play VR, but you have to remember something. Once I go in here,
I can't even breathe until I come out. You can't take a sip of a drink.
You can't eat anything. You can barely move. Here we go. Duck season is what we're starting
with. It's a real boomer game. I remember Duck Hunt. Yeah, I used to flash the screen.
It was fucking crazy. All right. Hold on. Where's my headset? Why does this feel tighter?
Oh shit. Oh shit. It's because Kim was playing this. I got to adjust. Not yet. Hold on.
Yes. Yes. The question. I'll answer that question for you. Sure. Yes. Me and my
girlfriend had a VR date night. I took her on a date in virtual reality. It's very expensive
to go places. It's called dinner date. You get to order the most expensive wine. You get to have
the most expensive food and I could just sit in the corner over there and just be like this.
Like, yeah, it's nice. And she's like, wow, hold on. Wait, you took me. You took me here.
She's looking around with like on vacation and shit. It's best bucket program you could ever
have. This is the nicest restaurant in the city. Yeah. Yes, it is. Okay. Hold on. Hey,
what do you think about that? Boyfriend of the year, right? And then I go in like for a kiss
and it's like, cause she can't see me. So it's like, oh yeah, thanks honey. I need to put these.
I can't see. I can't see anything. Come on. Is this left or right? I got to ask you guys.
I might have to put this into the camera. What a stalling asshole. I can't. I feel like
I'm looking through a microscope. Which one is this? Come on. That's left. This one's left.
This one's right. All right. I'm ready. This text is red now. Yeah. What about it? All right.
Let's take a look at volume. That sounds a little low to me. Hold on. Where's my mouse?
I see it. I see it. I see it. I see it. I see it. Hold on. There we go. That's what
I'm talking about. That's much better. How's that sound? It's probably a little too loud.
All right. Now let's test that out. Loud. Hold on. Do you tell me better? That's probably
fine, right? That's good. That's fine. All right. Difficulty medium. Uh,
dominant hand is the right hand. I was going to say Dalmatian. Well, light gun,
peripheral disabled, adaptive quality on. I don't know what this any of this means.
Just go new game medium. Uh, normal hunter here for the game. Okay.
Anyway, I'd have to stay in somewhere specific. Stress level zero. Life is strange.
Dibs make this game the kid that wants to be a superhero. Mom? They carry in these groceries.
Oh, you got duck season. One day rental. So make the most of it. Oh, I will.
Well, it's kind of loud. It's loud as fuck. All right. Hold on. It's loud as fuck.
I'll take care of it. All right. Hey hunters, it's duck season. So that means we got a lot
of first time hunters out there. How to use your shotgun today. All our shotguns come
preloaded. So to start shooting, all you gotta do is aim it and pull the trigger.
Now to keep shooting. All you gotta do is place your hand on the pump of the shotgun
now you got another round in the chamber and you're ready to shoot.
Just like that. Now reloading your shotgun is easy. All you gotta do is put your hand up,
summon a shell from your box and put that baby into the chamber underneath the shotgun.
And pump it one more time and you're ready to go again.
Now professional hunters, they like to keep their shotgun topped off. So each time you fire
up a round and you have a second, you know, put a baby in there. Keep yourself prepared for
the amount of ducks that we flying at you. They'll be coming from everywhere from the left
to the right. They're everywhere, man. So I hope you guys learn something. And remember,
first rule of gun safety is have fun. Cause remember it's duck season.
Hey hunters, it's duck season. So that means we got a lot of first time hunters out there.
I'm going to teach you how to use your shotgun today. All our shotguns come preloaded.
All you gotta do is aim it and pull the trigger. Now to keep shooting. All you gotta do is place
your hand on the pump of the shotgun and rack that baby. Now you got another round
in the chamber and you're ready to shoot. Whoa, a banana. It's huge. What kind of
mutant world are we living in? Why are these so big? I used to have a cup like this.
All right. Stop. Okay. Just play. How do I play level one? Oh, I got a level one.
It's lagging. Is it Cox? It's not doing that on my end. Oh, it's just, really? Oh,
it's a drop of frames. Fuck. The line controllers pulled trigger. I'm not getting any like
hardware lag. Let me just check and see how many frames I've dropped. It's never easy,
is it? It's never easy. Okay, just play a goddamn game. Oh, shit. No, it is. Like,
what the fuck is going on here? Hold on. My CPU is going like nuts. Why? I didn't change
anything from last time. I got nothing else going on in the background here. Let
me just do one thing real quick here. No, I got like, yeah, I got like an encoding issue.
What the fuck? It's BTTV. Better twitch.tv. I'm going to have to, I might have to restart
three. Why? No, OBS had a fucking major update today. There was a major OBS update today
that I think may have caused me a problem. Fuck. Oh, I'm going to change to the other
codec. Streams going to turn off. Tell me how this works. I'll be right back.
I'll be right back. Hello? How's it look? My CPU has dropped by an insane amount.
Yeah, OBS had a pretty major update today and I just changed it to like hardware codec.
That's the first time I've had to do that in like three years. Okay, well, sorry about that.
That was weird. Didn't expect an update to do that, but let me know if it keeps going or
anything else happens. Wait, I got an opportunity to drink an iced coffee. Yeah,
I was, OBS was at like 60% CPU. Now it's at 11%. Okey dokey. Let's go. Let's actually
play. All right. Duck season. All right. Put your hand here and then pump. Okay, just make
sure. Grab a shell. Force grab a shell. How many do I have in there? It's wicked loud.
Fucking Vive, man. I need like a tech director to play Vive. All right. Round one. Ready?
Just lower your volume for like five minutes. This is actually really fun.
So they're gonna get, does Nintendo like get angry with them for them?
I can see Nintendo getting angry with them. Okay, come on. I'm pretty good at these kind
of games. Throw like more than one at me. Got it. All right. Round two. Ready?
Actually, Nintendo's about to shut the screen down.
Lower the volume. All right. Hold on a minute here. Let me lower the fucking volume. This
is probably like unbearable. There you go. All right. Round two. I think I'm getting
the hang of this. See now it's horrible. Let me load the shotgun up a little bit here.
How many can fit in there? One, two, three, four, five. Okay. Bring it on. Fuck!
It's all right. I feel like I'm playing Diner Dash. Didn't even need to look, did I?
Oh, this is fucking fun. Can I like not even do the horror movie part? Can I just do this?
A little bit. Okay. Those are the ducks that I... I thought I was getting like creepered over
here. All right. Is it loaded? I don't need to reach. You know. Make it louder. Turn around.
What? Oh, look at me! Oh, nope. I ain't gonna do that. I ain't gonna do that one.
Look out. Oh, look at me! I don't have to do that. I have to though. It's VR.
Two more. What do I get for ranking? That's gotta be at least like a D. Is that at least a D?
Quickly! Quick! God damn it! Come on. Where's my mouse? Like around the back. Now I have to do
that, right? Okay. If you shot a shotgun that close to somebody's head, their hearing would be
gone for the rest of their life. That would be like a bang. Like the whole... Everybody would
be like going like this. How's that? Turn up the volume. Turn down the volume. Turn up the
volume. Turn down the volume. Turn up the volume. Look at me! Hey, Mom! Okay. I am against a wall.
This is fucking weird. I'm actually like sitting here like this. What wall is this?
Mom, can I have soda? Uh, duck season loading level two. Let's go.
Now it's as fucking loud as shit. Okay. Turn it up. Turn it down. Turn it up. Turn it down.
Turn it up. Turn it down. I've already watched this. Oh! That was perfect, isn't it?
Jeremy, I think you might need to adjust the game volume. Just a little. It's so loud.
I gotta get... I can't. Alright, I'm gonna go to like the steep... No, I'm gonna go back out and...
It's hard. Just turn your volume slider down. I usually have really quiet streams.
Just like turn the slider down for one. The fire? Use language. Use steam menu for volume.
Everybody use hand signals to communicate with him. Oh, no. He's... Oh, no. He's wearing
iPods. He can't hear us. Right? Let's keep the stream going.
Let me get times 10. I'll be happy. I can sense it. I can feel ultra instinct.
Round three. Is it gonna get three ducks at the same time? Gotta keep a rhythm going.
It's alright. It's okay. It's alright. I got it. What an absolute turret. Time's at 2 a.m.
Only 1995. Duck food? I'm not killing ducks, am I? This is just supposed to be a computer
game. This is not supposed to be real. What else we got here? Oh, thanks!
Thanks, Mom! Did she get angry? What the fuck? I've got a frisbee. Oh, who hasn't done this yet?
Dude, I watched a guy play duck season and I swear to God he started throwing stuff at the
mom. What? But did they hit her in the head? Spoilers. I spoiled it for myself. It's okay.
Advanced level. Oh, fuck. He went far. Come on, give me a...
Here we go. Round one. Oh, what a bad joke. Like, I snorted the bullet and I just broke my vibe.
Fucking idiot. Perfect. That's fine with me.
3,333 viewers. It's a sign. That means, right? I gotta pay attention. The sun is bright.
Ah, shut up, Jeremy. Make the shots. Bad. Bad. He's bad. I'm not in the right place.
Sign, R. Get a letter. Damn. Pretty good. Eat the shells. No, I already almost hurt myself.
Did Jeremy already do the shoot the dog joke? Yes. What the fuck? That was pretty good.
That's pretty good. What? I got it. What for, huh? Oh, I got it! Look!
How does it work? What? No, I want to shoot the thing. Come on, man. Oh, I can do it again.
I can't let go of it. How do I let go? You've seen anybody do that before?
That's pretty good fan physics. Would you like this when you were a kid?
I don't know. Probably. I did it with a beat.
All right, it's going to be probably harder. I'm ready.
Okay, by the way, this shirt stinks like a dirty laundry basket.
I can't. It's fucking me up. It was in the laundry, I think, for too long,
and it has that dirty inside of a gym bag smell. Oh, it's fucking with me.
Just fucking put one in. I swear to God, I'm ripping this shirt in half.
It stinks in here. It's not me. It's the shirt. It's not me. It's not me. It's like
it was in the laundry for too long, and it didn't get dried fast enough,
and now it has that smelly. I thought somebody just like fucking hacked me.
It's filling my nostrils every time I breathe in. It's not me.
It's because I started to get some moisture going through the shirt.
Everybody relax. Change shirt. Not yet. I deserve this. That's a pretty good tactic right there.
Let's go. Ain't going to go through the fucking tree on me. Did he? Good to go.
I'm watching in spell-o-vision, and this is unbearable. Please change shirt.
Yeah, just go get like a piece of dirty laundry and just put it in your face.
What the hell is going on now? All right. Okay. I'm going to close my eyes,
and wherever this lands, that's exactly where I'm going to take my next vacation. Ready?
One, two, three. Can you stop? Does it stop? I don't think it stops. It doesn't stop.
That's nowhere. All right. Where am I going? That's a huge piece of pizza.
No, don't do this to me. This looks like really good. I know this is like actually
it's kind of like a dirty laundry pizza, but I still think it looks good.
I, you can actually take a bite out of it. Fucking game of the year. What's that?
Can I like, you want to bite the whole thing? Some dogs go to hell. Where is the gra- that's
fucking creepy. This says, uh, radical racers. Look, I just got to stand still like this,
and then I'll be able to know what direction that I, like, where the gravity is.
Okay, so gravity's going this way, so I'm standing on the wall this way.
So I'm like, like that. Okay. Can I wake myself up? I'm in a dream.
Holy shit, he's coming to get me. Where's the wall? What do you want, the knife?
A knife? Oh, ma. Shit, knife, right? But the throw. Don't make fun of my throw.
She's going to be like the- I'm going to have to like hide somewhere. She's
going to turn into a fucking monster. I guarantee it. Watch some dogs go to hell.
Go. That was your warning shot. I'm going to get a perfect. I'm going to get a perfect
or I'll shit my pants on spring. What an immature fucking thing to say. Give me a break.
Where'd you go? Oh, they disappear quickly.
Multiple shits. Every time. Next time, we'll do it next dream, guys. I'll just drink coffee
and eat soft cheeses. That's not appropriate for work. I can't do that. A lot of people
watch my stranger at work. Damn it. My boss heard you. That's what I'm saying. I got to
be more careful. Not applicable for work. One would say it's not safe to watch this dream
if you're at jobs. All right, now I got to come. I got to shut up. I was doing so good.
Do it. What the fuck are you doing? I'm trying to pump the damn thing.
I'm going to cry. I'm going to cry. I'm a teacher. Please don't swear in front of my
class. Why did you wheel a TV into the room and put my stream on? What are you teaching them
about? I guess so. I wrote this song a long time ago, but I guess they just realized
what it's all about. Mom just kind of walks back and forth, huh?
Beatsaber. There's no I in Iowa. We'll be right back.
What's that? Kazoo Kid. I kind of want to see what the Kazoo Kid is.
Do you see what your child is watching over here? Get involved. That's about enough of
that I can take. King bit game system level six. Dogs go to hell. Oh, right. Dogs go to
hell. I forgot about dogs go to hell. Just how many levels are in this game? I mean,
do I have to keep showing like my extreme skill set with the light gun? Don't pay attention
to that one. I'm not fucking around anymore. Watch this one. I just shit my pants on stream.
What just happened? I just think this control is broken. Here we go. I'm ready. Now you
motherfucker. I gotta like move. I think I'm not getting picked up by the sensor.
I should have got a triple right there too. I know like the kids right there. Check your
six. Tonight channels. All right. Where's uh, where's dogs go to hell? Watch that one next.
I mean, that's unbelievable. This is an ode to G mod. I don't want to watch that.
Time buddies. No, where's dogs go to hell? Treasure hunters. I don't know which one is
this? Right? Right? Right? Everybody funny, right? It's gonna take off. It's gonna fly away.
I just realized the Travelocity gnome just started to tap into like the young millennial
audience, right? Didn't even need to do anything. The Travelocity gnome just has to exist
and he'll be like hip still. They make a Travelocity commercial where he like pops up
on the screen and just goes like, Oh, all of you guys would fucking buy that insurance.
Right. Wait. No, you'd whatever it is. No, that's kind of okay. What about these other games here?
Hold on. This is duck season. What's this one? Whaling 1842. Do I have to play this?
Jesus. Oh my God. I think I lost. What are the other games? The whales win.
Triple Tiger. Triple Tiger. This is a shooting game. Okay. Um, I don't know. That's not
like a Pokemon scenario there. Remember your training. I have a gun. You go for a punch.
Oops. Go for a high kick. Gotta go for a punch. Low kick. Gotta go for a high punch.
I don't understand. It's like rock, paper, scissors. Battle. Oh, the Super Mario Brothers.
That's like Tropical Fruit Mario Brothers. It's just Flappy Bird. All right. Hold on.
Let me try this one again. It's just Flappy Bird. No. There's a lot of random games here, huh?
Desert Boss. Behind you. What? Mom, Mom, are you eating a pizza sandwich? That's a slice of
pizza on top of face down on a slice of pizza. What's wrong with you? I gotta wait. Where's
my, where'd it go? It just went into the machine. It just sucked in. See, look, Mom
took one of these, flipped it this way and put another one underneath that is eating that.
I've never, I actually want to do that. I'm going to try that. Okay. Uh, what happened to,
no, I don't want to play that stupid game. Okay. Somebody says blowing it.
I didn't do anything. There's a microphone up here. I don't know if it's like,
could have thought I was doing something. Get that out. Try harder. It's not going to,
no, I'm not fucking humoring you guys. That's not real. Pizza Boy. Wasn't there,
I was supposed to play another game. Hold on. How do you play Pizza Boy? How do you throw a
pizza? Is it like throw pizza? Oops. I don't know how to throw a pizza. Oh, I just like
killed that guy. Oopsie daisy. Just pulling a guy over. Sir, you know, I pulled you over.
I don't know. Is it, is it the 15 to 20 pizzas I've thrown up my driver's side window?
All right. That's it. What's that one? Hover junkers. What's this one? I gotta play Sinatra first.
Fucking weird lady. I don't get it. This one's actually kind of fun. Oops.
What's this one? You know what's really funny about this? This is like,
this is what we did three days ago. This is just me with like a dream cast or like a
PlayStation 2 or the PlayStation 1. What's the next one? What's up? I died once.
Yeah, guys, this was like $485. Did I lose? How do I reload? That was pretty good, man.
That was like 48 bucks. All right, let's go back to the real game. No, dogs go to hell.
Let's see what this one is like. That one's not safe for work. What's wrong with it?
I tried. I have no idea. All right. Back in the game. Let's get back into it.
Hey, dog. I haven't played in so long. I think I lost my muscle memory of how to play this game.
I gotta get the better spot. Yeah, it's the spot. It's doing it like this right there.
Got four coming out at the same time now. I got an issue here. I got like a wardrobe
malfunction here. This like is going to come down and like rip off all my clothes.
Reloaded. Last round.
Got wiggly at the end there. I should be looking behind me. Shoot the sun.
Am I like stuck in an infinite loop? No, it's like six months. That's my bedtime.
How much are the wiggles? What the? Oh, it's that guy.
Wow, there's a guy over there. He was stalling because he was scared.
You can call it whatever the heck you want. Check this in training. What's that? What's that?
An intruder onto my right. That kid is going to play calm. I'm dancing to the fucking wiggles.
They all get different colored shirts on. Bang. That would just hit him right in the
fucking nose. I would break his nose up into his head. I'll show you again. Bang.
He'd fucking puke and that would sprint over in fucking one, two, three uppercut.
What would fucking happen? What a gamer. I gotta get like the hand. I gotta keep the hand down.
That works too, doesn't it? Beautiful. All right. Not bad. Not terrible. Not good,
but not bad. But pretty good. I thought he was going to be quicker than that. Slow than that,
I mean. Come on, man. I had it. Sometimes you just, you see how my hand comes down?
Come on, do it. Oops. Oops. Oops. Oops. Whoa. You're in the room. What happened? What happened?
Oh shit. Oh no. Now that's, now that's, that's something bad happened there.
Well, mom's, mom's seen better days. Come on. Got it. Okay. Oh, pizza. Double pizza.
See? What a, that's a genius fucking thing. Last meal. All right. Come face me. Anything else
I should be looking at here? Don't let the TV break. Well, what do you mean don't let the
TV break? That TV? I'm not ready. I'm not ready. I'm not ready. Ready? Shoot the moon.
Oh, he's throwing fucking bombs. Fuck. How did I miss? All right. That was just bullshit.
You saw that. Cock the gun. Cock the gun. Why does it not do it? What do I shoot him? In the
fucking eyes? My god. Oh my. Oh, it's making me mad. Oh, let me shoot the gun. Look at
it. Like, no, I want to fight him again. Give me like a fucking shock and then they're like
screws in it. Seven endings in this game. Stuck forever. I'm you. That was fun. Whoa,
don't do that to me. That was fucking weird. Uh, what does continue do? Can I start? Could I
do it again? I'm going to kill this guy. That will make me throw up though. All right.
Yeah. Let's go. Let's go. Let's do it again. I'm ready. Come face me. Let's go.
Let's get the good end. Ah, fuck you. Freddy Fazbear asshole. Let's go. All right. Let's
like do it. Well, that was bullshit. Play with the trombone to reload this shotgun.
Yay. Just wait a minute. Hold on. That ain't going to be it. Ow. Did I escape the video
game? Midnight. Is there more? Oh god. Mom's still dead back there. What? I thought I
would correct it though. Oh my god. He's here. Where is he? Where is this motherfucker?
Does anybody know where he is? He was right there and like right here. What the fuck?
Stay in there. We're good. I think I did it. Midnight. Oh, like stomped on the game.
I called the police.
Hello? It's my, it's my mom. Why is mom dead? Why would mom be dead here? We're going
to bury mom? What the fuck? Uh, okay. This is not just a good ending. This is a bad
ending too. What? Duck season. So is there an ending where mom lives? That was a little
out of control. It was a fun game though. Nice job, Alex. Nice job, Brandon. Nice job,
Cameron. Nice job, Kevin. Nice job, Jeremy. Tiffany. Nate. Nate. Chris. Michael. Spencer.
Spencer again. Two different Spencers in this company. Chapman. Tyler. Heldine. And of course,
we could forget Jake Watson. He's the one that kept it all together. He's the fucking lawyer.
Oh, I'm so glad that the Nickelodeon snick couch is behind me. That's, that's only 90s
boomers will know what that is. Well, there we go. All right. That's cool. That was fun.
That was a nice little experience. Shooting was fun. Let me come out for a second.
Oh yeah. Save mom. I, no, I can't. I'm not going to do that. There's five more endings
and you can get them when you play for the vibe in Oculus Rift. Do a pee break. Yeah,
I'm going to take a break for a minute. It's going to take a piss and just kind of throw
some water in my face. And then we come back. I got all this flot. Uh, there is,
like I could, I could start. I don't think I want to start a mind show yet
because if I start mine show, then I'm probably not going to get out of that for a while.
So, uh, there is, I'm not playing that right now. I'll come back. We'll figure it out.
I have like the Creed boxing game. I've got disassembly VR. I've got a horror game. I've got
jet Island. I've got another Island. I'm going to, I think it might come back and
do the dinosaur Island one. We'll find out. I got lots to do. I'll be right back.
Hold on. Let me just slowly put this down. Okay. See you guys. And did you just hear that like,
I made like a weird like cat noise at my throat. Uh, I'll be back in like two,
three minutes. Just going to take a quick little break. All right.
So I think I'm going to play the dinosaur Island game.
This is Island three 59. It's a game where you land on an Island and have to fight
dinosaurs. It's kind of right up my alley. Move this. All right. Uh, dinosaur four 20. No,
I need to change the game title. I don't think this is Island three. I don't know. This ain't
even on Twitch directory. No, yes, there it is. All right, let's go. Thank you for your
patience. Let's open Island three 59. I got to move. All right. We tangled. No, this
actually is not tangled tonight. I really have to move around too much in the last one. So
let's go ahead and bring this back. Instruction stand upright. Okay. I got to like do my height.
Get it out of your system. Now. All right. Get it out of your system. I will allow at least
25 seconds of height joke spam and then that's it. You got 20 seconds.
Virtual self. Where is this one? This is lying to me where this control is not over here.
It's over here. Okay. Stand upright. Make sure a floor height is accurate.
Okay. Using virtual self. Virtual self is in beta. Step into boots. Step into boots.
Click create new profile and then use the sliders. I fucked it up again. I'm going to
put like tape on this shit. So I know. All right. So we can step into the boots.
Am I in the boots? Does this count? Okay. Arm length. I got to make me shoulders forward
and back. This looks really strange. No, my chest is kind of like that does not look
correct. Like an earthworm person. No, that's not, I'm not even on the ground.
I have to at least be like on the ground. All right. That looks okay.
Characters. There's different characters. I'm just going to read this guy. Warning
impacts. Add spectator camera. What the name of God is that? What is that?
So I can add like my own president evil camera. Can you guys even,
how do you let anybody see that? Can you guys see this? No, why am I doing that? You're
in my arm. Yeah, but like that doesn't, this is not going to do anything.
Use the window capture instead of open VR. Yeah, that's going to run like shit though.
Now we're going without it. Jesus. Ready to start? You betcha. Let's talk about you
and your life. He's got a gamer in there.
Pick up that bucket. Oh, it is like a pew, right?
Both buckets of face. Oh, just look at the ground. The basics. It was a comfortable
movement method.
Oh, I'm going to say teleport track pad. How would you choose how you'd like to aim?
Look, look, get to the wave. No, go back. Go back. Go back. Did I?
Hold on. Didn't I turn off? How do I open the menu for this game?
The in-game menu. Yeah. Sorry guys. Movement mode. Teleport. Okay. Thank you.
Yo, that's so much easier. I'm not going to die now.
So press menu to drop on the X.
Hold the grip. Let's pick a backpack up.
Okay. All right.
It's not going to kill us, right? Wait, give him a knife. Yeah.
What the fuck?
Climb up the ladder. You got it. There. Wait, what is that? Why is there a secret like
Alice in Wonderland door? Oh, this is from the helicopter. Reach out and grab a run.
Oh, that's not even you sprint to enter tower.
Bucking for you. Lucky for you. Double agent.
You should be in the clear. I can't shoot the sky.
That's a good idea. This is the absolute worst way we could be having this conversation.
Oh, the kids, the kids doing good. All right. It doesn't, it's fine. It doesn't work.
Aim movement at ladder to exit. All right. Fall like a nose.
Restricted area warning. All right. We're looking for what? We're looking for dinosaurs.
I didn't mean to do that. Get to the thing. What? One, two, three. All right. Oh, you're too close.
What's in here? Oh, more of this.
Hold down grip with gun hand until ammo selector appears.
All right. That's odd, but fine. Thanks a lot. I don't know what this guy's name is.
Kill the raptors. When did they attack? Thank you. That was kind of lame. It's all right though.
All right. You got a leopardette. Pills? What is this leopardette?
That was scary. I thought that was a tree.
I thought it was a tree and it started moving. Grab everything. That's cool. Up into the house.
What kind of door? It's a push door. Really? Move upgrade to highlighted area on guns. Laser
sight. What was that? How do I get to the gate? Can I sneak out this way? Yep. Come on. I
can't do that. Shit. Where? Kill the stegosaur. Where's there a stegosaur?
Where? Okay. I want to see a clip of that. I want to see how stupid I actually am. There's
no stegosaur. I'm a fucking idiot. I could hear him, but he wasn't on the screen.
All right. T-Rex is going to show up right here. All right. Let's go. Island 359.
So what do you do? What are you supposed to do in this game? Update 1.0. Survival mode exists now.
What is over here? Mercenary store. Cash in merc credits for gear. Sell found gear for credits.
Okay. That's pretty cool. Let me get this shit on. All right. See you later. Good luck.
Survival mode? Which one? What do you want me to do? Sell your knife and gum.
Survival. A carefully paced survival experience. Traverse the open island.
Discover survivor stories. Explore camp, scrounge, loot, kill, and survive. Okay.
I'll give it a try. I'm going to throw up for this. Do I get a different gun? Same gun?
Yeah. Yeah. Give me that. I'm not doing that again. I'm going to wear the bucket. I just
want to land. Oh, that kind of hurts. That's a great feature. I don't even know what I'm looking
at. Am I crazy? Does that look strange? My hand is fucked up. That's all right.
I feel like I'm looking at the world through some strange filter.
What do I have to do? Eat berries or something? Eat weeds?
All right. I hear something. I don't have any bullets in this guy. Get out of here.
Stick it back on like a kebab. Is there an alarm on you? What the? Oh, this is on my hunger meter?
Okay. I'm just going to find the bed. That's just a JPEG. That's not going to do anything
for me. What about over here? Up in the top? No, there's a building right here.
There we go. Health. What about food? Do I need anything? What's this? Potato chips?
Okay. No. Give me the knife back. There's something in here. There's a crate here.
I don't think I can do anything with it. Can I not do something with this?
This is like a weapon crate. Should I go in the outhouse? This is just an open world.
Let's climb up. Pretty good vantage point though. A crowbar? I don't think I can pick
that up. Yeah, I can. Nice. I'm bashing. Somebody's heading with this thing. Okay.
Check the yellow one. This is not a rhinoceros. What are those things? Triceratops.
Are Triceratops friendly? Will he run after me? I don't even know where he is.
Oh my God. He's freaking out. He's like a dog with the zoomies. He's a dog that just had a
bath. What is it? Shit. That was so mean. Did he tire himself out? He killed that dog. I
didn't kill anything. Come here you motherfucker. Oh, he hit me. He's hitting me. All right. I
have to get out of this. I'm gonna die. Have fun. Goodbye. I'm getting killed over this.
I'm already like dead. He's just stuck down there in that ditch. He's still there? That's
so terrifying that they move so erratically like that. If you come across a huge...
Where was it? Where did I want to go? Is that him? I'm just gonna go this way.
How do I eat? Oh shit. I'm almost dead. What's up there? Okay. Fizz. I don't know
what that thing is. Do I have to eat the dinosaurs? Is that how this works?
He's not threatening, right? They're not that threatening. That's one of the
velociraptors. That's like some of the weird dinosaur. It looks kind of mean though. I'm
not gonna fuck with that. It's an elephant. It's an elephant. Run. Why is it an elephant?
Run away. Oh, that's unbelievable. Is that what that dinosaur actually sounded like?
Get out of here. Hey, you want something? Here. I think I ate it. He's running again.
I don't know. He's still chasing me with his tuba. Oh, come on. Why is he still here?
I don't know how to get away from him. I got dirt in the head. I was so called for.
I just spit on myself. He's still chasing me. Why? Aren't you out of breath at this point?
He's gonna kill over and die from exhaustion. There's a car. Can I get in the car?
Get on top of the car. All right. I'm on top of the car. He can't get me.
You bastard. Get away from me. Leave. Leave me alone.
This is the stupidest thing. He followed me for like 12 blocks.
That was too much. I swear to God, if I get off this and he's right there,
I'm gonna fucking pee my pants. Okay. Are we good? I'm gonna open this door.
How do I open this?
There's nothing even in here. There's just mold. I can't get over that. That was stupid.
Okay. Let's keep going. I need to... I'm gonna die. The whole world is red right now because
I'm one head away from death. Oh shit. Does he have a camera? He's videotaping like a
skateboard video. Look at that. Watch. A fucking velociraptor is gonna do like an
ollie right here and go over him. I think he's too far away. Yeah. He's recovering.
He's thinking about what he did. Is that like a base I can ransack or something?
I don't like how open this looks. This is a big open field. I don't like it at all.
I also don't like what's going on here on the skyline. It hurts my head.
Am I at the edge of the world? I'm so lost.
Is it that? I would have...
There's something right here. What is it? It's a stegosaurus.
Don't like run around in a circle like a dog. I can't get on top of this rock, can I?
Okay. I'm on the rock. I think I'm safe. Base. How do I get by you to get down there?
Wrap all the way around. He's just waiting for me to move. He's just got his eyes on me.
I didn't know stegosaurus was that fast. I thought they were slow lumbering animals.
Okay, we're good. Ammo. Give me something. The base is right down here.
There's air conditioning here. That's electricity.
What is that? Punch it? It's not gonna work. Is there like a front door? Here it is.
How do I open this? There's a big on button. That would work, wouldn't it?
Eureka! Give me something to eat or scavenge or something. I got AC over here.
Let's go in the building. Find story note to unlock. What is this? Slenderman?
Let me find story note. Bullets know nothing? Oh god damn it. Come on. What? Tent? It's getting
dark out. I can't even go in this tent. Anything in the dumpster?
Uh, okay. I'm supposed to be picking up sticks. I gotta get another note.
It's getting too dark. Resident sleeper. Crafting game. Look, let me just...
Next game. Hold on. Give me one second. It showed its true nature. It's a crafting game.
Huh, okay. Just play mercenary mode. That's true. We should probably... Wow, that's
main menu. Let's do mercenary mode. Let's see how it is. That's like putting sticks
together and making fires. I don't wanna do that. Mercenary mode. Move freely,
explore, hunt, kill, or be killed. We'll go to the beach. Loot drop. Big hunt. Loot drops.
Big hunt. Big hunt. Difficulty normal. Let's go. We'll move on after this.
I'm not even gonna give it a second. Wait, wait. No, no. No, no. Give me that.
Ah, come on. What was that? What was that? Go to the waypoint. Okay.
How do I give it a gun? Can't grab arrow with gun. Well, how do I let go of this? Okay,
arrows. Where are the arrows? Where are the arrows? What the fuck is this?
What is that? What is this? Where are the arrows? It says can't grab arrows with gun. Why not?
Oh, no. I want the backpack. I want the backpack. That's pretty fucking sick. All right,
let's go. I think I have infinity of these. Let's go. I don't put the knife away. All right,
hide. Wait, we point right in the neck, right? Wait! One more time. One more time.
One more time. Okay, let's go. No, I don't want that. Let's just, I'm gonna kill this thing.
I don't even need, I don't give a shit about anything else. Let's go. I'd like some radio
metal. What? Jesus Christ. Please just let me do it. Ah! Okay, moving on. This game's
actually pretty cool. This game's pretty cool. It is. It's a pretty cool game. I'll tell you.
All right, next up is Apollo Creed, the boxing game. This game makes me angry. Wait, why?
How the fuck did I end up over here? Give me one sec. I'm the bad guy. You look sad.
Sad? All right, you want to do horror? I do have a horror game. All right, we'll try this
horror game that I got. Let me close out of this. All right, how do I get out of this? Quick. Okay.
The game I have is called Dreadhalls. It looked like people thought it was fun. It looked like
it was pretty highly rated. Let's give it a try. Yeah, Dreadhalls. Not that one. What's
wrong with that one? Okay, launch Dreadhalls in Steam VR mode. That's the one I want to do.
All right, let's just do it. All right, I need to change the game to Dreadhalls.
Is this game going to actually cause me a problem? Well, as long as I don't throw up, I don't care.
And turn the lights off. Why does that matter? Turn the lights off? I'm in here. Why do I
need to turn the lights off? Turn the lights off. Hold on. Why would you want me to do this?
I can't even, why can I not control my lights? I'm not connected? Unable to connect
to my Phillips Hue? Why? There we go. Is that better? All right, see you guys on there.
By the way, if you want to know the plan on Saturday, I'm pretty sure me and Star are
going to do some co-op VR games. So that should be a lot of fun. We're going to try
like Wreck Room, a couple of the multiplayer games, see how they are. Ow, my hair. I got
to prepare for this. I hate this shit. God damn, like horror games and I got to put both headphones
in. Hey, get ready for some fake reactions. Yeah, that's right. It's tuber time. Let me
give you a good thumbnail first though. Let me get you a good thumbnail. Is that good? Both
these have to go in. God damn it. I'm doing both. I'm doing both. It's a horror game. I'm
going to do both. All right. Here we go. Just don't ever have hair. Just get rid of it.
It just gets in the way. It's just dead. Why even have it? It's just fingernails. You
know that your hair is just your fingernails, but finer. We cut our fingernails. Just get
rid of them. We're going to evil off our fingernails off anyways. All right. I'm ready.
No, I'm not. I am. Okay. That was, I was just puked. I was just like refluxed.
Fucking stalling. I know I'm stalling. All right. Options. Audio setting. Five hands.
Right-handed. Keep the tutorial on. How are we doing on audio? We good? How's that?
Pretty good. Video settings should be fine. Quality good. Anti-aliasing. That's whatever.
Moving settings. Rotation speed. Snap comfort. Move in looking direction. Press trackpad to
move. I think that's fine. Well, here you go, motherfuckers. This is what you wanted.
Content warning. This game is an intense horror experience featuring scenes of disturbing
nature. Player discretion is advised. Inventory move light. Interactive open sprint map look.
So I move around with this. I look with this. That's inventory. This is map. Interactive light
and sprint. Point with your right hand and press trigger to pick up. A bottle of oil.
You can use it to fuel your lamp. Right trigger to collect. Oh, I have a lamp. This
is just VR amnesia. You actually have to walk around. What the fuck is this thing?
What the fuck is this thing? Handwritten note. I can't wait for you. Not anymore. Not here.
There's an exit. The stone face told me. I'll be there. I'll wait for you there.
Follow my trail. Find the eyes. Find the exit. Hold right hand. Trigger and turn hand
left and right. Okay. So does that drive a weapon? Two coins? You can always brute force
locks. But using these lock picks should be faster. Right trigger to collect them.
What about these coins? A coin from the past. Right trigger to collect it.
What do you do with the coins though? Haunted house games.
Try to close this behind me. Close. Get this thing closed. How can I tell
how much oil is in the tank here? Use the oil in your inventory to fuel your lamp.
So that's the inventory. What the hell was that noise? Grab the lamp oil.
Okay. That makes it brighter. I have a couple more lock picks. When do I get machete?
Open the inventory and grab a lock pick. Place the lock pick here and then release.
So it opens it instantly. Coins. No! That was important information. How do I look at that
again? Where's that? How do I look at that again? That was probably like how to stop the
monster. No, that was just like geolocation. Is this like a dress? Oh. Cheeto location.
I need to be able to hear shit. Sir! Straight through here. Oh my god. Should I turn around
and run the other way? Looks like a receptacle or something. Hear this! What do I do? I hear
something moving over here behind me. I need to fill this up with oil.
I didn't change the game. Away from Dino D-Day. Whatever it's called. What's it called? Island
Dino? Is there a mod with power? Can you change it? No, I did change it. I'm just
panicking right now. Give me this. Give me these. Give me those. Give me this.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! What is this? What is this? What is that for?
A human eye. Find the eyes. Oh no, that's gonna activate her. I just activated her.
I just activated her! All right, I'm gonna have to- I'm gonna- I'm going with the
Burger Boy technique. You ready? Burger Boy technique. What would Burger Boy do? He would
do this. All right, I'm ready to breath from here. All right, I can go that way. One of
these is gonna open. That's the good witch of the west, right? The good witch of the east.
That did it. It must be another eye. The snake?
Where is that person coming from? Where is that person coming from? There's a room
to the left. Monoculars. Walking along the corridor, I can hear my footsteps,
my breathing, but also something else. A scraping sound coming from the darkness behind me.
It ceased when I stopped to look around me, but now I can hear it again.
Is that supposed to be a tutorial? That's a tutorial, right? What tutorial does that mean?
Just don't look behind me. I wanna make something very clear here. I am bumping into
something right here. I cannot go back. I'm bumping into an object. She's literally right on me.
I'm bumping into her back. I'm in like a fucking line at Disney World bumping into her.
She's right there. You can go ahead and just stay in there if you'd like.
I'm trying to close the door. Just stay in there. You don't have to worry about me.
I'm just gonna walk. I have an itchy eyeball.
She's gonna be behind me and she's just gonna jump in and scare me.
It's a big room. I'm like a shuffling old man.
She's right fucking there. I'm not looking. She might be in one of the... I got an itchy
ass. Hold on. Is this thing gonna stand up? Why did I wake up alone and I have no answer?
My head still hurts so perhaps I stayed unconscious for too long but
they wouldn't have waited for me. That is unless they couldn't stay here.
Oh fuck off lady. That's fine. I'll just stay over here. Can I see like a shadow behind me?
I can't. I can't move. Can I? Be gone!
Ah shit. Okay. What's the... Okay. You can go down here.
What? This creature moves when you look away. Don't turn your back to it. I thought I was
supposed to like put my back towards the creature. What? So the thing was just glued to me the whole
time? So I have to stare at that lady. I'm sitting there like backing up. She's just like
dancing behind me. Oh man that was... Oh god. There's more than one. Oh that's unbelievable.
The whole thing is computer generated right? The whole thing is just computer generated.
Alright where are you guys? I want to make sure I'm in the right spot. God damn it.
So I did find the other eyes. I was done. God. Alright let's go. I knew she was in the room too.
Oh I hurt my whole body. There's got to be another eye. Alright I gotta stare right at the lady.
I hate that mechanic. I hate this mechanic. I don't like this mechanic.
Okay stare at her. Right stare right at her face. Come here lady. I don't want any trouble
with you. Where the fuck is she? It's just pillows. Oh dude no no no. Humans weren't supposed to be
doing this shit. Where are you? Where are you? Where are you? Hello? Yep you're over here
somewhere. Humans weren't supposed to be doing this. I looked at you. I'm looking at you right
now. I'm looking at you right now. Food just came up out of my mouth. Like old food.
I just like puked. I just tasted tobacco. How? Was I eating cigarettes in my sleep?
It's not that even back here. I gotta go down that hall.
Oh shit. In my pants. I think she's behind me. I gotta look at her. Hey hey hey hey hey hey
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey there! Hey there! Hey boy! Hey! Hi!
Don't you dare get out of that! You! That hurt you!
I'm looking at you! I'm looking at you! I'm looking at you! Huh?
This is wrong monster. You shouldn't have looked at her.
Don't look at the lady. Look at the other one. I thought they were both ladies.
I don't do well in this environment, man. I got both the headphones in.
I'm fucking... I'm eating cigarettes in my sleep.
Alright, I'm gonna just do it. It's like sweat all over my mouth.
Are you gonna give me a weapon?
Come on, am I getting Luigi?
Sid, he was the one who told me about the god and this place.
He didn't want to come, not at first, but I convinced him.
I wanted to see it. I needed to.
Points.
I'm thinking how big this map is.
Ugh. So this... Don't look at lady.
Look at the... the smoke monster?
So, the cloud of dust. Look at the dust cloud. Don't look at lady.
Is there any other monsters that I need to have tutorials on?
But they both look like they could be made out of the dust.
Ugh. Standing around and...
Okay, is that the duster or is that her? It's a duster.
Magic staff. What does it mean? What does it mean? What does it do?
Take me. I have no idea what that does.
I feel like this is important.
Should I do something with that?
What is the point?
Alright, bye. Is this a safe room? Can I come back here and...
I have no clothes.
Don't look at lady. Look at the dust cloud.
And do I have to run from lady?
The hallways connect and it just causes me so much fucking stress.
Is it? I don't know. Is that it? I don't know what that is.
I don't know what that is. Someone's crawling.
I don't know what that is.
Somebody's like crawling on the ceiling?
Somebody crawling on the ceiling? I don't know.
This is horrible.
Ugh. Damn it.
God damn it. I don't know what I'm doing.
God damn it. It's lady. Don't look at the lady.
God damn it.
God! Is that a boss? Is that a guy? Is that a boss?
Is it a boss?
Is it a skeleton or a boss?
I don't know. I don't know.
No, I'm not. I gotta move. Where am I gonna go?
Is it a dust cloud? Is it a dust cloud behind me?
This is unbearable.
Holy shit. Come on, give me the eye.
No, another dead end.
Shit.
Is that the lady or is that the...
It's a smoke man.
That's a smoke guy, right?
Stare at the smoke.
Down, down, down, down, down, down,
out, out, out, out, out.
Okay. Do you go away?
Mission accomplished.
No, how dare you come out now.
How dare you come out now.
Is that a person? I don't know.
Wait a minute. Is that a thing? What is that thing?
Yeah, yeah.
I was never scared of small places
but the walls of these narrow corridors seem to be
suffering from a lot of attempts to feel like I can't breathe. Yeah, fine.
Oh, fuck.
I don't know if it's the lady or if it's the smoke.
It's not the smoke.
It's not the smoke. It's smoke, I think, right?
It's not smoke. It's not smoke.
It's smoke!
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Okay, straight ahead.
I don't care about shit about money.
I don't care about money.
Can I turn that? Can I please pull this?
Sir?
I hear him again.
Don't you dare.
Get down. Back to hell.
Why can I not pull that?
I have to go to the doctor after this.
So why can I not pull this?
Where is this damn thing?
Left and then down this hole.
Okay, here's what I need you guys to do for me.
I need you guys to scream in the chat
Is that lady or smoke? My brain, I can't do it.
You understand?
Is that lady or smoke? Which one is it?
Is that lady or smoke?
Which one is that one?
Lady?
Is it smoke?
I hear something.
I'm fucking panicking right now.
This is so bad.
I don't know.
Don't listen to chat.
Sweat is fogging up these mirrors.
Almost there.
I'm there.
Hey!
It's a smoke person. I think it's a smoke person.
I'm not cut out for these games.
There it is.
I tapped something. What did I tap?
What happened?
Is this what I wanted when I decided to come here?
This is a horrible place. I always knew what it would be.
Why am I here?
An exit.
Am I out? Is this wind?
I missed oil. It's alright.
I've been missing some fucking brain cells after this one.
I'm too neurotic of a person to play these games.
This is too more to do.
I think I'm just gonna go, like I said before,
with the original tactic
of just run as fast as I can to the exit.
I feel like that's gonna be a good idea.
Good luck.
My back hurts right now.
This is just like tense.
I'm gonna have to go get like a massage.
Oh, you have a lot of tension.
Wow, is this from work?
Uh, I mean, maybe.
Oh, wow.
Do you like construction?
Do you sit down for a long time?
I was playing a VR game on Twitch.
I was playing a horror game.
Oh, yeah, that's what I did for work.
That's fucking kind of weird, but okay.
Do a narrow-toed run into the entrance. Sure.
No, it's the other thing. Hold on.
There you go. It's time to go.
I'm not gonna waste any time. Get it open.
Go.
Fuck you! Fuck you!
It's a lady. It's a lady.
I need to not look at the lady. Look at the statue.
I need to look at the statue. Don't tell me
to look at the statue that's right here.
The statue... Oh, would you look at the
statue that's right there. You know,
the fucking monster that's gonna jump
in your face because you looked at the statue.
Oh, man, that thing.
He got off the pedestal, right?
That's what this is.
Punch it.
Who's doing that one?
Am I gonna get crowded by monsters?
I have to move. I gotta move.
But I don't know what that means. If I turn around, is he gonna follow me?
I don't know.
I don't understand. If I leave this room, is he gonna follow me behind me?
I don't know what to do here.
I'm so fucking... I don't know.
The door's open here.
Okay, I'm gonna say left.
Okay, fuck you. Bye.
Don't look at the lady. Look at the smoke
and look at the statue guy. Is he behind me?
Fucking crawling.
Oh, God.
Go, go, go, go. Out, out, out, out.
Oil, oil, oil, oil in the can.
Go, go, go.
Oh, you bitch. No.
It's the same room?
Oh!
Only one more and I get a prize.
Um, what the hell is that?
This is it. One more.
This game's crazy. Look in that door.
What?
I've already been down there. Don't, don't.
Your fly is down. I don't have a fly right now.
I'm wearing workout pants.
Alright, let's go.
Am I getting a shield?
Do I get to have a shield?
That's a huge shield.
So let me just clarify this one more time.
The statue,
I've got to look at that statue. You guys are not just fucking with me.
That's a real monster.
I just want to make sure.
So I've got to burn smoke guy,
don't look at lady, look at statue.
I'm going to have to like,
I'm going to have to wipe down this visor.
It's so dirty from my sweat.
Give me like a lucky break right here.
And it's right here. I don't even care about that.
This is a difficult lock. Let's just get it open.
I hear somebody.
I hear something.
Is that the gargoyle?
What the fuck is that?
What did I do about the giant dog?
This has been like a YouTuber scream stream.
This has been just like,
welcome to my YouTube channel.
I scream at horror games.
Thankfully, thank God I'm standing up in a position
where I'm away from the microphone.
The mic would have peaked like 16 times tonight.
Thank God it's bouncing off the walls.
That guy was huge.
Oh, that sucks.
Oh,
that thing's ridiculous.
Where's the right way to look?
I think it's so scary.
It's so much bigger than everything, too.
And this is all procedurally generated.
Now that I know he exists,
I don't want to play anymore.
Is he
coming down this hall?
I think he's behind me.
Hello?
Somebody's opened a door.
Can he open doors?
Shh, calm down. I'm gonna hate these little rooms.
I'm gonna come out here and bang him right.
Can he open doors?
Do you hear something?
Shit! Shit, man!
Okay, it's gonna be right here to the left.
It's gonna be in this room.
Damn it! It's not in there.
I don't even want to go in there.
It's gonna be right in here, right to the left, and right in this room.
Oh, thank God it's one of those sanctuary rooms.
Oh, yes.
I'm safe in here, right?
Thank God. I just heard a person.
I just heard a person.
Are we certain of this?
Why did I hear somebody's voice?
It's right in here, right?
Don't do me like this.
I hear something.
Bullshit! That's a lady, right?
No, what does that mean?
I don't know what that thing means.
I think that attracts people.
No, that attracts a bad person.
Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Is it the smoke?
Is it smoke?
I think the smoke guy is literally right behind me.
I think it's smoke.
I don't know what to do. I'm scared.
I'm not gonna answer it. Just give me the keys.
Just give me the keys.
Just give me the fucking keys. Where are the keys?
I looked everywhere. Where are the goddamn keys?
Where are the goddamn keys? I don't even know what I'm looking at here.
What the fuck is this?
Motherfucker. Come on.
It's gonna be in this room.
You son of a bitch.
Smoke guy.
How dare you?
What? Look at him!
What the fuck?
What happened?
I was holding the lantern in his face.
Was there no oil in the lamp?
Not enough oil?
Didn't I just fill it?
Shadows don't care.
It needs to be refilled immediately.
I checked so many places too.
That whole map was uncovered.
And I only had the two places I didn't go.
I got destroyed.
Gonna talk to the face on the wall.
This thing.
Why did you wake us?
Paid two coins. But what?
What am I paying for?
You have 21 old coins. You wish to pay the price?
Ask.
You were drawn here by the shadows.
Enthralled by them.
It was you who stepped into the darkness.
It was you who chose to be bound by it.
You are nothing but their pawn.
Did this cost me two dollars for that?
Now you're gonna go in a shell?
There's two bucks.
Okay.
I'm so close too.
Damn. I had it.
It was so much stress but I almost did it.
I was almost ready. I was almost out of there.
I gotta make sure I'm in the right spot here.
I thought it was dark in this room.
Alright. Let's just start here.
I'm gonna try again.
I felt something just on my neck but it's my sweat.
A sweat bead just went down the back of my neck.
And I thought it was a bug.
Jesus.
Can I talk to this thing?
This thing doesn't want to speak to me.
Alright.
I was so close.
Just let me get lucky here.
What if I just hold my fist?
Oh my fucking Jesus! My God!
You can't get in here!
Come on. Just give me the key.
Let me get out of this fucking place.
Where's that dog again?
Where's that darn dog?
The lady's in here with me.
Close the door.
Just leave me the fuck alone.
I can't believe it.
Can't believe it that she's in here.
And is there a smoke monster?
Can you spawn in here as well?
You've got to be fucking shitting me, sir.
Okay, well that was fun at the party.
The fucking scary people.
The scary people party. That was fun of us to go out and hang out here.
A full squad just landed on me.
I have to go that way.
I have to go this way.
Get me out of the doorway, please.
Sanctuary room.
Ah.
Show me with light in the
sanctuary room of our father.
Thank God.
What the hell do you want to tell me, lady?
What is your question?
About the coins.
Token of devotion.
What? What?
What is it?
What is it? Something in my
sanctuary room? Something in my
sanctuary room?
Is it the lady?
What are you doing in my fucking room?
Guys?
Let's go over here.
This is horrible.
This is the most stressed I've ever been on a stream.
Am I? Ever.
This is the most stressed I've ever been.
It's the fucking lady again. They're just like dumping on me.
They're collapsing on me.
Light in the lantern. I don't have any more light.
Left trigger. Turn the light back on.
What the fuck is happening?
Why is this happening to me?
They're relentless.
They are relentless.
I think I've had enough fun.
I think it's time for me to
do something else.
I'm going to go take a bath.
God damn it.
I hear the dog now.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Give it to me. Come on.
Give me the key. It's got to be right in here.
I don't have any more lantern oil.
Do I? Nope.
Right here. Key.
Do it. Key.
Yeah.
Thank God.
Man, this is unbelievable.
Now I see why people wanted me to play this.
This is like one of the nerve wracking.
There's so many people surrounding you that have different
traits.
Wait. Should I learn some more info?
I'm going to summon a demon right now.
Is it too late?
No.
There it is. There's another level.
Yes. I'd like to talk.
Oh, man.
We demand payment.
Ask why only one...
Where were you before?
Another wanderer.
From beyond the walls of this world.
I'd rather just sell these tokens
on eBay.
You can probably get like a hundred bucks
per token. Some ancient artifact?
Are you kidding me?
Alright, well, let's see what's in store here.
Make sure I'm facing the right way.
I am.
There's more.
I actually have to do more of this shit.
This looks different.
Is this different?
What is this for?
Hey, I need some...
We demand payment.
Ask about the corpses. Ask about...
All the wanderers just like you
judged unworthy,
devoured by the shadows.
Okay.
Now it's three coins.
Your price went up.
What the hell? I can die from that thing?
I only have...
oil.
Fuck off with this.
What the hell is this?
Oh, you're going to make me do like a gauntlet here?
Well, this is fun, guys.
Thanks for playing. Thanks for hanging out.
The stone here is colder, sharper. I think I'm getting
closer to the pillars. I can hear their call.
This was Blast.
I hope you guys enjoyed it.
Give me some oil or something.
I mean, this is like a new hub world.
This is not going to be a new hub world,
right? It doesn't look like it.
It is a new hub world.
This game is
ten hours.
What?
This is like a 30 minute
stream experience.
It only takes so much of this in one sitting.
Ridiculous, though. Look at how much bigger
the areas are.
This is times two.
The amount of stress.
I can't even speak.
See you later. That's enough.
That's enough.
Yeah, that's enough.
I'm just going to walk over here and turn it off.
That's enough.
See you later. Bye.
Coward.
No, I can't.
I'll take beating the first area.
Finish it. Finish it.
I'm going to go ahead and go for...
We're going to play the boxing game.
I have not left the game.
That's right. I think there's a monster about to come over to me.
I'm going to play it with the OBS preview.
Ugh.
Copy the Wii.
You were almost done. You were one guide super hard.
Really? You got one
guide. Where's this lady?
She's not even here.
At least see the monster.
I'll at least see what the monster is.
And then I'm going to take another quick break.
Come back and we'll do the boxing game for a little while.
Alright, let's go see the monster.
No, I'll look it up on YouTube.
I'm going to YouTube it.
It's so quiet. I'll look it up on YouTube.
No, I'll look it up on YouTube.
Right around this corner.
Pretend I'm on a YouTube video.
I'm on a YouTube VR video.
I don't know what it is. Is it in here?
I got
this
I can't
I can't do it.
It's so big.
Why did you wake us?
We must speak
when you bring payment.
Those are the rules, and we will follow them.
But we are not here for your
amusement, Wanderer.
It's fucking fantastic.
Here we go.
I'm ready. Let's go. Come on.
One more.
What's the gimmick for this new guy?
What's the gimmick for the new guy?
That's how I see red.
What does that mean?
Oh shit.
He's attracted to light. Why did you just tell me to do that?
What the hell is that guy?
How do I blow it out?
Do I have to stand still?
Jesus Christ.
Dog.
Is it a dog?
It's the dog, isn't it?
Is it the dog?
Yeah, it is. What?
Be in here.
I'm regressing.
I don't even know what it said.
I have no idea. We gotta go.
I'm just regressing to noises and shit.
I'm gone forever.
Right through this door. You gotta be in here.
Let's see what this lady has to say.
Oh no. Oh no.
Shut. What?
Don't leave me alone.
What's this say?
An ear piercing scream suddenly filled the dungeon without us sleeping.
It took me a few seconds to realize it was mine.
Get off the screen.
Look at how far away this took me. I don't care.
Son of a bitch.
Procedurally random generated.
Do these things attack?
One, two, three, go.
I woke up. Who cares?
Give me the eye.
I've gone so far around this whole damn thing.
Oh no, it's the dog.
But where is it?
Which way is the dog?
You stupid lady.
Fucking close.
I gotta be close.
It's the lady.
Come on, look at this shit.
Oh no.
I gotta go to the left,
and then out, and then right.
Is she here? The lady.
How did he get in there?
He can go down there? Not even possible.
Oh my god.
It's not the dog, it's that guy.
It's that bad guy. He looks like a fucking goat.
Okay.
End this.
Oh shit.
It's up there.
Oh fuck off, will ya?
Look at how much of this. I beat it, I win.
Hello?
Should I not have done that?
I maybe should not have done that.
What's the fastest way for me to get there?
Bang up right, and then bang up right.
Straighten.
Motherfucker, just pretend I beat it.
I don't know what it is.
That's a thing!
What is that thing? I don't know!
Should I stop moving?
I don't know what it is, I'm just gonna die.
Go!
Fuck you!
You can't do this to me.
How close I am.
One little bit, right here.
Oh my god, I win. I beat the game.
Open!
Open?
Jesus.
I stuck it through when I did it.
That's the end.
I'll see the ending cutscene, please.
Hey, the ending cutscene.
Give it to me.
I hope this is the end.
Is this not it?
I thought this was it.
Is it an eyeball?
I thought you guessed it was the end of the game.
Is this supposed to be like a cutscene?
Like the ending cutscene?
I don't know.
I mean, it looks pretty linear.
Only two more.
New hub, two more, two more.
No, I gotta get out of that.
That game is a ton of fun and it's so stressful.
But, I can't do that anymore.
It's gonna actually kill me.
So we're gonna move on.
We're probably gonna end on...
I was gonna play Mind Show, but I don't know if I'm gonna have enough time to do it.
I feel like I'm gonna have to start with Mind Show.
Because I've exhausted myself.
I'm gonna have to start with Mind Show another day.
No, Mind Show, not Minecraft.
Let me take another break.
I'm just gonna get some more water thrown in my face.
And we'll come back and we might just play the boxing game for like a little while.
I'll be right back.
What? Is something in here?
I don't see anything.
Alright, I'll see you guys in a minute.
I can't leave up track to the game.
Okay. Hello again.
We are now gonna jump into...
Oh, let's see.
Something like easy and relaxing.
Although I'm not entirely sure that the boxing game will be very relaxing.
Let's do it.
What the hell is it there? It's Creed.
This looks really fun, actually.
I can't even remember what I was even saying during that stream.
Hopefully that was an interesting experience for all of you.
Have I done Superhot? Yeah, I did a Superhot VR last week.
Let's try Creed.
Alright, going back in.
What's the battery life on these things?
Should I turn the lights back up?
I probably should.
Let me turn the lights on.
A bit higher than they are now. That's better.
That looks good.
So I heard this game is pretty realistic.
It really feels like you're fighting.
Press any button to calibrate.
So press any button to calibrate.
What the fuck?
That's not correct.
That doesn't look right.
Hold on. What happened there?
Stop stream. End of the stream.
I think that's better.
Hey, look. There we go.
This is also pretty wild.
Ok. Alright.
Career. Free play. Options.
Am I standing in a good spot?
Ok.
Gameplay. Graphics. Gameplay. Comfort mode.
On. Reset profile. Advanced.
Local motion. What does that mean?
Yeah, I know it's times two. Don't worry.
Gameplay. Let's just go through it.
Career. Pro.
I probably should change the title too. I didn't.
Delta Gym.
Seven months before underground championship.
Oh, this is cool.
I thought that was me.
Actually me.
Hold the trackpad while swinging your arms.
Ok.
Anything else you'd like to tell me?
Oh. Punch.
Punch harder for more damage.
Harder than that.
These are going to fly off.
This is kind of cutting off circulation.
How am I using a cell phone with these on?
Come on in.
Teach me.
Hey, there he is.
Let me show you what I can do.
Huh?
I just used all my energy.
I don't think I can even make it over there.
What? Oh.
Ok. Hold on.
Whoa.
Let's go. Train me.
Hey, Bonham.
I got to tie this.
This is going to be tighter.
I'm going to move around so much this is going to be bad.
This is going to fly off my head.
Ok. Defend with gloves.
Sounds easy enough.
Dodge punches to trigger slow-mo.
I'm going to see you guys every time.
Do I have enough room?
I will break something here.
Finish exercise as quick as possible.
Ok.
Stand in the center of your play space.
While counting down.
Rapidly hit the target.
Swing.
This is like happening too fast.
Did I do good?
Come on. Bring it on.
I wanted a relaxing game.
Ten exceptions to training.
Training determines stamina.
Hands are slower and weaker while tired.
Punching consumes stamina.
Keep hands still to recover stamina.
Not enough oxygen is going into his brain.
I'm fine. Don't worry.
First combatant.
Do you think you're going to take on me?
He's 0-12.
Well, what do you got?
Huh?
You're going to rip that off the bottom of your chin.
Keep this above the belt and inside the ring.
The fight starts as soon as you touch gloves.
Ok.
As soon as we touch gloves.
I didn't even let him count.
That's not how you box.
I would get thrown out of the gym.
I'm trying to get him in the stomach.
That's not how I would get tossed.
Dammit.
He's done.
He's out.
How is he going to go out?
What?
Whoa, what did I hit?
I'm going to go for the legs.
Where am I going?
I just beat the shit out of his head.
5.
Fuck you.
You want to come fuck with me?
Don't wake that up.
Label.
I did it.
This trip is tired.
I am.
Come on, I need this exercise though.
That was fucking funny.
I showed that motherfucker who's boss.
Yeah.
Where?
Okay.
Dodge, punch the bag without missing.
Dodge when ball glows red.
Okay.
I win.
Hey.
Alright, let's go.
You and me in the ring.
Why is it counting?
What are you doing?
This has been the longest 3 seconds ever.
What the fuck?
Alright, come on.
I've done training. Let me fight the next guy.
Alright, go.
I don't care. I'll take 3 out of 5.
I will take the same rating as a pizza hut.
That's alright with me.
Yeah, begin fight. Let's go.
Who's next?
Come on. You're next.
In fact, you know what? Fuck this.
Oh, that's a guy I gotta fight.
This is not a thesis guy that has knockouts.
That's me.
Give me that fucking mic.
I got something to say.
Why would I do that?
Ooh, right in the face.
Get down.
Uh oh, easy.
Oh shit. What do I do?
I keep on getting knocked out.
Over and over again.
I get knocked out like 6 times.
What's wrong with my leg?
Oh, right in the fucking head.
Shit, I'm losing audio.
Hold on, I gotta put my head back.
Put my head back.
It's time to play defensively.
I got him.
You're dead motherfucker.
Ah, I shattered my leg.
I was being a dick and I broke my leg in half.
Oh man.
I'm gonna be so sloppy in the next fight.
This is not fair.
Typical.
Typically you should fight in a boxing match.
You don't fight again 10 minutes later.
It takes like 6 months to recover.
Whatever.
What do you got for me?
More training?
Oh god.
Okay, I gotta...
Alright.
Alright, scan him.
You can't do it.
Hang on.
You're gonna kill me.
Don't have like a McDonald's rating.
That's all I care about.
No McDonald's rating and I'll be fine.
I have to have a better fucking local McDonald's.
Ah, shit.
I gotta do a new tactic on this next fight.
Here's the new tactic, you'll see.
Guaranteed victory.
I'm gonna Toy Story this fucking guy coming up.
Oh no, this is like a championship fight.
Oh shit.
This guy's huge.
Dwayne Reynolds.
He's 29 and 0.
Okay.
Here we go.
Oh boy.
Okay.
We got it.
Good luck.
Just wanna say, I respect you.
And I think you're a very good fighter.
And I've been looking up to you for a long time.
This would be the worst fight you could ever go to.
This would be embarrassing.
Work on the body.
Whoa, what?
I knocked him out.
God damn it.
Damn it.
Where the hell have you been?
I don't know how to dodge that.
No, come here.
No.
He's gonna get up.
I'll get you this time.
Starting the fight on your back.
No, I'll be fine.
I'll be fine.
Just give me a second.
Yes, that's me.
Alright.
Yeah, I'm ready.
Yeah, let's go motherfucker.
You and me.
There's this guy.
I'm gonna puke.
How do I grab? Can I grab him?
Come here.
Whoa, what?
Oh, am I supposed to be at my desk?
You know, it's too tired.
I can't.
He's been beaten up too many times.
He's been punched too many times in the face.
And so that's what I told him.
Like, oh, you're gonna go to the grocery store without me?
Make sure you pick up some Pringles.
You know what I'm saying?
God.
There's gotta be a strategy I can do here.
Check's activated!
Get out!
Fuck!
No!
Alright.
Get back to the gym.
Maybe I'll put this over here for a
just a moment.
Put this over here.
One sip of soda is not hydration.
I'm alright.
I'll get some water.
I'll get some real water.
Let's go, hey, let's go play a
relaxing game.
I'll be right back.
...
see that my face okay here let's take a look look at this this is somebody I like
was just in like a fire you know what I mean like it's all right I'm good that
mark yeah it's like let me get let me get off cam just been run I've been
run through all right give me one second all right I had to ask him
something all righty whoo he died it's so
weird to see the cuz I've better twitched if you know it's really interesting to
see the the red outline but anywho thank you too we had sticks renegade fifty
bucks we had a bunch of community subs too which I'll go over but thank you
sticks renegade for the 50 bucks earlier thank you so much it was very
very the very beginning Alec thanks for the three bucks Alec popcorn or pretzel
um that's tough probably pretzel pretzels are just just so versatile I
mean you could put sugar and cheese on popcorn but you could you could turn
pretzels into bread you can make them crunchy they can do a lot more I love
popcorn though I do love it mr. Kool-Aid thanks for the four
dollars mr. Kool-Aid hey Jerma since February is a short month can I get my
subscription pro rated I look forward to my reimbursement pro rated yeah
that is true it I mean it still is it's $4.99 still right should be like $4.81
but thank you mr. Kool-Aid thank you to Stevie the ex Evie thanks for the
ten bucks thought I'd donate as a small tuppence of how you much you
mean to me I was in a very dark place long ago and your pep talk in the
master of comedy about figuring out what to do at any age really broke
me out of it bit and motivated me I genuinely believe you one of the
greatest internet entertainers ever thank you so much for being you that's
an incredibly fucking nice thing to say thank you
Stevie really appreciate it that means a lot I just I'm just happy that you
have fun it's all I care about as long as you're having a good time
that's what I care about and thank you for the ten bucks really
appreciate it hey Divus thanks the 250 Divus thank you also to mostly lost
for the 250 the headset was too tight after Kim used it I didn't know it was
possible for another human to have to be smaller than you I thought you're
gonna say smaller head smaller head because yeah I've made my heads a
little bigger than her the neck but thank you thank you trust no one for
the 250 hey German I'm pretty sure your today's VR experience will be
worth watching so far none of my eyes are gone my ears are on the
other hand that shotgun sound I'm sorry we try to fix it like three
times anyway I guess you may recognize my name and you can find some YouTube
link below hope you have not already realized what is going to happen oh
hold on I got it I gotta prepare for this one hold on a second is it gonna
be a rick roll that's a good question I am gonna hold on I gotta
get up if this thing is still doing the relaxing thing I gotta close out
relaxation VR I'm gonna get known well let's see what happens I have to make
change this to not be on the vibe currently is hey now I can hear it okay
see what this is give it a click Wow you actually did it no you didn't
how do you did you how did you do this how would you have taken this
material and done this oh my god hold on I gotta put this on stream you
actually did the Mark Wahlberg you laugh you lose Will Ferrell Mark Wahlberg
thing I don't believe it I can't wait to watch this wait why is it not coming
through wait wait wait wait wait this is not playing through the stream hold
on let's see a possibility okay we'll restart it I don't know if it's gonna
happen hey hey restart it yeah I had the wrong I had the wrong things
selected the vibe takes over your computer's audio for some reason hey
look at that now we can see it good luck good luck with this one I don't
see a possibility I don't know how you do this I don't know if it's gonna
happen hey hey yeah so you still doing that thing you still in a still
what are you doing what do you call a lazy doctor lazy boy what do you call
someone who gets mad when they don't have any bread it's called wasting
time did you hear about the superhero with a lisp that always worked out
speed what kind of car does an egg drive me in a clown car driving the
clown car what was the foots favorite type of chips somebody's asshole what
did the plumber say to the singer do you eat ass boy what do you call a
person who doesn't believe in Santa Claus eggnog stick eggnog stick it's my
birthday today thanks everybody it's put me in the video what's next next time
I wonder what I did five oh it's just you laugh you lose again we've hit the
wall oh no it's the same video is it the same video that wasn't the same
video was that the same video no it wasn't hold on wait a minute you laugh
you lose Jeremy Elbertson no it's his this one all right we're gonna play
this one we're gonna get to the end of this one something for the entire
herpossal genes okay all right here we go ready no none of this counts god
damn it will Farrell and Mark Wahlberg insult each other putting in a lot of
work oh my god thank you trust no one again for your never-ending video
contributions put me in the video that was awesome thank you moving on here
also thank you to from Timmy Tim Tam thank you Tim Tim Tim the 250 yo these
pills are giving me mad shits I mean mad shits oh I'm a fucking idiot I
didn't link your video what am I stupid why would I not do that sorry
about that but thank you Tim Tim Tam thank you Marvish Magali for the 250
hi Jerma I subscribe to this channel exactly one year ago but I've known
you since the TF2 days just want to thank you for all you've done thanks
for helping me improve my English really that's cool the hell yeah forget
me in the TF2 community where I meet a lot of wonderful people thanks for
all the content the perfect antidote for sadness and melancholy I've thrown
away three years of University and I just joined dentistry school and I'm
loving it my next objective is getting my bit badge red dentistry
school well there you go that's a pretty high-skilled job that's awesome
and that's really great that you're loving it hope you keep enjoying it
thanks for the 250 and thanks for being part of the community mine is red thank
you though so much also thank you to daring ocelot code ban chunky baloney
I'm reading oh I'm mad my mistake I'm reading one dollar what am I doing
what am I thinking no but thank you anyways guys Joan smokes junior thanks
to the five bucks here's some bits have a coffee on me thanks for the great
streams German heart thank you Jones thanks anyway no thank you guys for any
amount of bits you give to this channel thank you and thank you Joan
smoke junior the streamer thumbnail face was spot-on failure is gonna come
back and potentially bite me on the ass smoking viewer oh thank you
axion for the 250 hey German you said you have to do you said I have
to do German news bloopers bloopers twice so here it is you need to break the
cycle this time because I don't think I got another one in me the well is
running dry just search it on YouTube like the last time how you did you
guys above bloopers this is part two this is Paris part two I can't believe
how you guys just turn these up put it on here this is news bloopers part
two news reporter Mike Amor learned what an occupational hazard while
shooting a story can be he was standing beside a Skype rat when these
happen thousands of additional scapegoat just take eight double stuff Oreos and
put them in a glass fill it up with milk and eat it with the ninja turtle
Michelangelo made an appearance
I mean come on really pleased to be there
wow that was really dramatic there's a reason they call these people heroes I
mean they were going at a really good clip there we've had some hot weather I
guess you know the good news is yes
something please rice breaks his silence today apologizing to his
something please that he attacked his wife knocking her something in a
casino elevator this last February oh no wait no wait no no no no that is not
the right video but rice has been suspended
scandals happen all the time the question is how do democracies respond
to those scandals and what will it mean for for the wider region I think
one of your children's just walked in I mean shift is shifting shifting sands
in the region do the relations with the north may change um I would be
surprised they do
I'm gonna die NHL miked up trash talk oh man god damn it
oh that's not the right video you know I've got the time no idea what
happened there oh yeah you guys are fucking hilarious seriously my god you
guys put together such fucking hilarious shit thank you axion the
cycle continued that was amazing but thank you fh Gregory for the 250 hey
Jerma my brother Sean and I have been watching have been fans of yours for
a while and I want to say thanks for giving us something to bond over we
love your content I catch the streams and he watches the VODs but lately he
keeps asking me what meat hub is he says you keep bringing it up oh I can't
remember having you heard it before maybe it was that stream I missed
with Vinnie vinesauce anyways thanks for all the laughs and keep up the
terrific work I've never even mentioned those two words I don't think
I've even said either one of those two words separately oh my god
that's fucking didn't say meat yeah I've never said meat before thank you
froding weapon for the 250 don't eat cigarettes in your sleep they're bad
for you I will not I don't know why it tasted like tobacco thank you Jess
you got it for the 250 tobacco is a good source of vitamins don't forget
a crunchy cigarette part of a balanced breakfast this is not real
medical advice do not listen to that it's not actual medical advice but
thank you thank you to neb na Jess you got it for the 250 hey can you play the
Lion King bonus feature game from the DVDs there's one that's like the
kayak game but way better what what is that for real that the
Lion King DVD has a game on it that's interesting thank you deus
morte for the 250 hey buddy looking very healthy today I guess don't agree
with you wearing that red shirt just thought I'll let you know that the
Phoenix Wright collection comes out on Steam on April 9th don't forget or I'll
be sad I will not I'm looking forward to it that has a do you want to be a
millionaire game on it why happy birthday Nebula brand by the way it's
caught it that's your 21st birthday happy birthday also we had some
community subs come in from Magellan thank you Magellan for the five
community subs thank you great Canadian fuck club for the five community
subs as well as well thank you both of you thank you to GTX 1080 quad SLI just
two minutes ago here for the 250 hey Jeremy when's the next movie night also
are you gonna play more Resident Evil 2 yeah I got actually me and the
mods we're talking about the encore night happening sooner rather than
later there's no music oh shit whoops yeah that's probably gonna be
put together fairly soon here so you'll see that I want I want to try to get
that ready in the next couple of weeks and music sad face but thank you GTX
1080 that the TJ thank you the TJ for the five dollars and they say thank
the German want to thank you for all that you do for me in the first thank
you to be what you do for me in the place I met mentally right now
since I joined the military life has been lonely a little contact of
family and friends it's hard but luckily I have something to look forward
to when I get back from flying and get back from my deployments to
Afghanistan from a longtime fan these bits are for you fella get yourself
something special thank you so much TJ we look forward to your return much
love to you thank you so much take care of yourself that's the best one I
anytime I love looking over here and seeing the chat so supportive so
wonderful really it's amazing it's great stuff thank you to shadows one
discipline for the 250 Germany ever heard of a game called road trip
adventure on PlayStation 2 it's an RPG would you play as a car I've never
heard of that that's interesting and a car RPG maybe we'll have to look
into that a car a car PG one would say and look what's popping up here
all the subs I was gonna run this earlier I just was so tired thank you
everybody the massive amount of subs this channel takes in you guys are
fucking awesome thank you so much much love to y'all and holy shit great
Canadian fuck club just came with a hundred bucks another hundred dollars
from great Canadian German makes me laugh that's so much money you can
you've given so much over the last few months all I can say is thank you I'm
happy that you like being here happy that you think it's fun to be around
the great Canadian coming it again and then we had another one from code man
ten bucks from code man they say just want to say thanks for the
entertainment you give us all you're one of the best streamers on the
platform no joke I'm so I'm honored and happy that you think that I try
to put forth the best streams I can and you know sometimes swing and miss
sometimes you swing and get a base hit I'm just gonna keep trying to have fun
you know I just like having fun and it's awesome to have a bunch of
people that also think the same things are fun and funny it's pretty
awesome actually this one was a miss wait no what that was one of the
most intense live streams I've done it like probably six months I
almost passed out on stream today that was intensity Kappa means sarcasm off I'm
sorry I just installed BT TV I didn't understand and then right at the end
clue the sniper thanks to 250 thank you guys a little bit on the shorter
scale today just under five hours I I cannot lie to you guys though after
that horror game and after the first I know after the second training session
in Creed I didn't think I was gonna make it I love I took one sip of Coke
and somebody's just like what the fuck are you doing that's that's not
gonna do anything and I'm just like oh wait a minute they're like they're
actually right yeah I can't I actually cannot screen tomorrow I have a
obligation I have to take care of and we're gonna come back I'll
probably do two or three days in a row Saturday is me and star gonna play VR
we're gonna do rec room we're just gonna have some fun maybe a couple of
other co-op games should be just a chill time you should play onward
together yeah we've been looking at VR titles that had multiplayer but yeah
nothing tomorrow I've got an obligation I have to take care of had quite a
few of those the last few days unfortunately but that's life you know
hope you had a good time tonight I had a blast I was a little
exhausted but you know I might like inner tuba shot out today have a great
rest of your night I will see you guys and who's in any streaming right now
who's like streaming right now anybody I cannot load any channels like
following a web page is slowing down your browser would you like us to
stop it what the fuck am I still live this is odd what web page is
my browser down there you guys are let me see who's screaming why can I not
open anything all right we got criken got Vinny Joel Nova there's a quite a
few people of streaming right now still Joel and I still have to do our
fucking gamer challenge let's uh let's let's let's go let's let's write
Vinny it's been a while since we read it Vinny we rated a Nova a
couple weeks back and then Joel before that let's go let's go Ray Vinny he's
playing a kid Icarus uprising right now interestingly enough moon's at the
ready let me just get ready here and let's open it up raid fine sauce yeah
so I'll see you guys on Saturday mean star gonna do more VR queue up if
you'd like to if not then we'll see you soon take care everybody have a
wonderful rest of your night