Goddammit. I went downstairs, and when I came back up, my Scribblio link expired.
So, I wrote a bunch of names. I wrote a bunch of custom things to Scribble.
And the gah. It's alright. Yeah, hold on. I got the quickest hands in the west.
Okay. Alright. Yeah, okay. Wait, oh! People don't even know what the fuck is going on.
Uh, hi! First of all, how are you? Today, uh, yeah, I just... I just started the stream as
if everybody knew what we were doing. Oh, my link expired! What link? German, what are you
talking about? Well, the next couple days, including today, are going to be, uh, chill,
short streams. It's getting down to the last seven days or so, six days, before the carnival.
And I really, really, really... I gotta put... Essentially, that's where all my brain is right
now. I'm having meetings every day over, um, the phone. It's... That is where my brain is
at the moment. So, I... As of today, I can't really focus on stream-related stuff, so we're
just gonna hang out. Tomorrow, though, is the activity book stream. We're going to go through
a bunch of the cool shit that you guys have done. That's also gonna be only probably a few hours,
because once I'm done with this stream, boom, I'm out of here. I'm literally gonna go and
do a bunch of other shit. Tomorrow, the second that stream is over, see ya. I'm out. I'm gonna
do a bunch of shit for that stream on the 21st. So, the next couple days, we're just gonna hang
out. Maybe this stream will be a few hours. Maybe. Depends. But don't expect the next couple streams
to be more than, like, six, seven, eight hours, like they are sometimes. But, what we're doing
today, that we're just gonna hang out, we are going to do something that has been incredibly
highly requested by everybody. And, I mean, every single person has requested this at least one
time. It's to play Scribbleio with your friends. And who better than you guys? You know? Who? You
did. I did. Yes, you did. I have a... Look, the only way I said I was gonna do this is if I looked
up a log, and if every single person that's ever come into this room, into the chat room,
at least once did they say, please play Scribbleio, is the only way I was gonna do it. And they did.
So, how this is gonna work is the sub discord is currently open. I have an invite link. I'm
just gonna send it in there. It's gonna be a sub only thing, because you know how player people are.
Speaking of subs, five of you just may have gotten a chance to do it. Whoever the five of you,
get in that discord right now. It might be you. What the fuck is this? Don't link gifts in here.
That was back in the five community subs. Thank you, back in. And I didn't even tweet anything.
I've been so scattered. I'm so fucking like lit right now. Yes, I did say that.
I have a coach now. I have a Twitch coach. Told me to use the word lit more often. Told me to use
the word epic more often. And I'm gonna see if it works. He guaranteed me five to ten percent more
viewership if I did that. Let me just make a tweet. I'll be right back. Is chilling out with a crayon
in my hand make sense for this stream? I don't think it does. How about, because it's a drawing.
There's another drawing game that I'm doing after this too. I fucking don't know. I don't
know. I never know what to write here. This is, I'm gonna give you guys the bane of a streamer
or youtuber's existence. This is like creating a new character every day in a game. I don't know
what this guy's name is gonna be. I don't know what this stream's attributes are at the moment.
AdventureMFDan, thanks for the five subs. I'm just gonna write drawing and drawing and decline.
No, that makes it. Drawing and, that's it. Drawing in. Because I don't know what the end is. Done?
Okay. Drawing in. All right, the link is about to go into the sub discord. I suggest you go fast
because it ain't gonna be there for very long. And people right now are doing something they're
not supposed to be doing in this channel. They're spamming and they're gonna get in trouble.
I've got all your names. I'm waiting for it to settle down in here.
That's right. Yeah, you're doing the monkey ass. You're not supposed to be spamming in this channel.
Here it comes. You've, I'm only doing this once, so blame your fellow sub discord member.
Okay, so I think, does that, does that mean that it's all been dumped in here? Is that what that
means? Oh shit, are you guys supposed to look at that? You guys weren't supposed to see the
words, the custom words. All right, I guess we're going. Oh, by the way, what's like my,
absolute kill switch here? How do I like ban somebody? It's my turn. No, Bruce is drawing.
Wait, but I do, I don't know all the words. It's all that you just guess. How many times can I
guess? How often can, oh wait, I don't know, it's two words. Um, tie? Bow tie. Is that a shirt?
Pre, is that a cross? What? Priest? Uh, shirt. There's a V in there.
V neck? Is there a switch? There's a switch on the shirt. Vertical shirt. TV shirt. Steve Jobs?
What? Why, was it an iPhone? Circle. Got it. Wait, people can just watch the stream.
Blueberry. Is that earth? Um, E. We're, we're, grass? Globe? Oh shit. Globe, of course.
Carrot. Anytime you see two orange lines connecting for a triangle upside down,
it's a carrot, no matter what. What is this? What is that? That's so funny. Carrot man.
Get a lot of time to draw on this one in this game. Uh, bed. Bunk bed. Is it a flag?
US, is it United States flag? What is that? Oh, forehead. No, I, no, I don't. North Canada?
Canada? Oh, help me. North? Oh, okay. I thought that said forehead or something at first.
North Canada. Kick Jermo. Well, I didn't do anything. Book? How would you get this? It's a,
it's a rectangle. It's an iPhone. It's an iPad. It's a, uh, it's a, it's a surface.
That's a surface. Oh, it's a tablet. It's a tablet. Well, I got it right. It should be like Family
Feud. If I say iPad, it should be like, you got it. I didn't make these words, guys. Like, Steve
Jobs, Apple tablets, not me. How would you get that? That quickly? Glove? That's like a South
Park hand. That's a minion. A minion. That's actually pretty good. Branch. Tree. Log. Map.
Country. Person's face. That's like, it's a nose and this, the mouth right here. A monster or
something? I don't know. A beard? Wait a minute. I, it was, you know what it gave it away? You know
what gave it away for me? The gray. This right here. A street lamp or something? A firework.
That's a nice touch. That was a nice touch. It was. All right, let me, I want to draw. Don't listen.
Don't say your answer. I'm going to type the answer. It doesn't matter. I put a sensor bar
over the text box. All right, I'll do that next round. Hat. A, um, bed? Lying in bed.
A teacher. Let's choose a chalkboard. It's just the first part. That's actually, I like this.
This. You didn't write the word chalk. That was pretty good. Oh, Otto is choosing a word. I wonder
what it's going to be. What? No. All right. All right. All right. I got it. I got it. I got it. I
got it. Boomer prince. Boomer princess. Oh. Boomer princess means queen. It's, you guys don't make
any sense of the boomer shit. That just is somebody that happens to be older than you
is a boomer. What if you're, what if you're like 40 and the person above you is 41,
are they a boomer and you not? I don't fucking, how the fuck do you spell alcohol?
Ooh, no, everyone's going to guess. Why did I? No, I got to turn. Oh yeah. Good luck. Oh,
fucking whatever. I'm still going to do it. I have to like, censor this shit. Otherwise like,
I might as well just be watching chat play this game. Is that what we're doing today?
For like the couple hours that I'm going to be here. You guys just play this game with it together.
Cover the top part. Yeah. Yeah. I hold on. I got to, I got to at least stay in the game here.
Bull. Damn it. All right. I'm going to, let me do this. I need to make some sensors here.
Okay. Background color. All right. No, what the fuck is going on? Wait, I got to guess this.
Uh, person. Kid. Man. Guy. I'm the first fucking one to get it. And now everyone's going to be
should have had that shit ready to go. Oh well. How do you? No, that looks horrible. I'm just
going to make it, just make it black. Blocked. That just looks like my computer's broken.
This is like grandma has a bunch of viruses. Trying to do like this. Are you trying to do this?
I got to do this side too. How do I turn that off? Cause people can still see that.
How is that not the sun? Just zoom it in. Yeah. But it's still going to bleed into the side here.
H. There we go. Uh, what is that? Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
What? How do I spell it? Got it. That's actually a really good. That's a good one. That's a, that,
I knew what that was just from the shape of the face. Good work.
That was Fred Flintstone. Is it my turn? All right.
Hmm. Let's see. I can't talk though. Hmm. I have a ladder. Hmm. Bed, large bed, bunk bed. It's bunk
bed. It's bunk bed. It's my, I got it before, but I can't talk. I just can't speak because every
time I talk, I give a hint. Just mute yourself. The next time the words aren't even going to
matter because I'm going to do only custom words. Good luck. You can mute the other players. Hi.
Hello. Just hello. Once you point to something, it's like, that's it. Game over.
No, that's toggle audio. Just put a face cam over there. I can't do face cam today. Um, uh, basket?
A, uh, what the fuck is that? How did I not get this? I don't know. Was it a candle? Oh, right.
Okay. It's a glue. Unblock the words at the top. I can't. That's cheating for them.
And I don't want to come in last place just because I'm the one that has the screen up.
I will get that. Okay. That really does look horrible though. That's just, it just don't look
good at all. It's fireman. There's one of the custom ones. Good. Nice work. All right. What's
this one? Hmm. What is this? That's what it is. Everybody got the word. Hey, good. That's good.
Just block where you type. Well, you'll be able to see what everyone else is writing. I don't want
you. I don't want anyone to come close. Yeah. But that lets people write this view. I know.
Why are you blocking the answers? I've seen this like 15 times already. You understand?
Everyone's screen looks like yours. I'm talking about your screen and my screen.
I've seen pee-pee poo-poo like seven times. You guys are distracting me.
Did I get it? I don't know if I did it fast enough. I don't think I did it fast enough.
It was like a one frame, I think. It doesn't matter. Okay. We're good. No, it don't matter.
Nah, it doesn't fucking matter. I didn't look. All right. But the people that didn't look,
I'm doing it. I didn't have very much time. Why are you thumbing me down? Yeah, he would.
And you want to tell me why are you blocking this? Yeah. You should only be blocking the chat
window for you. Heaven forbid somebody writes everyone right forehead and I look over here
and that's all I see. Village. Got it. At the last fucking second. How about what? It's not
what? Oh, that's pretty good. Incognito. I'm too innocent to know. Yeah, but incognito. Guys,
you don't need incognito when you live alone. Okay. What is this? What is going on right now?
I think is this like a zoo? Is it a giraffe? A t-shirt? What is that? It's supposed to be a zebra.
This is great. Um, I don't, it's a movie?
Oh, that was, that was, that was, that was adorable. That was awesome.
Hell, what? Hello? You're not going to write the whole fucking thing, are you? No.
Uh, yes, that was, that was Minecraft. All you had to do was write, hello, ladies and gentlemen,
and everybody in this room, or at least most of them. All right, my turn is coming up soon,
right? A, I knew it immediately. It was the shape of the hat. We just got five community
subs coming in from Jerma sucks. Thank you. Jerma sucks for the five subs. Appreciate that. Thank
you. I can make a fire with how fast I'm doing that. Pretty good. Pretty good.
Mm hmm. This is nice. I'm, this is relaxing. I need this. You know what I mean? I needed this
right now. All right, we've got a guy. T. Is that a T? Is that supposed to be T pose? Why is this
person huge? Uh, are they playing like poker? Food catering service? What can I do? Restaurant.
Well, I thought it was something to do with like how big this guy was.
Jerma, Jerma, that's the, you just, you did, that's the, you're not doing the American way
to spell gray. What is, um, yep. Good. Got it. That is the god of all gods of lightning.
That was a good one. You can cap that one if you want to use it for whatever you want.
It's completely royalty free by the way. That's royalty free. You can use that anywhere.
How, why would you already just guess this? This person just gets McDonald's immediately. Like,
come on. Don't be that guy on win, lose, or draw that hits the buzzer and just yells out a word.
And then they have to like pause the show. Ooh, it was tricky. Um,
what threw me off on this one was it wasn't a soda. It was a hard apple cider from what I remember.
Is the keyboard mega space bar. Sometimes I wish I had a mega space bar. If I, if there was a giant
space bar, that should kind of be pretty cool. Why? Cause it'd be like, you could put, I would
love just like a button right here, like a big one right underneath the space bar. I, you know,
I wish there was a second space bar. Hold on a second here. Uh, this is my idea. Whoever does
this later on down the road, if you're a company, I want 5% of all sales because that's bullshit.
You know where you got it from. I want a space bar under the space bar, two space bars,
two of them, one, two. You know how awesome it would be to map something to the second
space bar that's right underneath. I'm talking, we're talking crouches, jumps, slides,
even if you put a button underneath alt. So I'm talking, we're talking either between alt
and space bar have like one little long little log here. So you can just be like bang, bang on alt.
Oh, no, no, no, not a split space bar. Yuck. That's uh, you just made me almost fucking throw
up when you said that. It's my turn. No, it's not. I'm talking space bar, space bar. Cover my,
I'm going to cut. I know, I know, I know. All right. I'm covering. Uh, the answer was fortress,
by the way. Pretty good way to get fortress. All right. It's my turn. Nobody can see. Perfect.
Ooh, okay. These are all awful. Uh, that's it. That's it. That's all you, that's it. That's it.
It's, that's it. That is it. There's no other good way to do that. I'm trying to make fuss stuff.
It was bench. Yes. Hey, there it is. Game over. I lose. Thank you everybody for playing.
None of these come up. What's Jerma Odin? I don't know. I was going to see what they thought it was.
I'm going to do custom words exclusively. Uh, I'm going to make a new room and a new link,
by the way. Yeah. I leaked the invite. That's the doubt. I'm making a new room.
So I'm going to do exclusively custom words. Chat. What do you mean I leaked the room?
I'm going to make a new, I'm making a new lobby. Okay. Um, I would like it if you guys could just
write fucking anything you want in this chat, random words that I'm going to put in here.
I'm just going to start typing. I'm not putting that in.
All right. Quit stop joining the lobby. Okay. Okay. I can't believe I just fucking wrote that,
but all right. This is going to be terrible. It has to be one word guys. Okay. All right. A
couple more and then we'll be good. All right. That's it. This is more of just an experiment
from me because these are, I, how the fuck are you going to draw half of these? All right,
let's go. I'm going to put into the sub discord right now. That's right. That's right. Here it
comes. You better stop spamming. How the fuck did somebody get in here as impossible? No,
nevermind. We're good. All right. So here it comes. And you're already, by the way,
if you don't behave and play by the rules, I will permanently ban you from the website.
Okay. Good. Sounds good. Three, two, one, go ahead and come in. I'm about to start the game.
Everything's in the right place. We're using custom words exclusively. Here we go.
Round one. Good luck and have fun. Don't get yourself permanently banned from the website,
please. I made these. So why wouldn't I know? I made all these. If I don't come in at least
second or fourth, if I don't come between two and five, then like I may as well just
never play a game like this again. I know all the words, all of them, but I mean, I don't know
what they, I have no idea because it's very possible that people were going to draw something
that is not, there's no sound. Oh shit. Sorry. I'm, I want to see how people do this though.
The thing is I kind of, I don't think, I don't remember the words I put in.
How are people getting this already? What? It's the chin. Damn. I didn't think you guys were
going to get that that fast. I'm giving everybody a head start. It's coffee. I just said it. Whatever.
Wait, it's going to be my turn to draw here in a little bit. No, not at all.
Don't lose. I'm going to lose because of what? I'm just going to just win every round by just
typing in the words I know I wrote down. That'd be a bad idea. I want to see how people draw
and if people can get it. This is just one of the, this is a random word that I just
wrote from chat. That's it. This is not like a stream reference. It's just a bulldozer.
This is it. I just somebody said bulldozer. That's actually kind of hard to draw. I guess.
All right. What do you got? How do I not get that faster than anybody else?
Of course that is just so recognizable at this point. See if I had, wait, what is this one?
Is this cheese? Did I write cheese down? Did I? No, I didn't. What is this?
Is this a Spongebob thing? What is this? I don't know what it is.
This is the worst emote on Twitch. Press L3.
Press it. All right. I press it. Nothing happened. I don't know what this one is.
Lettuce? What is this? What is this? I didn't put like the Joker here. I don't know what this is.
Oh, gamer. I don't remember what I wrote. Like instantly. All you have to do is put the blue
on somebody's eye. What is he holding? A horseshoe? Does Sans play horseshoes?
What? Why am I guessing like I don't know? It's not like baby. What is this? What did I write?
Oh, all you needed was the nose and the eyes. Wait, his eyes aren't like that?
That's not what Elmo looks like. That was so all over the place. I put this down,
but I didn't know what Muppet that was. It's not Qbert. Qbert. No, that's not Trollface.
That's Jerm of Venus. Or Qbert. Jerm of Qbert. Yeah, it's me next. What's this? What are you
doing? What are you doing? Is this? It's Garfield. It's not Garfield. What is that?
Reckles? I don't know. What did I write? Let me see what the word is. It's supposed to be...
Okay, that was supposed to be bald. I must have pressed S. I don't even know why.
All right, I gotta... What color is his fucking hair? I need... Come on, somebody. Anybody.
Nobody. It's Austin Powers. But I did have a space. Why am I getting a repeat?
I picked these words. I picked... No, I didn't. Well, okay, I picked them, but I didn't...
I picked them, but I didn't make them. Somebody wrote that in chat and I was like,
all right, put it in it. Of course, I get it. It's the hardest one so far.
Are we just restarting? Did I not put enough words? We need more words. Ten words. Is this
a new word? Me? I don't understand. Money? Money. What? I don't know. Oh, all right. I got it. Yep.
All right. That's Vegas. Pointing at me. What? Oh, that's supposed to be the Luxor.
That's the Luxor and the Stratosphere. No, we were Las Vegas, maybe. Uh, tube? Oh, did I... No,
I didn't. Wait. Who is that? I don't know who the fuck that's supposed to be. I thought it was
Thanos. I saw the hand like... Okay, it's fine. Now I get it. He's got a big Thanos chin though.
Chin? Yeah, this right here. Look. What do you mean he has no chin? Look at that. It's a defined jaw
bone right here. It's Cheetos. That's a big Cheeto. Imagine opening up a bag of Cheetos and you get
one like that. That would have at least... That would have at least 1,500 likes. Imagine you open
a bag and it's just one big Cheeto. I'm surprised they haven't done some stupid meme bullshit like
that yet. What is this? Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh! Nvidia. That's good. I like it.
You didn't even get to draw anything. You just had to... What? Why is it Nvidia every time?
Shit, everyone was ready for it. Oh, gg at at at gg. What's this math problem? Gg at times
a plus a plus... I don't understand what this is supposed to be. How is that wrong? What the
fuck did I write? What did I do? A good game. A good game. Oh, that's because somebody said
play a good game. And I was like, all right, fine. And I typed in a good game and I thought
they were going to draw like a good... Like, I don't know, you're going to draw like the box art
for God of War. It's Peter. That was so funny. Somebody just wrote, you need more words, Peter.
Did you see that over here? Dude, you need more words. What the... Peter! All right, come on. Come
on, Jim. A good game. All right, well, it's pointing at me. For what, though? I wish I had
a word list over here that I could look at because I have no idea. Um, good luck. Is it,
right? That's Jerma Odin. It has to be. Oh, right. Ah! Bro, wah! Fucked it up again. No,
you don't have to do the same one. You don't have to do the same one. Wait, did you get the same one
as the same person? We're starting to fall into who can copy the thing that the word is the best.
I hope I get Peter next time. All right, next time we're going to do one round and I'm going
to write just random fucking nonsense words. NVIDIA, NVIDIA, NVIDIA. At me, chat. At me.
How do you draw, Leo? Um, I don't think you do. I think the answer there is you don't.
All right, I'm going to make, we're going to do one round. I'm going to get good words next time.
If you, if you, if I see more than 50 of these, I'm going to turn the stream off.
Peter. That was a very low effort, Peter, can I say? That was just two little semi-circles and
then eyes. No, not, not Waluigi. It's another, another like big strong purple guy.
How is that more recognizable than an actual container of mustard? Something about that is
not right. Not right. You know what I'm saying? You've warped our minds. What is that neck? Oh,
okay. No, it's, it's not Waluigi, guys. It's another big strong purple guy. I'm trying,
Jerva. Okay, I have to be ready for that, for my turn. Cause I haven't got the answer yet.
Purple guy. I'm trying, Jerva. Okay, I have to be ready for that, for my turn. Cause I am ending
this. Oh, it's, I'm, what? I'm trying, Jerva. I don't understand. Is this just the same one?
You actually, it is. You just did the same thing. What did I tell you? If I was going to get between
two and four, then I may as well never play this again. Um, it's six. No, this isn't, anytime the
arrow points at me, it's automatically Vegas. Yeah, I know it. Oh, what? Was it my turn? It's
my turn. No, it's not pointing at me. What's going on? Where was my turn? What? Did it skip me?
Hi. All right. It's my turn coming up next. This is deteriorating. This is deteriorating.
No, I don't. Okay. My turn. Come on. There it is. Jerva Venus. Nice work. Nice work. Number one,
number two, number six is me. All right. Okay. I came between two and six. Oh, I, I fucking leaked
it. All right. Let's do it one more time. This time we're going to do one round or two rounds.
We'll do two rounds. We're going to do a new word list. Right. Okay. I got to
mute that. New word list. I'm going to make this hard for you guys. I'm going to make it hard for
me too. Okay. Let me think of some other ones. Yeah. We need like, we need about 20, 20 words
because it's two rounds. How about, um, okay. How do you spell that name? I don't know. I actually
don't know how to spell that, but we're just going to do that that way. Who cares?
Uh, I don't know. No, why would anyone know that but me? Nobody would know the answer to that.
There's no, it's impossible for someone to get that. We're going to keep it.
This is our, some of these are impossible. So how about, um, let's, let's throw a couple of
good ones in here. There's a different, just to make sure everyone was aware. These are different
words. Don't do balls this time. I won't call this one 10 out of 10 streaming. Oh no. You saying
that this is a 10 out of 10 stream? Thanks. I appreciate that. All right. We got one, two,
three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 30, 14, 15, 16, 17, three more.
Some of you guys, come on, give me some better ones than this. All right. This is good. Yeah.
This would be hard. All right. That's good. I'm ready. I'm going to remake the room. Hey,
everybody in the sub channel, get ready. It's coming in right now. Two rounds, custom words
only. There you go. Go, go, go, go, go, go. Now I freaked everybody out. Didn't put it in yet.
It's in the now. You ready? Somebody left. Let's go. Good luck. Some of these are not possible
for anyone to get. They're just not even real mobile. What is that? Is that a person? Oh,
do, do bopping. Is it a grimace? No, there is no grimace in this. I promise. Now I get it.
It's dancing. I know it's a boring. I know you gotta throw a few boring ones in. They can't all be
like fucking Jerma Odin. All you need is just that. All you need to,
you need the left ear to be drawn. I don't even know what he wears for clothes. By the way,
I think I spelled his name wrong. I don't, I think it's Griffin, not Griffon.
You got to take that into consideration though, that it's going to be wrong.
That's where the difficulty comes in. This is, this is, I mean, there, there you go. Now that's
better. Now that's better. That looks like somebody's pressing their face up against glass and doing like
the somebody left back to back. I didn't know they were going to be back to back like that.
I thought they were going to spread out somewhere. No one's going to get this. Really?
It's a kitten, a cat and kitten. I wanted to try to throw you off a little very quick. Good job.
And that's me. If you don't know, I'm up in the top right corner. It's a toy boat. It's a toy boat,
toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat. Oh, I am so good at what I do.
It's unbelievable sometimes. Imagine having a barometer for success and how good you are at
something by being able to do toy boat like 10 times in a row. No, yes, I do. Yes, I do.
It looks like powdered toast, man.
Yeah, that is good work. That's super Peter. Is it my turn? No, not yet.
Damn, what's with the double face? What is if two faces? I can't even write it. I can't write it.
It's again. No, what that means, we're not going to get to this one. That's not going to be shown.
It better not be super Peter again. If it is, I'm gonna be fucking actually upset. It's not pants,
clothes, clothing, clothing gone. Okay. Yeah, I didn't know what this is reference to. So I
needed to wait for the J to know what it was. There's a Jojo. My turn. No, that's that's that's
your name is germite. Not that thought that was me. Okay, seeing if people get it. I waited. I
gave enough time for that. Come on. Come on, guys. What's in between those two pieces of bread?
McChicken. My turn. I don't know. Streaming, land gaming. No, that's that's that's twitchy,
whatever their name is. No, it's a big old box. How on earth would you get that unless you were me
knowing that this is not possible to know unless you are the person that typed this in.
That's Jerma Stewie and emote. No one wouldn't have you would not how would you ever write that?
I think my favorite is super Peter. That's my favorite one. No, I know this one. I will cheat
to first place. Don't matter. It's just fun to see how you guys interpret these. You got to get it
right. You got to get it right. That's me. You just drew me. What the fuck? That's pretty close.
Holy shit. That's I gotta go. I got it's not I got to go. It's I gotta go. That's how I type it
every time I write it. That's what those two are talking in the discord channel together.
Wait, this is what's happening right now. Oh, right. I forgot I wrote that. Nice. Good work.
I forgot this. Oh, yeah, the word pool that you get on. Didn't you get this last time too?
Yeah, you got this last time. How out of what's the probability you get in that again,
twice in a row? It's 100%. That's the chance 5050. I love even though you know you still finish the
job. I respect that you still finish the job. All right, I'm gonna give you a little I'm gonna
give you a small amount of criticism here. The button I think the bun should be I'm just kidding.
I'm kidding. There's no. This is perfect. This is good. Yeah, that's good. Nice work. Toxic. No,
I didn't say anything. Not I there are enough words. There are like 2324 words. It just keeps
giving us super Peter. That person's like, wait, oh shit, that's what it was. Super Peter.
There's a one out of 24 chance that we're gonna get super Peter. We've got it like five times.
Oh wait, they're picking the right. They're picking the words right. I forgot. Yeah, that's
true. Why you guys keep picking super Peter? Because it's funny. Yeah, it kind of is. You're right.
Hi with the camera. Nice. All right, green. We're about to round this out.
Why are you giving him a cape? This is not super Stewie. It's Jerma Stewie. Did I get it wrong?
What? Oh, no shit. It's stuck. There are there are plenty of words. People keep picking Stewie
Griffin and Peter Griffin. Someone left. They're like, fuck this. This sucks.
See that guy? That guy over there guessed to it and they guessed something that they shouldn't.
I don't even know what this is supposed to be. Awful. Oh, oh, oh, fuck. Oh, fuck me.
Wait. What? I didn't see this movie. You didn't have to see this movie.
That's Jerma Odin. All right. No, it's not me. That's like green. I don't know why I put so
many of these in. I should have known that people were just going to fucking pick them every time.
What is B? That's not balls. B for balls. That's Jerma Peter. All right. I I'm not going to pick
a okay. All right. All right. I got one. I got one and then it goes and then come on.
That's Sauron. Pretty good. I think guys, it wasn't fucking Jerma Stewie again. I win. I win. I win.
I win. Oh, fuck. I want this one. Like, how is anybody going to draw that? The best Disney movie.
I'm surprised nobody got that. There were a lot of like super Peters. It's pronounced Sauron. I
thought it was Sauron. All right. We're going to do the next one. I'm not going to tell you
what the next one is. Thank you for playing everybody. I don't want to tell her what you
guys have the next one is just because it'll I don't want I just want to get in there first.
So so I got I got there's no more blocking. I can delete the blocks. I don't think I need them.
Okay. Am I in? I think so. Okay. This is the doodle place. Whoa. Is that an elephant?
Strawberries. This is where he gets banned. Not because I'm going to I'm drawing my own thing.
All right. This is kind of a small screen. Show skeleton. All right, let's do show the skeleton.
That Oh, okay. Cool. And then it should start walking around, right?
How many of these can I make? That doesn't work very well. No, no, no, no. Wait, what was that?
That was like I can do different animation styles. A humanoid. Yeah, I wanted to walk like a human.
Okay, that looks good. By contributing your doodle, you agree that enters the public domain.
Oh, shit, that's public domain. That's my creation. Where is he? Where's my? This is just
the end of Roger Rabbit with all the tunes dancing around to that like
like Mickey Mouse comes out and shit. Like, see, they do even they're doing the same dance.
This is like freaking me out. All right, new doodle. Let's try long legs. There's a shoe.
Another shoe. Can I make the I can't make this bigger. There's a hand. Let's get another hand
and up to the head. That doesn't look bad. No, keep that. That's fine. And then down here,
that looks good. Let's take a look at how it moves around. Fish, a bird. You can make them fly.
This is freaking me out up here. I want to get away from this.
That's awesome. All right, let's go. This is going to be let's do some random names.
How about Eddislug? Okay, fine. This is weird. I was supposed there was audio.
Look at that guy over there. This one's good though. Look at this is like dinosaur.
That was pretty good. This is the realm that Jimmy got sent to.
Jimmy. Don't you mean Jeffrey? No, who was it? Fortnite Jimmy. You can load midi files in. I
don't have any midi files. I want to go get a look at this one. Oh, that I just like teleported off
the map. Right. Okay. Well, that's great. You know, it's gonna fucking show up at some point.
And not only that, not only, okay, not only is it it's running, it's running towards me. It is
sprinting towards the camera. Just make a giant shield. I'm gonna make a bird,
a flying bird. This is supposed to be the head. Okay, this is bad. Yeah, it is. Just clear it.
What if I just made like a giant snake? Will the game actually register this? No,
that I'm gonna do. I feel like this is gonna break. No, that doesn't work. Fish register what? No,
no, I'm saying like for the bone. I wish I could do separate bones. You know, I think I can hold on
go back to draw if I do set with segments. So I'm gonna make a huge snake. This is segment number
one up here, which wraps down here into segment number two, which is this now starting segment
number two. Now segment number three, segment number four. Okay, man, I just drew like a P,
but let's see if that works. Holy fuck, that's a lot of subs. More subs from phylactery lich.
Every stream, every stream, phylactery gives 69 subs for the last two or three weeks. It's
fucking crazy. Thank you so much phylactery. It's completely unnecessary, but you continue.
Thank you. That's a huge amount of money every time. Thank you, thank you, thank you. What's
plantoid? Oh, I like that. It's like a big hammer. Yeah, that's a good one. So should I call this the
P hammer? No, I don't know. I freaked out. There's a penis in here. Be careful. Guys, there are
probably a hundred penises in here. So I'm in fact, I don't want to turn around. If I turn around,
I feel like there's going to be four or five penis sprinters. All right, what about what's
going on over here? I like this thing. Hey, the swaying guy is still here. Nope. It's so laggy.
Nope. Why? People fucking like this. Penis sprinter detected. Yeah, that's a cute little,
that's a fun little game. It is. We're going to move on. You got to watch out for the fucking
paparazzi penis sprinters. Just leave it here. Grow up. Terror? Make it fly. Oh, that's a good
idea. That's too late. Read. You should be reading too. Enjoy your youth. Grow up. What is this
little thing here? Look at how slow this is running. Is that my snake? I think that's mine. I need to
see. No, it's not. Five FPS. Jesus. All right, I'm out of here. This is cool, but I'm out. This is
coming from a guy that streamed full unset. Hey.