There is one two three four five six seven people versus one dude on the other side and he's still
alive dodging man he's just bunny hopping he's just bunny hopping look at all these people
just firing and missing him look at oh he's taking some shots now look at all these guys
it's a fire in range how is this guy still alive oh boy oh boy okay get ready can we
things here it comes gonna jump over it i'm a master oh i'm so bad stuff like this you
start at one side and run towards it and then jump it's easier that's what i'm doing oh it's
going faster it's going faster though it does damage to you everyone's oh oh i think we're out
i'm still in oh i see i see you come on drama we're rooting for you i'm looking for i'm looking
for shredded cheese where is he he's standing here kind of at the end
look at them all just jump me oh it's like a black screen for me oh there we go
these guys are cool look at it it's going like oh how are they doing this
this is hilarious look how fast it's going seriously they're gonna have to be mashing
it as fast as they can here this is impossible three two oh and then he gets to murder everyone
that was great can we do that again that was awesome you get to walk up to a picture
they get someone gets to choose what we do it's it's only oh yeah it's only one weapon and he
chooses is that the i thought it was like star mode star mode activated what is this what the
hell oh my god all right how does that how how does that correspond with the gun what what are
these modes
what is this i don't know what the hell why is everybody flying
what's okay this is ridiculous why people flying around but i just killed you
oh yeah what do you do to fly oh you go i'm dead you go up the ramps i don't even know
where the ramps are oh there's like they're like made of wood they're made of wood everything on
this map is made of wood we can't throw the grenades look at them they blow up prematurely
uh yeah don't don't throw your grenades we wait we wait do we have a limited supply
tower there's more they're doing the same thing we're doing
what don't don't don't throw it blows up prematurely don't yeah it blows up prematurely
oh oh what did you just get shot i don't i think i did one guy down below there's one down below
bomb him drop them all this guy up here don't be up there don't we're all gonna die if you stay
up here go down oh actually don't die i'm staying up here i got another guy this guy is so good at
throwing grenades i've been hit by two of them now okay okay let's go team all i got is a knife
we're going down yeah i need a grenade before i go down there's there's a ton more like in the
cubby hole i'm going to that right one again all right oh i'm not what's going to where there's
fire this dude keeps dropping i don't think it even hurts you what the fire oh i got the taser
all right i'm coming to the taser i think everyone is where's the taser is that left or right
that's everyone left oh they freaking stole all of them oh no oh my god that's fire oh i just
bounced a grenade off my teammate's butt no i just bounced it back what the hell did i do that
how is it even possible what i know i'm damn when i was at the base got him nice i saw that i'm at
the base right now i don't want to go over there i want to i'm gonna watch is that you i'm going
to get the last taser that's right here all right i got a taser i'm gonna put this in the right side
i'm on the right side i'm watching i'm watching i'm right here watch out for the screen oh god no
i'm on the right side i'm watching i'm watching i'm right here watch out for the screen
oh god no there we go oh give me this oh my god do we just throw over the gate oh are you serious
i am are you kidding me right now this is ridiculous i'm dead i took cover behind boxes
i'm the only person alive on the team oh there we go
he's at the front like dodgeball oh my that that lasted one second i don't think i ever want to
well we're doing it again all right it's just you gotta just go just go immediately go just throw
them immediately this is like dodgeball the first people to make it to the balls win
yep all right here we go go go go go go throw them quick get them over there bounce the wall
because you don't want to go too far oh i'm dead look at that kill feed oh remember how
people say like oh did you get like a quad or do you get like a triple oh no i got like a
up to octopuple i survived oh you had you had to live where is he where is he where is he
went back and forth along the wall