Hey, what is happening guys? It's Jerma here with another gameplay commentary.
This time we are the medic as the quick fix medic on gorge.
This is not five gorge, this is two gorge as you can see by the two receptacles in the bottom.
Is that even a word? I'm not even sure.
Anyways, probably should have popped it right there, but I didn't want to waste it because I think there was only one guy up there.
I think it was like a soldier or a pyro or something that he was shooting at.
Wasn't a sentry, so I figured I'm not going to pop it. I don't want to waste it.
I think he actually got killed by a crit rocket and a crit heavy, so probably wouldn't have been able to do anything too much with it anyways,
because that uber obviously you don't become invincible.
So this is going to prove to you guys right here in a second why this is not just a lame excuse for a medigun.
It actually works pretty, pretty well. I'll give you the load up for the match too.
It's the quick fix, the blutsauger, and the ubersaw.
And right here I popped this heavy and check this out, there's a sentry in here.
He can't get knocked in around anyway, he can't get pushed around.
This uber is good. I don't know why everyone thinks that this uber is terrible.
When I did the uber update video that I did like about a month or two ago, I thought it was stupid.
I thought the uber was pathetic, but it is what it is guys. You have to think about it like that.
You're going to be able to tank massive amounts of damage.
Nobody's going to be able to push you around.
So pyros, rockets, anything like that, you will be able to stand firm when you use this, and it's incredibly important that you do that.
Think about how many times you've used an uber.
And a pyro just comes over and just ruins your day.
It happens almost 50% of the time to me.
Oh, let's go pop uber. I can't move.
And it screws everything up and it's a wasted uber.
That will not happen with this setup. It will not happen, not even with this setup.
It won't happen with the quick fix.
And that tree got in the way when I was trying to hit that sniper.
I thought I was being all sneaky. Didn't work out as planned.
So we're all getting on the point here. There's about five or six people on the point right now.
I have to come up here and watch what happens.
Pop the uber again because you get a great recharge rate on this thing.
Everybody is now at full health rather than scrambling around to try and heal one person to like half health or something.
Everybody's ready to push. We get the point. We move forward.
Quick fix is good.
I'm going to say the quick fix is probably not that good on defense, but on offense it's great.
It is unbelievable on offense because there's so many opportunities on offense where people are just scrambling for health because they're all pushing in.
There's maybe a sentry. There's maybe like a nest somewhere.
And everyone's running backwards for health and you can just heal people so quickly that it's great for offense.
Defense, I'd probably recommend you use the Kritzkrieg. It's just so dominating.
The Kritzkrieg is just hands down the defensive medic, medigun.
Like there's hands down. There's nothing else I could say.
You could use the regular uber charge too on defense, but for the most part, if you're going to play a defensive medic, definitely, definitely use the Kritzkrieg.
Following around this soldier now with another uber charge, and let me just briefly talk about one important thing that I love about this.
I thought that was a spy. It's not a spy.
One briefly important thing I want to talk about is this medigun does not force you to uber a certain class.
Now what does that mean?
All the other mediguns, the Kritzkrieg and the regular uber, they force you.
They pigeonhole you into thinking, if I don't uber a heavy or if I don't uber a demo man, it was a complete waste of an uber and nothing can happen good.
Nothing good will happen if I uber somebody else.
You can uber a spy with this medigun and you won't feel like you've wasted it.
You can't say that about the other two mediguns.
If I told you, oh, hey, why don't you Kritzkrieg that spy over there?
You'd be like, shut up. I'm not going to. Get out of here.
Get out of here, you free to play asshole.
And then I'd say, hey, hey, free to play people are just as relevant as you and I. Stop being such a jerk.
And then he'd rage quit. And then I'm going completely off a tangent here.
But you understand what I'm talking about.
This is not a big deal. If you uber a class that's not a power class, you're going to be fine.
You might even get a few kills out of it too.
So don't be afraid to pop it on an engineer.
If he really needs health, if it's really a big push, pop it. Just let it go.
The thing recharges so damn quickly anyways, you'll have another one in no time.
Got a nice kill on that medic right there.
It's a good thing too because if I didn't kill that medic, if I wasn't the psycho that sacrificed his life,
then they probably would have got an uber pretty soon and then ripped through everybody.
So it's a good thing. It's a good thing to sacrifice yourself every now and then.
Hey, if a power class won't do it, then you should, right?
Absolutely not. Don't take that advice because as a medic, you're not supposed to do that.
You are not supposed to kill yourself when you're a medic like what I'm doing right here.
Don't do this. Let the other classes deal with it.
I kind of stole the kill from that Crits Creek soldier, so don't be like me.
Don't be like me, guys.
So I was so certain, guys, that somebody was going to come through here,
and I was going to be able to backstab them as a medic.
Here's another example of what not to do as a medic.
Wait for somebody to get behind and backstab.
Don't do that.
If you've seen my other medic videos, I play medic very, very aggressively.
I play medic the way you're not supposed to play medic, so take that with a grain of salt.
Engineer has a lot of stuff built up here. Nice dispenser, nice teleporter.
This engineer gets an A-plus in my book.
You're going to see a big, big fail on I'm not sure whose part.
It was probably mine, but it's this demo man right here.
We come across this corridor over the left, this little balcony area, and I get an Uber.
I come over to him, and he kind of jumps up on the railing as if he's ready to go.
I didn't have my mic plugged in, so it's kind of my fault.
He kind of jumps up on the railing, and it looks like he's waiting for me to pop it.
I said, all right, here he goes. Let's do it.
Hello? What is going on?
He just didn't jump down.
It's not really a complete waste because we do end up doing some damage to people.
Who am I kidding? It was a complete waste.
Anyways, we're in a great position right now.
We've got two teleporters up. We're ready to rock and roll.
Respawn out right into the teleporter. Fantastic.
Now I'm just going to frantically run around.
Look at all these people that need heals.
Running around frantically, just jing, jing, jing, jing, just healing anybody I can.
This is where the quick fix shines, just massively healing everybody around you.
I come over here to the side, and I start laughing hysterically because, watch,
this guy pops Kritzkrieg, and watch what the guy does.
He's just like, oh, hold on, I need to get some ammo.
Hold on, I'm just going to finish up the last part of your Kritzkrieg
and go over here and get some ammo. I thought that was just so funny.
Just like, what are you doing, man?
Man, you've got to stay there. You've got to stick with the team.
You've got to shoot those bombs.
So watch this. This heavy drops down. I go, I'm going to follow him.
I'm going to follow after him. This is going to be good.
We're going to win, right? Oh, no.
Uber right here.
I was so scared right here because I almost have a full Uber,
so I just try to do a taunt kill.
I realized that it was a complete and total sham right here.
I died.
You know what? If I could get this into a gameplay,
it would be the best thing ever.
If I could taunt kill the heavy and then run away
and somehow get back to the team, that was my thought process,
but it didn't work out as planned as you saw.
So come back, rinse and repeat. Here we go again.
We're going to do it all over again. Come back out here,
healing just everybody around me.
Anybody that needs it, just running around frantically again.
Ching, ching, ching, ching, ching.
And then finally, somebody gets on the point.
I think it's actually an engineer.
Somehow an engineer gets on the point,
and then we all just follow him.
Comes about right about here is where it happens.
I think it's this guy right here.
Yeah, I think, no, maybe not. Yeah, maybe it is that guy.
No, it was a different engineer. See, he's down there.
So I just get down here, I'm like, all right,
we have to win this right now.
I don't want this to go on any longer.
And we end up winning the game right there.
Thank you all so much for watching.
You guys are all awesome. I really appreciate all the support.
It really, really means a lot to me, guys.
Thanks so much for 2,000 subscribers.
Let's keep it going, too.
If you haven't seen that video already, go see my 2,000 sub video.
It took a lot of time and a lot of money to make that.
So hopefully you guys enjoy it.
And also, if you're still watching the video right now,
I want to ask, does anybody have
anybody they know
that can make me a custom layout, custom background
for my channel?
Because I've had this same dumpy YouTube
layout background for so long,
and I'm just looking for somebody to make me
something simple, something basic.
So private message me if you know somebody
or if you can do it. It'd be great.
Thank you so much, guys.