Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight I'm gonna be playing as the Pyro.
And before I get started, I do have to apologize. I am getting a little bit of a cold.
Because I went to Burger Boy's house, and Burger Boy of course has a cold.
And I'm gonna get it, so I'm getting a stuffy nose now. I'm getting a little bit of a head cold.
But you know, I had this topic in my head, and I wanted to go over it a little bit.
But I wanted to talk about it with you guys, because I find it to be very, very important.
And it has to do with why has Team Fortress lasted this long?
And when I say this long, I'm really talking about why has the community stayed for this long?
Why have we been playing this game for over five years? At least for me, I've been playing this game for over five years.
I started back in Team Fortress Classic, as a lot of you guys know, and I've been playing this game ever since.
I've never got that urge to stop playing. Sure, I've taken a couple breaks here and there.
I've taken one or two breaks, maybe one or two months. I don't feel like playing it, whatever.
I'll wait for some updates. But I always come back.
There's never been a time when I haven't played this game between two or three months.
And it was actually during this gameplay, right here, that I had this epiphany, I guess you could call it.
My brain was kind of just telling me, Jeremy, why are you still playing this game?
It's been five years, and you're still having this much fun playing this game?
Because I love this game. This is one of my favorite games, probably my number one favorite game of all time.
And it's really slugged its way up there. It never was like that.
This game was probably two or three on the list. But it's made its way up to number one, and I'm trying to think why.
And the answer is very, very simple. And I thought about this for a while, but it's very, very simple.
What to do with developer attention.
Now, I'm going to bring up a couple of different companies here and a couple of different game franchises.
This is not meant to hate on anyone. I love these games as well. I play these games all the time.
So don't worry, this is not me saying, well, this game sucks. No, no, no, that's not what I'm saying.
But anyways, take a look at Call of Duty or Battlefield 3.
There are recent iterations. I'm not talking about the franchises in general.
So they get content updates, they get patches, bug fixes, all that kind of stuff all the time.
The main problem with those updates are, there's a couple of things that I think are wrong with the industry right now,
but mostly those content updates are usually not free, at least for Call of Duty.
And they're not really that much of a change. They're adding maybe some maps.
They're buffing or nerfing a gun or something like that.
The changes that they make are not that drastic and they're not that forward-moving.
You go to Team Fortress, though, almost all of Team Fortress's big updates are massive, massive game-changing updates.
And that's why people keep coming back. That's why I keep playing.
That's why I keep my butt sitting in the chair, because I know they're going to add something crazy for the soldier.
They're going to add something insane. Look at the Pyro, the Phlogistinator.
The Phlogistinator, nobody really saw that coming.
And they keep trying to change the game and they keep listening to the community.
And the reason why this all came up when I was playing Pyro is very, very important.
The Pyro back in 2007 is wildly different than the Pyro now.
They didn't even have a compression blast.
The compression blast was added into the game in an update.
So you got to remember, the Pyro, before the compression blast, you were an ambusher.
You kind of hid behind corners, you WM1'd into people, and you only had a default shotgun.
And you couldn't blow anybody away, pull the shotgun out like we do now, and shoot people.
That's not how it used to work. You just used to run down a hallway holding down the mouse button.
Now look at what you can do as the Pyro now.
There are so many fun, incredible options to play with.
There's the flare gun. There's the reserve shooter, which I'm using right now.
There's the detonator, or you could just use the default shotgun, and they keep adding more stuff.
And there's the man melter. There's all kinds of stuff.
And I think that's why the game has lasted so long.
That is why this game is still one of the best. That's still why everybody keeps playing it.
They just have so much attention to their franchises, and they really care about what's going into their games.
And that's not to say that Dyson, you know, Infinity Ward and Treyarch, they don't put a lot of time into their games.
That's not what I'm saying. Of course they do.
All these game developers, they put blood, sweat, and tears into all their products.
But it's just the way that Valve goes about doing business that I seem to really, really love.
And what you're watching right now, by the way, is you watched a spy clip, a little bonus clip, of just a sequence of ridiculous events.
I couldn't even believe that all happened.
But I wanted to add that because, of course, the Pyro game was a little short.
So thank you all so much for watching. This is going to wrap up the video.
And keep the discussion going in the comments section, guys.
Let me know what you got to say about all this.
I would love to jump in and chime in on some of the comments as well.
So let me know what you think.
And, of course, Happy Mother's Day to all you mothers, or all of your mothers.
I think I phrased that right.
But yeah, Happy Mother's Day, everybody. I'm a day late, but it's okay.
At least it's the thought that counts.
So yeah, take it easy, guys. Black screen, I got to get out of here.
So I'll see you guys all next time.
And take care, everybody.