Quick Draw! Fast Draw! It's a cowboy's world in the Wild West. Which one has the skills
to pay the bills? In this week's episode installment of... Fast Draw! Showdown! Only on the Nintendo
Wii!
Really? This fucking dweeb is going to shoot me? I don't think so, Larry. I just like tased
that guy. That guy got hit with a taser. That wasn't a bullet. Watch out for the actors.
Get away from the actors that run by from stage left. See you later. I died at that...
What the what? Are you serious? I shot that guy like so many times? Why is that lady smiling?
Why would you ever be smiling in that situation? That's not like a fun situation to be in.
There's two guys about to have a duel with a pistol and this lady is like smiling as
if she's in a wedding photo. This guy's shit faced so he'll be easy. That sucked! I'm planning
on it. Did he just not even shoot the gun? Is it in the book? It's in the book! I knew
it was in the book! I knew it was in the fucking book and now I lost and it's over.
Top quality acting job, lady. Which one is it? Is it one of the guys playing cards? That
was a giant cartoon bag of money. Seriously, she ran out of there with a Scrooge McDuck
bag. You're not going to fool me. What about this guy? That guy had no idea what the fuck
was going on. That guy missed. That guy shot the ground. That guy shot directly into the
dirt. Why is that guy a quick draw fast McGraw? That doesn't make any sense. I have no idea
what this guy just said. She's going to be quick. Oh, not quick enough. You see that
mattress behind her? That's like a stunt mattress. I'm glad you fell on that stunt
mattress inside of a saloon. You can't tell somebody to holster the gun and then shoot.
She just told me to holster. Come on now. Holster that gun. I thought we were going
to play fair and no, of course not. You mean business. You can't be serious right now.
I was too busy paying attention to his dancing. I knew it was going to happen. I just had
to watch him dance. That was... Oh my God. This is so hard. Cause like the Wiimote, like
when you bring the Wiimote up, it's like, how am I ever supposed to do this with my
like shaky ass hands? Here we go. I lose. I'm done. It's just too hard. I've already
killed this guy, but you know what? We're going to cheat. I'm just going to shoot the
guy right now.