Hey, what is going on everybody Jerma here with a crate unboxing video
I've done one of these in the past but not really at this scope
I did 40 just about a year ago and now we're gonna do
50 and I'm gonna try to do this in less than 15 20 minutes because I don't want to sit here and be like
Oh, yeah, I got like a spy watch. Let me like take a look at that though
we're gonna blow through this pretty quickly and
Most importantly if I unbox an unusual in this video
One of you guys is going to get it. So we'll cross that bridge if I actually get there or not
But okay, here we go. Not gonna waste any more time. We're gonna go with crate number 41. I'm nervous. Here we go
Use with 41. I'm sure blow through it baby uncrating your loot. What is it?
Strange diamond back sick. Let's go again. Not gonna waste any time here. No, no, no, no, no, I want to do that one
No, do it you idiot. I'm sure three two one strange part give kills adding this strange part to a strange quality
But we'll enable to track number of enemies you get with that weapon. Dr. Pepper moving on
Well, no, we still want to create number 41 use with so I got 41 42 and all 41
255 and then I got 1 2 3 4 5 here at the end. So we'll see how that goes. Yes
I'm sure strange part heavies killed. Okay, pretty sick. This one's gonna be the unusual now heavies killed again
Heavies killed again. Well, these give me some kind of hat strange pistol
You know, actually these are kind of I'm not upset with these I can put these on a lot of different things
Use with go we're almost through row number one almost through ten here another strange pistol
You gotta be kidding me
I'm gonna have enough strange pistol to shove into a bag to send back to Santa Claus that prick three strange
Pistols god damn it if I get a strange pistol right here, I'm gonna die. All right strange detonator. That's that that's not bad
I'm so like nervous right now. It's like ridiculous. How high my blood pressure is allies extinct allies extinguished allies
Extinguished would be a pretty big oxymoron moving on. No, we're still in 43. Yeah 43
Posthumous kills that's kills after you die. That only really works on pyro, doesn't it going through the second row?
Come on unusual straight short stop. I'm liking it. I'm liking it. I'm liking it
What else we got stout Shaco for to refight first had it only took like almost 15 keys to get to one hat. Oh
Nice critical kills strange part. That's awesome. That's awesome. I like that a lot create 44 the series of
44 critical kills again, I can use that on multiple items
Unusual the unusual is gonna be right here. I'm not gonna look Oh strange rocket launcher. That's a beauty
That's a real beaut almost through 20 strange rocket launcher again. All right, come on. I want to give an unusual away
Let's get it on. Let's get like like a burning team captain right now revenge kills. That's pretty sick. All right
What we got in this one? Oh, I got an unusual. I got an unusual
Alright, so oh man
So what's gonna happen here is in the comment section? I can't believe it
I got an unusual hustles Hallmark smoking in the comment section of this video
I'm picking a random person and you're getting this hat. That's awesome. I know I'm not even I'm not even halfway through yet. Oh
Man sick. I'm so glad that somebody's gonna get that hat. I can't tell you how happy I am right now guys
Hopefully I get another one again random person in the comment section is going to get this hat
So leave a comment doesn't matter what it is
As long as you don't spam because if you if you write more than one comment to try and get this hat
I'm gonna be pissed. So don't do that. Let's keep going. Let's go. Let's go
Let's go, baby. Another one right after the other strange Persian persuader. That's cool. I'm creating your loot god
I'm so happy about that strange Scotsman skull cutter. Oh
My mood just elevated so much right there crate number 45 series actually, but we've done a few 45s kills
Well explosive jumping kind of cool. I guess I'll take it
Oh, how sick would it be if I could give away two unusuals?
Come on, give me another unusual out of the 45s now
We're moving on to the 47s after this one strange skull cutter again. Look at that thing
Look at that beautiful hat backwards ball cap. Awesome. Awesome. Awesome. Awesome. I'm glad I got that now
Dr. Pepper breps, can we do to us? Is it gonna happen strange force of nature? It's alright
I'll take that with the bank and then cash the bank. Ooh
daddy like
Daddy like just about halfway through just about halfway through guys another hat. I'll take it Snipers professionals Panama
Wait, Panama. Yeah, Panama uncrate uncrate those boxes, baby
Uncrate uncrate where oh time for like a beatbox of uncrating. Here we go. Ready, by the way strange flamethrower
If you didn't see it, here we go
shovel
Uncrate the loot now engineers killed
All right, that was a little weird all the surges stale hype. Oh, yeah, baby medicat actually that things that things pretty cool
Come on another unusual strange home wrecker strange home wrecker
Sweet straight scatter gun. I'll take that
Absolutely. Come on another unusual another unusual. Come on. Let's go strange scatter gun again getting out of the wire here
getting down to the wire here boys and girls and
Animals if you're watching but the animals are watching this video engineers killed again strange part
I don't know if I like that very much because engineers like my favorite class
We're in crate series like the newer ones. We're in 54 and 55 right now strange sniper rifle. Hell. Yeah
55 another unusual. Oh
Yes, yes. Yes. I like it nerves are getting a little crazy here guys getting a little amped up right now
The hell is that surgeon side satchel? What the hell? All right, when I just put this drink down
I just splashed it all over the screen. So whatever I can't even like see that's a must-be miscellaneous for the medic getting down here
This is the last little bit hotties hoodie. I'm getting a lot of hats. I'm getting a lot of hats hottie city
Come on. Come on. Come on. Let me get an unusual hottie city right now kills while ubercharged. That's a good one
Sweet almost out of crate 54 moving on to 55 and then we got five special crates another strange sniper rifle
That's good trade bait right there. That's good trade bait pyros killed strange part. All right
55 strange Medigun really hold on a second. I thought wait strange Medigun is in crate 55
I thought it was in like crate like 30. Oh, wow. Yeah. Okay, cool. Cool. Almost through the 55 series
Pyros killed again, are we gonna get another unusual so I can give away two we'll see strange Medigun again
All right, where this is the last one for the the newer crates then we're gonna move on to crate number one
No, baby faces blaster strange. I don't know they didn't have that strange now. All right
So the final five keys are gonna be for crate series one, two, three, four and five
I don't even think you can get strangers out of these crates. We'll see what happens. Here we go crate series
No, no, no, we're gonna go backwards crate series number five. We'll start with that one. We'll do one last crate series five
Here we go. The regular power jack. Oh, wow
Crate series number four. Yeah, these are I don't think strangers were even introduced until what crate series 20 22 or something
Oh nice. I got like a white paint to paint my like new unusual that's being given away
Crate series number three getting down to the final three crates the bushwhacker. Oh man. These were not worth opening
I'm not even getting strangers for this. Oh when I say that it's gonna be worth it right here
It's gonna be worth it right here. Mmm
Final key
Final crate series number one the first crate series they ever introduced and it's gonna get us an unusual right now. Here we go
No, it's the old guadalajara
Pyro hat. All right. Well, there you go
ladies and gentlemen got a lot of new strangers a lot of new strange parts and most importantly a
Unusual hustler's hallmark with the effect of smoking
So one of you is going to get this hat in the comment section
Just write anything as long as you're not spamming i'm going to pick at random somebody in the comments
And one of you guys are going to get that thing. So
Unbelievable. I'm so happy
I when I when I did this when I when I thought of doing this again
Because when I did it last time I did not get an unusual with 40 crates
So I thought i'm going to give myself a better chance this time with 50 and I got one so
Congratulations to whoever gets picked for that hat check your youtube pms in the next five days
I'm going to pick somebody in five days
So if you do not check your youtube pm you go to your account and you click on inbox and it's private messages
Go there. That's how you're going to know if you won the hat or not. I'm going to pick somebody in the five days
So congratulations in advance to whoever wins this unusual hustler's hallmark and i'll see you guys all next time and of course
Take care everybody. Thank you for watching
You