Hello, good afternoon. How have you been? I'm on a mystery stream today.
I don't know, can you hear my Xbox in the background? I can. This looks like a spaceship.
The mystery stream is Viva Pinata for the Xbox 360. Mystery stream!
Only going to be live for a few hours today. I got a lot of stuff to do today into this weekend,
so I gotta get on it. But I did want to stream because I like streaming.
I had the demo disc. Well, let's see if the demo is as good as the real game.
I'll just tweet this out. I'll be right back. Okay. Also, I'm gonna be really honest.
I have no idea what this game is. I was gonna play it until I get bored. I've never played it.
I know this is one of the most beloved new, rare franchises, right? I don't even know what it is.
Every commercial I ever saw was just pinata animals walking around and you feed them candy
right up my alley. So I got them. I got them all. I have every... Don't ask me why I do these things,
but I own every Viva Pinata game. I don't know why. I just do. What if we get bored?
Well, read a book. Why? Because when I was buying them, they were like $3 each. These were not more
than like $2 to $4 each. It's not like I spent a lot of money on these games. But I got a few
hours, so I figured let's throw in Viva Pinata. Viva Pinata! Here it comes. Oh, no, no, no, no. I
don't wanna get spoiled. Look, there's like little snakes and stuff. This is gonna be great.
Do you get to pick the animal? This game is my childhood. I know it's like... Look, we're on
childhood week. Chibi-Robo. Holy fuck, that was incredible. What an amazing game. That's my
childhood. Viva Pinata. This is my childhood, Jerma. Cooking Mama. That was my childhood,
Jerma. I played them all. I was very good at chopping. This is childhood week. Are we ready?
I'm just gonna go. No Viva Pinata save game profile has been found. Do you want to create one?
Of course I do. Oh, no, no, no. I don't want him to see. Hello. Yes. Sign in successful. Welcome
to Viva Pinata. Warning. Viva Pinata uses an auto-save feature. And removing an Xbox 360
memory unit or powering down your 360 while that-ish displayed can result in loss of your data.
Additionally, removing an Xbox 360 memory unit at any time will return into the title screen.
All right. I thought that was a Wii mode. All right. Learn about online safeguards. Why would
I do that? I want to play a garden, right? That's all I can do. New garden. You make a garden?
Enter a name for your garden. It's gonna be secret. I want this to be a secret.
All right. Yeah. You guys are gonna laugh. It's good. It's good suggestions. I'm seeing
there. Yes. Put it on the hard drive. That was your joke. That wasn't mine. You guys have-
That was your joke. You guys all wrote that and I was taking your suggestions. So what-
Mine is to yourself. I'm just- I'm a man of the people. All right. Let's go in the garden.
Deeds. Stop showing my fucking name. I- You get to pick what animal you- I get to be-
Set for Viva Piñata, an ever-changing world full of endless possibilities.
Really? Because this is a world where you get to call the shots.
Yeah. The piñata creatures and plant life that inhabit this land are all determined by you.
From the minute you dig your first hole and plant your first seed, go well on your way to
attracting your first piñata visitors. If they like what they see, these piñatas may-
Piñata frog? Oh my god. As your piñata collection grows, you can choose which to collect
and which to train. Life on Piñata Island is never all daisies and apertures. When illness
or danger threatens, you'll need to be the one who comes to the rescue.
What? You can fight? YouTuber voice. He's a narrator.
This is called presenting. Of course, it's going to be like an E3 voice. It's a guy presenting a
video. Does this like- Do I have to clean all this up? Wow. More cleaning. I love it already.
That's all we do on this stream now. It's clean. All right. So I move around with the left stick.
Talk. To Leifos. Oh, hello. I was hoping someone would come and help.
I was hoping someone would come and help and tidy up this mess.
You must be the new owner. I'm Leifos and I'm here to help you.
All right. Tutorial. Is she a piñata? Everything's a piñata here, right?
Why do I feel like this is a Kinect game that I don't have the Kinect on? What was that?
I've given you the journal. When you finish talking to me, press X to open the menu.
All right. Then I'll tell you what to try next. Cool. Oh, I can't wait for this kids game.
All right. We're done. So now we have- Welcome to the menu. Close this alert with A and then
you can move the left stick and the leaf in the middle will point to the different things that
you can do. Point the leaf at the journal, then select it with A. Oh, okay. I don't. I don't.
This is the journal. It stores all the information that you discover when you are playing the game.
The journal is split up into different parts to make it easier to find what you need.
It works just like the menu. There's not much to see yet. So have a quick look and let's get
back to the garden. Okay. Let's get back to the garden. All right. Good. Louder? Why would I make
it louder than this? Oh, garden area, encyclopedia, how to, player awards. I mean, we can- what's this?
Encyclopedia? This just shows characters, garden constructions. We don't need any of this info.
I know what I'm doing. Point and laugh at funny creature that walks into screen. I already know.
Down there. Is that a mask or is that her face? Alerts explanation.
Alerts will wait down here. This is pretty cool. This is a Zelda character. This is a cool
Zelda character. The alert will open automatically. If you have more than one alert, you can choose
which one to open by moving the cursor over alerts with the left stick. Okay. When you finish with
the alert bar, press up on the D pad to put the cursor back into the garden. Cool. Time for another
present. It's something you can't manage without. An animal. An animal. A broken shovel.
You can't- you can't afford a regular shovel? Grab your shovel from the menu and turn this mess
into your dream garden. This is not going to work. Why are there bite marks?
Why are there bite marks in the shovel? You have to start from the bottom, friend.
Well okay. Menu. There's the shovel. The buttons in the top right of the screen tell you what you
can do with the shovel. I have three bits of advice. One, you can clear the hard soil more
quickly if you hold down A. Two, the shovel is old but it won't break. And three, if you hit
pinatas, they can become ill. If you'd like more advice- Wait, don't hit any pinatas with a shovel?
So this is one, you can clear hard soil more quickly. Two, the shovel is old but it won't break.
Three, don't hit animals. Okay, don't hit animals with shovel. Oh! Oh my god, it's perfect.
Oh my god, it's a perfect game. Oh my god, it's a perfect game. Chocolate? What's that little thing?
Worm? Worm.
Well done. You attracted a worm. The worm has turned up because you have-
Crush. I'm not gonna crush the worm. Worm first sighting. Well, where is he? All right, smash the
junk. Smash it. Money. Explanation. Do I need to- do I really need to explain what money is?
Where's the worm? Is this a mobile game? No. Sorry, this predates mobile games. This is what
mobile games wish they were. In fact, this is what mobile games exploit. All right, pick up the
money. How do I get the money? Mobile games took this idea and removed the actual video game from
it. Where are the pinatas? I don't know. You have a new worm visitor. Where is he?
The new one needs. If there's a big enough patch of soil or grass, it will want to visit.
Oh, all right. Oh, I got grass? I have to attract pinatas. But where's my like pinata attraction
spray? Then press X for the menu. Choose your new grass seed packet from there. Okay, let's- no spray.
Well, I'm going to clear this whole thing first, right? I don't want to leave any trash. They're
not going to like this. How big is my area? Okay, I got into the white line there. Did I
just become a Viva pinata streamer? I may have. It depends. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Don't hit.
No, get out of the way. Get out of the way. I don't want to hurt you. Whack pinata. Poke pinata.
Is that health? Wait, why can I do this? Why can I golf swing?
I don't know. That's my first friend. Do you think I'm going to kill my first friend? What
are you guys crazy? I want to clear this. There's so much- look at all this trash.
Kill. Chat's the psycho now. Yeah, you guys calling me a psycho. All right. Yeah, this is easier.
Just hold it down. Clear it all. Hey, do I get to expand? I get to pay money and expand, right?
All right. How's that? That's not bad. I have to plant grass. You missed a spot, did I? Where? No,
I didn't. No, I didn't. People- right there? Where? People coming in from stir? Hi, guys.
We're playing an intense game called Viva Pinata. There's a ton- there's a shitload of blood in this
game. You're going to want to stick around. Yeah, in the settings, there was a gore setting and I
kept it on. All right. Am I wasting time or is this actually what I'm supposed to be doing?
Am I- I should just do this, right? Just get it over with? Am I going to have all grass? This is
a problem. Am I doing this wrong? Because if- I don't just want the field of grass. Okay, I just
broke the dog house. The dog house is gone. I'm just leveling everything. Don't hit the slug. All
right. How do I get the slug to move? Move. Move. Move. Move. You're taking up all- I need to clear
that. Hold on, there's some spots that I missed. I can't- can I get them? All right, we're good.
Let's plant some grass. What should I plant it just down? We'll start at the front. All right.
Grass packet. The grass seed packet is simple to use. Press A to go back to the game and look at
the buttons in the top right of the screen. They'll tell you what to do with the packet.
If you'd like to know more, press 1 now. Let's plant the whole thing. I mean, I- it's grass.
All right, start pouring. Start pouring.
He loves it. Get over there. Are you angry? Oh, here comes a snake. That snake looks like Otto.
Oh, okay. The orange means resident?
Resident. Name the new resident. Okay.
What's the- what's the name? Wait, let me get some more- does this cost money? Oh shit, there's
another one! This doesn't even cost money? Those who said this was a mobile game, now you know it's
not. What I just did right here would have taken three to five days and probably fifteen dollars.
All right, come here. Worm 1. Well, that's not your name.
Weeks, you mean.
Okay, but I want to name this worm. Name. No, direct? Oh, I can tell him to go. All right,
information. You can get information on almost anything by putting the cursor on it and pressing
Y. Let's have some fun. Have some fun. Oh, nice. Then press the left stick to select basic info.
Comic Sans. Now you can change your pinata's name, which helps you to find it in the garden
and keep track of its pinata life. Name it Harvey? Name him Bait. I have ten- okay.
Romance requirements. One out of two. Condition status. All right, let's have ten square
pinometers of soil or grass. What the hell is that? There's a worm house in the garden.
Nope, not yet. All right, let's name him. Basic info. Age zero days. Travel- what is-
Worma. Hold on. What do I want to name him? Uh, Worma? No, that's so easy.
Worma or else. Oh my god. Fine, fine, fine, fine. There's gonna be like a hundred of these.
Should it be Worma 1? There's gonna be a dozen of these. We'll run around.
Ooh, I got an achievement. Okay, cool. Let's go back. Can I pick more grass? There's another one.
All right, so this is- this is via pinata. There's no point in this game
where they- they hang from a ceiling and you hit them with baseball bats, right? That doesn't
happen. That doesn't happen, right? I shouldn't be preparing for that. It does. I mean, it's called
pinata. Do- do they actually like hang from a string on the ceiling and you go with like a pool
cue and smash them? No, okay. You've attracted a sparrow mid. Sparrow mids can hear a worm wiggling
from miles away and will come to take a look. Are they gonna get scooped up? Wait, another one?
Come check out the grass. Look. Yeah. How do you like it? Do you love it? Do you love it here?
Do you love it here? Where's your best friend, Snuffleufagus? Who's this? Willy? Uh, just some
normal guy. Thanks to the five community subs. Thanks a lot. Uh, I'm Willy the- so where's the
voice acting? So you're the new owner. Pleased to meet you. I'm Willy Builder and I put up all
the buildings around here. I can see you have two warmas as residents. You'll probably need a few
more. All pinata need a house before they will romance. Since you're new here, I'll build you
a worm house on the house. Close this alert and show me where to put the building site. If you'd
like some advice on how to choose a site, press Y now. All right, I need to know this. Seems
important. You want to build a house, the cursor changes to carry the building site. Move around
the garden to find a good spot. You can't put it down if there isn't real more analog objects in
the way. Okay. Spin it around with X to spin the site. Hold it and left stick you can spin it even
more. All right. Just put a block on the ground. I- yeah, but I mean I didn't- this is a huge house!
Oh my- Jesus! This is for a worm? This is bigger than some apartments. Well, how can I tell where
the entrance is? I need grass over there. It's as far in the corner as I can get it.
Is it going? Holy shit, this place sucks. All right, I need grass. I want to put more grass.
Award for having a sparrow visit. All right, we need grass.
I can't see the line.
Oh, he comes and builds it, I was gonna say. This is a terrible house.
Oh, there he is. Oh, he has a hammer for a head. You're making it out of skin.
New visitor. Oh, here comes a snake. There's a sparrow. I see it. I see it. It's over there.
Do they eat each other? They don't eat each other, right?
All right, what happened?
Wake. Okay, let's smash the building. Where do you stand back? I don't want any splinters.
You mean a McDonald's play place?
Okay, so put the cursor over the worms. Hey, that's not your house. Get off.
Do not your house. Okay, select. Now that you have the cursor on a worm, close this alert.
All right, we're on two and Wormo. Wait, we need, hold on. I told you this was gonna happen.
I knew this was gonna happen. Just different versions of Wormet, Wormo, Worma, Worma,
Worma and Worma. Okay, Worma and Worma.
Okay, Worma and Worma. The snake is coming over here.
Okay, secrets. Okay, they're in love. Are they gonna have worm babies?
Poor minigame.
Okay, let's go. So I have to get from here to there. Come get me. I will. Oh, he didn't even
get the fucking secret coin. All right, goodbye. Well, one of you seems to be more excited
than the other. All right. Yeah, let's make some more grass. Grass time. Wait, and you have to
watch them. For kids, this is how, this is how these babies are born. Oh, a new piñata. Oh, it's
Storkos. Your piñatas have made an egg. Your piñatas have done the romance dance. A new baby
piñata is brought to the garden, safely packed in a patterned egg. Welcome to kids week. Welcome
to kids week, guys. Let me just get enough grass. Missed a spot. I can, I'll fill it in.
Oh, right. I have to, I know there's a spot right here. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. I'll get it. I'll
get it. I'll get it. Wink. All right. Your egg's been delivered safely. Can they not be delivered
safely? Oh, there's an egg. Hey, smash the egg. You can change your label by using the label designer
from the main menu. Wait, I can make like a Call of Duty emblem? Yeah. Hold on. I gotta,
hold on. Wait, wait, wait. I, let me just plant the grass first. No, no, put it that way.
Grass. Uh oh.
Are you looking for romance? What? We need more birds?
He's burning up in the sun. Get out of the sun. Oh, no, that means he's a resident.
Oh, there's another one. We're gonna have romance again. Let me do this first. What's going on here?
Baby piñata is ready to grow up. The baby goes into a cocoon where it grows to its adult side.
If you get impatient, you could give the cocoon some encouragement with your shovel.
That's, that's like things you don't want to hear a mob boss say. Okay. Um,
there's a spot right here that I can't get. I still have to make my emblem.
You either live or you die.
Leave some soil. Don't do the whole thing. Leave some soil.
All right for the worms. Okay. Well, let's just make it look nice.
It's a little too, it's a little too rigid. Here, a little patch.
Just, it looks rigid.
It's more natural. It's more natural look. Here we go.
If you've raised a baby worm, I feel like I can really trust you.
I have two seeds that are ideal for someone starting a new garden.
You can have either one. Please choose a seed from either hand by moving the left stick.
All right. What seed do I want to take? The purple pill or the yellow pill?
Which one of these wakes me up connected to a toaster? This one, right?
Ah, yes. A good choice. When you get back to the garden, your cursor will be holding the seed.
You need to plant this type of seed in soil. Look at the buttons displayed in the top right
of the screen to help you with the seed. Or you can press Y now.
Now I know. I can plant it. Seed choice. Let's go. Where's it going?
Where should I plant this? This is important, right?
Uh, how about over here? Like right over here?
It's going to go right here, right? It'll make this look nice.
Okay. So we can water the plants?
Die.
Kill. Die. This is a kid's game. You're supposed to say defeat or lose. Destroy. Yeah.
This thing looks cool.
Donut. I thought it was a terrier.
Why is the watering can so dirty?
I don't need information.
All right. So here we go. Short pour. Plant is overwatered.
You just gave it to me. You don't say, here, take the watering can and go water the plant.
You did too much.
All right. Get them to romance. Let's see the current status.
Okay. After two worms have romanced, they are ready. What about you?
Has eaten one worm. You have to eat one. Who do we eat? Worma? Worma? Or worm? Are you going
for worm three? Here. Have some food.
Douse it with water. Whack it with your shovel or keep it away from dinner.
What? I thought I was just going to eat it. Cheering. It just exploded. A bunny comb.
Did you see that bunny comb appear? You can smell the carrot?
Oh, shit. He's eating them. Oh, wait. That was right. That was there.
He's eating them in front of the parents. This is the last of them.
All right. Where's the carrot? Have you eaten carrot? Oh, it was a carrot. That's what it was.
It was a carrot. Okay. Are you ready to breed? A lot of new animals coming in. Well done.
When the sun goes down, the moth drop will look for a suitable garden.
Okay. I gotta build some more stuff. They sleep. Okay. Hold on. They sleep. I need to...
Where's the builder? Label. Oh, yeah. Label designer. Big bits from phylactery lich.
Holy shit. There was 5,000 bits, actually. 50 more dollars from phylactery. They say,
Jeremiah, I found this picture of you browsing around last night. Explain yourself.
Oh, it's the penis shirt. I've shown this. It's the penis shirt thing.
Four fucking years ago, somebody made this image. I don't know. I'm just showing it on screen.
It's the penis picture with the smoking camel guy, whatever his name is.
All right. How do I use this? What am I supposed to say? That's... That was like my first t-shirt
sale like five years ago. Somebody photo... That's your explanation. No, I'm not gonna show... I've
shown it already. I've shown it like a thousand times. What is going on right now? Wait, wait.
Customize... Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. How do I get like a... Okay. I don't want this. It's gotta
be... My... It's gotta be like the germa colors, right? Don't randomize the colors. Randomize the
shapes. No. Here. The castle. The lightning bolt. The octagon. The puzzle piece. I like the puzzle
piece. The mail. I'm not... I don't want this one because I'll think I'll just... I just have mail.
I'll just think that this... I have to click on something. The controller. The Xbox controller.
Gamer land. But seriously, five lakhs for it. Thanks for the fucking thousands of dollars.
I want to change the colors of the other one. I don't like this purple. Actually, that's fine.
All right. That's the one I want. And then I want to change this to
Nickelodeon colors. I'm gonna be too bright. That's fine. I like it. It hurts my eyes. It's good.
Would you like to save? Yes, I would. Was there a wink? No fucking way. By the way, Tuesday
is the final day for winks and they're going to be very, very significantly reduced in price.
Significantly. By a huge amount. All right. How's the flower? Can I water the carrot? What do you
do at night? Oh, I need to name you guys? Okay. Has eaten what... You've eaten a worm. What are
you talking about? Was it the wrong person? Oh shit. I think that was the wrong person.
Wrong bird.
Some gardeners use their clock to predict which pinata shows up.
Okay. They both have to eat a worm. Name him Sperma. That would be really funny.
What's the building menu? Do I have access to it? Journal? I can't. No, all these animals that
are here right now are going to die. Let's be completely honest. Be upfront with all of this.
Everybody here. They're all going to get eaten. These birds are going to eat the worms and then
the snake is going to eat the birds and then the rhino is going to eat the snake.
And then we end up with our character. That's what happens. What can I do at night? Just hang out?
Do we just keep the original worms alive and have the... That's so fucked up though.
We need to have... We need to breed, breed, and breed. All right. Well, how do I get the bunny
to come over here? Come on. Come on. Why is that universal for any animal to come say hello to you?
They probably have no idea what the fuck we're talking about. Come here. What are you... What
are you doing? Oh, listen. Come here. Come on. Get over here. Should I pick it up and give it to him?
All right. You. You. Let's go. Don't eat him. Hold on. You. Yep. Let's go. Oh, bunny combs.
It's a bunny. All right. What do you need? Okay. I got a lot of grass. He needs to eat three carrots
and he'll stay. All right. Let's get some extra money. Where do I get the seeds from? What the
fuck was that movement? Go. You unlock the seed NPC later. All right. Are you going for the carrot?
Whatever. You're just going to eat it, I guess. Do you like it? Okay. I need two more of those.
All right. Cool. Good. Please show Otto I need my endorphins. What are you talking about?
Here are the experience petals. I need my endorphins. When you do something to help the
garden, the petals will turn blue. If you'd like some more information about the experience petals,
press Y or level up experience petals. Where you going? Okay. You've filled the
pastels around the clock, which means you've taken a step closer to becoming a truly great gardener.
You shop new items, new pinatas. Good. All right. Level up. Do I pick points?
You've filled the pastels around the clock, which means you've taken a step closer to becoming a
truly great gardener. Okay. Level up. You've filled the pastels around the clock. All right.
Here comes Seedos. I didn't expect the mouse to move. I thought it was a mask. They're not masks.
These are obsessed with gathering seeds. You should try talking to him.
All right. Seedos. Egg delivered. All right. There's the egg. Hey, you too. Do it again.
Pick up the egg. Um, didn't it say I can hit the egg? This game is too cute. It's disgusting.
All right. I don't care about the coin. I just want children. All right. So put it down.
Come on. Here it comes. Worm four. He's looking. He's so cute. Yes. I want to talk to you too.
Come here. Hey, Seedos. What do you got? Hello. I'm Seedos. Take a seed and don't hit me with your
spade. Don't tell me not to do it. I'm going to do it. Have a seed. Carrots. Let's put it over here.
Beat his ass. Jesus. All right. Wada. All right. Do not hit him. Worm four. All right. Here comes an egg.
All right. What just happened? Why did worm four just explode?
Eat this. Don't you want to eat this? The builder shop is now open. Okay. Good. Okay. My menu. Okay.
Good. All right. Fine.
Where's the seed, dude? You said you dropped one. I was just kidding.
Keep hitting him. No. There's a wink. I get it. Why would I keep hitting the guy that just told
me he was going to come back and put weeds in my garden if I hit him? All right. It's time. We've
got to feed. Worm four. Nope. It's all right. It's time to. We need info here. Put this away.
Okay. How old are they? Age one day old. Okay. So that's not that big of a deal. Call the guy's
bluff. All right. Sparrow, come here. We need to. You eat a worm. You. Now let's build a birdhouse.
Willy builder. He wants the worm. You roll a slot machine.
Established 20 years. Regional award winner for services to island housing.
You need some work done. Pinata and helper accommodation. A specialty. I know my trade.
Don't you worry. I have to roll for a building. Buy items. Okay. Sparrow home. Price. 165. Place
the work shed down where you want the building. Then I can get started. Payment up front though,
if you please. Why would I not pay you up front? I'm going to keep the birds away from the worms.
Yeah. I'm going to put them over here. We don't want any fighting.
If I could just ask you to pay the balance. All right. Didn't I already do that?
We had a raid come in. Why malicious welcome everybody from why malicious is a
raid playing pinata. The game's fucked up. It likes flowers. Any kind. That's all I got.
That's all I got. Here's a taffy. It likes flowers. Any kind will do a taffy. I think there's
too many animals to keep track of, but thanks a lot. Welcome guys. Congratulations. You have
attracted. I already got it. I got it. Sometimes they are attracted by the noises of other animals
and sometimes the scent of flowers brings them. All right. Flowers and smell.
How many new characters are there? You should all know my store's open again.
I expect to see you in here very soon. Just bring lots of cash.
Nobody likes the taste of chocolate coins more than Lottie, I can tell you. Shop get.
Okay. All right. Can I?
They're chocolate coins? It's not even real money.
Everything is candy. So the currency here, what's the US dollar equivalent? A bag of
30 of those little chocolate coins is like 80 cents, isn't it? Oh boy. Okay.
Now cost a loss is open. You can buy romance sweets. If you have romance, the pinata species
before you could replace all their requirements, except their house with a romance suite. Buy a
suite and direct a pinata to it. They should eat it and instantly they will have to show they are
ready to romance. This should make romancing pinata easier. You need to feed pinatas.
Romance candies. All right. Can I open this thing now? Or is there anything else you'd like to
traffic jam tutorial me with? All right. That's gone. Have you eaten? What about you? You have
eaten. I need to spare a house and then you need to eat a worm. Don't eat him.
The happy meter tells you about your pinata's mood. Every time something happens to the pinata,
orange or blue, turn orange or turn blue. The more orange triangles a pinata has,
the happier it is. And you can see this on the face in the middle. Okay. Let's see. How happy are you?
You're all right. Eat. Who is this? Worm five. Eat worm five. Go for it. This is sad. Wait,
is the snake going to come over and get free candy? Look at the snake. What does the snake eat?
No, no. That was your brother. Oh, okay. Well, what does the snake need? It needs to eat a mouse
mallow. You got it. All right. Open it up. They will now live here. Oh, that was horrible. All
right. There you go, guys. We need more breeding. Okay. I'm going to make another worm. Should I
make another worm discovery zone? Should I do that? No. I need another egg. We need to have a
ton of worms because there's going to be a bunch of sparrows. The dumb birds won't even sleep in
the bed. Oh, no. He's going to die. Screamer sucks at kids' games. It's not a kids' game.
I keep getting corrected. Builder back at the store. All right.
Pretz tail? There's so many animals.
Bro, you're fucked. What? Is a pretz tail going to... What's wrong with the pretz tail?
Wait. Oh, I got to water this. I need to buy some seeds too. More?
Good. More? Kill the pretz tail. You're not selecting it. Make those birds have sex. I will.
I'm going to buy some seeds. Oh, was it an onion? It's a mystery seed. All right. We're going to
put plants over here. Put it right here. The egg. Oh, I don't know why I thought that eggs were
going to grow on that. Okay. Talk more? Come on. I can't leave. I'm confined to this space. What is it?
Big one. All right. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop,
pouring. Where do I get water? Hold on. There's a... Come on, get in here. I'm going to get this big
monarch butterfly, whatever it is. Get in here. All right. What do you want? How do I get you to
stay? You're beautiful. Has a light in the garden. Oh, I need a light. I need a lamp. Build me a lamp.
Stop ad-libbing, Jerma. Don't ad-lib. Read the script. Case in point, what you just saw right
there. There's no, I can't do one yet. Can I buy from the other store?
From this store here?
If it isn't the new gardener in town, you're guaranteed a warm welcome at Costalot's store.
Whether you're here to buy or sell, which will it be today? It's sell. Highlight and select one and
let's get those coins flowing. Happy shopping. All right. What we got? Buy items, seeds, candy,
vegetables, fence, lamp, firebrand. That's a lamp, right? Give me that lamp.
All right. I'm going to put it right over here. Right here. Hey, look what I got.
No, no, no. Check out, check out, check, yeah, yeah, yeah. What the hell is that?
I thought I was, I thought I could place two. It's all right. He'll be back. All right. You,
no, I don't want the birds to start having kids. The more birds that, why they don't have a tag?
If there's a bunch of bird kids, they're going to eat. Sell them. You can sell the kids. What?
We need more worms first. I'm not comfortable having three birds. Okay, here comes another one.
They don't need to eat. They only have to eat if you want to breed them. Oh, well, there's going to
be, all right. Well, they'll be, they're going to be quite a few of these. All right. You two,
it's time to make a bird child. You, come here. Where's the other one? Come on, stop going out.
Come here. You two, go enjoy each other's company. Go enjoy each other's company. All right. I got,
I got smack citos. No, I'll talk to citos. He's going to give me another seed.
There's nothing more valuable than a seed.
Me? Thank you. And put it right here. Hey, you, come here. Talk to me again.
All the seeds are mine, but I'm kind so other people can borrow them.
Me another one? Oh man, he's throwing them out like crazy. Wait, what? Hold on. What, what does
this weird elephant be? Hold on. What the hell are you? A taffy has eaten one flower. So the
taffy wants to live here now. How do I make it? This thing's cool. That is really cute. Yeah,
I like this thing. Okay. So now what? Has eaten one poppy. I need a taffy house in the garden.
I'm thinking, do I have any poppies? So this is a carrot, right?
Okay. Nice. What about this? Are these two both carrots? Don't eat that. Hey. All right. Do they
have a kid yet? Look inside. You can go into the house. This is kind of cool. You can just say,
put your eye up and look. All right. How's everybody doing? Lots of worm kids. Still need
to find out how to get you here. I need you guys to read. I need the bunny to come back.
Come here. Breed. I can't select you. If you're just going to stand up on top there.
Do I just make sure? I'm just going to give him a breed candy. Oh, wait, wait, wait. Look inside.
Oh, that was cute. All right. Can we? He's eating another flower.
Don't eat that. Not yet. I need more flowers. Have to fly, fly into the fire and he'll turn into a
new... Can I make him do that? Wait, have him fly into the fire. Why would I do that?
Is that like a huge spoiler for the game? Oh, I thought you guys were just being dicks.
I'm not doing that yet. I'm not doing that yet. I want to go buy some more stuff.
Well, can I make it more buildings? Afternoon, come on in. Big spenders welcome. All right.
Fertilizer, seeds, paving, fences, garden items, produce, vegetables. How much money do I have?
Seeds. Oh, these are cheap. Buttercup, daisy, turnip, carrots. All right. I'm going to buy
a ton of carrots. Let's put carrots over here. Point two, three. They're cheap. They're really
cheap. I'm going to have like a whole section. I want that bunny rabbit to come back. Shitload
of carrots. Okay. That's it. Buttercup, daisy, thistle. All right. I'm going to hold off for
now. Go back. Produce. I can just buy this shit. Wait, honey. That's a lot of money.
It's going to be a bunny invasion. Carrot. These are too expensive. Why would I buy these?
Garden items, pile of leaves, ornamental stones. All right. How about an ornamental stone? All
right. Ornamental stone is going to go. I just want it. I want it. I want an ornamental stone.
What's wrong with that? See? Look at how much they love it. Pile of leaves. All right. How about a
pile of leaves? Pile of leaves is going to go right over here. Good. Okay. Omega Lo, no money.
I want fun stuff for them to do. This is grass right now. This is just grass. Time to start
selling your piñatas for money. Sell. I can sell them for 100 bucks? Two snakes. All right. I need
to make the snakes happy. All right. No, no. I'm not going to do this yet. I don't need to do this.
So my chocolate coins. Thank you. Come again.
All right. I got the carrots. I want a bunch of, uh, these all good to go. I've got a seed here.
A carrot seed. All right. Where are the bunnies? And you?
Where the? I need a mouse. How do I attract a mouse? Let me know the seed.
If you like seeds, smile. I don't think you're. I need tall grass. What is this?
And what is this? The daisy. Is it bloomed? No, it's got to go more than that, right?
It's only worth $10. It's a dead flower. No, it's not. All right. Should I go to the
information? It's already grown. All right. Everyone's sleeping in their houses, except
for the snakes. The snakes just leave during the day. This is looking like a pretty nice little
ecosystem. What's over here? Oh, look at this place. Oh, butterflies back. I need a butterfly
containment zone. Ego maniac makes ego system. Quick look in the houses. Oh shit. That's right.
I don't want to wake them up though. Nice. They need to have some children. You can make
worms happy if you water them. I don't think that that I don't think that's accurate. Look
at this. This is a big family in here. It's a sleepover. What's the painting of a squirrel?
Worma, Worma and Worm 7, Worm 4, Worm 6. All right. Give me those rabbits. I want you to stick
around. You need to make a little moth house. Hey, Cito, give me the seed now. I'll swap you
a seed for 10 chocolate coins. This person is weird. Oh yeah. You like it? Yeah. All right.
I think we have a resident. We do. New resident. Yes. All right. Has eaten one thistle and then a
mystery. Let's rename this to Jermoff. I would have been so into this when I was younger.
Imagine coming home from school every day and opening this. Oh, it's so good. It would have
been so fun. What is this thistle? What are you? Daisy? I need a thistle. Back to the store. That's
a fox. I need a rabbit. Is the rabbit gone? No. Come on. Where's the rabbit? I need some thistle.
All right. I'm going to buy like four or five thistles. Put them in the corner.
The rabbit is resident sleeper. Good morning. Right eyed, bushy tailed, and ready to spend.
What about fertilizer? Do I just do this? Orange fertilizer? Bonus growth. I don't want to do that
right now. You know, this could start to get annoying. Yeah, like you every time I open the
store. No, no, no. Not fertilizer. Seeds. I need thistle down here. All right. The 13 bucks.
So that's your. He's sleeping. Oh, that's so cute. All right. You're when the thistle is
going to be over here by the fire because they love this shit. I'm going to do thistle. Nice try.
Cheapskate. You don't have enough money. You don't have the cash for that. Spend what you do. Okay.
Finish shopping. All right. Now. No credit or refund. All right. Now it's time to sell some
children.
Water these thistles. Very good. Oh, yes. Right this way. The carrot buffet is waiting for you.
Ew. Funny comb. Has eaten a daisy or has eaten a buttercup? You don't eat carrots? Wait, why
don't you eat carrots? There's so many carrots. What the fuck is happening? Kind of scary. You
don't eat carrots? Carrots are the ginger vegetable. This doesn't put pinatas up and you'll
have to look out for them or they'll be eaten. Somebody has to eat these, right?
Do you eat carrots? A squazzle. You guys were talking shit about me putting the leaves in
the stones. Now we've got a squazzle. Are you guys still having kids? Someone warn him please. What?
The ground is overflowing with worms. All right. We're good. He doesn't know. Pepe left. Pepe left.
I don't know either. He doesn't know. I don't either. All right. Can we? The birds have to
breed. Get over here. Bird. Stop perching up so I can't select you if you're up that high. Move.
The gardening is improving. All right. Move. Get off. Off. Off. Get off. Get off. Out. Whoa.
There's a bunny spider? A raise ant. That thing's crazy. The longer you work in the... Oh no. People
of far and wide are hearing about how awesome the garden is. Okay. We got... Look. Another one.
Another one. Keep eating. Eat as much as you want. All right. Now give me this. What is that thing?
Sour Shelly bean. It eats seeds? Why does he look evil? A seed feast? So a hit with shovel.
What is going on?
Ha, ha, ha.
Okay. I'm sorry. It's a seed feast. All right. Where is he? Oh. A new resident. All right. Give
me my shovel. We're gonna hit this thing right in the face. Come on over here. Why don't you come
over here? Come on. Oh, I want you over here too. Look at this. All right. I have children. No.
You're always so far away from each other. Yep. Go over here. Throw it in the fire. I want you to
get down. I'm trying to breed. I am. I have children. I'm... More worms. I think I have enough
worms. What is this? Oh. Fanny Franker? This is a base for a mailbox? What? Well, this doesn't
exist anymore. Another cocoon hatched. Good. More worms. Okay. This is... I'm done with worms after
this and I'm going to do everything I can possible to get those sparrows. You're not worming your...
Oh, there's a hand. I'm so sick of this worm minigame. All right. Finally. Land. You and you
go. You know what to do. Here it comes. Come and get me. It's just free money. It's the same
minigame. Just a little different. I'm coming. I'm coming. Get ya. Yes. You got me. You found me.
Do we get to see their fun dance thing? All right. Here we go. It's the moment we've all been waiting
for. This is kind of weird. I'm like, all right, let me look. All right. Now do it again. No. We
can't. What's wrong with you? What's going on? Why are you on fire? Is this on fire? Are you on fire?
What's going on? It's on fire? How do I... Why are you on fire? He's gonna die. He's not gonna die. All
right. Give me a seed. What is this? Is this a seed? This is more cube than seed. Where should it go?
Over here? How's everything else look? How the thistles look? Go eat those carrots.
That's what they're there for. We fell asleep eating. It's okay. When you wake up in the morning,
you eat them. Anything else need watering? Over here. Oh, shit. I think these are dying.
No, these are fine. What is in here? Stop. Stop. Stop. You're gonna kill it. Okay. A baby?
Oh, yeah. Look, a little baby. That's not your house. Get out of here. He thinks he's a sparrow.
Hi, sparrow. No, you're not. Get out of here. Eat a daisy or a buttercup. Okay.
Shovel upgrade. Nice. It actually is intact. This is progress, but it's very slow.
Let's see if a better shovel will make you a better gardener.
This is the seed shovel. You can dig seed holes with it by pressing A.
I'm sure you'll work out what seed holes are for. So this is to make them grow better, faster.
That makes sense. Okay. How's everybody doing? Another baby. The carrots are gonna rot.
I just sell them? How much is the reward for growing corn? Ten bucks to sell. Okay. Sell.
Sell. Sell. Sell. Sell. Sell. Sell. Sell. Sell. All right. Sell this one too.
That's a pretty good return. Move this corn. It's not gonna leave this, right? I still what do I
what do these guys need? I need to. What do I? Where's my money? You need to eat a poppy
and have a taffy house all right i gotta get poppies and buttercups poppies and buttercups
xbox live doesn't work it got turned off like fucking seven years ago
all right i need poppies and buttercups chocolate cash melting in your pocket i'll take it i'm not
candy candy i can buy a new watering can blue bell poppy corn and i can make i can plant
apple trees holy shit all right i want poppies and i want buttercups poppy so that's your thing
but wait i just i don't want i just want to place it because i have a new shovel
if you ever build a fence i beg you real fence hold on let's put the poppies over here
we'll do like two poppies okay finish up okay now let's get some buttercups nothing beats the
taste of hard-earned chocolate cash an excellent choice trust me that'll look great let's put these
right here and we'll do two okay no no it's fine you won't find thanks i wish i could say i replace
all faulty items but i kind of don't all right everyone's saying build a fence build a fence
fence fence okay wire fence so that's six bucks this is six dollars like over here put it around
the weeds you want me to put it over here i can't even build this shit over here remember stop
farting i'm sorry you're gonna have to deal with it um i can't i can't can i put this here
i can't place it yeah this is all wrong what's he doing why is this guy raining missiles down
he just keeps killing a bunny oh no he just killed it the fox is it's a free-for-all
no no no all right they're gonna kill all my rabbits i gotta go back i love this thing
if the garden is good enough for other nocturnal pinatas okay there oh look at me i'm a new
character i'm one of the other weirdos in the village you can buy romance candies oh sorry
didn't notice that you're you're eating each other in your garden hunter in this here village
look at my weird house that needs fetching just come find me i like pinatas so the only ones i'll
fetch for a garden are ones i know they can handle ones that have resided before we clear
we clear well there go all the rabbits rabbits are all dead looks like we breedin foxes boys and
girls what do you guys like to do fun okay uh i'm gonna go to the builder i need to see some things
you're gonna kill the birds too i hope not i gotta plant those seeds yeah morning can i build any
other you a bacon buddy but i've just eaten the last one for how much money do i have not i don't
have that much moth home happily home i have to sell all these kids i appreciate
it
one of your pinatas has been trampled
you were trampled you don't seem very upset by it who was trampled it's i gotta sell okay we have
a lot of worms we're selling the worms no no no not the original worm worm worm eight bye uh worm
seven uh any other number it worms six worm nine we'll keep worm nine uh
worm four no i like that 600 for a pretzel 600 for a moth drop i could read one of the one of
the pretzels no those are expensive um all right i can i can build a new i'm done i'm gonna check
out my shop now i have to buy a house for these weird little blue things what i need to do hold on
dig here we go so dig let's dig a hole here okay i need four right one two three four now let's
put this in here your gardening isn't kill snail where's the snail
the snail it's coming it's coming where oh my god stop
didn't i already get this need to put some more effort in
this garden is strength oh shit kill him kill this guy is he sleeping i'm killing him in his sleep
free food over here that's a little spider you have a track a rock knit a rock they only
visit experienced gardeners like me okay well that's too bad but it's okay oh my fucking god
is another one there's another snail plant what's going on get the fuck out of here get out of here
move uh why did you just do that did you do that why did you just do that i didn't do that
why did that just happen okay now i gotta build their house these guys athlete to build a tally
house i should probably build a oh hold on he's coming all right streamer keeps over watering
breed the foxes i think i have enough money for a one of those huts
lucky you caught me i was just on my way over for a pint of milk or ted okay so how much is it
at 415 it's all right let's build a pretzel home as soon as you boy i'm kind of out of room
there's no space for this where's the door okay this is all right yeah okay how's everybody doing
is there any snails oh a fudge hog a big toe hog he likes thistles and worms so if you have
enough of either he was here for the worms well sorry i just sold them all and what about you
has eaten one quack berry you're not gonna breed unless you i feed you a quack berry
have to be a very special person good job it's an aphrodisiac plant dried out where what i'm gonna
place this here what plant dried out where these are fine you've been awarded having a fudge hog
too much stimulation does um no is this fine look don't you just want to like put your arm
around and under and just like scratch his head you know what i mean okay let's open this
here it is there's your house go live in it what was that what was that is he throwing old tires
um are there any more where the worms
your land has grown has it i can't i can't move any further out this carrot is just gonna get
it is gonna rot all right i got a lot of you guys on here what do you want he has eaten one
newt gatt i think are all the worms dead i think our worm population is gone no no they're they're
asleep are you guys um living here yet look look what's in here see check it out what do you think
you like it go inside and have a look inside you don't like it trap him in there no he loves it
okay hey hey hey hey hey hey don't i'm gonna i mean don't have we got these uh little poppy
seeds here a pinyar is about to be eaten uh no no how many do we have any more we only have one
worm left you guys have killed all the worms all right everybody run everybody worm nine get back
in the house in fact we're gonna worm four and worm nine have sex with each other uh we're out
of worms you need to fence them in what a fence uh worm nine worm four you two have sex
okay fence wire fence wooden fence a wooden gate wire fence fence them in create a memorial
i only have 83 dollars i can't even place the fence here
here i can i can put a piece of fence right here not here not it's got all i can't even do
it over here i can't go this way i think we're gonna say bye to the worms forever
hunter can find more oh then we're fine all right now we can start for real i never needed help
when i used to run this deep holes for water oh shit all right we're gonna make a lake
i need more land all right get rid of this fucking thing no one's gonna eat this
puzzle gum probably likes honey i'm assuming garden has attracted a puzzle gum buttercups
like almost any okay now a lick a toad frog spider
like a toad has turned up it must have seen you receive a shovel upgrade and thinks you are going
to dig a pond what do they get mail heard about the new blur about the new community pool
okay here we go dig pond excuse me oh nice deeper deeper deeper how deep should it be
go in there don't go in there there's only so many of you oh okay deeper okay that's enough
we need to put like we need to put some hold on this is ugly fix this
yeah how's the uh how the plants look
we good they're good yeah this looks like it's dead no it's good these are fine they look at
how pretty they are i want to get some ducks in here and what all right bird eat that corn
just eat it first eat corn just eat it since when what do you put up with the crows
crows are all over the fucking cornfield snake eats corn set that tally on fire whatever where
the foxes are they're they're sleeping okay all right we got some permanent residents here
when they're another bird all right we need more i want more birds
sparrow two and sparrow three i'd like another bird you come here actually they're not in the
mood they need to eat sparrow should eat a buttercup sparrow you motherfucker
they just want to hang out uh no leave it alone no it's gonna eat all my shit
he's eating a thistle why do you not even need a thistle because it's gone well that's great
kill the fucking flies but did the bird just die wait why did that bird just just like
have quantum death save him how am i supposed to save him he ascended i need to build a place
for the tally all right we need a tally house
how much is it for a tally house 165 i don't know sell some shit no i can't i love all of them
i can't sell a moth or a there there i can't i can only sell worms because they have
tons sell the useless fox house what
they sleep in here give me another seed i could sell somebody but i love them all equally
breed the foxes but they have have a pretzel house i have to have to have to eat a quack
berry what the fuck is a quack berry you have 30 square pinometers of water okay i need more water
poppy seed no keep it i should be digging holes yes king stop all right i need more water and then
i can expand i can breed the foxes i need more water hold x to dig uh no you cannot all right
i think i got it burn the tally king i'm not burning the tally i'm just looking for three percent
square of pinometers or whatever it's called so i can get a duck this is a mess this is not a mess
look at those rocks all right do i got it can i go up here this is nice okay is this enough for
the a duck to show up look they love it it's fine ducker z hi i'm here remember your pet was on fire
what who was on fire no one was on fire a badger badger's not even my pet he just comes over here
and like shits in my lawn and then leaves don't eat that all right you two you two need to have
kids come on come on out out come on you're both in the mood get out of here you're not even my
you're not even my dog no no no no no no just just wait till just wait till they have sex
you i want a duck to show up i need money i need more water i think the sparrows are happy at least
more water more water be serious what about my leaf pile who's asleep no no wake up wake up
don't sleep in the water wake up wake up get out of the water get out of here get out of the way
huh you son of a bitch
what's this newt gat that's a newt cat here comes a newt gat that you made has made cool
all right what is this thing this is like an evil candy kill it all right so what is what is the
newt gat like come on over here newt gat oops no sorry i didn't mean to wake you it's just this
looks like shit so i'm trying to fix it frog get that frog in here all right not bad not bad
remove the dumb rock and torch what is it doing there that's decoration and the moths like it
yes i have arrived you have 20 square oh he eats tafflies oh no he eats tafflies
shit look at his eyes he's like i see one where's the like the newt toad thing where's the
we need him he's gonna do it he's gonna do it they need to breed that was sad but
we want a frog i'm gonna build a frog hut over here welcome happy because you're gonna get a house
i live here now oh he's green i want a frog house what else does he do nothing else weird right
has eaten one green flutterscotch for romance i need more water for the duck this game is so
cute it's just adorable i need more water why really that's not seems like a lot i'm taking
up my whole entire space here uh i don't really want the deer i'm gonna sneeze i must sneeze and
piss my pants information you didn't need but you haven't no okay half of my whole garden is water
at what point does this become ridiculous check your journal let's see the percentage okay garden
area view space info surface info okay so which surface each square is one percent of the total
surface area five percent water is what about the animals
what does the duck want oh do i not know checking encyclopedia for snail
okay appear requirements you are level four gardener or better
don't complain when your seeds start disappearing remember i tried to warn you
oh they hold on you get them to stay has eaten one apple seed and it'll live
before with it'll live with you i don't want this thing to live with me
my bunny comb i can't look up anything on the i think i have enough water
if you purify them
um
do you want me you want to buy an apple seed and purify the slug all right let me go pee before i
pee my pants that sneeze was a warning i'll bring it back hold on a second there bring it back now
we can do that hey see how you have the music this time very cool okay back to it
hmm now what frog i need oh he's sleeping look at this this is amazing he's so cute look at how
cute this is imagine if frogs were fuzzy that would be epic yeah it would what are you doing
over here are you guys gonna go uh yeah you guys i mean i gotta sell more of you i'm selling one of
the birds too yep i wish frogs were real yeah dude wouldn't it be cool if some of these animals were
real like frog fox worm i wish frogs were real oh here comes another one of these thumb things
no they don't live here yet i don't know what to do what's with the audio audio should be fine
that's just a video game i need to make money i gotta make money i gotta make some choices here
i could easily make a thousand dollars i could easily make a thousand dollars burn a fly i only
have one of these oh no there's only one left plant a bunch of vegetables and stuff all right
yeah that's the plan all right this is the vegetable garden right here need to be spread
out enough where i can actually plant them self-fertilized vegetables what could i what
can i put orange to pay the hunter for another one oh okay what does the orange fertilizer help
make fence this shit in i don't have enough money to do it is it carrots hey get out of the way
get out of the way orange stuff like a carrot you're gonna have to move actually yeah it needs
to be symmetrical you need to get out of the way actually no you don't you're fine right there
don't move all right i'm gonna get a bunch of uh fertilizer go on in first or fertilizer going
after after i'm doing all right like some of your uh vegetables please vegetable seeds
we got more poison ivy oh do you want hazelnut cool all right we're gonna do
i'm gonna do carrots get dog shit cheap too an excellent choice because i can afford it get an
apple seed for the snail we love snail all right but if i tame the snail take your time you'll
clean me up sorry that's the maximum number of items you can buy in one transaction
oh okay okay looks like i need to order
okay thank you okay finish up the snail's a huge investment yeah but okay if i give the
if i give the snail food this you know tame him he's gonna be eating shit all over the garden
that'd be horrible i'd rather just hit him in the head with a shovel orange fertilizer here we go
oh damn okay can i oh can i get them both in one hit i didn't think this through did i
what they're already done too slow why are they already done thanks i wish i could say i replace
all faulty items but i can only this is 20 bucks yeah the ones that are fertilizer 20
you you gotta go fast and you're gonna plant them right next to each other all right well
i got a taffly sitting on it in fact i was about to sell you no just just check out are you selling
all right let's do it again this time i'm gonna try to put them near each other
are these two close is that too close like right here the carrots is that too close it is too close
get out of the way hit the guy make it
now quick eat them actually no i just want i i want i want amphibious creatures
oh there's a new uh snuffle off i guess okay cool all right wait i gotta plant some shit hold on
chocolate cash melting in your pocket i'll take it i'm not fuzzy
okay it's quack berry time
so that's single you won't find plant them back to the items fertilizer no
hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry an excellent choice
okay get them all get them all thanks i wish i could show you don't want to come look at that
quack berry it looks like daffy duck oh actually don't eat that one they're gonna eat that bird
it's gonna be so sad should i all right so just sell the foxes and focus on amphibious creatures
yeah that's the plan are you selling because all right let's focus on amphibious creatures
always nice doing business with you yeah i'm selling the fox back soon discounts for regular
customers residents don't eat others on their own where's my new friend did i not pay attention
to him when he just left sell them and the house don't eat that not yet wait you're gonna eat that
all right if you eat that then you two have to breed all right i need a toad house all right
i'm selling the foxes wake up we're gonna give you to a owner that can take care of you too
they're gonna they're big and grown and they're gonna do really well they're gonna get released
into the wild we're playing a game made after 2005 jerma playing a game made after 2005 fog
that's pretty good that's pretty accurate 600 bucks this is 1200 dollars
this i got this is 1500 bucks say goodbye they're up they're the only friends you had
not when you're going to become an amphibious creature and dome now more importantly we're
making a bunch of water no no i didn't fill that kill the duck no i want the duck i want like
ducks and frogs and i have a shit load of money now i don't care about the deer i just want frogs
ducks and other things that like the pond i want a little walkway yeah we don't want to just one
big pond i want multiple ponds swamp i'm kind of i need a frog house i will burn that damn fly
fuck i i can only stream for like a little while longer shit well i've been having two it's been
two hours and 40 minutes almost i can't know it can't be it's all right we still have some time
he thought he was gonna get bored omega low it's just kind of it's it's just relaxing and fun
okay uh there's enough pond wait we have one more over here snail where i don't see a snail
that looks all right now let's build a frog house make sure i get that built
i'll get an apple seed no i don't want that thing living with me yes you do i don't want
early today and yesterday and the day before lick a toad home here we go
is this a game of the year 2006 material this thing is pretty big holy shit it has to be touching
a pond right or does it do i just put it right in the middle that's kind of cool right like right
here that'd be cool yeah that's pretty pog i guess i guess don't worry sooner or later you're gonna
have your own bedroom birds are gonna go to and the worms i just don't fit in with my strategy
if birds and tow the sparrows and toads and ducks no no we want bugs frogs ducks and platypuses and
shit you need a snail then swamps not complete without a snail that's fair that's fair all right
i'll buy an apple bushy tailed and ready to spend uh apple seed right hazelnut poppy was apple
poison ivy apple 55 bucks better be worth it found what you want just i'm just gonna put it
down don't plant it right you won't find them cheaper anywhere else on the island um you have
1.5k yeah but i just had to get rid of expensive animals i had two foxes in a fox house
that's i'm not taking that for granted pencil thistles and sell the blooms for huge money
apple seed to snail makes him good and stops eating seeds and bad ones stop coming title upgrades me
and your garden might expand so level up for that please didn't i already get one of those
all right let's open it up what does the frog hut look like it's beautiful it's even got christmas
lights on it i don't even have to do that it's perfect i can't wait for you to wake up when you
wake up you're gonna see your new house where's the fox hut oh you must have had the stream closed
for like the last 30 minutes and we're doing a new strategy all right we want what does it take for
you guys to breed i want to see a baby has eaten one green flutter scotch what is a flutter how do
i get a flutter scotch it's a bug green flutter master disguise it is easy to mistake it for
blowing leaves in the breeze what can i get you to show up um you better you better be going to
get that seed it's a pain in the ass seed might plant itself so just make sure it doesn't plant
just pick it up every now and then aimed animals do not eat stuff well i can make them eat and then
that's the romance category right to make them actually have sex with each other you have to
fulfill those categories right it's two out of three these frogs will not have children if i
don't do these three things right i think i have that correct stop saying the s word sorry i want a
they're meeting they're friends do you see that he licked him and he's like yeah okay now i can't
get rid of the birds they're friends it's called fucking look at they're hanging out on top i can't
get rid of the birds now wait there's a third frog no there's only two right what the hell is that
there was a big inhale oh i don't even need to do anything i'm just gonna sit here and watch
when's mario sunshine that's a pretty good question considering it might start next week
but i'm gonna have to dedicate up a whole week to three or four plus streams in a row to mario
sunshine i don't know it's gonna be the right spot uh i'm gonna go buy some stuff
stuff and viva piñata right i'm like a moth house uh maybe yeah this game kind of just one
of those games you can just turn on this is a game you can just turn on all right what are some
fruits garden items probably have some new stuff toxic drum why would i put toxic like waste down
here flower carving how is toxic waste a garden item produce this bread and cheese
bread who eats bread and it's really expensive bread for ducks it's 300 bucks do i get this
ducks love bread it's a loaf of bread people gonna eat this you know don't put it in yet
what about some paving oh stone paving slab maybe some stone found what you want
yeah this is nice ready let's do this terrible
what am i doing what are you talking about
what what's wrong with this this looks awful i'm not done
what's wrong with this i'm covering up the dirt plant grass i mean this looks so bad
uh mini golf course worse this is worse where is there no pleasing you guys what do you mean
worse it's just cobblestone 13 community subs just came in from spice plus plane thank you spleen
your problem is you don't recognize 13 subs the luckiest number in all the numbers
even worse i mean i agree with you that one looks bad all right
to get annoying real fast what are the different watering cans tin watering can the rocks were
fine yeah i know people are just super mean about it it looked fine let's get some more
i'm gonna dig some holes let's make some uh expensive shit i want some expensive shit
because i'm gonna sell it let's make a big expensive garden over here
i'm gonna plant expensive vegetables i might just do like 100 carrots and just dump fertilizer
on it and sell for like 500 bucks do some trees i will after this let's get out of the way why
can i not dig big pond i don't want to dig a pond i don't want to dig a pond i don't want to dig a
pond dude i want to dig a hole why would it not let me dig holes anymore there's a limit to how
many holes you can have what all right here we go what's really expensive because i want
to try to fertilize the graphics are limited oh what fertilizers do i have orange purple yellow
red and blue okay what's blue i'm gonna dump tons of money into this i want a blue seed
we got hazelnut blue bell blue bell so that's take your time you'll clean me out
let's take okay finish shopping for now fertilizer blue fertilizer beats the taste
so that's my hitting them how can i tell if it's hitting them is there a way to know what it did
did i get them all i think i got them all did i three times each on each weight fellas this
is a lot of money folks folks this is a lot of money folks this is a lot of money okay water
water water water water water water thanks i wish i could no i don't want to buy all right i need
the watering can right now hurry up are they good oh man look at these things plants stunted what
does stunted mean like were they too close it's still a lot of money that's all good it's still a
shit lot of money that's fucking a thousand bucks my shop fill these holes we're doing
that again big hole excuse me so how much space do they need but then i can't hit them all with
the same fertilizer the apple seed is rotten two spaces so like that like this to the red get out
of the way stop running by me you're gonna hit with a fucking shovel it's crooked it don't need
to be straight this is okay hey you're ruining my immersion what immersion of being a bad gardener
all right let's do it again just buying and selling buying and selling buying and selling buying and
selling well it's the most expensive flower i could possibly buy right now whatever it is i
wanted all right it's 83 bucks for a hazelnut seed what color is hazelnut this is a tree okay
stick with the blue bell all right that's the maximum number of you won't find them cheaper
all right get the fuck out of the way transactions done no creditory funds blue fertilizer so that's
this is gonna get expensive because they're gonna be spread out and i hit them both i don't know i
think i did it through three times hurry up all right i'll remember that for next time i think
that's one more okay that's enough that's enough that's enough that's enough water thanks i wish i
could say snail snail snail spotted snail spotted we have a snail spotting hold on thanks for calling
come back soon oh shit he's gone look at how fast he's going how easy looking is all right stunted
i mean they're beautiful that was an extreme investment only only 1062 i mean they're not
they're not done they're not ready oh shit all right no where's the apple seed get off these
flowers hey enough of that enough of that i don't know what you're doing but get off of that
get off stop it it's rotten hey get out of here what is he doing it's rotten all right just get
rid of the corn no one's gonna eat this it's a bug germ they like flowers yeah but still i have to
sell you because you're in the way we got a snail here comes the snail all right seed
apple seed i still have the pc copy from when i was a kid
this game ever released on any digital platform so is it only disc
isn't what it was games for windows live right you can't play it anymore okay here comes the snail
okay finish up come on this way snail he smells it you smell it here he comes all right come get it
do it come on we're in the fly already yeah but that's like a i didn't need why would i have known
i could do that that's just like secret animal spoilers we've been telling you the whole stream
game yeah but that's like saying hey uh i have a cheat code for you to put in right now you're
just you're you're two hours into the game this is the first time you ever played hey just here's
the cheat code for like five grand why would i do that get over here i need this five grand is five
grand it's still cheating this insider trading are these done they've been done i thought they
were not ready but didn't everyone say they weren't ready they opened don't they oh chat was baiting
you well just tap him with a shovel
are you going here because i need to plant you anyways like why i can't plant you
can't plant you how is it cheating if it's problem to progress what's not it's like all right it's
like one of the first things everybody started spamming guys i didn't even do the digging
tutorial yet and it was burn the fly make 2500 bucks now i didn't even like know how to dig a
hole please mr streamer hit something with your shovel burn it but keep it let it die if you have
to don't sell it under any circumstances what the fuck all right fly we're gonna do the thing
come with me go walk into that who's a clever gardener then you've changed your piñata into
another species
it's a red hot
in red hots and your gardening is improving does level up like 10 times i just leveled up like
three times it's like a peacock what red hot even want it eats three chilies does it sleep in the
same house are they fighting i gotta plant that tree there's no snail i gotta plant this fucking
thing fruit is op yeah oh new weirdo oh joy you've spotted me guess it's back to the pet shop for me
then you should drop in buy a petter accessory or just brighten up my day or something later
no i don't think i will i'm busy there they go they just opened you guys weren't lying to me
but i think they're ready art my triangulated circular friend can i bring to your attention
the arrival of my mobilistic dwelling and the tinkerific tool that lies within myself please
elect to pay me a visit whenever you like and we can talk some more about the signs of turning one
item into another cool the tinkerer now let's sell these why are they worth less
sell the blooms not the plant whack them you fucking genius oh you fucking genius
are you selling i need to dig don't eat that seed that's not cheating no because that's
that's just telling me what i can do with me creating a new species and the
send selling it for 2500 is different than hey you can tap plants one of them just died
get a stuff step into my garden buy a better watering can that's a good idea get the fuck out
of the way there's nothing you can do to make get out of here i'm busy there's so many seeds
i need all right wait this i'm getting overwhelmed i guess i gotta sell the seeds
i'm gonna sell them all wait water the plants back after they doesn't do anything javaid oh
what the fuck look at how happy the frog is he's like yeah i love that purple flower all right
let's tell i've got a lot of hold on sell sell sell sell sell sell sell sell it all 270 that's it
are you selling all right now plant i'm losing money what's this thing well not quite made 20
bucks yeah but look i have look at all the seeds i have hey any bouncers fuck i have to stop
streaming no i'm not gonna stop i don't care i have like important things to take care of but
i don't care playing with pretend fucking plastic animals is more important where's this
bouncing what's that all right i got a um water you throw out a weed oh to extending the opening
hours would pay off give you an evil seed he's a dick
i got a water hurry the fuck up thanks i wish i could water the tree it's a garden simulator now
i don't need four menus to go back to the game come on tree tree's okay tree's fine these are
okay kim's waiting in jail i really do have to leave though like soon really soon what's that
poison ivy seed rid of it this is a coin what is this good get out of here another orange seed
only rounder what what is this the mystery seed i don't know what's in him what's the mystery seed
pumpkin uh-oh a new evil enemy a bat no you motherfucker
how do i get rid of it oh you gotta get a gun i don't have a gun
entertainment apparently not very good at doing that where the frogs inside sleeping all right
we gotta get it's time to start selling i gotta focus i need more money i have more money all
right here it comes here holy shit it is pumpkin this thing's huge get out of here i will hit you
in the head with this shovel get out of here it is look at this thing pick it up can i like tap it
this thing's huge what what did i just do i made it rotten i just tapped it what
i tapped it once i how did i ruin that what is this thing i tapped it with my shovel to see if i
could lodge something on the mystery seed squash it i can't plant this here plant it near water
oh oh what is this this is kind of cool a little pond plant are you gonna play trouble in paradise
i have them all i own no small talk i got seed i need a where the seeds go oh something else
came out of the menu apple seed pumpkin oh i can buy the pumpkin seeds now that's cool
right here right here eat it yeah he ate it so now what
is ready to change the sour has gone into a cocoon where it will change into its tame form
problem paradise is the same game with more biomes that's cool first part of the tower of sour
let's see it the tower of sour as many pieces you will receive a new piece every time you make a
new sour pesto resident you may turn on those pieces by going to the menu and turning on the
tower of sour this is a town where you visit you don't go back you know there are some people
like myself who can help you with your more mundane tasks for example you should let a
sprinkling like me come water your plants for you i'm sure there's an initial fee but i'm worth it
you can find me an arfors in here if you want to take me up on the offer no doubt some of my
friends will be turning up too sooner or later really oh
he's so many of these random people these guys are their own germa rumble how are you
my inn's just the right place to come find a worker or two and now they've started turning up
you should come pay me a visit come for a worker stay for the milk okay uh big bits we had huge
bits from phylactery again totally 10 000 bits on the night which is fucking crazy thank you
phylactery for the huge money they say germa glad you're enjoying this game is one of my
favorites you should know though the sequel is just a much better game that has all this content
and more i don't think it would be a big deal just to skip to that one as is that that's true
that's an accurate statement if you did that's fine just to do that okay all right so should i
because this is a short stream today should i just do the tutorial in that game the next time i feel
like playing this and just kind of skip through that so we can just play gardening is improving
well done you just seem to get better and better okay yeah i'll do that oh my god look at him it
looks like he's gary he's so happy he eats blue bell seeds he's so nice now i'm selling all this
off i'm not even tapping him i don't care this game's really cool though it's just fun this is
a little it's just a little interesting little game this is one of those streams where it don't
matter what it has happening if it was like oh you know what what the hell do we do now
oh right i'll just turn on viva piñata that sounds like fun this is one of those i can turn
it on for a couple hours whenever i want are you selling because how much am i gonna get for this
600 it's not bad new chapter in the book oh is this done didn't they make a movie out of this
i don't they may have i still need a place for the tap please it was a tv show and there's
only one worm that's still alive now this too love these little toads i wish they would have
some children oh he's scared no get away from me well they did eat somebody you know it's true
all right this is going in is this done by the watering lady power of sour into the village
uh who's the lady that not the pets is the one that does work and a pet wait the pet dog
i'm petula another new face huh i guess there must be something interesting around here after all
yeah we sell pinatas pinata accessories for you for your friends whatever me i'm just watching
the place for my parents go ahead and look around piñata by cluckles or kitty floss
you need to just kitty floss so you're ready to good choice well this cat is so ugly
you accessories what first select were the eyes head oh no no don't tell me i can do these things
mouth as the i have to give those to the frogs give a nose ring gas mask see you around okay
hold on right here tomorrow i want to the next day i want to accessorize the frogs
teeth on frogs
frog accessories you what are we going to give the toad okay what about hats
i like it this is the best or the trash can like this is just a squid billy
oh daddy i don't know daddy tornation are you doing there uh daddy you like accessories huh
well let me know if you're ready to pay this is so weird clockwork key no i don't want to
fuck it up too much shoes though of bad food yep pink combat boots uh blue combat boots
going to stop gawking this is great this is i hope i unlock more of these all right that's good
see you around
it's so dumb it's like somebody made a slime or sock puppet it is a name
frogs are in the next game right good luck getting them to have sex now
how did i not play this 12 years ago what was wrong with me this is so fun it's just so
i just like it all right oh i grew it it's watercress
i'm gonna make everybody real sad though because people thought it was a baby game
glasses cat is cool too well if you're you're allergic get out of here i have to leave i thought
this was a game from moms have to get apples i have i have responsibilities they need to be
taken care of i have to do them tap the tree holy fuck that's a lot of apples how much does an apple
sell for that's pretty good all right next time i'm gonna have a bunch of apple trees
i'll leave a couple my shop is what moms would play before getting picking up the kids from school
move to the second game yeah what we'll do is what's the what is the second game this is like
two more right those shoes i feel like they're a hindrance trouble in paradise is the second
game so why do they not call like view of pinata 2 party animals is the one that i played all right
i feel like i'm just starting to unlock the reason why this game is fun so here's what's
gonna happen you ready so i'm going to play viva pinata trouble in paradise
off stream for an hour or two to get just through the tutorial no no don't no why i refuse what
did just to get it started because we've already kind of seen the beginning that's unacceptable
let's say i think that's acceptable to just say you don't have to so you guys don't have to see
that this is how you clear a dirt with a shovel all right oh well we want to watch all right we
want to spend time with you no we're putting all right we want to see all right all right all right
we'll do it so i'll just get to that game but for tonight this is it for tonight i gotta get some
stuff done and this weekend is i gotta get a lot of stuff done i've got i have to be an adult for
the next three days i know boohoo being an adult i know boohoo it sucks so i'll be back on tuesday
i'll see you guys on tuesday imagine being an adult i'll be gone for the next three days thank
you for watching this short stream we're still gonna do the bits and everything and hang out
for like probably 21 minutes and we'll sit us right at about four hours i am contemplating
starting mario sunshine this next week i feel like like a tuesday wednesday thursday friday
we could probably do all of mario sunshine this coming week or there's a couple of games that are
slightly newer you know germa only plays games made uh before 2006 i know we'll see but i'll
see you guys later have a good weekend you will see viva viva piñata will return just not this
one the next one i am pleasantly surprised by how much i think this is fun i'll see you guys on
tuesday have a good night goodbye thanks for sticking around for the few hours four hours or
so good night guys with that being said let's move on to the bits i think that that was a good little
taste of viva piñata now i know that i would i want the whole thing i want the whole meal
we'll get a good biome next time anyways uh we had earlier we had five dollars from
ank wank this game scared me as a kid i'm not joking really why i wonder that's interesting
masks well i guess some of them are kind of creepy looking i could i can understand it scared me too
really it seems like a lot of people were scared by this the guy who takes your shit and kills
things even piñata that's a straight-up horror game let me plug in here not me i'm a big boy
thank you whoa i can hear myself talking that just was weird let me turn that off i just plugged into
the go xlr and i just heard myself speaking in my own head all right uh hey drumager thanks for the
250 yo your short story about the frog costume guy made me think of a great stupid movie called
yakuza apocalypse we think it might be up your alley in most of the chat here i gotta turn my
monitor back to pc mode just in time for end of the stream i'm sorry i know short one tonight
here's a clip from the movie frog hold on let's we're gonna we're gonna go i want to see this
this is important mgs fan thanks for the gifted subs five gifted subs from mgs fan
thank you i want to just put this on i saw the thumbnail and i'm like okay what the
fuck is going on here let's uh let's check this out why is the audio so low what the
fuck is going on holy shit i kind of have to watch this movie what's it called
what's it called yakuza apocalypse just play the yakuza games it's the same thing
basically true i did play it i played the cues of zero and i got i got i just didn't give enough
time i got bored that was awesome that wouldn't even hurt though that's the best part about this
that's the softest fluffiest head in the world and it makes this thud on wood sound holy shit
is he darth raidering this guy well now i need to watch the whole movie so that was a good little
taste turned into a metronome yeah what the hell was that i think you'd like yakuza zero i got
through the first four or five hours of yakuza zero and i just stopped why did i stop i streamed
it what was the point of me stopping why did i stop i gave a reason right people were getting
bored i got annoyed with it because there was a hundred hours left there's a lot of dialogue
you had to read you hate good games i just played chibi rubble yesterday i said it was one of my
come on play it again and find out he hates good games he hates games there it is i was waiting
for it hey peaceful haley thanks for the 250 durham i'm so happy you're finally playing this
i actually used to get made fun of for playing this yeah people were saying that oh it's a game
for babies i i like the kids games now they're like fun i like the the e for everyone games
i love them now they're some of my favorites at this point it's not dark souls just wait
i i'm gonna be playing mario and sonic at the olympic games real soon probably no actually
it's um uh london 2012 i think is the the olympics game that i'm gonna play oh spoiler sorry it's a
game where you like old like oh can't wait but you'll see that eventually anyways uh they say
i can't find this game for cheap people are charging like 30 bucks or more for this and
i don't know if they sell 360 games anymore in stores anyway hope you enjoy if you get pinata
i thought i i thought i bought this all three of them i thought i bought them all for cheap cheap
cheap yeah you you can get this for like five bucks if you if you go on um amazon or ebay
amazon has currently amazon has 71 copies and they sell from five dollars and 42 cents
so they they are available sello yeah selling out for a 15 year old game that they don't even make
anymore speaking of not making things anymore what does rare even do now there's like a whole
rare office at microsoft they made sea of thieves yeah i heard sea of thieves is actually kind of
fun i'm not gonna say oh my god everyone rare used to make good games rare i mean i've heard
sea thieves is actually kind of fun i don't know how fun it's fun with friends but anyways uh yeah
you can get it for five to six bucks thanks hailey for the stupid they're doing battle toads oh
that's really cool i hope it's good when they redid uh the teenage mutant ninja turtles beat
them up it was absolutely fucking atrocious so old beat them ups they they try to translate them into
3d and they try to translate them into the kind of 2020 i haven't played one that i thought was
any good that was supposed to be some kind of reimagining a remake of an old classic
sure there have been some beat them ups that have come out that are 2d they made the original
battle toads so it should be good i hope so looks cool making a breath of the wild clone
really look into that hey lucas or lucius thanks for the 500 bits hey german just want to show
some appreciation i know this was a while back but i really loved your outer world stream so
i'm thinking of playing it myself i don't usually play scary games but i think having what you play
at first is going to help anyway have a good night that game is only as scary as you make it
it's more exploration than it is scary like if you fly a thousand miles per hour into a planet
you'll scream that's scary i did it a lot is that it was actually terrifying but the game itself is
the anglerfish are kind of terrifying and i guess you can't just avoid that place
you know what i mean like it's not just like oh i just won't do that part well you have to
you know what i mean you have to like do you have to go to like that all the planets like you can
skip it but yeah hope you have fun with it it was a great game it was very very very fun
a grave embrace thanks to the 360 three dollars and 60 cents uh they linked up an image it says
for safety reasons we recommend you to use a special password that you don't use anywhere
in the internet reliability level tall password must consistent what is this i don't i don't know
what this is i don't get it because i because i'm short or something pre-stream joke oh
phylactery thanks for the hundred bucks actually more than that 150 bucks because of the last
message thanks a lot dude you continue to give stupid amounts of money to the stream it's a lot
of fucking money and you give it all the time so thank you again thanks a lot the stalker guy is
going to give you a million dollars no i made it really clear i don't i don't i don't take bribes
but thanks a lot sam freelance police thanks for the 500 bits hey germa i turned 20 on monday
happy 20th birthday hope you had a good one what did you eat what did you eat on your birthday
corned beef hash what was it is it corned beef hash corned beef hash all right nice
this one i always have to make sure people are eating that i'm having a mild crisis though i'm
studying game design in university but i also recently got into music production i had a lot
more fun working on a song i sent you than any game design project and i've been spending my
semester break learning and doing more music stuff i feel like i'm going to pursue this
professionally i don't know what to focus on now for a future career if i should switch courses
or stay have you got any advice the best advice that i could possibly give for something like this
is i would try to do them both now i don't know how far into game design you are
because you say i'm studying game design at university how far into game design university
are you just do both well what i mean by that is you can make music in your free time but also
study to do something like game design and like i said before i don't know how many years or so
you've been pursuing a game design degree that's literally what i'm going to do yeah you're making
progress learning music on your own keep studying game design work on music as a passion yeah now
one of the arguments against that would be well i can't dedicate my time to both the same time
and put the passion i want to put into my music projects because of all the stuff i have to put
into my game design schoolwork and projects but that's how you try to make a balance just
for your life in general and it is hard to do that it is hard to work and do a passion at the
same time it is hard to have two passions that you equally care about and give them both the
same amount of attention it's hard to do that but i would say for as long as you can and depending
on like i said how long you've been in school for i would try to keep up getting your degree in game
design while doing music on the side but also i am not you if i really really cared about music
production and that's i that i know it now i this is all i fucking care about it's all i want to do
there's also that scenario where you'll finish your game design degree
and you'll be like well i don't even want to do this now it actually that that's not
unfortunately that's not necessarily an uncommon thing that happens in college
a lot of people will go to school for something and then just decide that it's not something they
wanted to do so it can be tricky and i unfortunately i don't have the right answer for you i think you
already might know the answer i think you might already know the answer i don't feels good man
but i wish you luck whatever you do whether you pursue music or you pursue game design or you try
to do them both i wish you luck some people switch their major several times it's more
common to switch than your major than not right that's true feels amazing man i don't know
but i wish you luck thanks for the five bucks gave the idiot thanks for the five dollars as well
there must want to let you know i forgive you for how you treated me in the mcdonald's
drive-through last weekend the coke you threw at me stained my shirt but i understand
you were just drumpy grumpy because your uh mcnuggets were late love you stripes beast
thanks with five dollars stripes beast germa i decoded your message on tuesday and i can't
find a smash mouth a jojo uh andy stinks in vegas i did find 500 bits though also please wear an
eyepatch until tuesday to preserve your winking energy love you and the community and what if i
wore an eyepatch all of tuesday and i winked with the eye that was under the eyepatch and that would
be fun hey zip flow thanks for the 500 bits thanks for all the streams lad you've helped me get
through some tough times and now you're playing one of my favorite childhood games keep it up i
told you this is childhood week give me robo cooking mama and then leave it be now i got the
penis shirt still saved as a tab but i just clicked on it god damn it penis like smoking camel guy
let's run the credits i'll see you guys on tuesday have a great weekend coming back with potentially
mario sunshine if not mario sunshine then no actually i probably no i'm not gonna do mario
sunshine on tuesday that's like the wink apocalypse no don't i'm not gonna do wink apocalypse and then
hey let's start mario sunshine no no no it's gotta be something else thanks for all the subs all of
you thank you the continued subscriptions to this channel is crazy thanks a lot again i say it a lot
i said every single stream obviously but thank you just keep links it's not that bad no we're
doing i'm gonna replace it it's got to change every few months you besiege or ellie bits i
want to do something where i can be on camera so it's going to be a full a total of an entire face
cam stream because i'm not going to turn cam on turn cam off to wink and they're going to be
significantly reduced in price we'll see but uh we had volemme and phylacteria lich back to back
gave 50 dollars a few minutes ago both of you volemme 50 fucking dollars phylactery 50 dollars
lemmy says hey germa been a while since i've been able to watch one of your streams
and i can't help but notice there's still no germa psycho emote would you like to explain yourself
yeah i know i know i have to sit on i just i've enabled more bt tv emotes than my own emotes
that you pay for in the last 30 days i'm gonna i'm gonna dump a ton of new emotes on you guys
randomly you're gonna get a shitload of them and i'm not even gonna tell it's just gonna happen
don't worry i will i will i will i will i will a 50 part bugleberry emote uh spiritual hog thanks
for the 400 bits check out amazing island for the game cube might be a good stream game i think i
was looking at that i didn't buy it though i was looking at it i think amazing island yeah i was
looking at this maybe i'll get it and finally blueberry juice with 250 thanks to the 250 they
say hey germa chan i also very much agree on you streaming the yakuza games again although i would
recommend one of the games with less mini game grinding like the businesses in yakuza zero okay
some other good starters are yakuza four or three those two are way more straight to the point
plus they're really easy they're really easy to get invested into yakuza zero is the meme one so
that's a bummer here's a clip of some of the chaos you might see all right all right all right okay
all right i might just play it all right i know they're fucking funny and they're crazy i know i
know i know i know i know i really should play them just for some i got i probably shouldn't
start with the cures of zero it was that was one that was in the ps4 though but uh without
further ado i've got to get out of here i spent it actually a little more time than i was supposed
to today but it's okay i can still get the hell out of here right now and go do the errand that
i need to do and then do the stuff i need to do this weekend have a great weekend goodbye
good night see you soon take care everybody see you tuesday