Good... Oh, I can't say good morning. I have to say good afternoon. Sure of my might. Yeah,
start a little bit an hour later today than usual. Stuff to do this morning. But I've completed all
of my tasks and I'm ready to play a video game. In front of all of you. Today, we're gonna be
playing Eternal Darkness. Ssssssadities. I've not... Let's... Let's stop for... Let's hold on a second.
Hadn't even been one, two full minutes. I'm just gonna... We're not gonna do that yet. I promised my
mother that I would at least be cordial and I wouldn't be like a weirdo for the first 40
minutes of the stream today. Sorry, Mom. Alright, turn to Dr. Synodys Requiem. This game came out
for GameCube. GameCube Classic. This game, uh, fucks with you while you play it. It's by Silicon Knights.
You might know them as the people that sued, uh, Unreal Engine and they lost.
Unfortunately, that's like the biggest thing they've done. Which is sad because this game is
really good and I'm actually one of the weirdos that liked Two Human. I liked that game. I thought
Two Human was good. That was the last real video game they worked on and then they had all this
legal problems and then they stopped. Two Human was good. I liked it. Me and my brother used to
sit there and play Two Human like three or four hours a day. Now, granted that only lasted maybe
a couple of weeks, but if we still had fun, you're Two Human. Hold on. I have a question.
Hey, how is me? Alright, this is important. How is me telling you a story about how me and my
brother played Two Human? A minus two joke or a plus two joke for that matter. That doesn't make
any sense. You know, my fond memories of me and my brother playing Two Human on the couch.
That wasn't very funny. That was really funny. Oh, you got an emote? Wait, you got an emote.
Only visible to you. You got an emote today. Thanks to EX Theo's subscription. Thank him?
Hold on. I can say thank you. What does that do? Thanks for the hyper slam. Hold on. How does this
work? Okay, I just hit enter. I don't know what I did. I just apparently thanked that person.
Hey, thanks. Thank me instead. I don't think I've seen that before. Alright, this is Eternal
Darkness. Let's move over to the streaming screen so you can see what's going on here.
Are we kind of loud? But it's okay. I will turn it down for you. I'm ready to play. I have played
this game before. It was about 20 years ago as you see 2002. So it's been a while, but I want to
relive it. Audio not synced up. There's no audio to sync up. What are you talking about?
Dude, audio is not even synced up. Let's test.
Fuck, I just turned into the demo at Radio Shack where you go in and you press the buttons on the
keyboard. You press like 014 and then start hitting keys. It's fine. We're good. Radio Shack isn't
real. Did they go bankrupt? This wretched book is where it all began so long ago.
Ace Camp today? No, not today. I love Roivas. It's a great tea. Oh, he's dead.
This is not my story, nor even the story of the Roivas family. It is the story of humanity.
Your perceptions will not change reality, but simply color it.
Humanity has been on the edge of extinction for two millennia,
ignorant of so much and dependent on so few. This is a scary game. This is not a scary game.
Let me correct you. What's going on? It just went purple. All right. Shit. Oh, come on.
Don't do this to me. No, no. Stop outing me. Is it emulated? I had to, okay, because I have the game.
I have the disk and it wouldn't capture through my fucking capture card. We're going to get like
purple flashes, aren't we? No, the disk. I've already shown it. Pick up the phone. We're going
to get purple. Should I put like a warning that says like, hey, intermediate purple flashing?
Of course, it could be perfect. Yeah. Who's this? This is inspector. I'll be on the next flight out.
Looks pretty good though. Could have used the Wii for this. I did.
Here's what happened when I went through the Wii.
It's because of the capture card. I don't know why it's doing it. It's fucked up for some reason.
I trust you had a pleasant trip. Yes, I suppose so considering. Yes. My condolences. This
most unpleasant. It's a shame we couldn't meet under brighter circumstances. Yes, it is. Can we
get this over with please? Of course this way. Oh, it's only going to happen when we change to a
different chapter. Not a pleasant sight. Oh shit. Okay. That's not that bad. I'm afraid there's
not much to see. Disable what? What should I disable? Disable store XFB. All right,
where the fuck is that? How do I store XFB?
Store XFB to texture only. To avoid this.
I already know what happens. Her grandfather was Edgar Allan Poe and like he wrote The Raven here
and then the place is cursed. I don't what that's who cares. There's no head. Now none of this
makes sense. There's no sign of intrusion and there was certainly a lot of force used here.
I have never seen anything like this in my 20 years on the force.
We have no evidence except for the body and what's left doesn't say much.
We don't have a single clue. When I go on my I'll turn I'll change it.
I feel like that's probably somewhere easy to find in the
until you do go into the registry edit hold on a minute I don't want to do that in the
middle of the stream I want answers so do I I wish I had some two weeks later purple flash
incoming no we're good turn on real xfb or after okay real xfb talked by her grandfather's mysterious
death and frustrated the incompetence of the local police alex vows to uncover the truth
she decides to search the mansion the place where edward al ad edward edward ed squidward
alan poe conducted his research if there was a tie to his past and possibly a tie to his murder
we'll be here welcome to eternal darkness sanity's end okay we got to search there's a punch game
already has plus one letter grade what do I think about vr salmon max kind of cool I guess
really is kind of like resident evil huh uh this is a sword with something I can
oh scary whispers a wooden plaque is fastened to the door taking the place of the lock
colored sigil is carved into the wood above a wide slot the slot is just wide enough to insert
a narrow blade I need a sword to open this probably if I remember how do I run is there a run
yeah it doesn't run okay but what about house flipper vr I mean that's kind of cool but I
feel like I already know what that's gonna be like I feel like I've already played that for
some reason I don't know why I haven't played piano the grand pianist dancer awaiting the hands
of a decent musician unfortunately edward never really lived up to that description and as such
the piano fell into disuse I wish I could just sit down and just do like a Mozart piece right now
you know I really think I wish you know how games have mini games that you said you like oh wow
this is a cool little feature for many why how come this has never been a full piano that you
control with left stick and like uh the two bumpers on the left side and right stick for
your right hand for the right trigger and right bumper that'd be so much fun if you just I don't
know why no one's done that it's so easy happens in half-life alex thanks for the spoiler hey thanks
for spoiling the entire series of a half-life alex to me there's a piano you can play thank you
the illustration features a collection of strange line designs related to each other in a cyclical
manner there's some significance to it but it's particularly evident it isn't particularly
evident okay I gotta find the secrets all right so what at what point does my screen turn off in
like the like the kojima of like hideo blinks in the top right corner doesn't that happen in this
game walk a beautiful carriage clock the hands appear to be stuck and the clock continues to
tick with the time permanently set to 3 33 there is a key in the back of the clock presumably for
winding it wind the key yes alex picks up the desk clock and pulls the key from it however there's
something odd about the key it isn't for a winding at all it looks like a dresser key
nice all right open a bedroom we're gonna find bedroom bedroom one portraits of the ancestral
roivas line the foyer walls their faces reveal a dark brooding edge there's something about
each one that gives the viewer an unsettling feeling this is the luigi's mansion house
I mean it's every horror movie mansion is the exact same they all are the resident evil house
they all have this gigantic red carpet bullshit that goes up two big flights of stairs that are
parallel to each other and then there's two rooms on the left and two rooms on the right
and one all yeah one all the way down in the hallway this is how every single the horror
movie mansion is it doesn't matter what game doesn't matter what movie all exactly the same
it's identical doors locked oh I gotta go to the dresser what a worthless hallway by the way
this is four why not just end the wall there save yourself like fucking five grand on new building
costs it's a secret room yeah that's true sorry all right this is the study five grand on new
building costs yeah I don't know what that was what what does that mean new building costs huh
that was just a bad translation I was trying to say a redone kitchen the warm glow of the candle
light the roivas family tree hangs from the wall shadows flitter across its surface obscuring the
detail if one looks closely the family secrets are revealed we'll look closely oh where's the
bedroom door is locked how do I where's the dresser dresser no I don't care about that guy I missed
the door I'm gonna hurry up it's but now it's 333 forever don't worry this one hey puzzle game no
I'm fine oh there there this is not a puzzle game by the way this is just to remember where the door
is game it's not a puzzle game I'll know plus you guys can just give me the answers it's fine
okay it's time for me to be up front with you I don't want to lie I have to tell you the truth
I've looked at chat more time than I've looked at the screen with the game on it I swear to god
I've just been hanging out with you guys just looking at chat I haven't even played okay so
I gotta play what did I miss if you I wish I could have a I wish I could time that or something
I would have what door did I miss this an eye tracker an eye tracker stream for me would be
you guys would hate it some of you guys would throw up you would just see how crazed I am on
a daily basis you'd be like wait a minute this there has to be a calibration problem how did
it go into the four corners of the screen 10 times in the last one second that's impossible
hey dude you calibrations wrong uh no it isn't that this set this time to 333 this looming
grandfather clock seems to stand ominously in the corner gazing on this empty room with an almost
patriarchal layer 333 yep the secret study don't touch that purple screen fix coming through
germawalk hold on a minute this is important oh man that I cannot can I like is that does that
person like have a sub they gave me a picture book like for a child graphics hacks bang bang
bang wait did you wait hold on wait do I check that box or do I do I just do exactly what you
gave me in like the fucking pop-up book all right wait I gotta get to a save point before I do this
let me get to a save point first again there's gonna be a purple flash by the way I have to
warn everybody there's a purple flash that happens like when we change chapters and then I'm gonna
save the game and then bang I'm gonna go turn that off okay so just I really am warning that's not
like a joke I'm not fucking around like seriously it's bad a large leather bounty antique book open
it and it opened to 16 by 10 resolution nor did I care the knowledge changed me have to do a
while reference will also change you every single strength as you read this oh you will come to
learn hold on I'm talking over the cutscene you too will come to understand this is her voice
talking or you will perish she's reading the book purple be careful purple I'm serious that once I
could not see beyond the veil of our reality to see those who dwell behind no that's bullshit
dude nobody reads a book in their own voice for I have learned the frailty of flesh that would be
strange why would you give every character your voice one fucking purple I told you sorry it's I
told you it's coming I hope I warned you long enough here is queer scandalous there is cons of
can you imagine reading a book in your voice
yes
read books in your own voice do you believe that it really exists centurion I do not doubt our
emperor's beliefs or his orders what but if we are to retrieve the artifact hold on a minute
and we must be strong and patient so when it when a character talks in a book you don't hear
somebody else's voice you hear your voice talking what no yes yes yes what are you talking about
I when I read a book I can let's okay let's put it this way so in like the game of thrones books
when little finger talks is it you doing a little finger impression
or is it the little finger actor talking and you hear it oh I hear a little I hear little
finger talking I hear the actor talking purple be careful give me a safe one so I can fix this
cat has no inner monologue omega low
second no that's not even true everybody has an internal monologue
my internal monologue I can get to be somebody else though like okay right now I'm okay I'm
thinking of a spongebob episode with spongebob that like grabs Patrick's nose squeezes it and
says this thing's gigantic that's not me saying that in my head spongebob is saying that I'm
hearing it not Patrick Squidward whatever that's everybody has that die on this floor is finally
crafted inlet with gold and gems that we can identify strong linear design is situated in
the middle and is equally unknown to the Roman soldier on that morning radio
all right so there's the symbol it's all about the symbols in this game I do have a weapon now
though which is cool this is a cock and then there's a whip you have to manually save how
this function allows the manipulation of inventory items yeah yeah yeah okay equip the character
with a with a weapon while the examination of objects press lr by switching back and forth
between the sections all right oh shit it is there is it is a manual save all right let me
get this done there we go all right I thought I thought I'm like my like my my fucking computer
I don't know what that was in the top left it could have just been like my fucking whatever
because that's good we're good s10w update gave 150 10 000 bits I'm stupid so that's like 150
000 dollars all right let me get this let me fix this before we get started for real so that's
saved in one sec that's that's a lot of money though hold on this is good to go let me check
this box reboot it okay well somebody just gave a lot of money that was a hundred dollars from
s10w update thanks to the hundred fucking bucks Jesus people still give me insane money I don't
even I can't believe it they say that they took my advice another the 47th richest person in the
world here's your cut peace and love all right let's get this I gotta I gotta get this to hold
on graphics hacks well mine doesn't look like that mine doesn't look like that uncheck it
wait uncheck that store e fb copies right or check it because it was checked already
okay that's all I have to do skip efb access from cpu all right I unchecked it let's see if it fixes
it uncheck everything all right I unchecked it it's unchecked I'm ready to start all right I
have the latest version of that software all right let's go deep into that darkness peering
if you fixed it I stood there wondering theory you unchecked the wrong one no no no no no no
this person gave me detailed fourth grade information a game all right it might flash
purple I'm just warning you hopefully it doesn't let's see what happens I unchecked it you are
from the third grade get banned get banned idiot ladder leads into the dank art of the labyrinth
danger lurks beneath let let pious her jesus
you know I I just found out a new category for 2020 is end of the year awards uh worst
we're eating or worst talking courage jesus like absolutely worst mispronunciation I don't know
what the fuck is going on man I aged a hundred years in fucking five I don't get it this guy's
gonna get up just like dark souls 2 okay so this is ready and this is swings look you just hit
people you can aim for their heads too right you can aim for different body parts this game is
actually pretty cool for a time you can target body parts and we have a five finish him we get
a five second slow mode so I can read chat and that'd be worse this beta represents life energy
every time a character takes damage the level will get lower when it reaches zero the character
will die okay I know what health does I mean this was 2002 right this was like 1930
okay people before your what slapstick sounds
that was pretty slapstick strange granite block lies on the floor okay I can put that block up
there do you smell burnt toast yeah yeah no no no it's like it's like sulfur right you smell
sulfur doesn't mean you're getting possessed by a demon wait should I go fuck knock on the door first
yeah oh I have to get all the cubes 100 sure it's something like that it's not like that
god damn it why does that person have to say that slapstick
it actually is oh you just have to add I'm so annoyed by that one of the editors
just here do me a favor I'm gonna swing in a bunch of them and then just put like
curly Larry and Moe talking and and locally wisdoms behind it it's perfect I'll get it for
you don't do that why not that that's funny watch out I want to go for the legs you know
you don't yet maybe have to learn it all right everybody quiet okay I'm realizing something
that's like early Larry and Moe killing each other you hear like a knife sound a knife going
into a body all the while with the three stooges goofy sound effect sound that's like Moe killing
Larry and curly with a knife in the kitchen that's fucked up oh I'm with their four blocks dead
all right all right get on the ground stay on the ground die I have three or four yeah I
gotta place them in the uh I know where I gotta go with it I'm gonna be walking right down this
hallway this guy's name pious gone highest I don't think his name is John here we go
no it's not biggest dickus I put the red one in here put into the walls a square
all right we have to ah that's I gotta go it's gonna have to go to 16 by 10 every time I go in
the menu it's so funny about biggest dickus uh look it up it's a funny Monty Python thing
did I miss one I actually missed one you're a fake fan what are you talking about
I mean that last one purple it's not pre-recorded save that word no now you know the word is p
it rhymes with uh intravenous yes
intravenous no no nobody said that I made it up I heard sponge I heard spongebob say it in my head
show don't you understand I can get spongebob to say anything in my head I just can you must
prove your worth by destroying this statue yeah so I have to destroy the whole thing
back the head in the arms prove it you I how can I prove something like that
right now spongebob in my head just said my name's German I-85 I'm streaming live on German and he's
at the computer and stuff like I can get him to say whatever I want I just heard him do it
are you guys figuring out that I have some kind of weird superpower or I can hear other people
talking in my head if I want to it's a superpower
I have an eternal monologue yeah I have both I can I can just I can shape shift it's really
hard to explain but a button attached to a small island softly illuminates the room a bizarre
energy seems to radiate from it press it press it hey if people that cannot think of words just
concept and images I don't know that's this is news to me I can see words in my head right now
like I'm spelling them out I can just see them like it's the ball is bouncing on the lyrics at
the bottom of the video I'm literally seeing every word I'm saying but everyone has the internal
monologue wait is it was I have to choose like a power what's the best Kingdom Hearts thing to do
health magic or damage it's never magic by the way they just put it there because Disney is
magical and shit it doesn't do anything shield and power the best one let's see details effigy
resembling a warped angel shaped from the dark green emerald covers effortlessly above the
pedestal should I just claim this artifact all right hold on no I pressed a I pressed yes
I was trying to press B looks like looks like we're going with the earthbenders
shit accidental super powered god damn it whatever this is the best one anyways
hey notice how there's no uh white symbol here hey it's supposed to be fixed and I have I was
once as naive as a child is sharp um that was our anyways notice how there was no uh air symbol
there of others and make them just saying mad with a fucking purple shit ruined my joke you know that
was gonna be funny fucking stupid-ass purple bullshit perish now the text is purple great it's
mocking me whom of the eternal darkness hey professor Richard cheese thanks for the 10
community subs read it this time oh fuck what do you mean read it there was no text on it before
read it just store it mine was already checked mine was already checked man I was checked already
graphics tax if efb access from cpu should I check it pretty cool game the game is actually
pretty cool because store efb right now detections only was checked already just make the check marks
that are in the image hold on fast step calculation I'm just gonna copy this person's homework
internal frame buffer wait why that two of these wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute this
minus two or xfb copies to texture store efb copies to texture like it's xfb right it's so
the efb was wrong I have the old version this I have the new version of I have the new version
chroma key out the color purple you motherfucker turn on real xfb or disable xf store so this the
tutorial that I got in the imgur link is wrong they maybe unchecked the wrong thing that's not
even a debate I think that person was trying to be helpful fuck I was gonna like mod that guy okay
I just tried I unchecked the thing let's see what happens key out purple I can't just key out the
color purple yeah it's store xfb not dfb that's the xfb is the one that I have to uncheck so
the really easy tutorial was actually wrong and hard I mean do it if it happens again I'll try
disable xfb fuck it was efb in this guy's image
okay I gotta pay attention I gotta pay attention I gotta pay attention
this is gonna be some coordinates here hold on all right what is this crank socket is mounted
in the telescope appears to be linked to a mirror supported by a brass pedestal curious contraption
to be sure what purpose can it possibly serve just it yes this reminds me of like how old tv
shows used to do guy is ai or made out of machines and it's talking oh yes mr stevenson it is so glad
to see you I am so happy to see you pretty pretty torn on that one I see a lot of people
didn't like it a lot of people did it's pretty interesting okay this is open what did it open
examine globe cradled in a wooden frame its glossy surface is painted in the likeness of an ancient
map the lens is situated in the northern hemisphere above a label that reads there be
dragons here there's two of these though just mirror right wait a minute there's nothing in
the top crank doll do you guys see a mirror where's the mirror did you say I was adjusting
a mirror thing up top how's it making that noise are there any more of these yeah there's another
one of these over here too fuck what do I do with this can I not do this yet I don't think I can do
this yet I'm back later the fuck I just got the twitter notification he sent out dude what
we've been let's go where can I not go before let's go this way this is open now
no this is locked this is green now okay please for the love of god don't do that
okay uh is it like a family sword I have to go get like ps's sword or something right
how come every game I play has instant messenger sounds fuck stop ruining a game I like why
that's true but I now I like this game now you're making me not like it anymore
all right where's the sword there's a sword secret down here or something sword I'm looking for
uncle's sword these books contain the history of the Royvus family yeah whatever it's the lore
who cares where's that sword it's here somewhere give me the sword oh let's go down here lore is
unimportant no lore is not unimportant lore is unimportant for me streaming good painting of a
jungle shrouded building it seems to be a temple in Asia perhaps from Thailand or Cambodia ancient
Roman weapon a gladius take it go put that sword in that door press her key and second floor key
I don't okay I can't use it all right got the sword let's try to stick the sword into the door
let her rest what why I can't oh right because I'm holding down left trigger okay she's fine
you're killing her she I'm gonna be fine I don't care about this I want to stick this into wherever
it was where is it this way it's one of the left doors you know you're gonna be fine we're concerned
about her all right stick it in stick the sword in the slot is wide enough to insert a narrow blade
god damn it Alex places the blade in the slot but feels it push back it is as if the magic of the
blade does not fit the lock so I gotta go like bless this thing in the blood of the green guy
right how do we do that gotta be a slime guy sword yeah all right well how do we do that though
so green eats blue blue eats red red eats green and purple is not part of the food chain
okay please make monkey noises we're not going we're not doing that again okay no you got you
did that once and I'm not doing it again please no no I'm not gonna do monkey noises no the key
comes apart in the lock the key to the second floor is broken is there a way of repairing it
Alex has picked up the broken second floor key can I not you well it's still locked he must be
repaired somehow god damn it okay stop and I'm never doing it again I am never doing it again
even for a thousand dollars at this still I don't know can I do anything with this can I stick the
sword in no minus two what a sellout that means he'll yeah that means oh no that's not what I'll
mean not a thousand and one I'm not doing it again I need to hold on I need to bless this
fucking sword I'm gonna go into the sword room back into the library wait book in the sword room
use your special book this is the tome of eternal darkness with spells whatever I'm gonna go should
I go back I'm gonna think I'm gonna go into the library where's the library again I read that
put in here do an antelope now I don't I don't know what an antelope sounds like I have no clue
all right what did I miss something in here some kind of mask faces serenity and composure
oh cool strangely with the tome of eternal darkness in her possession Alex can read the
page it is a chapter page from the tome itself take the chapter found the chapter page titled
the binding of the corpse god put it in the book and read it I cannot say no purple true beginning
nor am I sure of its end so perhaps here is the best place to start I am reminded of ideas I first
encountered in sir James George Frazier's book the golden bow a study in magic and religion
we are overwhelmed by a very human need to weave a weather of 1400s and 1500s
since time immemorial ancient peoples have dressed up their lack of knowledge
as gods and demons I have discovered that sometimes
Bible the fates of gods and mortals intertwine legends are born I guess I am just describing
the Bible I'm like yeah well I want to I want more of that though my time is done read the
bibles forever in shadow will you be master of chaos and to fade to nothing in obscurity
will be thy fate many millennia for this day it is the true chaos of all things
that you now must be entombed amongst the beings of flesh and bone see you have a great monument
here mount rock it is a pity that no lies it as yours may the darkness claim the
chaos and damn beast no longer will thy reign be kept over the ancients you have kept imprisoned
thou hast seen the last of this world no I killed this guy on this thing under here
brushing all of his eyes this is purple guy so I have claimed this temple in the name of the green
guy not even these mythical fables can keep me amused yes there has to be something to do around
here I wish something that fantastic and of higher purpose could happen to me
all right let's go I have a weapon gonna be like puzzles here and shit in there okay a triangular
design is carved into the floor the etched grooves are filled with colored sand related to each other
yeah okay just keep this in mind we kick red's ass blue we have to run away from just remember
that okay we are not afraid of anything red we are only afraid of blue statue of a goddess
delicately sculpted from sandstone it casts an alert eye over everyone who enters the temple
there's a strange necklace about its neck should ilia take the necklace from the statue yes
strange necklace this necklace can be used to heal elia make sure that ilia does not move when
the spell is being cast okay there do I have to use it I can heal take a look at what we got for
doors here it's kind of dark don't you think we're gonna go left I'm gonna get up emote only mode
incoming um why okay this is gonna this is harder than I thought it was gonna be
it's actually very easy it's not hard at all let's go left right
sentence fortress oh shit I didn't even mean to do that correctly and I'm doing all right
I'm located by creatures a sanity loss occurs causing a decrease in the level of a sanity meter
and the character to pulse green beware sanity loss affects perception and eventually health
aren't these things in Zelda okay what just happened there's your sanity meter this meter
represents a character's sanity every time he she meets a monster his sanity or her sanity will get
lower the lower the sanity meter the more the character will hallucinate yes okay here we go
performing a finishing move on a creature recovers sanity that was fucking crazy give me that sanity
back a bronze necklace take it I have two necklaces does one do more than the other
is that it not a door the design of the wall appears to depict the time of the day perhaps
the candles do too light or extinguish the candles no don't just smash it like a four-year-old
okay here we go okay so we need to we have extinguished them all one in the middle it's
sun time yeah I got it oh fuck I couldn't pay attention to what door just opened all right you
ever have that so I just drank uh I have a soda water over here it's like just a carbonated water
and I you know when you drink it sometimes and you do something weird with your throat
or you turn a weird way and it somehow hurts it goes into like your sinuses and in your nose
and it's like ah you like do it the wrong way somehow and it's just because it goes up to your
roof of your mouth and kind of into your yeah I hate that just happened like the worst it's
ever been by the way that was horrible on charts finish the sanity meter if you don't know if you
never heard of this game you're like what is this game this game stupid look at this shitty game
that he's playing well the whole point of this game is uh you have the sanity meter and the
game starts to really fuck with you game like deletes your save files like turns off the screen
it torrents movies behind your back you know whatever it does it's not good it makes everything
really bad it fucks up the whole game stops boiling oh yeah that's sorry never mind this
game just sucks never mind hey guys don't worry the game's just bad it's the game just sucks
okay there it's just a walk around and swing at enemies and open up doors that's it nothing
there's nothing cool in this game engraved on the floor is a striking design featuring the sun rising
above the edge of the world I gotta remember that puzzle or I gotta remember that for some
another one of these uh appears to depict a time of the day perhaps candle do-do-do
yeah they do all right so what's wrong with this one can't blow these candles out why not nice
dodging it's the easiest thing ever this one's red red is good right we can kill red easily yeah
welcome to pokemon this is how pokemon works right um not really engraved on the floor is
a striking design featuring a starry sky filling the heavens I feel like I'm gonna need to remember
this shit yeah this is there's nothing here but I can't touch it okay wait I can touch it
so it's all empty yeah that's it done both the doors came down when I came in yeah so the door
from that other area which god helped me if I can remember where that was that's the blood-borne
noise I don't know what do you mean which one small pedestal covered with decorative etching
stands before the wall the blowgun upon it must have some special significance for it to be the
focal point of this display I'll take it roll the credits oh my saber a shitty sword
yeah that sword was made that sword was made out of like rock candy not even glass fragments of a
shattered short sword lie up on the floor oh pick it up you can all right I gotta shoot this guy
with a blow gun in the head oh these wait these are my friends these are green guys I shouldn't
be attacking green guys right yeah I'm like my sanity's messing up late for that oh well
right so what are you what are you who are you the guard is grateful for Elias saving his life
in return the officer repair Elias broken weapon as a gesture of thanks thank you
thanks that was very very that was way shorter than I thought it was going to be
I didn't know it was gonna happen instantly like that I don't need that guy for anything right
I'm gonna it's red and stiffy happy happy joy joy happy happy joy joy happy happy joy joy
happy happy joy wait what's wrong with me
monster wait I haven't saved the game in probably a full hour I have to win as the slime guy
where do I go stupid no I don't want to beat this guy anymore is there anything I could do
oh let me regain my sanity let me watch like Fred Rogers give a speech so I can at least
gain my fucking sanity back okay this mural depicts a skeletal demon befriending the ancient
smear people by denouncing one of their fertility gods and I'm not even kidding anytime I tell you
anytime you feel like shit anytime you don't feel fucked up watch Mr Rogers talk about anything
you will feel fucking great afterwards I gotta save the game I'm I'm too insane to save the game
what did I have to kill that guy why what was the point of that it didn't do anything I just
I didn't know I thought it was I'm gonna get some sanity back right here come on
okay give me the sword the sword's better I want the sword all right what the hell am I doing in
here there's a holding device as though something can be inserted perhaps a key or lever
I need a key or what do I have what the hell is strange necklace 10 oh yeah heal
my insanity is too low all right I can't believe I didn't fucking save the game either that sucks
all right I need to get a lever or I gotta get a lever save now you killed the enemy yeah Jesus
God so that shit's already happening this hallway longer what this this room is different
okay I can kill these guys I'm gonna finish off like two or three of them
finish no don't look at me stop looking at me please you fucking can't be serious dude
because I had to shoot that guy all because I had to shoot the guy and it ruined everything
I'm here so I can finish you thank you my god okay I'm back to normal sort of now what opened
this is all right this is different save game now back yes that was whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
that would have been 45 minutes of lost time doing nothing what is this I got a link what's
this one filming eternal purple from a stream from a stream fortnight I know I don't want to
do that I'm not going to stream fortnight this is your way to you know make like a make like
a funny image and I'll look at that and somehow I'll be like okay yeah I'm gonna do that
play fortnight no I'm not gonna play why would I do that I don't I don't want to play fortnight
this is pretty good though wrong the link there's no such thing as a wrong link in this stream
what would constitute a right link all right what was this even a reference to no shit
there's me in the mirrors all right cool good we got it awesome all right let's go
let's go talk to the god when this thing supposed to be dead
but this is even way further back you are reduced to feeding on flesh and bone
mighty have fallen you will surely fester for millennia to come a slow and torturous fate
for thee you had best leave young fool or you will find yourself as food for the dead god
dead god start communicating with me no I didn't
I really want to go stand next to this thing and do the like the moon presence thing from
bloodborne what's it called contact
the essence of what's god the sun that is a source is small from those people you must
get it unless they use it to destroy the little brightness your world has left in it
it's like if the heart in your body was as big as a sunflower seed it's not even a heart it's
look at how big this guy is he's this guy is as big as three or four houses that was his heart
all right I have I have the eternal darkness
metal staff is held by the arms of the statue I have acquired the staff
there's your lever you know he looks like a cabbage I've not really seen it but
I don't fight him don't fight him don't fight him don't fight him oh my goodness
fucking gracious why did I just do that
okay fucking who cares finish this guy I just peeled my nose off but my whole front part of
my face just came off okay I'm not getting sanity for that oh hurry up I'm going
shit I'm insane I don't know what to do put the thing in quick what did that do it what if all
of them like he just got slimed that's it behind him wrong way wrong way what didn't I go from the
other room wrong way that's the only way okay I'm good wait it should it was the wrong way
what won't crush me wait am I getting Luigi'd did I get the bad ending already what did that
even do drum of the voices drum of the voices he was just saying chill out dude
all right we gotta keep going this way dude he was just saying chill out man
sponge bob voice you mean the guy doing happy happy happy look around okay examine who what's
this natural human female bears witness to the monstrosity that fills the room somebody puking
pick up fool you should have run instead you will die where is the essence of manta rock
do I use it to zap him where is it I will not ask again child very well then you will set
count of the horrors of oblivion after complete that's kind of a weird transition
candles are here now all right let's see the candles small shrine of candles their placement
appears to be very deliberate corresponding to the etchings on the table and an illustration
upon the wall etching on the table illustration on the wall I already know what it is ready I
already got it I remember things the cigar with the correct sequence of candles being lit a hidden
panel opens there is a message tube found the message tube what does the message say
antique leather bound message tube the kind used to transport sealed message scrolls
it's unopened all right chapter entitled suspicious of conspiracy your presence is welcome
majesty as always I am honored my concern is with the other ancients
it's a girl in harry potter should they unite with manta rock like the ghost girl
he floats around she's talked to harry
myrtle was unaware there is nothing like that it kind of is that's pretty close that's really
the only thing we're missing is like the then what shall remain the frank
what do you intend for him the frank is an instrument of light he seeks to unite europe
under his banner when this in place my guardians will be hard pressed to perform the functions you
require for your own schemes pious think of your future then charlemagne will be removed from the
picture explain like i'm oh no that's eu moment but he was doing explain like i'm five
of course he is as good as death okay after the chapter page is removed the message tube
is no longer needed alex discards it so we're good to hear about our god okay cool so now we're
gonna find another chapter page which do i have wait isn't this the save the game yeah
remember to save yep yep yep okay so i already did this one right did i not do this one oh you
discard it from my research it is apparent that the endeavors of mankind are mere puppetry at the
hands of the ancients whenever a king vows reform the ancients move quickly to stifle it sorry for
that uh apologies that image i made with the fix it was incorrect the new holy roman empire
it's fine it's all right the height of its power i'm just kidding around don't worry man
will you stop reading this to our lord and emperor charlemagne the frank
no one but him must see it yeah i fixed it already i did
yeah i know i got it we would have already seen it don't read that okay quick quick poll would you
open that ever again what sorcery is this would you open that ever again i have bewitched
okay and what do you do after that will become you tell anybody i have to warn him of this treachery
i'm not even sure i would tell my mother that happened what do you even do with that thing
destroy it you can't destroy it it's definitely too powerful to destroy burning it would just
make whatever god angry that you burnt it holy shit i almost punched this person after anthony
briefly describes his mission the monk informs him that charlemagne was last seen in audience
with the bishop in the visiting chamber is this why everyone was spamming for me to save the game
because i was gonna punch somebody in the face and ruin everything that's why i get it okay
thank you for the help i appreciate it i even have a punch funeral casket made from unfinished
wood it is not properly sealed should anthony open it yeah all right put the
close it close it close it you have closed this poor man has been the victim of great evil
look how his body has been defiled as if something has burst out from inside him here
take this for your protection and find the bishop yeah take this be informed of the same sword that
every single one of us and all of our ancestors ever through history that's like the historic
blade that's just passed down for 10 000 years right yeah the scrab mass six that sounds like
me trying to say a word and that's me saying it incorrectly like that's me trying to say sacramento
california that's like what i say in here in my head uh yeah i saw scratch the mass six california
i have been i've been there before it was cool oh no his brain we must warn the others
but i equipped that shit what else can i do in here i do have a map i'm just realizing this now
save charlemagne oh i think he's been dead for like seven or eight days how am i supposed to
save that guy awful voices emanate from inside the bishop's visiting chamber however the door
is locked and anthony will need the bishop's key to enter all right oh find this key the bishop's
key he's on the toilet no he's that's like his audience chamber now what silent hill ilia
pious oh yeah i destroyed his statue right on what appears to be a leathery hand lies a mysterious
book it's bound in human skin beckons to you should anthony claim the tomb of eternal darkness
you got it okay i got the book that was up there apparently who wrote it yeah
who wrote that that's a weird thing to think about who wrote the tome of eternal darkness
whoever wrote it was it was being dictated by somebody else or did like satan write the book
who actually wrote that book why would you write that book it had to have been like dictated by
some god i guess yeah i did it i wrote it for fun this up i know that it's red blue green red
blue green red blue green circle of power circles of power describe the amount of power that a spell
will have the more points within that circle the stronger the spell will be spells are magical
incantations that enhance a character's natural abilities okay here's the spell list it's an
inventory of all the spell information okay we're signed a quick spell collecting this will allow
the player to experiment with ruin combinations and discover new spells okay that's the inventory
of all the components of the magical spells and this is the quick spell all right let's see what
do we have a quick spell nothing whatever spells nothing new spell don't have enough
components to make a new spell what have i got again there ruins circle of power okay like what
am i supposed to do with that oh what's this uh there's one that can be moved always check the
bookcases always one spell andy sure uh-oh what's that does that mean what is it is he holding
something is it did he eat that or what is this supposed to be his arm off i can't i'm stuck in
this room good all right hold on i'm gonna stop breathing a second let's give it go right rest
yeah see all right we're good magical ruin all right so yeah you i remember this yeah you go
like ru ru parka parka ru parka and it does something i remember this yeah okay the key
elements creating spells you use them in different ways okay new spell don't have enough weird how
your brain just remembers those things i haven't played this game for 20 years since it came out
i don't know why but i know that i know that ruin the way that they say it boomer alert
what's wrong with me i didn't drink some water i look like me when i did the last green screen
this guy's fucking dehydrated you good what the is this the guy that used a wheelchair in middle
school yeah weirdly we're just that's a weird thing to hold on to that's a straight i'm just
gonna tell you that's a weird thing for you to know and hold on to for this long grateful for
his life the monk tells anthony what happened he was carrying a sacred urn from the baptismal
font but he was confronted by the bishop who was brandishing a large blade in whose eyes burned
with an evil fire the monk dropped the urn out of shock and ran returning to retrieve the urn he
found only the sword the bishop had left behind thanks he gives the bishop's sword to anthony
he's me nice i'm a bit i love two-handers no i'm not gonna kill this guy i know you all want to
see it but you know i'm not gonna do it everybody thinks i'm just gonna fall back and baseball
swing that guy's head off no i made that mistake already please rotate there is darkness difficult
to make out anything well i could probably help that picked up the piece of broken green urn
there they are piece of broken green urn mix them together two-thirds of a broken green urn okay i
need the rest of the pieces of it rip urn yep nothing to do with these uh boxes right nope
the whole thing together broken green urn is it like a glue what else can i do with it
another rune agmor arpstone tablet okay i got the magical codex codex runes cannot be misunderstood
roots cannot be understood without a codex without a codex runes in your possession will
remain a mystery uh right okay all right we need to collect those okay well he instantly died
cool thanks for the magical rune there it is all right so this is item no new spells i need
i think three right jeremy it's the power of fire why am i what's this why is this happening to me
all right damn this thing's awesome okay this is uh let's say you're in ruins
oh
i still alive red urn pick it up all right eyes of the fixed degree one
is there a quick weapon switch probably not this game is in from 2002
disturbing rendition of a monstrous devil can i drink urn urn urn urn urn
this an age tapestry hangs on the wall of the soils from the dank atmosphere and the
corruption about it after i burn that right yep i really do feel like i'm playing resident evil
having to go into the menu and switch weapons damn that was two hits that guy got wait finish
him he's a pair of legs he's like the number bunchers monster really do i have to finish him
everybody said the oh is annoying i'm leaving i don't know what that means okay an iron plate
in the floor is carved with three curious circles bright splashes have marred its
pockmarked and worn surface three curious circles that's where the urns go okay what is this one
i have a go this one antorbach project i want you to find julio amongst the books on the table
is an ancient scroll of what appears to be paper enchant item spell scroll
ha through this function the player can examine the content of each spell scroll that has been
acquired okay oh wow uh the note reads that which is broken shall be fixed that which is dull will
be sharp that is another the the nature of the enchant item magic the spell requires the
antorbach and magormor ruins i haven't bought all right let's make the spell new spell what are you
talking about okay antorbach and magormor i don't have it i got it the hell is this open the bishop
passed through the secret door there has to be a way to get through it shit how do i get through
it do i have anything or or the urns urns urns but i don't have hold on although the urns it
appears to sit correctly in place on the pressure plate it does not appear to be heavy enough to
depress it yeah i gotta fix the urn i don't oh oh god damn it okay hold on
while fumbling around the urn slips from anthony's stiff fingers dashing itself
into fragments on the floor oh wait there's a rune in there oh all right i found it
ulioth antorbach magormor you've just discovered the enchant item spell nice this allows players
to cast spells that have been found or researched and you can assign this cool this will enable the
casting spells without having to choose the book yes thank god like the alignment spells can be
cast directly from this book or from the quick spell you have to press up yeah okay there it is
magic meter this meter represents the character's magical energy the level will get lower this
meter regenerates whenever the character is in motion all right let's go so check this go cast
that spell nice voice oh three is that not enough to depress it what are you talking about it in the
wrong spot oh because it has water in it okay shit wow your character looks dead yeah i know
oh i love that sound sound of just like pee filling a jar like water pouring into a glass
asmr asmr piss video um that would be kind of weird because that would take you a long time
to film that video it would take like three or four weeks to get a three or four or five minute
video get 10 minutes of pee content asmr that's like four or five days of drinking food and water
but take one day no it would not 10 full minutes of peeing oh shit boss bike cut his head off all
right i got the key shit dude i even kill i like i killed this guy's clothes detail all right shrine
to a god that speaks of an ancient evil all right now i got the uh i got the key back to the front
door save the game i can't okay just don't lose don't lose and you'll win yeah exactly characters
just yeah i don't know no no i want to kill this guy finish to the bishop's door they do a lot i
don't i don't care little scorpions great i don't remember this shit trapper dimension sprawls in
every direction while in this place magic cannot be cast and the humans are subjected to odd
phenomena the portals cycle from color to color as time progresses and you own and only the quick
will escape okay i need purple oh i guess i'm good oh that's to refill your sanity did i die
i don't think i did oh i'm back all right well i refilled this entity let me save it
this is a little side thing rappers have no eyes but can sense sound very well if anthony can sneak
past them they won't be troubled oh just be quiet i have no idea where they are i can't believe
germa stole this game right next to me in fact i think the we is still i think turned on
oh it's off i got it it's off it's off wasting power it's no i just looked over it's a it's a
red light it means it's not on oh by the way i want to make sure everyone knows this tomorrow
is dlc movie night that's tomorrow doing it somewhere around noon 11 to 12 the idea
there is a ton of videos i don't know how much we're gonna get through but we're gonna see how
much we can get through in like five to six hours all right i got the key this is not community
content night this is only the dlc movie night i really don't look good this is it looked like
shit 12 hours or riot i can't sit here for 12 hours boss fight uh-huh all right i'm working slow
i'm just over encumbered cut his other arm off cut the other arm off cut his other arm off
good looks like you're using voice commands it would have been bad if he got up okay
it was sexy pose jesus this guy's still standing you know what i'm so pissed that germa didn't get
the sexy pose from that game i don't i don't think you are that mad about it i think you just
remembered because we just started talking about it and like two years have gone by and you
remember two years ago when you were annoyed you're not still mad about that oh we're trying
to save him anthony his fate was this game's metal as is the fate of this world yeah i guess it is
your faith there is little to save you from the power of yeah the book got too scary
i'm done reading today i don't like this part i'm gonna stop what else is in this room that i can
fuck around with go back down right save the game wait i can fix broken stuff now right every time
we read in the book we learn something in the real world you got stick bugged shut up stop do not
unbelievable unbelievable i refuse to laugh at that but it was funny and it's annoying me how
funny it was somebody just donate like ten dollars and do that or what leave no i want to leave
oh you're not coming in at the door no that's stick bugged oh my fucking god i'm so mad at that
come back another day fucking instant messenger why is it i don't even it's so i whatever benjamin
franklin too dark in here to do anything perhaps the circuit has been broken better room chapter
page has been hastily stashed behind the frame oh the gift of forever sick sick cigarettes ammo
let's read it chapter four dreams modern psychology offers only unproven theories
some see them as the meaningless tossing and turning of a brain settling into a restful sleep
others see them as laden with symbols of our unconscious desires
to still others dreams represent the upwelling of the archetypes normally hidden deep within
the recesses of the human collective unconscious of one thing i am certain after a brush with the
ancients our dreams metamorphosize i played it i already did it man all right this is 565 ad in
persia saw actually i have saw two here lord you for years advances i do is right there yeah
and think of nothing else i fear i desire you many hundred times more than you love me
my life has become a waking dream kareem for weeks i have dreamed of an ancient treasure
so precious that it changes all life around it it must be mine kareem if you truly desire me
as you say then you will find this for me bring this treasure to me oh relax i will be yours
both of our dreams will come true i need nothing more than you you have enthralled me to the point
i can think of nothing else promise if i leave will not forget about me you need not worry i
desire nothing more than the treasure that you seek leave now kareem and i shall await you
time for us to do some puzzles fell for it the end no it's not the end it's only the beginning
axe oh man's corpse lies fallen wounds cover the exposed flesh of his body where his armor has
failed he's gonna get up oh here are all the statues it's a new one anthony ours is gonna be
right here very very soon claim the tomb of eternal darkness that's part about games back
in like 2000 1999 2002 whatever is this is a mario no you know it's just like oh
really mario no doesn't do anything you just actually like step away funny if it did something
else tome of eternal darkness home the tomb why can i not move already insane how am i actually
trapped in the corner kill kill no don't climb down climb up i want to get my sanity back
tome is one of my fanfics don't read it please i lost a bet with a friend
okay watch out for green i lost a bet with a bet of what that you had to write
a story i don't know what that means all right a statuette vaguely resembling a man stands atop a
low pedestal pick it up read that guy's fan face uh so i'm telling you guys something interesting
here i'm telling you i've decided that i'm going to keep track of second i wake up the dream that
i had the night before and then we are going to put on kind of weird scary music two or three
months from now and we're going to do i'm going to read you all the dreams i've had over the last two
three months i want to keep i want to keep a dream journal and talk and tell you about all of them
like four hours then he does that because benny's fucking benny's a hilarious dude that like it
knows how to do comedy so yeah i got a new rune though what is it i don't know what it is all right
i need h okay wait anything else in this room or better yet like just commission out animators to
animate them all just give them exact details of what happens and i don't even tell the story we
just watched them it'll be like two hours and you guys can try to break down what the hell was
wrong with my brain that night oh lord starting to go a little bit crazy oh p already give me a
second how do you know that i have to go pee all right statuette codex what's this one for
this is the codex for zealoteth okay so i have to i got two statues now what do i do with them
i put the other one on it oh let me switch it up can't use that shit go piss now no i'm
just i'm just wait the door you have to pay animation wages for weeks that's fine go to
the bathroom no i don't have to go to the bathroom right now all right what do i do with these
statues is there a place i could put them here no you're shitting yourself you're shitting yourself
i am not shitting myself i am not it's not happening yours i told you i have to pee i
don't know where you guys are getting shit from you're shitting yourself you're shitting yourself
you're shitting yourself all right all right all right all right all right what do i do these
statues you promised you would shit your pants on stream like five months ago i don't i did not
do that i did not promise that why would i promise something like that that's the stupidest thing to
all right what do i do i'm stuck how can i be stuck these puzzles are not hard
or statuette use i can't put the the this one here what is this not what i'm not watching videos
right now that's what was happening which started like a little kid you guys are like
go to the bathroom now and i'm like no oh my god okay all right what do i do with these statues
seriously crudely scruffy statue if it seems perfectly heavy for its size but where do i
press them oh save and go to the bathroom save and go to the bathroom oh watch out i don't want
to go to that red one that one's already occupied by bowser ow mario party yeah i don't want to
look i want to land on the red one because then we'll be on the same team remember if
you read this it's time to change means what just got my sanity back so holy shit hey thanks man
watch out run you're on this guy's team just wasted so much health for no reason i could
just walked out there's no experience points i'm fucking leaving okay so what did that do for me
this thing went up well what does that what does that do for me for this do i does that do anything
for me didn't do anything elevator i'm gonna get transported to this that weird spirit world again
fuck just run run run that can i kill these things go blue what is like a weird like red
light green light thing damn it i want health red heals blue mana green sanity yeah
i use the health one i still get it red has the health right right right right right
oh i want to get hit by one of these guys again all right come get me now let me go to red
red's occupied by this guy all right turn red i can tele-frag this guy right oh my god he's
running a fucking breath how much okay seriously how much breath do you need step on a fucking red
red you actually can't tele-frag him i thought that was not real swinging into the ground
please kill okay full health i'm gonna save the game now what do i do about this
all right all those things are gone examine oh so i had to get rid of all those red things
go to the bathroom go to the bathroom i will go to the bathroom when i get a chance not right now
all right dead dead old blood has it got a sword in his back there's a tolwar sword
the wounds are deep and furious take the tolwar i can now wield two tolwars simultaneously
well that's pretty cool this is gonna sound weird and maybe some of you will get what i'm
trying to say here why does it feel like a 2013 to 2016 german 985 thumbnail that was weird right
get off kill him how am i already this insane dude i can smell you all right you're in trouble
whoa am i not hurting him all right i got my sanity back i'm fine all right large blade
get off me i missed an item i'll go back i don't have invincibility for at least a second after
that come on we're gonna get softlocked i'm not gonna get softlocked i'm gonna go get it
hey look what's that the recover spell cover spell requires the sand tack and
narrow calf runes do i have those runes no no no no no put my sword in here it's my favorite
toothpaste flavor just cool refreshing mint come on dude you're rito it's frozen me your way cut
his arm off dude do i have a heal wait it was just playing the beginning cut scene okay what
did he kill me no i'm okay i'm all right i'm all right wait wait wait wait wait
why can he fit down here i did i do it again get the fucking book hey
wait what's that noise what's the birds no i want to go there i want to go there i want to go there
i want the sanity yes green turn turn turn turn ah there we are back to normal this game sucks
play potty racers um somebody's true true i don't true what all right i'm gonna kill this guy
wait till he does this big charge move there it is i go for the right arm first
fuck i got greedy trying to target the arm target the arm oh my god target his fucking arm
sick parry am i doing i'm doing all right how are you doing did i get a heal um i got this
these two don't have them yet all right let's go am i doing on health what's the spell for you to
go to the bathroom that's a great question it's called when i get to the end of this chapter
and you order the pizza for me tomorrow night i i i cannot order a pizza for you that's the one
i just got all right i got recover that's recover let's put that quick spell go with uh
uh yeah new spell power level three spell list recover assign it only blue i can't can i not do
green what does it do
what i just recover to the end of the chapter i'm fine it recovers mana oh
oh that's kill there's the long sword of ramdow take it yeah i don't like these two swords they
suck see let's check it out yep a two-hander quick burger boy technique and get out of here
all right stay down stay down stay down good good good good good
dude what the fuck we can see the green stink lines coming through the screen
so well i'm sorry about that
that's so stupid almost dead rhymes with art art art all right can i leave bathroom stop i'm not
going to the bathroom until i'm ready everyone jesus how did i miss shit he turned him one of
those bird people come on come on really really are you serious really now that's what happened
i'm gonna die no get away from me please
ah kill kill kill kill what get away from me okay cut scene i win
all right when was the last time i saved the game that's not good how far away was this
ten minutes ago all right i'll fucking speed run this all right all right right right i'm
gonna go to the bathroom we're back how you doing broke his turkey dick again
again something like that but not really i forgot about that already
oh what's going on around my game what happened i lost communication with the controller oh i'm
good that was weird so where where the hell did i end up here i don't remember how far away was
this this seems like a long time ago what was the last thing i just did no it's not that far it's
all right i'll go quick yeah set that heal recover spell okay sign it there it is
save save save save save i'm gonna do this whole room again that sucks release this right here
it's so loud all right hold on i'll get it i'll get it i missed the rumor oh don't wait for
reminisce about the rumor i miss him too i get it i miss getting visibly angry every
30 to 45 minutes every single day on stream i love having my whole day ruined i love lying in bed
two o'clock in the morning and having my eyes rip open because i hear it
and i think that somebody's about to drive into my fucking house man miss that quick quick quick
one of these guys turns into one of those things i got lucky it's not this one
i really wish there was a dodge that's the next set right it's the next set
you don't realize what you had until it was gone now you're right
didn't did i get it off no okay i got the rune now just to get get away from the sanity thing
these guys with the sanity bullshit why i kill it before it kills me okay good that's it right
it can't be another one okay is my sanity too low to save it god i didn't pick the green thing
i did it on accident i didn't even mean to game sucks playing nintendogs instead
um i don't have nintendogs i'm sorry man kind of fucked up all right the blades in the slot
feels pushback is the magic of the blade does not fit the lock really why really so what now what
am i supposed to do i have to enchant it so now it's blue isn't it a green lock
i need to i need to enchant it with green all right hold on how do i do that a new spell green
oh shit um okay there it is and she discovered the enchant item spell green all right
take a green recover too that's smart isn't it i'll do that right now a new spell green
self absorb okay now quick spell enchant assign green on recover oh no
oh that's good do it again
again
that's very very handy okay save it i forget this entire game why are you not letting the
insanity effects happen resident sleeper why is this door not opening resident sleeper no
insanity effects resident sleeper yeah you know i guess i guess you're right yeah let's think about
it the one selling point of this game is the game fucks with you all the time i'm not you guys aren't
even seeing the selling point of the game i can't make a red one can i all right breathe for a
second game sucks you're too sane too much sanity going to link the corridor the ceiling has given
in collapse should you climb over the rubble yeah oh shit this is bad can i i need i gotta heal
with this little locket thing at least one more time shoot me through walls are you fucking kidding
me let's go i'm who cares just go down the i don't care these bones blast from a sculpture made from
human skin and bone all right so wait can i put something on here let's go put let's put the
necronomicon on here but you're playing too good i am not playing good i'm not playing too good
i have to save it shit shit shit should have to play good he's too talented hey he's doing
this on purpose but he's playing good on purpose it's usually the other way around pretend or riot
no that's not how this works he's doing good on purpose
of course i am i'm trying to win start pretending holy shit okay i'm doing good
start pretending start pretending finally we almost done with this wave of enemies thing
hurry up more more funnies pretend all right fine fine if that's what you want no i don't
no i don't care i have to be good i have to play good i'm gonna die in a second
it was so bad i hate these little guys then miss shit how did that not land contact on his head
and stop pretending stop pretending start pretending stop pretending guys are fucking crazy
actually bad laugh out loud that's what you guys want you want to be able to write bad oh he's bad
not today it's my turn to be good today not today all right do it good play good what's this shit
what's he doing what are they doing what are they doing okay here we go go to the bathroom no not
this again i could just google a playthrough keep pretending yeah i guess you could google the ending
of the game thank you just google the ending yeah you could you could google anything
david here it actually won't be funny if you did that as a joke no i don't want to google the
ending of the game because now i'm it's wild how this game is only one year younger than me
yeah that is insane all right should i go blue i'm gonna enchant this thing blue all right
chant item cast blue these are purple right does that matter come on dude i have to finish
every single one of them i really don't want to sometimes i think about just how old i am
you guys are gonna vote oh wow this game is only one year younger than me every day i wake up and
i just go 35 this year this feels wrong to say doesn't it i turned 35 this year 35 is one of
those ages that when you're like 17 18 19 you just you'll you just never see yourself as a 35
year old what am i gonna be like when i'm older like oh when i'm 50 when i'm 40 nobody ever
thinks about when they're like 30 or 35 you always skip i do maybe some of you do you know what's
crazy 35 was always the age that i thought was like the old wise teacher okay this i'm gonna die
again i'm stuck in the corner please move what the fuck i'm gonna die again i'm going to die
again get off come on i was just waiting for him and he didn't jump on my face of course he
does that move twice in a row why would you read this with a skull the human skull facing you
it doesn't do that there's no reason for you to do that replace that with like a bowl of pretzels
like what are you fucking stupid pretty good pretending yeah all right can i refill this
am i just is it over i'm just gonna lose forever oscar i need health but i don't know i don't know
any healing spells i don't right i don't have any red ones just can't get hit get about i don't
even care about killing him with an execute i'll just continue to be like this he'll die eventually
right you made my day better hey well thanks for stopping by hope your day goes good continues to
can i save it here you can't save in combat no one said that
making up compliments now making up like things that people say that are good
hey like that you hey nice job hey you making my day but i'm making that up
it'd be very strange if i was come on kill him
i all right i don't think i made it this far last time did i
it's this exact part right here shit oh my god you little shit how did that not hit him
the sword went through his body there's a fucking huge guy what my controls are backwards right now
get away from me no please no please don't kill me run away from him run away from him
okay wait this i know where i can even go what the fuck dude i need full health
i didn't want to get stuck in the hallway with him because i'm just guaranteed to die
oh my god how you supposed to do this just use the torch use the small swords fuck i've not been in
the same room for two hours stop gaslighting everybody give me the torch we're gonna use
torch only it's got so greedy gaslight him to believe he shit himself you convince me that i
shit my pants here right now do i freak out run to the bathroom and check okay so when i check in
there's nothing there do i still think i did it yes so how many of you guys have had the weird
panic-inducing moment where you're out somewhere and this is why i don't like to fart anywhere i
don't fart i'm not a farter i just this is a dead serious conversation i don't fart i i try to
wait and i try to do it in the bathroom or something because i always have this weird panic
where if i'm out somewhere and i'm doing something and if i fart and i shit my pants
if this is panic always in the back of my mind where like i cannot fart because i may shit my
pants uh and even if i know i don't i still think i did and i will have this i'll be going man i
really probably should check see if i shit my pants i know i didn't but what if i did
uh i think i soft-locked myself by the way i don't have enough health to do this and enchanted
you can heal sanity if you wave with the torch i don't like these i want the big one
i'm just gonna i'm gonna win i'm gonna beat it right now i'm gonna win right now
sanity ain't gonna go down back it up i'm way too close there's no reason to be this close
pretend to be cool kill him
no no no no this is the guy that's the guy that's the guy i guess i gotta kill him kill kill
swing swing got him okay big guy coming ah where's the big guy oh fuck big guy coming
big guy coming big guy coming big guy coming get full sanity big guy right in the way
big guy on the way all right just gonna save the game writer okay here we go
no i can go dude it's so stupid what i can't even swing at him why would you why would they make you
fight one of these huge fucking hulk monsters in a room that's as big as a bathroom in an airplane
like what why are we doing this here i'm trying to cut his arm and just like
eat and i got it once and oh my god stop no i've ruined it already i need help i'm soft
locked i can't even be the game out the game's over i have a tiny little bit of help i can't
even do it why can i execute the people on the ground oh i'm so dead again oh i'm about to
fucking rip i was gonna say i'm about to rip the disc out but that's not even possible anymore
do i just do it even though it's not anything i'm not gonna do anything
i'm so dead one of these guys gonna turn into the bird and then the birds gonna slash me and
my sanity is gonna go to zero uh what there he is there's the fucking goddamn bird sanity zero
there's no other safe point i can't there's no other safe point of the whole game
use the torch it kills in one hit you are gaslighting yourself by using the big knife
don't tell me that don't tell me that if it's real then i get very upset
just to only use the torch in the sanity spill okay that's what i'm doing use the chalk rooms
what do the chalk rooms do throwing weapon uh throwing weapon at the big guy how did i use one
why then 19 okay i'm ready don't even look at them why am i letting them look at me
then this had to be the room that everybody said start pretending look what happens you
guys just get what you want you know that's not what i'm doing so you know in all your minds
i did start pretending to make sure that i that i could make well what a funny stream and he's
stuck in the room he's stuck in the airplane bathroom why did i have to line up that way
that's pretending stream of 2020 all right here when the birds coming big knife aim up
yeah i was trying that look at the sanity it's too fast stop being so i hate that i'm gonna
fucking scream i'm about to fucking yell as loud as i can swap to other weapon for the bird
this is the one i can feel it just use emulator saves wait what do you mean hold on
wait don't tell me i can do that because then i'll ruin the rest of the whole stream
i'm gonna abuse the hell out of that i'm gonna just gonna be completely abused
that's i'm not there yet all right i know it exists good to know i'm not there yet
we'll see maybe it's very maybe not yet let me try to do it on my own
all right come on try to fight the bone thief in the hallway
it's guys gonna get one or two clean hits on them and i'm just gonna throw the
it's not a children's game this is rated m for mature
this is for mature adults only it is rated m m for mayonnaise okay let's go
gotta hit them one two three grab the grab the just the two-handed sword and hit him once
in fact i'm gonna do it up here okay okay do it spells good good not bad good start good
start good start good start good start okay now put on the how do we use these where is he
all right my controls are backwards again
he makes the analog backwards my analog is upside down no this is unbearable
fuck this is not even like i don't remember this being like this no i can't use safe state
i'll never do it i gotta do it on my own why do i have to fight the huge guy by the way aiming
those little frisbees is it doesn't make any sense once you get restore life you'll never have to do
this again yeah i'd love to get it now we're going back to original strategy chant the tiny
swords blue how do i make a save state what's the what's the button don't say alt f4 if you
say alt f4 you're getting timed out for 10 minutes what is it shift what hello germy your biggest i'm
your biggest fan all right wait what are you showing me i don't need to put it in m girl link
load state save state capture go to save slot one shift f1 okay here we go ready let's see if it
works got it okay we're good we're good we're good we're good we're good thank you shift f1
whenever i'm feeling scared cheating i don't care i gave up on that a long time ago i'm only
going to use it seldomly i promise now it's over so everything's ruined because now i'm going to do
that forever i'm not going to use it all the time i'm only going to get out of this fucking room i
promise no i'm gonna abuse it get away from me stop running so fast good okay here we go
your experience is ruined no it's not this is only for this room i promise
good okay yay yay blue hog i guess it's it is not a pug i'm embarrassed but i don't care i
wouldn't i wouldn't be able to do that no way all right so did i get anything from this
besides the blue thing lighting up shit shaped like a delicate dome a pale blue
statuette floats should i claim this yeah she's dead who did this to you
what are you teaching america's youth cheating i can't believe i let my
children watch your stream ready them for maturity that's what you press when you first come to the
spring
so much for thinking
no i we're getting over that i'm not talking about like
the artifact which i'm not talking about that ever again and it is not for us to possess
if we are to be together again you must make a sacrifice only when that is complete will we be
together sacrifice why should i do anything for you you lied to me betrayed me you really don't
look so good anymore you must forget the past despite who you are now you will also become
something more just as i have but the sacrifice must be made we must remain here and guard the
artifact things will come to play and you must be strong to keep it from them without your sacrifice
the world will fall into darkness the things i do for love she kisses me to death it's going
off his nostrils he's like he's what was that what was that like 1995 screensaver okay so now
what did that what did i what did he do i have the key to the dresser which i haven't done anything
about but what was the last what did i get i got like a did i get a new spell sword door oh yeah
that's right the sword door that's not the sword door dave i am oh that's pretend saving you're
talking about real hard saving yep so i can enchant this green and we'll do the green door
okay uh somebody just a phone call why is this why it's so odd all right that's actually pretty
creepy that's creepy i will say it's creepy all right we got we got a quick spell all right
enchant item this one five it's just a pantry sealed it away for centuries i didn't want anyone
to touch my marshmallow fluff you can only get that shit in the northeast can't get it anywhere
else which is bullshit by the way spice jar well that's a huge rat all right what's in the
spice jar firmly sealed glass spice jar the aroma of arabian spices in in there open it up the
future is yours the light in the age of always in those spices has been extinguished the pillar
of flesh has been constructed the master of chaos the keeper of the ancients is long the master of
comedy the planets will be in alignment soon all is prepared for your arrival i will begin the
final incantation will bring you into our world in days the next millennium will truly usher in a
new age your guardians now prepare the gate okay so i got it what's this one this is chapter five
what year is this i will not argue that i was shocked by the sudden mention of one oh this is
1760 the distinguished dr maximilian roivas it chilled me to my bones it all just takes
place in the same house come from how had my ancestor stumbled upon it i feverishly began
to read more eager to learn his story seems that maximilian had inherited his father's mansion
just as i had alone since the death of his wife and since his children had their own adult lives
he explored the house to discover his family roots i saw that that's okay it has been two weeks
since the death of my father and it has finally come to me to look over the mansion
now i am truly alone forced to start a new life here in road island i intend to make the mansion
mine and live in it there's my four those powdered wigs are so cool the family tradition i wish it
was still cool to wear those the mansion has its secrets i'm sure why do these go out of style my
time here they're ugly but at what point in history did people just take these off and go
nah nah fuck that i don't want to wear that looks terrible what was the first generation that's like
nah i don't want to put on that looks horrible something had to have happened this had to have
been something weird okay the flintlock pistol oh you get a gun i have a gun now i got a gun
walking around my own house with my gun okay that's is this a that's not a monster is it
no this is okay this is a it's a servant okay jesus i don't look so angry was something in the room
why did i do that i didn't you ever seen the adam salem movie where he rewinds time you can do
whatever you want you can do anything because it's fine he's right there he's alive interior
outhouse oh i get more ammo two more what about this candle thing the door of the servants quarters
are securely locked and if i feel uneasy an ominous presence lurks behind that door
all right okay stained glass window uh resplendent with bright colors and exquisite
workmanship there's something odd about it perhaps the curious detail curious calling everything a
stick bug more ammo okay that's stick bug the letter what does the letter say a letter written
with some precision in the long hand dear friend the antiquity of which you ask is indeed the
tomb of eternal darkness or a copy of it at least its secrets are still hidden from me for i have
been unable to read it as have most scholars who have tried it will remain within the sanctity
of the mansion for the wrong hands it would be a powerful weapon you know it's roibos medical
journal used to take notes on medical and pathological analysis okay i got 15 bullets
i closed on today no the answer to that question is always no i swear to god i keep thinking they're
bad guys toilet wait here's grim reflection returns max's question and gaze more ammo all right i got
a lot of ammo shoot window you're exhausting shoot window would relax stop i haven't even
gone in all the rooms yet i'm just looking around i've pointed the gun at every single person here
put jingle keys into the mic or riot is that a baseball bat pump handle cool uh while going
about her duties the servant casually remarks about a strange quality hanging in the air
something weird going on jingle keys jingle look how about this i have two glass bottles how about
i just go like this that better yes people happy oh you what are you doing here are you what's this
there's something written beneath the image when darkness spreads its wings before my master
zelotath's greatest foe the path to truth will be opened uh the biggest foe is blue blue blue hates
uh green hates blue blue hates red right i was shocked it's red wait i thought it was blue
enter secret passage not yet um sword curled scroll of age parchment reveal invisible spell
and a cutlass i'll take it gerber just fart no but i did used to do that though i know we've
gone i we've talked about this i know we have but just to give you a little bit people that might
not know there was a time during my youtube career he said career he said office where i
was putting just fart noises in videos and i did it like three or four times over a course of a
couple of weeks and after like the third or fourth time nobody even noticed they were there and i
just was like this is not funny anymore like nobody cares nobody thought that was funny nobody
even mentioned it it was just so i guess so normal that nobody cared to even say what was that at
like four minutes in like 25 seconds this went on for at least a week or two and even said like
years later i did it still and nobody ever said anything which i do i do i have no idea what
videos they were i have absolutely no clue he never stopped farting i there was one specifically
where i was talking to somebody i think i was talking to star and i was like blah blah blah
blah i said a sentence and there was a fart noise yes you found it wait hold on did you actually
find it found did you found one just being like dickheads shooting everybody and shooting each
other can i even i'm gonna spray the hell out of these guys yeah shooting everybody and shooting
each other but i did it i did it at least a few times trying to make an honest living putting out
fires saving cats and these two were just being like dickheads shooting everybody and shooting
each other can i even i'm gonna spray the hell out of these guys yeah that's not you know the
role players are fighting back right so i uh and i never talked about it i don't think either
this was never brought up ever again and then i did it a couple more times and it wasn't funny
it wasn't even making me laugh and i still put it in the videos there's another one how would you
even know where these were there's no way you found them all already today we're going to do
a dish that i remember from my mother what is this this has nothing to do with me at all
that's jacob panning world's greatest intellectual on earth uh thanks though i mean like i would love
to watch it found another one if you want to check it out go check it out
take everybody see you all soon take care of everybody and do the dance you get for free for
downloading the game well we won that's loadout guys it's on steam it's free to play if you want
to check it out go check it out take care everybody see you all soon take care everybody and good
okay wait wait wait this is how did you find them all already how do you have these bookmarked
do you remember specifically when you were melee we're in the fucking call and i told you i was
going to a halloween party what'd you tell me you guys thought i was lying you thought i was lying
everybody thought i was making it up everybody thought i was making it up
there's not another one here there's definitely not a fourth one though right i farted in this one
there's one in this tf2 halloween video from 2013
oh why would i put this okay you know what this loadout video from february 9th 2014
in the comment section does anybody say anything about it i don't say anything
people just stopped giving some people stopped caring do you see how i i i had to stop doing
this because it wasn't funny and this is the this is a year apart by the way okay this is tf2 i bet
you 100 bucks november 3rd 2013 february 9th 2014 was the loadout video this is a full fucking year
apart hey we're in the fucking call and i told you i was going to a halloween party what'd you tell me
all right is a stenographer jesus christ yeah i probably at least and what's the gta video
october 16th 2013 hold on hold on hold on i want to see if this one's real i know i did it at least
five or six times this is a family guy peter farting compilation all right i'm gonna move on
another gta video no i'm getting linked like just random like peter griffin fart sound videos
all right you get the idea though okay examine there's to be a wax rubbing of some kind
i have dual pistols went lock pistol oh dual pistols what no way are we gonna go kill that
guy out there okay well i didn't i didn't want to shoot him reload reload the gun we found another
one the video we're looking for was the august 2015 gta video hold on wait i don't know how to
fuck you guys find this shit it's another one in cry and cry of fear hold on wait wait wait wait
cry of fear no this is the simpson song no you guys are not even lit this is baby crying
this is a real fart from you what watch it again real quick also by the way i'm having
an insane epiphany right now and this is tearing down the entire fabric of my fucking mind
i was doing that on streams too recently i had a fart machine and i would play it sometimes
like over the like over the last six to 12 months and i never said anything about it
i did it on these streams too yeah i have i have been doing that no you haven't yes i have yes i
have i've been i've been doing it a lot somebody have a clip of me doing it on stream i'm not
gaslighting you guys this is real this is really happening i know for a fact that one of them
happened at least on the stream that me and joel did at least two or three times we did um that
bomb defusal game i did it like three times on that stream and didn't say talk about it at all
and then did it like another like i swear to god i did it like two or three weeks later and then a
month later it's real it's real stop linking me the fucking family guy thing you're fart lighting
us so i'm not somebody will get it i swear to god somebody will actually get the real one
holy shit was it the second bomb defusal i did it like 10 times 134 15 all right i'm gonna stop
because no one is actually linking me anything you guys are just all linking your favorite
fart videos everybody's got one i have not laughed at every single fart absolutely not i got
no way i mean you you might queen i have not laughed at every single one you bring me documented
proof i did not i i know i did not bullshit i don't believe it what where will list the thing
here's where this doesn't do anything laughed at every fart blue wire laughed at every
there's there's no red wires there's one red i fucking said that okay there's only there's only
one red there's one red wire okay all right is the last wire yellow no it's blue okay is it one blue
wire there's germa i swear i'm gonna fucking come over to boston i'm gonna fucking all right is it
what i don't even live there anymore man well i'm fucking all right where's the fart is it one yes
or no is it is it one blue wire there's i there's no farther you guys are fucking this all up
fine that's one all right i have to move on from this shit i can't sit here all day
that was a real one no it wasn't real oh here's another one red blue we have we have we have
we have we have we have red we're looking at red blue
i did it so many times i swear to god people got pissed one time people got pissed one time
i forget what the exact context was but i did it and people got fucking mad they were like stop
dude that's not funny did he skyline stream there's at least a couple somebody got pissed
and it was like it wasn't funny at all he's gas no i have to have a distinct memory i just don't
know what the fucking what game it was it doesn't know the omega symbol no no no no no no i'm done
i'm done i'm done i'm done skylines clip you'll stop i not click it mods when an autopsy has been
performed max can do the new entry by turning to the journal section of the tool i think autopsy at
the bottom of the page okay autopsy the creature wears the skin of people to protect itself
gross but yeah i i it was a couple times that i did it on stream and people did not notice
and i was sitting there going nobody knows i did that i nobody said anything oh god he's here
wait he's kicking this guy's ass isn't he's not a bad guy but they were all possessed some are
possessed oh shit i don't know if i hit them move out of the way you do the same thing in god hand
hold on i haven't saved stated in a long time i'm gonna die i can't shoot his arms off okay just
kill me when was the last safe state i miss god hand it's far back i don't even know how far
back it is we're good i just had to load that safe real quick okay take out the cutlass stop
please all right there we can see the autopsy cool cool cool let's just get a little bit of a
save state somebody's gonna find them because i said it and now people are gonna look and
you'll find them and we can be embarrassed for me when we hear them eventually i want to load the
gun i'll open the door black and white two vod had one i'm not gonna click him unless they've
verified modeling off cut his arm off he's dead all right what a pain in the ass he's not dead
just shoot him in the head that's not his head thank you god mods we got one mods we got one
all right do you verify me please mods okay let's see this is this is in the black and white stream
where is it in this game why is this so low game is too well i'll turn the game down
okay let's listen to this wood where is it okay that's what that does i really wish my um
dog could have seen that it's not even there do it again keep watching
right is that me or is that in the game
this one's at 412 art with extra reverb i don't want to play this because i feel like it's gonna
hurt everybody's speakers i'm done i'm done i'm done invisible spell uh uloth nerecath okay cool
let's go ahead and go back to what we're doing here all right so let's put that on the little
bar here a spell list it reveal invisible we do blue or green doing reveal invisible down i guess
be
play the reverb thing i just did i played the fart reverb one
all right what do i have for uh items i got kind of distracted there okay i've got this
letter i got the tomb of eternal darkness i gotta put the tomb of eternal darkness somewhere
yeah wow i should i would not be very good if very bad not be very good all right
i'm gonna have some bad news for you remember when you said that auto had a savory dog smell
as he slept that's actually little dog farts you were sniffing his sleepy dog farts and you
said it was savory and that's not even real that's not that's not accurate that's fake
that's not actually what was going on but sure okay nothing nothing reload the guns why do you
huff your dog while he's sleeping what the fuck this is look don't listen to everybody in here
are you listening to these people he's bleeding get get him get him
if you don't know what to sit with what the sleepy dog smell is i'm sorry you just don't
you don't have like the part of your dna that allows you to smell it all right ones in the chat
do you know what the sleepy dog smell is ones or not it's just like having an eternal monologue
thank you i'm thank you so much all of you it's not dog farts it's like a scientific thing that
happens with the dog when it sleeps and if it's something with their paws in there i don't know
oh what's this an envelope let's get it i was supposed to scare me but i was looking at you
guys talking to me about how my dog doesn't smell that was supposed to scare me um melted
wax an odd rune is pressed into the wax letter addressed to one of max's father's aids and i
got the basement key that's totally tubular hey uh dear friend i expected the beasts are drawing
closer to our discovery they want the book by themselves it seems and do not want us to have
it in our possession i have taken steps to ensure that their ilk will not touch the key in this
envelope if you fall prey to their claws the envelope containing the basement key has been
sealed with a corrosive magic one not aligned to us tries to handle it it will be released
inflicting pain suffering and a grievous blow to this sanity okay it's blue so just be blue
load those guns up load those guns up so people are asking tomorrow what time
i want to just make it clear again dlc movie night is tomorrow starting somewhere around
between 11 and 12 pacific i'm around like 11 to 12 p.m 11 like 11 a.m to 12 p.m i'm assuming
we're gonna be sitting there for a good solid five to six hours i'm just coming down the hall
down to the basement why are we why are we in like sepia tone where do you go
why should i do the invisibility spell he's abusing cheats no i'm using cheats not abusing
how many times am i gonna shoot him in the head it's not the same thing three heads okay should
i keep shooting in the middle head for a quick part viewers are plummeting no that doesn't
but i don't care good freeze frame look at that zoom in on that that's a great picture
oh i stuck like this okay no wait i finally got it thank god okay new spell list
heel we want recover so it's noracath and santac thank god
all right it's time to drop the ban hammer should i just put heels around the whole thing huh
cover assign mana to go up here
oh
this isn't doing anything
wait am i back to my back to normal he's an invisible horror stalking him have you no eyes
can you not see it oh wait hold on look at what's fine the invisible guy it says this invisible guy
stalking him guess not mind i'm fighting green guys oh there's nobody here what's this design
is oddly reminiscent of a circle of power mentioned to the tomb of eternal darkness
probably first to some kind of spell why am i so slow i need to unlock the basement this is not
the basement jump king waiting room you can't be waiting for a very very long time where's the
basement it's all waiting room is it is it all the way in the back hold on when is germa gonna
go insane this is clickbait look i don't i don't know i played this game 20 years ago i don't
remember why did i even shoot him classic tuber yeah well i am a classic tuber yeah that's right
i was making youtube videos back in like 2012 2011 i think that makes me a classic youtuber
isn't it are you punching me for real leave me the fuck alone you're really odd to walk into
though you're one of the other servants for a second i thought i was not doing this right
you might know me from the servers wait that person was normal that wasn't a why were they
attacking me did she or did she not walk up and punch me three times let me know she walked up
and threw like three haymakers at me i go i thought the game was actually broken you got me
i'm i don't know where to go i'm trying to find the basement what was that that was the somebody
in the house dropped something in the shower sound for some reason it always sounds like they
fell and just smashed into everything and like broke three of their bones am i blind
letter five letter four letter two your friend whatever all right i need to go to the basement
i don't know what to do well you don't go up to go to the basement you would do invisible
what is an invisible door why do i hear a loud smashing oh is somebody in this room
hey who's in here is he upstairs there's nothing even in there's nobody here okay that was weird
okay so i need to do um invisibility use the red and reveal invisible spell oh okay oh i get it
because it's it's the red hates green green hates blue blue hates green and purple hates them
all of us or something right rock paper scissors yeah he's ready the guns
oh they're gonna turn into birds weird bird things not fight on the stairs can can you please just
back up a little so i can what am i doing i'll get stick buck you fucking loser
now what's down here you spell rewind time the image field a tattered scroll yeah yeah the
sanitation exerts a force of mystical power within the confines of its ruins nothing may
enter till it is dispelled oh i need the ruins mo what's this pump some water a rusted pump
stands by the well its handle appears to be missing oh i have one of those i already have
rewind time that's true yep you're right let let me actually get a youtube thumbnail freeze frame
that's what it would have been and my thumbnail sucked they were always so bad it was always just
hey to have a guy standing up that's a character in the game and just use the rule of thirds and
people will think it looks good a guy pointing a gun a guy pointing his fist a guy punching it
it was every single thumbnail i just couldn't be bothered you know i just like just wanted to
upload the fucking video like i was done just upload it just shoot myself in the head do i
have bullets wait why am i in a prison wait hold on i was okay i was in jail oh all right well
for that give me that you know the main gimmick of this game i just punched you in the face i'm
sorry i'm so sorry i really am that like just that was probably loud all right uh damage field
spell so nobody can walk through it should i turn it on stop touching the fucking mic dude seriously
i have this ruin now right purple desolate ruin of a fantastic a p e g image built into a huge
naturally formed cave oh you don't have to render it that's no that helps you know that would get
me if this wasn't too you know 2020 this only works if you are alive in 1998 turn it back up i
don't know how i can't they turned down the cutscene all right hold on wait wait wait
i'm sorry it doesn't matter wait so i have to do my spell
does that do a power level protect protect protect protect did i do okay green should i do green
let me do green maybe okay green red
work oh got him he's invisible though he's i gotta turn this visibility off ah any more
magical energy tear parka parka tear parka yep i had it right fuck him shoot him
i guess i could try to shoot him but i don't think it hurt him didn't do anything that you
lied enchanted with red oh nice okay yeah you're right you're right yeah yeah yeah yeah all right
now i have red enchanted guns so tough anymore are you come on come back oh shit reddit enchanted
guns why does everything have to be read it with you guys i didn't want to shoot that guy
why is he so defensive about reddit i'm not but what am i going to eat today
wait took you three months to figure this out it's a very long time
damn the powdered wig really does make you look really different he just looks like
every dude i've ever seen at walmart before he was like in a pirate outfit and he had the hair
if i'm like the the audio director here it's like that that was a perfect take what a perfect take
that i would i wouldn't even change anything what i do what i pressed a button oh wait oh
fake dlc okay that was cool i can go into that into the basement now right
they are not already in the basement i can go to the hidden door skipping lore
remember you should make i'm not going to be coming out for a long time okay if you want to
go to the bathroom use the one downstairs just leave me the fuck alone this is where the hidden
door was before yes there's a hidden door i have like new spells i have a reveal invisible
damage field where have i not been able to go there's wait the glass can i break the glass
what the hell is this glowing medieval maiden luminous even with the faint light of the setting
sun there's something in the and there's something in there what that wasn't it
germa germa germa germa germa germa germa germa germa germa germa germa germa germa germa germa
what is it what is it kids dark to scene perhaps the circuit's been broken
telephone i have a dresser key dresser key i mean where's the dresser the key goes in
isn't that a con what do they mean by dresser i need a funny voice so i can sleep real mcchicken
wink what i want something i want something delicious i want something that's 10 out of 10
but i can't eat i'm trying to stay away from uh red oh i'm gonna eat wait dresser right here we go
okay all right hey hey hey hey hey look searches hey hey hey take it out take it out i got it
invisibility spell reveal invisible green hash house stuffed blue cheeseburger but replace buns
with lettuce wraps there we go there's a new page oh it's a gun sorry is a chrome finished
revolver in a tattered page from the tomb of eternal darkness make it a journey into darkness
did you seriously forget that you shat yourself earlier good call back to four and a half hours
ago
how long is the game i don't know i don't think it's that long your future depends on me majesty
without me to open the gate
and minutes longer than that i got my new book gone on this guy looks tiny the ancients influence
13 hours according to how long to beat from all walks of life to all parts of the world
their tendrils crept and wrought 1983 their prisons decayed constantly as their guardians work
continued i discovered mention of a breakthrough in satellite radar imaging that revealed the
presence of a hitherto unknown temple mound in the anchor tom region of cambodia an archaeologist
of some repute dr edwin lindsey took it upon himself to investigate the area 1983
unfortunately the local government at the time thought differently requiring that lindsey find
other means into the country and to finance the expedition he found these in paul augustine a
collector of rare items who professed an interest in the discovery and agreed to help after a
dysentery riddled two-week venture lindsey and augustine located the remains of an ancient city
temple this is like indiana jones back to the 12th century there's a bunch of traps in this one
i mean that's just the guy from indiana jones on the right yes this is it it has to be
oh i'm thinking of i'm thinking of the judge from uh the who frame roger rabbit
i have searched for it without success oh that's it he's in that yeah no that's true
it's mr x mr mr x before the roids i get him god
haha you are a scholar dr lindsey not a warrior that regard i have several centuries more experience
than you don't be a fool die quietly you cannot oh he's got oh he's it's it's augustine guardians
of zelda kill him okay resin evil
why would you aim there wait till he opens up okay wait till i shoot him in the stomach
wait what's going on don't eat your stomach again please whoa where's this guardian sucks
attack open open open dead okay finally jesus all right somebody just said this is just like
your colonoscopy i'm reaching to try to find out what that means it's just like your colonoscopy
a worn uh bronze dust get out of here wait i reveal invisible i have i have a broom
oh i had all this other stuff i have a shotgun okay cool i don't have any spells oh i need to
find the book first okay where do i go thick layer of dust obscures the there's the bronze
bracelet pick it up hmm the lot that goes on in the chat the germa doesn't address
uh it could be hard to address everything going on it's a hundred dollars we just gave a hundred
bucks shangyi just gave ten thousand bits a hundred fucking bucks thank you for the
hundred dollars internal fart internal fartness germa's rectum uh eternal fartness right well
thank you for the hundred bucks dude seriously miss karim we all get consumed by the old gods
hey they make a statue out of all of us there's another one here look derivus three more pedestals
stop stepping on those faces they're in pain yeah all right let's do an invisibility check
what would it be green or i don't know red it sounded like something opened use the sword
what is it a kukri is there an explanation for why the characters know the spells well it's my
understanding that these guys pick up the book and then they kind of just know everything because
the book rocks their brain and it i guess i'm apparently walking through this without getting
hurt okay it absorbs into your body and your brain and stuff and it gets uh give me that
shit you're doing a real bad job stealing uh red i need red damage right put on the
bass pro fishing it didn't work i love fishing games so i i can't move this guy
now all right just stop getting hurt and go i'm a big fan of fishing games
remember the pc fishing game it's got pre-fired i definitely want mana i'm so excited for tomorrow
i am mentally preparing myself for tomorrow it's been so long
i went into the green screen like three and a half months ago i cannot wait and i've been a good boy
too i haven't watched anything i did initially i did i could help myself i watched a few things
initially but i've been very very good what time tomorrow somewhere around 11 o'clock in the morning
specific okay let's do this again i have another necklace okay let's go where is it where is it
there it is you can't go back to fishing clinic as fortnight jimmy has not forgiven you unfortunate
what about the bird watching stream yeah there's there are so many different things to do i just
need to do them another bracelet is it a bad thing or a good thing just shoot at me hey what
the fuck are you doing to give it back wait don't i have a shitty one
all right i'll give it back fine i can't i can't somebody help me please
well i gotta replace that with something is there a way to go
you're my auto i just wait that way can you do the auto laugh does what does autos laugh the auto laugh
what stop all right just put the knock him down i want that rune do the laugh what i don't he
doesn't have a laugh the auto laugh i don't think what that means autos laugh oh okay when he goes
like whatever right i can't just do that right now i can't i can't do that right now i'm just
like chilling playing a game i can't just like start doing the auto laugh wait what's that funny
man funny man funny man wait is that it's hiding there can i burn it burn it i said this chapter
has a miserable ruin that you can end up not having for the rest of the game by the way
oh god that's not good i want to use the brush man is that the one you got that the
rune you're talking about dispel magic oh i can just spell magic on that guy now
i gotta stand there this guy spell red shock and equip and reload it like what i can't just
reload the gun i'm just preparing the guy's watching me prepare all this okay he's loading
up the gun he's opening his spell book should i do anything about this or just stand i don't have
the runes really use it whatever my head i lost a arm now i'm just the tofu from resident evil
hold on give me one second i have to pee bad it's all good all right what do i need i need i need
to get that necklace i need to have to dispel magic on that guy wait okay yeah my character
freaked out all right dispel magic i don't have the fucking ruin right we save this for real so
i don't ruin everything when i play this again great i tried to do that i'm not trying minus one
i didn't say anything that wasn't funny even going back to fucking 1983 minus yeah yeah yeah
cringe yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
is that the ruin that i needed some where's the spell do spell a list spell magic
netflix and red gormor i don't have that i have red gormor where's netflix netflix is this netflix
you know what i would love for a video game it'd be so much fun if there was a game just
about trying to avoid traps in a room like just make a game with this same character in the same
environment but all the rooms are trapped and it's very clever you have to get no not like saw
this ruin what do you need to put on here shit play minesweeper i don't want to play minesweeper
vase wait what's this blue thing invisible blue invisible green invisible green right
eliminate all the spider webs fuck did i miss the spider web back there
i'm just looking at the ground i'm looking for webs oh no webs here right oh shit go back go back
go back give me that bracelet just get hit by everything doesn't matter i can just heal instantly
i can heal i'm gonna be fine okay let's go in here where the hell is it put the metal one on
and then put that one on the it's gonna be a pain in the ass isn't it okay here we go all right
give me it silver put the metal one on here okay good just a web i don't see a web
those are bones oh that's a fucking web on the ground okay that looked i thought that was bones
i don't know why no go back here there it is okay spell magic and i can put the silver
bracelet on that lady's neck in the hallway down here and i can dispel magic on that guy
so let's uh get a good save here what do you mean you can't use that now what
i need four bracelets we wrote in all caps illegal emulator illegal that's illegal
okay let's do dispel magic red give me that silver necklace pick it up shotgun this guy's so dead
good yeah
garage roll no sorry this is before every video game had that cool now i have the necklace go back
here put the necklace on and maybe that'll open do not die here i'll go pop broad necklace gonna
work thank god i don't have to get three more of these damn things illegal boot rune give me
be clear the second cobweb that was on the first floor um i i don't know is that what this is
minus one did i get it he's fine with cobwebs okay good shotgun back on so remind me again
depending on what you pick depending what character or what color you pick that's the
enemies that are in the game right yes wait really that's pretty cool yeah it is kind of cool the
green is the most fun is it and just what order you get the color ruins i think oh okay
green affects sanity more
whatever i made it
so swing swing swing swing swing why do i need to swing this is gold it's probably
gonna say give that back right carrying something valuable i can't pick it up actually a car of
granite a ceremonial temple guard appears to be keeping watch on the seated goddess in the
corner of the room so how do i turn it like this it's not scary at all i got it i think it's on a
timer you know i good i have another silver bracelet where's this one going what the hell
it appears to be a hole in the wall but it is large enough for a small dog to pass through
your shrinking spell i'm being poisoned i'm fucking around there
turkey dick spell hey dispel uh blue just back away from this damn thing i need to dispel magic
dispel magic red right what's the point of these enemies like i can't even get out of my game
i can't even finish him because he's inside of this stupid thing he's inside of the wall
all right dispel magic red right um i did not tell him to shoot the shotgun and he
de-shot that was on his own marine is uh green is what i meant to do oh god i've got to dispel
all these i don't even know where the hell they are oh basin font situated beneath the statue
beside that an orb shaped button sits on a panel press the button yeah water smells like acid i
have to put something in there to pick up uh i don't want to do it again what can i do with that
do i have a cup i don't i don't i can't hold the acid in it i'm not gonna put my hand in the basin
wait wrong way wins monkey ball very very very soon wait is this the wrong way
okay oh wait is it i'm so identical this one it's this one right yeah super monkey
ball is gonna i'm gonna probably 100% that game shit i stepped in the goddamn gas oh
no no no no no no no i need uh shit run come on i'm not gonna get by it smash wait i just
get off what the fuck is that what oh shit no when was it oh my goodness
i gotta wait for the mana don't cheat the last save was like an hour and a half ago so i have to
save scoundrel yeah i finally heal
okay wait wait wait wait who i don't care i don't Jesus Christ the stupid fucking plate
all right here we are no no no no no no no no no no all right i need to turn i need to use equip
um even the shotgun okay what i cannot why can i do it you're gonna attack jupiter
sorry to hear that all down already this guy is here there's a ghost under the bed in your house
quick hit it with a knife okay dispel what color is it it's blue right it's not fucking green oh
my god it's do it there's one more red where that is i have no idea this panel recess panel uh
what did that do just run shotgun shells this feels like a trap why is this i feel like this
is broken it was this trap or what i feel like there's gonna be a hammer at the end of this it's
gonna hit me right in the fucking head that's so sad kill him all right watch out this guy seems to
be very vocal about how scary it is the other ones weren't like this
oh shit that's not a good place to save okay uh shotgun i shoot really god damn it
dispel with blue stop cheating it's a game from 2002 you have to okay so that's open
run run run run pop web oh yes finally i have okay oh that is the wrong that's the wrong one
you get what you fucking deserve yeah kind of all right we'll just leave i can just shoot him
actually just shoot him just actually shoot in the head good there it is it's like sliced meat
don't do that shit again i have the necklace i have the bracelet i can open up the dumb door
there's a door to open what do you want ever since ever since my parents died ever since they were
killed wood pyramids plummeting i actually have to eat i'm fucking hungry
i'm gonna have to stand up here in a little bit too we'll see what i get let me put these
items down here and see what happens wait that was that was a hallucination that didn't happen
is this germa pluto a new emote it's already an emote you already have it i don't want to go
stay down here right i'm confused wasn't there another thing to put the necklace on
so yeah like wasn't it like right here it's up and around maybe
dissolve the thing in the acid yeah i could do that too right i don't know what this thing does
some sliced turkey and shove it okay thank you i'm glad you said face i was a little
concerned there for a minute all right here we go shit i can't put it on okay i have to dissolve
this thing in acid all right the acid things back here okay here we go press the button
dissolve it have you played this game for five hours um i don't know just kind of what i decided
i was gonna do today i'm just chilling man this game is set in ohio i don't think this game is
set in ohio why would you even say that all right where are we now that's just like kind of made me
mad enough to turn the stream off i'm gonna be honest like i don't want to walk down the stairs
again i prove it oh i will i will real soon don't you worry about it it's a big guy down there
that's a new monster what the hell is that all right we need to do uh green right
you can't green the red guy all right here we go you can't green shotgun blue beats red
okay now reload it and blow his head off i've had about enough fucking you
oh he's dead oh okay no more tricks right i know i'm just trying to go all right i know what i'm
not supposed to be doing that oh shit no no save the gun he's getting angry i think he's getting
hungry i'm honest pizza no no no no no no pizza no no no it's got to be healthy it's got to have
at least 10 turkey 10 tuna 10 mayonnaise uh uh i thought that was him saying that for one second
get squished get sandwiched please yes i'm smarter than you oh shit oh no enchant with green quick
blue ike why it's because it's christmas colors that's why it's it's got me messed up the whole
time it's red and green red and green christmas christmas santa santa santa i'm gonna fucking
eat this controller i turned around can we please please fall down why do you have to finish every
single fucking enemy what are you looking at okay yeah it's a nice hieroglyphics on the wall all
right it's time to eat i i'm gonna get out of here you can call me a cheater all you want it's all
right i'm gonna save the game really get a lungo that was three hours and okay that was a full
almost hour and 20 minutes past yeah it's probably time for me to go anyways i really
want to try to stay under this like five to six hour mark the bugs all over the screen if i could
just run if i could hit by every single trap i'm gonna die please it's ruining there i'm not dead
i'm alive who's dead i'm doing just fine somebody said why save when you are never going to play
this again you don't know that you don't know if that's true or not you don't know that omega
yes we do no you don't know that you don't know it's it's no no you don't get away from me
no you don't have you have no idea beautiful joe i played beautiful yeah but i've only played it
for like an hour no i'm not i'm gonna just hold on i'm not done yet i don't know what i just did
if i don't get by one thing i get a thousand dollars i'm trying to make it so nobody has
to give me a thousand dollars like please okay good cutscene cutscene i'm a trapper spell scroll
what summon trapper i do it right now summon a green trapper
there we go there's like a little shit wait after trappers been summoned press a to trap an enemy
it's targeted wait what i think are release control the trapper trappers cannot open doors
oh i'm the little guy are they all they're all exploding at the same time they're all gonna
see you guys tomorrow tomorrow's green screen dlc movie night we've been waiting a long time for
this one 11 a.m to 12 it's probably gonna go for at least five or six hours it's it's at least three
or 400 videos it's gonna have to probably be over the course of two or three different days
i cannot wait i'm so excited for it it's gonna be tons of fun the last two times we've done this
tears have been streaming down my face so i cannot imagine it'll be any different
see you tomorrow let's roll the credits thanks we had some community subs that i missed we had
five from forlitty and 10 now i got professor richard cheese i missed forlitty deal thank you
thanks a lot guys we'll see you soon tomorrow more specifically let's put the uh
let's get those credits rolling what do you say dudes please tell me i didn't break it
did i break it i didn't break it yes yes thanks for the subs guys what am i going to do go to
the dentist on stream what you should have said is when am i going to be a dentist on stream
and work on a pretend patient pretend we know you're an irl dentist you're promising too many
streams i actually was talking to this about uh exactly what you're describing so the guy that
does a lot of the producing work and who is essentially coming on as somebody they can help
to do a bunch of the projects with me we talk a couple times a week and what unfortunately what
was happened is with the coronavirus all these things that keep coming up and all these ideas
they're all being worked on they just can't happen right now and over the in the next probably few
months next three or four months there's going to be a lot of streams that are just going to be done
and ready to go when this shit is under control so it's going to be back to back to back to back
there's going to be probably three or four huge streams in a row because they're all have already
been worked on they're all done the last three four months when you hear about a stream that's
like hey i'm gonna do this i'm gonna do that let me the bird the bird stream that may may or may
may or may not have already been worked on and is being looked into with a bunch of other ones too
and he's like he was laughing about he's like yeah you kind of do have a bunch of stuff that
you're gonna just dump back load on everybody because it can happen like three or four times
in a row i'm like yeah that's fine when's the slime stream you'll know i'm not going to tell
you who it is i'm not going to tell you where they stream but i'll give you a hint yeah we'll
see you tomorrow uh it's going to be an exciting day i cannot wait i'm looking forward to it more
than anything i'll see you guys tomorrow have a great night