Sup. How you doing? How you been? How's your family? How's your father? How's your mother?
How are you kids? Good? Good. Good to hear. Just open up. Crack open a fresh beer. Okay.
Early. Now gift 2,000 subs. That's not part of the deal. That's not part of the deal.
I said if I was even one minute after two o'clock. I said I was gonna be early.
If I wasn't early I was gonna gift a thousand subs and this is this is 30 minutes early.
Just about 30 minutes early. Something like that. I do have something very very quick to say though.
While people trickle in. Very very important stuff that I want everyone to pay attention to.
So listen up if you could. Sonic is the number one movie in the world. It's the funniest movie of the
year. Critics and audiences agree. Sonic is the funniest movie in America. Sonic the head
shark. Reddit BG. Critics agree. Sonic is the funniest movie ever made. Audiences say Sonic is
the funniest movie of the year. You know how many fucking times I've had to hear that?
It's burned into my brain. I've heard it so many times. I keep hearing it and I'm not even trying
to. Stop watching TV. I can't. Sonic is the number one movie of the year. It worked. They got me.
I laughed. Yeah yeah. Sonic is the number one movie in America. It's the funniest movie of the year.
Critics and audiences agree. On Rotten Tomatoes. They do that shit now. They do that. They start
talking about Rotten Tomatoes. Dave L from Rotten Tomatoes says I shit my pants. It was so embarrassed.
Sonic was the funniest movie I've ever seen. I feel really bad about the movie theater.
Hopefully somebody can help clean that up. Should I help?
68% on Rotten Tomatoes. It's the funniest movie of the year.
Okay. Let's go. Are you using a voice changer? Nah. What? I don't do that. Oh we got a wink.
Real quick. We got a wink. Does it have a camera set up? Oh shit. I don't even have my camera set
up. Two winks. What? Oh shit. That is two winks. Get him out now. He's disabling the voice changer.
I've heard him in real life. He always sounds like that. It's the funniest movie of the year.
Ten winks? No. I can't. I can't stop doing it. That's going to be what's going to happen today.
I'll do it like 30 more times. I'm sorry. Talking black and white. Oh I've got a wink. Two distinct
winks. Ten thousand points equals funny voice. No. I'm not going to replace winks with something
else that I have to say or do. We're going to make some cool channel point stuff. You'll see.
No brace today. Yeah. I'm trying to loosen up a little bit. I've been a little tight so I don't
want to put a bunch of weight on me and pressing in. I want to be a little loose today. But we're
going to do black and white too as you see. We left off last night. I want to play until I'm kind of
done. I'm still having a good time. I think it's still fun. Where's the audio?
Why is there no audio?
Hold on a second. What the fuck is going on here? Can you guys hear this? I don't hear anything.
It's because the game is paused. Right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. You're right.
All right. Oh, there it is. There it is. Okay. So if you want to get some zoom out here,
you can see what we've been doing. This Murius growing up big and strong. If you missed last
night, Murius beat the absolute shit out of somebody. Murius has a bunch of new fighting
techniques. Is he planting flowers? Who's doing the flowers? That's not one of the fighting
techniques, but that's still pretty sick. Look at that dance. Are people pretending to like this?
That's a sick wedding dance. No, they do like it. They love it. I love them. I'm a bit hungry.
Well, eat something here. Eat this. Yeah. If you just caught the stream today and you didn't
catch yesterday's, we're about... eat it. What are you afraid of grain? What's wrong with you?
What? What's the skull? I mean, somebody's dead. Here, eat. Eat this. If you're hungry, please.
Eat it. Eat it. It's good. I'm fine. You just said you were hungry.
Broccoli. I don't like broccoli. Holy shit. That face. All right. Fine. Fine. Do whatever you want
with it. All right. I got to take over two more towns by force. I'm doing pretty well. Look at
my city. We've got the development over here. We've got this little town this way. We've got
some development this way. We've got some development over here. We've got a couple
more developments. We have some developing over here. The idea is I need to spread my influence.
We're going to build up this way. I just took this town and I think it's time to take another one.
What's above here? Oh shit. Are there people here? Yeah, this is mine. This is mine. I need
citizens. Anybody live here? Nobody lives here. Okay. I'm going to start building towns.
Actually, I want you. You guys take a walk over here. You take this town too.
That one's pretty far away, but it'll give me some more influence. Remember that's my house.
Well, it's sorry. What you meant to say was it's my house. This is my house. No,
but that's what's happening. No, it's mine. No, that's actually it's mine.
It's mine now because I'm going to get it. It's mine. Can I just take this one too? Maybe I'll
take this one first. Yeah, I'll take this one first. Wait, he's got an army over here. No,
no, no. That's not that big of an army. That army sucks. Take it. Take this. I'm going to
send Murius up here too. Where's the archers? How come the archers don't have a flag? Where's
the archers flag? Why is this guy going so fast? Oh, the archers are already on the way down to
the other town. This is perfect. Perfect. All right, Murius, I need you. You have to start
to spread some influence here. Come with me and then we're going to make new base of operations
up here. This would be perfect. All right, well, here comes some resistance, you know,
to do Murius. Get fucking angry. They think that, oh, they're archers. They're archers. All right,
get in, get in, go in. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, this is important. Go attack, attack, attack.
They'll just stop picking everybody off. Attack. Just kill them. Murius, get up here. Good. Good.
They all leveled up. Nice. All right, come on, bring it in. Wait, you're not sending everybody,
are you? Defend, defend, defend. Fight, fight each other. What are you doing? It's not musical
chairs. Fucking start swinging. What are you doing? We're good. Murius, dude, this is not going well.
What are they doing? Why are they like, are we winning? I don't think we're winning.
Build up them troop numbers. Okay, why did we just get stomped? It was like 30 of us.
Murius, what are you doing over here? Murius, you're just stepping on our own. All right,
here, I don't know what the fuck you've done, Murius, but we're taking this town instead.
Murius with the other way. Why did you go the other way? You got fucking distracted. No,
not time to take a piss in the woods. Let's go over here. Support your friends. The gate is closed.
He doesn't know how to open the gate. He doesn't know how to open the gate. Oh, fuck. Okay,
whatever. Just hang out over here. What are you up to? Come here. Let's cap this. Okay.
God damn it. Hey, never trust Nanner's. Thanks for the 10 community subs. Thank you. Never
trust Nanner's. It's an old, old YouTube. All right, he's kicking. That's good. Old YouTube,
old YouTube series, huh? It's an old one. I wish I could get this one without a problem.
Murius is up here now. The mine workers have to walk so far. Wait, why are they going all the
way over here? Why are they doing this? Or there's no ore in here. Oh, shit.
Do I get some tribute? Let me see if I can find anything. Multi hand pickup. Extend your grabbing
ability and pick up many tribes people at once. But you can pick. Yeah, I like this.
Click and hold with the action button when picking up an object to engage multi pick.
All right, that's good. I like that. I want that. Multi pick up is nice. Yeah, it seems like it's
pretty nice. So there's no more ore in here. We'll have this city. Where's the nearest ore?
Up here? Shit. How am I going to do this? Am I going to have to make like a store room over
here or just people are going to have to walk? Oh dear. Okay. He's coming back this way. He's
not coming all the way down. I got archers. That should be okay. Are you going to get a lizard?
Probably not. All right, let's keep working. How are we doing on breeding? What does the
population look like? Looking for food, but people are unhappy. We got 500. There's still
300 male to female ratio. 300 male to... Wait, why is this still like double the amount of men?
I don't understand. All right, let's get some more groups here.
Let's do like 50. No, let's do like 70. What's wrong with the cow? He's just kicking stuff.
Look, I came over and he loves me. He's so happy to see me. Turn your blinker off.
Ah, shit. How long has the blinker been on? We've been on the highway for two hours.
Oh, I feel like a fucking real asshole. Let's get some. This is still mine. It's time to build
in here. They don't have anything. They didn't have anything. That's all, folks. How do I drop
it? Okay, I'll do it. I'm just going to play this all out. Let's get a bunch of wood because I want
to build some shit over here so we get some plenty of wood. All right, I got a store. I want a field
up here for food. What the hell is that? Because they don't have... I mean, they have one field over
here. They have a granary, though. You missed Wink? No, I didn't. Take over three towns by force. I
must have it. There's no fucking people that live here. Let's get some small houses. Let's get a
couple of villas. That's a nursery. Villa. Why do they... why do they always... they're already
pissed off about this? That's okay. They're unhappy in certain places. Okay,
they're happy next to the storeroom? Actual Wink? Well, use the one I just did.
Fucking that stupid thing, man. That shit's got to go. It's not even hard to do, but you know
what I mean? It's just got to go. It's not even hard to do it. I just did it. Another... oh my god.
Wink again, slave. We take a town. Oh, they captured that town. Well, it's mine now, stupid.
I'm soaking. Yes, you are. All right, now I got to build a war room. We're going to put these guys
away. We're going to make them live here. We need an archer factory. I want these people to just
start populating here. So, another one. Because can they live in these houses? I'm sure they can.
All right, Murius, you can go back to doing what you were doing. Use some free will.
Go, go do whatever you want. Another one. No, that was... is it really? Holy shit. Okay,
you're not lying. All right, whatever. All right, I need to build an archer factory.
Put this over here. No, put this like down here. What's the... all right, there we go. Right there.
Take some of this wood. Dump it on here. Every time a streamer winks, an angel gets its wings.
Huh? That's them. We need more food. Pronto. I like that word. Pronto. We need ore.
Ore is going to be... All right, I need you to get ore. Murius, come here. It's time for you to gather
ore. You can do it. You're very smart. Fake winks? I know. I can see them. I can see the winks.
I know which ones are real and which ones are fake. All right, let's turn these guys back into...
Uh, let's make them just citizens. We're gonna have them live here. They're gonna start to collect
shit here. I'm gonna bring the other army who are this way. You guys right here. Fortify here.
Open this door first. They're gonna... I don't want to leave this just open.
You guys can live here and shit. Got another wall to build. Good. Build it. Continue to fortify.
The ticking is the wink counter? Oh shit. Can I even do this? Okay. That was um... How many was
that? That was like... That was like 20? 30? Inflation. We need ore. We need more. We need more
gold. We need more lumber. I'll take care of it. Don't worry. This winking shit is stupid. That's
why it's going away. Citizen of the German community. Yes, the winking will not exist
anymore as of next week. So, hey, don't worry. He won't be here anymore. Why, Pepehands? Why?
What do you mean nobody said that? It was very clear. Someone was like, this is dumb. And then
I'm like, yeah. And then they said, yeah. And they agreed. Trust me. I agree. All right. Get the
creature to help build 30 houses. All right. People live in here now? Are there any women? Oh no,
it's all men. All right. I need to... I need to get some breeding going on up here. And then those...
Let's start farming. Foresting. Get to the mine. Wait, breed. Yeah.
How does she sound stoned?
Does she? Not really. What? What are you talking about?
All right. This town is going to start rocking here. Let me get a, uh, a field.
And go. Let's water that field. Are we doing an ore? You can multi-pick people too. Ah,
shit. That's right. I forgot about that. Thanks for the reminder.
Iris, what are you picking up? Wait, what is that? No, no. You're getting... You need to get the
mine. Where did he even get the tree? Where is he getting the trees? No, there's wood on the ground.
No, no. Don't pick up the fucking... One pebble. You could go into the mine and pick up a huge one.
This is like worth 10 cents, Murius. That's not worth very much. 1305. Okay. It was 95 ore. Good
work. But pick up the big ones. This is when a little kid actually helps you clean the house.
You've got like four bags of laundry on your back. You've got a mop in your hand. You mop in the
floor and they come over and they're like, I found this on the ground. It's like, oh yeah. That's...
What is that? Oh, that's a hair tie. Yeah. Good. Okay. Good work. Good. Yeah. Oh, mom's kind of
busy right now though. Okay. I found a coin. Oh, good. Yeah. Thanks for the coin. Okay. Yeah. Good
cleaning. We're cleaning. We're cleaning. We make up a song about cleaning. And then they go like,
yay! They get fucking happy. Stop doing the mom role play. He's not doing very much. He needs
to learn more. All right. Okay. What do I have? I need to... I still don't understand that.
Let's get some more food. All right. This town is going to start to become good. What is this? Is
this a temple? It's a temple. Did he just put sand in there? All right. I need... I need tribute.
Gathering. I will always gather ore. Good. So now let me... What's the next town? What would...
The next goal is to start to encroach. So I'm actually not going to do any violence here.
I'm going to build up and get to right about here. Or is it always violence? What do you think?
It's over here. Always violence? No, not always. What is this? A maze?
If you spend the signs, you might be able to get them through safely.
Those dumb ambushes will also follow the signs so we can send them on a wild ghost chase and make
sure the spy gets through. What? Oh no. Okay. Make sure the spy gets through. Wait, do I just have to...
Hold on. Save it. Oh, they seek me here. They seek me. You have to turn the signs.
Okay. Save it again. Where does he need to go? Oh God. Wait, what is it? Which way does he need
to go? I don't know which way he's actually supposed to end up. Here? Up here. Where does
he need to go? Right here? Over here? Oh, right there. Don't turn this way. I win. Wait. I'm in
a weird fucked up camera spot right now. Oh my God. I'm trying to move the fuck over here,
but I can't move. I'm trying to get this... This is fucking RTS bullshit. I didn't get it. I got it.
This isn't going to be an actual living hell because when you get down here and you try to
move around, it's like... I just tried. I just tried to move like five times. You saw it happen
in real time. I was trying to move the camera and I was stuck on like a rock behind me. Here we go.
I'll get it. Remember, your odor is foul. Whatever. I'm going to tell you.
Using natural sea salt underneath my arms. What are you talking about?
Where's the next one? Or is it the left? All right. So this is okay. We're going to go... We just
got to follow that, whoever this guy was. We're going to go left and this guy's coming up.
Turn this around. Which way is he going to go? Is he going to go straight up or is he going to
take a right? All right. We're good. All right. It's okay. He's going to go before I do. Yeah,
we're good. It's the new follow the guide mission. Hold on. Save it. Type a check. Let me see. We're
good. All right. Wait, what do I want to... This way. And then over here. Anybody else coming? All
right. This guy is. Turn that sign this way. Make this guy have to walk around the whole fucking
thing. Who else is around? Anybody? I... Anybody here? Wait. Guy coming. Who's going to get there
first? Who's going to get there first? Turn. What? Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
We're good. We're good. We're good. Save it right here. All right. We're good. I'm going to get the
second piece of fucking info. Nobody else, right? Okay. I'm offended on all sides until I get this.
Cancel germawink and replace it with germapoop. Why did you read that one? Because I like to read
the oddities. I'm a collector of oddities in chat. You have another piece of information.
Save game. Where's the last one? Okay. The last one is right over here. What do we have to deal
with? Is there a guy coming? It doesn't look like it. Let's check this out. All right. I go down here.
This guy right here. Oh man. Oh my god. There's so many people. Um, I think I did it. I'm going to do
it. All right. Nobody coming. Save it right here. Please one guy me. I got you. So how many more do
I need? Two more? Three more? Bounce it back. You have another piece of information now.
How many more are there? All right. So if I go here and then go this way, there ain't nobody over
here. Save it just in case something fucked up happens. And then we wrap around here. There's
nobody here. Another scroll. And then there's, I have no idea. Where's this last one? All right.
We got a guy coming. Spin this guy around this way. Is there one down here? Oh shit. Where is he?
Into you. I think that's it. Excellent. You have all of the necessary pieces of information.
Now what? Information. Did it. I can't believe it. I can't wait to see Sonic the Hedgehog.
It's the funniest movie of the year. Don't stop doing that joke. Well done.
You know. 40,000 tribute. I'll take that tribute and I'll bank it. 40,000 tribute. All right. Any
more? Any more scrolls? Any more scrolls? Oh, my poor dolly. You look so poorly. What on earth is
wrong with you? What? That sheep isn't ill. It's giving birth. Catch her lambs or they'll get hurt.
Catch the lambs? Better go nice with some potatoes. Maybe a little salad, you know,
little onions, tomato. Yeah, that'd be nice. Little tasty. Here comes another. Now put it down.
Save the game. What does this do? I used to cast it a water spell.
Wink for the fans. Hold on. Dude, this is fucking morbid. You know what I mean? Like,
what the heck? This is so fucking morbid. More? More? Fire it. Oh, that one's
spinning. Ten lambs saved. How many more do I save the lambs? Ten more? Do I have to have
ten completed? Ten total? Uh oh. Well, that one, I think that one hit the ground. How many more?
This is quite the litter. How many babies does a lamb have? They don't have like 20 babies at once.
No, they don't. They have like one. That's 20. Sheep can lay up to 16 eggs.
Yeah, it just goes it swims around and then puts them on a lily pad. Get ready. Here it comes.
That one hit the ground. That's really funny. Seriously, that's like, that's almost as funny
as the funniest movie of the year. Sonic the Hedgehog. Critics and audiences are saying
it's the best movie of the year. I told you I wasn't gonna stop doing it. I told you.
You're better now. And we've got these new friends to play with. You did it, leader. It's invasive.
It's February. I know that's fucking stupid. Oh, dude, can you believe the funniest movie
of the year? It's been like six and a half weeks. I'm gonna see it though. I am. I'm gonna see it.
You're not gonna tell me I'm not gonna see the Sonic the Hedgehog movie. Why would I not?
The same reason why I saw cats by myself in the theater. Nobody wanted to go with me. I
went by myself. And I just was sitting there going like this the whole time.
That's literally me when I watch your streams. Oh, get the fuck out of here. Oh, the wink. I forgot
to wink. That's me. All right. What was I doing? Oh, I want to do it again. So bad. I know. Okay.
When the stream's off, I'm gonna do this every fucking 10 seconds in my own house.
I don't have to worry about it. Pot market. No, I need to upgrade various.
Siege workshop. Powerful siege engines to do battle. These machines can attack fortifications
and buildings with a power no man could hope to match. Should I teach them water? What about
a university? All right. Intelligence or violence? University. All right. Let's teach them something
else too. Heal miracle. Smelter. Advanced entertainment. I don't think I want that.
Should I get the siege? Water miracle. I don't know what to do. Smelter. Probably that smelter
is so necessary. I don't have, I gotta get it. 25,000. I can also do a lamp. Pot market. No,
no. Let's save it. Save the money. You didn't research advanced entertainment. I know. All
right. Wow. We need food. Who needs it? There's food over here. This is fine. Where's uh, where's
Murius? Oh, Murius. You probably don't want to do this anymore. I guess you're, yeah, you're good.
You're good. Do whatever you want. I'm really lonely. Okay. Entertainment time. Go be an
entertainer. I'm feeling a bit ignored. That shoulder. This is bad posture. Okay. You good?
Go play. Go play. Go entertain. Go have fun. Let's go back to where I was before here.
Tons of shit going on. We need more food. How many people exist?
We're almost at max population here. I need more houses. All right. We're going to go up this way
with houses. I'm also going to put a smelter over here. Melt her first because this is where the
mine actually even is. All right. Smelt. Hey, what are you doing? It's going to come back and hit him.
It's going to throw it into the wall. It's going to bounce back and hit him in the face.
He's going to get even more angry. All right. Smelter. I don't want to do it again. I want to,
but I'm not going to. What's he laughing at? He's laughing at war? I love how he just makes
himself laugh. Those people don't have any houses to sleep in. Is he laughing? Oh no, he's puking.
Oh, he's puking on people. Be gentle. Gentle. Gentle. They're your friends. Yes. All right.
That might be two broken legs. Good. Okay. See? All right. Smelter's online. That's good. No,
I also got a, what else did I get? I got something else too, right? Let's get a market in here so
everyone's happy. All right. Murius, can we favor? Build that. Build that. Help me out. Do some stuff.
Help me. All right. I also unlocked. What else did I unlock? Something else too, right? University.
There it is. All right. Let's bring this over here. This is where the most people are.
University can go. That's a, I mean, that's a pretty good spot for it. Or right over here.
No, right here. University. Please tell me what Sonic is. I don't know. It's a movie
that they remade almost the whole movie because, uh, Sonic was looked like a real hedgehog,
not a, like the actual Sonic the Hedgehog. It made him look like a person hedgehog thing with
like human teeth and shit. It was weird. From the writings of their scholars.
All right. There we go. So people are going to use this. Get the creature to help build 30 houses.
Build a wonder. Still like research of wonder. Mansion skyscraper. Is that a wonder?
Bats. Best siege engine. Meteor amphitheater. Best a hundred soldiers. Best a hundred archers.
Here we go. Wonders. This is fucking 600,000. I'm not going to have that. How am I going to get that?
Is this a funny movie compared to others that may have come out in the last six and a half weeks?
Um, yeah. I mean, of the year so far, I would think so. Probably. From what I've heard,
on all the stupid amount of AdSense space that they've paid for to make sure to tell me that
every day. More than once a day. Uh, okay. Good job. Did you do it? You did it. Okay. Now build.
We need a, we need some houses up here. I want a well too. Build this too. Build everything.
I'm getting tired. Build that. You can do it. Get a manor in here. All right. I gotta get them off
this leash. But continue to build though. Not enough space for a manor. My house. Come on.
Then we're going to put a well right here. The university is going to go over here too.
Right there. All right. Now we can build it. Repeat the joke. More wood. Place Wink with
wasting points. But it just says you throw away 75,000 points. People are using it because they
know they're going away. It's so, it's actually like a, it's an interesting, uh, experiment if
you will. Because people know it's going away. So they're like, oh fuck. I gotta, I gotta use it
now before they become worthless. It's, uh, I'm saving for whatever's next. It's smart.
Saving for the future. We do need wood. Yeah, you do. Um, what am I supposed to do about this?
What happens if you run out of wood? Game over. That's game over. If you run out of wood.
Getting concerned about this. I'm getting concerned here. Wait, Munga S question mark.
Is this the time for me to do this? I say Munga S. I mean, as I think so, this is kind of scary.
We need wood. Gentle. What did you do? Don't throw them. I'm going to rip out and gather that tree.
Good. Very useful, Murius. Thank you. Is this a Munga? I don't know if it is. I had a story
to tell you guys. I don't remember what it was. It was weird. I'm trying to remember what the hell
it was. What was the story? Oh, nothing to do with Sonic. Um, what was it? I don't remember.
Maybe it'll come to me eventually one day. French fries? No, no, nothing to do with French fries.
All right. Now we have some actual settlements here. It's time to go get it. Why are you looking
at me? I like, I sometimes decide to get wood. Yes. Very good. We'll go get it. I want wood.
We'll go get it. It's right next to your town. I'm getting it. Look at me.
Disciple Forester. Do we have a lumber mill? If I don't, I will soon. Disciple Forester. No
lumber mill here? What the fuck am I even doing with my fucking life right now? No lumber mill.
I think I just want to drop somebody in the torch pit and just see what happens.
Ranery. We need lumber mill. There it is. All right. Let's get this right over here.
Okay. How much wood does it need? A lot. Not very much. It needs a lot of ore.
It's a very cool game. It is. It is very cool game. I agree. That's why we're doing it. Two
streams in a row because I'm still having fun. Is chat behaving? Yeah. Yeah, they are. They're
doing just fine. Taking a nap. All right. Now we get foresters. We have, how's this town actually
even doing though? More wood. What do they want for desires? They're okay. They want more children.
Uh, you're a farmer. You are now a breeder. You are a, I don't know, but you're a breeder.
Looking good. Looking good. All right. It's time to continue the plan. The plan is
the areas we're taking the city. What do I have for soldiers right now? We've got a good group
right here. This city doesn't have anything though. Do I build this place up? Look at all
this wood. I'm stealing it from here. I mean, this is a ton of wood. Just take it. These guys need
wood. Bad. There you go. Check it out. Actually, no, don't take it all. Take like, I mean like
five, three thousand back. Wait, are there other subs? There are other people subbed to other
channels other than mine. That's, hold on. I'm not processing what you're saying.
Is somebody, this other stream, wait, what the fuck are you saying? I'm just a little,
I'm just a little confused. That's all. Why is this not built? See if I can do this now.
It's time for you to go soldier mode. You don't need to gather anymore.
Let's get you leashed and let's get you into soldier activation mode. Eat that.
Get some food. Yep. Trust me. You're going to like it.
All right. It's time to take the city. This one. And then I got a good central location to feed
everybody. Bring up the soldiers. Murius is going in first. Murius is the base of attack operations.
These guys are here to take. Murius is going in first. Are you smelling the flowers?
He was not quite smelling the flowers. All right. We're in. Get up here and just hang out up here.
We're trying to bait a response. Murius, do your thing. Bait out a response. We're looking for
an attack. Nice. Oh, good. It worked. Very good. Very good. Murius. All right. Nice. You
kick down the fence. Go kick some ass. You ain't got nothing on fucking Murius. The Murius.
Now we're moving with the other troops. Ready to go. Oh, just take it. Where's the capture point?
Right there. New move. The mega stomp. I'm going to eat that villager. Do so. Do it. Wait, who are
you eating? Oh, you've reached into somebody's house. Oh my god. You just. All right. You just
did the original rampage arcade game. That was fucked up. Here comes another group. I'm ready.
Murius, how you doing? I need a heal. Let's get a heal. Heal. Do I have it yet? All right. Come on.
Let's take it so long. This would be a character. Yes. I'm surprised it wasn't like a cow character.
How do I not have this yet? Do I have no worshippers?
I'm going to destroy that storehouse. Didn't you just build it? All right. Murius here.
I think I don't need it. I think it's fine. Let's see. How you doing?
Make sure we get it. I don't care about anything else. He's just staring at it like he can't believe
it. Oh, did I just do that? Wow. That was kind of easy. All right. Now let's build this place
up now. Quick. We need to have this place ready to go. Defend this. Get a whole city here. Here
they come. Look. He's fucking. Look at him. Stay right here. Look at this shit. He thinks he's coming.
Let's get this shit built up. What do they have in this town? A lot of room too. All right. Let's
go. I want a temple right here. Right now. Temple. Altar. Let's go. No. Temple. No. Yeah. Altar. Yeah.
Right here. Let's do it. Who cares? Put it down. I want a creature pen right here. Get it down.
What? Why do I have water in my hand? Creature pen right here. Bingo. I want.
I want a temple. Do they have a temple? What's this thing? What's this? It's a tavern. All right. I
need a temple. Quickly. Get this shit going. All right. Murius. Listen to me. Very, very carefully.
Listen to me. We got to build this shit. Build your house. Oh no. The free will. It's okay.
Murius. What are you doing? Why is he going so far away? Murius. Oh, he's going to get wood.
In the time it took him to go get the wood. How much wood did he pick up? All right. He picked up
he picked up like five wood. That's not a whole lot, Murius. It's okay. You're trying. I'm going to
we're going to go free will after this. Do you have a link to my only fans? Uh, no. I don't have
one of those. Big boulder. Watch this shit. You guys want to see this? Get your fucking camera ready.
Go to sleep. Get some rest. I'll take care of the rest.
Can't pick these up. Oh. What are the trees? Fuck. What are the trees? Fuck. I will. I'm going to
play with that rock. That's a bigger rock. He don't think he could do that last time.
Okay. Now, um, water. I need to. Okay. I need a war factory. I'm going to turn these guys into
citizens and they're going to populate the area and we can keep going. Where is it? Uh, right at
the edge. I got to get a bunch of wood. How much wood do I need? I need a ton of wood. A ton. Silo.
Ready. Silo. Ready. Building. Instruction complete. Building. Instruction complete. Building.
Building. I took that out of red alert. I actually modded that out of the game or
or or or or or or or or or a shitload, like two, a thousand.
You guys have a lot of stuff. Right? Yeah, you have the most. I'm going to get like 3000. That's
fine. All right, bring it back. This will give me much more influence. Maybe people will start to,
uh maybe people start to uh defecate def what's it called not defecate what's it called people
not what is it defect defect defect defecate i don't know why that was in my brain
defect people will start to defect i mean the act of defecting could be like defecating
like if that's a verb i just fucking killed that guy
i got smoked more hey merius let's play a game merius play a game called throw shit at army across
the way you're starving okay wait no no no no no no no just um this you're okay we're gonna feed you
wait back up imagine being the army up on that hill oh that really took out one of our guys in
the back line um you guys see this hovering rock right moving back and forth in a one two three
throw animation uh i don't think we should be standing here it's all right we're safe
what is he puking uh hold on i'm throwing a fucking tree i'm gonna get these motherfuckers i promise
i gotta get back to what i was doing all right get disband disband disband disband
disband and start working around and doing shit here and what rocks i can throw oh no he's
learning he's learning come here come here come here hey take this take this no you have to throw
it at different people different people over here come here over here come here i want you to throw
that see we're gonna learn i want you to try i want you to throw that at those people over there
can you do that for me not as okay not as good not as good not as good still
something to learn no no forget the rock forget the rock forget the rock forget the rock
oh shit they're coming in they're coming in they're coming in we need to go in i just
spent what's the last time i saved the game back up back up back up back up back up all right going
going going going going he has to he has to do a big kick big kick murius nobody move nobody move
move nobody move nobody move nobody move nobody move nobody move what do you
think about that what do you think about that one you can have a ball back okay
we're fine is there dog barking why isn't he moving
Monka S well because I told him to go for a rock well he drew a rock
incorrectly and I tried to correct his rock thrown and then he aggroed the whole
army and they fucking slaughtered him and then I mean you watched I don't have
get him back actually you know what what prime time to fucking go take this what
do they got here nothing oh they got like no no no no no a patient
God knows when to strike when to not strike a patient God knows exactly what
movie to see patient God knows that of all the movies that have come out in the
last month and a half the absolute funniest movie of the year is Sonic the
Hedgehog why did you put this over here he said the oh he did it he said the
thing and that's the last time I'm gonna say it jokes so good it saves Murius oh
Murius I'm dead I'm here it's time to go to bed eat that grain and then take a
rest go to free will you did great you did great you really did eat some food
store oh yeah that's right he keep threw a rock at the storehouse I forgot don't
take a take some breath rest you need to we need some breeders breeders I need
breeders we have one let's get some farmers in here where these people come
from are they defecting who are these people who are these people and why they
all the way over here who the fuck are these people what are you doing wait
this is walking over they're just walking through hey wait I don't who are these
people welcome
farmer they defecation stop saying that and making me say it again are they
defect how do you say okay if somebody defects what are they a defector a
defector they're a defector not a defect hater there are it's defecting I'll get
it I need a more houses here what do we need oh we need a lot more food and we
need a granary big food big food huge food big food wood I'm so angry he's not
free world right now so all right I gotta do we need water let's do the
water miracle I just need to use some miracle spring water if you get my
miracle spring water all your crops will grow ten times their length good work
put it in ah you need a bath how many farmers over here I'm just trying to
let's get somebody we need farmers lots of them we need so many farmers that is
too many and then like 20 minutes I'm gonna come back over here and be like
why the fuck are there so many farmers dude what the fuck is this this is
stupid that's how many I want I need a granary because food is gonna be fucked
up here granary I got 41,000 tribute I need a granary there we go let's put it
right over here I fit it right I can fit it now they don't want that they hate
this over here this needs hey German what day is it today is Friday it's
Friday liar how's it a lie it's Friday Friday afternoon 1500 wood I'm gonna
take it from here he's a defecator all right what we can do their most annoying
impression of Friday gets a hello from me next time I turn on the stream I just
say hello no not very good no no I'm seeing FR I'm seeing capital F R I I I
no not accurate sorry there we go that's pretty good except it wasn't
capitalized so very good very good there you go yeah it's Friday so it's capital
F R I capital F R A I E dash da why yeah well somebody got it you get a high
from me next stream I'm gonna say hey the person that said Friday correctly
thanks for saying Friday correctly and hey a good fucking day what is this all
right whoa whoa whoa what happened you finished it they finished it they
actually finished it good job guys now we need some we need a mine is there any
mines anywhere all right I'm gonna I'm just gonna I'm gonna destroy their
whole fucking town with this rock watch this I'm gonna be working over here why
not make an army because I'm trying to get as many resources as possible pick
that up before it hit somebody how many builders all right we have we need or
help me find a mine a little of God I'm almost out of resources completely we're
gonna take another time the only mine that exists is the one that's down here
and I think it might it's probably empty and this shits empty or remaining
zero is it any or hold on it I don't think there's any more or it's empty
there's one up here this is it people using this I don't even own this I have
to keep my influence going this way until I can move people over there no
no no no no all right now here we go no ah don't do it I'm gonna do it whatever
who cares ah my name is Bernie Sanders and I approve this message it's the
funniest movie of the year critics at Bernie Sanders are saying it's the best
movie in February Sonic the Hedgehog ready BG good now I'm pissed wait why you
look at all these resources over here they're hoarding let's go 20,000 20,000
they have a lot of shit over here I need all of this stuff give me or two we want
mountains we want what are you talking about we want mountains we want mountains
we want mountain this person dead no their armor I need more houses fuck I
need to take over this town this person sleeping yeah this Murius that person's
asleep please put them down no don't put them in your room I love all right
Murius go to sleep and when you get up in the morning you're gonna go destroy
an entire city good awesome cool with your electricity hands yes get some rest
and get the creature to help build 30 houses I didn't do that yet but whatever
okay what do they have do I I'm gonna build some more houses up here and we're
gonna slowly we're gonna move up this whole line are you ready house let's go
time to start influence they don't want to be near the granary but I need you to
do this so I can get more influence let's get it on gentlemen what is that oh
that's the United Fighting Circuit Irma has watched Inuyasha yeah um I have that
before anybody freaks out it's because it was on every single day every single
fucking day on adult swim at like two o'clock in the morning they would they
play like seven episodes back-to-back you just if you had adult swim on it
would be on yeah that's true of course yeah what am I gonna deny that that's
real influence influence influence more influence I want your people see these
houses going up and go fuck that actually looks like a pretty good place
to live right through a mountain pass Wow that looks awesome what how much that
cost oh what are those what are those going for free free free I think I'm
gonna join German land all you have to do is spend time in the mines and have a
ton of sex you just have to you just have to have a bunch of sex that's all I
asked I really am just like building up into their face this is so stupid all
right this is dumb I gotta put another building over here this is really bad
once we get up here I'm gonna build it like a temple or something what's going
on why do I know I'm doing gestures and I don't even mean to be I think it's
pretty cool to be honest I mean yeah it is kind of cool all right now it's time
to stop building houses and put like a tavern right here let's go we're gonna
put a tavern back here so these people get yeah look at that look at look at
how much happy everybody is a little road connect to this yes yes yes yes yes
Gavin I need a road we're just gonna go from here all right from here what's
wrong there we go have her and the local tavern everyone's happy I'm going to get
that wood I'm gonna sneeze in about 20 30 minutes or maybe even 30 seconds I'm
not sure you know how that works I couldn't tell mine worker I think they're
walking into their territory to use their mine is that what's actually
happening anymore rock second throw all right let's keep going I want to put a
well right here so they can have some good drinking water and you know what
you build it let's also put a statue market right here very cool and you
build it and then we're gonna build a temple now I can't do that yet uh what's
what's small enough where I can put a nursery over here there's gonna be lots
of children laws again okay and let's do I keep seeing the stock market for that
university I don't have a university here yet no you don't Sims University
all right does this have to be within a certain range to do anything or what
university right next to the tavern perfect what else am I missing here I
we got lots of food I need a do I have a lumber mill in this town I do that's a
granary bummer mill I need a lumber mill up here I don't have a lumber mill up
here right what am I gonna do if I when I reach 10 million views on my twitch
channel how close are we how much further do we have I need to put some
more let's do a manner we got to keep this going manner manner I will take
care of this nine million nine hundred fifty six thousand views right now I'm
almost a ten million views on Twitter that's pretty cool I need water those
trees over there this done no look I gotta come in and fucking fix it actual
link okay 94 we go now I can take over this little spot good we'll put a
something over here what should I put over here let's keep the orange shit
over this way all right what do I put over here a temple there were two wings
temples going right here yeah right here so just so they can see it as far over
as I can put it like right there look at this it's gonna be whoa Murius I need
you up here because there's a potential this potential for some violence as I
tell people to come and defect over to me when I tell these people to defect
over here defect to me I need you over here to hang out in fact you can help me
build this then go poo that's the first time I've ever seen you sit down to go
poo everything all right you all right why do I always get the camera ready
for it I'm gonna squeeze out a big log on that building they have to make it so
disgusting how do you play with a building all right I just picked up he's
laughing cuz I picked up his shit oh you think this is funny huh that's real
funny he thinks it's funny it's chat siege poop the boy they freaking out
cuz I hit somebody with it funny funny people happy people happy funny I
finished building this this time to laugh later I need wood we're running
out of wood I'm gonna take this place over just you wait we're gonna get extra
here we go I my my border is hitting your border my influence is hitting your
influence I wonder what would happen if I were to put let's say a really cool
hey hey guys imagine looking out your window and seeing well those the Greeks
are really pushing forward and they have a ton of influence and they're right at
our gate here and they built a temple in a bunch of cool towns and suburbs what
do they build it was the first thing they're gonna build in front of us way
far away from everything else we that's he's been depositing trees again look
what I found in your room Murius more trees I don't want to find this shit
anymore I know mom don't go through my stuff but what the fuck is this Murius
no more but was Anthony over here today is that what it is you know I don't like
him I mean or he's a bad influence on you torture pit all right we're in so I
can let's test it wait I need a anybody what happens if you cross the streams
here I've crossed the stream I'm gonna put a graveyard over here because it's
needed this is the graveyard I'm gonna use that
villager as a free weight okay are you are my towns person where's anybody in
this town these people are fucked up over here all right let's build some
biscuits more influence I need oh he's already going for it okay let's do what
what has some influence it's not a temple oh this is what I think about you
yeah fuck you I'm gonna put a wall up right here they already all left for you
oh we did water it's waterless freeze whatever just vibing I know the meaning
of that word now all right oh okay I want to do this so we're gonna do a
storehouse up here cuz everything's really far away I'm just trying to dump
into there I'm let's just take it just take it I need a shitload of wood who
has the most wood somebody does one of these towns is a ton I think it's this
one yeah you guys have so much wood look at this ridiculous okay I don't take it
all that's good who died okay we're this is mine though I own this hey we
both own this that's not fair what's up with this we both own this curious it's
time pick that up where's he going no no no Murius did not go that way Murius
pick up more rocks Murius pick up here is step on yeah just who cares make it
through the legs did you see that that was an advanced technique advanced pick
up that rock Murius get that rock all right throw the rock at the building
yes good job I'm making him into a killing machine all right now let's take
this over just hang out over here we're gonna get some soldiers to take this
over and then I have I mean then he's it's over I went the shits over are you
ready are we ready for this because I'm gonna have like a thousand troops are we
ready I'm gonna make siege weapons and I'm gonna have like 1200 soldiers you
can take people over with love and kindness I just tried I crossed the
streams I made it the DNA strand it didn't do anything nobody cares I tried
to influence him with well doesn't matter kicking this shit all right let's
take this capture this over okay please where I need some soldiers just enough
to take it over let's just get like 20 use the torture pit there's nobody even
over here they've all they've all defected I stop kicking this stop it
stops a free will do whatever you want but that works too good use of free will
to be honest yeah not bad I just need one person to go take this over he still
doesn't know how to play no we've had people defect we've had the flag that
you click and drag over but there's nobody here they all left I think they
already all left anyways look at him he's still snuggling on the tree he
loves trees all right here we go we have a full platoon 1112 how much that's all
that's I don't want anymore why is this why so many people come over here I did
what I do ten people why is it still happening men oh 20 okay kill every
living thing 20,000 I don't think I want to do that
he's up let's take it and be ready because he might send all right while
they take this I need to make siege engines put it in here Murius okay
siege engines free will you're on I got 41,000 we'll save it siege engines
actually I have to upgrade it don't I what called it what is this an ancient
home forgotten lore oh it's just a lore book okay siege weapons 50,000 I don't
have enough I can't do see but I already have a massive siege engine yeah
um that's fucking let's go save it let's go I'm taking him over he's dead let's
make like 5,000 troops I get it saved right before this too we're going all
in you want to see where the real army is gonna come from there's a thousand
people in this place you ready for the real army so it's war then it's treasy
easy tonight on 60 minutes that's good tonight on 60 minutes the ad that you've
probably seen more than a hundred times is too much advertising taking over our
entire lives and I can look at this perfect whoo nice throw yours all right
how we doing we have like 50,000 fucking troops where's the real army
oh look at that oh what's that after they fucking like 10,000 people oh even
more keep it going open the gate we have 131 is still coming we're eating all the
food but it doesn't matter we're about to conquer do we even need these yeah we
do look at this this is good all right are you ready I think we throw rocks
first we need a good supply of rocks I know just where to find them can't get
these not enough on it god damn it not enough on it it's too heavy
was that what is he doing he's possessed oh what is he making
Mary stop stop he's getting abducted too much you all right all right bring the
army okay here we go pick it up you got a long way to go it'll be worth it and
the archers an army marches on I have a creature down over here right I do do I
need anything else maybe a wait there's a graveyard over here that I didn't
finish now you're right you're right what do I need no it's it's there
somebody fished somebody did it all right Murius you can do whatever you
want a real battle begins at dawn battle begins at dawn look a messenger
send him I thought he's gonna run that way look a messenger I want rocks
Murius I need you to find rocks and bring them to me all right Murius we've
got some rocks and we need I need you to pick up that rock armies are ready
bring that rock over here I want you to put that rock down right here I'd like
you to get the other rock I want you to have a supply of rocks oh the other one
right here yeah because I want Murius to throw them over the gate okay this we
have so many troops let's do a die here let's do it we engage this group on the
field we aggro with a Murius rock throw let's see if we can get an aggro here
they have archers doesn't look like it holy shit I didn't think you could go
that far that was amazing all right get him away from the gate pick up
something else pick up throw some more shit pick up a tree you don't want to
put yourself in harm's way not yet he just let it go oh boy okay good kick
bring him in let's go use your hotkeys what oh fuck that's what the numbers
above the mean my god I thought that was their level I thought that's what I
thought that was their level I thought it was like that's how strong they are
like their level threes level fours prepare to lull them with a siren call
what's a siren call is that is that a bomb what who's the siren
Murius turn around Murius Murius turn around Murius come kill this thing
Murius attack pick up a pick up a rock pick up the rock throw it at this lady
throw it no he's just going in what do I do what's going on huh is everybody
all right what wait what is going on why they all what they're all just
wandering how often can you do that they're they deaf they're defecating
they're deaf they're defecating are they they're still my citizens get back in
there and fight can't avoid it are you sure about that because I can send in
like two people and and who cares and then I can send everybody else in after
it's wasted just go in after that okay take it over we got it now I know what
happens report the stream for safe scumming no that's a plus two smart it's
only ten minutes I'm right back I gotta be so the strategy here is to bait out
the siren eight siren out have the siren happen send in the real army Murius is
not happy does not pay attention to the siren you got a wink okay capture it
take it and then I'm gonna save the game again but should I what if I should get
this first you know I mean should I just take over the whole thing or just who
cares this town's not even worth it just go for the main one
who cares bro all right guys it's time to make a small group Murius is gonna
have a little bit of target practice up here let's get here we go this group will be
the siren group simply get the door open and let's do um platoon size of five
people five people can you adopt strat chat and have us all move into your
streamer mansion that's you're describing the town you're describing
just as big as a town is I would just be the mayor all right here's the bait crew
bait crew here this is actual attack crew streamer town now you want free will
the time being Murius get on free will do whatever you want relax have some
food let's get this game saved here just in case this does not fucking work it's
a very well might not so we don't have to wait again all right army is coming
back all able-bodied men let's get you in here I want let's go with how many do
I want soldiers here I want I want a hundred one hundred now hundred and
hundred and a hundred and fucking fifty now 140 140 and then I want the rest of
the archers not gonna get siren this time 90 is there any other towns that
have a military capability because if you do I'm gonna be using you oh look at
this hi guys you as well how many can you spare ten so all right well we'll
take them all we'll take whoever you got hope you can get us and then you you've
already got max okay I will subscribe to the germa town tier with my art I don't
need art is that there's no like art on command on the screen I don't know where
you think you are what stream you think you're at but this is not the one this
is one two three four five I'm gonna make a separate save well games like
15 years old it's all right to do this what I say everywhere like 26 is the
last day for links hundred and thirty six thirty four why second so people so
long to get up here what happened too old to be a disciple are they still
alive this is person alive I get we have was a graveyard was the graveyard I'll
take care of this how many do we have I need 90 almost there all right three can
move out because this is what 140 all right open the open the door let's go
get you up here we're gonna do a separate save I'm gonna scum the
absolute shit out of this I won't get another wink in time probably not it's
okay though because I'm gonna reduce the price on it for the final day I didn't
we trying to I'm gonna gather that again oh grain I thought he's trying to put
him in the torture pit I was like no he's not all right how we doing where
they come 90 almost there lower it to 50 points that would be terrible no that's
not gonna be that low 61 I'm just gonna let's go let's go I'm done I'm ready
come on how many more was it two more like old people seven it's gonna be a
wink only stream yeah it's gonna be yes we'll make it we'll make it interesting
don't worry all right 70 I'm just waiting for one more and then I'm out
moving out all right get dressed 70 well we're almost there remember the plan
send in these five people the sacrifice will be written in the history books as
the most important of the five troops in the history of our entire mythology
Muris is doing all right hungry are you Muris I want to make sure you're okay
get get that shit out definitely get that out of your system because I don't
want you to be constipated while you're fighting all right go do you think
I heard it good shit is pants almost ready here they come and then I save
let's just save it now and get ready save the game this is called military
option I guess yeah military option like that's our military option is this it's
saved right just make sure okay Muris soldier ate the door to get the door the
doors open doors open Muris and one okay guys let's do it open that fucking door
didn't quite work and I'm Muris here comes the siren here comes the siren
good it's not gonna work on Muris tack you already got the wall down Muris you
good Muris not necessary here we go ah it worked wait pick up I quit pick up
what did I pick up oh it's a dead body Muris shield your eyes shield your eyes
Murin eat it run period hey their goal what the fuck he's got to work out those
who's eating agros all your troops that's bullshit Muris we're even need
him get me the fuck in there siren or not you must know that you're fucking
doomed just Murius kill something this is bad punished for saves coming okay
Murius retreat retreat retreat retreat everybody retreat retreat oh so bad I'm
gonna tear down those walls how many people in the military do you even have
a lot just cause a problem just break shit what do you did he just suck that
into his ass
too much he did he was he was too much for he went too hard so what happens to
all these people they are all these people gonna come back over here put
stop sound the fucking military bells again what the fuck let's go let's go I
need military where they're not yours anymore what where the fuck are they
going they're obviously going here wait hold on so they're not my citizens
okay so new plan save scum version 2 disband all military send one there
they're out of range weren't they were all the way back wait hold on I tried
one more thing military option we're gonna disband it works on citizens wait
it works on everyone oh it doesn't matter it works on literally everyone oh
it actually just ruins everything I wonder if I can get in there I wonder if
I can throw fireballs over the fucking fence and blow up the building let's
hang out here for a second a true true military master knows exactly when to
attack we're gonna burn that we're gonna burn their fucking city don't move them
out of range all right we're gonna move everybody down here I'm gonna teach
Mary Mary's fireball is that far enough away I know plus one two three four one
time nine I know this is not far enough away well just get him out of the way
whereas there's Marius no fireball there's no lightning do you know fireball
shield water eel lightning you already know lightning fire miracle 90,000
don't know moving closer it's time to encroach and then just rain help I will
bait out the siren by throwing fireballs probably right is that what's gonna
happen I think I might just have to live with it all right somebody confirmed
that this military is still too close should I should I move them even further
away or is that actually can I not the siren has a limited range you can save
them do it just in case all right we're gonna move them all like all the way
back here talk them up mega milks ass and said that's not even his name okay
we need to encroach a little bit let's encroach with a I'm gonna put it I just
put another temple up here just to get even more just temple strategy I got
plenty of resources I'm gonna do temple strategy that's Tavern that also starts
with a T Jeremy yes you're learning very good you're gonna help muscle milk put
it up muscle milks mega ass all right that was funny I like that one he did
it inhale a whole military tent up his ass let's just face the fact I'm gonna
bring all this up happy Friday happy Friday hope you guys are doing well
because I'm doing good I'm doing good just chillin here with fucking Murius
the muscle milk it's not Friday it is Friday all right we keep going now I'm
gonna pick that up and well we have access now to I'm gonna build a couple
of this dumb all right we're gonna do I'm gonna make a couple of houses up
here just enough to you know maybe get some more space so we have perfect
access I thought it was Saturday no it's Friday there was stop house
cheesing hey I'm given my godly powers to do what I want I'm gonna do the house
cheese encroachment strategy okay good this is a good spot this is enough room
for me to be throwing fireballs just all over the place maybe a seems like a bad
idea house encroachment just so I know what it is
damn it can't get this anywhere in here when the next naked Lord of the Rings
marathon I did them all don't even fucking know it's in store for you
motherfucker all right I need to wait put these in a place where I know they
are back him up nice temples have a much larger influence radius yeah but in case
these get attacked it's all right they're inexpensive put this back in the
store room Murius is asleep all right um let's just do a test here say this under
encroachment strategy new stream my taxes Jeremiah don't know how to do them
that's why you hire a tax professional get a tax professionals to help you
figure out what you need to do burn it down oh that was that was a lot welcome
to hell where's your siren see I got dogshit strategy too oh what's that sorry
oh I've got dogshit strategies as well and I have unlimited mana because people
have been worshipping for like an hour and 45 minutes on spring I got to get
right in there this is wipe them out gate god damn it the gate is too high the
gates open furious come on get it in there I gotta like bullet in and then
Murius goes in they get it
got it oh that was a perfect fucking shot okay good that Murius you know what
to do well the doors closed oh no oh my whatever will I do what are you holding
oh get that gate open no no you're not done you're not done get the gate open
I'm gonna attack that building yes you are there's only one group here there's
two groups we're gonna bait him back and I'm gonna throw a fireball on their
heads this thing's going down okay yeah why isn't I using this ass he's trying a
different strategy this door is too hard which no that was harder got it you
don't get to do anymore you know just just like break the rest of this all
right bait him out this is my bait come on out oh what's that oh look at that
here they all come Murius no no Murius back here interesting I missed what
did get in there he just hit himself in the head of the rock why did he just he
just like went like total fucking like psycho mode and hit him so the head
here it comes the ass blast is he gonna get it didn't even take the whole thing
you didn't get it all it's just the shape of your ass pick up that firetree
all right you're going in with a fucking giant torch all right it's yeah pick it
up pick it up yes you can yes you pick it up all right I'll do it I'll pick it
up just get in get in and hurt somebody like lightning yep here it comes through
the legs his special technique all right we're still good I'm starving you can eat
the second eat now hill you you come back all right reel it in reel it in
reel it in reel it in reel it in eat you need as much as you want one more should
do it I don't I don't want to send anybody in I'm afraid he's tearing the
walls down though okay there's a lot of people here though I don't think he can
kill these guys himself on his own burn trees and throw him over the walls not a
bad idea is he throwing what he just did he just ass blast that over here he's
just as blasting this guy at least going over there oh shit they are come on
spread a fire don't go over there yet watch out various oh shit that's my own
stuff he just hates these walls so much god damn it I got a like why can I not
go further than that oops expand the influence now all right let's build a
house encroachment good idea good idea more and it's like you should fuck
building houses in their houses they don't Marius is still going after these
walls okay here we go line it up line it up nice and good here this is so fucking
stupid I love it we're trying to get enraged to throw fireballs this is ah
I almost have it more set the cow free no no I don't die he's gonna go bring
you killed and wait you know what various creature faces us in battle this
is worrying it is because you're all about to burn fun back back back back
back back back back back to go retreat back to go retreat back to go retreat
okay burn stay on that rock for a second they didn't follow he wants to go back
there's so bad it's like let me back over there please I don't want to throw
didn't hit him Marius just watch out I'm gonna throw it I'm quite afraid move
out of the way move out of the way go over this way get Murius watch out
various your face it wait come over here move move flaming boulder this is so
stupid this is so fucked up I go okay now Murius comes back here eat this
person just eat this person and get some health no you don't have to eat anybody
to get help here look no free will fuck all right free will you're right you're
right you're right right yeah free will free will do whatever you want I know
what I'm gonna do I have a free will as well I also have free will
he's got a weapon he's got a weapon this time he's got a weapon you learned from
the best can you anybody else besides one person he's gonna pick the wrong up
again and throw it isn't he I don't have any jurisdiction here I can't heal
him that's why I didn't want him to go in fucking annihilated he got he
got mad he threw a rock it didn't hit anybody threw another rock missed
everybody and got pissed off you didn't get the you didn't get to cast his
lightning bolt on anybody now here we are these games are so fucking funny
this is what this where you get fuck I'm gonna make a couple more houses can I
yeah I can oh I'm moving in I'm moving in this is so funny can I build another
one hello wait move this tree hi neighbor
erected that was perfect shot the left side wait a minute oh my god oh my god
yep watch this you don't even fucking know you're about to get red alert to
motherfucker that's where this that's the wonder I have to destroy the wonder me
and mirrors are gonna go in and we're gonna destroy the wonder the 50 year
long siege of houses temple check this how fucking irritating am I this must be
so annoying these are the people that you play in an RTS and you're just like
oh it's this guy this fucking guy great no I know this is gonna be not a fun
game I mean I know I'm gonna beat this guy because he's he's not fucking good
at the game he's not good at the game he's just annoying and sometimes he
wins more than he loses because he's fucking irritating there's nothing to
do with him playing the game well like people just leave his game it's a big
ass tree you can fucking have this I don't care it hit okay I need a or the
guy that just builds farm skeletons around the map I need or anybody have
or are we out of or oh no I don't think there's any more or nobody has any
somebody yeah you gotta have a little bit right here we go yeah that's enough
I got a lot of wood I tried diplomacy it did it did not do it didn't look at
this border I can get in here all right I'm in I'm in I gotta get that fucking
thing get torched torch the whole fucking city in it oh I got it all right
burn burn get it light it on fire it's almost there spread freeze ready okay
and action get it yes light it on fire it's burning it's burning it's burning
more do it again is Murius alive no mega low get it over there siege trees can't
throw it the how effective of the siege trees take it down the whole thing come
on come on time-lapse time-lapse eat the ice cream cone the whole thing eat the
ice cream gentlemen gentlemen gentlemen gentlemen
gentlemen it's done it's dead Murius it is no more everybody in is it dead is it
actually dead let's just let's just make double sure I'm gonna get my siege
weapon ammo in there fuck no it's not it's not ready the milk is alive rejoice
no that's not that the things destroyed now we just do suppressing fire nice
all right suppressing fire they're ready in all right three I want you over here
three get in four light him up five capture get it eat him alive good where's
Murius take it take the city the city is ours excellent work all it took was us
getting rid of the siren tower with our siege weaponry we're good to go I had
so many more resources so much more playing this lane in the name of the
yes we do there were one guy that's my suggestion what burn trees and throw
them over good thing it wasn't raining five minutes ago oh they made it just
cap it put every single person on here you know while we're at it
don't do that you didn't kill me they're all cheering this is not the screams of
people in the village these and they all these soldiers screaming and cheering
for half like they did it yes these brutal Greek armies was overwhelming to
us as they were to the north I face the shame of being defeated by them my
brother must be told it is like the prophecy these people have a good I have
seen miracles where's this creature I must go through the portal to find my
brother immediately now we can move on to Nagoya and click on the gold scroll
when you want to leave this land we had a raid raid from limealicious thank you
lime welcome everybody playing black and white we just used a lot of diplomacy I
still had that on here that but thanks a lot for the raid welcome guys we're
gonna I want to click the scroll I don't want to throw fireballs are you sure you
wish to leave the land like I can still need to build a wonder I didn't do that
anymore scrolls that I missed I don't see any scrolls right because that's just
free favor at this point was that slap was that slap thing the Japanese know
what I like a CGI that's weird they're sure to take measures against us let's
go to the next land 49% evil yeah I know it's towns taken by force town taken by
impressiveness settlements by him see look 50% evil we took five by force we
took five by diplomacy and inspiration pretty balanced 50% happiness birth rate
highest mana highest size ring 30,000 number of deaths of 1300 okay player
water mill miracles 30 fire miracles 45 healing three times five hundred
thousand tributes and spent and gained did most of the side stuff besides build
a wonder all right creature creature alignment is 80% good if you could
believe it seven years old he's now ten feet tall he's now 6400 pounds he's now
very strong very muscular very fat and very fit he's all he's everything so
he's piece all right so he's fat fit strong and huge so he's every wrestler
from 1985 number of bowel movements a hundred that's a perfect score 255 kills
hundred bowel movements all right let's keep going 100 good poops out of a
he's about to overflow on kills what's next I could not stand up to the Greeks
they overwhelmed us you are a fool with defenses and a strong army they could
have been held at bay no I have some power
I have seen miracles they have no God you failed no it is as the prophecy says
a weak race will survive an onslaught and will rise again with a good to lead
it silence I will deal with these Greeks according to the teachings of war I will
let them build to destroy them why not destroy them first remember why let them
build
I want to get like Armageddon we really do have to build a wall to protect us
and quickly I want to get that volcano holy shit look at myriad
he's a stack look at those legs look at those glutes oh you ate that person all
right we need to go quickly quickly quickly let's go store room or and
where's the most shit we need a forest let's go right here there's a mine right
there too right there they fill their stores more for us to take as our own
this shit back here alters the teaching say a farm just nothing but the sword
and the arrow bomb right here big their fields will provide our warriors with
their victory meal nope sorry you don't have a Murius I do many houses me roads
all right road gonna be going straight down what we have fuck they have what's
over here small settlement over here we're gonna build down this way we're
gonna get these two settlements immediately as fast as we can let's go
ahead and start making people get get some rolls here you're alive you're
good
easy careful or a stir now we want like 10 foresters good readers good you not
working we need a lumber mill no we don't houses first
Murius stop trying you're gonna hurt somebody homes roads roads first
you know he's gonna be built out over here looking good all right houses
Greeks build homes in which to hide would be hiding in a house no you live
in a house you hate me you hate me he hates streaming he hates us he hates me
various various move tavern these people have a drink to hide the fear they feel
tavern okay don't say things really quickly as you do them commentary okay
move that got it building house that's done all diplomacy no balls what
trees running out of trees already I got it we got up I mean we got a fucking
stuff plant some damn trees who died various all right that's enough enough
enough enough enough no no no enough enough no yeah no you're killing people
he's throwing his toy around and hurting people need some worshipers
worship me worship me come on worship I'm not seeing enough worshiping please
drink didn't I just say stop playing with that I need more worshipers what
was that crying more trees damn it bigger water what are these need more
trees hello various various various various various
various come here here's the problem get up don't let them just fucking waltz in
here what I mean maybe they're like eat somebody do something get somebody good
belly bump didn't even get your sentence out sorry don't go too far to the town
you can eat after this trust me hold it up boom that guy's probably what you
killed you kill a townsperson nope that person still alive good all right stop
stop stop stop beast seems to be aware of the teaching he's like huh okay we're
good happy happy happy all right go back to free will nice job there is now we
need to rebuild this is using our brew and they can follow them to get me like
fires to get this is gonna be very very difficult oh got it that's really hard
oh and go oh come on a little bit less it was way too less on door calls paid
on it's so I must have hit the siege engine that's it no dear it was very
you only get a certain amount of temps I get it come on hit it that's it you're
gonna be kidding me how's it not it you to go way too hard or way too little and
this is not very much in between that's it right oh my god he's gonna come in
the frame and be like that wasn't very good what oh holy shit this is so hard
no 90 minute side quest I got it what was that one so fucking line
what with Murius he's just been eating he's just been eating food look at how
fatty is Murius come here oh my god he's just been he's like he's like a beanbag
Garfield did you do it kill them please all right turn around you don't know the
wrong way Garfield fucking enormous you don't need to use don't use any more
energy okay all right build I have work to do over here come here Murius build
this shit good work okay let's go back over here he was just sitting there
eating I don't know what he was eating probably people he was shame eating
alone forest great short leader this gives too much oh god damn it didn't
even throw it that far I really didn't even throw it that far oh my god I'm not
even throwing it this far it's my mouse acceleration that's it no the mouse
settings that's it that's it come on hit this West didn't work when the game
first came out and it doesn't work now what okay really oh my god damn it okay
that's it a little too much I know I can't cheat how much was cheap install a
different mouse that's it that's it big bits oh shit we do the big bits right
now I thought I missed it wait wait wait wait wait not as important hello wait
no no no no no no this is not this quest is not important this no not your bits
your bits are fucking and very important but this quest is not important this is
important get in there Murius soldier he's so huge all he's do is move his
body up and down he'll kill people but it was bit slave thanks for the
5,000 bits thank you dude he hates money no I said it in wrong order he still
hasn't built this he's been trying to build this with like two hours anyways
bit slave thanks for the 50 fucking dollars dude and what do you say you
say PSA don't drink a whole bottle of Johnny Walker in one night I threw up
from 9 a.m. to 3 p.m. I thought about going to the hospital because I was
Holy shit dude we were trying to tell you to drink some water don't do that bad
not good not good one or two drinks all right not a whole bottle you guys slow
down a little you gotta be careful with that careful careful careful with hard
alcohol just drink fucking wine and eat bananas you under restaurate made my
power remember that was because of you no I was saying distill I was saying I
was saying slow down I was the opposite of what I was saying that's the one
right there no anyways they say also more importantly I got banned from League
yeah we do remember that if you remember that one I got a new account so if you
want you you want to get one too we can play go on go on Jerma all of us and go
on Jerma all of the chat know you want to run down as a mooboo again I won't
play drunk as an added bonus just kidding play League on your own if I
install League of Legends bingo got it if I install League of Legends it'll be
because no I would never do it I just don't there's no I have no really I
can't I could never do it I know I hosted League of Legends for like three
straight days that was another reason why first try please he hates League of
Legends no I just don't want to play it oh I did a way less way less a lot less
power don't fucking stop me yes you should take this up professionally why
did I do that because me we were going back and forth Joel and I were raiding
each other and we didn't want to have to but none of us were live so I was like
fuck it whatever I'll just host League who cares it was a joke from like two
hours ago in the night it was a joke from like three hours previous in that
night 40,000 favor nice nut oil all right now back to it that's a lot of
favor though but bits like thanks to the 5,000 bits and take care yourself be
careful oh no hey look looks like he's lost a little bit of weight you see oh
wait here they come okay I have to build a wall build wall build wall build wall
wait wait wait hold on no no no Muris you can't go into like a like a fat guy
food nap no no no you gotta get up get up get up get up get up he's killing so
many people don't build the wall I'm gonna build it right now nice
I don't stand a chance he's too good we will avenge your death on our war warriors all
right let's put the wall up their beast seems to be aware of the teachings of
war how can this be I don't know that's like the fifth group of people you've
sent to die I think it's time for you to figure that out I wish I put both why
the wall started there it seems like a really stupid place for this why is the
wall started here all right what if I go over here teaching say walls around the
city loose around its neck low or on map this time oh well I'm gonna be fucked
all right um they're sending in like military oh thanks for watching the
stream everybody it's been fun I have to get a military going we need to do tons
of breeding tons of houses I need a nursery we need a lot of breeding we
need a lot of warriors I need a let's go up here let's have this go up this way
this is shitty Warcraft knockoff my child my child you sorry no but
Minecraft mod is this it would surprise me in the nursery we are not monsters
I want big houses to manners only have sex sex and food my captains will take
these manor houses as their dwellings these houses are terrible they're in
the worst fucking possible spot let's all get it once this way they'll be
fine it's all right let's build them I know I'm going for it
trust me I'm trying for me a town sucks days later it's different town it's not
the same town it's different talent you saw two days ago different town more
come on this you know attack us every second freeze water those trees I need
more wood I'm ready to get on it I'll do it or wait this is creature versus our
arches are the best defense against enemy creature wait they're coming the
wall built oh what oh dick the town is getting destroyed here comes the
catapult various you've been training just for this purpose various turn fight
Murius I have to drop get the fuck out of here you take that catapult and you
can fucking fuck off their beast seems to be aware of the teachings of war
attack this Murius attack a blow that was weird okay back to normal I'll help
I need this anyways don't is there another who's coming down here
somebody's sprinting down here oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god Murius
Murius Murius Murius Murius eat this guy Murius get this guy did you just where
is he going what what's happening did he just impregnate that I don't wait
baby just furious get in here yep get him he ran in there hurt baby I thought
like is it like two spies wait did was there a spy that got in and this is
freaking me out I thought there was like a spy
villager and he came in and like impregnated spy village okay we're good
we're good can you finish the wall please finish the wall before we get
killed again build a gate I have to wait till this is this is done we're gonna
get this how much or is needed here here just just finish it finish it pick it up
from here just finish it it's 4,000 right there finish the fucking wall
please they're in the way I have to build stuff here almost they'll do it
you Murius please just go do it go help all right now so I have we need
breeders people who just keep dying so reading food and houses and then
military look we need food get another farm here we need a granary granary is
next not as evil no not really who's doesn't have a job I want you to farm
Murius you're gonna be on here I sent you on gathering mine in the mine they
can't get him he's so smart he's so smart he's so smart my special boy he's
so smart he'll get it eventually he's so smart but we need these trees we need
the trees Murius this I know I know and I would be doing the same thing but it's
how that was very poor how many times is he gonna try he's getting pissed what if
he runs out of stuff to throw dude you Murius come on man are you like
pretending so bad oh mega lol they're right over the gate
holy shit so fucking bad I'm gonna let this play out I'm gonna let's play out
what happens when he runs out of stuff to throw over the fence he's taunting
I think he's tired yeah I know I know it sucks it sucks I think he's pissed that
his toy is over there you threw it over there various I can't even get his toy
back I have no jurisdiction over here he threw it he also threw every tree why
am I doing it now oh okay okay okay I don't want to lose those trees there's
so many trees back there okay I have to build a gate let's get a gate built
it's up in the front right okay give a gate the teachings say those who build
gates okay trap themselves in go okay Murius go get your toy go clean up
after you mess good job okay wait there's somebody left what are you doing
oh he's going he's going for the sicko play for the last guy oh he didn't
we're taking damage is this guy gonna walk in the oh come on good I don't know
what to even do with this guy seems to be aware teachings of oh I just hurt my
chest all right just stay over here and gather
please gather mine yet or that was fucking ridiculous how many trees are
out here I should have just given up a pile of rocks that's what I'm gonna do
I'm gonna I'm gonna find of all the rocks and he's gonna have as many rocks
as he wants over here and he can throw rocks over it's gonna be perfect my
special fucking how like these over here we need to start to develop stuff how
we doing we need food what's the birthrate birthrate low how
is to live anymore homes that heal I'm trying to get water do they just plant
it like how do I make more trees grow how do I get down here we had big bits
big bits another $50 donation Jesus 5,000 bits from judge mortis thank you
judge what do you say you say recently more than ever I felt extremely average
and unimportant I feel like when I try to do something I learn how to do it
slower and do it worse than most people I'm unambitious which has led me not to
pursue college a better job a significant other etc do you have any
advice other than watching you stream never a dull moment here thanks well
here's the thing depending on what you like to do it sounds like it sounds
like you might be you're not passionate about very many things correct me if I'm
wrong you kind of have to find something that you are very very passionate about
that you really really care about and then those things that you really care
about you you'll never feel that way because you really like it it's it
doesn't even have to be potentially for work or for a job if you really enjoy
something do it make yourself happy try to make yourself feel better make
yourself happy about something try to truly care about something because when
you start throwing darts that's when you can get into trouble you know oh I want
a significant other that's one thing to put time into I want a better job I want
to go to college I want I want all these things I want them I need them all right
you almost have to focus on one thing that you know you want to do and the
other things might come you talking about like significant other I I didn't
have a girlfriend or anything for like eight years it's great it kind of just
happened Kim and I just sort of happened I didn't even try I wasn't even trying
you just don't know what's gonna happen but all you can do is try to stay
passionate and try to care about something and try to do it there's no
real secret recipe I don't think that was a humble wait I just I just told you
I didn't have a girlfriend for like ten years how's it hey guys you know look at
me I haven't had a girlfriend in ten years until I came came along that's
how's that bragging that's just real life actually I want to take some of you
guys away you didn't have to try oh oh wait hold on people at the gate wait I
see you saying no I mean like I wasn't pursuing it it's sort of just happened
and I've tried you guys remember the tinder years I was on tinder I was on
dating websites trying to I got stood up on a fucking date from tinder I told
why we already went over that I was trying and the the moment that I just
stopped trying for some reason it was like okay a few months later I just met
this person like a Christmas party and it's not like I gave up on tinder or
anything like that it was just I it wasn't a priority for me anymore
tinder is garbage yet tinder is is 75% bots 10% people making accounts just to
see what happens like they did not oh I'm just gonna make a tinder I match
with this person well all right cool that's how many matches did I have today
that's it and like 4% people that want to like go on dates more like 1% it's a
hookup app no it's a place to get bought phone numbers to data mine your
fucking cell phone but to put a cap on that I should probably game actually
because a lot of time just went by to put a cap on that it's hard to it's hard
to give advice on stuff like this because I don't really know the answers
I don't really have them I wish it did all I can tell you is
experiences that I've had and some of them are fairly fucking strange I wish I
had a way to answer
wait Jeremy you're not an internet psychologist
but I feel like I have some experiences that could maybe help people or try to
tell them how I did things but I did things really strange
did you try Bumble no I was I was out of the game by the time Bumble was like
really the thing that everyone talked about look how much food I have all
right start breeding nobody has any houses to breed in okay I got a breed
standard houses install tinder on all their phones they don't need tinder on
their phones they all live in the same square mile hey more houses but they
can't get it there's a gate but all these resources I'm starving all right
yeah yeah like get off guys that you can do it everyone free will go to Taco Bell
I gotta put like a market or something down here for people where's the ground
consecrated why is it ground consecrated it's
cuz I'm evil I'm only 50% y'all the grounds have like 50% consecrated I say
I can it's the opacity on the consecration it's like 50% I get it all
right more houses I can't build them on the cliff come on let's get something
down here feed people feed Garfield more people let's get a statue trading
thing another nursery nursery here we'll do a nursery down here as well I want to
be just pumping the population up like crazy you got to go out further with
like something else put it up here no hold that thought me back give me back
you don't
dude we have any rocks it has to be like a rock he can pick up or something
that's not the trees we need it's not doing anything Murius new strategy new
strategy oh the doors open no stop I let him in I'm trying to let him out
don't run away where are you going why are you running away what's the point of
this what was the purpose of this you fucking idiot stop you're gonna break
the fucking wall he's out of control he's out of fucking control your death
honorable warriors close the gate their beast seems to be aware of the teachings
of war can this be he's spoiled no I think he's just kind of dopey how we
doing need more any more homes fucking come on all right what do I have to
review 200,000 here we go what do I wanted to learn hot market shield
miracle siege workshop siege workshop I think water miracle advanced builder
advanced gatherer the heel miracle a lot but it's worth it
mansion which is fire 90 should I hold off and give him fire should I invest in
mansions I don't know probably mansions that's more practical all right Murius
can heal now but we need more room we need more houses we need more space I'm
gonna build a mansion back here we're gonna put all the mansions I'm gonna
put a ton of them back here where's the entrance a place for my elite guards I
wasn't eat 1,200 wood 400 or they guys killed somebody no Murius it's not
gathering or if you take it out of the store this or is it's empty all right we
need more mansions and then I'm gonna build the military I need wood we have
so much food but so little wood I need to build like a lumber mill all right
that's next hey keep going back here with mansions after a number after a
lumber mill lumber mill is gonna be back or granary I need to put up some roads
over here this way go this way okay I want a granary right here no I have so
much food I need a lumber mill sure yeah okay yeah yes they too are preparing
for that way this way that way what do you guys what are you guys cringing
cringe why'd you guys cringe what's a cringe why are you cringing cringe 600
or lumber I'm gonna pull over those rocks go for it let's just have this go
right here they can go all right now we got some room mansions wait you're at
the gate who cares they can't get in there's a lot of trees over here let's
spread out this way don't tell me he went to go get the little tree to throw
no he didn't he's planted a tree that's not where that goes what that's not
where it goes all right there's a lot we're getting a ton of births I need
another nursery okay okay okay okay okay okay okay road this way houses how much
how much they have to have to be regular houses they can't be big ones I
don't have any or I'm gonna put a tavern in the middle or a store or something he
planted that for you what's wrong with this land it's bad land damn it it's
okay now let's get a plant market right here no everyone's like waiting for
their house to be built move out of the way get out of the store get out of the
store Marius move plant the trees everywhere well I got an encroach on
some other place I think he just stomped on a bunch of people but I don't know
plant market needs or really plants home girls more impressive but our people
shall not be fooled by their tricks don't let him eat villagers do we have
any or I thank God that's enough houses now we have to start how many people
exist in this world hundred on 200 people put it down don't throw it over
the edge she's gonna throw it over the edge eventually when we get I can
reliably get out here yes he's gonna keep doing it plant trees he's ruining it
hold on put it down put it down stop stop stop all right stop stop stop stop
stop stop no stop I picked it up you can't have it plant trees near houses
give me that give me that give me that I'll grind up enemy soldiers into human
paste whenever I see them just relax all right trees he's rebelling stop pick it
up trees no I don't know I'll occasionally attack trees I'll seldom
attack trees you're good okay relax I'll seldom attack trees you mean
constantly it's right it's so many I'm controlling this character but I'm not
he's taking he's trying to attack the enemies I need to give him something
Murius I just planted that put it back down hey I'll attack enemy soldiers
whenever I see them yeah yeah go do that go do that go do that thing you're doing
go do that get out there and attack I'm trying to close the fucking door I don't
even know where we are where is he he wants to throw the rock you can't get a good
angle okay take the rock with you take the rock with you their beast seems to
be aware of the teachings of war take the rock with you no no no no no no no
no pick up the rock pick it up no you know what you're gonna do you're gonna
bring all these trees back inside that's what you're gonna do you're gonna bring
all these back pick these up put those back over here you plant that tree right
here thank you my toy good okay we're good um so what the fuck was I doing oh
right I stopped injuring villagers what I'm gonna make that villager better
wait he's gonna heal do it do it do it do it you need to learn nice good work
no that's gather or shit all right what do we got we got we got we got we got we
got we got we got where I'm just keep it the gates closed right okay it is give me
some water it's more water that was heal it's okay it's okay to miss click
that's a misclick again I think it's time to start having a military presence
there are some buildings that I desperately need I'm full on food I
need a what do I need a smelter zero my his mind is done it's dead we have to
come down here is there another mine no but this is really bad there's no other
mine here there's some ore here but there's no mine is there great or what
about through the wall shit I'm in deep trouble here just make the town pretty
who cares about an army okay I have to actually leash you because you are such
a psycho you're gonna start throwing trees again yes you are you're gonna
throwing trees I would like you not to do that I would like you just to hang
out over here and let's do some let's grab get this do some gathering put it
down gather just get grain okay we have to go down here I have to start
influencing out this way let's do a another storehouse no what should I do
I want to go down here please watch but no I'm not watching the video I'm
focusing how do I want to build this out because I have no or how the fuck am I
gonna do this there's a temple need or two temples it's a good video we'll see
you don't we're home we gotta I gotta do I gotta just build out I gotta use the
remaining that I have I'm in deep shit I just had a green where is it where is it
I just had it just said yes they build temples where they shall pray for mercy
all right I'll watch the video all right let me let me get this bill I enjoyed
every second of that video it's not done boom now all right save it as this save
sounds good all right what are you what's going on here where is it what is
it this is all this better this better be the best video I've ever seen 12
seconds okay let's check it out
that was pretty good that's
hold on I turned it up the volumes too high you know let's go that's pretty
good that was pretty good I laughed I cried all right free will time
Murius has to go kill people this bitch is hard let's do another temple just
fucking do two temples I'm through another temple what's the what's the
worst I could happen is this bad idea because this is a huge amount of
influence than just building a bunch of like houses down here plant the trees I
mean I was but he kept on taking them out of their roots plant trees I will I
will hold on creature was into battle the Greeks will soon regret coming here
okay here we're gonna our mighty creature don't gather I want you to just
relax in fact just go sleep put that all right put that down do not don't take
trees how do I say stop taking trees do not take a tree I'll attack enemy
soldiers whenever I see them then I don't do that don't no no no no no no
I just have like red guy purple paint on my hands no oh cuz that cuz he's
ripping the trees up to throw him at the people I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
okay here we go trees are getting cut down now looking for a spot to put it
next to houses he's pissed he's just still doing it
look at me okay what it down put it down just caught it out of my fucking hand
and just stay there for just your own timeout you're gonna be saying I don't
want to be down here well don't do crazy shit just wait till I get out of here
I'm gonna make your life a living hell dad trees we're impressive we're cool
people like us this is done all right now we're gonna do we're gonna build
some roads out this way don't think we can hold on this is what I made good
this is what I made this for continue this way 4500 not enough let's do a
another nursery so I need a second one I have a lot of kids being born only one
nursery this is just wood we expand my brother was right to admire them we go
but we cannot allow this to continue I'm starting to drain out raiding parties
I'm starting to drain influence from almost both of we have both these towns
what is the most needed thing at the moment armory we want an armory all
right fine we're gonna plant more trees over here use some of them oh oh go so
I can close the gate oh shit they're just watching don't spread don't spread
don't spread no don't hit the fire nice guy no no no no no it's safe here we
know you're liking it you're like it you're like it no no no no don't run
through the fire what's going on just stomp and you'll be fine stomp stomp
stomp step on him no I wanted you to pick up the
rock I don't even know what to say anymore bring that rock behind the gate
I need you to have it so then you can have something to play with leave him
outside I need him inside lock him up all right I'm gonna leave him outside he
can just destroy all this shit if he wants he's so scary he's so scary what
face okay he's let him just do this I don't care teach him to heal people I
did I did I can't pick I want to pick her up toy no there is no toy you're
locked out you're staying out there that's so itchy I'm like I can't even I
can't give you anything I just want to watch I don't even care about anything
else this is like the most entertaining thing I just like watching him make his
own opinions here comes another attack oh we need houses actually oops this game
is so fucking funny all right I just want manner nothing too expensive we
need spare time spare time for second I thought they said spare tire all right
you get in there and fight all right he's already doing it good chain good
all right let him just do his thing keep the progress avenge your death or
no war warriors their beast seems to be aware of the teachings of war but
isn't wanted too far though we need actually do another couple he's gonna
become a super evil he's gonna go so evil um I don't think so maybe a little
hungry I could bring him food oh no no no no no no no no no no no no no you're
not no you're not no you're not no you're not no you're not no you're not
no you're not don't don't don't don't I have food wait wait wait wait wait stop
stop stop don't eat the villager just wait don't move don't eat the villagers
wait eat eat that back what's the lady in that let the lady in get in get the
lady in no I want you to walk no no no no no no no drop drop okay now get back
out there why did I teach him to hate trees I didn't he just does he saw me
throw a bunch of shit and now he hates to he hates everything here eat some
more food like that I need it all right now just hang out out here he watched me
throw shit and now he's always upset about everything how we doing we got
these houses right yep okay two villages one down here and one over here let's
make some do some impressive shit let's make a rest home right here where's the
best place for this probably like here right here okay rest homes soon all
Greeks shall lay down to rest the city is truly formidable if we do not put a
stop to this they will drain all our strength with their lies let's do a
let's get a market let's get some markets and shit out here that market
yeah nice nice and they scale the mountain I don't think so he's all right
over there right it'd be more influence let's do a smelter no waste what else
gives good a graveyard nobody wants a graveyard near them put it back here no
nobody wants a graveyard why are these people happy about a
graveyard avenge your death or no war warriors their beast seems to be aware
of the teachings of war these eating people the Greeks have a graveyard they
will need it gonna have some fun with that tree good the Greeks have a
graveyard they will need it to bury all the bodies that I've been sending their
way sick I'm this way right this way everybody you're next anymore let's get
more influence about a mansion let's get a mansion out here everybody loves
having a mansion in their neighborhood or dude I don't maybe they don't makes
your property value go way up and shit I don't know no mansion plant trees I will
I'll put one back here I'm gonna get a fresh batch of resources here too so
food and we have a surplus of food who's eating it who's eating all this food I
just had so much ratio is waiting at our borders for you to accept them 25,000
food thousand or 14 something welcome guys I'm gonna put a big farm over here
and why don't you guys get to work
you think I'm an old folks home there's a lot of old people okay now we need um
what do we need a some more I got or right I think I did almost out of 1600
all right let's get some trees planted I need or freeze good right yeah do you
all right he's getting attacked hold on let this fucking tree plant it no he's
all right he's given so much combat skill then you'll see he knows they know
how to fight their beast seems to be aware of the teachings of war on this
beam it's wild I can't believe it either okay I got a shitload of trees it's
having good time out in the yard yeah he is he's having a great time almost got
this one too and then I don't really do much for me I'm tired okay I think yeah
I think I can let you back in I can let him back in all right come back in um go
to sleep been out there long enough come on and you're gonna make that
villager better yeah get the go to free will you've done a lot of good work but
it's time for you to go to sleep get some rest but not even have a creature
done but I'm not even build one I don't even have one I do don't I don't have a
creep oh fuck it's not that's not it all right back here it's not enough rooms
the perfect place for it there there is their creature wants a home this shows
weakness but an awful father I know that's bad it's very bad
go okay there's your home go use it go sleep can even get there go inspect it
you can't get there you see well you've blocked the path with so many trees he's
blocked he's uprooted every single tree to a point where he can't move okay good
now get in get some sleep Greek lies the other town I got it very good
close-up shop give me all your stuff appreciate it I have upgrades 44,000 I
don't think I can do mine I can do a prison shield naming fountain rename any
member of your tribe all them impressiveness mighty column show how
elegant and impressive your city is yeah let's do it fertility statue inspire
the population increase the birth rate the meadow enhancement of the town yeah
let's get some of these enhancements you're gonna nap in the storehouse you
have a bed I where are they need a road going over here it's a block by trees
shouldn't be I what do they have for resources go to sleep now the way that
they do it are they having I think they're having sex and they're not
sleeping let the mighty hurricane do the work of our sorts but mighty one why are
you guys going the long way here okay I was gonna say mighty hurricane wait does
have spells migration is waiting at our borders for you to accept them 20,000
nine okay get on in all right it's time for another storefront over here I hear
lightning and shit what's this the seven samurai legend it is said that seven
brave samurai were turned into statues by an evil entity that's it just one
sentence we need some impressive shit meadow all right we're gonna put a meadow
down here I put it like over here yeah that's fine it's on a slight incline
that's okay excuse me pissed him off all right just stop doing that rotate all
right go will you go to go to bed go to bed too many trees in the way can you
knock it down there I can't get there shit really yes you can how can you not
get over there just walk it in there and go to sleep stay in here for a little
bit I can't get in there but he can't get through this no really why is it
still here okay going in an infinite throwing what we still can't get in yeah
I get materials for this right I better I you don't get a refund get rid of this
throw it here I'll help you there is this no don't eat it I'm quite sad
I'm just charcoal and wooden sticks he's gonna puke I'm gonna crush that
villager like a bug why what villager who and why there's no villager even over
here he's delusional he's on he's on drugs he's on drugs no stop okay no go
relax somewhere you've given me you've given me and also okay I got side yeah
you can just go back out there just have fun
went you both fucking bloodlust okay what's going on over here we will avenge
your death or normal warriors their beast seems to be aware of the teachings
of impressiveness how can this be all right now he's hungry what toy
take this take this and eat it hey this you don't take this take this thing take
it come on take it eat it yes good good good good okay have fun goodbye that
him to free will he's not free will he gets to do whatever he wants we'll check
back on him later I need to build some stuff need more we got to start to go
forward I think because there's nothing else to get the only thing that's left
to get is to continue up this way but I guess I could maybe get all this I'm
going to go smash that like button if I get enough influence here maybe they'll
join but I don't know I'm out of materials what's the play here if I'm
out of materials do I have to just make some military and try to go forward and
try to take one of these other towns that are up here good all they have so
much military just plant trees it's free send in the cow press the village all
right let me I just unlock some new things where are they well all of them
how much does this cost I mean these are tiny just put them everywhere should I
just put these fucking everywhere how much they cost 150 or ah that's not good
not the old folks home pressiveness looking for cheap impressive shit 100
that's a well or that's too much average is not doing that towards your
pit stop stop moving to the right and left oh these are 20 and free yeah but
I need to have a place to put them okay so I'm just gonna build a shitload of
houses I'm gonna build a shitload of just crappy houses and plant trees all
over you going up a little too far here is you don't have to go up this far that
was nuts they just got killed against the fucking wall okay all right that's
the strategy that's what I'm gonna do it begins the cheapest house I can buy
that's like a hundred wood we will avenge your death or noble warriors
their beast seems to be aware of the teachings of war let's go that is no way
for a warrior to live doesn't matter let's go give me the wood I'm gonna
start a train give me a ton of wood let's go scam train incoming I'll
connect all this later when I have more of an idea of what's going on the road
will be going this way and I'll connect up to this road why am I getting
negative impressive points for this why is this negative because I have
mansions hey let's connect to the road I didn't want to do that but it's okay
all right keep going nice dude gone the thing is it just would and then I was
gonna put trees fucking okay along every row and people will be so impressed
that I was able to build 500 houses in 30 minutes I'll get it don't I'll get
your food on all right let's pause for a second let's get some food going I got I
want another storehouse door house is going over here
nobody lives in this one it's okay all right tree time you ready but let's get
a road out here first oh boy I can't get a road out here and I it's just too big
oh come on I gotta make a smaller I gotta get rid of the farm and then make
it a different I know it sucks but I have to I can't everything has to be
connected I can't why what are you talking about what are you talking about
what are you talking about why not what's the problem is there's like a
level feature or something where I can just smack down all this bullshit oh come
on it's right there just jump just fucking jump just jump no I want the one
behind it how is this one not worth 20 points
enough big enough why will I avenge your death for noble warriors their beast
seems to be aware of the teachings of what his mirror is doing this be a
grinding XP go I have a ton of trees that are not doing anything over here
same go to munch on those trees imagine if I met just planting trees and it's
enough to make everybody love you I guess that actually is kind of accurate
though like we got to protect these fucking things you know I mean that's
pretty admirable all along the wall too oh yeah it was okay how long do I have
to do this for he's like hey let me in forever oh I wonder what games was it
sometimes I do stuff with trees whatever man is there a way I can look to see if
this is working or do I just have to assume this is gonna work
I'm speaking for the trees I guess I'll poop on the trees good that's
fertilizer jingle for his jester now I don't think it will I don't think it will
kill jet you can't kill me I have I have a pardon from the king he's the one that
gets to tell if that happens or not and he hasn't decided that sorry how much
impressiveness do I have to say putting fucking freeze down I'm no better than
Murius right now that's all I'm doing what is this doing for me fourteen
thousand impressive is required to capture so I need five thousand more
impressiveness this shit's gonna take all day I'm not there's no room to get
five thousand points for this it's 250 more trees it's time to go to war
forget about the trees forgot it's time to go to war I'm not planting 300 trees
I don't even have enough or to do this though I will avenge your death or no
warriors their beast seems to be aware of the teachings of war stopped how can
this be how many people can I make it's curious I can make 235 men no saves
going I'll save it right here I think I might be screwed though new military
option yeah I might be in trouble I guess you only have that one mine at the
very beginning of the game if you don't you gotta only build stuff that but if
there's no or for the whole game then you're just supposed to try to make
impressive shit to influence everybody I guess yeah I told you I told you right
when you started I said it in the chat with four thousand fucking people hi why
did you not see this I am upset with you how dare you you read it out loud I
didn't you read it out loud when I said it I didn't you don't have proof you
don't have fucking proof you wrote it we wrote it four thousand times that's
fucking really funny I like that a lot that's awesome
very very resorts to lying to save face cut that shit up no no no no listen to
me you got to listen to me I'm the fucking one that's right
just don't listen to anybody else only me you might actually have to restart
actually kind of good that you brought these out here this is actually working
maybe I don't think I have to restart hold on what is impressive that's made
out of wood 4700 paper um yeah I might be I think I'm fucked uh meadow what's
him how much is metal doesn't do much okay impressive just 40 the villa it's
wood or or to my left where what do you mean where
tavern is only wood is it just make a shitload of bars down here 200
impressiveness oh yeah let's go everyone's gonna be shitfaced no no
restarting coming right up I'll get there real soon
zero link good good good good good this is gonna be a bar build eight TGI Friday
TGF right sucks I don't why would I want that avenge your
death or no war warriors their beast seems to be aware of the teachings of
war how can this be TGI Friday's Chili's and Outback are all the same restaurant
that they painted over new signs on oh I didn't say that they I didn't say
Chili's was bad I just said well yeah I did although well wait wait wait I will
I will rephrase my statement here let me let me make this very clear
does Chili's still have the you go in and get the two entrees for one deal is
that still happening it's like 20 bucks for two fall entrees they still do that
and people go in there and they order them for themself it's supposed to be
two people split them but people go in and just get four entrees two for 22 yeah
okay all right then it's that's cool pretty cool all right what do I need now
what about University are we doing 39 74 to impress where is that time where is
ego ego maniac bar on every single corner this is messed up but whatever
we're taking down every tree to put bars unlimited starters is a scam what do you
mean oh is there anything else more efficient than this well I'm getting
diminishing returns oh okay I am shit I'm getting diminishing returns what
else is there alter 3,000 would 700 impressiveness I actually do have to do
take care of food I'm gonna build a storehouse over here we I'm gonna
actually make this work okay let me make this work I'm gonna build a storehouse
now I have to we have to have something going on over here this is just all
fucked up if I don't do this how much is the storehouse it's just wood okay we
need that over here somewhere down here and we have to I gotta stop building
some farms and shit behind everything wood are you crazy bar 5 has the best
cocktails right arm let's get a granary out here too I'm working on it stop
screaming at me they care about feeding their people it's screamed at any food
but I'm getting yelled at I told you I told you that we needed food like 30
minutes ago no you didn't actually yes I did actually you read it out loud you
just said it I didn't know what the fuck are you talking about or still have a
little bit of war left don't I just enough 500 Murius is up there he's up
there just causing fucking problems oh stop I know first it's food then it's
or then we need now we need houses and now we need food and now we need a
torture pit to throw people in these are all really good South Park tray Parker
voices they're actually pretty good all right let's get some good or a stir no
farm use multi-pick for people I know I'm sorry I know I don't even I didn't
even know that existed it's like you act like somebody told me to that that to do
that and that I've seen it I haven't I didn't know that existed come on they
off they did you don't have any proof you're being a bully I'm just fucking
kidding I'm just kidding live out loud with me all right what we got I'm getting
there I don't have any more or how much is University too much that's very
impressive though this is not that impressive this is very impressive it's
a lot of wood let's get let's get it up here and he can actually make it to this
one he can actually come over here and sleep here classic just a joke jock
fully feed Murius how is Mary is doing he's eating he's resorted to eating
trees oh no he's allergic he's doing just fine all right you know what come
back in he's got to come back in and sleep and shit he can't just he's got a
rest come in yes you can just go over here he needs her to rest he's just all
fucked up okay come back over here I got a pen for you going up go over here make
it however you need to make it 766 I'm getting close tons of wood only 2,000
more to take over this time how we doing on food not great actually got a lot
of people just fucking standing around if I'm honest how many farmers can be on
here at once whatever okay what else is impressive that I can build lumber mill
or retirement home it's only 300 or rest home is only 300 or 500
impressiveness no I could do some more trees do a carnival big old metal right
next to the cow pen big old metal big old metal okay you got it big old metal
right here big old meadow all right yes King thank you constantly gonna be
replacing these because of him where did that to go we're almost there it's oh
these throw that into the storehouse planted in the way from his pen have a
good people using it there's people hanging out here people are doing it
it's working okay now let's um all right or people in the
meadow ethics the most powerful of miracle is an epic to cast one of these
you must first build a wonder yeah I'm not gonna be doing that right now did
you know miracles epics yeah I don't have any epics it is time to make our
stand warriors this day you fight for honor and for our lives coming in attack
I got a gate man you can't get in give a siege weapon no the fuck do I have to
worry about okay how close are we to impressiveness 1823 we need some more
impressive shit another what do I have for or actually 1350 is it time for an
army well is an army impressive is having soldiers impressive I don't have
enough food for this though no just make babies you want archers on the gatehouse
I need food first though archers on the wall archers on the wall they can eat
off food who's it not farming everyone over here seems to be farming too old
term I hate babies well I distraction it's a distraction no I want you to do
far water this shit I can do this so much better than all of you can come on
you know there's like 15 of you on the field sleep and free time well how do I
make people go to sleep how do I make people have free time
sleep and free time like why won't they go to bed free time impossible free
sleep but how come they're not going to sleep what about a wall no I need or
market need or siege workshop is not that impressive ranged armory is not
that impressive breathe them if you want them to stop crying
zero a can like free them from their work I mean it's people in there
drinking that is it is deleted that person so who should work and who
shouldn't work I don't know who's hasn't been working who to how can I tell if
somebody's been at the bar for five days versus somebody's been working all
night 14,000 all right I need like another 1500 time this bar is everywhere
there's a bar every 10 feet please enjoy them what is this all right what's the
seven samurai thing build them on the other side of town oh shit yeah it's
going up the tower is going up thank God this one right here is outside the gate
of waiting more food what we got sleep and free time sleep free time and food
1640 impressiveness 1640 where do we get that another altar just a creature pen
back here fun is it mean I do want more than a few places room to be that's
worth a lot it's only wood there's only one creature pen even if he can't get to
it there we go we're good I would with where's Murius at the cow entertain
people all right it's 500 well entertaining people bring impressiveness
would it all right let's put him in the middle and is having been entertain
everybody where is he thought there was a fire around him I was about to say
what the fuck are you doing healing is impressive I mean that's pretty pretty
impressive I don't think I'm getting points for it though you know what else
is impressive is throwing fireballs over a gate will that work about watering
plants like any less than a thousand which means 900 and I'm and I take over
that time all right I'm doing I'm making I'm making archers we're gonna make
archers the camp over here and I'm gonna try to put them on the wall I don't know
if I have enough to do that nice let's hope I do I need a road over here 500
or okay I have been too patient send the armies out and we claim our land how
impressive is this 46 points and impressiveness let's put some marches in
the wall what was fucking nothing oh no I have to replant my trees so I'll play
scary music that was all bark and no bite now I know what you're capable of
and let me tell you not very impressive not very impressive at all they seek to
conquer us to send our warriors out the last guy I fought had a god that came
out and turned every single person in my whole city against me and they've ran
away from me you just gave the amount of wind that we get like typically like on
a Sunday afternoon didn't nothing even happen back in business you'll be check
it out and I got food here okay so let's get these they're already going for it
they hitting anything guys guys hold on hold on it's free kills don't even need
Murius okay now we're almost at a level of impressiveness that is
unsurmountable we need where's that I already take it where is it where's um
that was that town EGA what happened to EGA they're on their way are they from
where oh they're right there you guys were a long way away is this EGA what
you I gotta protect them they got a free run they'll be alright look I have
archers just killing them they can't even do anything all right man let me
let's start I'm gonna start smashing food water I'm gonna do my own props
check this out let's get this happening more it's gonna get used pretty quickly
but I'm gonna stockpile it useful powers oh my sorry just look at how it's
getting eaten before I can even do anything about it you're coming no no
don't gather the grain put grain in Murius put grain in get out of the way
let's do let's do like it let's do that two or three more times got a lot of
population increases impressiveness burning through so much food right now
though I got a I gotta get a good like baseline food okay that should be alright
for a little while at least for now in fact here you guys are on your own now
but just take another miracle or two where do these trees come from is this
been planting trees over here all right we need 35 we got I think we have two
different groups coming over this way is one is there more than one coming or is
it just that one I thought there were two that were really close to each other
all right more houses let's put some houses down here wood-based houses only
let's get some breeding going pregnancies come on I haven't kids
nursery I'll put a nursery down here too population is impressive just go to war
I don't know I can't from a message is poor what are you talking about what
message you talking about the most recent message it's time for it's just a joke
times a thousand but the last message I'm just trying to make children for God's
sake this is where we have to really really start to go nuts because I they
still alive out here all right Marius I know you think it's very funny I'll put
that back don't kill all the children in the nursery with a tree it's not funny
Marius it's not funny Marius I need you out here on your I need you to fight
because I'm gonna get a new I don't want them to get killed I want them to come
in safely let's get back over here was this because that is the way this guy
didn't read the message didn't read the message and I laughed so fucking hard no
no more throwing stop stop stop healing people of what is going on he's
throwing them backwards I think he healed the guys on the rafters I have no
idea I closed the gate perfect timing don't bounce into the wall please good
all right there they are it's time to increase our impressiveness hopefully
they get here before this come on hurry up in fact Marius just go meet them out
there don't meet them halfway there's old people there's old people and
children you have to meet them halfway how come this be what's that he's gonna
kill this lady here oh he missed them oh my god thank God okay at least the kid
got out the kid got away come on keep going guys okay the kid got away good
they have trebuchets up top too all right move move move get out I welcome
you open the door let them in free will okay let's let them in I don't want you
to no no no I don't want you to eat a village of them we have to show them
that we're nice people he's planted so many trees out here look at all this
bullshit if they're fucking everywhere he was out here just bored planting trees
let them in holy shit that was 20,000 or no you're not gonna eat a bill I get
it's got a lot of or where's the hurricane I hope he misses I hope it's
like an incorrect and it just goes like the wrong way wait a minute who the
fuck are you who's this motherfucker various various turn on the fucking hate
turn on the hate Murius it's time for you to go kick ass look at out look at
us so much bigger than him he is nothing to you yeah he's running away look at
him he's cute he looks like you it looks like you before the gym yeah I get the
fuck out of here he's running away him all the way down here to see all right
I'm gonna make a ton of archers because I have the ore for it now I need to have
some defense oh my god yes yes yes yes yes yes let's put like let's put like
70 fucking archers up here no one will ever get in and then now let's also we
got to have some more food here oh well it's how we doing now we need 3,200 to
get the next town we need some impressive shit all right what's it
what's really impressive universities oh yeah oh yeah yeah yeah no not a torture
device universities we will get so many towns right there boom there will be
much for us to learn from this university I'm just gonna build like
three of these and we'll take it that's it it's over I win check this out 1200
here comes another group we get another nut well that's build like two more of
these university with put one over here there's a ton of houses over here we
need a good place for it yeah like minus 71 that's a little minus
too close to shit is 1200 we go put it right here we've taken over the town yes
we have violence is not the answer unless they come to you and Murius kills
probably four to five hundred people I can't wait to see the end of this one
because Murius probably has like 600 kills this game we get there they go
they're done guys there's only like three towns left to take before the big
one feed the soul of our land with Greek blood it was he just making shit up when
he said he was gonna fire the time to save yeah get him on the walls get on
is this a penis stream yeah dude yeah hey welcome hey welcome to the penis
stream yep here yeah that's what I'm glad you came here here we go
let's give a ton of subs ready dread just give a shitload of subs holy fuck
Freddy thanks for the insane amount of subs 50 community subs 50 50 subs 50
subs 50 subs give a hundred yesterday holy shit Freddy you've given this
stream so much fucking money thanks seriously there are all right I'm almost
got the next one more universities let's make another college ready another
fucking 50 subs you fucking mad man you're mad mad man a hundred more he's
mad thank you dude thanks a lot dude that's fucking insane yes it's actually
Freddy dread and I'm ha I'm thanks a lot dude that's fucking awesome 25 more subs
from Freddy dread already dread just dumping it just dumping them 75 fucking
subs just no nothing more than that a hundred and twenty five huge and insane
amount just huge dodged yeah that's pretty pretty good dodge five don't and
not to be overshadowed lobster just gave five community subs to thank you guys
thanks both of you Murius they're never gonna get in and I'm just gonna
continue to influence behind my giant wall and I need another university we're
gonna put it over here 1200 minus 96 though here we go I know this diminishing
returns but it's okay cuz this is a huge boost 225 community subs from Freddy
dread this week this bonkers thanks a lot dude scam train I don't have them
turned on just pretend like we're doing one right now I need a little more or
that was the game saver right there I'll tell you taking that town and not giving
up I was gonna restart the mission I didn't have to hurt anybody I didn't
have to hurt a single person wait but wait 500 subs 500 subs holy shit you
know what that means that duck penis stream all right thanks for the 500
subs that's what it means you came to the right stream you came to a penis
stream okay guys here we go hope you get get your pogs ready get your pogs
ready okay get your pogs ready get your pogs is it working can you hear that oh
okay get your get your pogs ready get your pogs it's time for a penis stream
you know what that means it's time that's the face you make a pigeon flies
down when you're eating the lunch and flies into your face
Freddie Dredge just gave a fucking ton of money
Freddie Dredge just gave 110 dollars in bits he just gave 11,000 bits I have to
pause the game things like pause love you German man hope you having a good
stream got paid today so I'm giving back seems like you got some it seems like
you got some paper there you got some cash holy shit man seriously thank you
wink scammed hold on first of all I can I not have like dickhead hair I tried to
fix it and it has made it worse penis hair 225 subs in hundreds of dollars in
bits penis hair doesn't make any sense all right you don't stop getting me banned
from twitch okay where's this where's the other there's two groups that are
coming down I got this one we got that one no violence penis hair does not make
sense I didn't I'm didn't say it I was responding to somebody else that said
that's strange I agree with you dude I'm gonna take over everything it's all
gonna be mine what else has huge impressiveness I'm just gonna start
building columns these are these what a hundred each how much or they 150 and
it's a hundred it's 80 I think I can do it right now games oh sorry is this
worth doing you think but I gotta do it I gotta do a test run here I've gotta do
a test run test run like the movie about the blue animal when they released the
first trailer and people weren't happy with it it was sort of a test but the
future and then they ended up changing it into the what the character is now
it's then progressed into from what I've heard one of the what is it s comment
is really here oh sorry you had to be here four and a half hours ago look at
these fucking furious go here and eat all these fucking bodies I was sick all
right can I beat this I've only got okay but you're distracting me stop
distracting me I'm busy if you don't see on your damn screen hey you boy 10
community subs thanks a lot you boy thanks for the 10 77 all right it's not
80 thanks to the 10 subs 75 it's still worth doing for a little bit
74 okay hold on oh wait wait wait wait wait wait wait this is the okay these
are this column city it's not worth it is it how much is university worth I
have to I used points you have I have you have to look at this university is
worth like 700 it's like it's 500 or for a university are they here they're not
here yet they'll be here in a second somebody it's definitely more cost
effective to do this at least for now a couple more universities and put some
more houses all right I gotta give her something Muris his trees he went way
overboard just overboard 578 okay I've been 78 it's 500 or to do it I'm on what
I almost got another town what else had to I not have like diminishing returns
of 1500 or but it's probably gonna be at least it'll be probably it'll be a lot
let's move up it'll be like probably 1200 we'll put in a temple here I'm
gonna put another wall up here yeah it's gonna be a wall before the wall it's
like it'll be like when you go with the guys like the hazmat suits go into like
the room before the room and like the team goes on them which I'm not sure
where that was of the antibacterial agent I don't even know if that's
supposed to be don't kill them please I got so many arches they're not gonna do
shit didn't have anything they didn't have anything they had nothing and 160
they had 160 pieces of snacks really all right sorry no you're welcome everyone's
welcome come on except except for that guy that guy's running very fast well
that guy please okay somebody kill that guy hang out out here at Muris and need
more all right I'm kind of what do I have I've got 14,000 or I need like 300
hope this is worth it 619 I got another town coming in though Mr. Wink this time
I gotta get rid of these trees we're gonna build houses up here all right I
need another wall wall wall quickly before they get here sorry it'll be up
when they did not they got how much what do you got for food 10,000 hundred and
hundred and two thousand food Muris where are you going what's he up to what
Muris we'll get back here he's drunk I just stay here for now Jesus are we gonna
get this built I want this up immediately get this built I want it
built immediately I got this one Muris you know what to do keep building keep
building now we need houses Muris you go build this don't take care of this
yes Muris make it what do I need or needed 259 I got that I got that thing
build it you go good yeah he's trapped on the other side but is this big enough
to where's Josh where's the door what's Josh where's the door just build this I
might be able to do it from here it's right there to break and Josh when this
is built up I shoot I can do that right I've never even seen that episode night
like I know what happens in that episode you know I'm saying I don't know you're
talking about but God I do I know what you mean something he gets stuck they
make like a plan to build like something I already know what it is
hurry up and build this fucking thing God just watch that clip what does it
called like Drake and Josh like stuck in Drake and Josh Drake and Josh stuck
door where's the door where's the door hole goes right there see I drew it with
a magic marker you were supposed to cut it out with the power saw dude I'm gonna
oh really yes so go get the power saw okay I will I see the problem oh do
yeah classic scene I was gonna say is it a
treehouse it's a treehouse right
god damn it god damn it that was like 500 or two if it comes down to if it
comes down to I need 500 or to beat this level you know where I'm gonna be
screaming you know I'm gonna be screaming here okay do it again don't
know big enough yes it is it's big enough it's big enough it's big enough
it's big enough we're good link descending everybody pull back pull back
pull back pull back oh he can't he has to fight for his life out here build it
lightning he was so concerned about that guy
eel nice where's he going stop stop stop stop gone so far a man is falling into
the river oh no let go extravaganza this still just feeding people down here I
hope and get this thing built so he can leave all right I need some more
impressive shit we need houses we need nice houses good houses cool houses
impressiveness we need impressive houses like mansion for instance 240
impressiveness a manor no just regular houses no too much or regular house
avenge your death or no warriors this is impressive I'm just me even putting
these here is impressive ain't it he's still going get the wall built so he'd
be done he's just on he's on a rampage he can't be stopped although I want that
tiger to come down and I want to throw a rock and hit him in the face and it's to
kill him I wanted to be running down and I wanted to throw the rock and just
instant death you need to eat some shit it you're gonna eat some people what
fire he's good all right this is almost done build help them build if you could
I need uh you pick this up is it big enough rock to do like damage to a
tiger's head and brain anything minus 87 no no no no no no no stop building
these stop building these enough no no no no no oh my god oh my god oh my god
it's all right 584 and I get the next village what build villas well weren't
those villas 40 to 80 is that 40 minus 89 it's got to be something nicer it's
got to be like mansions for manners right 120 minus 86 build a metal I got
a metal right here this is 700 rest home it's 500 what's
going Murius what he's staring at why is he's getting hit like what are you
doing fight back fight back fight back let's have a stomach ache free will
fight watch out for the workers stick connected to this rock build that thing
will avenge your death or no war warriors build this wait a minute wait
a minute wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute right this we're gonna
break this oh I hit it too I fucking smashed it he's got to throw it he's
gonna do something so what what's going on over here what's going on over here
oh this motherfucker this motherfucker I need rough Murius come here I got
something for you various take this rock and I want you to throw this rock over
here throw it over there get the rock throw the rock over there
okay you'll throw trees but you won't throw a rock fine just get get over
here I need you to stay leashed over here so you don't die okay just why did
it bounce why did this shit just bounce direct hit you gotta be fucking kidding
me we will avenge your death got it yes what the fuck man God it's dead all
right build okay they just continue to feed troops
I'm so fucked all right I need to start building something now thirty four
thousand it's impressiveness 180 or impressive something impressive 200 or a
lamp not that impressive voodoo doll not that impressive hey what are you doing
hey he was trying to get out you want to get out and get out wanna go I think
about all right I'll be right back and take out
you
okay I'm back I'm ready to finish this
and a little bit more
tribute and we need to build this fucking wall
we good save it because I haven't done that in a long time
sorry Otto had to go I do and I he's got an even better I want his tiger to come
down here don't you I want the target to come down I want to fight the tiger
we will avenge your death honorable warriors their beast seems to be aware
of the teachings of war how come this be right they've actually why do I feel
like no one's doing anything here this there's been no progress on this wall
they've made a skeleton or was it because there's no or over here big bits
oh I get to it in one second like what's the problem somebody do this
don't really build the fucking wall anyways carry carry USA way carry USA
way thank you for the it's carry us away yep okay I'm just coming to that
realization right now it's not carry USA way thanks for the 5,000 bits if the
doll is a lot of $50 drops tonight which is crazy here we've been following
you country for eight years now that's a long time never been disappointed it's
so easy to tell how much you care about your community and your content I'm
super hyped for the GameCube streams coming up me too
Super Mario Sunshine is by far my favorite Mario game art it's fucking
fantastic it's never just because I just finished the wall everyone's fucking 80
years old why are you all so old hold on I got distracted that's why it's not
getting built because everyone working on it is fucking a hundred Super Mario
Sunshine is my favorite Mario game any chance you get Super Smash Brothers
melee probably not I mean I didn't play ultimate I didn't play brawl on yeah I
can't do it anymore I can't play those games anymore well that's one way to
clean up fighting games for me or I've become so bad at them and I don't play
enough to it's just it's not good it's an embarrassment when I play I still
have trouble doing regular smashes and stuff anyways want to say love you dude
love you man I honestly see you like the older brother I never had love you too
chat hey look at they look at how much they like you too come on you're a
fortnight streamer now thank you for the huge amount of money and the GameCube
screams should be pretty fun I'm looking forward to it especially Chibi
Robo you finally did it nice work Chibi Robo got you force those are the two
that I'm most looking forward to we get this fixed all right can you please come
through the door yeah a GameCube is one of those systems
Murius are you fucking kidding me dude get it built quick why is he so itchy
I'm going to poo on their defenses why is he so itchy he's so he's got like
fleas build he's allergic to doing work what do you want to do Murius what do
you want to do I don't understand what's going on with him
is there a vet with the best holy shit what the fuck was that it's the scariest
thing I've ever seen in my life it's a solution it's a solution I put a tree
there it's I blocked it see oh he's so fucking funny that's so fucking
ridiculous I'm trying to wash him Murius you don't get it that's not how you put
a wall be careful this is hurting yes hi it's because he ate I was gonna let
him do his thing oh give him a snack I need to get him out of the way he's not
he's got easy he's just gone he if this is work will they not be able to get
through the wall is this is this gonna work just okay you're good you're good
you're good you good come over here just go be nice to you did a good job oh my
god he's obsessed he's blocked himself get movies uh no more trees Murius
please okay close the door don't let him back in finally is he gonna go to the
bathroom this is a forest he made he said to take his shit for two hours oh
my goodness bit slave came in with another $50 huge ridiculous large money
they say didn't know thank you but that's a huge amount of fucking money
thanks dude finish the wall it's it's uh it's done this wall the wall is done
well it's done I'm gonna let Murius do what he wants here and that's how he
decided to finish it okay so they say I didn't know you're gonna play be
streaming GameCube games I love playing the GameCube with my brothers thinking
about it makes me sad that we're in different parts of the world and only
see each other on the holidays if we're lucky please you give me play League of
Legends on the GameCube I'm gonna shit my pants all right uh I'm kidding but
for real please play Majora's Mask it's my favorite it always scared the shit
out of me I had to build up courage to play it game on gamer you're a league of
legend legend of League I think we're gonna keep your account banned is what
needs to happen your account has to stay banned okay what's the where am I
finally all right this is okay it's like you walked into like little Timmy's
room and there's toys everywhere there's dirt all over the ground like there's
six animals there's like four frogs just jumping around this soil on the ground
it's like what the fuck is going on here and it's like well we have this we have
this parenting that we do with little Timmy it's called like we just kind of
let him do whatever he wants he's a free spirit that's what this is hey and Timmy
like walks out he's got like four pairs of socks on he's got like his dad's
boots on get two different hats on get a green shirt and like bright red shorts
he's got like Christmas decorations all over him and he's like hey like hey hey
how are you and he just hey he has a plate of food of like spaghetti and he
just goes mom he just dumps it on his head and fucking like wags around like a
dog and goes all over the walls and like hits like mom in the face and dad in the
face and they're just like oh okay right on Timmy that's what is happening
right now I have blood I've data control look what I've done he doesn't know
it's trees yes free will okay what do I have in my hand this is fucking too
funny I have to like I gotta I gotta like relax this is the best part of the
whole stream this right here like the last two straight days this is just it's
doing it for me all right hold on let me just I got it I got a text let me look
at it it's texting Kim hold on Kim has a question I'm just responding okay so we
need influence these there's somersault into the building and smash it okay I'm
all fucked up right now let's put some food in impressive shit let's get some
food built up that's what I want my god get some food I still have some ore so
that's good all right that's not bad thank you Murius appreciate it you still
have a good stronghold here how many more do I need what do I need for
impressive only 268 I take another town which is as simple as putting up a
couple of we should do houses homes what do I need though probably another
another storefront with a farm over here farm right here storefront the trees do
it with trees I mean okay I mean you can't beat him join him right you can't
beat him join him he's one whom I can he's just gonna pull these up at least
he gave me plenty to choose from that's not it have we not gotten another town
the northern outpost has fallen they will pay for this Wow that's a big town
to take that's a big town to take I'm gonna get a lot of resources for that
one are you harassing the archers up here leave them alone they're working
next up on the list is 4600 I'm gonna go out this way because we there's a ton of
space out here that I haven't done like over here so let's build some which I
do out here put a rest home out here this is kind of uninhabitable isn't it
what do you guys got the wood over here good next to the bars yeah whatever I
would be good for enough 300 in here this 1900 in here nice 400 keep building
and this level kill them all I'm don't think I'm gonna need to put another
university down here or field university I can't believe he's still evil in the
pacifist run well it's because like I told you at the end of this whole thing
we're gonna see potentially hundreds of kills so I'm not being evil but I am I
am bring over like 5,000 more shit over here cuz I know I'm gonna want other
stuff built so let's put it down there's wood I'm not evil but I am 620 getting
there I have 34,000 what is impressive fertility statue kind of impressive hot
market actually pretty impressive 400 it's only 300 300 let's do it let's do
like two or three of these put them over here scatter them around hot market
where is it plant market where the heck am I stupid hot market there it is all
right let's get it in here where can I stick it right there and I can't get it
right over there 400 minus 29 is next to a bar minus whatever you know minus 60
minus 37 no no no over here plus 39 get it another one okay it's a god game yeah
it's a game you play as a god your goal is to influence people around you or kill
them and take over their cities you also have a companion that does everything
that you tell the two for the most part 379 that's 6 but just about 800 let's do
more of those let's put one of those up here boom another one come on that's
plus 75 give it to me that's 100 plus 161 get it right about more I am I am
don't worry I'm going for it 406 stunning wood on the other one here I
gotta remember where these piles are 28 I gotta be getting close to the one of
the last towns all right I'm gonna put the next one up here oh that's a good
spot right there that's a good spot no statue market or 100 plus 199 plus 200
I'm gonna pick it all up plus 200 600 wait how close are we 946 and then the
last thing is just the last town and then I will just spam columns until I
read this read this I read it oh you got me oh you got me plant market right
about plant market what under here a migration is waiting at our borders
yeah uh-huh here comes another one so they have taken one of our outposts this
insolence shall not go unpunished who's at the door a lot of people come on in
hello and welcome 5,000 20,000 20,000 that's game over that's actually game
over they there this is the where their last town is right here I'm gonna take
it I'm gonna just the enemy crumbles under our strength we shall drive them
out close the gate close close close close close close close the door close the
door thank God I have archers up here sorry they don't stand a chance we're
good yeah but what am I concerned about various just forget it do whatever the
hell you want oh that's an entire army coming Murius no no no Murius get over
here we got a fucking fun thing going on we got rocks to throw Murius get over
here I'm telling you this fucking tons of people throw rocks up nice wall
Murius I'm gonna get angry how many can fit can they all of them get on here
okay this this three people in here well are they all just sitting up here his
renders three okay Murius I need you over here we also have but we have
another they're coming with everything we have another migration coming but it's
time just I'm gonna win by the love of the people
Murius is so strong I want Murius to one-on-one fight that motherfucker you
hang out in here Murius just for now at least where is this creature is once
this goes oh boy okay we need to fix this don't we they're coming in why did
you do that fine eat them is it hurricane we need rocks Murius find me a
rock furious take this check this out I want to bring as many rocks as I can
over here how do you break up rocks like can I break this up double tap yeah I'm
against a wall I'm not gonna do this against the wall I think that actually
fixed it if I'm gonna be honest with you I don't think they can get through this
pretty sure that actually makes it better all right I need more
impressiveness like glorious impressiveness okay what do we need to do
down here I need a bunch of shit so I just start spamming columns just call
it a night really get in there okay we need stone give me some stone please I
want to have some fun with that tree 28 so really it's just a it's a it's a race
right now to try to get is more influence than I I need 7,000 influence
and I win that's like four universities I'm gonna do that temple I'm doing a
temple right here or a creature den I think I'm gonna do a creature den so he
has a place to sit right here so he can rest yeah that's the play that's the
play you put one right in here right there perfect look this trees around to
help me do this I didn't need to go get wood 336 not that much but that's not I
didn't do it for the money now you I need you to rest up because we got quite
a big day tomorrow as you see the there's thousands of people at that wall
I'm gonna be torching them with explosives as you know a big day
tomorrow hot market I want to pop market in here another graveyard probably huh
get the graveyard away from everybody no they want it they like it they don't
hate this they don't hate this yeah sure let's go right here I don't hate you
Jeremy where the fuck are the droop crews tonight ah they couldn't show up
sorry try to tell you I thought you saw this would give us big 600 yep all right
there's got to be a final battle before I take all of his people from him right
then these guys aren't gonna get slaughtered are they oh yeah looks like
you've grown up a little looks like you've grown up a little isn't that just
interesting isn't that interesting hmm Murius I feel okay go have some fun they
preparing for a final battle this is final battle to me it's about four or
five hundred people but what they don't realize is every single one of them is
going to die in one hit I'm gonna roll a fireball across everybody and I'm
surprised I haven't done it yet you know I'm just kind of seeing if they
put it enough how many people they put here it comes Helms deep I gotta be
careful opening this door what's the final number I need six forty seven make
sure we get plenty of rocks over here okay we're good
why the animals in here 20,000 15,000 more favor all right get over the door
doesn't work I'm ready for this okay there we go no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no stay here stay least of this rock oh the tiger oh what I'm
sorry the tiger wants to come in close the door close the door close the door
close the door is that fucking tiger oh sneaky huh sneaky like to come over say
to my face I'll let you in one-on-one nobody will hit you nobody will shoot
you I promise one-on-one
the gate is closed come on tiger oh no close the gate clip mom your east kick
his ass come on come on daddy's daddy I'll help you
daddy well what about your watch your back watch the backside fuck oh it
worked kill up the door open too far too far back
up
too far holy shit man that like huge butt drop on his face that was insane
Wow what a finish what a finish that's two-handed clap right there we had our
fun I'll get the fuck out of my land is that one gonna land oh and the back
fleet oh that's a bad one that's going right in the middle whoo whoo that's
rough wait I'm supposed to be the good guy right I'm supposed to be a good guy
how many points do I need I absolutely clowned on that tiger though let me be
honest oh now I need 90 oh no now I got to take it by force because of that well
you know times reload the saves come that which one was it 852 850 430 902
wait it's not even 902 right now it's 858 Pacific what 852 is this one right
yeah this is Maria game zero zero one we had a wink I'll get it right here
some primer shit save before I load that's not a bad idea just in case
something horrible happens we're gonna call this one post battle okay now let's
load game double oh one yeah cuz I'm playing this not military so that's
true I did kind of fuck it up are they charging all right so we're friendly
we're friendly close the inner gate we're fine so I just need like 4,000 more
favor 4,900 that's easy that's easy whatever you have your fun right when I
have all right let's let's do the favor route let's do the tribute route let's
just build some more shit over here I have plenty of resources now I have tens
of thousands of everything let's do what's the most impressive thing that I
can build but it's the most impressive thing pond pond universities has to be
I'm just it's I have so many schools schools are just everywhere this is the
most educated group Murius even gets his own school oh there's already he already
has his own school okay let's see what this but how far this gets us let's do
or first I forget where I put we now need to just simply put this back get
some wood was that was that lightning shit I need I'm gonna need like 10 20
thousand fine I'm looking forward to watching the VOD later hopefully there
are no dumbass winks oh there aren't I got rid of those if you see when it's
probably like a glitch on your computer I'd probably get a new computer if you
see one all right that was a lot more colleges all right I'm just I just so I
want to roll a boulder out the window 2,600 that's five six more colleges okay
you got it I got no more room for these colleges Beach College build a wonder I
don't have the I don't have the tribute to be able to research it all right let's
get a bunch of wood start the building process and win the game as my next
class is on campus 36 and it's 247 miles away sorry to hear that this would be
the first time ever I think I've ever completed a video game mission without
like cheese ball throwing rocks over wall right this is this is the first for
me this is pretty remarkable actually all right there's one two three four
isn't over here right got these ones okay I'm running out of room for
colleges so hopefully we're almost done wink redeemed all right I'm getting
close to having not enough to do this I went be so strong brother go through the
portal to our home he will surely go there next that's our captain you get
the two sides of the Japanese even with a god they will not succeed this is an
enemy worthy of respect but we shall be stronger when we next meet the war is
not over all right where's Waldo and what is Waldo doing where's Waldo what
is Waldo doing playing with trees yes that's correct you got it um so let's
save it I just beat this level I'm gonna save the game right here and then
I'm gonna go slaughter everybody and then we'll load it correctly and we'll
leave the mission you know just open the gate open the gate let them in hey
rematch this time no wait a minute no interference round two entertainment
only it's not entertainment that's not entertaining
Murius all right fine switch to fucking soldier get angry big right uppercut I
hope I hope he beats him and I hope he shits on him oh he missed the huge
uppercut come on you had it come on Murius you're getting caught in these
random oh that was a big miss there it is finish him finish him yes big finish
did you get this shit he said can I get a little privacy behind the tree
everything is a tree everything has to be used as a tree can you get a little
fine I'll give you some privacy look okay you had your fun good work now how
do we roll him into the water make it so he can't get up I'm a bit hungry that
was like yeah all right let's end it where's the scroll wait there's another
scroll over here I didn't even see it what is this free favor link hold on I'll
look at it and say
there is an ancient room hidden around the camp somewhere it will direct us to
where the mystical building is hidden let's begin our expedition I believe the
first of the rules we seek is very near to where we currently stand let me get
this link if you scrub the ground around the camp maybe you'll uncover it
hold on this is worth 40,000 there's a link let me check it out
it's perfect it's actually perfect
this is great
the blur
awesome it looks fucking great
uh do I even want to do this right now I don't think I want to do this right now
so did you get a scrub what do I have to do scrub no this is this is the mission right here
that's what you do
at the base of the tree
same person
when the sun is sleeping on the solitary rock
hmm I wonder what that means this is not the rock right here that's the big
floating thing that I was just over here where is it solitary rock um yeah but
that I mean any this whole thing is a rock we found it under the rock on the
rock yeah a point point to it point to it the whole planet's a rock the rock
that you tried to crush the villagers with yeah but it's that rock is gone the
rock does not where the fuck is it where is it it's the same area I was
just I was just spinning around in circles I don't know what the hell that
is right here the single rock over the hill on the coast this one right here
talk about this right here I can't move this okay I thought I was trying to get
on a what we are getting close to our goal now let's see what it says I thought
was gonna be on the rock the point between tasks passed what a bad game
like what about it what about it what a bad game it's not me it's the game is
bad what a bad video game God so annoyed by this video this game is so bad if
only it's not me everything else is fucking dumb not me of course not mad
because bad stop banning that I don't want to see that anymore I don't want to
see that again mad because bad no it's because the game is not very good
actually so what are you talking about okay fun honey really funny and mods are
doing it too yeah I'll see you guys in like three weeks I'm not streaming for
like another three weeks yeah no I'll see you guys like in a month I'm you
know no you're just doing a good job thanks I've never ever that meant that
I'm better I appreciate that that means a lot really okay yeah thank you is my
webcam like squished hold on something's weird with this webcam today
something's off about it what happened I like stretched it okay it was just ever
so slightly stretched like this it looks it looked I looked strange okay that was
something about that was fucking strange right it was like this I let's complete
this in uh I'm gonna be going to bed well not bad actually I need to get food
need to eat something we'll call it pretty much exactly at eight hours
McDonald's no no McDonald's none of that um all right I got forty thousand
favor right what what happened wait wait wait wait what happened here I wasn't
paying any and I mean a single fucking piece of attention is another one I
didn't even hear what they said what was the clue find the point between tasks
past hmm a difficult riddle point between tasks past point between tasks
past bad on purpose what what's going on we talking about between tasks past it's
like in here somewhere point between tasks past wouldn't be in the middle
of all these geometry he's actually pretending sad face I don't I wouldn't I
wouldn't even look at it anything how is this the middle didn't I already tried
this in this clearing he's the guy I already did it in here but he's actually
pretending just tell me where it is I don't I I could give a shit less about
what I'm doing right now triangle what it's the green patch on the hill this
point between tasks past that doesn't help me middle of a triangle turn on
click maps I can't cuz I can't all tab the game these are the tasks right here
in the middle point between tasks past wouldn't that be like right here or like
here I don't understand I'm just as confused as he is that's the logic I
think well it can't be serious no you're not serious because you don't know where
the fuck it is either so where is it on the patch rocks I did it here like
fucking ten times why won't it do it I did it here like already a bunch of
time it shows me the way to the ruin follow me I actually did it there like
at least three four times here we are the ruins must be beneath these huge
rocks oh we would need the strength of the gods to move these who will never
get to examine the roof fuckers wanted me to go up to the mountain all right so
I wonder if anyone will give it a rest ruins okay why do you I go in I cleared
it for you go take a look smooth them throw the rocks into the water fuck you
can't just walk in here it's the funniest movie of the year Sonic the
I thought I was getting hacked I thought I was getting hacked dude what the fuck
just happened like an ad just started playing fuck I must have downloaded
something weird holy shit this is too many people we um I don't think we can
take this many people how many this is like six million people it's a thousand
people I don't even have a thousand people my whole town all right there's
so many you look like Nickelodeon floam for God's sakes there's so many people
there it just looks like floam it didn't happen you didn't see it you did I'm
going back okay I don't want to see that it's too much it's too much for my brain
let's let them in let them in with sick where's the save it's 936 p.m. right now
there it is okay we're fine let him in make him in ah my chest is killing me
I've laughed so fucking hard tonight like a random shit I haven't laughed super
hard at anything but I've just said it's been a constant stream of comedy and
humor for me like it's been almost seven straight hours of me just laughing oh
all right come on in everybody in successful penis stream why don't I
just read that so many people let's at least go see the next cutscene
Murius be nice Murius be nice he's shaking his head he's like no no no no
too many people they're having a food all right we're there they're in let's
check out the next area and then I'm going to bed and I gotta get out here
and then I've got I've got physical therapy tomorrow so I'm not gonna be
live tomorrow or on Sunday I'll be back on Monday I'll be back like Monday
Tuesday Wednesday something like that but I really wanted to see this part
because this is uh this is important no towns taken by force the whole night
well actually that's a lie I beat the last level to 9% evil I didn't do
anything impressiveness yeah happiness was pretty good population the highest
population was 1234 which is because I got 778 people what happened here 1100
male population a hundred and forty three female is that why we're having
so many props that I just get really bad RNG or something that's weird that's
number of enemy soldiers killed five hundred and fifty five I wonder how
many of those are Murius 17 hundred and fifty eight deaths 58 water miracles six
only six fireballs that's pretty good I did most of the no I didn't do any of
these didn't not oil are here's the good one 70% good 70% good he's 12 he's 11
feet tall he's now 8,000 pounds he's at 92% muscle 75% fit mmm hundred hit
146 bowel movements he killed 800 people that's though in the whole land he was
responsible for killing half of every single living person on in this whole
country over the course of what I assume is like three or four years he killed
half the population himself Jesus good job my head take a look at this next
cutscene as we ready ourselves we will let the Greeks prepare for our storm to
come you are right they have divine help but the prophecy says they will rise
against those who nearly destroyed them the Aztecs if they can triumph over us
we will have no option but to offer ourselves to their side you speak sense
brother we have both seen what these Greeks can do but we must make us turn
here first finally this is a tiger that I humiliated three times I'm sick that
but the second brother isn't a city builder he prefers destruction you
should be where beware him he can kiss my shiny right behind this level is
huge let's build us some armies and get cracking on those nasty miracles this is
gonna be it is imperative we protect ourselves with walls the Japanese won't
wait for you to make your move they will be desperate to drive us out and that's
where we're gonna close it for tonight I do want to take a look at the map this
is a big boy not really actually it's just too big stronghold soon no one
shall be able to save it here I'm gonna call this one not two fronts exist the
beauty of my city classic RTS map yeah and there's one in the middle that's a
big point of interest this one I wish this is the one we just played this one
looks fun but that's gonna be it for today I will see you guys later see you
guys on Monday we are not going to come back to black and white to on Monday
we're gonna change games get a good look at Murius beautiful beautiful it's still
quite itchy Murius we're going to do on Monday chibi robo I have it it's ready
to go should be a lot of fun pet Murius after chibi robo is done we will see if
I want to come back and finish this because I believe this I think there's
only one or two maps left in the whole game there's also the expansion which I
do own as well so I'm assuming I could probably do another stream on this and
finish the base game at least we'll see I'm not gonna be doing that next week
we're gonna have to put the cap on this for a little while but it is available
the black and white two is now just available and the expansion mentions
like five big levels cool available in quotes no but I love this game so I'm
having so much fun it's definitely something I want to play again on
stream at the cow before I do okay I'll pet cow before I turn it on hey you hey
come here you're hiding watch out goodbye Murius we'll see you again soon
and that goes for you guys as well we'll see you again on Monday it is saved
there Murius for rumble Murius for own TV show I'll see you guys later I'm gonna
get some food I'm hungry Murius replace bugleberry let me just load up the make
sure I have the bits in the right spot I should I do okay let's go back earlier
today we had two dollars and 80 cents from for real dough 280 bits now you've
been enjoying black and white any chance you'll reconsider dungeon keeper maybe
but I think the reason why I like black and white so much is because there's so
much to look at at any given moment having the creature just do shit and run
around and I can just laugh at the things that the cow is doing takes me
away from the actual video game of city building and that's why I can stay
interested dungeon keeper is it's an interesting game but I think it's more
so I would probably lose interest in it after a stream and that's correct me if
I'm wrong but that's a pretty long experience isn't it isn't dungeon
keeper more than like a 30 plus hour game potentially just look at Chad
instead it is well not that long but the bit yeah and I always have trouble
finishing games on stream anyways that I don't know and look I'm speaking
completely kind of out of my ass here because I've only played dungeon keeper
for maybe 30 minutes total more than 15 years ago I just don't I didn't grab me
when I was younger this did I remember what I'm ever being 15 years old playing
black and white one 14 something like that whatever how old I was I also
don't like to completely say I'm never gonna do something because sometimes it
just happens so I don't know I'll have to look into it but thank you for the 280
though thank you raddest raccoon for the 250 I need to know if you're gonna
replace the wink with something else do I sell my wing points or do I save them
for something better there's gonna be a couple things on the new channel points
you'll see you do what you want with your own currency though whatever you
want to do with it it's your call it's your idea I'm gonna be adding other
stuff though that's hopefully interesting dark soul thanks for the 250
dark soul hi I'm here from goop gaming really excited to reach out to you our
very first partner the 10 million dollars you agreed to has been wired to
your account oh he asked us that you plug our new sea salt flavored deodorant
thank you so much for teaming up with us to spread some alternative remedies
remember to stay goopy I did yeah I said the sea salt thing earlier whatever I
said thank you dark soul for the 250 and Adam thank you and Adam for the 1500
bits German just want to say thanks for all the entertainment started watching
when I was 13 same age I started playing black and white I turned 20 today happy
birthday you give me a lot of joy growing up and influenced a lot of my
humor which is the main reason why I still don't have a girlfriend
thanks for all the laughs also please play Jedi Academy and fart on the
microphone please I will maybe do none of those things I might do one of them
maybe which one it is you'll have to figure that out thank you for the 15
dolls in the little horse anytime I laugh really really hard over the course
of a whole stream I my voice just turns into diarrhea thank you for 1500 bits
internet Jorge thanks for the 1500 bits back-to-back 15 dolls thanks guys it's a
lot of money it's a big bit drop what's the funniest movie of the year so far
um I don't know uh I was it onward that's kind of funny it was cute and
funny I'm moving out yet it's not even out yet I was out on March 6 whoops and
that looks like the funniest movie to me I'm not gonna let some advertisement
tell me what the funniest movie in the world is and the best movie in the world
is I'm gonna make my own decision I'm gonna go see onward when it comes out
and see if it's the best movie of the year hey Emanuel depressed thanks for
300 bits hi Jerma I know you're getting sick of winks you ever thought about
replacing them with uh twonks or twinks I hopefully didn't just say anything bad
you did well whatever thanks for the 300 bits
yeah winks will be replaced by something don't worry uh bulbous swag thanks for
the 500 bits just get a couple of just get a couple clips of you winking and
play whenever someone redeems it no one has to know people will know immediately
something that twitch chat and the internet kind of culture in general can
do is sniff out bullshit instantly instantly it would take one or two times
before it was cat was out of the bag you know I mean thank you uh jump T thanks
for 300 bits love the stream do you think you'll be playing the new Animal
Crossing game when it comes out yeah I would assume probably I don't see why
not I have to turn my switch on for some reason it's been just neglected
sitting there in the corner not turned on ever it's kind of turning into the
way that my Xbox one was but I haven't really turned on my ps4 either I need a
reason to play something we are getting close to the end of the console cycles
or at least Xbox and ps4 ps5 is coming out this year it's so is it's so weird
it's so strange that the ps5 is gonna come out this year holiday this year you
think they'll delay it been like seven years for this console cycle yeah but
for some reason it feels like it hasn't been this has been an incredibly long
cycle going into eight years after right it's doesn't feel like it's only been
out for like three years four years feel like it hasn't been out for that long
subway rat princess thanks for 300 bits three dollars thank you
Esquilo thanks for the 250 hey jerk ma 985 a sandwich is defined as a
carbohydrate product or other containing edible structure of reasonable
structural fortitude utilizes a vehicle for ingredients to reach the mouth with
excessive dirtying or greasing of the hands a sandwich must have portability
and relative tidiness its main function is to guide the ingredients to the mouth
without the use of utensils thus a pizza is a sandwich hot dog is a sandwich a
taco is a sandwich no they're not pizza is a pizza it's not a pizza sandwich a
hot dog is a hot dog it's in a bun it's a it's not a hot dog sandwich taco is a
taco it's not a taco sandwich and by the way we have pizza is a pie and what's
an open-faced sandwich a sandwich that's not completed it's is not a pie it's a
we talked about this in the discord for like 40 minutes no no no a sandwich was
created by some some dude modern concept of a sandwich using slices of bread as
found within the West can arguably trace to 18th century Europe John sandwich the
use of some kind of bread or bread like substance to lie under and over some
other food or used to scoop up and enclose or wrap some other type of food
so we talk about a complete closure here is a sandwich hot dog does not have a
complete closure pizza does not have complete closure taco does not have
complete closure a sandwich is a complete closure and you could also say
well hold on a second what about a sub what about a sub sandwich what about a
sub well I mean technique I mean it's a hoagie right what about a wrap that's in
closure completely enclosed burritos are sandwiches yeah that's you got you got
complete you have complete enclosure closed up bread on all sides top and
bottom burritos a sandwich shit too much how zone is a sandwich yeah if that's a
cat it's bread enclosing innards shit no that's that's correct taco is not a
sandwich by the way sandwiches is it's just a term now that people use to
describe bread and stuff in the middle you know that's not like I guess
technically you could be like well a hot dogs the same yeah but I mean like
that's everybody just knows that a sandwich is just bread and stuff in the
middle eyes are sandwiches no they're not what how is a pie a sandwich it's
crushed on the bottom and then a bunch of shit on top of the crust that's not
a sandwich that don't closure apple pie is an enclosure on top oh fuck an apple
pie is a apple pie is a sandwich huh it's crushed on the bottom crust on the
top and this enclosed and heated and you eat it all right what about no but
you do no no no you don't eat a pie with your hands a sandwich or something
that is used you use your hands to eat not a fork and knife sorry myth-busted
no people don't eat pie with their hands okay frost is not bread that's true yeah
true that's correct just pick it up idiot all right thank you for the the
discussion a pizza is not a sandwich and I just out of curiosity why did you
link me an image of like a car on a snow storm car on a snow mountain what does
it have to do with sandwiches it's like a car and like a plow and a plowed road
what is it why did you give me this I was just freaking me out I don't want
no I don't I didn't get an image never mind mountain is wrapped it's a snow
sandwich the mountain is underneath the snow and this no no there's no snow
inside the mountain the mountains not sitting on snow sorry hey Mitchell
thanks with 20 bucks Mitchell 2,000 bits I don't need to stir earlier today and
he told me to go fuck myself can I make it two for two this is that's what you
want you guys heard it here first this is what this is what they want I am
being asked to provide a service and that service is to tell this person to
go fuck himself okay I am providing a service it was $20 Mitchell 256 clip
prevention clip prevention clip prevention I was asked to do this clip
prevention don't fuck yourself thank you but for real you're pretty good dude
thank you he didn't say anything after earth is a sandwich no earth is a
that's not a sandwich it's a fruit snack hey dr. clay thanks with $5 500
bits no bullshit your god caused utter chaos but don't have a cow man I'm sure
your citizens won't be seeing red there's been a lot of beef between
Murius and your followers but you just got a steer Murius in the right
direction before you know it everyone will say cowabunga
Murius is one rad God after all when the stakes are high he knows what to do
soon your enemies will get the horns after messing with the bull well I
believe I milked this long enough hope you enjoyed the puns hope you enjoy the
24-hour ban thanks for the 10 bucks clay thanks a little bit hey scruffle thanks
for the 300 bits you're my auto hey thanks Rick Bilby thanks for a thousand
bits a lot of 10 10 10 15 15 20 20 50 50 50 you guys give a lot of money
tonight thanks guys Rick Bilby gives 10 bucks and says hey German I'm gonna go
German going to the new Massachusetts casino tomorrow and if I win big I'll
give you a little treat but for now I want to ask if you have any advice for
making new friends I recently pushed myself to do a few new activities to
meet new people sometimes feel like I'm just too awkward or slow for people to
slow to for people to enjoy my company that's very discouraging thanks for the
laughs and to be honest ASMR like voice please fart on the face cam alright you
look at you looking for advice and then you end it with like please fart on face
cam you've thrown me off alright making new friends the best place to make new
friends and you've said you've recently pushed us up to do a few new activities
to meet people you kind of need to do something you already like and that you
know that has people around that also like those things doing something that's
new it's much easier to it's much easier to do new activity with friends and make
new friends at new activity and it is to go to new activity and make all brand
new friends by yourself going in groups is much easier for something brand new
I'm getting question marks for this what a new activity except if you something
well why am I getting question mark for this did I not say that correctly doing
stuff in groups that you've all of you never done before it's much easier for
you to bounce off each other and meet new people and hang out with people
because it's not just you that has to talk to new people that makes sense
right yeah I'm getting question mark yeah spend money to make money I get it I
get it you just went full I was pretty articulate all right anyways solo
activities it's harder to kind of assimilate yourself into a group but the
internet has done so many things to create places for you to hang out and
spend time and kind of make friends so you got a fart or what into the webcam I
don't know if I can do it into the webcam into the into the web I didn't
have the webcam that just came out I didn't have the webcam on I you can't
time these things guys Jesus Christ sorry there was still some there there's
still some in there you can't just let it sit in the chamber it's got to go what
was going on oh yeah making friends I made a lot of friends on YouTube because
people were just we were doing the same thing you need to find something you
really like that you can do solo that also has other people that are doing it
solo at the same time if you really have trouble making friends tuber friends oh
yeah tuber friend term it's 1 a.m. please I'm going you got to go to bed
don't get on to bed German I don't like collabs Albertson giving friend advice
that's not what I said oh being so twisted I'm being at my words get so
twisted oh I'm so glad this is happening not on stream it's on the path of the
post breakdown part of the stream you know how okay this 2500 people here
right now what was there about or 5000 at the peak of today imagine doing that
when there was twice as many people here how many people would be furious that I
did that more than once oh it would be bad it would be people would be they
would be minus two is it be like stop stop dude what the fuck this is not this
is not canon none of this stuff is can it's all off-stream my broadcast is over
when this screen pops up streams over didn't happen on stream but anyways now
making friends can be hard it really can be I wish you luck hopefully you find
something that you can care about that you can be knowledgeable knowledgeable
about and there's other people that are trying to look for people to see how I
make my friends yeah that's that's a killer that's that's that slays them all
they love that one just make sure you're the loudest fodder in the room
it will flock to you especially in a restaurant all right Goiki thanks for
the 500 bits really glad I caught the penis stream thanks Jermia yeah thank
you all right it's fine what's a penis stream I know I don't know either I said
it like four times though it's my fault it's my fault I take responsibility for
this one stripes beast thanks for the 500 bits a
Jermis want to say your five day stream really helped me keep my spirits up
well my dad well with my dad for his final days in the hospital I'm excited
for chibi-robo when I first played it took a day off work to play the whole
game love you and the community I'm sorry to hear that take care of yourself
may he rest in peace I'm really sorry to hear that much love to you and yeah glad
you can take your mind off something and hang out here we got a great bunch of
jokers here thanks for the 500 bits and chibi-robo I feel like it's gonna be a
lot of fun I might have to do it over two streams I heard it's like 12 to 15
hours long and that means it's but it's gonna be 20 hours long for me you got to
add the the streaming factor on there times any game by about 30 to 40 percent
and how it works yeah let's run the credits while we have it open here there
were a lot of community subs tonight I'm sure you'll see him fly by let's get
the other screen the true actual wind downstream see you guys on Monday have a
great rest tonight have a great weekend we're gonna come back with chibi-robo
maybe one to two streams depending on how long it takes me to do I really hope
I don't hate this game is that possible am I gonna not is it possible that I've
been like talking chibi-robo up am I not gonna like this game you clean and and
cook food and and rearrange furniture right that's like up there in best
genres for me it goes cleaning and furniture moving genre then RPG then FPS
we still have some bits to do let's go to Bryn Jar Bjorn Bryn Jar Bjorn thank you
for the $10 and what was this link this is link I'm out of context penis music
this this is someone this is twelve and a half thousand likes I can't even get
that on my on my German 985 Twitter I can't even get like a third of that you
need to do more shit posting shit post on Twitter you got a shit post more yeah do
I really even care about Twitter you know what I mean I for some reason I've
always held no I don't want to drink that I've written so many fucked up
tweets that I just delete delete delete delete did it didn't a whole delete
button it's gone gone gone word word word sentence and then I hit escape it
can't so I get out I do it all the time you know it's time New Year's resolution
New Year's I'm just gonna write whatever the fuck I want who cares I'm gonna I'm
gonna do like pictures of like a close-up of like inside my mouth like my
teeth or something I don't know I'm just gonna be fucking weird 2020 I'm gonna
lose a lot of fun no I'm almost over a hundred thousand followers I don't want
to lose any followers why would I do that leave it to the German penis music shit
post channel to like do that for me okay yeah we've come to a conclusion you're
gonna double your followers but anyways uh Brynn thanks for the thousand bits I
felt like sending you a message of appreciation for a while ever since I
was first recommended you by a certain rad streamer I've watched all your
content both via VOD and YouTube even alongside as I work and via the streams
that I can catch on weekends I've been fortunate enough to meet you in person
and can attest that you are as genuine and fun as a person as you are on screen
I wish you all the best this is a really really nice message thank you glad you
found the channel and I'm glad you didn't end this with me putting my hand
up and going like this like this they're closing my hand and that I scanned 15
individual pineapple juices and said there was electrical in it in veterans
or whatever I'm I'm very happy about that thank you what do you what are you
guys doing what the fuck is this I didn't even I didn't do this why is this
on the German out of context it's not even me oh yeah German out of context
just kidding it's Jermis face deep faked onto somebody else why did you film
this oh I fucking can't even watch this I closed it I can't even what it's
freaking me out I can't even watch that okay but thank you Brynn glad you found
the channel hope you stick around Yoko Nova thanks for the 1500 bits thank you
Yoko Nova hey what up kid hey you and that auto character do make a wicked
good team here's some funds for your crime fighting efforts thanks for
keeping the streets clean German auto hey thanks Yoko Nova for the 1500 bits
$15 and thanks everybody for subbing too thanks for the community subs it flew
by I've got a little distracted by my face imposed on somebody else's face but
me making faces I actually make in my mirror and that's my face actually
moving fucked up world we live in 2020 what happens in 2030 when it becomes
completely different there's no difference and anybody can do and say
anything and put somebody else's face on it saying them as if it's them talking
and it looks identical we've got quantum computing coming just start just you
know what start buying gold bars start buying gold and start stockpiling food
because in 2030 it's over it's like the robots are taking over we're all gonna
he's prepping gold's gonna be why would you buy gold I'm prepping for y2k y2k I
know I read in this tabloid magazine that in the in January 1st 2000 every
country is nukes are gonna fire at each other people actually thought that was
everybody thought that every country's nuclear bombs were going to fire at each
other because a clock reset but buy gold and start stockpiling food because the
robots are gonna kill us the robots are gonna take us all over I'm telling you
listen to me world continues world continues we continue to be scared of
things that's my scene applause looking there please clap yes for me that's for
me that's for me all right so we have dubsy thank you dubsy for the 300 bits
German my friend Morgan smells could you give him some encouragement by telling
him how to take a shower um say some powder a little bit of talcum powder
just top top top top under the arms just a little dry take a shower you know
every day at night in the morning every other day I have to wash your hair too
much I know it's really you really want to make sure you're using a good if
you're gonna wash your hair every day and condition it just make sure you you
using something that's not gonna dry out your hair and fuck it up washing hair
too much dries it out good health tips German thank you just trying to do my
part just trying to do my part thanks to 300 bits dubsy Morgan somebody thinks
you smell a wind are wind are thanks to the 500 bits hey German fan here I've
got a bit of a sad story sad story I showed my mom the penis music video that
you are in he said she didn't get it and that you seemed like an overgrown
manchild with no purpose in life please understand my mom doesn't hate you I'm
sorry German anyway thanks you for all the community I cherish every moment I
can watching your streams your mother has one thing wrong she has overgrown
manchild correct she has the second part incorrect why is your mom what's what's
your mom why you might as well go mom got such a problem with me what did I do
I danced around with it well all right hold on wait wait wait wait you let
hold on back this up a little bit before I say what's going on here you showed
your mother a video your mother you said mom come here I want to show you
something your mom oh yeah what is it this it's called penis music here's a
video and it's a guy dancing weird in this in this music in the background
that's going crazy you showed your mother a video that said
penis music and then she saw that video of me doing that she's gonna be what
she's gonna want now she wants to probably gonna see you all your report
cards I didn't do this you did I didn't make that video I didn't make that's
not what I call it you're not you just brought an extra scrutiny from your
parents how would you show your mother that video you should show your mother a
fucking B plus that you got on a test see influencer yeah I would I'm sorry mom
if you're watching I'm sorry I didn't make that video I am an online media
personality influencer e-clown it's my job to influence other we're all friends
and this is all my family and that's right let me get it right you're all
family members of mine and well how do let me make sure I get this right we're
having fun here and I'm glad that every single person here is a just don't show
you mother penis video please look what you make it look what's happening hey
on the heroic thanks for the 250 hey German what are your thoughts on evil
wizards that could cast evil spells while a wizard I would think that I
would hope that I would think that I would hope to be I would think that it
would be using a Diablo 2 Paladin sceptic I wouldn't hear the word wizard I
have that just happens uh thank you opster narwhal for the 259 saw the Red
Sox jersey and want to remind everyone that the Red Sox cheated hey thanks for
the three dollars actually bad actually true okay look let me okay you want me
to defend this here what do you want me to say oh shit my Boston Red Sox I'm on
that team how could we have done such a thing I can't believe I did that I lived
in the city that they wear the laundry of that says the city's name on it we're
what have we done if I done I'm sorry I'm apologizing what do we want to say
they cheated and they fucking who bunch it but they're assholes that's a
condescending villain what do you want me to say here's the thing I think I
think people when they bring this stuff up like hey just want to remind you the
Red Sox cheated you don't deserve you did your city didn't deserve that
championship what do you want me to be people I'd be like yeah they fucking did
I don't care if they cheated I'm a cheater too and then it's like ha I knew
it all people from Boston are fucking cheating and lying assholes and it's
like oh no shut up idiot uh no I'm not I uh good you're trying to catch people
in this like yeah you must condone that to you Boston bastard and I save scum to
all day today so go ahead and put me in that category fine just like the
Patriots just like every goddamn team guys you remember baseball back back 15
years ago every single person was injecting steroids and human growth
hormones into their body it's a sport based on cheating where everybody
cheated everybody's cheating they're all cheating they're all cheaters all of
them and then what happens is when someone like how many teams have to get
caught before everybody's gotten caught cheating just legalize it and make a
league of superheroes everyone they're all doing this under-the-radar shit and
they know that they're not supposed to be and it's like all right well the
Astros just got caught the Red Sox just got caught before that it was like
Cleveland before that's the Patriots before that's the Jets before that it
was there was the Raiders no I remember like five years ago one night it was a
pretty big packers and then remember they fucking they were stealing sides
and remember the coaches were working for the other team and it's just you go
back and Pete Rose Pete Rose bet on the games he's coping advocating for
steroids and animal fighting in the same stream what what the fuck are you
talking about I don't care about sports sad face just remove pitchers and no one
can steal signs yeah just have a pitching machine fire we'll make it
fair have a pitching machine only pitch fastballs right down the middle but
they're 120 miles per hour good luck that makes it a little harder for the
batters I think maybe for you the Red Sox cheated how does that make you you
know what that is that's the equivalent of being stopped on the
street somebody with a camera and a microphone hey I said see that you have the
Boston shirt on yeah yeah I do Boston Red Sox I've been I mean I've there been
my family and like I've watched him for years and what do you think the fact
that they cheated in 2018 Mike in the face um well I mean I don't condone it
I don't you Mike is getting really close to my mouth okay he's still no all
right all right all right oh I can't get over I can't get over okay I love the
Red Sox all right if you fucking come in here and you drop shit on the Red Sox
I'm gonna fight back even though I haven't watched a regulation exhibition
baseball game in over a year and six months I am gonna fight for the Red
Sox anyways thanks thanks for the it was like 12 you get like 12 bucks is it
just realized I had more bits why not German ninja German pog German
sunburn German crazy these real what are these does that do anything does that
show up does that show anything they're on BT TV oh okay I was like did I when
did I enable these thanks though a bit slave thanks for the two dollars and
fifty cents 25 cents times 150 70 500 and that 50 70 100 50 times I don't know
some number that's more than 10 10 thanks the 25 cents times 10 German
think you'll like twisted fate twisted fate is a casino type champion who has
charmed his way across the world you live in Vegas and you charm us all so
when you get League of Legends tonight you should try to play him look up his
lore it's super interesting too not only that but he looks a bit like you if he
was smaller and if you had a mustache and a beard the league I'm never gonna
install League it's not gonna happen I don't even like those games where are
what but why are you getting the idea that I would even want to play League
considering all the nice things I've said about MOBAs I don't know don't get
your account banned don't drink full bottles of alcohol only drinking enough
to feel like slightly good and maybe one more after that and that's it if you're
responsible and make to drink water too for God's sake be careful it's tough
that's dangerous but thank you appreciate the huge money that you've
given tonight off what's thanks for the 500 bits hi I hope you're doing well
it's nearing the middle of the semester so I haven't had much time to watch
streams for a second facing an onslaught of tests and exams oh yeah a
lot of a lot of colleges semesters are gonna be ending here soon aren't they
like the next month or two was it may April oh may late April you're an idiot
it's February mine just started it's February oh yeah it is like February and
you did just say it's the middle of the semester oh yeah kids are getting at
school soon here sorry I just did the thing I did the thing oh yeah kids are
getting out of school here soon yeah yeah I see that makes sense I said that
all I like that that's just a response to pretty much anything really it's the
dead middle of the semester yeah that meant still you said school you said
semester and you said nearing the nearing semester so I oh yeah kids getting out
of school anyways I've been studying ancient Rome in Greece and I'm slightly
disturbed at how accurate everything in black and white 2 is depicted really
that's kind of that's fucked up lots of breeding and then off but again thanks
for five more dollars 500 bits of the Carthaginian named Hannibal was born
and as a kid he swore to be an enemy of Rome his first battle against Rome was in
216 BC the Second Punic War there was six thousand Carthage casualties out of
52,000 army and 50,000 to 70,000 Roman casualties of their 87,000 person army
the Romans were understandably very upset how many of them were killed by a
giant rolling boulder I wonder and how many were eaten by a giant cow will
never know nobody lived back then will never know the real story they say
thanks for the entertainment while studying you're making school bearable
yes yes please fart on face cam somebody said I want to get the clip I went to
get the clip hold on this is the clip of what stir star saying Mitchell the
person I told to I was paid in service to say something they gave five more
dollars I said I want to I went to get the clip I don't know I feel like
always on our flanks hey Mitchell Mitchell I really got a saying after
something like someone's generous as that go fuck yourself he's just mean he
just he just did it on the meanness of his heart I was paid a service he did he
did that just on his own you didn't even pay him well you did but you didn't pay
him to say that a bit slave thanks for the 500 bits or 2250s German this message
is for chat I want to say that drinking excessively is not fun or good in any
way I have a problem and it sucks plus it cost me the one game I play and have
fun with for 14 days because I was running it down and spamming obscenities
also don't touch that shit if you're under 21 peach good listen to this
person please they also say just realize black and white reminds me of this one
flash game that I used to play before I played League of Legends greatest game
of all time it was like you throw your villager or something I forgot just a
hand-throwing villagers trying to run off screen or something I forgot what
it was called it be exact does anyone chat know what this is pillage the
village that's it you got it a shadows one disciple shadows
disciple thanks for the 250 a German what does it like to live so far from
most of your family I'm looking to move in the future from Kentucky to Utah so
not as far as you went that's still pretty far though still that's still far
but very far I guess the main differences with me is that I'm single
and I'm also an only child I really don't like it here not because the
people of politics or anything but it's like it might be difficult to live so
far from my family thanks German um yeah I was fortunate enough to have my
girlfriend who was just was gonna follow me anywhere and continued will we're
going to continue to also had a buddy Alex he's right over there that also was
wanted to check it out and do it for a little while and it's much easier with
other people it really is but with that being said how do I do it a lot of
people have come up here and again this is another thing of how I'm pretty
fortunate with this too is I mean I live in Las Vegas and that's a destination
people are like yeah I got a trip to Vegas in two months I'm like okay I live
here oh yeah great I'll see you a lot of people come up here but Utah Utah's
actually a pretty great state from what I hear you people will come to you is
what I'm saying especially with some of the cool shit that you could find and
entice people to come up is it yeah Utah Utah supposed to be pretty good what's
wrong with Utah now what do you mean doubt the Grand Canyon is in Utah that's
kind of in that's that's one of the most biggest marvels of our entire fucking
world doesn't Grand Canyon doesn't pass through Utah I thought it did I thought
it passed through Utah it doesn't I thought it did I thought it hit the I
thought it hit like the bottom like like the self I thought it hit like the
self fucking the southern point of the state it doesn't know it's only in
what about those salt lakes those salt lakes are pretty sick salt Lake City
it's a great fucking place from what I've heard look I'm gonna fix this I'm
gonna fucking enlighten some of you guys Utah is actually pretty high up in like
the in this in the rankings of states rankings Utah numbness is not bullshit
take a look I want you to see this Utah is in the top ten in health care top
ten in education top the second strongest economy the third best
infrastructure in the entire country the one of the most fiscally stable and
one of the safest states in the country okay that's real data that is pretty
low if that is like 38 sounds stupid why don't you just move to rank one just
move back I want to go to rank well what is Nevada that is 37 Nevada has two
things that are going for it it's top ten economy and top five in
infrastructure and this is based off of you can pull up each one that's this is
actually a really really interesting website because I sat here for like a
couple hours picking out individual states and being like why is that why
wait no education how why Massachusetts is number eight to explain
infrastructure roads bridges buildings infrastructure like the actual big
hella way number one Florida is the best state in the world what state has the
best health care Hawaii and Massachusetts massive mean that that's a
no-brainer Massachusetts is some of the best
hospitals on earth so I mean it makes sense Hawaii though Massachusetts
number one in education Colorado number one for economy Oregon number one in
infrastructure New Hampshire and number one an opportunity I actually was gonna
move to New Hampshire it was one of the places I wanted to go to fiscal
stability Tennessee Tennessee New Hampshire is also the safest state in
the country and Rhode Island has the best natural environment which is air
quality water quality etc it's getting expensive yeah Rhode Island is Rhode
Island is actually at the almost at the very bottom for infrastructure which
means the roads are dogshit like the power lines are all in disarray
bridges are fucking falling apart but it's got some of the cleanest air it has
the cleanest air and cleanest water in America and top five in health care so
great doctors in Rhode Island anyways oh yeah but Utah Utah's supposed to be a
really great place to live and that's how I knew that because I looked at the
that states rankings list don't base your future on a top 10 list well then
I'm gonna have to unsubscribe from BuzzFeed watch Bojo how am I gonna exist
states tier list I can't do a states tier list because I've I've haven't been
to every state in the country I've been to a lot of them I haven't been to all
of them what states have I been to no no no no I that's I that's gonna take too
long we'll do this another day start walking buster anyways let's go we got
only a few more to do stream is over good night bye take care of yourselves
you guys on Monday but how's it to live so far with my family I it's easier with
people around you but that being said I mean I I grew up around tons of friends
that were back in Massachusetts my whole family network is back there and I do
miss them I do miss them all the time they do come up periodically but you know
you try to make you try to make your own home and then people come to your home
and you make your own way over here right I see you can stand that's the
thing you can still go back you can still visit you can spend a weekend have
somebody spend three or four days try to get somebody to see if they can spend
some time with you always where you feel at home that's right he's doing the
awesome excuse nine-hour starting screen pardon me wants to do this but
it's gonna take too much effort and I'm tired have the starting screen beyond
and and just actually leave for like 15 minutes and you guys talk about how I
think he fucking turned it on I don't know what he's doing it's been nine and
a half hours everybody can get a hold of him I don't think he realizes that the
streams been on he hasn't done anything and then I come back camera pointed at
me I turn the webcam on lights turned off and like in the bathrobe and like
make my eyes like like watery and red and be like two people will have maybe
trickled in at that point by then and it's real it's elaborate it's too
elaborate I gotta go I'm tired I'm going no I can't I can't I'm tired I'm tired
I need to eat I haven't eaten I haven't eaten nine and a half hours I have to
eat some food what the fuck we'll do all right save that one we'll do that one
next up razzle thanks for the 250 hey Jeremy my wife's boyfriend it's kid love
watching you play go giant enemy spider hey bit slave thanks for 250 these bits
are just to get me to the number one bit donator slot owo owo furry League of
Legends okay thank you what is happening wind are thanks for the 500
yes I showed my mom that video it's fucking funny as hell but she said that
because she doesn't understand what you do I explained it to her and she was
like oh okay the title of the video is penis music you didn't show somebody a
video that's your mother that was funny dance video no it was penis music there's
already gonna be something weird that you're doing that you're saying you're
showing that to your mother that's a guy it's already gonna be weird from the
very beginning oh my god please fucking do the bathrobe
I want to be laughing about it just a little bit no I can't I can't I'm hungry
and when I don't eat I get angry sheepish deep dish thanks for the 500
bits it's late thanks for 499 you never beat the shovel game and coin game what
gives man you promised you one blondie thanks for the five dollars boss gave
me a raise so I wanted to support my favorite stripper with some bits bada
bing thank you thanks a lot guys I'll see you guys in a couple days I'll see
you on Monday or chibi robo see you soon eat in 15 minutes no I'm way past my
food bedtime my food bedtime is like eight hours nine hours if I don't eat
in eight or nine hours I become a gremlin it's the reverse and I can see
in a few days take care have a good weekend goodbye good night and take care
yeah yeah it hurts yo streams on the fuck you talking about kid I just got
up yo hey yo what's up guys got a fucking funny little thing there for
you yo um shit I have this is gonna start but something I'm tough man