Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with some Facecam Fortress 2, Monday's edition.
And today you're gonna be playing as the Pyro Scout. I don't think so. Maybe I do. Maybe you do think so.
Oh, it's a rabbit and a goose. There's a lot of people here. Oh my word! There's a lot of people here.
Oh my god! I only... Can I take on everybody? That's the real question. Absolutely no.
Can I get it? No, somebody already got it. Crap, he did.
Oh yeah, playing as the Pyro on the new game mode. This is Doomsday.
Give me that, Medic. Give me that, Medic!
I actually... I kinda like this mode. It's... It's hard to play, but at the same time, it's...
No, it was a spy. It's hard to play, but at the same time, it's just total chaos.
This entire mode is just pure chaos. I don't even know how the mode works still. I mean, I do, but I don't.
You pick up the thing, you put the suitcase on. Only one person can have the suitcase.
And you stand on the point, and you cap it, and then... I'm pretty sure I still don't know how this works after like 5,000 times playing it.
You have to put it in there. I'll do a more thorough review of this another time, but for now, it's just crazy. It's just absolute chaos.
And they got it again. We can't have that, baby.
Hmm, looking for someone to smoke. Like this guy!
Oh, boy. Where is he? Where is he?
Alright, he dropped it. He dropped it. He dropped it. We're good.
Come here, get healed. Oh... I'm gonna need that health.
Gotten this thing like it's my job. Because it is.
Alright, can we get the australium? And can we stuff it in that rocket and send Poopy Joe to hell?
A lot of scouts.
Oh, no. I'm trying to catch him with a flare gun. I can't even hit him. I can't even light him on fire!
My god, what's my ping? Pretty good. I don't know what's going on with that.
This sniper is probably gonna kill me. No, he's not.
Oh, wait. Is this the sniper? My brain cannot handle these situations.
And I missed again. And I missed again.
Not this time! Yeah, this time. You know, I'm just going in for this.
If the flare gun shot's not there today, then you might as well just go for the chaos smash.
Where's that spy?
Oh, here we go. We're gonna cap it.
Come on, cap it! No! No! Somebody get up there!
That was a random critter, I think.
Oh, now I got auto-balanced.
Well, that's one way for your recording to crash.
I'm sure there are other ways, but that's definitely one way.
Whoa. Let's start this again. I'm gonna actually...
I'm gonna get the Australian this time, and I'm gonna miss this sniper over and over again.
Maybe not this time. This time!
Nope. Scout.
Come on, come get it.
Come get it, you shut-up-a-bitch!
Spy? Spy? No.
No, no, I got it. I got it.
Burgaphone's got it.
You know what? We're gonna fake him out!
No, there's nobody there. All right, let's go.
Let's take it down the tunnel.
I'm gonna cap this, and Poopy Joe is gonna meet his maker.
Let's sneak around this way.
I got the bomb, guys!
I got the bomb!
Protect me, please. You're not a spy. Get on here, let's do it.
Come on, dudes. Everyone hop on this point.
I'm gonna cap this right now.
It's all about the dodging. It's all about the weaving.
Get out of here!
Get out of town! Get out of town!
Open up! Open up! Come on!
Open up! Open up, you son-of-a-bitch!
Open up! Open up! Please open up!
Please open up!
Oh my god!
That takes so long!
Holy crap, that takes a thousand years to open.
All right, let's try this again.
This thing's a toad. That was a lot.
Get out of here.
Poopy Joe. Poopy Joe.
Poopy Joe, start the chant.
Maybe it'll actually open this time.
Come on, open up.
I wanna send Poopy Joe to hell.
Oh god, it takes so long.
Get in there! Get in there!
Get inside!
Oh, here we go. Everyone's in the rocket.
Hey, oh my god!
Somebody please help me!
That was definitely the noise they were making when they were in that rocket.
Hell, that's pretty cool. I did it.
Go in there and dump it into the thing.
That's a smart idea.
You know, I'm not gonna stand up there.
That's a bad move.
I'm gonna sit right here and heal.
Because nobody will shoot at me.
I'll be able to sit down here and then I'm gonna get up top.
I'm gonna hit this heavy in the face.
Like this.
And like this.
And like this. Oh my god!
Hey everybody!
What's your name? My name is Jerma.
And you're gonna get smashed!
Oh my dear god!
I got an uber again.
Who can I do it to?
I just have uber forever right now.
Who can I do it to? There's gotta be somebody here!
Oh come on!
No! Run, run, run!
Wow!
Can't believe I'm still alive.
You wanna talk about combat medic?
He's almost had three ubers in a row right there.
I'll miss again.
Oh, he's running now. He wants none of this.
He wants none of this.
Who can I heal?
Whoa, bad idea, bad idea!
I thought...
They're gonna cap it.
Unless Derpy Dash can do something insane.
Let's move.
I think I've said that like five times coming out of spawn.
Let's do this!
That was so close!
That was so close to being a taunt kill.
But, it's the end.
They're gonna get it. I'm just waiting.
I got him! Did I get him?
Oh come on! This guy ruined everything!
Well, that's gonna wrap it up guys.
I'll see you guys all soon.
Thank you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And of course, take care everybody.
I just spilt this.