Hey everybody, what's going on? It's Jerma again with a gameplay commentary.
More like multiple gameplay commentaries, because this is a new series I'm doing called Arena Madness,
which is where I play three or four classes in a row on two or three different maps on Arena.
Arena only, so if you don't like Arena, if you're not an Arena fan, I'm sorry,
but this is about 15 or 16 minutes long, so grab the popcorn for this one, guys.
Playing as the Demoman on Arena Badlands for the first of these four gameplays, I believe it is.
Get that scout with a nice shot from the splendid screen and the Persian Persuader,
so that's half the loadout of the match. The other half is the grenade launcher,
as you'll see here, kill that sniper with a nice couple of shots.
And this is great, this setup is unbelievable if you're going to play on an Arena match,
especially because you can get healed like that from anything on the ground.
It doesn't matter if it's a health pack, ammo, if it's somebody's gun,
that's the best part about doing this, because as you know, Arena matches,
your health is so important. Barrel into that scout, and I'm trying to get him to run over
one of the grenades, but he doesn't end up doing it. Instead, he just starts to taunt,
and I don't know if he was a bot or not, I don't think he was, but regardless,
it's a nice direct shot anyways. Top bee-hiving like a bee's nest, as you can see there.
We're going to move on to the next one now, this is still a Demoman. The next two,
I believe, are going to be Demoman gameplays. After that, it's a Pyro, and then after that,
I believe it's Sniper, and then Engineer. So you've got plenty of stuff to look forward to
if you're a fan of any of the classes. Stay tuned, alright, because there's a lot of stuff here.
Starting this one out, just absolutely spamming into this little corridor over there. I get a
random kill, and you heard the ding-a-lings, I got a ton of damage on so many other people that were
there, which is huge because there's no health packs to pick up, unless, of course, you're a
Demoman using this setup, or you're being healed by a medic or a dispenser, but that's the only
way to get health in an arena match. A lot of people don't know that, that health is not
available, and they go, where are the health packs when they come into a game? So I shoot my last
three shots over the cliff here, trying to get some random hit, and now we're just straight up
Demo Knight, and there's nothing I can do about it because with this setup, you cannot replenish
your ammo at all, but that's fine because arena matches don't really last that long anyways.
So I'd be a real Demo Spy, as you'll see. I'll try to explain this, look at this. See, I come around
the back and I'm being a real Demo Spy. I thought somebody saw me because somebody detonated a
sticky. I was like, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on a second, but watch this super lag mode. Oh,
I was so pissed about that, but it doesn't end up mattering at all because I end up smashing this
guy, picking up his health, which would be his ammo. Uber Heavy on the point. Now it's three to
three. This Heavy didn't even see me, so it's his demise. I take his head off with his head.
Final person is a Scout right here. I crush him with the shield, and then my teammates
get the final kill on the other Scout that was down there. So we are the winners. I didn't top
Gordy Smith like a gourd, so that's too bad, but anyways, let's move on to the next one. This is
the final Demoman gameplay of the series. This one starts off okay, but as you'll see, I really,
really blow the first blood buff. I was so pissed about it, you guys don't even know. I was freaking
out because it would have been so awesome. You'll see, I get under the bridge, smash this Pyro.
I have the buff now, and here we go. Oh, I don't do anything with it. I didn't even have grenades
loaded into the chamber. If I had turned up here with that first blood buff, I could have killed
five people with those grenades. It would have been insane. So now I'm just trying to help my
teammates right here. There's a Heavy medic pair going into their spawn area, just trying to get
a couple grenades in there. I get somebody with a random one, direct shot this guy, see the Spy,
and that's three kills in a row. And now I'm just trying to patrol the area to see if anyone else
is around. There's one person that's floating around somewhere. I don't know where he is. I'm
sure he's back by the spawn. So it doesn't end up mattering at all because I got the place guarded,
and the Heavy medic pair down there gets the kill, I believe. Or I think it's actually a scout. It
is a scout. We win the match, and I get five kills out of 10 people, which is pretty good if you ask
me, especially on Arena. So let's move on to the Pyro. The Pyro loadout for the first match is
going to be the degreaser, the shotgun, and the power jack. I didn't want to use the power jack,
but Steam was having all kinds of issues the last couple of days with item loadouts. So I
don't even equip it. I don't even take it out one time, so don't worry. It doesn't matter.
Coming around the back here, trying to be a good Pyro. See this scout? Light him on fire,
and he tries to run away, and I end up getting the kill on him. Not with the shotgun, but the
afterburn, which is kind of odd because we were both shooting at him with the shotgun.
This Heavy is not paying attention. He goes down. I thought I was screwed, but I do end up killing
him with the shotgun. Me and this soldier down here trying to be a little cautious because we
were down by about three people. Now it's tied, and now we are ahead. A Heavy just completely
dominated three or four people right there. There's a sniper here. He's not really paying
attention to his left, so I take him out just with the flamethrower. I think he's a spy,
but no, that's just my soldier buddy. Get an assist with the shotgun on that scout,
and now it's four to two, and when it just a second ago was nine to six in their favor.
Coming around the back here, this Heavy does not know that I'm going to do this for some reason.
I get him with a shotgun kill, and now it's four to one. We have this pretty much in the bag. We
came back from a pretty high deficit. I get killed by the needle gun, and he kills two people with
that needle gun. He came pretty close to the amount of health. Look at that health. He came
pretty damn close to taking that whole thing back, so good try for that medic. This next pyro gameplay
is going to replace the shotgun with the detonator, the new uber update item for the pyro. This is the
same thing as the flare gun except you can detonate him in midair like this, and watch what happens.
Detonate at the right time, and I got somebody. I have no idea how. I thought that was really
cool, though. Just a long-range blind detonation, and I got somebody. I get an assist for that,
too, by the way. Come down here just to try and do a couple more random detonations, and let me talk
about the detonator for just one second. I don't care that it has less crit damage. I know that's
a big problem for some people, and hold on just a second. I almost get myself killed here. I almost
just run into my own death. I got to blow this scout out, too, because he's on fire, and I'm
looking for him. I thought he ran behind me, but he's right there. I get him. Don't worry.
So it's 6 to 4 now. We have a pretty good advantage now. I come up here. There's a sniper
that I picked off. Nice shot. He doesn't think I'm going to go this way. He tries to go the
other direction. I get him with a crit. 40 damage is okay. That's fine for me, like I was saying
before. I get a nice shot. This is a good example right here of why the detonator is great. End the
game. I didn't even come close to hitting him, but I detonated it at the right time, and we win.
Time to move on to the sniper, and the map changes as well. We move on to granary. I'm a sniper. Like
I said before, using the sniper rifle, of course, the Shahanshah, and the Darwin shield, I believe.
Yep, the Darwin's danger shield. So I have been practicing with the sniper rifle. I wanted to get
good with it, and I found, as you'll see, bang, quickscoping is all I can do, and I do very,
very well with quickscoping. I can't sit there and camp and get a headshot. I over-aim. I under-aim.
I'm terrible when I hold the thing down and wait for it to get a charge, and you will see,
I don't think there is one time in either of these two sniper gameplays that I wait for it to get
even halfway of a charge. There's another quickscope headshot. I don't know. I have such
ADD and such like ADHD that I can't stand to have to sit there and wait, and some of these
headshots should have definitely registered, but they didn't. Like right there, I thought for sure
that I got that guy right in the side of the face, but I guess not. So five to three. This is
looking grim for our team. It actually has a pretty cool ending, even though it's a complete failure.
Five to two now. I'm trying to find a place where I can sneak in. Look, it's five to one.
I get a nice little body shot on that soldier. I'm trying to hide. They know I'm here. I'm trying
to jump around all over the place. Nice headshot. Quickscope on his face. Four to one now. I thought
I could get a headshot, or I thought I could pick them off from above like a bird of prey.
Don't get a headshot right there. And now I'm just like, you know what? Screw it. They're
going to get the point. I'm just going to go up there and kamikaze. And he ends up killing himself
on me. So I ended up killing like three people right there. So take it for what it is, I guess.
So this is the second sniper gameplay, and you'll see the same scout does the same path, but I miss
him this time. Or do I? That's what you'll see in the end. Result, bang, right in his face.
Coming around the corner, another scout I tried to pick off with a headshot. That would have been
sick if I got both of those scouts. Because we all know that scouts on arena maps are incredibly
powerful. They're like the main artery of arena maps. They're the ones that get all the stuff
done. They're the ones that are running around killing people, capping points. So getting rid
of scouts is incredibly important. Nice headshot there. It doesn't matter. He was overhealed,
and he was a heavy anyways. He wouldn't have died. I get an assist on him, though, which is
pretty cool. So this is one of the only times I charge to about full, and I miss. See? I'm awful
when I have to wait, even though I've missed like half of the quickscope shots anyways. But you get
the idea. Coming up this little area here, I want to make sure I can get a nice spot. I end up getting
a nice quick little headshot on this Demoman right here. Spank, but didn't kill him, but I get the
assist. I saw that there was a medic down there, and I figured that the heavy medic pair would be
right here, which they are. I come down here, get a quickscope headshot. Probably could have saved
the day, potentially, but there was an uber down there anyways. And then the final person is a
medic. Where is he? Nobody knows. There he is. Headshot to end the game. And now we are going
to move on to the engineer. This is the final one. It is the most devastating I kill. Well,
you'll see. I do very, very well. So playing as the combat engineer using the Mini-Sentry,
the Frontier Justice, and the pistol, starting it up trying to get this dispenser built because
this is the only way people can heal themselves without a medic. It's very, very important. If
you play engineer, make sure the first thing you do before doing anything is building a dispenser.
And as you can see, we had 10 people on the team, and we just got demolished right there. Nice
shotgun kill on that scout, and here comes another scout. I thought for sure I was going to be able
to kill this guy. Pull out the pistol, and nope, not enough. I get a lot of people with stray bullets,
though. I don't want to get too overzealous over there because I am only an engineer. And watch,
what is this other engineer even doing? He's just switching his weapons out over and over again.
I have no idea. It could be a bot. I don't know. Because arena matches, they're very,
very synonymous with not having people play in them. So at least two or three people on each
team will probably be a bot, at least in my opinion. Get a nice shot with that shotgun,
get another shotgun kill, and my Mini-Sentry killed somebody before that. So that's pure
awesomeness right there. This sentry gets placed in a very sneaky spot, and it kills two people
right off the bat. And you'll see the numbers. Check it out, what happens. Three to two, two to
one now is what it ends up being after that last sentry kill. It's me versus these last two people.
So let's see what happens. I have some crits. I'm ready to rock and roll. Place the sentry down.
Do I get the kill? Yes, I do. And what happens one on one? Who is going to win this battle?
It's going to be me with my Mini-Sentry. Seven kills and one assist. I ended up killing like
almost the entire team right there. So that was pretty awesome. And thank you guys all for
watching. Again, I appreciate it. I'll see you all next time. Take care, everybody.