Hey, today, continuing from yesterday, we are going to play the part three, or is it part four?
I don't even know. Of the FMVs. This is like part five. We've done a lot of them. We may see the end
of the FMVs tonight. It's possible. Depends on if this first one is the only real, substantial
FMV video game that I have left. There aren't any more after this that are substantial.
I still have a couple of other fucking stupid ones, but, you know. And coming up next is the
carnival. No, that's next week. What would you do if I just turned off the intro? Then there was a
carnival behind me. I pulled it forward a week. I feel like people would be very upset about that.
Jerma, what the hell are you doing? I took off work on the 21st to watch this.
Oh shit, sorry. But no, the first thing I'm going to do is called Fox Hunt. This is a game made,
I think, by Capcom. I think this was on the PS1 as well. Maybe. I'm not 100% sure.
But, I got it ready. It's just open. Do you guys want to go? Do you want to see it?
You want to see this one? No? All right. Okay, we don't have to. All right. We can sit here.
All right. Do you want me to turn the stream off? Do you want me to just go? Should I go?
Do you want me? Should I leave? All right. Fox Hunt. There it is. I don't know what to expect,
although how can you expect anything with these games? They're all a fucking mess. It is a Capcom
game. There's the logo. The original Capcom logo. That's how you know it's going to be good.
Here we go. Let's get a good countdown here. One. What? How does every James Bond movie and
every wannabe James Bond movie have a skiing scene? What?
What? Is anybody getting any of this? Why are these guys' hands all burnt?
I know they're speaking English, but I can't understand them.
Now we are cooking with gas. Oh, now we're cooking with gas.
Grace falls for a schoolteacher, but got amnesia. The teacher that has amnesia?
Can't remember she used to be a stripper. What the fuck is this?
What? Why does this guy have Mickey Mouse gloves on? I don't understand why he's wearing those.
I don't understand why he's wearing those.
Briefcase switch. These are agents and there's the CD.
This is not exactly less stock for our board codes.
Oh, the shit. What the fuck is happening? 1972 height of Cold War. KGB set me up as big time
Hollywood producer to create a television show so bad, moral backbone of the United States would
break. Movid shows and soon Russians crave the same garbage and Kremlin blame it me for destroying
communism. Now I demand screen credit for all my shows or else hidden Soviet nuclear missiles set
to launch in 36 hours will cancel Los Angeles in mid-season. And to prove I am now loyal capitalist,
you will also pay 100 million dollars cash for disc fit launch abort codes. Idiot. Moron.
Who is he talking to? Don't kill him. He still has disc.
What? I had no idea. That's not me. This is me. Was that a TV show thing?
I might have just been making that up in my head. All right, reading a book. That's not a book.
Fighting must ward off attacks from vicious frontier morons.
The pacing here is kind of just way off. So there's a Russian agent who's going to
want 100 million dollars. Oh, we have the access. Wait.
Okay, I like the control. Controlling is fun. Computer. That's it. I just press W.
No, it's S. Okay. S is I don't know how to turn the computer on. How about the lamp? Oh, the phone.
I want my stuff back. Hey, Biffy Wiffy, turn off that video camera.
Is that supposed to be a is that like a friend? Is that. Hey, Jack, freeloader,
Fremont, I know you're there. I can hear you whimpering. Pay up, Mr. Fremont.
Borrow it from your folks if you have to because I'm going to be your touch if your phone is still
connected. Jack, darling, which is nicer, your baby brother's new Mercedes or your sister's new
Lexus? Anyway, I hope all is well. I love to call your mother. You know, if they paid for watching
reruns, our eldest son would be a millionaire. Hang up. Okay. Sure. We had the skiing thing in
the beginning. How do we leave the house? TV? No, I want to. What do I have a backpack on?
How do they get the backpack? So open the fridge and eat from the fridge.
Am I doing this wrong? Do I have to touch the latch or? All right. What do you do? Oh, easy.
It is. Okay. Rob Lowe is apparently in this game. Paid bill may already be a winner.
Open it. Collection agency. Tax returns 1988. What? I have no idea what the fuck he's talking about.
Go out the window? What about the pans? No, look over here. Tacos? Is it Christmas?
Chocotero tacos. So good. It'll save your life. Jesus. I hate this.
This is just like inside the apartment of like a creepy person. Just like a weirdo every day on
UBC. I can't read this. This is a Sim's house. It is. Even the way he's spinning his keyboard
turning. How do I leave the house? Get me out of the fucking house. No, I'm not looking at
it anymore like boobs. All right. Don't forget your keys. Don't, what does it say? Let me break
it in the house. Why am I not paying attention to this guy? Why are they acting like this?
This is just the principal from Billy Madison.
Did you just kill me? I'm pressing one, two, and three. Don't do it! What happened?
I can't, I have no idea what's going on. A guy broke into my house wearing a Donatello from
the Ninja Turtles thing on his hair. Look at his eyes. I made fun of him and then we had like a weird
play fight and then he jumped out of my fourth story window. That's it. I don't have anything
else to add to that. Live! 15 frames a second. It's time for Destiny TV's online game show
extravaganza. Here's our first question for our players. What do you say, King? It's Destiny time.
What the fuck? Is this an internet cafe?
Am I the only one playing this game?
What? I walked into a bar and I'm the only person playing the fucking game.
I just got syringed. This goes up a full letter grade. This goes up two full letter grades. I got
syringed in the neck. This was an F. It's not like a C minus.
It's still an F. Not yet. That just went up two full letter grades. You guys don't understand.
A car is one. A syringe in the neck is two. All right, so I just got syringed.
I woke up. Let's see what's in this box.
He said that? Yeah, you know, put your right toe in, put your right toe out. You know that one.
This is so unsettling. It is. It is unsettling, but I'm intrigued. Is that the Joker?
Wheatley, get a load of me. These are like, it's like Truman Show type stuff where he's making TV
references every now and again. Open it. All right, how do I? Here comes the fake stomach
egg. Let's do it. Wait, hold on. Boxes? Can I open them? Is it going in here? Flowers? Is it food?
Cigars? That was pretty, that was pretty good. What? What else is in here?
The classic, the classic. I don't know what this is. I'm going to sneeze into it. I hope I don't
get in any trouble anymore. What about their computer? Can I turn on their computer? Yeah.
No, this game was made by a fucking alien. No, back, back up. I don't want to try to turn the
computer on again. I'm hungry. He just starts smashing it. What else on the table? Not that
I can see it. I have to do that. I go back to the top secret. There it is. How the hell would I
ever have found that? What? What? Give me the top secret thing. I just want to, it says top
secret. Just give it to me. It's right here. Stop knocking stuff over and making like Jim Carrey
faces and noises and shit and pick up the top secret data. Spies must wash hands before returning
to work. Personal hygiene is no big secret. All right. That's like fine. Right? You know what I
mean? There's more. They've more stuff in the CAA credit card. Okay. I stole the credit card out
of here. Do I have an inventory? I don't think I even have an inventory. There's more. This guy
has more shit in his pocket. Is that a sandwich? Why does this guy have so much stuff in his
pockets? You got more stuff in here? Okay. So now we go back to the door. It's a spy weapon. Yeah.
But what about where's my inventory? Nuclear missiles, do's and don't. Nuclear missiles,
do's and don't. Well, at least they have a manual. Did I miss something else over here? No.
We can just call Washington and tell the director he's a spy weapon. This maniac also has new
ward codes to stop Los Angeles from becoming the world's largest barbecue pit. He wants his payback
from his shows of the 70s and now you want me to tell Langley that he's bluffing?
Hello, Jack. I'm the dealer. I am the croupier. And I'm not supposed to talk to strangers. We
apologize for the circumstance, Jack. We're CIA. After the end of the Cold War, we've had cutbacks.
Serious cutbacks, Jack. We need you to deliver a briefcase in exchange for a package. Now,
if you do this, we will deposit $100,000 in your bank account. It's not that much.
Our development will be your contacts. Well, you know, um. That's Dr. Reva levels of under.
I'm not a spy. We have reason to believe that the double agent has compromised our security
and our identities. We don't need a spy, just a guy. This is going to be dangerous.
It sounds great, really. I can't believe my luck. But if I wanted to be filled with lead,
I'd continue to eat the paint off my bedroom walls. We'll give you $500 in advance. Cool.
$500? $100,000? No, add a couple of zeros. 20 years ago, the Fox had a kid with one of
those hot TV starlets. A girl. I wonder if she's cute.
He's fucking terrifying. This guy's terrifying. Where's the Pessy?
Is this the president? Who's the president? Oh dear. There is your CD-ROM reader. You
probably won't need it. I already got one. Not like this one, oh boy. It'll play anything,
including coded government discs from any country on earth. Cool. And my vibe has been
looking for the wolf. Wow, here you go. It's a wolf. The coolest thing I could possibly
fucking hand you. A non-region-locked CD player. Wow. Unbelievable. No, don't-
Another cocktail? Wise guy, I'm not sure. Uh-oh, it just went up another two letter grades.
I swear I'll never drink again.
Okay, so now I still don't have an inventory though. I think I just have this shit.
What is the credit card? Ah, that Global Terminological Threats. Fox. Codenamed the Fox.
H-53. Ukraine. National origin. Uh, the king of disinformation. The real name. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So the number one spy during the 70s and early 80s. Ryzenpol's particular former film director.
He was enlisted by the Soviet KGB to destroy America by polluting its communications network.
During the 70s, he secretly created over half of all American television stories. Storylines and
plots or episodes were sent anonymously to the networks where executives took credit and made
millions. The Fox was promoted to the rank of KGB Colonel and was eventually one of the only five
men granted access to the launch codes for Russia's nuclear arsenal. The Fox traveled to Los Angeles
for a period in the early 70s and hobnobbed with the entertainment elite. There were even rumors
of an affair with a young starlet and possibly a child. Interesting. Soviets planned an attempt to
mesmerize America by sinking the level of entertainment so low that national morals and
moral morale would also die. It was a terrible failure. The disinformation plan backfired and
eventually Russians desired the same subversive television. His work has been greatly credited
for destroying communism worldwide. Rated extremely dangerous. Rumors abound that the Fox has stolen
the launch codes for Russia's remaining nuclear missile. CIA contact made and broken codes may
now be available on the internet for some reason. I thought it said on the internet.
Codes may not be available on the internet on the international black market. Oh,
that is what that is. I'm sorry, it's hard to read because this is like in a small window on
my screen and I've blown it up on your screen because I'm trying I have to squint to see this.
Okay, enter access code. Wait, these are all hold away. This is a mouse button. Look at all
these fucking things. Look at this shit. Fast cars and the chameleon is a former surfer dude
turned spy for hire. Son of a former female KGB agent and a California surf boat.
Favorite drink whiskey. Remember that bingo extortionist code name bingo age 32 from Montreal
self employed flower arranger archery ice sculpting bingo magnum is an international gambler
and extortionist who has vowed to finally earn the big score. Her goal is to obtain cash precious
medals and negotiable securities young beautiful and deadly. Miss Magnum is a university educated
mathematician with a photographic memory trained in her native Canada at the Royal Canadian Mounted
Police Academy in Ottawa to disappear from her job as an analyst in the anti terrorist section
and hooked up with members of the Quebec separatist movement. Okay, extremely dangerous.
We are when we know bingo unknown unknown presumed to be American. This computer hacker
is the only person to ever break the code to level one classified CIA files. He's the screen
name marauding avenger extra cheese and l chubby and has perpetrated a number of annoying pranks
rated annoying. Is that the guy from the beginning the guy that broke into my house and jumped out
of the window? Company personnel stationed or on assignment throughout the world are judged to
security risk if private behavior dictates a possible intelligence breach evidence confirmed
by two unrelated company sources indicates a breach company personnel may be compromised
via personal information or financial inducement by a foreign intelligence service
corporation or an individual individual okay okay okay okay okay company okay director level okay
Alan and Alan okay they got they gave they gave the game a be like just like you did okay
Sir Hugh Benchley promos okay access denied okay all right the dork computer systems analyst
who also approved also approved in weapons combat activate only for information analysis
programming proficient in satellite data access weapons trajectory okay currently deep in cover
in unspecified southern california location employed as video game developer okay the dork
this is me new world order i'll have san jose all right this is a whole book all right end of the
end of the book all right i got that cd i can read it if i need to can i get food
do i have to my have to leave my backpack on the whole game
why is he doing like the snorting all right i'm gonna leave wait i check my phone
hi jackie are you there are you there are you there oops i forgot it's the first of the month
that means you're not answering the phone it's still the first of the month
hey turn off that video camera
always aspen okay what's this this is like the weird laptop ipad thing
the guy on the phone sounds like homer simpson everybody sounds like homer simpson
he is an accountant from las vegas always believed he should be a world war one
but boss he's blind we are going to put them in an old car shaped up and make care of them
once again we will prove that all is not what it seems
boss you're a genius welcome friends welcome
i could could you ever watch tv like this i don't know what it is
with some people i'll tell you we can't throw the book out i'll talk about this after this
we've searched everywhere it's not there aha i knew it rotate that table 90 degrees
so i can't you can't watch fucking can't watch movies like that
god i gotta get a new tv right exactly because i people that download movies illegally and i've
seen an illegal movie before you know what i mean like a oh i downloaded this i don't know like
15 years ago i was in college and when my roommate wanted to show me right and i it looks like that
it's like all crusty it's like fucking you can't even hear what people are saying it looks like
just go fucking watch the movie is i can't even fucking stand it that was 15 years ago
that's not true anymore they are it is i wait it's not like somebody has like the
like the handy cam in the seat like pointing at the screen people don't do that anymore
cam rips are mostly well that's it it's got a name it's called cam rips what's this guy doing
oh my god he's like is he laughing or crying all right they it's blu ray now oh well just pretend
that you're like just pretend it's 15 years ago i couldn't stand it i remember sitting there
watching uh i believe it was napoleon dynamite was the movie and i had already seen it napoleon
dynamite like twice in the theater and i remember just sitting there and thinking i can't hear this
what they're saying i can't see what they're doing i am not watching this movie i'm experiencing
noise and everybody turned and looked at me and it's like what and then i got up and went to the
bathroom and when i came back to go back to the room where everyone was watching the movie the
door was closed so i fucking booted up world of warcraft and it was at that moment that i became
one of the best priests on the whole server so you know it's all good that was where i started
the journey uh-oh scary music it's this guy what who the fuck is this person
is what
what is he talking about what's going on just wait here for a minute will you wait here you're gonna
you're gonna hand this to me fuck over the door i just want to see the movie wait he hasn't
what do i have to do what am i supposed to do is real i think this is like a dream this is like
is this is actually happening
that actually is just jim carrey wait a minute i don't have to do the whole thing again do i
should i save it oh you got me what should i call it file name and save file as so what's
going on here right here why am i saving it now i don't even know how to give that how do i get
back to this menu hold on there's there's no like menu screen i guess we'll just this is not
good is it time for a speed run we might not have to speed run now i pressed resume restore
how do you save the game i don't think there's a way to save a game in mid game going to control
look there's nothing here move spin use shoot look left look right look back punch block kick
there's no like menu let's see if i can speed run it i can
you have to see that i'm sorry okay now we have to wait for the guy to come in the
collection agency here we go okay all right you know the macho man randy savage that video
where it's just him breathing i'm making one of those right now don't forget your key stupid
all right here we go all right get in here fight me let's go what happens if i hit escape
oh escape doesn't get a menu or anything tab tab no tab is skip i'm gonna press up
okay so i figured it out the button you have to press is x cool so how the hell do i save a file
okay got it it's i'm on one so x is to pause the game
how the fuck would i have known how to do that okay you can put the you can put the menu down now
what the hell is going on did i just turned off my brain apparently okay
all right sure i guess that worked we're good okay press the button when does he come in
when does the dude come in and that's like looking outside
believe why won't he i can't trigger this event i have to lick the plate you're right
fuck out the knife lick plate out chocotero tacos so good will save your life
hey little fishy okay i'm ready i can't eat the fish that's not it's not an eat fish game
why would i want to eat the fish anyways all right please get in here so i can skip everything
okay my keys what i didn't get these before
how do i get to the fucking door it's over here i need to just turn a little bit more turn
spin what is spin what a spin s it's not doing anything oh my god i just want to leave
look at the people i'm just trying to get the door in focus but i can't get the door in focus
it's i want to go that way holy shit i'm gonna lose my mind it's left no not the phone left it's
right here the door is right here what the fuck is happening i didn't even click
the door is over here why can i not get it into view anymore the game does not want me to look
at the door ever again that's the only way i can see this door i have to be at the table and hit
right twice how the fuck do i here we go jack freemont your cup is mine freddy
i'll see you fred i'm gonna date with destiny at least she's got a friend for me
that was just the three students but they cut out all the parts that were funny
okay here we go wake up all right let's save the game here
save it as one dot pml replace yes let's go okay now it's a question of uh touching everything
touch everything touch everything touch everything i'm almost there
bear with me twice three four five times in the jacket six times in the jacket seven times in the
jacket that's it sneeze sneeze into the jacket computer wash the hands why does this work now
this didn't work before what i say we can just call washington and tell the director he's a
this maniac also has i've just been staring at the computer all day and all night
they had their conversation and they left sun's coming out now okay remember reading this all
right save again save as one dot pml yes resume we're good to go let's do it now what am i supposed
to do here this guy comes in and he does like the weird fucking bugs bunny bullshit and then he
leaves and then i have to dodge what he's in the fridge you're kidding right no huh i was
lying in wait it's different go away you've lived past expiration day i have to fight him again
you got chocolate in my peanut butter got peanut butter on my chocolate
it
is the guy gonna walk in here with like a gun goldfish i ate a fish i did
oh now he jumps out of the window okay there's that there's that bugs bunny bullshit now we're
gonna get bugs bunny bullshit part two he's outside
all right how do i do this
you know i'm not gonna pull this
now
why all right so what about what about the guy with the the donatello headband the fat guy
why was he not out there no it would have been really fucking ridiculous if he was lying out
there too all right let's go he was outside the door uh what am i doing here we go
no all right he's in the fucking fridge i forgot is he walking with a drumstick
and then he jumps out
all right see you later thanks for visiting
yes he just landed a second ago he got up there real fast all right get me the all right go
other window no no no no no it's just a different window
oh i have to save it right when he's pointing the gun you know what i mean
what about the knife i don't know if i can do it i'm gonna have to try to like attack him
do i still have any of the stuff that i wish i could have i wish i could look in like an
inventory or something i want to go to the table no table all right god let's go
what
okay just in case something goes wrong here this is gonna be two two
why did he point at him all right we're good all right so what the fuck how do i
know i can't turn this way that way look i can only go i can only go out the window
i don't have any enter s try all the windows didn't i already do the left window
and the right window that's the okay there's this window what about this way
to jump or not to jump i already did both windows
oh i did the windows both of them
i okay i'm gonna punch punch block kick punch block kick punch block kick
what the fuck just keep spinning around i don't think that's gonna work okay so um
the walkthrough says to jump out the right window what
what this is the left window this is the right window
but this is the left window you only can go out the left window what happened what
what happened meet me out what a trip i'll say eight o'clock my place
make it dictionary rewind am i dead damn bloody nuisances undercover outfits and all
i mean he's such a disappointment frank who now what we have here is a dna verification factor
try not to break it we've identified your target's dna and match it to
i i guess that is the scene meet me out what a trip
i'll see wasn't they just concrete on the ground eight o'clock that doesn't make any sense
make it dictionary i jumped out the left window on the first try and i died here is a dna
verification factor try not to break it we've identified your target's dna and match it to a
graphic display inside this helmet his code name is the fox now non-matching targets will be in
green the fox will be in red wait and the faint flicks of red you see a similar dna strands that
i share with the fox now the fox has always prided himself on being able to blend in with the crowd
this should separate him out nicely but i would have laughed at that work that would have been
awesome if it worked what if you think they're people if you're trying to scare the people
cool what am i what what did it say huh what mr crab said feel good feel good oh good
okay we need to i need another oh god damn it
i'm going to i'm going three i'm following them who am i following why is he running so
frantically i don't even know who i'm following oh that's him wait that's the guy briefcase from
the beginning what am i stopping for
stop skipping i have not pressed a button you are seeing how the game is put together on its own
i'm not skipping anything
they can't take away our pride
i like you
yes that was so hard
yes
what
just a delivery boy
but jason they've forced our water killed our cattle and burnt down
what happened story it's an observation but um i think you should get out of here obvious
i just thought i could help oh behind me behind no where is she but you're not shaving my head
oh
are these scenes are filled out of order i feel pretty good at johnsy what happened to me oh hello
dear boy i live under the weather mixed chinese with mexican stomach feels like he's gonna explode
doctor yes look i'd love to discuss new valve cuisine but i figure you're here for a reason
quite right doctor doctor both
i've got a bad case of blood a small turbine to store behind the binding
this will be very useful in los angeles jack are you okay oh yeah you know a couple
little bruises but hey hey super spy i saw her first i'll be this week from shirley mcclay
it's too tight to a little snug i think maybe good evening mr freeman how nice it is to finally
meet you they've infiltrated be good boy and give us disc disc let me take a wild guess here that
you're the bad guys girls weissenheimer nurses oh shit
oh
that was completely unnecessary what the fuck am i doing to this guy
did i just faith heal him wait does everybody have everybody so many things going on
big send off and i've got the dish and i've got the girl
waving yeah i gotta i'm
oh for the love of god this guy has to happen again okay i'm gonna take us up i'm gonna skip
every two or three seconds and you will not notice a difference from in real time ready
just assuming that it was going to kill all those fight scenes but it's not it goes right okay it
goes right to you in the chair it's got rockets on how do i stop how do i stop the fucking chair
how do i stop the chair i can't stop the chair if i'm supposed to be finding somebody
made it i made it i didn't make it
why do i have to go around so many times in a circle and the noise is
and he's on a rocket that thing doesn't have that much fuel and how am i doing this around
us or no one has grabbed the chair there's like dozens and dozens and dozens of employees here
no one has thought to just like like push me over or grab the chair i'm going around the
circle or on same hallway and no one can stop me go grab a fucking mattress from one of the beds
in the in the hospital and put it up in front of me do a reverse wily coyote to the roadrunner on
me oh this is fucking unbelievable okay here we go all right he's still wrestling with that guy's
brush what why did that go so slowly you guys talking about rockets the rockets don't fucking
matter it's going two miles per hour i can't go that way i'm gonna fuck it up straight
and then i'm gonna try it left did i do it what i did it you to get a bath right here
i didn't save the game what wait hold on it's not it
somebody help me i can't stop
oh my god where are they what's going on the rockets are gonna explode i don't know how this
is still going on they're gonna run out of video files to show what i can't look at chat either
so if you guys are trying to help me i can't look beating accident you know thank god i had
ride the elevator down
what the fuck wait i why i can't laugh anymore it hurts i can't i have to stop doing this
please let's stop second floor pull my finger
oh go back in the chair second floor second floor what are you doing what is this this is new
i have to i have i need to take a break i'll be back i have to get like i have to i'll be back in
like fucking 10 minutes i'm not i'm kidding i'll be back in like fucking five minutes
my whole body hurts that was one of the most fucking ridiculous stupid goddamn things i've
ever seen in anything i've ever done uh on this stream like in a video game like what the fuck was
that for i can't fucking believe it this just went up with that i that qualifies as a car i think
another phone letter grade it's at like a b minus i'll be right back when i when i was just peeing i
just peed all over my fucking floor and all over the toilet seat and everything i said to clean it
up i just started i just saw in my i started peeing in mid stream mid piss i just started laughing
fucking hysterically because i kept seeing an image of that guy with the crutches just they kept
like fucking every of the maybe every four or five scenes was them knocking the crutches out from
underneath the guy and like ripping it out of his hands that was just ridiculous they're dressing
nurses outfits and they're just like fucking just making this guy's life a living hell they
weren't even looking for me and now i'm gonna do all that shit again i just had to like clean up i
just had to clean my bathroom let me just open up my pineapple juice like that guy that guy like
broke his leg or something oh that's so fucking ridiculous all right i'm gonna try this again
and now i so apparently it is this long i guess you have to go all the way to the top of the
elevator and then don't go in the elevator a third time just use elevator all right i'm gonna try
here we go three two one action right here where's the elevator there it is okay there's this one
there's the next scene we go out what's that scooby doo i just heard like record floor
what was that no no what the fuck i did it did i i didn't do it i didn't do it yet get out of here
what hold on i stop the first floor dub dub is this urine
i'm on first first floor what am i doing back on the first floor
what back up into the second floor let's stop second floor hey pull my finger
i have no idea how to get the fuck out of this i'm stuck in a dream oh god
somebody just copy pasted how to do this you gotta find the exit on the first floor
first floor and then so go to the first floor and then fucking find the exit on the first floor
this is why is this doing this five is supposed to be our in the elevator first floor go straight
and then turn right and left am i on the first floor not yet all right let's get the first floor
oh
so now i'm on the second floor
first floor first floor guys i'm sorry i have to go first floor
and then right immediate left straight is that correct right straight left beating accident you
know thank god i had enough time to save those little kittens right straight left
right straight left right immediately it's straight right left left straight right right
straight left straight right straight i ain't listening to you guys anymore i'm going for it
i'm just going to do it on my own free will rocket chair he's in the rocket chair forever
let's stop second floor second floor pull my finger
i can't i'm losing control i'm having trouble actually flicking on things right now
oh
god damn it please all right straight right left on the first floor
speeding accident you know thank god i had enough time to save those little kittens you know straight
right left i can't say if i tried that before it doesn't do anything right right left straight
right i missed it i tried just don't go on the elevator what no i tried to
why did they have to show me that why did they show me that scene
why did they show that to me they were trying to throw me off so bad oh fuck all right i'm
taking audio out i'll turn the audio off make the jump cut sound effects
i can't i'm nope i'm not doing that
doing that please stop fucking hurting that guy leave that guy alone
it's gonna fucking ruin everything in the elevator and then once i'm in the elevator
i tried i missed here we go all right straight right left thank god i had enough time to
save those little kittens you know
next up saving doesn't do anything straight right left please help me debate please
the guy got to do to get a sponge bath right here
huh
this is gonna kill me i'm gonna fucking pass out on screen i'm gonna look a guide up i'm gonna get
the guide myself give me where's the guy where the fuck is the guy i'm looking it up right now
no fox hunt guide okay oh my god so in the hospital from the third floor the first floor
t junction proceed to the t junction and then turn left continue along until you find an elevator
on the second floor on the next elevator first floor go straight at first then turn right and
next until you find the exit what go straight at first then turn right and left next until you
find the exit you have to go up to the second floor and then back down fuck just keep going
left and right until you find the exit so it's straight then right and then the next time you
can take a left wow god damn it all right i'm trying to go too fast god fuck no i don't want
to do it again i have to take off the sound i'm trying this one more time this fucking rocket
chair second floor let's go don't go in the elevator back down to the first floor
oh straight right and then the next time i can take a left here we go straight right
left the next time i can take a left it's not there oh i get it don't go back in oh my god
that was fucking ridiculous okay i did it would you just quit fooling around if you had the disk
this is because of the disk look i think it would just be safer if i just get you out and let's not
forget they're after me too okay have a look nightmare to give a listen no really relations
my friend but sorry this is not exactly less stuff for a board course you are about to do things and
go places you never dreamed of i digress less than 24 hours remain by the way thanks for the cash
casino what do you casino how am i supposed to trust you we'll just pay you when it's over fine
where floor decide so what are you gonna do i'm getting out of this mess can we get the key first
what g oh wow isn't it it's worth a hundred grand they're gonna give you a hundred g's for one
lock cd i'm missing it in the trash last night
hey it's okay jack i'm not greedy for partners right i'm only gonna ask 50 g's for this
cashier's
what the fuck what just happened what hello what's going on freemont you're ready to call brent
oh
i tried to run him down straight at the weirdo approach
why is he always wearing these gloves why is he eating the fucking flowers don't look at me
did he kill me with me is he looking at me no
oh
that joke is in the simpsons
six hour express car phone please it's a lot of money that you have in your
possible weapons violation
what the fuck is going on disc two let's go
this game is fucking outrageous disc two let's do it using discs in 2019 yeah that's what happens
when you have to pretend that your computer is 20 plus years old las vegas welcome to las vegas
nevada elvis is here all right do i get to are you serious this is this is fucking awesome
i get to play slot machines and shit let me go let me in let me on those slot machines let
me in that blackjack table let me on those jack we think it's downstairs in the show goals
dressing room this id is only charged for five minutes after you enter so make it fast there's
uh you know this neo parmesan from fucking rest of development jack freemont
gene yeah not what i say neil
get ready to cover the screen don't
uh i couldn't i uh no i went back here again oh god damn it i gotta switch discs i didn't
fucking save it i have to switch discs save the game switch discs again get through ah is there
i deserve it no you're right i do it's all good the history of video games are right here
here all right let's do this get in the car all right go what's up there we go there's the money
insert disc two and then save the game remind me to do this if we get to disc three
because i will forget and i won't do it because yes there is a third disc if yeah if we get to
disc three okay here we go save eight there it is let's just make sure it's there eight it is
okay let's go so i go down here into the show girls room and then i have to fight the show girls
jack freemont talent scab yeah i'm casting a 100 million dollar movie about uh show girls
interested double mugs yeah i'm uh shooting a movie about hawaii i'm shooting it up in canada
save a little money all right here comes let's try for like a kick that's just part of the story
let's try this
okay so
block block block block okay block is two punches one kick is three so i was pressing two
two let's try for a punch
no no block what okay i'm just gonna mash two
that's not gonna work you go girl what
i'm trying to block and
i'm trying to time it to block and what's the guy say block the first two then punch the third
what look two two two
this is this is blocked i think there is timing it has to be what the fuck just happened
uh isn't that a there is timing see oh how's that not a block
god damn no you go
no every time like you go two two two
two fuck is that it i didn't oh fuck don't
no don't make me do this again do not make me block
i hate this i don't want to do this again i have to fucking focus end this please is this the same
person kill again ginger i'm so confused with this friend ginger what the fuck is going on
no no i don't want to do it again i don't want to do it again
can't rage no i'm just shaking in my chair that was so hard toddler tantrum yeah i'm just like
ah fuck wait wait save it here
all right i have to stop i have to stop it's too fucking hard oh no it's too hard to do this
it's too hard to do that like 10 of these in a row all right this is my last try i'm fucking
turning off sound because sound fucking me up turning up sound turning off the game
i need to see this game is so crazy i have to fucking get by this part this is our only
opportunity to ever see this game and how fucking crazy it is i can't have anybody watching what
i'm doing all right i'm almost there i got i keep i keep losing to the third person i keep losing
to the third person i don't i don't know how i did the first time i have no idea i tried punching
i've tried blocking i've tried kicking i cannot beat this third person i'm trying to kick her
it won't work here look i'll give you something else to watch i'm looking at the guide right now
it says kick the third one i tried kicking four times in a row didn't work i have to get through
this shit this is my last try no god
my voice is gone i just fucking screamed for a full 10 straight seconds i just i fucking screamed
and i it's i it's gone i can't i'm sorry this is gonna be my last try on this and then i'm gonna
have to move on to another game what the hell i cheat i can cheat i can cheat i can cheat guys i
can cheat
fuck i did it i did it i didn't cheat suspect second disc in colorado ski hut stop all cia
i did that like two weeks ago i would say that was like childish and not funny i did that a couple
weeks ago on the connect stream where are we going i don't even get to play like a casino game
all is that's the game's budget
i would spend i would spend one million dollars on a stream and then i would plant like 600
billion trees ski hut which one should i go to two i'm pretty good at skiing i don't know who's this
all right do i have to do anything two go to two they found me apparently that guy was having
trouble that was an actor that wasn't even a guy that's like a stunt man why would i be doing this
now everybody what ted blake is rod nickles
i'm lying down watching tv on my portable tv display did we get to do anything here
but do i just have to watch this guy ski in like a prison outfit oh no can i resume
ski hut let's try let's try four
he just goes off the cliff but what if he was all right what if he landed here we go what
what i'm losing points right you're supposed to go around them or
i can't do it it's too much it's it's the stupid it's the fucking rocket chair again
all right i never skied competitively in my entire life i don't know anything about skiing i don't
know how the points work you you go to the left of the blue flag and the right of the red flag
is that correct or did i just describe our political party which one is it yeah i got
right that's so hard what i didn't do it right
check the poles you're supposed to fall but only in a different place you have to fall the right
time what did he just shot me in the head
i don't know what's going on uh i have i've cheated but i'm looking like i'm looking at
like england right now that's like a picture of great britain that wasn't even like trees
oh no no no no no ski hut you die you go i got i have yeah i know i gotta really pay attention
oh my god i clicked it i was right there i was right there god damn it man
it's been a while since that fat guy came back he'll show up again what what happened
what did i do wrong there i don't understand what happened there i i went i did it i went left
please it was too many head hits okay
just go around them what do you think i'm trying to do no it is left right left right
i'm doing it too fast that's the problem okay i have to do it right okay i need to save it
uh what am i on 12 i don't know let's go 12
all right i i guess i have to just aim it on them and just click when the things were there
i don't know okay
it's just
what happened i don't know what i did wrong i don't understand what i did incorrect
why i'm so overstimulated okay we can start from here i can't do it like that
i just drive by the same guy twice huh
do i have to be faster or slower i think i have to be faster where the fuck is that guy
no audio take it off i don't know what to do i got him okay there's only how did i miss
sweat is pouring out of my armpits oh there's more save the game we're skipping
let's go we're doing 14 we're skipping 13 14 let's go
i'm having the same reactions that he is
oh
this old bit that i'm too nervous and too shook up to tell you anything
well snowboarders are trying to kill me but i killed all of them
oh
all the money you said this budget was two million first million seller came out 1979 december 9th
ubc one minute spot on episode there's most of it dom on the door or jack i'm impressed but if you
act now you'll put an unsightly wrinkle in my master plan but that's not all i like to think of
these as nuclear accidents for fun and profit most of these other so-called commercial hosts they
sit back in los angeles they hog their pathetic where's the ho ho ho witness missile it's mr
bad sweater guy your toast that little bald chick and all of her minions well they won't have any
weight problems anymore they'll all be able to fit in one ashtray hello phone psychic what
about my love life well you don't have one did you dad what is rob loathe competition you're
you're pretty uh los angeles gone a secret satellite will beam my infomercials all over
the world to every country i desire i will remake the world so you see jack i can't let you
rob lowe the bad guy
but uh i thought we have to do something with you have to punch
why is it dubbed what's what's what the fuck is going on
what why are there like four rob lows even though i know the rest where's
to be a skinhead now i'm an idiot who the fuck are these people
he's the pilot too he's everybody rob lowe is everyone do i have a parachute is my backpack
in a parachute this whole time i'm still wearing my backpack in the very beginning of the game
it's this guy the fucking weirdo what
there's a green screen am i gonna fight the rob lows in the air no there's no way
i didn't even shoot him somebody shot him accidentally what the fuck is going on am i
in control get him now they're dropping cartoon anvils on let it go let the anvil go just let
it go don't hold the whole time why would you fucking hold on to that that was weighing you down
oh that's bad no it's not
i honestly don't even know who i'm aiming at here no don't ah just don't touch him
don't touch the anvil i keep grabbing the anvils on just reflex
oh get him don't touch the anvil let it come okay he had like five clones not like 30 people
i'm out of ammo oh that's not good
open the backpack i landed on my feet i i i just landed
i didn't skip it i promise right all right here it is what drugs did we take
um i don't know they didn't add the parachute scene they probably rented a money and they thought
hey well we don't have any money but don't you think it'd be funny if he just landed
and they probably all laughed on set probably had like a good time making this
to see you too we need to get out of here but you'd be killed where are we going now
this is the fire fest of video games
so what we're going back to vegas then we just leave vegas
thank you come on come on baby daughter she heard nice i need a room and some information
that's nice i need hemorrhage surgery at the force
why don't i see if i can get someone to talk to us oh there he is again
hey gene pardon me joe
i did it right uh wait this actually helps
evening old boy oh no there he is i'm sorry about what happened the last time
but the clue is it's still somewhere down there great but now they're on with machine guns right
now remember you still only have five minutes down there okay old timer let's go i got a show to do
that's pretty good elvis thank you very much that's pretty good elvis coming king
oh not this shit again um i'm afraid to open this okay it was nothing it was
what there's a trap door here am i just taking shit what is underneath here is this drugs
what is going on why would they be letting me do this
what the fuck is going on am i watching tv
he's been shot in the in the in the no in the bud let's make haste but doc don't you need no
tools i'm a proctologist son these are my tools what the fuck turn it off why would you watch this
i didn't even why did i click that well i didn't even do anything
no i don't want to watch it again what is in here ah mr freemont we have all russian expression
oh
you blow on my head and kiss on my neck wrong i blow off your head and piss down your neck
oh what i that was i what do i got nothing i i don't got shit i got nothing oh no that was too
it was outrageous i what the fuck does happen that was like these games are fucking ridiculous
what am i doing now it was so easy for you not to do that you dumped that on yourself on purpose
anything else to do i don't think so what about the door over here no now i'm going up the stairs
i i don't know what that was i just planted something oh no not this
mr freemont thanks for dropping in nice place who does your decorating please don't struggle
to bring what's going on here well since you're going to die anyway i guess there's
an elevator of clashbacks from the rocket wheelchair income for the cia since washington
cut our funding we've been skimming off these slot machines for years years i'm gonna make it
oh it's a they're just dumping like a laundry chute of coins down here
this is the scam operation okay why are they all in why they don't dress like this
you could clearly be in like casual clothing you don't have to why they dress like that
they're not handling hazardous materials you is kind of chinese torture thing up above you is
mrs fletner she's been gambling for 36 hours straight pumping in those george washington's
hoping for that big 10 million dollar pay off 200 million nickel something like that
for what she doesn't know is that machine's been fixed to never pay off
look up above you mr freemont this is like an old lady don't even think about such a thing
they eat alone or burn right through your fragile little ass buried alive and munched
okay what are they locking me in here and i'm gonna get it's gonna fill up and kill me
gene for 36 hours but the last time it's not gonna pay off i think it's ready i can feel it
i'll tell you what they're having a pretty nice and special
leave my lucky machines in that gym
what you hear something funny
did she win what was i holding jackpot barkeep hold on how did wait wait wait wait how did i get out
how did i get out how did i get out of there did i just open the door wait was it 17 i don't know
i'm just gonna start it too i'm just gonna do the thing that you know like developers do and
programmers do and code and they make new new pieces of software i don't know was it like 1.1
was it 1.12 was it 1.012 then just just just make it just make it 1.2 make it 2.0 turn it into 1.3
1.4 minus 2.0 i get out of here
what did i order water on the rocks
no that shit gets you thrown out busy trying not to get killed
great by the way he's the one who's been trying to kill me
no he won't try anything in public trust me why should i trust you i can modify the angle of the
casino cameras to take a peek into the dealer's whole garden and once we know what's coming
we can cheat the cheater so we're gonna cheat at the casino to the guy that's cheating there's a
guy cheating at the table already we're gonna cheat to make him loop just got fucking earpiece
hanging up buy yourself something nice that would have been great if they had just shown that
and kept it there
what the fuck are they saying
uh your rob low portion of the video game development
we just got a gym from the office it's in every game okay what do you mean right or left
well mr freeman i see you two would like to beat out got a hunch what did i pick
16 being a blackjack player this is not how you bet in blackjack
did you use a card sir i bet right or left in blackjack what stand no i wanted to hit
it
i just lost a million dollars if i stood on 16
room in 10 minutes are they gonna find no i have to win oh no hey buddy have i ever played blackjack
yeah i didn't know it they said take a card i don't know what i was supposed to do
there was no like button on the screen there was no like oh button press yes no what was
the exactly is that the guy the guy on the plane oh shit no not rob low the guy that was on top of
the plane we made it to disc three how many discs are there total this is it the three is the last
one 16 uh take a card take a card jack i think i stood so what the hell happens now i think
there's branching story in this uh what i should have done the real thing to do would have been
depending on the disc so we're on disc three this is disc three now right that would have been
smart if i had done that i should have done two like 21 22 23 24 please you too jack it's not what
you think the wolf is working with the cia to help stop the launch only half right we're working with
the wolf no you told me that mushroom cloud will send our budget sky wait it's a total double
cross here you are sick
what do i do i can't block you punch like a girl frances lose what i thought i just like died after
saying that big putt shake my legs and
good mi5 has recently passed on some information special yes i didn't touch that he did it's not
the volts but the amps that count i need to save this holy shit that wait wait hold on a minute
that's a that was true somebody said that the amps it's the fucking amps that's a callback
from a couple days ago when i said a 10 million volts and then somebody corrected me and said
jeremy you're an idiot it's not the volts it's the amps that actually electrocute you and i was like
oh okay sorry well then it was the amps and then somebody else in chat said that that was a lie
and that person was fucking with me and it actually is the bolts that that electrocute you
so i i'm gonna i guess this game decided that that's the decider there
it's the watts that kill you they both matter well either way it's the electricity that kills you
yeah five has recently passed on some information shoot the special cheers but the amps that count
nice what's up filling out your men's applications looks like you're the dummy
cut us the final disc final disc with the launch code you guys are so smart why is it 90 degrees
oh no the two-person horse jump the two-person horse jacket bit got him nice kick he's done
kick again punch uh what does this guy take to die
oh do i do this do i have to walk away leave s oh yeah it was turning on it actually it was
turning around kick good don't come on good jabs shit did i get him i trapped him oh that was a
good one now what i think i have to turn around again
he's just sitting there waiting i hate this i hate this but i love it at the same time
down down him down him don't all right first try i got it repeating me repeating me
and the heads together free studio style oh i cannot wait to save because i don't want to
do that again all right here we go oh all right then in that case you can't lock me up in here
can't let's see we have over 200 murders 100 random acts of violence property damage totaling
in the millions police captain i think you're trying to seduce me vandalism vandalism never
in case you haven't realized a buddy you do not have a license to kill
or tell bad jokes let's see what we have here what's in them what's in there look this is no
joke a nuclear missile is about to blow up los angeles and i'm the only person that can stop it
that's a pretty good joker left i think i blew it i would rank that at like top five
oh
you know what we should do we should get all the people of american all the people of russia
together young woman looks like we would need one big boat a guy looks like you're a genius
and you're weird no you are cool
he still has the backpack on
if you get the no yeah he does it's it's over his right shoulder that's unfucking
believable that's actually ridiculous whatever they pay you it is not enough i expect you still
want to stop those awful russians thought i'd cross my mind i've got to get you out of here
i'm not getting in there don't worry just flush on my cue flush and stand back back
okay so what happened to gene parmesan is he still alive did gene parmesan just sacrifice
himself to get me out of jail give it a break before i have to kill you hey an xbt5000 portable
cd that would hurt so bad back into the government he took that really well how does it like you get
a hold of this thing well i'm a spy you know my uh pathetic life is just a cover where are we so
where's the fancy cars the beautiful women uh no car um lost a woman somewhere and that
guaranteed our own nuclear destruction great good job bummer hey is this cd your clue
ladies our secret weapon has arrived how you doing good great and job
not quite i think they decoded something and crossing the x and the y pits
us freeman freeman here so humong cord hired you to throw us off the trail
godfrey and goodfoot bad acting bad wardrobe and bad luck for you there is a fourth disc
tri ambassador hotel visual boulevard you got a car freddy yeah you keep the xbt5000
i'll get a ride i kind of wish he had his thing around his eyes he felt like a superhero
i want like a superhero sidekick friend right i
thank you very much for handing over a final disc what's with all this the new world order
will be based on software planes tanks missiles all are obsolete ideas entertainment is where the
real power lies with hollywood corn where will the world get the entertainment and software
that it craves in russia there are brilliant scientists engineers software designers writers
actors are starving in a few moments for who rules with ideas rules the world where my country of
course i gotta be ready three quarters of all the world's moot to this building soon the world will
experience its most bizarre and horrible nuclear accident yet i mean this is remember back this is
back in the 90s guys they were probably only like 125 modems on earth in like 1992
all telecommunications will be switched from the united states okay it'll work why are you telling
me this where is customary in american entertainment for a bad guy to tell good
guy what he's doing just before he kills him he forgot the good guy always wins
it really is just a jim carrey impression it is with like the wrist slapping like that one
thing i forgot to tell you save it it would be making it would just make it so much better if
you just said like take care now bye bye then and then go to the left you know he's going to
do something like that i think he already has actually like three times
the world will experience its most bizarre and horrible nuclear accident yet
a missile will be launched from russia by mistake and 30 minutes later all telecommunications
will be switched from the united states okay it'll work why are you telling me this
we're like over three hours in this is probably entertainment for a bad guy to tell good guy
what he's doing i don't really i don't know who that is i kind of do you forgot the good guy
the good guy always wins
it was that was a really moment
what that guy didn't even try to attack he was just a model stay down my boy you'll
be hit thanks because this isn't my task for sporting gunfight don't you think oh
when do we break for tea this is so bad
really that's the guy that kills me
hey charlie get down here we go you know jack i can't really let la blow up i bought a retirement
disconnected brains right on the 14th fairway jacuzzi syndrome our incoming
gdc oh my god what the fuck was that there is nice okay don't die got him good shot
get him skiing thing again did it burn me as they say in your country let's get ready to
what oh no get him shit no what
what
huh i switched hands i can't even i just pretended to give show explain the plot i have no idea
i is it hold on i need to i need to fight this guy how do i fight the guy with the weapon in his
hand as they say in your country lock punch i wonder maybe block i'm gonna have to start blocking
it's the video's lagging no shit i broke wait i broke it no i didn't i don't think saving is
gonna do anything i think saving puts you back here i'll try it next time
okay he's gonna take a guess of what to do against that guy with the fucking spear
fuck he's trying to skip it oh by the way the walkthrough does not say what to do against the
big guy there's no info here i might soft lock myself here not being able to kill this guy
i love that so much all right give me give me some help here what's it what should i try
punch him punch block i tried dodging and blocking all right i'll save it right there
here we go dodge what
was it that long to do that did you really just do that i really just lost
thank god you guys were right
no god damn it no he i wonder if it's when he has the thing he spins it around like that i
wonder if it's a kick the punch when it's in the air no when he spins it i'll try kicking
i have no fuck
yeah okay
he keeps going for the
i don't think okay when i dodged it last time we got that cut scene
i hit him there hit him there dead this is definitely one of those scenarios where it's
gonna be like you have to block the first one dot like i punched the second time punch the third
kick the fourth time or something i have no idea what order it is
any other guides you guys got any other guides i typed in fox hunt guide and it's like fox hunting
tips i don't know i don't want to do that i want to fucking know how to play the game
the same guide uh does not have it no one's ever got this far just push buttons no you have to time
let me try this all right
okay i i'm spamming one did i get it i got i literally just pressed one as fast i could
what is this guy still alive why can he not get up wait why is it cutting
him he's on the ground and then he's here
i don't get it why does he keep turn around i can't the turnaround button doesn't do anything
what the fuck it's left i had to press left
okay there's two down last one
is this guy caveman oh shit he's gonna win god damn it he's a club please no
all right i know how to beat the first two okay second guy last guy
yeah
there's another one oh you gotta be fucking kidding me i have to go through the gauntlet are you
shitting me wait what kick him oh i've been keeping an eye on you old boy you mean you could have
killed all those guys yes duck okay mr super spy with all the answers where's lisa you only got
one of there's two more there's two more thanks holy shit this is uh it's there's so much over
stimulation here uh i don't i don't remember 38 39 i don't know going jack where the hell have
you been i've been keeping an eye on you old boy you mean you could have killed all those guys yes
duck okay mr super spy with all you know i really would have loved the one guy to have a death scene
be the caveman thanks hell aren't we in like vegas still this is the basement somewhere right
no where are we am i gonna play the video game in the video game is that what they're going with
uh
actually i'm uh next in line for street fighter i'm just waiting for uh
sean claude
this kind of freaks me out
electrical current
why is he waving why did he punch that guy there we go he's he's he's using the hands kicks punch
back in the punch did i chip a tooth he's like letting me win now for fast three months five
hey am i gonna zap this guy i still don't understand the plot
ranking number one
that's pretty good joker left not bad he's still alive oh no oh god i broke a name i could just die
launch in seven six four three two launch wait i don't think i was supposed to do that
maybe it's because ubc has never had a good friday night lineup jack i love that show it was
candle i'm just gonna leave after all the finally lost the backpack why
no he's behind me
i counted your machine gun shots save the game you shot hundreds and hundreds of times
i'm gonna go with 40 because i don't know rocket ship same work frankly i haven't got the slightest
idea why don't you just let him go you get in that mobile that guy alone tried to kill me over a
dozen times where the fuck are we right now i am i supposed to be picking i maybe it's the arrow
keys left right okay i just pressed right yeah it's the arrow keys why is the top kid coming off
blue the different colored hallways green and red and then what was that
this pops up so fast i can't even shooting at me
um
how do i stop this guy from shooting at me when the guy's in front of you shoot
shoot oh for the love of fucking god you have to hit enter you're not clicking on the screen
what was i shooting in front of me
i pressed all right but who is he where the fuck is he where is this person who is that and where
are you behind me when they're just looking behind so he's behind me so i have to like turn
i can't turn all right once he starts firing i can't do
anything and i can just look behind me what the fuck you have to get out of the rocket and just
wait what is he going is i got green or red what here you go he's firing at me i can't fucking even
see what i'm supposed to be doing here i'm looking i'm looking at the guide look down the tube to see
which way the guy is going what do you see a guy going down a tube right now
where i didn't see shit which tube there's nobody there and now he's behind me the object here to
shoot the bad guys ahead of you and avoid the gunfire from behind the trick is to maneuver the
guys from behind you to in front of you while spinning to avoid their gunfire spinning spin
spinning i this is going too fucking fast man why i can't even make a choice
spin huh who is who shoot him
i think i got him spin spin what the fuck no what the this is the most confusing shit and fucking
ever this is this is the wheelchair rockets with guns spins spin how the fuck is this guy
always behind me this is the final scene of the game i have to be as fucking stupid as this is
those last four or five these you couldn't pay me money to tell you what the fuck's happening
right now shoot oh i didn't even press the spin button once i didn't press s one fucking time
this guy is still here why is he still here spin
he's dodging how are you dodging hello what the name is jack jack freemont did he say yak
how the fuck did that even make any sense oh i love this game but i hate this game at the same
time i think this is the end is it one more decision good work jack wait thank you i didn't
stop the the nuke 1966 spring harvest wait didn't you get shot well in another two minutes you won't
she got shot like point blank in the chest now i am i get a little filly when i drink
okay maybe just one if this ends with the nuclear bomb going off
and great i'm gonna go to los angeles at least we didn't lose the money good show bye
it actually happened they actually did one of the end this multiple ending
how do you get the good ending yeah that's it that was fucking ridiculous
okay that was fox hunt we beat the whole game it was an absolute journey and it was a mess
it was all over the place but you know i i enjoyed my time didn't beat the whole game well i got to
the end i got to one of the ending you have to complete the hospital wheelchair scene on your
first try dude that seriously almost killed me this game is outrageous fox hunt by capcom
weirdly enough i'm still trying to get over the fact that rob low was in the game
for less than five minutes he just in the game and a couple clones this but that must have been
a favor you know he must have known that the dp or something it must have been a personal friend
hey you want to be in this movie this movie game thing for like five minutes just cameo it for fun
yeah sure why not killer soundtrack there you go capcom capcom capcom you're gonna do new game plus
no i'm gonna use the bathroom come back i'm gonna play another one
and unfortunately this is really it's in out of the fryer and into the frying pan
because the next one is there's no i don't there's no relaxing fmv game that i have
from this point going forward we are going to do uh crime patrol two drug wars so there really is
no there's no slowing down here so let me uh bear back i'm just gonna get a water use the bathroom
and we'll keep going do i have the game that has rob schneider in it you're talking about a fork
in the tail i really really wanted it but i had to make a decision because a fork in the tail
seems ridiculous like this but it requires windows 95 so what i had to do it i would have had to
make a new virtual machine for windows 95 to only play that game so i decided to spend time
in the windows 3.1 emulator do it i mean i probably will it's easy well it's not that it's not it's
not that it's hard to do it just there was a shitload of games on the 3.1 and i said all right well
i might as well just focus on this because remember i had to there's a lot of fucking
bullshit that you have to do to get some of these to work and some of them they they don't work even
with uh virtual emulation so virtual machine stuff i tried to get there are a couple other
ones for 3.1 that i tried to get to work and they just aren't going to no matter what i do
like oh you don't have quicktime 1.0 installed i refuse to run but i have quicktime 2.0 installed
that doesn't matter sorry um so i need to go find a win a 3.1 quicktime 1.0 installation file
and then install it and then hope it works but i have to install it on the virtual machine
like i have to go to like a super super duper it's like it's weird and i've done that before
and then the whole vm breaks quicktime 2.0 doesn't exist yes it does this is quicktime
2.1 did somebody did somebody say quicktime 2.0 doesn't exist people what hold on i thought it
didn't exist i thought it didn't exist though i thought it didn't exist please hide this i feel
old i disagree what happens if you disagree does it turn off windows no that's 2.1.2 wait that's
2.1.2 yeah for a second i thought the camera was on and i'm so glad it wasn't that would have been
embarrassing all right i'll see you guys in a minute we'll do uh drug wars see in a second
oh shit his pc turned off i'll be right back relax okay we are no longer playing a fox hunt
so i'm going to change that this is crime patrol 2 let me make sure it's being captured correctly
it is hello same thing i got three difficulties although i'm probably gonna have to i'm probably
gonna have to resize this let me try something here hold on does it stay the same or is it all
fucked up i can't see yeah i gotta change it that looks okay right there maybe a little bit more
yeah that looks all right a little bit more looking good there we go okay turn the volume
on and let's go we should be good right how loud is it probably very loud no it's fucked up
turn it down a little because i can't see it because it changes my resolution
i fucked it all up there we go all right better here we go new game welcome to shearer county
now drugs are something we just don't abide down i say you got six years
pretty sure you pick an assignment you may go kick a little butt this is a really crunchy game
take some target and train american laser games why would you come up twice all right here we go
they're dealing dope in this bar dealing dope behind the barrel what else i thought i didn't
know that fucking hurts in that hurts in real life oh my god they're dealing dope in this bar
do we buy these guys i like this song unironically i like that song
let's do the shit in the arcade same guy he he walked around the building oh no who's next
what is this guy on his phone he's trying to get good reception he's like yeah can you hear me
oh god damn it okay look at this guy at the bar he's trying to like talk to somebody on the phone
oh nice job uh this looks like game boy color i'm just that's just how it is it's here county fast
wheels mean drug deals i know i'll chase them you waste them oh here's we have a driving shooting
sequence great he's always the worst because you can't tell what blob is the thing you're supposed
to be shooting at like i just guessed i think i did it somebody out somewhere in there is a uh
is a really cool scene there's stash and drugs in this place what do you say we get
what you shot an innocent what who's dead they're dead there's stash and drugs in this place so
what's the deal i don't know what exploded in there oh he just don't know drugs in this place
the special effects are crazy american laser was really really really cool
they spent they put a lot of time and a lot of money into their things they did in the games
oh come on there's stash and drugs in this place what do you say we give them a little
shots watch out on the left side guy comes out here right in front dead shit i thought the guy
was dead ah i thought he wasn't dead there's stash and drugs in this place
left right and there's a guy up top no now what did it holy shit this video i shot between them
so that's good dude that was not even a person back there that was like a like a broom closet
it wasn't even a person did she say we're not worthy did we win you got guts guts are good
you're heading north chicago show the big boys what you got don't look at the camera
look at this outfit is this all the pizza
i want one of those so bad right now i so desperately want one of those right now
i'll drop it in on the cartel get back here this is that guy everybody just why do they all
it's so it's i can't help it that was an innocent you shot big mistake
how is this one crunchier than the last one this looks like it was painted frame by frame all right
watch out for the guy with the hard hat watch it what i thought that was my partner
neither's your shooting later dude this is crustier than fox hunt wait which one is it this one
okay it is this one really this could be the end of the game or not what's going on
did i lose too many times i think i'm wait but i was able to continue a bunch of times before
welcome to sheer county huh time to get good apparently yeah right right when i
take some target shit well i'm gonna save the game when i beat oh god damn it it's even on wimpy too
all right good let's go save game that's all it takes the guy just tells me he just speaks it okay
fine let's get a scan back and forth like this good we're in the phone by the way i this is that
guy's like a fucking time traveler they want to sell phones back in the late 80s what the hell was
that 1993 there was no cell phones in 1993 and here it goes see i haven't even lost a life yet
this one's hard i can remember it's like bang bang bang bang
yeah i'm in the damn window in this place i'm in the damn window
wait i went fucking dammit what am i doing
fashion drugs in this place we say we give them a little shots for me
you know bingo right here then up all right we're in don't shoot guy behind him in the corner
done show time all right back to chicago
all right let's do let's go with this one in the middle please where where who
what great partner i don't i don't know who the fuck i was supposed to be even looking at
how about no no no i'm all right continue all right save game
save so this guy at the right and the guy on the left the cartel is holding hostages in the
courthouse hopefully they're all right here now who where the fuck am i supposed to see
he's gonna memorize where they are the middle left and then right again
this guy gets up again god damn it that was an innocent you shot big mistake
all right not this guy then this fucking lady in the front row
okay okay this lady turns around get it cartel wait i'm so confused right now
check the obituaries pal you're in them what just happened the cartel is holding hostages in the
court i don't understand they was was that a quick your day job just got the call
twice and then the guy spends no and then this guy on the left
down the left and then okay then now this weird thing happens where it's like there's a person
here with the security and hope that guy went flying guilty i have to do loaded
loaded what's going on why am i stuck here did i save and i was dead i don't know what
loaded so can i go back from two different menu let me try if i do what if i quit you saved on
the continue screen well wouldn't that good point shouldn't that be able to right how do you not
save on the menu isn't that i feel like that's where you have to save the game let's see if it
works well maybe it's just gonna get stuck here forever quiet please i'm thinking uh-oh is it
because i'm talking so should i stop talking didn't work i'll reload it hold on that's annoying
yeah that's that's annoying okay so let me load it again uh actually i don't even need to
no i have to turn that off because it'll fuck up if i try to capture it all right where is it
wait wait wait hold on don't you guys you guys like to see this shit don't you here okay you
can see it see look at how smart i am actually i don't know what folder it is i have no idea
folders in uh crime patrol okay uh crime patrol e f and v slash uh patrol two slash
crime patrol two dot iso dash t iso mount that please change directory let's go ahead and go to
oh let's go here we are it's loaded loaded god damn it
pretty quick though i'm doing that with my hand he saved on the continue screen well let's go here
we go this is the run right here this is the one let's do it here we go three two one action
how did you not get you i'm shooting too fast
ah fuck here we just go shooting like that let's go much louder this time around i don't know why
i like that the siren stops when you shoot in this place i like when they stop talking to
that was i completely fucking missed sorry don't
oh
all right i need to just get to chicago and then i can go and then save the game in the chicago
menu i almost shot god first two shots are nice
term is so done not yet i just keep screwing up the whole transitioning scene thing the director
says all right now save right because that's here correct i'm gonna load this game load
loaded here we are all right here we go let's do it same one we did before
i forget which way i forget the whole order here god i forget the order this way
fuck i thought the guy comes from this is what why god oh i keep i keep everything so blurred
in my brain because everyone's so blurry in the game guilty guilty these people's faces
are all mosaiced i'm with the band what do you mean the band at the court that guy these guys
have blended in so well okay i did it let's go am i losing my mind or is the game getting
is the game looking worse am i crazy or have i just been staring at pixels that are so large
for the last like four to five hours that like it's it's messing with my head my god
i'm giving this like a few more attempts before i fucking delete all right let's go
oh
just cutting the music that you get the first note of the song i didn't see that guy oh my god
that was an innocent you shot big mistake i can't believe you did that you shot them
all the orange blobs on the screen and then one that came up that was a blue blob what were you
thinking didn't already do this guilty i'm gonna grab this guy on the left is the one that's the
hard one to shoot okay right here got it okay now i'm gonna save we're good they're the same
color as the bus they're the same color the bus what the hell i just can't i only got one chance
to do it always do i get one life for the rest of the game what did i lose hold on you're good
very good the director says to buy the fat man hot chicago your kind of town pirate marriage
welcome to the border me sam all right here we go saved thank you
you know i don't even get no intro this guy runs out with gun there's no way to tell me
this is no way there's no way to tell they're so out they're so out of focus
that there's no way you can tell them look at these guys on the left and right
this is the canadian border i don't even canadian border hey that guy already had blood on
that bait right here oh come on that bait bullshit oh that sucks what the fuck
oh my god it's getting faster oh whoof all right that was wild
does it grab your pizza what where who what happened one life one life only that's it i can't
make any mistakes they came up from the same exact place why did she scream into her hands
extra crispy she may have just been blowing her nose oh i don't look at this am i in the car
are you serious what the fuck i didn't even know we were going again i'm dead again
oh my god so what has to happen is i have to die and then i have to save with the one life
i thought this was the second scene and that was it okay kind of water that lady sounds like a seagull
oh my fucking god guys that shit's not fucking possible loaded the fuck
then loaded i don't have to see somebody all the way down there do i uh i think that was
fishing of course it was here we go it's too crusty fucking god there's no way for you to do
this i'm so close i have to are you emulating this on nintendo don't make me laugh what happened
there i clearly got him rewind that did you see that can i press the menu button during a round
i might be able to but that's terrifying because if i try that if i try to save it in the middle of
one of these it might not work and it might be really bad i'll try i'll try it let's try it
i'll give it i'll give it a go let's see i'm like this is i can't let this game like tilt me can i
is that what's happening right now that's not like that can't happen
okay here we go let's see if that person's right if you're wrong then i'm gonna exit the game
okay like i just want to just let's see what happens ready
what what that person just saved the whole screen this is risky
yeah no i shouldn't wait what i just had an opportunity to save the game
i'm hold on i just freaked out oh you motherfucker
what are they saying i have no idea not twice
that was quick i was right there you can't do that much faster
oh
watch your aim i keep shooting this person because it's impossible to tell
and sometimes it they throw it's random see
god this fucking guy keeps coming out of that window and it's fucking driving me crazy
stop shooting the potty guy what do you mean potty guy i just got everybody relax i just gotta
continue for that it doesn't fucking matter it's the same same outcome you see how that guy
i'm using the potty i'm using the potty all right dude uh that's what we call
grade a dog shit that is packed up in the fucking grocery store with a stamp on it the butcher
approved of this grade a prime dog shit loaded i tried to shoot what about the guy that was on
the party you just killed him very what's left what was left oh the party one with the rocks and
shit i gotta get a good save point here it doesn't make any fucking sense loaded
doesn't make any fucking sense i tell you it don't make no fucking sense there's no fucking
reason why hey jesus there's no fucking reason why i just am i do i do trailer park boys
where did that come from i gotta save it right here fucking boppels man
i've never even seen that whole show i've seen like a few episodes innocence no the director
says you kiss the lady goodbye i did it you kiss the lady goodbye you're going south south america
there's another layer here save it my name is nick here in south america if the heat don't get
you the cartel will wait the people that in the chat said that was the canadian border
okay this is going to be a living hell of a mission they don't just smuggle don't they lose
your luggage let's you disappoint the cartel wins this round i saw petrol and it was dotted why not
loaded they don't get smuggled don't they lose your luggage let's ground them i knew he was bad
good luck seeing that guy that was a miracle that was a full rotation excellent work i did it again
somebody right here oh come on i thought that was the end why oh that was like the ending cinematic
really that's such bullshit loaded they don't get smuggled what was behind there was no
jesus don't do that holy shit that guy sprung up that was insane that guy was spring loaded
loaded i like this guy save it i got two i got two hp now top 10 twitch meltdowns what do you mean
meltdown i'm doing just fine i'm i don't want to do this party we're going to plan b night scope
no you come 3000 miles to shoot innocent that person was pointing a gun at me
i don't understand they were when they were holding a gun at me loaded this party what that
was that him hold on that was a bird but you're not out uh that was a bird that wasn't even
loaded we're dressed for this party oh come on i'm right here i'm gonna be
pissed off and i'm gonna accidentally press it what's where which is camouflaging in the
wall or something what loaded for this party we're dressed for this party
and what's going on here loaded i hope we're dressed for this party
so
these people are just hiding in different places and popping out like why are they there
and why can't i just shoot him why would i waste any time here i forgot about the fucking girl
what was the like swat anti-cartel guy doing in that closet why are you in there
you were in there the whole time there was another person in there
you a bad guy and a good guy are hanging out in here come on oh come on oh my god
i forgot about the girl again i'm fucking gonna lose my mind we're good
that's it okay that's it fine oh my god oh boy village no what
jeremy what are you doing why would you run in front like that you didn't even say that you just
ran dove and you think you would say something oh my god loaded loaded loaded i don't know
am i can i not do this loaded i think this is soft locked i'm gonna try it loaded let me try this
don't shoot god i've got money don't shoot them they do the same thing three times and then that
motherfucker actually shoots me i'm gonna save it after this already one two
oh no a geyser erupted is that a camera loaded this person has a camera you come three i don't
know i figured the person next to them would be the one shooting this is so crunchy uh-oh
why does this guy keep having loaded
oh holy shit that's not a good place to save save here
shoot save shoot save shoot save shoot save i can't i'll fuck it up and end up locking myself
oh don't see that play i thought that was somebody laughing
and
on second time here and it doesn't sound like a person laughing doesn't sound like a person
laughing fucking reiki you've got to get yourself fucking out of here all you do is you drink and
you come down you fucking have my kids my kiddies are very important to me was that a person in
here oh this is so bad with all the grass and the it's the bit rate is even i hope there's
no innocent people just hanging around the fucking trees
what was i supposed to do
what the fuck are you doing here
do it you've made it this far you know what to do do it
you fucking know what to do do it that person was part of the that person was part of that
truck that wasn't even a person where the fuck is this guy i have no idea what this dude is
i don't help me out here loaded well i got him where is he holy shit
wait he took his jacket off all right he's all the way to the left no did i screw it up
it's time to blend together things are starting to blend in my brain and it's getting to a point
i can't tell who is who i don't know who is who
forgot all right no
what did i imagine doing this shit with a wiimote not possible good game player
did i win good game player let it go let it go
so the next one we're gonna do is uh cycle mania it's a motorcycle game we'll find out
i do have to reboot this though put the brb up i keep thinking my webcam's on it's freaking
me out because i don't i really don't have any clothes on all right let me see make sure
this is installed in the right place should be okay fmv cycle slash well cycle apparently
all right so that's good should be is there in what the hell did i do i think i broke it
oh shit i'm so bad i'm so stupid what a dummy dumb idiot
cycle slash cycle all right that's good to go i am now ready i'm not ready what the
fuck how do i open this uh does anybody know how to open the game actually wait no i think i got it
let's see yeah there we go okay or maybe not what is this doing why is it doing this
sound blaster 16 no what the hell are you doing sound blaster 16 port number what the
fuck is all this shit oh get the fuck out of here i just did it i just had to write the word cycle
all right cycle mania all right if i want quick race one race championship load game demo options
boy this is gonna be a mess uh quick race all right how do i drive the how do i do this
whoa wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait it's not first person in my i'm following behind me
all right that was very confusing where's the cop so this it's it's a real road this is horrible
god why does that guy not fall but i do this guy can take a lot of pain though that's apparently
what the fuck happened here okay let's go for the championship select bike jeff the breeze
robert electric bob uh crazy bill bill crazy really okay oh we can't play this crazy
phylactery lich 69 community subs again back to back days 10 streams in a row unbelievable
i still can't fucking believe that you do this shit all the time can't fucking believe it
you're single-handedly pushing this channel to new highs in subscriptions thank you the category is
drug wars oh shit well it's all right what are we doing now we're making a bike oh you know i know
that you you might not want to work right now but i know i'm not stupid i know that's a cardboard
cutout of some nascar driver or something you can't just put that there and i think that there's
somebody at the store four into one high performance exhaust gas charge progressive
suspension five position rebound damping adjustment upgraded racing engine higher rev compatibility
polished and ported cycle heads i how much money do i have i have a hundred bucks i don't have
enough money to do this race aggressive friendly aggressive opponent level amateurs control level
just got here i'm good i just got here grid position what does this mean long all right
what about i can't select the track qualifying let's go but i don't know why the other why the
car is on this road 162 miles per hour jesus helicopter can you get arrested why the planes
flying that low you can't get hit by a fucking plane right are there any other buttons
i'm almost an 11th gear maybe i shouldn't have done long did i qualify i was in lap two
right okay i've not stopped going 162 those are rpms not gears yeah see it goes
i'm in six right zero so what does it mean let me ask you something because you guys that like
cars what does it mean when your car so let's say you have you have an automatic right you're not
driving a manual and let's say that you're you know between one and like two rpm right on the
bar there uh let's say that you like you're going like 20 30 miles per hour and you start to go
down to like one to two rpm right why is it and they're telling me what was you got somebody
that knows about cars let me know what you think about this so why is it that sometimes when you
slow down if anybody's in here that knows anything about cars if you slow down between one and two
rpm why is it that the um the car sometimes will all right hold on it was the like binaural beats
in my ears were fucking up my whole brain i couldn't even talk to you guys um anyway so
when i go in between two and one rpm sometimes i can feel the car like pulling up and down
uh gears why is that doing that i can feel it it's like
it's like ah it's annoying it's downshifting but every the car i've ever driven
didn't have that problem i didn't i didn't feel the car downshifting i do now why
where am i it's probably fine it means it has wasps in the car your gears are sloppy
huh slipping transmission what do i do about that is that a heart is it an easy fix is that
just like a hey man i'm i think my transmission is slipping fix it it's not what do you mean
how what do you mean it's expensive how expensive it's a couple hundred to a few thousand
that's a huge ballpark but am i getting some i'm getting some uh some slip it's slipping
that's not good i can feel it it only happens between like 20 mile between like 15 and 20 miles
per hour doesn't happen any other time is there a punch no of course why am i the only one that
falls first to second gear is fucked they can't go anywhere that apparently didn't get a hit all
right i'm in third place this is not bad i have an opportunity here to pass and get in first place
and win how did they not get hit by that stuff what kind of car do i drive but that would probably
help uh i drive a honda civic so maybe that would help oh no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
i just told people my car was my first place yeah it's a it's a 2023 honda civic i got the
new one early don't you guys know that they make these things fucking five years in advance to make
sure they have a shitload of them so they can just keep oh it's it's 2000 it's 2019 here's the 2021
they make there's like fucking a thousand of these cars already made guys new cars are like new
madden they just do a little bit of an update they change the paint and they make it look
shaped differently and then they smash the thing into walls a bunch of times and say hey we got
this safe yes it fucking better be don't you know i mean in every car commercial we've got
five star safety rating okay if you didn't i wouldn't have the car what do you mean the car
is working fucking safe good i it should be absolutely what do you mean why is it a selling
point two star safety and nobody ever talks about how their car is a two star safety car
they don't exist every car company likes to tell that well let me tell you a ranked five star safety
from yabba dabba doo associates okay well no one has a three or two star rated car
what does a two star rated car mean is it like yelp if you go to a two star restaurant you're
gonna get like sick so if you drive a two star car does that mean that it's gonna like break
i mean i can understand four stars five stars but but two i don't think there's any car
manufacturer that has a two star safety rating if they do the car is probably like
600 bucks how am i gonna win i'm in first place yeah get the fuck out of the way toad
always causing problems back here just lapped you going like two miles per hour oh it's 30 laps
oh shit why would anybody have a 30 lap race you're gonna run in a gas before the race is over
i made it 30 laps no i made it 30 long i didn't know what that meant all right what about a one
star rated car does that exist wait hold on let me answer that is a one star safety rated car
like a go kart right do they rate those does like jd power rate go karts this game this game is
sucks i think i actually am gonna run out of gas what's the left meter is that meter on the left
gas this is a shitty road rash yeah this is a road rash without the rash just the road it is
a real road though they definitely drove around somewhere because that's a real place that's real
grass real road now just 24 more of these finally i saw somebody else crash oh wait i died oh that
stupid that was terrible i want to no i want to turn it off 30 oh my god no i want to turn this
shit up yeah let's get let's get the fuck out of here well that was cycle mania pretty good
pretty fun ragequit no i saw i pretty much saw everything there is to see in the whole game
all right here's the plan oh my gosh here there are a few more but don't act like you have a plan
i do have a plan the plan is i'm going to i'm gonna leave it up to you guys okay we've been
doing a lot of fmv like the last three or four streams in a row have been fmv games so i'm
streaming tomorrow tomorrow is the last stream that will be a video game stream before the carnival
so i'm gonna ask you this very simple question with a poll do you want me to do more full motion
video stuff tomorrow or do something else i'm gonna make the poll right now that's something
else is just not fmv could be anything but there are one two three four there are about four
give or take fmv games left that are gonna take a long time to play kind of like the first one we
did i'm okay with holding on to these for another time but let's put this in here this is a simple
yes or no question there you go interesting okay can you tell us what the fmvs are um sure they are
uh flash traffic it's another one of those oh no there's a there's a plot that you need to stop
kind of like the first game but just not the same there's critical path the hell cab and
dracula you never did the second dragon's lair yo yeah i beat it i beat all the uh anime that
i i that hurt my whole head but yeah i did so it looks like uh most people would like to see
something else we can change it up it's been a lot of fmv we've done like 10 12 of these
it's it's a it's an overstimulating thing all right we'll do something else tomorrow
i will find something else to play tomorrow and then of course no whoops sorry and then of
course on the 16th is going to be the activity book stream that stream is not going to be very
long that stream is only going to be probably a couple hours long however long it takes to do
the book because then i have to get ready and that whole week is going to be setting up with
all the location people and the where we're going and get in touch with who's making the robots and
getting them and it's going to be a whole ordeal so i want to make sure that that's completely
taken care of and it's going to take me about a week robots question mark i am going to pin a
tweet tonight it's just going to be there for the next week and a half saying the date and the time
september 21st at 12 p.m eastern and i'm going to make a command here as well what is left for
tonight well i kind of i don't know if i want to start these right now because they might take
longer than a few hours and it's been about six hours now we've had these fmv streams have been
besides the one that got cut off they've been like a clean six hours so that's good and then
obviously the bits and everything so ends up being like six and a half seven so i like that
we'll hold on to them how many robots do you have for the carnival um those are spoilers am i going
to keep it under wraps i mean not there well let's just put this way that there's more than one
there are more than two you have there's more than two okay there you go all right told you
how many i did no whoops but you know what yeah i think we'll call it here this is a good place
to stop the other ones i'm certain i know for a fact that these other ones are going to take more
than a few hours so tomorrow we're gonna do something else and i i also want to be completely
honest here that fox hunt burnt like literally all of the fuel in my tank that was some of the
funniest fucked up shit i think i've ever seen it again so the first three and a half to four
hours of this stream was like all gas has been removed from the tank but it was awesome so yeah
i'll um i'll see you guys tomorrow we'll play a game we'll hang out probably we'll be probably
going to be a chill stream the next couple streams we're going to dial back the insanity
we'll just hang out and do something but uh with that see you tomorrow we'll do the bits
uh scrolling back here play monster rancher 2 monster rancher 2 memories but thank you door cube
for the 250 vhs streams are always fun you know what it's funny you say that because some of the
there are a lot of fmv games that are on vhs tapes somehow there are d i was gonna do a whole
thing playing dvd games from special features discs that is gonna take a whole ordeal getting
that set up you know when you buy like uh the lion king new animated blu-ray and there's just
a dumb fucking game on that disc i was gonna get a shitload of them that have it we were just gonna
play dvd games so like you can potentially look look forward to that in a later date
but not right now and not for a while there's a garfield dvd game well i'll have to get it
but thanks door keep for the 250 well germa with the activity book in carnival stream coming up
i think you know what the next big project is an fmv game of your own if you would make an fmv game
how to play would it be a point and click like fox hunt or more like security camera like night
trap it's funny you say that because that's something that i've like always wanted to do
i've brought up making an fmv game but i'm talking years ago more than a couple of years ago
the problem with game development and especially high budgeted development stuff
is that would need to be done the right way completely that would be a lot of money a lot
of potential people involved i would really need to get the right people involved in that
because it costs lots of money just to hire people and be on a location somewhere
even location scouting guys something that is a lot of people don't understand about
making a video or making streams or anything like that is
finding a place that will let you do things like a studio space or like where i was doing the
green screen stuff or the warehouse space or something and finding those places they're very
very very fucking expensive thousands and thousands and thousands of dollars so just
filming it just like principal photography for whatever it would be as i mean you're talking
about having to hire actors and people to make costumes and where are you going to film this
stuff do you have the permits to film this stuff before even pressing record on the camera you
might be looking at 50 60 70 hundred thousand dollars worth of stuff now some people we were
talking to like an fmv game right if you grab a camera with a couple of your buddies and you make
a movie then you get permission to film on location somewhere that's different hire random people from
craigslist you still have to hire those people but what would the gameplay be i always i wanted to
make a western i think that old school western like mad dog mccree is just the pinnacle of
full motion video games and i would want to make it authentic too i wouldn't i don't want hd cameras
at all if i was ever going to do something like that i want like 16 millimeter film
this shit doesn't have to be 1080p in fact i don't want it to be and have branching paths and stuff
i i've given this way too much thought for something that's not ever going to happen
at least in the near or far future but everybody does this everybody everybody sits down
and just thinks of you know what would be a great video game i think you just spitball
we can pull off miracles there was a lot of money given and i missed a big 50 dollar donation i'm
certain of that but cats beanie thanks for the 50 bucks 50 dollars from cats beanie and i this is
exactly what i was talking about not sure if you saw my big bits at the start of the stream it's
cool if not i was wondering what inspired you to do the robot carnival uh i don't know i just
thought it would be fun the original idea was i was going to get a dunk tank and have chat control
the pitching machine and then it was okay how you do that i just thought that would be fun i just
thought that that's it that was the only motivation or inspiration behind it because i was imagining
everybody in the chat like fighting over the controls and me just talking shit sitting up
there and everyone like missing and you try and then trying to we're gonna dunk them you know we
gotta dunk this motherfucker and i'm just sitting there like with a cigar like you ain't gonna
fucking dunk me and then it evolved into a bunch of games and a bunch of stuff so i don't i don't
inspiration and motivation stuff for me really just stems from i i don't know it just i just if
i think something's funny or interesting and i think it's worth pursuing and i'll do it
is really it we're gonna dunk you good luck go for it i wish you all the luck in the world
because you're gonna be fighting with the person sitting next to you because they're gonna want to
go left they're gonna want to increase the speed they're somebody over there is gonna want to
reduce the speed good luck oh that person just like decided to turn it that way i have faith
you still gotta smoke a cigar we're gonna get you in 10 seconds i would be shocked
if you dunked me in 10 seconds there is almost no way that's possible unless that every single
person works together no fucking way let's practice okay let's practice you're spoiling
commands i don't even i don't know if these are the commands now we have to go over that
increase speed 5000 yeah twitch could beat pokemon i'll get dunked oh maybe i won't
well i'm not gonna make it easy for you just thinking face on that one guys you know get
your brain cap on thinking face i'm not gonna make it fucking easy for you thinking face
about phylactery lich gave 100 bucks they say fund it more money from phylactery more
hundreds and hundreds of dollars hundreds of them thank you phylactery thank you cats beanie
for the donation earlier too hope that answers your question thank you they also say will there
be a birthday stream after the carnival that's cats beanie as well so thank you for the 100 bucks
cats beanie birthday no i am gonna be i'm not gonna be around i'm gonna be out of commission
probably until the 24th of september 23rd or 24th and then i'm back and then by then you know it's
time i'm streaming i gotta stream i don't like i said i think i said this yesterday i don't want
a scenario where i stream one time in two weeks if i can help it i'd like to keep broadcasting
because then twitchcon is that next weekend a lot of shit going on but maybe i don't know
we'll see but thank you thank you demons v for the 250 do you find streaming to be fulfilling
besides the obvious financial benefit do you feel like you have a creative outlet in your work
stimulating yeah i mean that's the whole point of doing something like the carnival
is to make sure that i continue to stimulate myself i get bored really really easily and
when i get bored i start to not care about something so that hasn't happened yet on stream for
streaming i don't want to have it get there because once it becomes boring it gonna parrot
what i said yesterday once it becomes not interesting and boring to me is when i would
just hang my hat up and be like that was fun i don't see that happening anytime soon but when
it does and if it does then you know you have to start to you know you close the book and you open
up a new one so this is a good final stream this one right here i don't know i cannot predict the
future i don't have a crystal ball but streaming at the moment is completely fulfilling and it
continues to be and we'll see how it goes from here i think it'll be good that's just me being
real that's it uh thank you to uh liberal liter for the ten dollars ten bucks from uh liberal
liter it's a good stream thanks for watching and thanks for the ten dollars thanks for the
thousand bits thank you to d soyd kaj podfa for the ten bucks thousand bits as well back to back
here germa i just came into your stream please make it stop i think that was when i was in the
rocket chair thank you matt thank you mattis for the three dollars hey germa twitchcon is sold out
on saturday you're gonna be there on sunday i'd really like to meet you i will not be at twitchcon
on sunday unfortunately i'm only gonna be there for two days saturday is the day that i'll be
mostly on you know walking around and doing stuff so i will not be at twitchcon on sunday also the
first time where is it where is it is in san diego twitchcon where is it yeah that's i've never been
to san diego so that'll be a first time visiting san diego jexpo yeah but if i if i miss you i'm
sorry matt i do plan on being there next time probably have the same friday saturday whatever
it is but thank you for the three bucks appreciate it thank you zomie games or zomie games for the
six dollars and 55 cents they just say pogchamp thank you hopefully it did something cool
thank you froidian weapon for the 250 thanks froidian hi germa i haven't been able to tune
in for a while i've only seen a small chunk of this game but the main guy kind of acts
how i imagine you would if you were a secret agent it's great have a good night that game was
just ridiculous that's the kind of i would want to make something that was just not supposed to be
taken seriously but was interesting enough that the game had interesting things to do
i don't want to make just like a straight up strict meme game where it where it just has
only like crazy funny things whoa crazy what oh he he shit his pants and you pooped his pants
no i don't want to do that it would be i would try to have some comedy aspects to it but i think
i would want to have it be an actual game but thank you for the 250 yeah i did like it i thought it
was really interesting hey wolfstar thanks for the four dollars this is the longest time i've
ever spent watching a stream um the longest time i ever was on a stream was simpsons hit and run
13 hours right but thanks for watching for that long it yeah that's thanks i hope you enjoyed it
thank you egg johnson for the 250 hey germa when are you going to give the people what they want
and do a chess stream i know how to play chess but i don't know how to play chess
i would never do that phylactery with the 69 subs let's show the subs thank you everybody
for gifting subs for subbing for resubbing for if you're brand new and you just subbed
if you've been here for years and you decided to sub if you don't sub at all that's fine too
thanks for being here you guys think i can handle chess after the checkers incidents
thank you bro luck for the five dollars i think this stream has proven you don't know much about
cars it's not one rpm it's a thousand rpm i know i'm just saying on the dash
rpm is revolutions per minute revolutions of the crankshaft every minute also most cars before
like 2005 have basic basically zero star rating because of all the new safety features in newer
cars like crumble zones better airbags crash avoidance systems and overall better engineering
get your transmission looked at but are there any one-star cars now is a lawnmower a like zero
safety rated car right is a one star safety rated vehicle of rideable lawnmower it's not a car
it's an automobile it's a traveling vehicle with an engine it's not road legal
it's not road legal imagine seeing some fucking dickhead on like the road with a
rideable mower this is out of red light you look at the window you're like hey man what the fuck
is wrong with you now don't worry about it the blades aren't down i'm not the blades aren't
active those things can fucking move but the blade's not done i've worked in the country
people did that that's so fucking dangerous all right hold on what about a forklift is a forklift
a five star safety rated vehicle it's its only existence is for safety it has to be a forklift
is a safety vehicle therefore it has to be a five star rated safety vehicle otherwise would you get
in one forklifts don't have doors or airbag but uh what if they did what do you mean a forklift
doesn't have an airbag imagine being in a forklift and just like bumping into the wall and a big air
bag hits you in the face the airbag would fucking like knock you out you're going like eight miles
per hour like you just face first in the airbag here's a zero star rated car from 2014 wait
what is this actually real crash test of the the ford fego what is a ford fego
ford what ford fego safety rating the ford fego facelift has received a three star safety rating
in the new one what about the 2014 one i ain't gonna eat at that restaurant are you guys like me
if it's not mcdonald's burger king or wendy's if it's less than three stars you don't go
right i feel like most people right let me know if it's not mcdonald's burger king wendy's
arby's any of the ease arby's wendy's burger king ease mcdonald's ease if it's less than three stars
i ain't gonna go nobody reviews mcdonald's if you leave a two star rating at a restaurant that's
not one of those fast food places there was a reason why i can't remember the last time that
somebody forgot half my fucking order at mcdonald's and i was like let me just go on your fucking
heel pretty give them one star i know you go oh mcdonald's like sucks whatever and you like
either go back and get it fixed or no you don't well you don't leave a review oh shit my burger
king uh my whopper it tastes like somebody and it looks like somebody sat on it it's missing all
the things i asked for it and then the bun is it looks like it has mold on it get on me open
no you just let go of that i'm throwing this in the trash this thing's gross and you move on
and also some people that here's another thing this is where this is where it gets like kind of
weird some people will review restaurants and and they give it a bad rating when maybe they
even shouldn't have you know sometimes it's just somebody's like i and you know the way i'll tell
you i was gonna i was gonna give this place four stars because the food was great end quote but
let me tell you something about the server katherine okay she came over to my table
and she didn't ask me if i wanted a water refill places a one star restaurant there was this the
sugar wasn't repacked on the table i mean my my burrito was absolutely delicious it was probably
one of the best burritos in the city but what if i wanted fucking coffee and i wanted to put sugar
in my coffee it wasn't on the table jeez what the fuck why is this person putting sugar in their
burrito you know i sat down at this table and i am not kidding i saw a smudge a big smudge on the
table somebody's thumbprint and it made me gag and me and my nine children left sometimes people
do big orders and i i gotta you gotta give some credit to the restaurants right sometimes
if you go in with like 10 people and you let's say you all order the exact same thing let's say you
all there's 10 of you you go into the restaurant you all order the chicken thighs you're all going
to get a slightly different food slightly just only slightly because like no two chickens are
the same one of them might have a little bit of fat on it one of them but they're still good you
know it might still be good you can't everyone can't have the exact same food no matter what
the chicken is a different it's a different chicken possibly what if that chicken was lazy
and didn't run around what if that chicken was a little tougher than the other one it's just basic
science guys it's just basic food science and then i take a bite out of my food and the same exact
order on the menu it's got the same sauce same everything it's a little tougher oh this is kind
of tough today and the person next to me is like this is fucking absolutely scrumptious let me try
yours yeah that is like good i think i give it a one star rating because like the chicken didn't
fucking run around in the coop it's just basic science people that leave yelp reviews on
mcdonald's you know i was thinking about i don't know just a random thought just go to like
mcdonald's just go and like go and uh that was a good that was it was just a regular decent
mcdonald's experience and write like an absolutely wonderful review like five stars like as if this
place is like 200 dollars a plate talk about the inside i walked in and oh i was wowed by the
architecture the beautiful the crimson red and the mustard yellow it was just the color combination
just matched so perfectly well and the chairs were very sturdy and do like a full five paragraph
about how amazing the place was the stunning design choice of the ketchup on the table yeah
just go fucking nuts how do we end up in this topic i don't know i have no i have no idea oh
talk about cars right like two stars for car yeah okay that's all don't say it was a mcdonald's
until the end of the review well it would have to be like on a mcdonald's page ah you know what
this is gonna be it might be i don't know it's possible that this might be an unpopular opinion
i don't think that there should be stars on yelp i think it should just be have to ride fucking
review that's just me i just like sip this there's nothing in it i did like the kermit the frog thing
like well you know sip the fucking tea sip the fucking tea well i'm why am i doing the bubble
so often i don't even watch that show thank you bro luck for the five dollars appreciate it
hey christin thanks for 30 bucks what about team fortress 2 what about team fortress 2
it's a great first person shooter with an awesome array of classes and lots of gameplay choices
one of the best first person shooters i may have ever played it's a great game
what about it it's good you should play it i i honestly you know i i may have drained i may
have like drained all the vampire type blood out of that game that i can you know i i've like sunk
my teeth into tf2 and i drained all the blood it's all gone for me step on it come on that
wasn't even very good df2 yelp no i have no intention of playing it again really it would
take something very very very significant for me to ever play that game again i still think it's
one of the best games ever made but you know i also think pizza is the best like food in the
world i like love pizza i love pepperoni pizza more than anything but i sometimes sometimes
you just don't want to eat pepperoni pizza you want to move on to like sushi or something and
it becomes your new favorite thing you can't eat pizza every day don't even give me that bagel bites
bullshit commercial about pizza in the morning pizza in the evening pizza at suppertime
pizzas on a bagel it could be pizza every time no don't do that pizza should not be eaten in the
morning in the afternoon and at the evening every day but thank you for the $30 30,000 bits
i have no intention of going back to team fortress i do love that game and i do like seeing it pop
up when it pops up from time to time you'll see it somewhere usually it'll there'll be like an
image or there'll be some artwork or there'll be um something like meme that uses the characters
you're like oh there they are it's a nice little reminder uh modus pons thanks for the 250 there's
a repair pal there's a possible oh this is for the car possible shift control solenoid fault
i'm gonna i'm gonna bookmark that thanks for the help that actually like maybe you just figured it
up pizza is more nutritious than cereal what cereal are you eating because i would have to
tell you that like like Kellogg's corn flakes i'm not sure is less healthy than a slice of
pepperoni pizza but what about total how do people put sugar on their cereal i don't like can we go
over that too why do people do that i've seen people have a bowl of cereal and they go in the
little sugar bowl and just one two three four and you spread it on the top and you move it around
what would you don't do that depends on the cereal no it's not supposed you're not supposed to put
a bunch of sugar on your total brand flakes that's you breaking the design philosophy
of the developer the dev didn't want you to go through that door and you broke it and you went
in anyways and you glitched through the wall and you saw all the items that are in the fucking game
in the dev room breaking and now you you got it you fucked it all up and you soil it for yourself
i don't even put sugar in my coffee anymore did you guys know that you're only supposed to have
35 or 38 grams of added sugar a day did you guys know that did you guys know this
if you drink one soda if you drink one coca-cola classic out of the can your entire day of added
sugar is over and then you are now over what the heck is going on here they're sweetening us to
death this is what they're doing i have this this powder it's like a little uh it's like a
flavored like vanilla powder right you can put it in your coffee you can add it to
pretty much whatever you want on the back of this thing it's oh here here's the the serving size
a third of a cup of this sugar powder is one serving a third of a cup of this
dusty vanilla sugar fucking bullshit is one serving shit's almost 40 grams of sugar why
why would you put that much in there are you okay calm i can't calm down we're talking about the
health of of talking about our health i'm talking about your health did you know
did you know that if you cut the amount of sugar in half that you put into your coffee
you wouldn't know the difference in a blind taste test did you know how can you cut zero and half
good good job i think if i'm i think it's the soda companies the soda companies just want
you to be all popped up on sugar you know that honestly it would be if i would drink two or three
from a day if it were me and i was up to me i would have like three four five sodas a day
every day in fact like before bed too that's something about that is just really very
interesting to me to do that and die wouldn't i don't go don't go to the dentist anymore either
huh hey thank you quarter dime for the three dollars appreciate it
dream of all the games you would stream for over 13 hours it had to be that one
the moment i saw it in the feed i committed myself and over the course of three days watched the
entire thing i was waiting for it and it will remember it fondly that was i went from
really happy and thinking things were funny and fun to being so angry to wanting to just turn the
game off to just accepting everything that was like happening on the screen to madness
that i went over every every single possible emotion was in that 13 hours i i felt every
single emotion happiness fear anger sadness distraught anxious greed gluttony every emotion
wrath yeah these are the sins never mind it was wild though but thank you quarter
dime appreciate it thank you also to bro luck for the five dollars thank you bro luck and they say
this is uh you what you said is real what's real oh this is riding lawnmowers
it's lawnmower races are they are these these aren't road tested though hold on
that's not a lawnmower though yeah this is not a lawnmower where'd they go that's it all right is
it no i feel bad for the person all the way in the back left there that is like a little rinky dink
one why is the guy in the front here allowed to compete there's like different weight classes you
can't like but you can't have like a featherweight versus a super heavyweight how fast is it gonna go
holy shit that's not a lawnmower that that goes faster than my car oh my god something something
and the blades are up thank you bro luck for the five dollars in that video hey wolfstar thanks
for five dollars i watched stream from beginning to end usually only indulge in your youtube
highlight vids definitely watching live again thank you for some reason i thought you i thought
you were gonna say definitely not watching live again i don't know why i just felt it was gonna
happen but hey come on back we'll be here thank you to quarter dime for the three dollars to
uh round us out here it's a clip from god no god i can do it with the jump where is he
that game is fucked
you were insane that stream i hey i'm just me you know that's all there is to it but i'll see you
that's phylactery lich again fifty dollars five thousand bits again more money the hundred dollar
bills are just falling out of your pocket while you just ride by on your lawnmower but holy shit
thank you again for the insane amount of fucking money they say remember when italics called you
dad i do when did he call me i don't remember that dad when it talks call you dad
he's got a scrooge mcduck pool maybe i don't know how do you why does everybody have this
ready already how many monitors do you guys have
thank you i don't know how you even have that ready like 10 of you guys have like 12 monitors
and unfortunately the other two are watching on an iphone so you all have one monitor and you found
it good why do we have to remember everything for you i don't i don't know i do you know how
many words i say you know how many things i hear on a daily basis i hear so many things i say so
many things we have so many things going through here so many words so many people talking so
many fucking games so much stuff happening see you guys tomorrow he called yeah he said he said
thanks dad i was like what are you talking about son and then that was it see you guys tomorrow
we'll just chill we'll play something see you very soon delete that clip guys if you delete
something on the internet you create two of them that's not how it works no but i see you guys
tomorrow i have no idea what we're gonna do i have a few options we'll figure it out i'll be in stream
chat like 40 minutes 30 40 minutes before we'll figure it out hey you know what you know just
just because you know run a virus scan you know when was the last time you done that
it was like to be like cleaned out your fucking c drive do it do it tonight do it tonight run it
scan to make sure you make sure you're good you know nobody nobody ever talks nobody even tells
you to do that did you get yeah i know i'm just saying just like keep up to date on your like
computer and take care of it i just did i got 1482 threads okay well i'm guaranteeing that you are
over the age of 65 you know how you can tell you want like you want a magic trick you guys can do
or like just here's just a complete magic trick in general you could tell the age of somebody
just by how many viruses they have on their computer like all i need is a uh all i need is
a name oh hey all i need is a okay just look at what the last like the last five websites were
in their history you can do one of those like cold reading like okay so um well what what was her
name oh okay what and how old was she you could really do that just scan the computer for viruses
if there's more than 500 viruses that person is over the age of 65 years old i'm getting the fact
that um i'm getting the fact that they that they're older they're wiser but not quite old
the last five tabs the last five history like walmart.com and it's bookmarked as amazon oh i'm
getting some i'm getting some new shopper okay all right i'll see you guys tomorrow have a good
night take care guys see you soon goodbye goodbye goodbye goodbye see you guys later
raid raid just run in random directions and find somebody all right see you tomorrow