Hello, and welcome to Jerma's first ever Spooky Trivia Night.
I'm your host Shannon Sharon, and you're you're involved tonight as well here at home. We have you here on chat
So you'll be answering some of our questions. Let's go ahead and introduce our guests over here. We have first up Jerma
That's me, Jerma985. Y'all know who I am. Do I need an introduction?
I'm going to destroy. This is trivia round, which you're involved in. By the way, happy Halloween. Those of you that are having parties
Hope you have fun. I mean, I'm stuck here doing trivia, but I plan on destroying. I plan on doing very well. This is you guys here
This is chat. That's you. I feel like I'm gonna be I feel pretty confident. I do really do.
I'm glad that you feel that way. Let's see what the board says afterwards. Yeah. So secondly, we have you here, chat
You can see yourselves. Smile and wave, boys. And lastly, welcome back, Dr. Schmortsen. How are you doing tonight?
Absolutely wonderful. Thank you, Sharon. I'm so glad to hear that. I hope you're having a spooky day. Very spooky.
I got scared in the car. Did I tell you that? That's concerning. What happened? I don't remember. Oh, they took my memories.
They? There was multiple. It was like 30. I mean, that's fine. It was very strange.
Are we even live? Oh, we are. Okay. Hey, welcome everybody. Welcome to the trivia section. So, uh, how we do this?
How do we do this? All right. Well, let's introduce our first categories here today.
Here are today's categories.
We have
17th century poetry. That's a good one. Super good. My favorite.
Oh, I need to change this. By the way, if you're having a Halloween party right now, pump up the music.
No, no, actually turn the music down because you want to be able to hear us. You want to be able to hear what we're doing.
So again, here we are with today's categories. First off, we have
17th century poetry. Okay. Next up, wide open space.
Interesting. Thirdly, Goosebumps books part one. Yes. He's pumped. Water, water,
everywhere. To be or not to be. Sounds pretty good. And lastly,
spooky things. No. All right.
Now, uh. Because it's Halloween, right?
Jerma, as this is your show, would you like to kick us off here? I get to go first?
Yeah, you do. All right. Well, I think I'll take 17th century poetry for 50, please. All right.
Let's uh, let's see what we got here. John Calvin crafted this Christian
Ideology stressing God's power and the moral weakness of human beings that many of the era's poets followed. Uh, what is?
Dr. Strange. I have no idea. Times up. All right, Dr. Schmoyzen. What do you got for us? Yes, Shannon.
It's what is
Calvinism. Why is that?
Congratulations, Dr. Schmoyzen. You have won the first points of the evening.
Uh, and uh, you know, as the rules of our super generic non-trademark finding show goes, you get to pick the next category.
What would you like to go for? I will continue with
17th century poetry, please for 200. 200. All right. Let's uh, let's start racking up these points here. Now,
followers of Ben Johnson touted themselves as this family-oriented namesake.
Who are the sons of Ben? Well done. All right. Sons of Ben. Okay, the sons of Ben. Pretty good job.
Appreciate the nice work. Yeah, got some. All right. So now we're at a 250 solid points category.
How about Shannon wide open spaces for 400, please. All right, Dr. Schmoyzen.
Let's uh, let's see what's in this category. Let's open up this box.
This curious individual was the first person to ever look through at the moon through a telescope.
Uh, uh, uh, who is Thomas Harriot? Thomas Harriot? Who is Thomas Harriot? Yes, that would be the correct answer.
Thank you, Dr. Schmoyzen. That was Galileo. Wasn't it Galileo?
I'm, uh, not sure that Wikipedia would agree with you. Is that even correct? Apologies for this. That's not even correct.
That's not a correct answer. That's Galileo was the first person, wasn't it? That is right. Who the fuck is Thomas Harriot?
How do you, why do you know that? I guess he's a damn, he's a goddamn doctor. What am I talking about? Go on.
All right. Sorry about that, Dr. Schmoyzen. We have a little bit of a rowdy crowd this evening. It wasn't Galileo.
Uh, would you, uh, like to take us to the next question?
Yes, please. Uh, 17th century poetry once again for 400, please.
400. All right. A religious allegory by John Bunyan, which has never been out of print and was the first ever novel written in English.
What is Pilgrim's Progress?
What is the Pilgrim's Progress?
Well done.
Can I? Yes, Sheremo. How many of these are you going to get right? Can I answer a question? Is that possible?
Well, if you could get one right, yes. Well, I didn't, I got the first one wrong, but all right, go ahead. Keep going.
All right. Dr. Schmoyzen, take us back.
Surely. Um, let's go with wide open spaces for 800, please.
All right. Wide open spaces for 800. Measuring at negative 240 degrees Celsius.
This is the coldest known spot in our solar system. Uh, yes.
Do you know it well, Dr. Schmoyzen? I do. What is the lunar south pole?
What? What? What is the lunar south pole? Yes. No, it's Neptune. That is the correct answer. What?
Neptune. Is it Neptune? I thought Neptune was the coldest spot on the galaxy.
What were the questions? Idiot.
Oh my. Oh my. It seems like we have a little bit of a rivalry here folks on this evening show.
All right, Dr. Schmoyzen. You're, uh, you're taking us away here. What, uh, what are you gonna crush next?
Certainly. Let's go for
water, water everywhere. All right. Four? How many points? How about 200 points? Water, water everywhere for 200 points.
Reaching down nearly into the underworld. The world's lowest lake sits at
1,371 feet below sea level. Uh, what is the Dead Sea?
All right. Let's take a look at that answer. What is the Dead Sea?
Correctamundo there, Dr. Schmoyzen. Jerma, how you feeling right now? We should have invited Burger Boy.
Because he's getting all these answers right.
Uh, so how does it work if he gets it wrong that I get it right? I can answer or we can answer, right?
Should he ever? We're in this together. Yeah, Chad. Chad, how you feeling right now? How's it going out there for you folks?
I mean, I kind of wish I could answer a question.
I feel like Chad feels the same way. Go on. Go on. No, keep going. All right. All right, Dr. Schmoyzen. Take us away.
All right. Let's try
to be or not to be for 50.
To be or not to be for 50 points? Absolutely.
This carrot crunching
Wascley Wabbit
soared Warner Brothers into the spotlight in the 1940s. Dr. Schmoyzen, might you know? Jerma seems to know.
Unfortunately. Who is Bugs Bunny?
We get double points. Put that down here. I get points for that. Let's uh, let's take a quick point check.
What do we got here? So we have Jerma, proudly.
Would you mind saying aloud what your points may be? How well you doing this evening? Zero. Zero. Okay. All right.
Uh, we have chat over here also with zero. Sorry guys. We'll bring back the doctor. This is what happened. I swear to god.
And uh, you bring the good doctor back and he just okay. I mean he's a doctor.
He's a doctor. What do you what do you even do about it? Dr. Schmoyzen, proudly here with
2,100 points. Doing pretty good. Doing pretty good. I will give you a commend you. Doing well. Doing pretty well. As we should.
Good sportsmanship is always appreciated here. Love to answer a question. On our first ever spooky.
I would love to talk on my own stream. It'd be great. Eventually.
I've got the buzzer here, but gone. All right, Dr. Schmoyzen.
Why would you like to blow us away with next? Let's go for a 17th century
poetry for a 100, please. Gonna be easy.
It's gonna be like who is. One of the most influential poetic figures of this era. Most know him now by only two syllables.
Who is Voltaire?
And the answer. Yes. Who is Voltaire? Congratulations, Dr. Schmoyzen. You really know your stuff. How can I say?
How do you know all this stuff? It's frankly quite embarrassing. You're a lie detector doctor. You shouldn't know all this information.
Maybe you do. I don't know. Maybe. All right, Dr. Schmoyzen. Next category. Yes, indeed.
Let's try to continue. Let's try with to be or not to be for.
To be or not to be for 400. All right, Parker, Griffin, and Dinklage.
All famous faces sharing this common name. Dr. Schmoyzen. Yes, I believe that is
Beater. Who's Beater? Who? What is Beater? What? What?
What?
There's no way you know that question's answer. What do you mean? I should have known that. What does that mean?
What does what does happen? I mean, that's why you have it. All right, Dr. Schmoyzen. Take us away.
I could have got that question right. How much was that worth?
Let's try.
Whatever. Are you quite done? I'm, yeah.
Let's try to be or not to be for 800, please. All right.
Oh, looks like we have a daily double. Daily double.
Daily double. Hooray. Is it worth double points?
I hope not, for your sake. The best hand is the natural nine in this Bond beloved card game. Dr. Schmoyzen?
Yes, that is
Poker.
I'm sorry, sir. Oh, I can't answer. I'm sorry. Mr. Elbertson. Are you ready to answer?
And that question is what is Baccarat? What is Baccarat?
Congratulations, Dr. Schmoyzen. You get another several hundred points.
This is fucking stupid. All right, Dr. Elbertson. I'm sorry. You're not the doctor. Mr. Elbertson. I went to school.
I imagine.
But not for any of these.
All right, Dr. Schmoyzen. What do you got for us?
Uh, Shannon. All right. We're ready again. Let's try wide open spaces for 50, please. Okay.
Really still going for the low points here.
I mean really racking them up. The flattest planet. The flattest planet in our solar system.
This was originally thought to be three separate planets.
Yes, because of. Can you get me a drink?
What is?
Saturn. What is Saturn? All right. Yes.
Congratulations. You've won yet another question.
Dr. Mr. Elbertson. How you feeling? Oh, would you like to hear from me? Uh, just this once.
Um, no, this is all right. I guess we're supposed to be able to play together and
2020 hindsight, it really was probably a bad idea to bring somebody that was that smart. We need like
50 IQ people up here because I have like 72 IQ. It's just not very good. Oh, he's falling asleep. Oh, it's not great.
Okay. All right. All right. This guy. This guy. Me and this guy. What do you got for us, Dr. Schmoyzen? We got history.
Are you crazy? Let's try Shannon to start to wrap things up. Let's try
water water everywhere for 800, please.
All right, bigger points.
This lake just sits at an interesting junction between the borders of Germany, Austria, and Switzerland. Uh, yes.
Lake Mead? No, that's in Vegas. What is Lake Constance?
All right. Yes. What is Lake Constance?
Wow, I'm not sure that we've ever had a streak this long on the show. Thank you, Dr. Schmoyzen. All right, take us away.
What what's your next pick here? And uh, only a few left. How about 17th century poetry for 800, please?
All right. What do we have? Oh, I'm sorry about that folks. That's all we have time for.
That's all we have time for. That's all we have time for for round one. Round one. Round one is over.
Yes, and Dr. Schmoyzen has 5,000 and 50 points. Let's uh, do a quick point check here.
Jerma rolling in with zero points.
Chat also with zero. We didn't get a chance. And Dr. Schmoyzen at
5,000 and 50 points. How you feeling there, Dr. Schmoyzen? Can I take off this Lisa Simpson mask? I'm having quite an evening.
Thank you, Shannon. Unbelievable. Oh, I'm so glad that you're enjoying yourself. I'm not sure about uh, Mr. Elvis.
There's a second round. There is a second round. All right, thanks. We're supposed to be banking points.
All right. Does this use a buzzer too? Yes, this does. This does. This does use the buzzer.
I was told it didn't. There it goes. It's out. All right, no more buzzers. No buzzers on this round.
We're done with the buzzers. Schmoyzen just
fucking whip it behind you. Who cares? Okay. Wait, new categories too. Yes. So
ran out of time for round one. Uh, we got a little overlay there. Okay. So, uh,
let's check out round two's categories. Shall we? First off,
anime. Anime. Cool. Jeremy's Life. Okay. That's weird, but. Very specific, isn't it? Thank God. That's, thank
we've got some real categories here. Goosebumps books part two. Thank God.
Jerma 985 Kanta. Okay. Jerma's Friends. What is that? What is that? What is that? And what is that
is the category. We're about to find out. Very, very, very interesting stuff. What is that? Okay.
All right. So Dr. Schmoyzen, as you did lead us in the last round, uh, you do get to pick the first
question. Uh, choose wisely, I advise. Um, but, uh, what would you like to talk about today?
Okay. Thank you, Shannon. Let's try anime for 800. Please. All right. Anime for 800. Now this is a
multiple choice around multiple choice this time. So chat, please answer a, b, c or d. You know how
it goes. All right. What multiplier is super cyan three, a three times B 250 times C 400 times
or D 9,000. Don't give them enough time to look it up. Uh, are they voting? They're voting.
How are you doing there Dr. Schmoyzen? Uh, uh, B perhaps. B perhaps. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Jerma.
I'm gonna go with a super saiyan times three means it's been three times. I'm gonna go with a. All
right. A B. Yes. Yes. And, uh, chat. Do we have chats answer? Chat has voted D. 9,000. 9,000.
That's not three. It seems to be a pretty popular number here. I mean, I would imagine, Jerma,
with this costume you have on, you might know a bit, a bit about this. I mean, I know a little.
I know a little. I mean, if you, oh, this costume. Right. Cause well, it was either this or a child
size incredible hook. That's what happens when you buy a costume two days before Halloween.
Child size, you say? Yeah. All right. And you're sure that wouldn't fit? How tall are you?
What? How tall? What do you mean? What? How tall might you be? Five, six, six feet tall. Six, one.
Six, one. You're sure? Yes. In the empirical system?
Whatever. Can we get the next question, please? Okay. All right. So what was our answer here for
question one of round two? 400 C. So I don't think. Wait, what? It was 400? It was 400.
How does, how does 400 times? Wait, hold on a minute. Let me just get my points back in the
middle. There we go. It's not three. It's not three. It's 400. Why is it, why is it not super
saying 400? Whatever. All right. We all fucking lose. We're still at zero points. You guys,
we got to do something about this. We're at zero. Okay. All right. So chat, we're going to let you
pick the next category as a kind of rough goings on scene here. What, what category, what number,
what are we going for? I think we have Goosebumps books, part two for 1600. Goosebumps part two.
All right. Let's see what the question is here. What do we got? Who is Naruto's father? Good lord,
saying his names. All right. Option A. Minato Namikaze. B. Remember this one? Kakashi Hattotake.
Goosebumps volume 58. Naruto. C. Kushina Uzumaki and D. Hiruzen Sarutobi.
Jerma, might you have an opinion? This is not a Goosebumps book. This is a, this is a Naruto
question. They were just pumped in to be mean to me. Okay. Who is Naruto's father? Yes. Minato
Kakashi, Kushina or Hiruzen? I'm going to say, I'm going to say, well, wouldn't it be Naruto?
Something Naruto? What's, what's Naruto's first name? I'm not sure that that's how their family
names work. Do you know Naruto's first name? Not sure if there's a logic behind this. No, no, no,
wait, it's Naruto Uzumaki. I'm not going to say it out loud because you'll get it. It's, uh, wait a
minute, but you'll hear it. I'll tell you. I'll just tell you. I'm going to whisper it to you. Okay.
Okay. The answer that I'm going to give is in case I don't want them to hear. All right. I know
Naruto. You really going to know what the fuck I'm doing? Absolutely. I gave my answer. Not a
doubt in my mind. Doctor, go ahead. Oh, yes. Let's uh, well, let's, let's let chat chime in here.
Oh, chat has an answer. Chat, how you doing over there? What do we got for chat? All right. So chat
has voted A, Minato Namikatsu. Wait, what? Yes. Why did they do that? Why? Because it may be the
correct answer. Why did they do that? I could not tell you. It's, it's, all right. All right. Doing
great. Doctor, we're all friends here. Don't be frozen. You know anything about anime, doctor?
Certainly. Uh, it's D, Hirose and Saratobi. D. All right. So chat has voted A. We have Jeremie over
here with C and the doctor with answer D. Now, uh, what might be the correct answer? Who is Minato
Namikatsu? A. I need to get one point in this whole game. Otherwise it's going to be bad. Wait,
it's not, it's, I thought it was Naruto Uzumaki. It is not. But that's not, isn't that Naruto's
name? Is that, is that Naruto's name? Naruto Uzumaki? You don't know. Does anybody back there know?
Does anybody fucking know? I can't see the chat so I have no idea. What? Okay. All right. All right.
Where are they going next? Where are we going next, guys? And it is a somewhat even split.
Where are they? Somewhere in between. No one has a favorite. All right. It looks like Jeremie's life.
Okay. We're going to take this. Jeremie's life for 800. Okay. I hope to God you get this one right.
Oh, what is that? This is our, uh, daily double scare. Daily double scare. Okay. You may be asking
what that is. I don't know what that is. So does that, does that mean points are deducted or? It
means something fun is going to happen. What the fuck is that thing? What is that thing? Hey, hey!
All right. All right. Fun. That was fun. Here he is. That was fun. I think it is. That was very fun.
Okay. What was that? And who is that person? I don't remember that person being here an hour ago.
Well, he's a ghost. Can I stand back on my thing? I feel so much more powerful when I'm on this.
If it makes you feel better, yes. Oh, shit. That's better. All right. What's the question?
What is Jeremie's grandpa's last name? Once again, Jeremie. I hope to the Lord and Savior
that you get this correct. I, I know this. A. Boyle. B. Richards. C. Wilfred. D. Steelhelm.
I know. Tell me. Oh, you, I go first? Yes. Oh, um, but if I say it, then everybody's gonna hear it.
That's true. All right, chat. All right, do chat first, do chat first. Chat, what do you got for us?
How to check it? Oh, right. All right. I know what I, my turn. Okay. I'm gonna go with D. D.
All right. So chat has said D. Jeremie has said D. Dr. Spoitser? No, C. Wilfred, please. C. Okay.
There it is. All right. What is Steelhelm? Congratulations, chat, as it was your question.
I just wanted to give Jeremie a little bonus there that he got to answer your question. I did.
That's a good question. So there he is. That's an old question, too. That's really cool. All right.
So here we go, chat. Still your turn. Winning points over here. What do you got for us?
I wonder if it's Naruto's father again. Okay. You're, but you already did Jeremie's life. Yeah,
we already did that one. All right. Okay. So we have anime for 2000. Oh, boy. I wonder what this is.
Here we go. Another daily scare. Well, I can see you here standing there. So wow, this is really
fucking scary. Oh, no. There he is. He's scary. What's on his face? Oh, shit. That's what I
should have done. Another fucking Naruto question. All right. All right. Go on.
In Naruto, which of the following is not a current Shinobi village? A. Hidden star village. B.
Hidden grass village. C. Hidden rain village. D. Hidden ice village. And this is what is not
currently a village. It is not. There's a lot. I don't think any of their villages are out in
the open, honestly, based on these answers. Okay. Well, let's see. Whatever. All right, chat. Chat,
what do you got for us? What do you got, chat? What do you got? Are they voting? No, there are
more than like three animes that aren't Naruto, right? I don't think they know. Maybe talk to your
people. All right. So I'm going to say, all right, grass. I remember grass. That's like what Naruto
is in. Naruto is in grass village. A lot of grass. So definitely rain. Grass and rain. Naruto is from
grass village. So I'm going to say D. D. I don't know. That's what I'm going with. Okay. So Jared
comes in hot with D. Hidden ice village. There's no hidden ice village. Chat has let us know that
a hidden star village is their choice. And a doctor. I'll go with hidden star village. A. Sorry,
which one? A, please. A. All right. Well, we do have two winners. Yeah. Ice village. That's the one.
I knew it. I'm telling you. He's from grass village. There's only like two other options.
There we go. He's getting more points here. So not exactly taking the lead. 2800. Holy shit.
That's pretty good. That's pretty great. Yeah. Second place. Come on. You got to suck it up a
little bit here. Professors look a little sleepy here. All right. Jerma, your turn. I get to pick.
You do get to pick. Oh, all right. You know what? I got an idea here. Why don't we do
Jerma's content for 2000. Jerma's content for 2000. Hopefully. I hope so. How many
YouTube subscribers did Jerma have when he had 100 uploads? What? How would anybody know this?
10,000? B, 50,000? C, 75,000? Or D, 100,000? At any rate, pretty impressive. Do you know?
I could take a pretty good guess. Chat, go first. All right, chat. You go first. You go first.
Chat, what do you got for us? All right. So it seems that there's a little bit of a split
in chat. Really? But B is winning. So chat believes that you had 50,000 followers for 100 uploads.
I don't think so. I think it's more. No, or less. 100. Okay. My first, my first like 40 uploads went
to like 30 people. I know that for a fact. No, I'm going to write. I'm going with A. A? All right. So
Jerma's coming in with A. It might be a little too low. Chat has B. Dr. Schmoyzen. What is it?
You know what YouTube is? C. C. He doesn't know what YouTube is. Okay. What is 10,000?
Congratulations, Jerma. You know your own life. I know my own channel. It's doing great. And I'm
fucking posing. Let's do a little point check here. We have Jerma with 4,800. Climbing up on you.
Chat with 1,600. You guys are not doing very well. And the professor with 5,050. He's not doing very
well. Yeah, it doesn't seem like he's doing too well in the second round. I'm about to pass you.
Yeah, yeah. All right. So let's let chat pick the next question here. Get a little interaction.
All right. Where are we going? How are we doing? All right. What is that for 2,000? Frankly, guys,
I'm pretty excited for this one. What is that? What is that? What does that mean? What is that?
Maybe the category. Yes. Okay. Who is this? I have my own guesses, but I shouldn't say.
All right. A few seconds left on the clock here, Jerma. How is chat going to be able to answer this?
What do you mean, who is this? They can't answer this question. There's no choices here.
It's just who is this? All right. What are they writing? Is it a better idea? What are they
writing? It's a gnome is what they're saying. Okay. It's anum or it is gnome. I'm going to go with
a close-up of a mustache. A mustache? What's the red? What is the red? That's what I want to know.
Doctor, you're a doctor. What is that? Yes, doctor. Might you have a live opinion of this?
Sure. It's a rabbit. It's a rabbit. A rabbit? I'm going to go with a mustache. I'm going to
go with a mustache. A mustache. All right. So we've got a gnome, a mustache, and a rabbit.
Chat's answer is A. What is it? Which I hate to inform you, it's not a multiple choice question.
It's Ronald Reagan, folks. Ronald Reagan. Unfortunately, we're not going to be able to
give out any points for this round. That's impossible. That is an impossible question.
I think we should all get 1,000 points. We all get 1,000 points for that one
because that's impossible. Mr. Albertson. You know what? No, fuck it. We're going,
what is that for 1,600? All right, he's taking the lead. Mr. Albertson. Let's go. Let's go. What is
it? What song is this? What song is this? Listen up, folks. What song is this? How are we going to hear
this? What? What song is this? You've got to give more than a tenth of a second. What song is this?
Do it again. I need you to do it again. Professor, where are you in all this?
We're both on the same page. I don't think we can both get this. Do it like a couple, two more times.
So chat's answer is in. Okay, chat's answer is in. So a couple more seconds here.
I'm pretty impressed with their knowledge, honestly.
There are like 700,000 songs that all of them start like that. I'm going to say
And time's up. Professor, what is your answer? I have no idea. I have absolutely no idea.
Row Your Boat. Row Your Boat, folks. Row Your Boat. All right. Actually, that's pretty good.
Chat's answer, Blue Daboudi by Eiffel 65. Jerma.
I don't think that's an answer. Whatever. How many points was that worth?
1600. All right. So chat got 1600 points just in that question. Congratulations, chat. What's
your final time? 3200 points. All right. We're still in third here, but we can still catch up.
All right. So chat, you're up next to pick the question. Let's see what you got.
15, 18%, 20%. All right. Jerma's Friends for 2000. Okay.
Oh, look at this. He's ready. Oh, look at that.
Too much. Look, let him see you. Let him see you. Go to this camera right here. Look at this. Look
over there. Let him see you. He's got like a metal face. There he is, folks. Hope you're enjoying
that at home. Here we go. All right. How many formal appearances has Mr. Sneak Man had? Mr. Sneak?
A, three. B, four. C, five. D, six. Formal appearances. That doesn't count. What do you mean
informal? Has there ever been an informal appearance? What's your opinion? Okay. One.
No, he wasn't even in Jerma, but one. Two. Chat, what do you think? Okay. I think I have an idea
because he was in like, he was in at least two. One, two. I have an idea. I have an idea.
I got an idea. All right. Jerma, what do you have? Five. C. Five. C. All right. So, Jerma,
answer C with five. Chat, A with three. Professor? A, three. That actually might be three.
That actually might be three. All right. It's six. What is six? What are they, though? Do we know?
Jerma Rumble 2, Jerma Rumble 3, Jerma Rumble Rumblehouse. Is it three? Do I not even know?
Is it three? Did you black out? There's only been three rumbles and then like one or two offshoots.
It's six? What's the other video? I have no idea. All right. I have no idea. Well, since you don't
know your own life, we're going to move on from this. Well, I mean, let's pull out random shit
from everybody else's life from 10 years ago and find out what it is. All right. Chat, what do you
have for us? And what is that for 1200? Our favorite category here in round two. Who is this?
That's either an eye or a mouth. I don't know. Bold statements there. Professor looks a bit
perplexed. But we don't get any. Nope. There's no way for us to answer this. Nope. That's all you get.
Eight grainy potato pixels. Why do you think they're spelling out? Is it like an I? I think
it's an I. There's no way anybody can answer. You think it's an I. I'm falling off my body.
Let's go with. All right, Jerma. Chat has their answer in. What do you got for us?
How do you mean chat has their answer in? They're very confident. There's a consensus already.
They're confident people. Okay. So chat has their answer in now. And it took them 15 seconds. Is
this something that I don't know that I should know? I'm going to say my eye. Your eye. Your own eye.
My own eye like zoomed in or something. Wow. All right. Chat, your answer is scout and professor.
That's pretty good. Lassie. Lassie. That's could be. Jeremy's own eye, scout or lassie. All right,
let's see who it is. It is the one, the only Genghis Khan. Could you at least have made these
like slightly related to like the community? Congratulations everyone, you all lost. That's
a painting of Genghis Khan. That's not Genghis Khan. That's a portrait of Genghis Khan,
right? That's a portrait. That's not a picture. All right, whatever. All right. Are they picking
again? Back to the board. Where are they going? Chat, what do we got? I think we know. What is
this for 800? Shittiest category. Best category I think you mean. Thank you doc. What song is this?
What song is this? Oh, I wonder what it is.
Oh, I've heard that one on the radio a thousand times.
Three seconds. A full three seconds. Do it. A full three seconds. Do we not have a full three
seconds if the song is not available? That's the whole song actually. That's the whole song.
Every song starts like that. Every single song in human history goes like
that and then it goes into the song. What song is that? Can you even name the song you just
saw? No, but they all do that. I don't know. Gorillaz. A Gorillaz song. Not even a single
specific one. All right. Might be a Gorillaz song. Congratulations to those three people.
If you can sort through all those comments, you may be one of them. Three people got this right?
How? Unless this is your favorite song and you just know it like it's just automatic.
Find them after an award. This is ridiculous. I think this is ridiculous. Oh wow. I mean I'm
creeping up on you and I'll probably I mean I'm getting close but you know. Not too close I hope.
I mean you're still in the lead but we'll see. And professor, your answer? Sound of music. The
sound of music, folks. You just played every dubstep stop. I don't even know how to say it.
You played every dubstep song I've ever heard. Is that correct? It was Beetlejuice. That's not
Beetlejuice. Beetlejuice goes. That's a dubstep mix. That's a dubstep mix of Beetlejuice. Yes.
Have you been on the internet? Yeah. That's what we listen to. What's going to happen in 20 more
years? Are they going to do a dubstep remix of the remix of Beetlejuice? How the fuck would anybody
know that? All right. So are we giving that to chat since three people got it right or?
No. They're going to be dropping glasses on the ground. It's going to sound like
Beetlejuice and they'll do it. It'll be like another remix 30 years in the future. God damn
millennials. All right. We're going to give that to chat. Congratulations to those three people.
You know who you are. Go wild. You're giving it to chat even though three people got it right.
And guess what category chat has picked next. What is that for 400? No, this better be really easy.
It's not. What do you mean it's not? Oh. Who is this? That's a lampshade. That's what you're
saying in that? No, I'm not saying it yet. I'm not saying it yet. All right. Hold on. The professor's
down. It's not. You're looking for the exit. All right. I think he's pretty done. All right,
Jeremiah. Give me your best shot. I know what I'd guess. It's an egg. It's an egg? No, it's not an
egg. Is it like an embryo? Yours are very thematic here. Is it like an egg? Is it like a zoomed in
egg? Like a microscope egg? All right. So we have egg. Egg. Chat says doge. Doge. And professor?
UFO kazoo. A UFO kazoo. Oh, it's actually. I hope for your sake it is a UFO kazoo.
Oh, it's Banjo Kazooie. Here we have it, folks. Banjo Kazooie. You got it pretty close.
You got it pretty close. A UFO kazoo. You just had to add an IE on the end and you would have
added it. Unfortunately, Dr. Shmoysen, that was not the answer we were looking for. A UFO shaped
kazoo? Or a UFO with a kazoo? Why don't you tell me? All right, Dr. Lee, the category.
This has been wildly concerning. Chat, we're going to let you pick the next one here.
Banjo Kazooie. A bit of a mess on site here. What do you mean what is that? We already did all of
them. They want more. All right. All right. There you go, Dr. Shmoysen. Well deserved.
UFO kazoo. Get that as a tattoo. I'm going to give you a clap for that one. All right. Who is
the narrow-toes father? Who is it? All right. Anime for $1,600. Good Lord. Who is the only
homunculus without... Excuse me. It's Ouroboros. I know. I've got the outfit on.
You better get this right. Who is the only homunculus without Ouroboros tattoo?
A. Envy. B. Pride. C. Gluttony. D. Sloth. But what anime? It's just anime. Who is the only
homunculus in anime that doesn't have a tattoo? Showing his true colors here. Honey, come on.
What do you think? I got this. Well, it seems like we have quite a consensus from chat. So,
they seem to have narrowed down. I actually do know this. Full Metal Alchemist Brotherhood is my...
I hear people laughing. I hear people laughing back there. Multiple. And it's messing with my
psyche. All right. I know this because it's one of my favorite animes ever. It's one of the only
animes I've ever watched. That would be... Well, Doctor, why don't you answer for me? Pause. Yes.
C. Gluttony. All right. C. Gluttony. Pretty good guess. We have chat here. Strong answer. B.
Right. I said it at the same time. Wow. Right. There you go. Hey. Hey. Hey. Come on, man. Ready?
High five. Ready. Get in there. Well, I was talking to chat. He's in it. He's in it to win it here,
folks. All nine of us. All right. I'll still give you a high five, though. All right. So, the answer
is yes. B. Who is pride? Yes. How much was that worth? That was a really high point question for
being so easy. So easy. That was very easy. Have you ever seen Full Metal Alchemist Brotherhood?
Not the original one. The original one, they split halfway through. Full Metal Alchemist,
Full Metal Alchemist Brotherhood. The Brotherhood is a real story from the manga. I'm sorry. No,
like the back here hid. Oh, I thought you said it's not. I was like, excuse me. Oh, my. Say it's not.
All right, Jeremy. We're going to give you this one. All right. We'll do Jerma985's content for
$1,600. I know my own stuff. All right. Jerma's content for $1,600. What did Jerma do to personally
thank his first 500 subscribers? A. Tell a personal story. B. Create a TF2 server. C. Lift weights.
The funniest part about this is the correct answer is like the shittiest one. Nothing. Jerma,
how about you go? Let's have Doctor answer first. Oh, yeah, Doctor. What do you think I would do?
Sure. How about nothing? Nothing. Strong nothing, Professor. What about chat? Chat? Chat's gone with
C. Lift weights. It is C. Lift weights. Doctor, you haven't seen my 500 subscriber thank you video
where I was in the bottom of my parents' Facebook, lifting 35 pound dumbbells, pretending to be really
cool? Possibly. You haven't seen that video? Best gift to us all. Yeah, I mean, it probably was.
All right. Wait a minute. Hold on a second. How many points is that? How many points do I have?
I'm doing pretty good. 6400 to be exact. Chat in. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait. Chat just get all those points. Update. Jerma, we have... I want, I want Goose,
I get to go, right? Yes. I want Goosebumps Books for 2000. Let's go. Bring it in. Goosebumps for
2000. In Monster Blood, what is the name of the witch that gives the blood its abilities? A.
Sarabeth. B. Ymiriden. C. Valshesh. D. Syndral. In Monster Blood. Yes. You ever read the Goosebumps
Book? No. He must like reading Doctor. Yes, certainly. Doctor Professor. I mean, you've read
a lot of books, but have any of them been Goosebumps Books? I don't think you're allowed to wear elbow
patches if you don't read all of them. Oh, come on. Goosebumps? Goosebumps? Yeah, R.L. Stein. Great
literature. Yeah, that's good stuff. All right, I got my answer. Okay. I'm gonna, okay, I'm gonna,
my reasoning for this answer is it's the only one that has a apostrophe in it, so that makes sense
to me. It's elegant. So I'm gonna say, I'm gonna say Valshesh. C. C. Valshesh. Because that's like,
oh, it's a scary name, because it's like, oh, it's Valshesh. It's like a different, you know,
that makes sense to me. And Chat, what was your answer? What was Chat's name? Chat says A.
That's like a regular name. It's a very regular name. Hello to all the Cerebets out there.
Professor? Valshesh. That's a good, right? That's a good answer. So we have two Cs and an A. That
means I'm as smart as a doctor, by the way, if anyone's watching. That means I'm as intelligent
as he is. All right, so the correct answer is A. Cerebetsh. It's actually Cerebetsh. It is Cerebetsh,
yes. It's actually Cerebetsh. The apostrophe proved you wrong, unfortunately. Okay, well,
that's all good. All right, Chat, since you won that round, where are we going? I believe...
There are no more what is this category, so stop choosing it. Please do not all choose
what is that. Anime. All right, anime for $1200. I think we have a specific crowd here. They do
know they're anime. I could... Rightfully so. What is the name of the cage in the hidden mist?
A. Hokage. Hokage? I don't even know this answer, but I know it's kage. It's kage and hokage.
That one. B. Raikage. C. Mizukage. And D. Kazekage. I already said it. A. All right,
well, we have your answer. That hurt my hand a little. Professor? Give me a minute.
Will do. D. Kazekage. Kazekage. It could be. I don't know. I think it's hokage. All right,
and then we have Chat's answer. C. Mizukage. And they are correct. What is Mizukage? Congratulations,
Chat. Congratulations. You won another, what was that, 1200 points? Is it 1200? I believe it was.
So what do you have now? Was it 9200? 10,400 points. They have broken the barrier, folks.
They're in the five digits. All right, congratulations. Are they going anywhere else?
All right. I'm sorry to say this, but I mean, you gotta get it. Come on. You know, you gotta
get a G. Come on. You're Jeremy's life for 2000? Let's see how well you do here.
Here we are. Jeremy's life for 2000. How did Jeremy get the scar on the back of his head?
A. Baseball accident. I know this, like very, very, very vividly. B. Being karate kid. C.
Falling off a ladder. D. Thinking too hard. Well, that's a funny meme answer for the last one.
I wonder, I wonder how many people actually get this. Me too. In the chat. I really am curious.
Me too. Because I think I've told the story, like, have I ever told the story ever? I don't think
I've ever told the story. Maybe I have. Professor, what do you think about Jeremy's life at this point?
How do you think he got that scar? I have a scar on the back of my head. Maybe you could take a
look at it later. Why don't we try thinking too hard? I see he's making fun of me. I know he has
like 132 IQ. He's trying to make me look bad. That's all right. Getting a little heated in here.
That's okay. That's fine. Everyone's allowed one, right? Chat says C. Falling off a ladder.
Well, unfortunately, you're all wrong. It's from B. Being the Karate Kid. Karate Kid was one of the
most popular movies when I was younger and my brother kicked me off the bed. We were doing it.
I smashed my head on the back of a fireplace. I actually had to get a bunch of staples in my head
and I remember it was very, very, very tragic. It was very, like, very, like, very, like, tragic.
It was horrible. Sorry. I remember it for the rest of my life. It's Karate Kid. That's correct.
Being Karate Kid. That's right. Not acting as Karate Kid. I mean, like, in that moment,
you were Karate Kid. I was like 11. Got it. How many points was that worth? 2,000. Why was
that worth so much points? And Jerma? Okay, so I get to pick now, right? All right. Absolutely.
Why don't we go with, I'm going to stay there. Let's go. Jeremy's Life 1600. I'm going to bank
points here. Jeremy's Life for 1600, folks. During what year did Jerma's brother get married?
A. 2009. B. 2010. C. 2011. And D. 2012. Jerma, do you know?
That's really easy to get wrong because it's a four-year span, so I could be,
I hope you're not watching because I'm probably going to get it wrong. I have an idea.
25% chance of getting it right here. There is a 20, but it's like, look, okay,
let me explain. There's a way, when you have a span of, like, a lot of people got married
during that time. I had my brother, my sister, a bunch of friends, and it all happened between,
like, 2009 and 2012. We're looking for a one-sentence answer here, sir. Okay, I'm going to say.
I think the professor knows. Do you know this? He's there. I was actually at the, were you at the
wedding? You may have been. The best man, pay attention. I'm going to go with B. 2010. Final
answer. That's how this works on final millionaire. Final millionaire. I think it was 2010, I think.
It could have been 2009. I don't know. All right, so Jerma with B.
Chat, your answer. C, 2011. I don't think it was. Professor? B, 2010. Right, I know, come on.
B, 2010. All right, and here we have it, folks, the correct answer. What is 2011? Right. Okay,
well, I was, I was one year away. Just one. Just one. I mean, it was, all right, so I, I switched
him around. I switched him around. I switched him around. It's okay. I was, it was within like
eight months. Okay, that's fine. Happens to all of us. That's right. Okay. All the best of us.
Where's chat going? All right, chat, we're going to let you pick this next one.
People still, okay. Still loving the what is that, aren't we, folks? There are no more questions
left. Anime for 400. Clear second favorite category here. Oh, I wonder. Who is Naruto's
father? We can't, we all can't get this wrong. I actually do not, I swear to God, I do not fucking
remember the, I don't remember. Seems like a personal problem, sir. I'm sorry. I don't remember.
I don't remember. I was paying attention. If you had to guess. Why would I not pay attention during
a quiz show? Okay, it's not, doc, it's, let's work together on this because, are we allowed to do
that? It was, it was not, okay, it was not Uzumaki. I remember that. What, what, what's the answer?
You remember? I don't remember. Try A. Is it A? Okay, I'm gonna go, I'm gonna go with A. All right,
we have Jerma with A. I actually don't remember what it was. Chat's coming in strong with A,
professor. A. A. Yes, all right, we have a consensus here, folks. Who is Minato Namikaze?
Thank you, doctor, appreciate that. Congratulations, everyone. Appreciate it. You've all won.
Who is Naruto's father? Who is Naruto's father? Let's see those points. Okay, so we have Jerma
in with 10,400. How many years are in the lead? Chat with 12,400. I'm gonna rip the
cord out from you guys. Then we have the professor here with his award-winning first round 5,850
points. That's just what happened. The tables have turned here, folks. All right, so who picks?
Chat? Chat's gonna get to pick this one. Jerma's friends for 1,600. My friends. I love all my
friends. All right, who eliminated Beanbag Sonic in Germania 2018? A. Glooman. B. Greenscreen. C.
Adam Sandler. Or D. Fireman. A few seconds on the clock here, folks. I'm gonna say,
I'm gonna say, no, I gave Adam Sandler zero in every category, so definitely listen.
I'm gonna say Greenscreen. I'm gonna say B. A little bit of a kerfuffle here on the set,
folks. We're doing all right. We're all right. A little rowdy. Am I hurt? No, I've never hurt.
How are the knees? I'm strong. I'm fine. I'm gonna go B. Greenscreen. B. Greenscreen. We're
back to the game. B. Greenscreen. We're good. Chat here with B, also Greenscreen. And professor?
D. Fireman. D. An enthusiastic fireman. Who is Glooman? Would be the correct answer for this round.
No, that makes sense. It does make sense. I'm gonna get off this. That's actually, like,
dangerous. Maybe we go back to your real height. All right, last question here, folks. This is the
last question? It gave me the last question. All right, Jeremy. What do you want to go for?
All right, I'm gonna do Jerma's content for 1,200. Let's go. Jerma's content for 1,200.
Which of these choices is a real video title? The Binding of Isaac, episode 3. Here we go again.
Again. B. TF2. I promise I will heal you. Jerma and Star. More nonsense. C. TF2. Facecam uncrating
video. 50 crates madness. D. Peppa puke party. Caveman chug. Stream fun. Jerma, any strong
contenders here? I know D is real. It's a real video title. Yes, which of these choices is a
real video title? I wish all of them weren't. I'm gonna say B. B? Yeah, B. TF2. I promise I
will heal you. Yeah, I don't think I'd have that much bullshit in the title. Maybe I would.
We're looking for the real video title. Oh, okay, the real one. Yes. It's so confusing. There's so
many words. C. C. All right. Chat, what do you got? What is a real video title? Chat says B.
I promise I will heal you. Professor, any thoughts on the matter? C. That is a real title. All of
the above. All right. Okay. All right. Okay. So I suppose you would all get the points there.
Do we all get the points? What do we have? Right. What's our account right now? What do we have for
account? Total. 12, 4, 10, 4, 13, 11, 7. Doing well here, Chat. Crap. Well done. Oh crap. I have
a question. Yes. Can I go to the bathroom? Can you go to the bathroom? I mean, it's your show. You
can do whatever you want. Really, really badly. I mean, if you really have to. I mean, yeah. Do
you want to stop the stream? I mean, it is your show. No, no, no. Keep the stream going. I have
to go to the bathroom. Okay. All right. We will keep going with that. Stay strong. I hope you make
it. How many points do I have? Let's do a final count before he checks up. I have 11, 6. If they
change that, tell me, Chat, okay? There he goes. All right. 13,600. And Dr. Schmoyzen, what did you
have? I think, oh. 7,050. All right. Okay. So Chat, you're still in the lead here. All right. We
do have time for a couple more questions. Apologies for that before, folks. All right. So Dr. Schmoyzen,
would you like to pick? Certainly. I will take Goosebumps 400. All right. Sorry. Goosebumps for
400? That's right. In Welcome to Camp Nightmare, what was the name of the place in the camp where
nobody was allowed to answer? A. The Evil Chamber. B. The Ghost Room. C. The Forbidden Room. D. The
Forbidden Cabin. Are you that familiar with the Goosebumps books here? It's not exactly top of
my library. D. Forbidden Cabin. All right. So we have D. The Forbidden Cabin. Chat, what do you
got for us? All right. You've agreed with the professor D. The Forbidden Cabin. And our correct
answer would be? It is D. The Forbidden Cabin. Congratulations to all of you out there at home
and the professor. Wonderful. All right. So let's trade off here. Chat, we're going to let you pick
the next question. All right. So we got Goosebumps books, part two, for 1600. In The Abominable
Snowman of Pasadena, what allows Jordan and Nicole to escape the grasp of the snowman during their
first encounter? A. Loud construction work. B. A barking dog. C. A police siren. D. The cave
collapses. Professor, are you familiar with this specific work? No. Barking dog. All right. The
professor goes with B. A barking dog. Chat, could you help us out here? What do you got for us?
Chat agrees. B. A barking dog. All right. Let's see if we're all right here. The correct answer
is B. Congratulations to the both of you again. Well done. We're really racking up points here.
All right. Professor, we're going to let you go. Select a category. Select your points here.
Goosebumps, once again, for 800, please. All right. Let's go with Goosebumps for 800.
In The Haunted Mask, what does Carly Beth notice when she puts on the mask?
A. It doesn't fit. B. She looks taller. C. It changes her eyes. D. Her friend has the same one.
How embarrassing. She looks taller? All right. The professor's going to go with B. She looks taller.
Chat's going to go with C. It changes her eyes. All right. Well, let's see what happens in this
novel. It is C. It changes her eyes. Congratulations. All right. What points are we up to now?
16,400. Really crushing it out there, folks. Folks there at home. All right. Looks like you get to
choose the next question. We have Jerma's friends for 1200. Did Jerma kill Santa Claus? A. It was
self-defense. B. Jerma pleads insanity. C. No, he did not. And D. The magic can never die.
Professor, thoughts on this. Did Jerma kill Santa Claus? When's the last time you saw him?
Jerma pleads insanity. B. Jerma pleads insanity. Answer B. Chat, what are your thoughts on this
subject? All right. Also B. Jerma pleads insanity. All right. Let's see what our answer. What is
none of the above? Sorry, guys. This is one of our first rounds in a while. And it looks like
we're out of time. Thank you very much for joining us again here, professor. Let's get a final point
count. All right. We have Jerma currently in the bathroom with 11,600 points. Chat with 16,400.
Congratulations, guys. And the professor again with 9,050. We look forward to seeing you again
next time. I'm Shannon Cheryl. I will be on the next rumble. And we're going to go off and pass
this off to B.F. Bugleberry. I got something to tell you guys. No, no. Have we ever seen him again?
Have we ever seen him again? Who knows? Lord, I can't believe it. Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to my scary, horrible portion of the screen if you don't know. Because I am B.F. Bugleberry
V1. And seeing all the feedback, I've seen what people have been saying. Every single person says,
Bugleberry, we love you. We love your stories. We love the funny things. You do the funny things.
You say the interesting, horrible things. What would I love to see something do from you? I've
seen the response. And I have something very special for you today to do one of my other passions.
That's not just scary stories. It's something else entirely, endeavorish, something awful,
something that you will throw up in your mouth when you see the disgusting thing that you're going to
see today. We're going to do pottery. Pottery with Bugleberry will show you the techniques you do.
If you will get your materials out of class, I will show you horrible ends.
Well, the first thing you need to do is you have all of your materials.
You need clay. You can get it at a local clay store. Make sure it is pottery clay.
We're going to slap that right in the center of our pottery here.
So full of demonic energy. Oh, I can feel it. Do that too if you need somebody to do that for you.
If you need somebody to curse your clay, you're probably asked, what do you use these for?
Well, you see, I get my friends together and all of us, all of us get together and we make urns
for all kinds of purposes. And what I'm doing right now is centering the clay. That's right.
You need to get a little bit more water. The thing about clay molding is you need to feel yourself
get into it. Don't just put your hands on the clay. That's not how it works. Get into the clay.
Feel it, center mouse. We are making today an urn to keep up.
That's what we're doing. Now, when I put my hand up, you want to make sure all the wheels
to put your hands in as if you are driving a car at 10 and two. Very tightly around the clay.
We are doing this to create a center mass, like I said before.
It gets very hot, especially if you get your clay from the underworld. Once we have achieved
the circle in the center, we're going to move with this part of your hand. Use the bone.
Don't use this part alone. That's not the part you're supposed to use. You're supposed to use
the pinky all the way down to the breastbone. You're simply going to place it here and you're
going to put some pressure down to give yourself a nice center. Just even pressure down the middle.
Not too much. You should end up a nice flat top like that. I have a little bit of an issue on the
side. You don't have to go full throttle. That's my father used to tell me. He said,
Barry, you don't got to go full throttle. I'd say, fuck you, Barry. I never saw him again.
So as we center the clay on to continue to put pressure down into the middle just enough to
give us a nice urn shape reminds me of a story. We don't need that today. We're just making urns.
And as I continue, and my people, we need to get really close in here. Make sure your clay
always needs to be wet. Do not ever try to mold clay. There's a large presence
in this part of the moment. I can feel it. There's something in this room.
But as I try to, what is that?
Don't worry. I got it on my bottom, everybody. As we continue, I'm going to start creating.
I do this with my friends all the time. We always get together. We create. Creation is incredibly
important. As you see, we have a nice piece here, which I'm going to now put my two thumbs down,
do this at home. Two thumbs go in. Just let the clay do the work we're trying to do.
If you need to wet your hands again, absolutely do so. I'm not moving at all. The clay is doing
all the work. Simply going down deeper and deeper. Mind-destructing portion of the clay. You see here,
if you got some scraps, give yourself a bucket. It's hard to squeeze sometimes because I can feel
the presence at the beginning. That's okay. How beautiful that is. Your stories are cool, but
how beautiful that is. You should come back. I'm getting deeper down into this clay,
just letting it do the work for me. Do not move during this procedure. You could get seriously
injured. I mean seriously. You have to go to the doctor. Working all the way down. You see,
we have a little portion. Don't touch it, Robert. No shortcuts here. I want that. Let's go look at
that. That's a big one. That's a huge one. Can I zoom in on this? I'm sorry. Just seems appropriate.
And only use this for touching up your piece. I'm putting gentle pressure down.
We pay attention to this portion of the clay. I'm just letting it do what it needs to do,
smoothing out the center piece. It is delicious. There we are. Like I said, once every two weeks,
me and all of my friends, we get together and we do it to a point where all of us can present.
And it's not about winning. It's not about winning. Oh, I didn't win. No, who cares if you won?
It's about creating. And that's it. That looks pretty good. We have a nice little piece in the
middle. I can move that. Two fingers down the box. Storing whatever you want in here. Could be
cigarettes. Could be cigars. If you have cigarettes, you can go. And remember, it's about constant
pressure. It doesn't need to be perfect. I tried to put together something and it didn't
turn out perfectly. Death flows through into the urn. Now, as you see, finishing the urn requires
newt. Finished up choked. Finishing the urn requires newt inside the center. And that's
for display only. The lid is very difficult and you can't make the lid until this portion is
completed. It's like eggs. Weirdly enough, but it's something I enjoy. And don't tell me when
I'm doing this. You shouldn't be making these things. Do you know what day it is today?
No trouble. So as you see here, I have finally crafted an urn that is full of god scar started.
Make the lid. If you put your finger down, just press it. Don't push down here. You will
ruin the lid you created. I'm not moving. Edge is turned up a little, but that's okay because
it needs to be just elegant. And elegance can come from destruction. It can come from chaos.
This is the rising wave.
Stop, stop, stop. Did you hear it? Sounded like a spirit was flying through. If I could only
catch him. Oh, if I could catch that spirit, he would be in a bad spot. For the lid, I have
two pieces that I'll be making. One is the top and the other is the bottom. This is the bottom.
Me too. Hello. What's the matter? Hold on, he's bitten somebody? Did he actually bite somebody?
Okay, he's eating raw hamburger meat backstage. He doesn't get on the house very much. He doesn't
get up very much. His face is very, very, he's not. It's all right. It's okay. Is it a problem?
Do you need me to go get him? Is anybody injured? Okay, well, just put some hamburger meat on the
ground. I'll go get him. You just put it in a trail over to a hook. You know the traps if they're
making looney tunes? You know the stick that falls down? Okay. Ladies and gentlemen, ladies and
gentlemen, I have to be quite short because problems are a little difficult. 15 years, son of a bitch.
I will be back. You don't think you'll never see me again. You'll see me again.
Which one is this? Hello, how are you? I had a little. Hi, welcome back. We're currently set
up right now for the actual main event portion of the stream, which takes actually a little longer
than you would think, right? I'll explain what's going to happen here. I am currently for what I'm
going to do on the computer because we're trying to figure this out. Like, oh, what the hell are
you even going to do? We have a couple of things that I'm going to do for the actions. But if you're
just watching for the first time ever, right now, well, not right now, but when the round starts,
you know, over the last like three weeks, there has been at least three or four hundred actions
that the community has come up with to try to slime me on this broadcast. We have a couple of
angles as we see. And over the course of the next probably 40 to 50 minutes to an hour, we're going
to see if I do any of those actions. I do not know what any of these things are. I have no idea.
I have not been briefed. No one has told me, oh, Jeremy, oh, by the way, the action is say,
look at me. You know, that's like action number one. I have no idea. Hopefully that's not action
one because I just did it. But also at the same time, while I am doing this, you also are going
to be judged because there are actions that if you do them during these rounds without you knowing,
you will lose points. The points that we banked from over there, by the way, Bugleberry was $800.
Just want to make sure everyone's aware of that. It's the worst $800 I've ever spent.
And I absolutely will spend it again next year. So how this works again, each round we're going
to have a series of actions. When those actions happen, if I do one, I have kind of a death trap
up here that is going to slime me. If I do it during the round, you will be aware of those
actions. I will not. Who knows? We're going to keep score. If I get slimed, I lose points. If you
say a word that you're not supposed to say, you lose points too. And we're going to keep track of
them. You may even get banned too like that. That's probably not going to happen. So the game that
I'm going to be playing is plants versus zombies, because that was like the most easy thing to play
because it was like, oh, what are we going to play? Oh, I could play a horror game. I played them all.
I could play like a shooter game. I played them all. I could play a, I don't know. We've done
them all, right? So we've done them all. So I'm going to play plants versus zombies while we do
this. And when do we start? Oh, look at that. You can see it. That's coming at me. That's coming for
me. That is trying to kill me. Don't you understand? You thought this was all bullshit. You thought this
is a joke. No, we don't do jokes on this stream. We do real, real stuff. It's actually
kind of menacing and there is slime in there. Yes. So I have like a thing. Can we see plants
versus zombies? Oh, we're gripping game play. I'm going to play plants versus zombies. Oh,
look at that. It's a tutorial level. This is, this is great. We're recharging. Okay. So when
do we start around? Do we have any idea? Are we, are we going to get like started or should I just
play plants versus zombies for like two hours? How am I losing in the tutorial? Is that one of them?
That's not the first one, right? Make sure that's not the first one. I actually am losing.
So that we have the points should come up on screen. Do we have points? I can't even hear
this audio. So instead of secret slime action. Hey, I'm just like a weird guy in the lower
corner of your screen playing plants versus zombies. Oh, I got, I got a bomb that guy.
Imagine waiting for this stream. And it's just like, nah, nah, this is what we're going to do.
I'm just going to play play. That is what we're doing. Let's see how fast I can click it.
The real time killer. See if I can break the record. You know, I should just do that right now
while we fix the technical problems that are going on. Just click as fast as I can. I cannot
even, I actually can't even see chat. So I have no idea what they're saying. They could be saying
anything right now. Well, the guy in the Halloween costume. I'm not even in Halloween costume.
Oh shit. He's not out. Drop it on me. It's not the Halloween costume. So there are,
there actually are like 400 things. If I do them, then I'll be in a lot of trouble. We came back
to the break just because it was like, you know, just put me live. Do it.
I have like one of those secret service things. Actually losing in the tutorial. I know what you're
saying. And it's true. I actually just lost in the tutorial. I lost in the tutorial.
Well, shit. I'm going to try it again. Whoops. I was just, all right. You put the sunflowers down
and then when the sunflowers, okay, take the sunflower at 25. I remember, I know how this,
the whole back row is sunflowers. And then the next row is the pea shooters, right?
We got doctor, doctor, doctor. Dr. Sparks. Are you still in the house?
I think I need my blood pressure taken. So how are we doing? Are we, are we any closer?
Are we any closer to slime time? Or should I lose in the tutorial again? He's pretending to lose.
How many times can I win? I know I haven't played, this is actually a pretty good game.
The second one's stupid, but this one is actually really good.
Just dunk them, dunk them now. We're stalling. I might actually, this is what you do, right?
Works, works. Let me, let me just get a full row. Guy playing plans versus zombies.
That's why I baited you all. I baited you all here. We started with that trivia
round into like Bugleberry was here. Now, hey, settle back in the play. This is riveting.
The funny thing is, there's probably some of you here that are like,
now this is great. Just keep doing this. Let's do this for like another six hours.
All right, fine. Whatever. We will. Definitely not six hours.
So how are we looking? What'd you say? Secret service. What'd you say?
I've lost, I've lost communication. I've lost communication with the back team.
Wait, we're going? Wait, we're going now? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, hold on. We're going
right now. How long have they been there for? What? I thought I was still like, filling time.
Oh, now you freaked me the fuck out. Now I'm like, I'm scared. Wait, everything's ready.
What? I thought I was like, filling time still. Okay. So that means I'm armed. Uh, okay.
Okay. Let me put a back row. So let me first of all, my back is killing me. Let me just like,
my back is just absolutely killing me. You ever get like a tense back? I mean,
seriously, that's how you get like a bad back. That's how you get a bad back. You sit too long.
I was sitting for too long. That's my problem. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I gotta watch out
down here. So wait, I have actions too. I'm sitting there just like, well, who knows if we're
starting or not. I hope I don't lose. Oh, I gotta put the onion there. If I put the onion there,
I win. I'm sorry. It's a walnut. I know what it is. Oh shit. Wait, I got one lawn mower down.
The thing is, I'm trying, I don't touch any, I keep, what if I don't touch anything?
How long is the round? How much time do I have in round to like, worry about this?
That makes it even worse about knowing because I'm completely in the dark.
Again, let me just like, good shot of him. I almost just dropped it. I almost just dropped it.
Yes. Cherry Bomb. Best gameplay you're going to watch on Twitch of Plants vs. Zombies 1.
We can talk about a quick story about how Plants vs. Zombies 2 took this formula and then they
turned it into a pay to win game that really nobody cares about. It's where people come back
to this game and they talk about how this is like, oh, what a fantastic, awesome game this is.
And the second one is just, I don't think anybody's ever played it. Only like,
I'm just moving. What did I do? Did I, what did I do? It started to, all right, this thing started
to move. So I'm going to stop talking about that. I heard like, I don't know what to say.
When you, when you have like nothing you're allowed to say, you have no words to say.
I could, I could just like say, I don't know. I don't know. I'm scared. You guys, okay.
You just have, oh, there are points. There are the points. I can see them. You guys have,
where'd you guys have 16,000 points from? Oh, from the trivia. Right. That's right.
This game is like, oh, this game is good. I'm trying to think of something. Imagine one of
the actions is play Plants vs. Zombies 1. No, touching the nose is, it might be one of them.
I ain't going to do it. A huge wave is approaching, but from what direction? East? West?
I, how do you get more? No, I have to actually set this up, don't I? I got to be careful because
every time I get, if I get slimed and I lose like, how many points do I lose if I get slimed?
500. That's not good. Well, it's probably not going to happen. So that's fine.
I'll just be quiet the whole time and just actually play this game.
That's what we're doing. I have a lot of money. When is the round end?
Oh, click to remove it. Wow. This is, I love Plants vs. Zombies. Now we're going bowling.
I should, I should just like dance on camera. Just dance in action. Oh, it's been to the left.
Right, right, right. Oh, it's bowling. Okay. I would laugh my ass off if this just didn't happen
one time. If this doesn't happen once, I will fucking laugh. Hey, we set all this up and it died.
Nope, not going to happen. This is the big explosion one, right? Oh, by the way,
I got some cool clothes on.
How was your guys Halloween? How was your guys day? Did you guys have a good day? My day was great.
I did, uh, well I did all this. I set all this up and it was really good.
Do you remember, you guys remember when conventions, when people would wear these
to conventions, it was a huge thing. Why would they not make Plants vs. Zombies 3?
Everybody loves this franchise. This is gonna make a mobile game and that's it. Make it free.
Make it a real game. Oh, with ricochets, right. You gotta try to get free. There we are.
Why did I just do that? That was stupid. I gotta hit this guy.
Yes. All right, final wave.
Everybody has this. I remember being at PAX East in like 2012 and they would just be cones.
I'm going to win this. I'm definitely going to win.
All right, if it's not like, oh, touch your nose, touch your face. Look out. Whoa,
what happened to you? Oh, watch it. Watch his bum. Watch out for his bum. I am safe,
I think, this whole round. There's like, yeah, no, call this round. I'm not, it's over. I win.
They didn't get shit. Hey, what was, what was your word by the way?
Their word was diaper. Your word was diaper. How did you do?
You. Minus 800, 840 of you said the word diaper. That means you lose. That means you lose 800
points because one person's worth one point. Nothing happened to me. I'm fine right now.
It was probably something really specific. It was probably like,
talk about Jemercraft. Actually, I probably shouldn't say that word.
So we're officially on the second round in five seconds. We've got the next round, the next round.
I, I thought it was going to be way more than 800. That means I actually cannot get son. How
many people are here? How many people are watching the stream right now? All right. So out of 7,400
people, only 800 of you, I'm wearing a fucking diaper on screen. How did you hope you could
contain that? You could contain yourselves during that? I don't know how that's possible.
Wait, is the word still banned in the chat? No, it's not. Okay. Thank God I unbanned it.
I thought it was still banned. It was banned like two months ago. So we're on round two, right?
So this is new actions, right? Not the old ones or are you compounding them?
All right. So, all right, put my hands down. I'm going to put my hands down.
That means you guys have a new thing too. Watch what you say for the next little bit.
Be careful. Something about like something about my hair is just fucking bothering me.
Something about it. I don't know what it is.
Maybe it has to do with the fact that they're right. What are you doing? What did I do? What did I do?
What did I do? What did I do? What did I do? What did I do? What did I do? What did I do? What?
What did I do? What? What did I do? What was the action? I touched my hair.
I touched my hair twice was the action. Well, how many fucking people said that I had? Oh,
for the love of God. Did I just, how many points? 500 points? How am I going to play?
We didn't think this through. We didn't think this through. How am I going to play?
I can't play the game. I can't do anything. My fucking hand cannot come back down here.
Touch your hair twice. Oh, for the love of God. This stuff stinks.
This smells so bad. Does that end? Can we go to the next round? Oh, we keep going.
I need to play with my left hand. Thank you. I just got a towel.
This is my eye. This stuff, this smells like baby puke. I don't know why I know that. It
just smells like baby puke. Am I losing it in the game? I'm not even paying attention.
All right. I need to, okay. We're good. The thing is I heard, I heard like the crank
and that's when I was like, what the fuck happened? What's the score? 11, what is it? 11 what?
1100. Okay. I didn't lose it. I won actually. That's good. The thing, this is going to be
horrible. Honestly, I'm not kidding around after one. Cool. Let's not ever do that again,
because now like I feel like shit. Let me fill this back up. Oh, we're still on that same round?
Good thing I'm wearing a diaper. All right. I got the, I got the ice snow pea. So Jesus Christ.
Oh, don't touch my face, right? Oh, touch my hair. Should I not touch anything? But what if I have
to rub my face? Cause there's slime in my eyes. All right. How does it look? This shit's not even,
this is not even orange. It's like fucking, it's like, it's like white. It's supposed to be orange,
but I don't think it doesn't. Is it because of the light? It looks like it's like pale.
It should have been a green. That would have been better.
I need like, it's like, it's hardening in my like ear canal. Hey, welcome to the,
hey, welcome everybody to the stream. I gotta, I, all right. What do you, I, what do they have?
Okay. Can you pump it to me what they have for action? So this round is over. The word was
bald, by the way, but apparently in doing so, I had to touch my head twice, which is technically
my hair, but it's not really my hair. So that's a technicality. I don't believe that that should
be allowed. Do you guys have a timer up? Just going by, you know what? I can see the chat.
Why is everybody saying he said orange? What do you mean? He, what are you talking about?
He just said it. Orange is, orange is one of the words.
Somebody just shit in my pants. Somebody shit my pants. I didn't do it, but somebody else very
clearly did. Holy shit. The word was orange. I talked about how this didn't look orange.
Can we, can we like watch a movie or something? Because I can't even, I can't even touch the
screen. I can't touch anything. Are we on a new round? I just got an achievement. Watch rat movie.
No, that's probably an action. Actually, it's going to happen with playing Plants
vs. Zombies because like there's no way I could have done anything else. Oh dude, what the fuck?
You should be playing like Soma. Yeah. Should I? I'm sticking to the ground. Jesus.
Your hair looks dumb. Wait, I didn't do anything. Are we on a new round? We're on a new round,
right? I just like burped really loudly and hopefully that's not something.
What am I doing? I gotta, I gotta get rid of this guy. It's hard to even grab.
Oh, you guys don't understand. I don't have a mouse pad. It's slime here. Slime is my mouse pad.
I think like, really? How am I going to do this? Wait, wait, wait, wait. No, no, no, no. I can't
lose. I can't lose. I can't lose. I can't lose. I can't lose. I can't lose. Don't lose. Don't lose.
Please don't lose. I'm going to lose. Look, you don't have to deal with somebody getting slimed.
I do. I have to deal with somebody sliming my ass. It's actually in like the back of my underwear
and every time I get up and get down, it's like, it's the worst feeling ever. What's,
what are we slated to do here? Like an hour and a half. Uh, just kidding. More like 25 minutes.
See you guys next time. Cut his mic. If I lean over good enough, I can see. All right. So
here we go. New round, new time. Let's do it. I have to at least win one round.
Did they, how many? Okay. So it's 10. What is it? 10? What is it? I can't see it from there.
10 what? We're, we're, we're in a new round, right? Am I on actually new actions right now?
People are spamming show the actions, show actions. I don't even know what they are.
Oh, new actions are going up now. I think I'm just playing, playing for zombies.
I think. Well, show actions, show actions, show actions. There we go.
Do they, we haven't, are they up? Okay.
Spitters. Hey, mine. How long does the arm take to mine? 20 seconds. 25. This is so unnerving
because I just hear like production people like going like this. I hear them like
they're like moving around back there. All that happens is you guys lose points. What happens to
me is somebody goes to the bathroom in the back of my underwear as it happens to me.
I'd rather have it hit me in the face. Seriously. I have to win this. I'm starting to harden.
All right. I need to take care of this guy. Okay. Look at how covered I am in shit. I am from like
up to down. Let's get you a towel. Let's get you a towel. This is like a face cloth.
Don't lose again. The gameplay is what matters on this stream. Nothing else matters. Only the
video game is being shown. What's going on? What's wrong with the computer? Just blue screen. Wait.
Oh, wait. The computer blue screen. What? Oh shit. That's an action. That's an action for the
computer. Oh, God damn it. Oh, what the fuck? Oh, I was like, what's going on here? It's like
smoking. The computer is smoking from the back. It's smoking. How many points does the computer
lose? How many points did the computer have? Is it all right? Somebody reboot it. Can you reboot
it? If you hit control, I'll delete on it. See if it works. Let's see. No, I'm not getting anything
from this PC. Should I blow on it? Damn. Okay. What do we do? Okay. Because that's actually like
this thing's dead. I'll have my iPad. Do you want to bring up my iPad? Okay. I'll get my iPad.
We can play something on the iPad for a while. I'm Jerma and now we're going to play iPad games
because that's what we have. Yeah, it's not just you and me. It's the computer as well as involved
in this. This is actually caking. It's an iPad stream. This it is. You didn't think we were going
to come back to this, but we always do. So where do we stand on points? I am currently losing
because I went to the bathroom during the trivia. I had a long piss. It was about four minutes.
But we have right here in our hands Halloween themed horror games. And we are going to start
with one called Spirit Oracle Board. If you don't have TikTok, now's the time to get it.
There are ads on this. I'm going to do it. The scary stories. I'm not going to click that. It's
going to open up like a webpage. All right. Start the seance. Okay. We got a full page TikTok ad.
Okay. Instructions. Can we get some ambience in here? If possible, darken the room. You are in
and light some candles before starting a seance. Place your finger on the planchette.
Is that the term? The wooden piece in order to initiate the spiritual connection to the other
side. Ask the spirit your question loud and clear. Always start a seance with a question,
is anyone there? Wait for the spirit. This is a lot of, this is a huge amount of questions.
This is a huge amount of instructions here, not questions. Wait for the spirit to respond. The
planchette will start moving. Okay. Always be polite and ask normal questions. This is a way
to make it so kids don't say anything bad. Right? Don't say anything mean. Don't say fuck. Be careful
not to upset any spirit. A couple running around here today actually. In case you have anger to
spirit, quickly move the planchette to goodbye before the countdown is over or unexplained
things might happen. Sure. Speech recognition required. Do we actually have to do this? Do I
have to do, do I have to allow speech recognition? I don't want this like, you talk, you can always
change this later. Okay. So I allow access, right? Are we good? Spirit would like to access speech
recognition. Okay. Why does it need to know all this stuff? Listen to your microphone. Okay.
Turbo seance. Unlock these special features. Turbo seance. Messages will, no, no, thank you.
I don't think I need to do the turbo seance. Place fingers on the planchette to start.
Do we have any scary music going here? We do? Okay. Place finger on planchette to start. You've
got it? Ask. I don't know what to ask. Do you, are there any spirits here? Are there any spirits here?
Are there any spirits here? Are, are there any spirits here? Oh shit. You're going to see me
doing this. This thing sucks. What? Hello. Let's try it again. Warning. Seance in progress. If
you've made contact with a spirit, you should end the seance by moving to the goodbye. Exit. I love
how you, I love how you cut that. I saw you go, but look, no, no, no. Come back. Come back.
They're doing it. They're doing it. Look, that's like G. Oh no. So you got the bomb. Oh shoot.
Oh shit. What monster is this going to summon? Oh, the rainbow. That means you got five.
Give me a fucking, no, I don't know. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. I don't want to,
I'm going to try this one more time and then move on to the next fucking iPad game. No, thanks.
Place. Okay. Are you here? This thing even, does this even do anything? Do we know if this even do
anything? I don't think this does anything. This is fucking stupid. All right. I'm going to hit the
button and we're going to do another one because, okay, I'm going to hit the button. That's the end
of the round for chat. The word, what? The word was turbo. How many points did they lose? Holy shit.
That's some next level baiting if I've ever seen it. All right. Do I want you to show? Okay.
This is granny two is this one. This is granny chapter two. So do I have new actions?
I didn't do anything, right? We're going to keep the same one. All right. We're going to do normal.
Granny play as options. That's fine. Normal quality. Granny and grandpa move at normal speed.
That's fine. Be quiet. Granny hears everything. Grandpa doesn't hear very well, but he hits hard.
Press and hold the remove button to free yourself from bear traps.
Hiding under beds or in wardrobes. You have five days. It's a long time. Use headphones.
My best experience. I don't, I can't do that. So how many actions do we have for chat right now?
Do I, is it, is it, is it like a gyro? Oh wow. This is so scary. What's the goal here?
Do I just have to stay away from granny? Why are there spikes in this? Wait, if I go in here,
is this going to kill me? Is this an iron maiden? Oh, you can crouch too. All right. So what do I
do? This is granny chapter two, by the way. If you don't know, this is the number one downloaded
game on the whole app store. I don't know why granny is just number one on the, it's just,
there's like 700,000 reviews for this game as well. Wait a minute. Can I open this? I just spit on
this, but I've had slime up my nose for the last like 40 minutes. So does it really matter?
Oh, I spit it. Where the hell am I? What? Is the slime yummy? Is that what you're asking?
Uh, not particularly. It just, it's, it just smells like, like baby formula. Is it actually
edible? I think it is, right? No. I, what'd I just do that for? No, I can't touch this.
Is the slime yummy? Is that a trick question? It might be. So now I know. Don't put the slime
in your mouth. That's one of the, I know one of the actions now. I got a man on the inside.
The shower tonight that I take is going to be the best shower I've taken in my whole life. All
right. What am I supposed to do? No, I haven't gotten any in the mouth because it went back.
I've only been slimed twice. I've been slimed two times. I think I'm good. And one of them was
bullshit because I had to point to my head twice. So I need a key in granny's house. Oh, this game.
Wait, I can't see. Can I talk shit about like the most popular game in the app store?
I probably can't, right? Like, can I say like granny sucks? I can't. That, that there's like
800,000 people that disagree with me. So I'm wrong, right? I don't even know where I'm supposed to be
going. Back upstairs? And what did, what killed me the first time? Can I turn the brightness up on
the iPad? All right. I, I, I'm going to put, I'm going to turn the brightness up. It's pretty low.
I can't see that. All right. Now I can see it was so, it was really low. Now I can see. All right.
We're good. Now I think it was so dark. All right. I'm upstairs. Okay. There's there. I am assuming
that was granny. There was just people in granny's house. What does he know? Like how do I peel?
How do you feel? How do you feel? It looks like, Oh, I'm going to peel. Sure. No, don't click the
ad. Don't click the ad. Don't click the ad. All right. Well, it's time for me to peel, I guess.
Let's go choose my peeler. I think that's a good one up here. Nope. Nope. No, no, no, no, no.
I'm not going to do that. I'm stuck to the ground. When I stand up, we're carving a pumpkin soon.
Oh, that might be a slippery action. That may be, don't say it. He's doing a pumpkin carving.
No, I can't, but we're doing a pumpkin carving after that, after this. So there's more to see.
I, I think I'm done playing granny. So I am going to move on to the next one because granny is pretty,
it's just, it's just granny and the other person in the house and they attack you.
Okay. Good old iPad horror games that I don't know how to accomplish anything in them.
I also don't have audio, so that's another thing you guys maybe not, maybe might not know.
You guys might not know that. I guess I can sneak. I'll try one more time.
Well, that's the death room. I probably have like, hold on, let me fix my nerd neck.
I don't want to have like nerd neck, but how do you, okay. I'm dead again. All right. So granny is
a fun game and she's a wonderful, wonderful person. This five, should I just do all five days? I'm
going to go to the next game because this is just stupid. All right. Round over or are we still
going to stay with whatever we have here? Keep it up for a little bit on here. Oh, cause this,
cause this game sucks. All right. New game. Uh, how about, how about scary butcher 3d,
new actions, new game. All right. How about scary butcher 3d? That one looks pretty good play.
Chad says that you violated one.
What do you mean I violated one? What do you mean I, what do you mean I violated one?
People saying rigged. What do you, what do you mean cheated rigged? What are you talking about?
What? Well, you can't just like retroactively add a slime because you, we didn't do it. I just like
backed up. I was like, okay, I guess I'll put that. So what, what do you mean hand motions?
So what? Okay. All right. Well, I, I'm just going to say, I have to, okay, I have an idea.
I have to keep my fucking hands down. So in the small town of Erie, they lived a butcher
bee with his wife. One stormy night, Elena got, I'm stuck to the back of the chair. I'm stuck to the
back of the chair. Can you see this? I'm at, I'm actually stuck to the back of the chair. Who cares
about the butcher's life? Since then, he cooks all kinds of sausages. Who gives a shit about
the butcher? I'm stuck to the chair. Since then, his pets keep vanishing all around. I can hear it
being refilled and it's seriously causing me a lot of anxiety. Since then, the pets keep vanishing
all around town. Some believe it's the butcher who captures and eats the pets. This guy's fucking
crazy. Okay. You know, when you watch a cartoon and there's always that like weird part of the
cartoon where, or no, you know, I'll put it this way. Um, men in black, right? I got, and like in
every men in black movie, I've been eaten by the alien and then spit out, you know, like,
what the fuck? I'm the guy that got eaten and spit out by the alien. I think I'm doing pretty
well. Okay. I'm the person that gets regurgitated. Okay. Let's continue. Your cat fuzzball went
missing yesterday. Could be captured by bee. The butcher's hill is heavily protected by alarms.
So you have to be careful. This person stole my cat. Press button to throw the stone. Hold follow
arrows to reach destination. When we throw the stone, why did I do that? What was the point of
that? Keep your fucking hands down here. No, no, like download now promotion. Well done. Level
completed. Walked in a straight line. It was a close call and I'm still going to compute. Okay.
It's good that you managed to hide or you could be his next victim. Breaking to beat. Then that
game look fun. Right. Cool. No, don't watch the whole ad. I can't even click the X. Okay.
Stop opening the fucking app store. Okay. Breaking to be shed and steal his night vision goggles.
Use this button to toggle display. That's him in the corner. Can he not see me? Oh, there he is.
Look out. Oh no. He got you. And he just goes like, he just like dances. Oops. Butcher caught you
red handed restart. Here's that shooter game. You know, I can't, this is that shooter game for you
kids. I can't hit the X. We just have to let it play out. Oh no, no, no. It's like opening,
like to actually opening the app store. We have to move on. All right. We're going to do
horror clones. Are we on a new round? Same round. New round. Okay. Uh, the iPad is upside down
because the game crashed. So we're going to pick a different one. How about evil nun? Evil nun? Uh,
evil nun might also be broken too. Evil nun doesn't work. How about, uh, Emily? How about Emily? Do
you work, Emily? We'll find out. Emily wants to play a new game. Holy shit, it actually works.
And what are we going to get into the ad? Oh, of course we are. Here it comes. No, this is actually
has a cut scene. Oof. Uh, did you see that? This is, I have, okay, this has been fucking stupid.
The iPad segment was a bust. Interact. Although I still have, what was chat's word? What does chat
have for a word last time? Ass. Okay. Well, sorry to hear that you guys lost so many points.
Why was it ass? Ooh, hold on. What's on the computer? What's on the computer? Let's get a zoom in.
Thanks for what? Thanks for ordering. I don't know what I ordered. Thanks a lot. Okay. Uh,
can I go on? Oh, that's a hint. Wait, I can just turn the lights off in the whole house?
Oh, let's play at midnight says one guy. Sure. I'll try. All right. This game sucks too. I'm going
to just carve the pumpkin. This game sucks. No, it doesn't. That's not fair. That's not fair.
That's not fair. Let me give it like another 30 seconds. Look, tap center to interact with objects.
This game actually is for an iPad game is pretty good. Let me turn the lights back on. Hold on.
Can I leave the house? The slime has caked underneath my head. I want to so badly take
this off, but I can't because if it happens again, then it, this is real life. I want you to get this
like, look at this. This is, it's like glued to my forehead. If I take this off and I get slimed
again, I will be very upset. I ain't taking the bald cap off. Does anybody know anything about
these games? I just heard dump it. And why are we dumping it? I'm not going to, don't look up into
it. What do you mean? I'm going to get in my eyes. Close your eyes. Holy shit. This is disgusting.
You put extra in this one. Okay. Oh my God. That's, that is, this is vile. I'm trying to be,
I'm trying to be normal about this. It smells, it smells like acid. What smells like, but
over exaggerated detail. That's not, that's a real life. That's an over-exaggerating.
No, there's no glue in this. It's just eco-friendly slime. Oh my God. I just saw.
Hey, remember I met in black when the guy gets like fucking puked up. The guy pukes and he's like,
it's me. What's that? Don't do it. Move. Mom, if you're watching, I'm sorry. I'm sorry, mom.
I really don't mean to be like this. I have to take this off. Where's the pumpkin? I still have
the diaper on. Nice watch. Hi, welcome back. Welcome. Right now, we're going to do a thing.
We're going to do a thing where I carve a pumpkin. By the way, the diaper has to stay on
because if the diaper comes off, the pants do too, because they're way down to a point where I,
I have to keep them on. Let me get rid. I have like, okay, this is, I'm making it worse.
So as you see here, we have a regular size pumpkin. I'm going to draw a stencil on him.
I look really bad. Really bad. In fact, like, so as we see here, I've, I don't, I don't know shit
about carving pumpkin. I'm realizing this right now. Oh, what do we want to do to like do the,
what's, how do you want to end this, this like show? I'll carve a pumpkin. Okay. I don't know
how the fuck to do that. So where, what are you doing? What are you doing? What'd I do?
I swear, did I say the word pumpkin? The word pumpkin. You're going to set me up with a segment
where I get a pumpkin and I say the word pumpkin and that's a problem. So that's not fair.
How's that fair? Okay. I can't just, the pumpkin is gone. I can say the word pumpkin now. Okay.
So I'm going to draw a stencil here. Can you see that? That's my stencil. Okay.
Okay. There are knives of now around. There are knives. I'm going to move the knives over here
because these are knives. Okay. So, you know, why don't I just punch it? Okay. You guys have no
fuck. This is like a challenge on a game show, which is pretty much what this is.
I'm going to have to get up with my hands because there's fucking slime everywhere here.
So why would you give somebody a knife when they're standing on ice? This is a challenge.
I can't get in with my nails. Okay. That's unsafe. It's unsafe. All right. We got a vacuum.
That's not, that's not a risk. Okay. The word is not vacuum. I just don't want to be harmed on
spring. That's not the word. Is it the word? No, it's actually not vacuum. That's too bad.
Oh, that's better. That's better. Okay. Anybody want a pumpkin? It's not that I've never carved
a pumpkin. I just don't want to. Hold on. All right. Here's what we're going to do. I'm going to make
let's go like this. Wait a minute. The hammer, the hammer with the hammer. Where's the hammer?
The hammer with the like, literally nobody on production knows what I'm trying to say.
The hammer with the little nails that light up. The chisel. I can do that.
Scary. All right. That this works. No, I don't have to worry about it. I'm going to make a,
I'm going to make a face. Is it a real pumpkin? What do you mean is this a real pumpkin?
Like this is a real pumpkin. Look at the stem. I can see. Oh, I just have to squint real hard,
but I can see what you said. This frame's pre-recorded. Oh, is it? Would it be
pre-recorded if I went like this? It's a fake stream. Just wait a minute. Let me just get this
because I know what your, I know what your, where's the, there it is. Oh, let me go.
Doctor, how am I doing? Oh, I'm doing just fine. All right. That works.
I'm going to hit my fucking hand with this. That, okay. We're getting there. I can't even
pick it up. Okay. What about, hold on like this. I am making something. The face I'm going to make
is going to be a very special guest. You might find this thing at the circus. You might find
this thing at a birthday party. Ow. I need like red. I need like purple. We actually had one of
these on stream. Uh, actually two of them. So that was red. I can't even get in there. Okay.
That looks fucking terrible. It looks like somebody just put three pegs into a pumpkin.
We're getting there. Great. I can't, I've done this first. You got to get it in like, there we go.
You know, don't even, why am I even hitting it like this? Just press it in. I'm using it like
it's an actual mallet. This thing weighs like four, like maybe four ounces. My pants aren't
falling down, right? Okay. That's just the diaper. I thought that was my underwear. I actually thought
that was my actual underwear. This is Jeremy gets hurt on stream. Don't try this at home. It
ain't going in there. It's going to have to go somewhere else. We should have just had somebody
make one. We should have had somebody make one of these. Hey, can somebody carve a cool pumpkin?
I'm not, I'm, I just, I'm not going to do that. Let's do it with my hands. It's way easier.
Fuck off. Can these be eyes? No, there's no red. Guys, I'm having trouble. What's that thing?
You have no idea how to do this? No, I do. It's, it's with knife. It's with knives.
And I'm, I am no, I, I am slippery. I am that's like my superpower right now. You want the slippery
guy to hold the knife? What? That actually felt pretty good. Hold up more than three fingers.
Have I, how have I not done that before? He's not reacting. Don't, he's bad. React. React harder.
React harder. Halloween. No, I, oh, for saying clown, you guys lose points. That's the end of
the round. You said clown. He didn't react. No, cause at some point it just becomes like numb.
You know what I mean? At some point, like I, it's happened so many times. It's like, okay,
I guess it's happening again. You guys said clown. What the fuck am I even doing this? What? This is
like a, okay, this is like a map to where you've been. You know, you have this shit in like your
living room to make like your friends jealous. Oh, I've been to Canada. I've been to Toronto.
And then I, I've been over here, up here into the great lakes down here. Oh yeah. I love Oklahoma.
Are you doing it again? Oh, I was like, what the fuck? Um, how do I get in this? Can this be taken
off? This is like bad, right? Can I like pull this off? Audio and video are now out of sync,
apparently. Why, why is that? He doesn't know. He didn't react. What? I mean, how does he not know?
What are you talking about? What? What did I not do? We have to get their points down by the way.
I, I, okay. Lightning round put up 15 actions for me and like 10 actions for chat. Don't tell him.
Hollow out the pumpkin. We didn't do that beforehand. Oh, we ran out of time. I don't
know. I seriously might as well just like go like this action. You can fuck off. Oh, look at me.
Get it all out of the way before anybody has any actions. There's no battery in here.
Oh, can I just draw on it? What's our, what's it? Feed it into my ear. What's our actions?
Hold on. I can't, I used to have to go to my diaper. Hold on. What is it? Say it softly. I will,
I will win this if you give it to me. Give me their actions. Okay. Guys are fucked. Although I have,
how many do I have? I'll have eight. Okay. Um, that's solidified enough where I can,
no, I can, I'm not going to do that. I'm not going, okay. I, people might go, oh, come on.
You're not going to carve the pumpkin. I'm not going to be the guy on Twitch that has the knife
in his hand and is like, not going to happen. It's, I'm not doing that. Does that violate TOS?
Oh, I, oh yeah. Violates my life. It went right down my ass crack right now. Just went in,
it went all the way. It didn't, it's, it's just right now for the first time. The diaper has been
breached. Uh, so I'm going to draw on this. We'll spin it around. I'm serious. Just spray me with
the hose back. Like I was back. This is not, this is not a joke. This is actual, like spray me all
of my whole body with the hose. So this is, this marker is dead. We're just going to look at the
pumpkin. Might as well just play like funny videos. Might as well. Oh, I have new actions?
Okay. Chat sees them. Can the pumpkin have, we did the computer. Can we have the pumpkin actions?
What do I have to do here? Get off of that. We're almost at the end of the show. If you guys are
curious. Should I try running again? This is a treadmill. Ready? Remember that? How's my
nerd neck? All right. Move the knives. Ready? Don't run this way. Run this way. But then what
if I like, all right, this is, this looks fucking bad. I look like I'm like soaking my, oh darling,
please help me. All right. Not bad. I can get it one more time. That was a false ride. That was a
false ride. I think I got some on the camera. This is what we like to call, this boy is out of material
and he can't get into the pumpkin. So he's been, he's at the point where he's got nothing left
to do. Dropping him. No, I'm not going to drop it. This thing weighs like 200 pounds. What if I just
like shot foot it over at production? Drop it. I'm not going to smash this. You know, that's
bullshit. Just do Gallagher. This is Gallagher. You're watching Gallagher right now. Let me tell
you something. What? What? Funny voice. Hey, so what we do here now that a funny voice is done,
we just do funny voices for the rest of the stream. This is not a good diaper. It's actually
pretty good. And by the way, it's over the top half of, it's, it's over of my clothes. Put the
diaper on the pumpkin. Give me a diaper. This is like 20 in that case. Do a back flip. I might
need three. Should I just wear them? Should I just put these on? Okay, let's test it. Dump it. Oh,
he did a thing. He did something fucking weird. Into the diaper. Let's test the diaper. Dump it.
Let's see how good these are. You guys talked a lot of shit. Nothing got through at the bottom.
Look at that. Pretty good actually. This is what I'm doing right now. We're testing diapers. That
means I'm out of content. I just, like that image is now forever on, on camera.
Is dumping slime into a, into a diaper to test it. Shit. Put it on the pumpkin.
Okay. I'll take that. That's a bad idea. Why, why is that bad?
Diapers are going to protect me. This thing can hold like five gallons. That's bad advice.
It's kind of good advice. That's disgusting. It just, can we get the vac back here, please?
That was nothing in there. I don't like that sound. Can I see that for a sec? You'll see it
for just a sec. Up here. If you could. There you go. Thank you. Thanks a lot. It's like up my nose.
There's no point for this to even be here anymore. There's no reason for this pumpkin.
We can wash this pumpkin off. All right. I'm going to try to get into the pumpkin.
Very gently. I just want to get in. Carve it. What is all over this? I thought that was blood.
I was like, what the fuck is that? Behind you? Yeah, I know.
I can hear them. No, not the top rope. We're going to get like frog splashed. Okay. I just
got to get in. If I can get in and we can see what's in there. It's like a science experiment.
I'm being extraordinarily careful. The most careful I've ever been in my whole life is right
now. All right. I'm almost in. Okay. I'm in. Okay. I'm in. This is bait. It's not bait.
You know, when you do some things and you go, you know what? I probably should just like go
to church tomorrow. That's like, that's kind of what's in my mind at the moment. Like I don't,
I didn't do anything wrong, but I really just feel like I should go to church.
I can't get in here. This pumpkin is thick. What we got for a time? We got another five minutes.
You want to putt his chat? Okay. What was the words for chat?
Ooh, woo. Comcast. Wait, the word was streamer. Omega lull. Wow. And P. How many points did they
lose? 1700, which puts them way ahead of me still. P. Streamer P. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
When we thought about this, like two or three weeks ago, it was, it was a great idea.
I don't know if you guys heard that, but the people at production said nobody said that.
Oh, but we got like, I like this. I actually like this costume. Be this for Halloween next year,
except don't put the diaper on. People will think you're something's wrong. You know,
if you have like a diaper on over your clothes, actually Doug does that.
All right. Uh, we, we should probably close it out here. Maybe one more round and that's it.
Put the rest of the actions on the screen. Yeah. Put every action at the rest of every single action
that's available on the screen for me right now. Okay. I am going to literally just stare into the
camera. What am I going to do with pumpkin? Um, I don't know, wipe it down and, and clean it and
give it to my mother. No, I'm not going to throw the pumpkin. Like what is going on here?
Oh, it's like dirt. Oh, it's actually really dirty. I wait, I, you guys have time. Okay.
How are you guys doing tonight? You guys having a good Halloween? Did you have a good Halloween?
There's new actions on screen. Okay. How many? A lot. There are more than two dozen. Okay.
A pose. That's not, let's try to get the whole hat orange. I feel like I'm like that first grade.
I'm just like, Oh, this is fun. Oh, that looks really good. What you're doing there. Oh,
Johnny, that's really nice. Yes, it is. Oh, wow. What is it? What'd you make up? What is it? What
is that a pic? What is that? What is that of? Oh, it's a face. It looks fan. It looks so good.
Wow. I can't wait to tell you mother about it. Thank you. Like what the fuck am I doing? I'm
just standing here rubbing a pumpkin. I've been rubbing a pumpkin. This is the stream content
you've received in the last like 30, 40 minutes is rubbing a pumpkin with oil. Is it, it's what
is chat's fault. That's true. You guys did come up with these actions. They're pretty good.
All right. So how I've only done one in like two dozen actions. Really? Okay. Wait, that actually
might be an action. I'm not going to, I'm going to do something. Okay. I have to decide. I have to
continuously move, but not do anything. This thing is heavy enough where I can hold.
I'm like fucking Jim Carrey from dumb and dumber. Jim Carrey with the suit on.
I'm not losing points for this. Am I? I should be. What about chat? Does chat have a thousand
things to do? It's a shitty Freddy Krueger. This is Freddy. It's Splatoon Freddy Krueger.
Oh, oh, oh. I would be right now. Right now. I would be, I would be gagging right now. I would
be going, but I'm not going to freak out. I'm going to be everyone. I'm going to use a diaper.
Okay. Because that was horrible. You know, when something hits you on the lip and it's something
that you really don't want to have in your mouth, that just happened. And I almost had that immediate
reaction. It was immediate, but I slowed down and I wiped it off with a diaper. So thanks for watching
everybody. Really appreciate everybody coming out and hanging out here. That was a lot of fun. Hey,
how about that? Dr. Schmikeson comes and says, hello. That was a treat. Glad to have Dr. Schmikeson
back. Did pretty good. Trevi was fun. We got Bugleberry. That was fun. But I like, seriously,
this is getting like to a point where it's too gross. So I like, do I have something I can like
spit into? Do I have something I can spit into? I know that sounds disgusting, but it's been like
in the back of my throat for like at least 20 minutes and I need to spit. Do we have anything
to spit? We do. Okay. Where is it? I need like a cup or a glass or something. Not on
the, no, no, no, no, not on the floor. There's something over here. I can spit it. Doesn't matter.
Oh, oh, holy. Whoa. Oh, that's, oh, what the fuck was in here?
What the fuck is going on? Hey, no, no, no, no, no.