Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with my Pax Prime thoughts slash wrap-up slash I'm home slash.
There's a lot of slashes, but I'm at my house now. Pax Prime 2012 is officially over, and I've been asleep all day.
Right now it is 10 p.m. Eastern time on Monday. My plane arrived on today, on Monday. God, it's such a blur.
I woke up at 7 in the morning, and I went to sleep right when I got home. It's like 8 or 9 p.m.
So this whole day has been a blur, and I'm looking at the screen right now. This shirt is on backwards.
This shirt has been on backwards this whole day. Oh my God. Well, you know what? Hey, sometimes you do things that you don't mean to, and that's one of those things.
But anyways, I want to give a huge shout out to all the guys that I met at Pax Prime. All the guys, all the YouTubers, all the fans, everybody.
It was such a great experience, guys. And if you have never been to a Pax, you gotta get to one.
And even at any gaming convention, whether it be Quake, Con, Pax, they're all just so much fun. You meet so many cool people there.
And I wanted to kind of transition that into this little compilation of clips I have here. It's about maybe four or five minutes long.
Just a goofiness in the hotel rooms, of us just hanging out, going to different booths, and that sort of thing. So that's what's going to start playing right now.
But before that video kicks on, I want to talk about this really, really quickly. It's just a small little giveaway I'm doing, and the light's kind of in the way.
So this is for a Artemis skin, an exclusive Pax Prime 2012 Artemis skin. If you do not have Smite, and you still want to try and get this, then by all means go for it.
I actually have a beta key I can give you if you don't have a beta key. But yeah, it's for the Smite Artemis skin.
So leave a comment on this video if you want this. And if you don't want to enter, then just simply write a regular comment.
But if you want to enter, make sure you put Artemis skin colon, and then whatever your comment is, just so I can more easily decipher through the different comments.
But yeah, that's for a little skin there. I got an extra one, so I figured I'd give it away. And that's going to wrap it up here, guys.
Enjoy the little compilation of clips I have here. And of course, take care, everybody.
Oh, that's so cool. It's crazy.
How's that working out?
What's right-click? What's right-click?
Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
What is right-click?
I don't know.
With German 95 going absolutely ham, Sniper would be a terrible choice for you.
German, German, German.
Just go fire on this.
It's like, insane.
Willyrex, happy face. Willyrex, happy face. Jesus, I love you.
Like, he's legit a rock star.
What a boss. Willyrex, you're watching this video. Shout out to you.
Shout out.
That shit is all Spanish now.
I can say, oh my god.
No, it's like EIU to really, no, it's not it.
So this is day three of PAX Prime in Seattle, Washington.
I just wanted to show you guys the view, because it's actually pretty crazy. It's right next to a highway.
So I'm on the 20th floor, which is pretty damn high.
It's crazy stuff. Look at all those cars doing.
But no, I'm about to check out of the hotel right now.
We're going to the smite booth right now.
Are you vlogging?
What do you think this is?
What are you doing?
We're going to be going to the smite.
This is German, this is Orb. No, wait.
One of us is Orb and one of us is German.
That girl is really cute cosplaying.
Where? Who? Who?
Who?
We got some free play Call of Duty happening over here.
Incredible Orb on the sticks.
Faze cross on the sticks.
Oh, he's on the sticks.
It's getting nasty with the sniping in here.
Watch this kid play. He's really good.
I've seen him before on YouTube.