I told you guys I was gonna be early. I told you. I mean, I'm only five minutes early,
but I'm still early. Still counts. Well does. How you doing? Are we doing good?
I gotta tweet this. Today, we're gonna play some FMV games. One just came out that piqued my
interest. If we're gonna play the first one is not late. No, I'm not late. I'm precisely on
time. The first one is called American Hero and apparently this game is like 25 years old
and it was never released. So some company, I guess they like got 90% of the way through
development and they just didn't finish the game. So some random indie company, I don't
see what the name of the company is. I kind of forget. Got all the footage
and actually released it. So this is a very old game. I'm very interested in this one.
You're a hipster king. Well, not really. This thing's on the Nintendo Switch right now.
So not really. I didn't like go get this on some secret place. You can literally get this
on Switch right now. What about Monster Breeder? It's possible we play Monster Breeder later
today. It really depends on how long these take. Because with some FMV games, some of these games
are 40 minutes. Some of them are three hours. It really depends on how many. Maybe if we play
through it again, if we move on to the next one, I don't know. It depends. We'll see.
We can play among us. It's never gonna happen. It's gonna be awful or bad.
Is that what you said? Did I read that wrong? This is gonna be awful or bad. What about the
Goosebumps FMV with Jeff Goldblum? I did not even know that existed. But now that I know that
exists, I'm very interested. I'm like an FMV wine connoisseur. It doesn't matter how bad they are.
It doesn't matter how shitty they are. I have to play them. All of them, if I can. Also,
I want to make this really clear. There was a content warning on this game. Apparently,
it's pretty dated. I don't know exactly what that means. But like I said, it's on the
Switch. I don't exactly know what to be looking for. But we'll be on the ready.
Are you gonna stream bad mojo? Probably not. So if we do come across something that's
fucking shitty and bad, you know, you fucking behave yourselves. Come on. Come on, Gwen.
You know what I mean? Are you gonna stream crab game? No, I don't. Every one of these
games it takes off. I don't play them. I watch. Okay, this with like trends on Twitch.
It's kind of like how a lot of people jump into like the stock market and stuff.
It's like a game will come along and I'll go that looks kind of cool. I would like to
maybe try that out. That looks like a great experience. And then I don't play it. And then
two or three weeks later, it's it's incredibly popular and everyone's on it. Oh, that's
awesome. I probably should have maybe I could get in now. I don't think I'm gonna get it. I
you know, maybe it looks fun. Now it's like the biggest thing on Twitch, the biggest the
biggest thing in the world. I don't want to buy the top of the crab game meta.
You know what I mean? Stop calling me a hipster. Why are you saying that?
Why don't you stream McDonald's hamburger adventure? I don't even know what you're
talking about. All right, you guys ready? Apparently this is something else I read about
this too is the actor that's in this. They had to have him rerecord lines with the restoration.
And I mean, the guy's like almost 25 plus years older than he is. So I don't know how
that's gonna play out. But it might be pretty funny. But this is American hero. I am ready.
Our choices matter apparently. Are you gonna play Fortnite or should I just go?
You liar. Euro how many months up? You're a six month subscriber. You've been here for six months.
You know what happens on this channel. You're a liar. You're lying to everybody.
All right, you ready? Let's go. This is American hero. Viewer discretion is advised apparently.
And let's go. You ready? Oh, by the way, very important. That's the guy from That's My Bush
from Comedy Central. Yeah, I don't know if anyone remembers that show.
That was a really weird reference. But here we go. American hero. Yeah, okay. Well,
this right off the bat, right off the bat. I hope this I don't think there's any nudity.
I hope not. No, there's not. Oh, God. My home away from home. It's I crystals looking
good today. I think that's the I think that's the voiceover. I think that's a new line.
Relax. Just care. Asshole. There is nudity. No, there's not. It's on the switch. It can't be.
It's on the Nintendo Switch. It's impossible. They don't allow any nudity on the switch.
That's a lie. It can't be possible. Here's trouble. They were right. Now you can piss
off Sergeant. It's Colonel. BFD. The old man has a problem. Why does it sound like he's
in a bathroom? Not interested. It involves Laura in a dangerous mind control virus.
Dangerous. Okay. I think she's been kidnapped. Can't say more.
It looks like Borderlands characters. It looks weird. Why? You're interested.
Meet me somewhere a little more private. You're a big fucking dork. All right,
let me pay attention to the game. A rock in a hard place.
I have to make a decision here. What do I want to do? Bad news. Bad news or party?
Party. What? Bad news. What's going on? What do I do?
Did he leave? Oh shit. Am I going to get run over by a car? Why is there a truck?
Do I have to move the QTE? What do I do? What do I do?
A ledge. Run. A ledge. Run. A ledge. Run. Run.
Jump. I'm going to jump. I'm going to drop. I'm going to drop. He's going to get run over.
New item unlocked? Oh shit.
Wait, hold on a second. Hold on. So I was in a strip club and then I was either going to
go do this mission or stay in the strip club. And then he left the strip club,
running away from a somebody in a Mack truck that ran my whole body over lengthwise,
which is fucking crazy. I got steamrolled. Okay. All right. No, Jesus. We have to do this
again. I don't want to have to show this again. All right. What should I do? Should I?
I'm going to go get the bad news. I'm not clicking party on a game that has been
confirmed to have nudity in it. No way. Not going to happen. Nope. Not happening.
My home away from home. I could run up a lengthwise. That's fucking it ran up from
my heels. Looking good today. To the top of my head. That was insane. Hey, Sherlock,
you got something against me making a living? Relax. Pinhead. I missed that last time as
well. He's drinking carrot juice. I don't get it. I don't believe there's nudity on
the switch. Here's trouble. They were right. So now you can piss off. Oh, there's not.
It's Colonel. BFD. The old man has a problem. I'm not clicking party. I'm not interested.
Involves Laura in a dangerous mind control virus. I didn't mean to click that. I think
she's been kidnapped. Can't say more. It's upscaled with AI. You're interested.
It does actually. I'm actually kind of glad it looks like this because some of the old
FMV games we've played in the past, they look like absolute dog shit. So this
doesn't really even look that bad. All right. No, no party. No, I have to get this right.
It's like a rhythm game. Bad news. Bad news. Bad news. Bad news. I clicked bad news.
I clicked bad news. I don't want to run away from the fucking truck. I clicked bad news.
I clicked. What the fuck? No, I'm. How do I skip the cut scene?
I'm not going to get run over again. The truck is bad news. Oh, no, it's not. I didn't do
anything last time. All right. All right. This time don't drop. This time I'm going to,
I'm going to go for the ledge. Ledge. Ledge. Run. Ledge. Run. Ledge. Ledge. Run. Is he doing it?
What? He's not making decisions. What the fuck? Drop. Jump. Drop. I can't do anything.
Do you hear me clicking? Do you hear this? Why doesn't the game work? Mouse one. I'm clicking
mouse one. Oh, this is not good. It's not right click. It's left click, right? Maybe I
should unplug the controller. I don't think I have one and plugged in. I mean, the mouse
apps. Yeah, that's left click. I don't think. No, there's no controller plugged in.
It's just my mouse. I was spamming too. 10 second reaction time. Try right clicking. Hold on.
Options. Dirty full screen. Set keys. Set. OK, select left click, right? Yeah. Action space.
There'll be pressing. Well, why would it say left click? I guess I'm going to try to hit
space. It's also up, down, left, right as well. Well, I'll try space. God damn it.
All right, I'll try space. You better believe I'm going to try to make sure this get this to
work. You don't get run over lengthwise by a car like that and not like play out at least
some of the game. You kidding me? No way. All right, let me see what happens. The tutorial
doesn't give you it just tells you like the gist of the game. I read it already. All
right. Can I skip this cut scene? How do you skip cut scene? Escape. There's definitely a way
to do it. Enter. I mean, it tab works. My home away from home. Right click. No,
that's definitely a way to do it. Looking good today. I'm going to see if space works.
Pinhead. Are you making us watch this? I'm not making you watch this again.
I'm trying the game's controls are not accurate. Here's trouble. They were right.
Now you can piss off. Sergeant. It's Colonel. BFD. The old man has a problem.
He needs your help. Not interested. Bad news space. It involves law. It doesn't work that
I don't know what I'm going to do. It's not the game. Oh, should I like? Should
I plug it to controller in? I think she's been kidnapped. Can't say more walls have ears.
If you're interested, meet me somewhere a little more private.
And let's see. Base rock in a hard place. Come on, please work. Please work. Bad news.
Space. It's fucking space. What is that meter at the top? I know you'd make the right
choice. Okay, Colonel, this better be good. I hope I still get run over by a fucking truck.
I'm sure Laura would be impressed. I'm not here on a social visit.
So many cigarettes. Kruger's escaped. It's up to his old tricks. Laura was working for us.
She developed an antivirus formula that kidnapped her before she could get it to us.
Tell me about the virus. The old man will do that. What matters is you want Laura.
We want the antivirus formula. Okay. No, that's not. That's not Nick Cage.
Jack, can you get it up for another? Fuck you. Yes. Fuck you. Yes.
I just blacked out.
Why did I black out? What was the point of blacking out?
Oh, it's sensor. Get it. Split. Lemon. Get it. Lemon. No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no. It's all the Switch. It's
on the Switch. It's all the Switch. It's all the Nintendo Switch. It's not gonna happen.
It's not gonna happen. It's all the Nintendo Switch. It's just drinking big water. That's
it. It's all the Nintendo Switch. It's not gonna happen. Things are looking up.
No, they're not. They're not no. They're not. I have to get out of this.
That's three options. I think I'm playing a fucking Mario Party game where you have to
like hit the dice at the right time. Give me a break. That's weird. I don't. Okay. Get
get out leave leave leave before I hit the escape button leave run no leave
leave now leave now I gotta get out I'm out I'm out I'm out I'm out skip how do I
skip skip skip skip get up no I'm not fucking doing this not gonna happen
it's on the Nintendo switch she was just drinking water that's it not gonna
happen I didn't want to do this it's this
control system just watch it is there's no nudity right if there's
nudity I'm out no I'm out already no you don't say here comes the finale and no
I'm not happening I'm sorry I'm sorry I have no I have a clean record with
twitch I've never been suspended I've never had a terms of service problem
if I let her drop her hair and what is I'm assuming potentially some of her
clothing material I am it's not gonna happen no I know that's possible so
I'm gonna do I'll meet you halfway I'm gonna I'm gonna send to the spring for a
second and I'll let you know how it goes I think it's okay I think we're
okay we're good so far I don't know what he's like looking at the I don't
know what he's looking at what is it what is even happening she killing
me what the what what is it boombox escape escape dude I have no she sat on
me I don't even know what to say this has been it's been insane this has
been absolutely insane I didn't know to say I jumped out of a window but what
I didn't know where the window went I want to go back and do what I wanted
to do I want to do what I wanted to do in the first place I want a new game yes
new game I want to do what I was trying to do before I'm not gonna get
soft-locked into that I wanted to take the limo yes I'm gonna play
through this like 30 times don't worry this has been fucking hilarious so
far okay let's try it here we go oh god damn it I'm blocked in I like
half I actually have to do this the game won't let me do it okay well
then boombox is the right answer then I think right I can't just get the
cutscene give me a break whatever you're walking on eggshells I'm very
aware I'm very aware so that that's she's just wait a minute wait a
minute wait a minute no no no no no no no no no no no no you're still
wearing her underwear yeah she still has her clothes on okay we're back so it's
on a black screen yeah she's pretending like she's going to like sleep with
me or I guess I don't know and then she's just trying to kill me that's I
guess what's going on right now and then I've been like hypnotized by
this thing boombox I'm trying to feed back this thing oh it hurts me in real
life though all right get out take it I get I'm not in a no I get take that
whatever that is I'm not jumping out the window again it kills you don't
okay limo shortcut Laura's shortcut Laura's shortcut Laura's limo cut
through limo limo cut through took me a long time to get here you know I
wouldn't be here I've died like four times this time he has created a
genetically old and brain virus and you lost Laura before she could get the
anti-virus formula to you Laura's my wife let's check that toaster this guy's
reading like a parent that's just barely getting through a story at
story time with a kid late at night
random acts of violent from single murders to full-scale riots we don't
know how cook was spreading the damn thing we heard that he's working on a
sophisticated delivery system which will release a virus everywhere
it's a raid hold up the only man for this one Jack but for God's sake then
keep your shorts on we're running out of time well I'm gonna turn the game
volume up I turned it down because the feedback we got a raid what's the rate
from we got a raid from RT what's up RT RT game crowd welcome everybody I'm
gonna give you a very very quick warning we're playing a game that's got
some pretty fucked up themes I guess it's an old FMV game it just released
it's on the Nintendo switch though it's on the switch therefore you know
I don't think they'd be very much nudity or anything like that just
know that is on the switch but I'll welcome everybody thanks a lot for
the raid I turned it down wait I'm not even going anywhere I'm just getting
out of the limo why didn't we go somewhere but didn't I just do this
Laura's KVK Laura's KVK Laura's gonna go to la VK that was too loud yeah
those things are loud door looks open looks like somebody might have gotten
in gate door climb gate door climb holy shit you got up there
quick anybody home he's so much louder than everything else the internal
monologue is so loud Laura's left your purse money in there looks like Mark
Zuckerberg forget it need it forget it need it okay was it like 200 bucks 200
bucks in like 1990 was like fucking eight grand so I'll take it hmm gotta
go hmm gotta go wait was I gonna take a shower
Kruger's goons oh goons oh shit oh they're telling me I can lose these
creeps how what am I gonna do find the telephone pole hell of a day and it's
only two and I lose them wait hold on I will now know how to play
go for a leg I think you have to get hit by the truck a leg run I think run
a step oh shit I did that sequence this guy's just walking in circles
they were still on behind me still with a hit it for the truck cab all right
run fight all right run fight fight I can take a nice but that wasn't really a
fight I just kind of run nice you want some to bring it on the tried
and true henchmen stormtrooper routine just don't have a helmet on
shit yeah all right well now they're not gonna be following me right at super
cab
all right where are you going the old man sent me told me to keep an eye on
he said you need don't distract
got a gun that's on it hold on curse
the shooting the shotgun
far away
right left right what about driving the car
his decision not mine oh you're dead why is all the stuff
everywhere there's too much stuff breaks gas fight breaks gas fight I blacked
out why is this so much hard for it my head hurts hold on
are we driving that he's ripping the wheel back and forth I'm not the one
behind the wheel I'm not driving the car you folded like a lawn chair god
that was so stupid I know people saying certain thing I'm just gonna move on
and scream it's very funny oh my god damn it what an American hero I'm not
gonna fight this time I'm gonna stay in the car
hit the brakes in front of them it just mass breaks you can't believe that
happened this game is insane
hit the brake brake brake gas fight nice all right good decision good call
I know we're gonna be great friends wait you're gonna break yes
fine no kids it's my lucky day we're good I think look at I think that's
I think that I thought that was the right decision it was not the right
decisions probably break I yeah okay what if I hit gas here's what the
other option this game is having a nightmare it is
kind of having a nightmare it's break break is the right play we're gonna get
the same ending it's my lucky day this is the outrageous is brave the way Jack
would watch it be ashes to ashes dust to dust what was the budget for this
game I don't know but the crazy story about this game is that you weren't
here in the very beginning this game was never released it it was done
filming and I don't know if they ran the studio ran out of money or something
but it was never actually released a new company came in and kind of
remastered all the footage and restored it it's the only reason why
we're playing it today okay it's great great oh it's just was in a Jaguar
right we're not arguing about McDonald's or Wendy's we're talking
about life and death here there we go okay we're good on to the next sequence
what are you waiting for let's go okay what is this pretty tight security
this is the lab why would I just walk to the front door like a fucking sim
that's a neighbor what are you doing oh what are you doing he was wearing a
suit under all that holy shit he must be sweating hey well I think are they
gonna try to like melt me into the into the chemical that was a fake hand
it was a rubber hand I will release my virus into the system within minutes
the disease will ripple out exponent it will be the greatest biological
conquest of all boys in the water oh that's why they're drinking the water
out of the big bottles a new order shall prevail my another failed attempt
oh sadistic bastard I got ready to turn and fight put him with a good dog oh
no I'm gonna get like tortured what information do I have anyways I'm
just like an agent that's Laura if it's a story recap so far I was in
retirement I came out of retirement to solve this madman poisoning the water
supply done already on my case what oh no they took away the light that
bulb is so expensive that's very okay we're gonna take the solution here
quick okay all right right right hairpin the guard hairpin the guard do the
medical salt I'm sick I have diarrhea what something anti-virus formula has
an error yeah yeah he's gonna get crushed what would you open the door
without like a weapon yeah I was in the middle of pressing the squish
what do you want we're gonna help you with oh yeah they told me never to do
one thing I forget what it was I think it was don't ever open this fucking door
when people are in it that wasn't even cartoon logic that was like they had a
whole scene and like they had like that the scene they threw the whole
scene away and they had to get an extra to be that guy like there was
like a full ten minutes of dialogue there left right left that was a
reshoot left right they had a whole sequence with a guard oh shit they went
left oh god oh here we go oh no don't push her into the way sound effect if
you type in punch sound effect on YouTube right now that's the first
that's exactly the first one I have not had a decision to make they're
just doing it on their own the AI is just picking direction left right
left right right that'll do holy shit she's running way faster than me and
she's in heels that's crazy left right oh my god I have no idea
let's go left right was the same guy this guy again we're gonna okay we're
gonna see this guy again I that's the wrong way I think if you make the
wrong decision you go in a circle you see that guy every time we're
gonna see him again um right left right right that'll do we're about to
loop again is that guy gonna get up again not just shoot that guy left
right not again all right there's no way that guy comes back another time
it's not possible you understand it's not possible that guy's back he flew
off of a balcony like 15 feet no way I need to know right I have no that guy's
still alive somebody's watching these cameras just going oh he doesn't they
don't know he's back again no more running why is that you see single
shots there's two there now okay oh no we just we got an we got the end card
shit no ah damn it all right well we'll get it we'll get it this time
Oh auto bolt action Uzi okay well this is this game is insane I we have to
get at least some kind of other ending and having far too much fun to
let's go again let's try a new route let's go wait unlockable find every way
to end the game at Jack's funeral reach all the endings where Jack
survives I find stuff flatlined like a pancake by 18 wheels of steel oh these
are all the choices all right let's go oh we can start from here sadistic
bastard what wait what what happened where's Laura this didn't happen
should to me and you'll never see this didn't kill him later you still have
the gun shoot him in the face you have the gun you still have the gun alright I
should just try start the whole thing over see if we can get to the end from
here well what I didn't do that before I didn't punch the guy and grab the
gun last time all right what do you think ones in the chat to just go from
that checkpoint and try it to keep going or two in the chat if you want me
to start the game over and go different route that looks pretty that
looks pretty unanimously one all right let's go sadistic bastard okay so
this time I'm not gonna shoot grab the gun apparently where's Laura
okay don't shoot kill him later kill him later later they still so what I
don't I just don't care about having the weapon bar is a fight or flight
meter yeah the more it's on the right side it's aggression the more it's on
the left running right we have to do this again I need to play through this
game one more time at least it's too ridiculous not see everything else try
the hairpin apparently a lot all right let's try hairpin I'm sorry it's so
loud but it kind of has to be otherwise because there's no subtitles
otherwise we won't be able to hear anything. hairpin. I hope we get smushed. hairpin. the guard.
what are you what are you doing what are you doing what why in the
name of God no no no no no no no no oh that guy's fucking reaction
oh I fucking oh that guy just did like the butthead from Beavis and Butthead
okay no no no no no no no no no no no no I actually not gonna show this
all right we're good oh my god they just let us open the door okay don't
screw this up okay I'm gonna go right first I went left first last time
left right all right now we're gonna try I'm gonna go left all right wait they
just went left oh here it here he is let me out of here okay so now it's
left left right that'll do okay I think we made it okay now where right I
don't wait where do I how do I go where do I go where do I go where do
I go which way which way which way which way which way which way which way
left left right no it's back at this guy again we talking about no I'm not
to see this can't happen again fuck just stay right right right right
only right only right right right left and then left again it's left and then
right left then right stay right left and then left left right left left left and
right left and right left and right not left no it's left left right left then
right chat chat stop what are you gonna you trying to get me killed I don't I
have no idea what's going on I think it's right left left left is right no
left right right left do I do right oh god damn it stop doing this to me what
do I do right not again what's the first one just do left left right right right
twice all right I'm gonna try right right right twice come on right right
right left right okay right right what I do it I got through the vent they filmed
this in a high school classroom sneak in break in sneak oh I'm breaking it with
the axe you better believe it we're gonna hear Johnny these motherfuckers
you made an error oh I told you you did that Jerry you move two decimals kill him
first hey Paul well actually this is where you're gonna get off I'm gonna
take Krueger down at the reservoir and there's no place for you I'll see
I want to be with you Jack oh they caught up to us yeah let's take it let's
take a full 10 to 15 seconds to kiss don't worry about the automatic assault
weapons that are right this is a long shot do it forget it do it what
forget it do it forget it forget it we just go back to the strip club who
is that who is that I don't know who's we on this team all right why
dress like dick Tracy among us it's yellow from among us whose team of
these this is gonna be a bit oh this is me I told you to stay someplace safe
yes don't minus to me minus to the people in chat had said that I was
reacting to it don't touch those are like electrifying these definitely
you think snake oh wait a minute goodbye Hoover goodbye Krueger double
cross the deputy yeah they were working together the whole time destroy the
mobile lab for the lab or is there another option or is this it guys
really desperate to get the old Butterfinger recipe back wasn't
poison after all it's just not the same in the middle trying to recreate it
don't have much time minus two forced joke yeah yeah I'll take the I'll take
the I'll take the yellow that one can I get a decision it's gonna be a
really bad one to have to redo it's been people walking around setting up
for like five straight minutes Krueger Hoover
Krueger Hoover drums
nice job son who the fuck was that why am I looking behind me they didn't
hurt you did they Laura they get looks like she's got herself oh that
definitely probably sounded way better in the mirror two days ago
oh no I've been infected we selling your body is gonna mutate you're gonna
be another one of dr. Krueger's mindless on me a few seconds you'll be
my own personal can you say that again a plane drove over ruined your
moment exothermic reaction is gonna multiply that virus all right three
minutes take it away didn't he say a few seconds that turned into a few
minutes right this is the lose did I lose within three minutes Los Angeles
will be mine perhaps you might enjoy sharing easy you're gonna spell that
shit so what do I do Hoover Krueger Hoover Krueger what do I do Hoover
Krueger I can't shoot him from up here oh I hope the checkpoints really close I
thought I was gonna snipe him from all the way back there that would have
been so funny oh I was right at the checkpoint good very good yeah it's
this it's not I think it's time for this guy to go back to the
drawing board mojo Jojo tried this like three times already all right oh
god damn it all right whatever it's all right it's all right we've
watched this whole thing again all right this time I'm gonna who should I
shoot I point the gun at Hoover who should I point the gun at then not the
barrels right I thought the barrels is a great idea I'm gonna shoot the barrel
which is gonna destroy everything and everyone's gonna get the virus or
whatever all over them right that was like okay but then the guy just came
behind me the extra came behind me and hit me in the head so I was
supposed to know that was gonna happen it's gonna take it's gonna
take oh god it's gonna take forever yeah I'm gonna aim at Hoover that's a good
idea give it I I don't I can't you can't get cutscenes I don't get down
there I told you to stay someplace safe you need to watch this every time I
think we'll get it this time skip no way not in a hundred million years
let's go all right we're gonna aim the gun at Hoover I feel like Hoover's
gonna be like no no don't shoot me all right hold this is what's gonna
happen don't shoot me this guy's a snake right goodbye Hoover goodbye Kruger
I said the guy looks like Joe Biden no it looks like it looks like somebody
took young Joe Biden and put them in one of those age of five apps to make
old Joe Biden that's what it looks like all right we got to aim at this
guy go after him because I feel like you'll probably get another decision
guns don't even have barrels really bringing the crane well it gets the
same message
don't screw this up I don't want to watch the first five minutes of every
RTS phase no I don't want to watch this don't have much time okay here
we go over construction complete building building construction complete
unit lost unit lost Kruger Hoover drums what the fuck who did that and they
don't see me do that I don't care about him yeah I fucking knew it god
damn it
we have to watch the whole thing again or whatever I okay okay why would you
pick the goon I know I'm I don't care about him he's nothing to me kill him
it has to be the main guy but can I even get to the main guy I damn it that's so
funny it has to be a way to skip I'd really don't think there is it's space
I don't know I don't think it is yeah hey yeah this is very important to
remember this is 25 years old it's 25 years old how old are these actors
now the craziest part is the main character recorded voice lines with
this remaster so how old is this main character here probably in his I want to
say probably the 40s maybe early 40s probably so this this person the actor
might actually be in their late 60s into early 70s late 30s early 40s yeah
that's another thing spam every button no it doesn't do any I'm telling
you there is no skip he's George Bush from that's my bush gotta get
it was on Comedy Central he's almost as old as you are now now what I forgot
about that's why Bush yeah that was correct me if I'm wrong but that was
Trey Parker and Matt Stone made that show or at least Trey Parker did South
Park guys I think it was only live for like four episodes or like six
episodes goodbye Hoover goodbye Kruger here we go don't screw this up Bill
Murray is on the crane pay attention what Bill Murray pay attention how
carrying the virus somebody said I missed Bill Murray both times well I'm
not gonna miss him this time you said he's on the crane Bill Murray on the
crane so ready of over anticipating this I feel like it's not gonna be as
funny as you said it was okay where is he brain is the big moment that's not
even that's not even close it's his face is so pixelated in what is this
that's just a guy that's just a guy with like Bill Murray hair actually
hold on a minute don't have much time that was actually pretty close that
you okay here we go I gotta be ready Kruger what if none of them are
correct Murray's not in the credits drums then Hoover oh god drums then
Hoover Kruger is bulletproof Oh Kruger Hoover drums drums then Hoover wait what
the fuck oh okay right no no no no no now we do Hoover here okay it's true
we it's been proven that he's bulletproof remember I tried to shoot
him earlier and now it's go for him I forgot there was a second choice
here you did Hoover last time no I tried to shoot him from down here I
grabbed his gun I tried to aim up at him and he shot her in the head
it's still a little bit in there I just picked that thing up and just
start going I would start inhaling right because you get like the
vapors in my help a little
yeah or like just touch a little bit of the wetness and get it again you
mucous membranes just put your fingers in your nose all the way
back and try to get it in there you get absorbed in your mucous
membranes I really don't want to have to view this whole thing again so
this better be right take it away did Hoover last time no I didn't I tried
to shoot up at Kruger I was like I'm gonna shoot him from here and I aimed
down sights and he killed Laura it's Hoover I'm gonna pick Hoover
within three minutes Los Angeles will be mine perhaps you might enjoy
sharing okay here we go Hoover there's only two options right
Kruger oh no I'm the stormtrooper oh no I'm not oh my god I just lit him up
wait that guy I wasn't even aiming in that direction that shit ricocheted
off the wall and hit that guy I was even aiming over there what a god
gamer nice shot Laura wait wait till I leave oh we definitely gonna dump
I'm gonna dump the guy in the ass who's gonna turn to a skeleton
holy shit this guy did not hit me don't let it dump come on get up there no
don't let us don't please what rabbit rabbit fight rabbit rabbit fight how am
I gonna grab it from here wait this is stupid this is stupid I can't
reach that wait what they kept like zooming into the thing they kept zooming
into it no this is horse shit you know why this is bullshit because think of
the other times where I've picked a decision where it was like oh go get
that guy and I just appeared tackling him that's happened like three times
guys there's been choices where he just had a gun in his pocket and he
didn't have it there before the game was showing me its hand do you remember
when I picked go for go to Hoover he fucking just was in mid tackle after
hiding behind a bush whatever the fuck was over there the game
gaslit you oh god damn it please tell me that no okay so to me fight
would have been stupid but oh grab the the plot device of the entire game but
how am I gonna fight a guy when I'm hanging from a ledge like that you
don't plot device plot device plot device plot device I've clicked the
plot device put something up distract us I have I have a really big apology
here for you if I click out of the window the game pauses and cannot play
we have to work again this is gonna be a bitch I can turn it down all right I
turned it down we're gonna talk about for like two minutes which we're
talking about you know well you get to see Bill yeah you'll see Bill Murray
again that's cool that's pretty cool stuff what I have a breakfast uh I had
a coffee and then I had nothing else I don't eat it's hard to eat
breakfast when I get up in the morning and going all the way into the early
afternoon I can't eat anything thought of eating breakfast a lot of times make
me kind of like nauseous I'm just not ready for food the first three or four
hours when I get up but coffee that I can do I usually eat lunch lunch some
kind of snack some kind of small mid late kind of afternoon meal and then
I do dinner breakfast is overrated anyways I mean breakfast is
incredibly important your body needs fuel to burn so you can function it's
important to do something you have any he'll I actually don't have any heels
left smoothies are good yeah that's that's a good idea you're being played
by big breakfast okay let me get this remember this drum Hoover fight drum
Hoover fight drum Hoover fight drum Hoover fight the essential breakfast
breakfast thing is legit just Kellogg's propaganda well I mean if
you if you eat just like sugary cereals all right here we go a lot
of cereals are just cotton candy with vitamin powder sprinkled all over it
pretty much the same thing Kruger over drums drums I feel like that would be a
great skrillex intro I mean don't shoot the drum call them off or you're
dead
mods aren't allowed to minus to me in this channel by the way game on it
see plot device plot device plot device plot device plot device here it
is why would I not click the plot device they've just been whatever royalty-free
movie night well this is this is pretty much not royalty-free but it's
a game drum Hoover fight all right let's go for it
somebody said watch Bill Murray does it is the Bill Murray character here get a
does he make it I hope so hey within three minutes los angeles will be mine
perhaps you might enjoy sharing
he said scuff scuff Biden versus scuff bush all right here we go now
there's no other choices to make I wish you'd just shoot him now I just realized
they just did the Roger Rabbit routine same exact scenario bat of the acid
the juice dip weasel falls over laughing hits the thing and it moves
okay well first I'd rather was what 80 knowledge if this devil Roger
rabbit came on first 25 years old all right here we go don't screw this up
dip was monkey s Christopher Lloyd is the judge is one of one of my favorite
acting my favorite characters ever he's just so good in that role it was
unbelievably good if you have not seen who frame Roger Rabbit it's required
reading for this stream okay fight this is it this is where we actually
get this correct fight there's not a third option right let me just
double-check rabbit rabbit fight fight that's it fight oh okay this is a last
long enough there it is oh god please I do is the green screen movie night
thing where I'm like strangling you do I take that I think I have to take
that what do I do what do I do get it fight no I don't know what should I
do I didn't make a decision oh shit no I'm fine I'm okay I press space I press
space I swear to God I press space I swear to God I pressed it I press
space on get it you hurt you could hear it you could actually hear it oh
my god damn it it's gonna be a checkpoint is my mouse on the screen or
was my mouse off the screen does that matter hold on professional game I'm
not a who said we who did what professional gamer by the way we
talking about I don't I barely can tie my shoes correctly when did I tell
you I was a pro gamer I please give me a checkpoint please oh fuck all
right keep okay it's rum Hoover fight fight or fight yet should be fight
fight this is your job so you have to be a professional how do you be a
professional at full motion video game fight fight you have to get it or
you're gonna get yeah yeah that's right so there's a huge bait here the
first date is this is gonna be a bitch I'm gonna turn this down because I can't
hear it all right so it's definitely get the second time around it's get
for sure it has to be cuz I'm gonna turn into the zombie person yeah I
think so rum Hoover fight yet rum Hoover fight get can I get that
written down please rum Hoover fight Bill Murray drum Hoover fight yet
it's probably something else after that too we're gonna do this shit a
whole nother time if you want to go to a furry convention with a fursuit how
are you not a furry I just what just cuz I'm gonna I just cuz I'm gonna wear
one drum Hoover drum Hoover fight get right there's another option to fight
I'm gonna do that I think so yeah if the after getting and taking it if
fights an option then I'm gonna have my my wits are gonna be back about
me so I'll be able to fight and you do the ignoring annoying orange sound I'm
ignoring whom what am I ignoring are you a furry answer the question no I'm
not there you go is that is that's matter of
facts for you isn't it should be matter of fact for you somebody said
this is just golden eye except everything sucks don't you love it
though I'm so glad that we get to like see this and experience this
harvester meets James Bond harvester was fucked I would not play that game a
second time all right let's start the process here get the audio back where
it should be all right let's go I didn't realize the run he screams run
at the people drum Kruger Hoover drum from over fight yet and if there's
something afterwards again I have to remind myself a thousand times it's
fight if there's another choice is therefore I would have taken the
antidote marijuana is a memory loss drug I'm not
that would have been a huge mistake for this dream these serious don't get it
wrong every cell in your body is gonna mutate you're gonna be another one of
dr. Kruger's mindless zombies get it is wrong then that's not my fault
because you all we all have come to a consensus here that I need to get it
when it's on the ground because otherwise I turn into the zombie
we get a poll we get a short poll as to what I should do on the second after
I fight the first time in a poll I need because I if I'm gonna be wrong I
need a bunch of people to be wrong too so we can all be wrong together so
I don't feel as bad bite or get on the second attempt one that we just
died at we go within three minutes Los Angeles will be mine perhaps you might
enjoy sharing do a prediction it's good that prediction to take too long okay
Hoover Hoover Kruger all right that was a perfect opportunity for a real
Wilhelm Wilhelm okay why do we got anything 80% yet so if I'm wrong you're
wrong too this guy shoots so many bullets like I
probably gonna throw in a rock and hit me easier than his shooting okay
right right yeah I swear to God if it's not like rabbit fight there we go I
am so nervous right now I am like my heart's kind of pumping because I'm
scared that this is wrong we have to watch this again please get it fight
get it fight get it yes all right now I fight I don't know what to do now I'm
gonna fight if it's fight what do you grab on to wait it's gonna go in the
water baby baby baby scream I did it did you hear that like you may well have
saved us all why does why does Laura not get a medal sometimes it's all
worth what was what why is Laura not get a medal for that you sponsor her like
kill count at the end there was like fucking 30 people I can't do that
without her that's cool we need an alternate ending all right I am willing
to play through one and not play through I just want to say there's
some stuff early that I really want to see there's a lot of other shit
that we need to know where it goes play I start from the beginning oh
shit I can do this checkpoint locked all this so much this will be locked
checkpoints all right I'm not doing party party torturing 14,000 people I
this is some of the most fun I've had in a while what are you talking about
I love this I'm loving this all right let's go to I'm not doing party
party is gonna lose all previous progress does that mean I can I not
start at the other ones I'm gonna do party but I'm gonna sense of the
screen to make sure it's okay my home away from home crystals look at it
actually censored this re-release the original game did have nudity
interesting okay
pinhead the voiceover lines were not in the original now no way the actor
actually came back to rerecord them I'm surprised they didn't port this to
something else here's trouble this whole thing was done even if it was
not on the Jaguar why would they not release it all right so now you can piss
off Sega Saturn or something take a CD it's Colonel BFD the old man has a
problem not interested it involves Laura and a dangerous mind control
virus shit we think she's been kidnapped can't say more it's had an
adults-only rating balls have ears if you're interested meet me somewhere a
little more private and you nudity in any piece of media is gonna have
that especially in a game ESRB rock in a hard place like real people on camera
like naked I think that would get bad news okay party oh it's just this
thing again it's just going okay we've already seen this we've already seen
this nice dress lose it we've already seen this she's not she's not drinking
vegetable oil that's weird all right I don't I'm really kind of playing with
fire here I'm not I can't I'm not I can't show this I can't show this like
a fourth time you know what I mean I'm not I don't I can't show this a
fourth time which TOS allows this yeah I mean yeah what you just watching it
alone huh you can't I didn't okay I didn't mean to press more but I'm
curious I'll watch it okay okay the way you guys can see this maybe you
can okay so we know that does I want to go back to the car chase like
there was some something else to see there it was a whole other place to
go is home of the area I can't stop seeing that is like sunflower oil lose
it feel like drinking vegetable oil is something that's gonna that's in some
like weird like dystopian game setting or something where that's what people
are drinking instead of water can't do this you're not all enough that's
basically oatmeal what's the matter what do you mean oatmeal tell me what's
wrong yeah what I'm old enough 37 18 plus yeah but I don't know I gotta be
careful what was the purpose for you 72 hour bit well this is if I got banned
for 72 hours I scream once a week that would just be like I don't want to
get me I don't want to get like suspended oh the reason why we give a
given you a warning or suspension you showed the girl on top of you potential
sex like eight times once twice three times okay that's pushing it but you
showed it like 12 times drama get out take it get out take it alright so
I take this so now there's a whole there's another area I did not see
shortcut Laura's okay shortcut Laura's already shortcut Laura's there's a whole
other building limo cut through limo a cut through goddamn truck again hell of
a day and it's only two why is he louder than you yeah his voiceover is
louder than me on my microphone he's the screamer not me all right I'm gonna
try this alleged run run then I'm gonna do the jump I'm gonna see where it
happens drop jump there's a huge mattress oh he's the henchman
fake them take them fake them fake them take them thank you we don't even know
who those people are I want the backstory on those two I want to know
what was that for there has to be an explanation of who these people are
I guess that's my first name Jack fake them take them fake them take them I
think that's him yeah that's definitely him what
idiots oh my god I just got that guy killed that guy's just on a jog what's
wrong with me downtown shortcut okay downtown downtown limo cut through no
no limo again cut time we might be at the end they're still on me
here it is all right just get in the car right go to limo then KVK I think
do I have a choice here where am I a shower door
climb somebody's here take a shower at the house who is this guy what no no
no no no no that same guy in the hallway all right well we'll do the
next one we've already seen all this going forward is there anything else
I could have picked here good to see you again I'm sure there's a few
little things we didn't get to see but that was an absolutely hysterical
experience my head hurts the next one that we're gonna play is let me see what it's
called the next one is called a death death stalker yeah the specter files
death stalker is the next one now what is gonna kill it here I'm gonna go
pee I'll be right back I come back we'll be in another one see you in a minute turn that
off because that's gonna be really annoying you're back hello get this open
I really don't know very much about this one the specter files death
stalker are you suited no no play Elden ring no I don't want to play the
first 10 to 20 hours of a game and then just not be able to play it like
four months I would get so hyped up and so into it get a third of the
way through the game and then just now what February I don't want to do that
that's all I would be thinking about for the next three or four months this
game has death in it I mean it's called death stalker I would assume so
it's kind of in the title all right here we go let me just make sure
it's not too loud which it might be I don't think so this one looks a
little more let's find out play okay a B and C yeah I have to use the law you
can't see anything hold on oh can you not see it to be able to see it now
interactive film in oh my god that's terrifying oh oh my god that was
horrifying I should come play this I'm kind of scared all right make a
choice use the left mouse button to select your choice pressing the space
bar skips videos okay in case we get stuck somewhere and escape quits the
game so don't press escape all right play play it's a music video don't play
the music video I just quit the game I don't like this there's scare I was
scary I don't like this it's just very unsettling I don't like it all
right let's play the game Howard Howard Howard I I didn't like that I
don't want possibly there's probably spoilers in there change the
which category oh shit you're gonna change this to this even on the
categories on twitch death stalker it is inspector files death stalker
there we go all right I'm ready ready to play it's time with to help things
gonna be really loud I'm really sorry if it is it is very loud okay so
we do have to make choices you learn two things in detective school first
detective school
and second a case that involves a missing blonde will inevitably drive
you to drink something about this case intrigued me besides I was between
clients at the time and certain bill collectors
coffee mug papers said she was last seen in durr hatchet hollow walking
her chihuahua through a nearby graveyard not much to go on but I had
to start somewhere I'd like to go out the window do you hide your wallet
shout I'm not here or Shay I'm not here you wanted money all right
inspector mr. vaseline he wants to give you five good reasons why you should
pay him the money tonight I didn't give you a chance to pay the money right
dead losing consciousness is not healthy and should be avoided touched by
my secretary's concern poor kid was crazy about me don't you think you
ought to start looking for that girl I mean I'd like to get paid this
do you say sure thing start earning the reward money just drive to the
Institute
our water hatchet Institute was founded by a Nobel prize-winning scientist
who disappeared in the late 50s leaving the place deserted for nearly
30 years okay doors locked knock on the door look under the mat it's gonna be a
key under the mat that has to be it's Scooby-Doo music naturally there was a
key to the front door under the mat the stench was awful it was like
entering a tube or rotting stairs to my right room to my left and I felt a cold
chill on the back of my neck okay do you carefully climb the stairs that look
over the shoulder look over the shoulders gonna be a monster right here
I world about in time to see the wind slam the door shut then I realized I
wasn't alone oh shit it's this lady okay uh race up the stairs ignore her
make polite conversation run just race up the stairs I did a fun farewell to
the fanged femme fatale and ran up the stairs I paused to see if I was being
oh I hate this I was I hate this okay run into the darkness give her a
breath mint um what does that mean I'm not sure what happened next I vaguely
remember staring into someone's eyes eyes peer directly into your soul and
you black out I don't know how long I was out but someone or something had
dragged me to a cellar below der Hatchet manor okay I lost a health as I
struggled to clear my head I clicked on my flashlight and looked around
any fool could see that the place had more than its share of dingbats and
I was no exception this music keeps playing okay
explore go looking for trouble find the friend who dragged you here I'm gonna
explore the cellar it was there in the cellar that I discovered the little man
with the evil grin I couldn't hear him over the music I don't know what is he
asking me Lance past him say don't turn around
grab the his coal shovel grab the shovel before I could move he brought his
shovel into my face I think I died I'm dead I woke up with the feeling that I
was at the end of my rope wait I'm not my am I dead I was I was fit to be
tied the situation was bad and my life hung in the balance what the
fuck how do I was no time for reflection this is the guy that knocked
me out what do I do to get out of this take a deep breath stand on your toes
do something clever there's not enough time for me to think about this I'm
gonna do something clever I was trying to think of a diversion when I
started to slip away as the rope bit into my neck what do I do wait I didn't
have to do anything when I got up I saw that my breath made quite an
impression on laughing boy okay make good use of the rope take the candle
and go uh take the candle I grabbed a candle and headed out a sudden
breeze blew out my candle and I could barely make out my surroundings in the
darkness I should have taken the rope or something use your last match go look
for another candle uh match don't have a flashlight since I didn't get the
match lit it's him it's the same guy bad misuse of your resources you
blackout am I gonna be up on the gallows again I came to in an attic
I'm supposed to be dead someone or something was sitting across the attic
from me at long last the detective decides to pay a visit to his host have
you enjoyed our hospitality so far what the hell it was difficult not to
listen his voice had a strong hypnotic effect we never did I feel
like we've met before you don't know me but I know you is he drinking booze
each time you laughs in consciousness I get to know you a little better come
sit drink with me it's something I picked out close to your heart that was
my blood he was sucking on did I drink it I think I'm gonna drink it
yeah check your pockets lunge forward and attack I mean it's clearly a guy
with a mask on right I tried to attack but thought come to count your
Chakonsky stared into my eyes and I knew I had failed I blacked out
you now haunt the halls of your hatchet Institute and the case remains
unsolved okay in hindsight you probably could have made better choices during
your investigation yeah we got gum shoot got the we got gum overconfidence
was your undoing never count your chickens before they're hatched I can't
imagine the the spooky scary ghost person calling me gum shoe holy shit
okay there's a lot of stuff all right let's go you must solve the
mystery to qualify these are the top gum shoes all right go this time I'm
not gonna screw up in other words don't lunge at everything it's a game for
children this is not a game for children in detective school first
always keep your files neat and orderly I lost health center in the
beginning a case that involves a missing blonde will inevitably drive
you to drink something about this case intrigued me besides I was between
clients at the time and certain oh I can skip right okay this guy's looking
for money uh let's meet him let's just meet this person he wanted money all
right you missed us but it was for a good cause all proceeds go to the
orphan wait this is different person of course tax deductible I don't mean
to pry but your secretary mentioned that you might be driving out to dear
hatchet hollow that was like five dollars it's a very evil place I want
you to have this oh wait we're gonna get a save your life it's a vial of holy
water what where was this the beginning twelve dollars tax deductible okay send
in the next okay go find the missing girl I have holy water
the dear hatchet Institute was founded by a Nobel prize-winning scientist who
disappeared in the late 50s leaving the place deserted for nearly 30 years
it's packaged up I walked up the creeping front steps and turned the knob all
right the ladies here I have a choice to turn around or get the key from under
the mat and then what do I do about the lady try just naturally talk to the
lady there was a key to fit the front door under the mat the stench was
awful it was like entering a tube I just keep running from the layers to
my right and a room to my left and I felt a cold chill on the back of my
neck carefully climb should I carefully climb the stairs yeah if I sneak I
probably can as I ascended the rotting stairs I began to feel as if I were
being followed from the top of the stairs I could see a woman below okay
I don't have a weapon holy water use the holy water her skin erupted as
the water splashed on the stench was awful the second floor looked dark and
uninviting okay that was a waste I don't know if I could have got away check
on her condition run into the nearest room right I don't you have so much
there's not enough time my fear faded as I fled I felt fine till I fell so
I flipped over and found I'd been followed by a fanged femme fatale with
a fried finger it's her use the vial of holy water I don't do I have it kick
her teeth out oh I don't still have any left it wasn't till I cut my hand on
the broken glass that I realized that the bottle of holy water wasn't
shatterproof I just well here we go again I don't know how long I was out
but someone or something had dragged me to a seller below der Hatchet
is this guy as I struggled to clear my head I clicked on my flashlight and
looked around which disappeared after the fool could see that the place had
more than its share of dingbats and I was no exception
find who dragged you in here explode go looking for trouble find who dragged
you here I don't I think these are all the same thing it was there in
the cellar that I discovered the little man with the evil grin what's
the correct play here
all right so now what are the choices don't lunge at him grab his shovel
glance past him say don't turn around and you bait him he fell for it so I
took the opportunity to bash him in the chops I never hit a man when he's down
but I knew I should have white an exception when I felt his fingers on
my throat you can't be serious I have to flip that second off she's not
gonna do anything flip up I flipped him into his coal bin and ran into the
darkness that's not gonna kill me okay laundry why would I hit somebody with a
shovel and be like you know I don't hit a person when they're down even if
they're a degenerate murdering zombie person find an elevator find an
elevator I found myself ascending a steep circular stairway when a green
ghoul in a rented tuxedo made a dramatic entrance these people just
went to the Halloween store and bought everything on the rack and then just
decided to shoot stuff with it and they made choices around it they were just
having a they're just having like fun for like a weekend let's make some
small talk see if it works I approached the zombie reluctant took his hat off
and asked him who his tailor was his response he took his hat off like oh
it's me hello oh floor surprise me um surprise me we arrived on the first
floor and I got off I could hear faint piano music coming from somewhere
piano music this is it could be anything I have no idea um enter the
room on the left the room was crawling with vermin but otherwise
empty they're so cute they just have that is vibing leave him alone follow the
rats yeah they know what they're doing the next room I came to had nothing in
it there was an old freezer on one side and a wall full of potions on the
other Frank one of the random potions just as I started to examine them I
heard a scream okay find a place to hide open the freezer I'm putting the few
reasons I opened the freezer be only to find another prisoner of this horrible
place
we have to keep this guy alive
you wouldn't have a car by any chance you wouldn't be going to your Fresno
area Fresno's really not that far he was unfortunately an obnoxious jerk
who didn't have anything intelligent off money or a cigarette you thought
what a jerk it's remarkably still alive what are you talking about this
guy could probably help see what he knows about the house what do you know
about the house you've been here probably for a while oh shit the
crazy I mean I couldn't get out of the box how am I supposed to know how to get
out of the house no no man don't don't leave man look I just give me five
bucks five bucks will give me my sister's house and I'll leave you alone
I swear he just wouldn't let me go this is a monster this might be a
monster in the house maybe this is not a person I give him five bucks I
gave him five dollars and left okay leave this loony bin behind search
remaining rooms search remaining rooms that actually might have been a
monster to the next room I heard the scream again take the source of the
scream we have to know we have to know returning to the hall I glanced
up to where the sound came from Jesus see run away right but I don't know
see what he does next run see what he does
was thrashing about so I backed up and gave him plenty of room I don't but what
if what if he's not hostile I don't we might not be hostile how yeah but you
know you never know god damn it I was at the end of my rope when I realized
that I was I was fit to be tied all right so we got this right last time
life hung in the balance we have to like tie this guy up or something this
was no time for reflection if I didn't stream I would probably be this guy
like if I was on a streamer what did YouTube or something I would have
probably been that guy at some point something clever I was trying to
think of a diversion when I lost this was the right thing last thing hit
something okay you need to get the rope I got up I saw monster or the
actor the actor on laughing boy the actor not the guy what he's doing the
actor oh my god all right make good use of the rope I told laughing boy he was
bound to be out of circulation for a while but he didn't appreciate the
gag okay head for the hallway exploded look for a sign and head for the
hallway I guess artifacts you are that's what the piano music's coming
artifacts or music room we already did the elevator I don't want to go back in
there artifacts artifacts the next room contained an old writing desk under
the der hatchet family crest on the desk were many items of interest hey
old coins wine cryptic runes decipher the ruins just as I picked up the
papers the candle lit itself and a funky phantom friar floated into the room
this guy looks friendly okay burn his papers enjoy wine and candlelight he's
snapping his fingers the candle and a glass of the house vino and the
phantom friar gave up the ghost what I didn't want to kill him he just wanted
to hang out oops well I guess I won half of these monsters come up to me
varied non-hostile I'll get the golden split I'll get the gold music
room I want to go to the music room quickly leave the cellar search the
cell where's the music room just leave the cellar oh it's this guy
music room whistle a happy tune first floor say second floor second floor
we're already on the first floor the second floor look dark and
uninviting it could room at random find the kitchen the room I next entered
was obviously a library of some sort great job finding the kitchen there
is there was a door to my left another dead ahead but most of the
action was taking place in the kitchen on my right someone was practicing a
bizarre form of culinary preparation right let's go right let's see I
couldn't put my finger on it but there was something odd about the
woman in the kitchen I think maybe it was her three-day beard okay grab
some food and go can I look in the fridge oh it's Edna fine a find the
edibles find the edibles everybody on this house is on them might as well
join a clove of garlic and a couple of potatoes definitely take the garlic
shut that down the boss's throat of garlic okay I'm gonna leave sneak away
quietly I don't want to do anything else out of the kitchen and left her to
work a faint breeze carried a musty odor to my sensitive nostrils okay well
over to the closed door okay we're gonna peek through that I'm not going
in there just yet this room seemed to be a laboratory there was something
odd about it and then I realized what it was the room suddenly I realized
that someone was coming up behind me it's a vampire see the teeth jump in
the tub and quickly jump in the tub thinking quickly I stepped into the
shower and pulled the curtain closed a hairy paw reached in and turned on
the water I peered around the corner and saw a she wolf busily primping
yourself for a night on the town this is such a crack game it really is what
do I do I don't know I'm not clicking any of these I don't know what to do my
dead I came to know no attic someone or something was sitting across the
attic from me okay I have the garlic
I mean I'll be honest difficult not to listen his voice had a strong hypnotic
effect there's only one person that's really tried to hurt me everyone else
is kind of been just a weirdo hanging out like vibing like no one's
really attacked me or anything I kind of just bump into you don't know me but I
know you each time you laughs in consciousness I get to know you a
little better come sit drink with me it's something I picked out close to
your heart but that was garlic my blood he was sucking on yeah we're
gonna put the garlic in his drink like your pockets find something of
value check you um if you check pockets right is that I got garlic I checked my
pockets my pockets were empty what I learned your Jedi ways by count this
was count your Chakun ski sister I knew I had failed when I looked into
his eyes I was powerless to resist him I got 6,000 points you got to get the
garlic up there and get to him without being knocked out shit are you round
up to 6,000 here all right do we try okay I'm gonna speedrun one let's
just speedrun did it crash yeah crashed again oh we're good okay there
we go all right speed run time I'm just gonna go in places I didn't go
see what happens okay meet the gentleman should be the priest you wanted money
all right you're best for acceptable you said that thing deductible all right
send in the next client I'm cute have another drink I decided to take a few
moments to organize my thoughts so I poured myself another drink and began
to read it leaves to pay today or else easy cat why am I doing this
found these clippings in the newspaper not sure if they mean
anything but I thought you should see them what is this all about hospital
dental clinic I passed out sometime around midnight I passed out as I slowly
regained consciousness I was touched by my secretary's concern and are you all
right poor kid was crazy about me I didn't lose HP go find just gathering
clues find your car keys okay let's go doors locked try something else I was
there the whole time weirdly enough it was taped there I'm not sure why look
over your shoulder all right explore the room the room was crawling with
vermin but otherwise and I'm getting different things explain this if I
hadn't been so busy talking I might have noticed that she wasn't really
listening damn it I shouldn't have skipped it stop thought I took a
different route that's right fuck it that's right I took a different route
damn it I don't have the holy water yeah shit okay Oh looking for trouble
we didn't do that one I went looking for trouble and found it in the
form of a phantom friar oh this guy again didn't appreciate interruption no
sense of humor I guess oh this was fast never go looking for trouble oh here I
am with my lightsabers I will take you I woke up with the feeling that I
was at the end of my rope when I realized that I was I was fit to be
tied I'm what did I say I'm here with your lightsabers I didn't have a chance
I didn't even have a chance okay we know what to do with this this is a
this whole thing's a wash let's see if I stand on what happens but I was
trying to think of a diversion when I think they all do the same thing I got
up I saw that the pipe it made quite an impression okay use the rope
over this game sucks has that ever stopped us before bound to be out of
okay go all right look let's try look for a sign I'm still very interested I
want to get to the music room because the elevators up I mean the music room
is up and up the stairs on the steps above me a green ghoul gestured
gracefully this is the elevator guy okay makes polite talk he puts me in
the elevator I don't want to go anywhere though I don't want to go back
down I'm surprised but I don't what if I don't say anything will he keep me on
this floor somewhere back in the elevator right down the hallway the
next room I came to had nothing in it all right here's there was an old
freezer on one side okay we're gonna try to get more info from the hippie
okay do you know any escape options what if I don't give him five bucks what
about do you know anything about potions I read the labels extra
strength potion instant steak pill anti-grav tablets instant steak instant
strength steak or strength steak or straight steak I wasn't hungry now but
an instant steak might come in handy later yeah we have to put this into
his wine right because it goes in you and it's a steak and you what
about the stench why does it smell because then it'll the steak will blow
up in his body right it sticks to your ribs yeah that means that it's gonna
turn into a steak inside your body you could bathe more off all right I
gotta leave we're gonna we're gonna both die from this like poison I gave
him five dollars and left if the vampire eats this somehow whether we
have I don't know how we get it to have him to eat it all right we're
gonna leave we're gonna leave leave leave he takes it yeah but that he
takes yourself if you die which I haven't died yet if I get knocked out
again yeah I ran into the next room I heard the scream again this guy we
just do avoid this do not go investigate this at all just keep no
keep moving forward this guy knocks you up I ran through the door and found
myself near the elevator okay up I pushed the button and waited there
was a green door to my left and a stairway to my right wait for the
elevator but what if he comes out what's behind the green door I walked over and
opened the green door well the last thing I remember is staring at the
hole in his chest where a steak should have been oh come on come on I
came to in an attic someone or something was sitting across the attic
shit
Don't go look for double E
I wonder if this way I can get through this
maybe maybe it's too small maybe he didn't take it okay uh yeah I don't know you
I love this costume
okay uh should I offer him a bribe that's the only thing I haven't
picked my pockets were empty I took the liberty of removing everything from
your pocket I love this guy this was count your
Chakonsky I knew I had failed when I looked into his eyes I was powerless
to resist him all right I'm gonna try this one more
time let me try one more time come on at least well I opened the green door and
it was okay like I choose your adventure game there's a reason why you
hold your finger on the previous page because open door on right guy kills
you you know that's okay well fuck that I'm not doing that one and you
keep your hand your finger on the tab you go back and you choose the
right one you're cheating at books that's not cheating it's not cheating
there's still so much stuff okay where do I where am I what am I doing wrong
there's a lot more in this game that I really thought there was all right one more try
holy water and then we gotta leave he wanted money all right but it was for a good cause
okay it was nice to see you the okay don't send in the next client it's the guy that
punches you so I'm gone the derhatchet institute was founded by
under the mat of course naturally there was a key to the back of my neck okay now what
over my shoulder is the girl explore the room everything is the girl I think the
candlelit room should be okay the room was crawling with vermin but otherwise empty
she follows oh god damn it she follows you both times she follows you in both scenarios I don't
think you can avoid this wait explain I can't run I could sense that she was attracted to me
what run tell her she has nice eyes what I don't understand what do you if I hadn't
been so busy talking I might have noticed what why isn't a run really listening I can't believe
there's not oh god damn it I could have avoided that all right there's one here's how
you avoid that one you just have to go up the stairs and run because if you go to the
candle it wrong I was out but someone or something had dragged me to a cellar below
derhatchet holy water works but she follows you up the stairs as I struggled to clear my head
I clicked on my flashlight and looked around
all right these are yeah these all don't go look for trouble these all lead to the same
place anyways it was there in the cellar that I just okay so what's the correct thing with
this guy don't turn around glance past him just just glance past him what if we don't attack
he fell for it so I took the opportunity to bash him in the chops he fell for me looking the
other way I never hit a man when he's down but I knew I should have made an exception when
I felt his fingers on my throat can you avoid this guy oh flip over backwards right
I flipped him into his cold bin and ran into the darkness
Egyptology laundry look look for a stairway I don't think we did the stairway last time
I found myself ascending a steep here's the guy with the hat when a green ghoul
and a resin tuxedo made a dramatic entrance I wonder if there's a wrong option with this guy
proceed small I don't think it really matters let's just do small talk
I approached the zombie I don't want to go down I don't want to go down the to the
what if I say mind your own business that's the one option I did not do
we arrived on the first floor and I got off I could hear faint piano music coming from
somewhere all right where's the steak kitchen I don't I don't remember where the kitchen is
is it straight I'm getting so turned around like I don't even know what
any of these options really go the next room I came to had nothing in it okay here we go
there was an old freezer on one side and a wall full of potions on the other
so that we want the steak one we gotta give this guy money uh what about those potion bottles
hey man you don't want to be messing with those chemicals man they're bad for your karma
I read the labels extra strength potion instant steak pill anti-grav tablet
anti-gravity I feel like the steak is the is the correct option steak I wasn't hungry now
but an instant steak might come in handy later we'll stick to your ribs I gotta get up the
stair okay wait should I take the anti-gravity one too anti-grav tablets I noticed something
strange from the moment I opened the jar get some strength stop get the all right take the
instant strength potion and run taking the extra strength I gotta get out of here like a good
idea till I read the fine print oh god damn it we're dead we're dead ask take a deep breath
no run run run how do I get out run leave the fumes in the room no I'm trying to get out
and consequently I oh come on so I blacked out well how was how was I gonna know that
like it was there was a two joke options that I was at the end of my rope the anti-gravity
pills oh they fly up I was fit to be I did the situation none of this matters I was trying to
think of a diversion when I lost my footing and then how do I get up to the attic started
to slip away as the rope bit into my neck okay let's get them make good use of the rope
I told laughing boy was bound to be out of circulation for a while but he didn't
appreciate the gag okay so now from here look for a sign oh I don't think we clicked this
yet I'm pretty sure this is one I have not done look for a sign I did okay music I need
like a piece of paper that has like the blueprint of this house it's just like teleporting around
I was like my brain cannot remember where I am oh let's go do this the next room contained an
old writing desk under the derhatchet family we'll get points for getting rid of this on
the desk were many items of interest decipher the cryptic rune and then that makes him come
over and then we put it in the thing and we burn up the papers the candle lit itself
here we go and a funky phantom friar floated into the room
okay enjoy wine and candle light I extinguished the candle in a glass of the house vino
and the phantom friar gave up the ghost okay so from here we're still down I have the coins
I need to find my way up to the second floor find the elevator look for a way out okay
I'll get the golden split we did this last time which takes us outside
we can go to the elevator okay get in the elevator I want to go to the second floor
what floor please second floor so then from here where do I go from here
then remember second floor look dark and uninviting remember where to go from here
to get to the guy the kitchen all right yeah the kitchen already beat the last score the
room I next entered was obviously a library of some sort there was a door I don't remember
what timeline but most of the action was taking place in the kitchen on my right
where someone was practicing a bizarre form of here we go we're gonna go into the kitchen
get the points and towards the right I couldn't put my finger on it but there was something
was good eat holy shit it actually was good eats I think maybe it was her three-day beard
wow okay look in the fridge no way are you kidding me this game came out like how long ago
10 20 years ago inside the cupboard was a rose a clove of garlic and a couple of potatoes
so let me get this right my memory is fucking dog shit after this where do I want to go after
this I don't want to do the um I don't want to deal with the the wolf I reached in and took
the clove of garlic wolf is a death scenario okay sneak away sneak away quietly right I need
a drink I need the rose tiptoed out of the kitchen and left her right from here from here
where the fuck do I go from here a faint breeze carried a musty odor to my sensitive
I'm not going in there okay peek through go over to follow the breeze all the breeze I don't want
to go in the bathroom this room seems to be a laboratory I thought that was the closed door
I gotta get out of here right now realized what it was the room smelled like a wet dog
suddenly I realized that someone was coming up behind me I don't what I do I don't know
what to do what do I do what do I do turn around think quickly what the fuck am I
supposed to do think quickly thinking quickly I stepped into the shower and pulled the curtain
closed a hairy paw okay I don't think what should I do I peered around the corner you
have to flirt with the wolf she wolf busily primping herself for a night on the town
okay I'm gonna try um I give a you want me to show the flirt
and giggled like a school girl what then she started towards me are you kidding me
those eyes my life what do I do um um um puck her up puck her up puck her up puck her up
she's coming over I don't know she looked forward and planted a wet sloppy kiss on my lips
then stepped aside to let me pass got it okay now what smile and leave enter the room across the
say smile and leave the room all right bye bye smile I don't want to have to be followed
I stopped for a moment near the doorway okay we've not gone this far for good luck and now
from here I rounded the corner and very nearly bumped into a female vampire
she was starting to leave when I gave myself away shit okay well I have garlic confront her
hide um confront her I have garlic I have garlic I'm gonna do it I have garlic I'm gonna do it
I have garlic I'm gonna do it could see she was in no mood for a confrontation I have I have
garlic in my pocket what I have the stakes I have the guard why can't I attack I came to in an
attic someone or something was sitting across the attic from me I have garlic and I have the
steak pill and holy water decides to pay a visit to his host oh well have you enjoyed our
hospitality so many 500 points it's fine at least we seduced the werewolf it was difficult
not to listen his voice had a strong hypnotic effect god damn it well let's just get as many
I'm trying to get to 8000 points you don't know me I love this guy but I know you you have in
my inventory in consciousness was all the shit that vampires are weak against holy water see
steaks garlics I couldn't use any of them I picked out close to your heart that was my blood
he was sucking on I'm not gonna beat it you have to this is guys this game came out like
in 1984 1985 or something find something of value I don't have anything quickly I checked
my pockets what is it what's going on what's in my pocket throw a gold
coin kick in the groin what should I do I tried to attack but I can't do it into my eyes and I
knew I had failed I blacked out what would you pick the gold coins out why wouldn't you take
why wouldn't garlic be an option why wouldn't the steak pill a holy water he didn't take the
shit out of my pockets this time I have coin where I throw a coin at him why don't you give
him a coin because I want to try to kick the guy in the groin all right this game came out
in like 1992 are you serious you don't think it would have been like a comedy routine where
it's he goes like oh my oh my balls I was going for like the stupid like 90s comedy routine
this game came out in 2016 it wasn't yet but it wasn't filmed in 2016 it was filmed
in probably like 1990 shit all right well that was fun the game was made in 84 yeah come on well
now let's watch them well now we can see the music video wait did showing him dying what the
hell was that we didn't see any of this stuff oh we didn't get any of these options behind
the scenes yeah I think the skeleton guy's mouth is partially made from a baseball mitt
is this like a wizard like cantaloupe no not really I can't believe there's a wizard that
can cast fireball at you play it again oh you need to probably have the ace for that
the thing with these old games though is you have to be so weirdly specific about everything
to see some of this stuff some random lady we saw that plenty of times wait was that the real
ending villain that was fun actually in love with this game play more play again use a
walkthrough I could just use a walkthrough you look at the restoration of a 16 millimeter
film adaptation of the original interactive text adventure designed wait this is an
it's a text adventure that's why it feels like this uh remember the chance to create
a feature-length interactive film I wanted to read that vampires wanted restoration
that's really cool I did not back-to-back games that just never released
it's really interesting I love this shit I really do this kind of old-fashioned way to
have the sort of old 16 millimeter fmb games with all the weird goofy choices I love this shit
people still make them now but the people make interactive movies right now right
there's been a few of them one more playthrough all right one more time with I'm gonna get a
walkthrough I'm gonna go pee though I'll be right back boys and girls a little bit of an
issue here we have a little bit of a small problem here I don't think a walkthrough exists
for this game I don't see any there are no walkthroughs so that's bad make the walkthrough
did you even go to the bathroom I did I was promised to overwatch I don't I think you're
in the wrong place nobody's beaten this we'll help you you gotta be quick though you gotta
be really quick it's like two seconds it takes three seconds for the stream delay to kick in
for you guys to see what happened we're not gonna be able to do it I can't elongate that slow your
CPU down what if you alt tab does it actually let me test that let me just see if this works if I
like tab out will the game stop no it just keeps going yeah it keeps going wait a minute
wait a minute wait a minute what if I had known this shit this would have been so much
better guys oh my god damn it take a look at this get a good view get a good view
the timer doesn't do anything when it gets to zero it's just points I was panicking half the
time because I thought are you kidding me it's just puts your score up higher well you can help
let's figure this out together and this needs to be unanimous so the obvious play here
is I can't believe this I could have whatever we're gonna meet the gentleman
wanted money all right for a good cause thank you mr specter whatever your name is
tax deductible deductible they're not deductible okay so this just means a lot of points mid
points not I don't care if I get zero points I just want to see the end of the game okay
we do click maps click max is gonna take way too long all right the obvious thing here is
I have the holy water I don't want to send in do click maps I don't even I don't even
have it like installed we can do quick polls how long does the poll take just give us two
seconds to click hold all right well then give me a second I gotta like enable it again
oh this again I might I might not be able to do it no click map the shortest poll is one
minute that's much easier click okay to enable click maps have you guys click and me disable
it is like 45 seconds a b or c let's go the very obvious one I know how to get here it's b
I know how to get us into the room into the door the derhatchet institute was founded by a
noble prize-winning scientist locked is what okay fine we have not done we've only done look
under the mat what do you guys want to do let's open it up why not we'll do a full
chats choice run how does that sound and I look I can look at this as it's coming in
and yeah it's not gonna take 60 seconds look at 66 percent of the vote wants me to go a
so I could theoretically just once it once it becomes like a 50 to 60 percent majority
I'm just gonna go can you just close the poll like if you cancel the poll right now just
close it like I know that's 67 percent of voted for a and there's no way B is coming back
I can just do it right yeah let's go that works find another way inside as I walked around
the house I saw an open window high above me isn't that where the guy is I found a ladder
leaning next to another window okay I think that's where the guy is well there we go
perfect so after the poll is over it gives enough time after majority is seen to just
keep going that's perfect timing okay we can either climb the ladder look around explore
the extensive grounds or move ladder to access the open window I'm just going to tell you
I am under the impression here that I think that's the um the Count Dooku guy
uh the gravest guy is up there this is extraordinarily unanimous looks like we're
going to see I moved the ladder and started I hope it's him I was halfway through the window
looking at the ground below when I was struck from above by what felt like a Louisville slugger
the gorilla hovering above me was a bat from the big leagues push its face in swing for
the fences or maintain a safe distance I doubt any of these work if I'm going to be honest with
you a bat from the big leagues well B makes sense because B is part of the pun right
it's waiting for the fences a big bat from the big leagues all right we'll go and be
it's unanimous waiting for the fence I grabbed the bat with both hands and swung
away from me to say it looked angry would be a gross understatement that definitely hurt
the actor okay snare the bat with the rope climb up to the rafters or use the rope to escape
snare the bat with the rope that's in that it's 80 percent of the votes so far
yeah okay snare the bat I grabbed the rope and a trap door opened as we're running fell
for what seemed to be a long long time they hit the ground hard fortunately I broke my
fall on something soft well well what do you think you're doing mother doesn't like anybody
playing in our laundry do your mom that's right stay out of my laundry why did he change
his voice halfway through this guy was obviously a psycho this guy's a psycho uh
why does it sound like bobcat gault wait I mean I had to like make sounds and make voices
and stuff like that it sounds like me you guys say this to me all right give the psycho
a closer look go find the butler give mama a friendly smile well I think this is the death
one but we have to click it because that's what you guys want to do give mama a friendly smile
yet within striking distance casually gain his confidence or go find the butler
I'm convinced that you made this game and this is some kind of prank stream I wish I
did I wish I made this game all right we're going to be I moved cautiously towards mama's
watch it right okay you guys got that double wrong that's double wrong he flattened your nose
I don't know how long I was out but someone or something had dragged me to a cellar below
der hatchet manor as I struggled to clear my head I clicked on my flashlight and looked
around any fool could see that the place had more than its share of dingbats and I was
no exception FMV game you know how badly I've okay here's the problem there's I have to be
careful for like shotgun blasting out a bunch of ideas that I think are really fun because
I have to focus on only a few things at a time make no mistake about it I would love
nothing more than to put hundreds and hundreds of hours of time and any amount of money
doesn't matter how much it would cost to make an FMV game that's like this but holy shit that
is like a monumental undertaking and there's no way I'm going to be able to do it there's only
so many things that can be in the tank you can't load up too much luggage in your car to the
point where your car is touching the ground because it won't drive yeah I can't weigh the
car down with 500 cinder blocks make that one the last bit before retirement all right
explore the seller it was there in the cellar that I discovered the little man with the evil
grin I've actually talked about it before with people in the community about like things that
I've wanted to do but it's just I can't I get it's too much to think about too much to do
all right I mean we already know how this one plays out I probably just do this on my
own it's don't turn around and then we flip them he fell for it so I took the opportunity
to bash him in the chops I never hit a man when he's down but I knew I should have made
an exception when I felt his fingers on my throat how fucking awesome how fun would that be
man imagine making a full FMV game and we just do it when you guys play it like I don't
even play it you guys pick like this oh god damn it that would be fun yeah do it I don't tell me
to do these things because I will fuck up every other project just give me a little bit more
time I have a lot more things to talk about just a little bit more time um I want to do
so many of these things a little bit more time all right what are we doing all right
well Chad is deciding to lose another heart so uh we're going to tickle him he just tightened
his grip and laughed while you died I woke up with the feeling that I was at the end of my
rope it didn't work realized that I was you lost a heart the situation was bad and my life
hung in the balance but this was no time for reflection just make an unfinished FMV project and
have somebody else need to finish it in 30 years that's really funny well it would have
to be shot in 16 millimeter that's one of the things I'm going to make it really incredibly
incredibly clear if I'm if I were to do this it's being shot in 16 millimeter I don't care
how expensive it is this needs to be led that way it's going to be like two million dollars
fuck it I don't think it's gonna cost that much do 16 millimeter and then get it restored
wow now that's a big brain play that's a big brain play where'd you put somebody say cringe
all right uh we all we know this is easy all these are the same I was trying to think
of a diversion when I lost my footing the control started to slip away as the rope bit
into my neck have us pay for it do like a pay-per-view stream when I got up I saw that
the pipe had made quite an impression on laughing boy I wouldn't want to do okay here's what I
wouldn't want to do I wouldn't want to make it so people couldn't watch it even if that okay
let's say that this whole project if it was ever if it was ever done remember this is not
me saying it's happening I'm just saying that's I'm interested if it was oh here's an idea
we'll make the whole thing and then the stream will be you pay for the stream like a
pay-per-view stream no I want as many people to experience that as humanly possible
maybe do paid physical copies yeah I honestly I would not give a shit at all I mean obviously
I don't want to like lose like millions of dollars like that would be fucking devastating
I don't have millions of dollars that would be pretty bad maybe there's a way maybe
maybe I'll find a way all right what do you guys want to make yeah of course I told
laughing boy he was bound to be out of circulation for a while but he didn't
losing millions is really funny though no not really okay well all right this is where
it all goes completely off the rails what about getting it sponsored
yeah you don't know you're gonna get the sign it would need to be done with actors
shot on film I wanted to be old where we going I would make yourself an actor no I
would know I don't be the only actor I would be I would be in it for like 10 seconds
I'd be like the the old prospector that you run into like in a hallway somewhere
this is also pretty this is very unanimous look for some artifacts
the next room contained an old writing desk under the derhatchet family crest
on the desk were many items of interest did you get streamers to be actors no I don't
think so I don't want anyone I feel like okay I want them to be unknown I don't want
anyone to know who they are I wanted to be actors I wanted to be I'd like to be like
because here's the thing stuff like that would be really funny but let's just say it was like
streamer x it's no it's it's like streamer x playing character right it's not that's the
that's a monster on the screen so if I would ever do exactly the same reason why I said I
don't even want to be in it either like I would want to be in it for like 10 seconds
as like an easter egg I don't want to be in this I want to hire I want to like direct
actors right because then it's just oh look it's germa as this character you know I'm
saying so no it would be all just actors that we would be hiring and I'm talking like this is
happening soon but it's not if it did happen it would be like that all right uh taste the wine
we already know how to do this one we already know how to do this one why are you doing
this as I reached forward the candle lit itself and as if by magic a monk appeared
well this is a different option now play more of these games if you're a relatively new viewer
fold motion video games I've played almost all of them over the last five years or so
there actually aren't very many left that I haven't played some of the new ones I haven't
played the ones that have come out in the last year or two and we're going to be
dunk the flame in the wine oh yeah okay wish the candle and a glass of the house vino
and the phantom friar gave up the ghost at least the ones that looked like we'd have a good time
playing them right some fmv games that are very much meant to be taken very seriously
and it's not like oh my god look at how funny that was look at how bizarre of a scenario
that was it's just actors doing things in front of a camera so it's supposed to be
taken seriously and not like oh let's have a fun time and laugh at this
all right pocket the gold and split I think that's what it's going to be it is you guys
cannot make another mistake okay you want to go I don't want to say anything because it's
kind of close when is the baseball stream baseball stream is going to be at some point
in the first quarter or second quarter of next year somewhere when baseball is played
it was a theory that we might be able to get it done this year but it's not going
to happen too cold but that I refuse to not do that stream and what about grotto beasts
grotto beast actually let's do this right now I want to shout this out so grotto beasts I
can't give you a time or a date for that but I really really want you to be able to have
that stuff in your hands the physical cards in your hands by the latest quarter one of this
coming year I'm giving a huge window for that because it's very very possible that's
but I don't want to rush people on the work that they're doing so if you get it at some
point at the end of this year or January maybe you do but I'm not going to tell you that
because I don't want to put on just a dumb amount of pressure on people to have to get
stuff done that's I don't know I do not want to do that so whenever it's done
and whenever it's like okay it's ready to go and with that let's go ahead and talk about
this so the grotto beasts team as a twitter and they post various updates I actually just
retweeted them on Halloween here's the official grotto beasts twitter account let me put it in
the chat go give it a follow if you want to know more about grotto beast coming up
they post all the time all the various artists and here you go here is the official twitter of
the grotto beasts trading card game I was holding off on talking about this until it
was clear that we had sort of like an end goal of soon grotto beast nfts these are not nfts
but not there's not going to be an nft there won't be any grotto beast nfts this is you're
going to be able to hold these in your hand well not you get that it's a you're going to
be a whole it's cards you will be able to purchase and open for yourself packs of grotto
beasts by the way let's make this very clear too if you think that this was just going to
be a repackaged thing that I opened on the stream you are so wrong there's going to be
an astronomical more amount of cards and it's going to have a playable game behind it as well
you're actually going to be able to play this with people it's a real game have a game
designer and I hope you like it when it comes out because there's other stuff that I haven't
talked about yet with it too but you know what yeah fuck it let's just talk about it why
not hey I I'm the goddamn CEO okay um should I hold off on some stuff so the grotto beasts
card game is going to end up being a pretty significant uh when people talk about like
merch right oh what what should you do for merch should you do a t-shirt I could do
another t-shirt oh maybe I'll do a t-shirt maybe I'll do something else or maybe I'll
do like a toy or something in the grotto beast card game is going to be not just
grotto beasts it's not just going to be grotto beasts it's going to be tons and tons of this
channel's references characters it's going to be a gigantic crossover so it's not just simply
the grotto beasts there's potentially lots of other things too that you'll be able to have
and collect it's the biggest crossover event ever and it's two things that were created
on this same channel in this same community it's not even a crossover event it's the same goddamn
channel um so I've been pretty tight-lipped about this because I don't I didn't want to
like hype this up until I knew that it was going to start to become a thing so it's a
game you can actually play it you don't even have to he's losing viewers no stay don't please
don't leave please don't leave please what about people that were in the germa rumble
uh yes so that there's a lot of plans for like that project in the future maybe
just know that it's gonna have a lot of cards it's gonna be I don't want to talk too much
about it because I don't want to get anything wrong and community jake right now might be
fucking speed dialing me going like don't stop talking so I gotta be careful I don't
want to talk too much but follow that Twitter you're gonna get that's where
official updates will be on that Twitter what about t-shirts yeah they'll be merch
we'll have some merch are they gonna be different rarities don't right now jake is
fucking spam texting me stop talking stop talking what about a sunflower update um sure it's
November they're gone all right let's go back to this what did you get I don't even know
what you guys picked this is a nice get rich scheme no this is it it's me selling you
card packs get rich more scheme all right settle down settle down real life gotcha no
we're gonna okay community jakes gonna scream at me I'm gonna get screamed at on the phone
um there's gonna it's gonna be don't worry okay no I'm gonna I'm okay let's go there's
no NFTs associated with this what the fuck um I never said that what about EU I do I don't
I have no answer for that time I don't I currently do not have an answer for this time
I'm I think so I just can't give you an answer I don't know I do not have an answer
for this time and my phone just blew up uh I've got eight unread notifications on my phone
uh I see a stop sign emoji a hundred times okay I probably should um let's go ahead and
play the game what did you guys pick it was a I don't remember it I can't it was b all
right b let's go on the steps above me a green ghoul gestured gracefully I'm really really
excited for not just the fact that the grotto beast are really awesome but it's going to
be this interesting kind of mix of like a ton of references to this the last decade plus
of this channel and community it's a really interesting way I was hopeful to do merch and
we're going a proceed boldly I approached the zombie reluctantly and asked him who his tailor
was his response was to push him backwards into a rickety old freight elevator yeah you said
you end up going to do the germa joke plus two minus two futures market with channel
points that seems like a fun idea yeah I did but that's the problem this is why I get into
trouble I get in a lot of trouble because we okay I tell I tell you guys about four or five
different things that sound really interesting don't they but in reality only one or two of
those things can possibly be worked on so what ends up happening is you are like oh my god
he talked about like four or five different cool things going on when in reality one of these
things is actually going to work these are all things that I really want to do every time I
talk it's things that I really want to do but here's the thing right since the dollhouse stream
there's been some potential here to do more possibly maybe hopefully maybe find more people
that are willing to get on board and help us pay for projects and help us do things
some of these things are possible now because the dollhouse happened and the dollhouse was a
really really fun time so I can't tell you exactly what's going to happen because I still
don't even know but if some of these doors are starting to open a little bit more with
like okay now people are aware that I want to do big projects and I need capital and I need
people and I need um more crew members and stuff right like this is all stuff that's
knowledgeable to a lot of people now so if I can get some of these things to help make
these projects come faster that's what I'm gonna do networking Andy well you bet your ass that
I want to try to make some of these things a reality right and if they do become a reality
that's what makes me happy I don't care about anything else I really don't I don't give a
shit about anything else I could not make a single dollar from any of the projects
none of them zero I would not give a flying fuck at all I wouldn't care at all I don't care
if they if the projects can be paid for and I don't have to worry about it then fucking
perfect that's exactly what I want I don't care he's lying by the way I'm not I swear
I promise you I don't care you've seen okay you've seen the leak I don't even need to
tell you that like we've made jokes about it before do I really need to make a shitload of money
on each project because I'm I have to no I don't care I'm for 98 yeah I'm not a liar says the
lie yeah all right I am a liar I'm a liar but not in not on important stuff like this I'm not
trying to make a bunch of money I'm trying to have things be paid for right that I'm
I hear about and sometimes people will hear about some of the how much some of this
these projects costed right holy shit it was that much money yeah I I it kind of sometimes
it has to be but don't get do not give me any money I'm seeing people give money don't do that
stop giving me money right now I demand it somebody's give me a hundred dollars
thank you for the do not do not give me any money stop that immediately I command it I
demand it it ends at once where we going stop reverse engineer Andy I'm just saying all right
just know in the future whatever projects we do I'm just I'm glad that they were able to happen
that's it just think about this thing this is like the kind of shit that I've wanted to do
since I was like fucking 12 right I cannot even begin to tell you guys just how how it
feels to like something that I wanted to do when I was 11 you are 12 like I am I'm really
I'm living every single one of my fantasies from when I was a kid it's unbelievable to me
and the fact that I'm able just to do that alone just just by itself is worth more than
anything anything so the fact that I can sit here and talk like this is already enough
just want to be clear Jesus fucking Christ just play the game already I just I just had a
major announcement come on I just talked about the grotto beast that's a major announcement
I'm from I'm going I'm going I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm going I thought it was a major
announcement I have a major announcement and I don't want to be oh look at me I'm so good
oh I don't I don't care about money I'm the good guy I'm a good guy no I don't want to do
that either all right okay I'm gonna go we're gonna go I'm a fucking bad guy all right I'm
the bad guy don't worry what'd you guys pick surprise me I don't want to be like a preachy
asshole either well you know I'm so much better than I look at what I do look I don't
care about only me oh I'm the only one that cares about not receiving a monitor I'm the
only one no I don't want you to think that either I love money okay here we go all right
walk straight this I don't think I've done this before the next room I came to had nothing
in it there was an old freezer on one side and a wall full of potions on the other
just as I started to examine them I heard a scream open the freezers the correct play
we've all seen it like five times already although there's opening the freezer stop
whatever the laughing screaming person coming in the room I think Coolsville sucks just open
the freezer ignoring the fumes I opened the freezer I love this guy uh can I just do this
on my own because I know how to get there please do okay hey man you don't want to be
messing with those chemicals man they're bad for your karma I read the labels extra strength
potion instant steak pill anti-grav tablets okay uh so it's the take the steak leave
I wasn't hungry now but an instant steak might come in handy later where's your choice
that's what everybody was gonna pick all right this is it's a and then you leave these are
both this is gonna kill us so don't don't be don't be stupid about this thank you hey man
like I don't mean to be rude you know but like there's something in here that smells
almost worse than I do you know he did have a point
that noise at the end uh yeah we gotta get out of this room it's your one year
anniversary with the sus face I want a divorce I gave him five dollars and left all right
this is a tough call because I don't remember exactly which one of these means you get
grabbed but how do you feel about the rats becoming extremely popular and tiktok
sorry say that again say that one more time I didn't hear that that well say that again
I want you to say that again the rats are incredibly popular on tiktok the rats are
huge on tiktok excuse I'm sorry I'm leaning with my ear say that one more time what did
we talk about like a few weeks ago what that I I am huge on tiktok and I'm not even there
so I'm excuse me I'm just trying to understand why everyone was saying that
that was not accurate the rats are also huge on Facebook all right let's search the room the
rats are popular not you bozo as I ran into the next room I heard the scream
again I am the rats the rats are nothing without me should I make a tiktok video of
doing the rat song but make sure I'm doing it really poorly and I'd be pretty relatively
unknown on tiktok would people like hate me for it would be like oh that was terrible
nice try my video is way better on the tick on the rats meme it's like I'm I'm the one
who made it talking you talking to the guy that made it up keep moving forward why you're
not actually gonna do this are you I ran through the door and found myself near the elevator
oh I thought you fall I pushed the button and waited there was a green door to my left
and a stairway to my right okay I know for a fact that we don't do the green door
this is a really important decision but I'm just kidding I scramble up the stairs
is it time to release release release is it time to release the third rat song
I wonder if we're gonna get to the end at the top of the stairs I saw an ugly dwarf
private eye versus private eye gory how tall am I okay show them your license take evasive
action and put down that shovel take evasive action when he moved I jumped over the railing
it was a long way to the first floor and laughing boy was no help at all
that would hurt so bad holy shit that was painful looking I think you guys are in some
trouble here grab his shirt and pull punch with your stronger hand or let go of the
railing grab his shirt and pull is winning by a way too much I grabbed his shirt and he flipped
over the railing symbol crash the second floor looked dark and uninviting okay where we go I
told my friend who used to work with a company that helped with this game and he thought that
it was crazy that you were playing it I mean it's we're having a great time the last one
too I applaud the companies that actually tried to restore this stuff this is awesome
I'm having a lot of fun ask your friend how to beat the game all right we're going I don't know
it's 5142 a and c if it were me I would probably pick the one that we didn't do yet
which is probably whatever medical records so and that's winning right now so that's what
I'm gonna pick the room I next entered was obviously a library of some sort well kitchen
regardless I'm gonna get the garlic there was a door to my left another dead ahead
but most of the action was taking place in the kitchen on my right where someone was
practicing a bizarre form of culinary preparation but we don't necessarily have to do the kitchen
but the garlic seems pretty important huh yes the library kitchen I couldn't put my finger
on it but there was something odd about the woman in the kitchen if you're hungry get it
it's really cold in this room I think you see the breath coming out do you see that do you see just
how cold it is in there I feel bad for the actor uh yeah we look in the we're gonna look
in the fridge of course uh find other edibles we've gotten this right plenty of times
make the fmv game and make sure there's no references to you in it no there won't be
it would be it would be I mean well there'd be you'd probably know I made it somehow but
this would not be a like germa 985 fmv experience it'd be like an old western
game or something like an old horror game inside the cupboard was a rose a clove of garlic
and a couple of potatoes what are we doing don't tell us you made it and just play it one day
well I think it would be really fun if the first experience ever with the game
was on the stream and you guys are doing this maybe we'll build like an extension or
something I have like some kind of use of an extension for you guys to do it easier
so you guys will get the first experience of the game and then I reached in and took
the clove of god a week later or something it goes on steam or whatever stop giving him
the idea he only cares about money I care about money I don't only care about money
money's somewhere on the list somewhere take the potato I feel like I'm gonna get hurt
I you guys really I think A is you took too much die and we get stabbed
this is a gg I think yeah all right well
what the hell I came to here I am it's me I took all the things
was sitting across the attic from me at long last the detective decides to pay a bit
hypnotic effect this doesn't matter oh I feel like we've met before
you don't know me but I know you that's my favorite shot of the whole thing when he's
kind of leaned over you all said A anyways I want this guy it's something I picked out
close to your heart that was my blood he was sucking on this character okay this is
actually important I want that exact character in another game find something of value I should
have the coins quickly I checked my pockets okay throw a gold coin that's the only option
that probably results in something different that's a different video clip let's try it
I threw it in his mouth expecting him to choke to death what but instead
very tasty when I looked in his eyes I knew I had failed I was powerless to resist him
it was so stupid that sucked that sucked it was a great throw but Jesus okay you guys
want one more chance at this I'm gonna give you one more chance but let's get to the end
I know you can do it collectively I know you can is there another FMV I have this I have one more
that's ready for right now but it's new and I don't know I'm not sure if I want to do it
right now it looks like it might be long depends on how long it is is it the battle
royale one omega lol it is why are you saying that omega lol omega lol omega lol no
chance what do you mean fortnight is not an FMV dude it's short all right well let's try it
this I this is really fun though I like this a lot it's only been three hours um excuse me
it's been four hours excuse me we'll try it let's exit this that was the specter files death
stalker was that was great I had a lot of fun hopefully I gotta turn this down because it
might be very loud what's it called blood shore blood shore let's give it a roll
let's change the game uh I cannot capture it why not yeah this is like it's it's a
like squid game well it's like live it's to viewers squid game type shit I don't know
why can I not capture this oh there it is okay all right this is uh this this looks kind of
right this is bright at least the subtitles can be on what streamer mode oh yeah it's kind of
bright isn't it uh set those on medium subtitle background uh borderless window streamer mode
you can pause choices I don't think German knows what squid game is I've I've seen squid
game I've seen the whole show all right you ready name one character fine pop culture Andy
you're a fucking pop culture Andy pop culture Andy name one squid
yeah see it's this game it's this game with a handful of squids they have a bunch of squids
they get to come in and have and all of them have some type of money problem I don't want
to give I don't want to give anything away watch this show bye I was really high when I
watched the whole thing so I don't even know anybody I don't remember any I don't remember
the plot either the front I know I don't want to say that because that could be a spoiler
I know who the uh you heard me say some words there and you know that was the character
you heard me say it's that I just said something I you heard it you I you I know that
character is no I don't want to give spoilers away can I just say the main character's name
do I say the main character's name get off the IMDb page I I the main character's name is squid
word okay just quiet the following content seems that some of you may find disturbing
is not suitable for younger audiences including graphic depictions of violence blood and death
viewer discretion is get out of here kids yeah oh my god I just have my hand hurts
oh the squid game name one character I fucking god damn it it takes now you know I didn't see
it I'm just pretending to because I want people to think I know what I'm doing the ultimate
prize I want people think I know pop culture and shit I haven't seen one episode
I've seen the whole show I can name 10 characters I just don't want to
you ready
can a mod change this to blood sure see it is like squid game I told you
kill stream now entering its 13th season has been criticized by human rights experts
for its brutality having claimed the lives of 210 of its 470 contestants thus far
showrunners Alan Kroll claimed that all contestants are fully aware of
all right I know where I can get it I got it
volunteers they chose to be in this arena volunteers please they're desperate
poor brainwashed often completely unstable my agent says it's gonna be really good for my
career any problems these good problems you're right many would argue that the
corporation is abusing its position of power to take advantage of the destitute and are
responsible in large part for the cutthroat society we live in Eugene Kristoff when you
created the show you put the world's deadliest death row inmates on an island to battle to
the death the winners of the first few seasons have become some of the wealthiest people in
the world yes is that justice I guess I have what it took death or glory in the past few
years who do we play as have risen in line with the economic downturn what could do
everyone these people are a byproduct of the society created by you some would say
you're a coward having tapped out they can say that's my face you have been inundated
with applications they have been ground into dust by the boot heel of the rich and powerful
who are now using them for their own entertainment socialist mother if I didn't know
any better Chris I'd say you were accusing me of exploiting the poor I'm not the only
person to find your show utterly abhorrent have you ever fired before the terms are
agreed upon by both parties I've got to be playing a game to witness deaths on television
since the beginning of time man's been pitted against his fellow man in combat
surely we've evolved from a more barbaric time I'm not so sure we have
we play as one of these people people want they keep watching what the fuck they're like
instagramming this shit I'm not gonna lie carlott influencer 207 000 followers
mom dad don't sweat this is it people it doesn't get any real than this auto
strike royale player 400 000 followers holy shit for life nick 900 000 followers
to find an ally early helps keep you alive through the chaos of the first few rounds
no alone only I don't trust anybody none of you sounds like that would get complicated
gav extreme vlogger 87k I don't want to get stuck with that ass fish video game
streamer 40 000 followers game streamers shooters mainly should come in handy
what about the cannibal life is all or nothing yeah you know that I'm our people out there
don't you know you just lost half your subscribers in the last six months
microphone anything to do with this this what's with a huge microphone travel vlogger
we all know it's time for the world to see I'm going to be streaming the truth why is everybody
British I don't know maybe it was made in my mind when you really set all this up
my money is still on the pedo ring Ari 200 000 followers podcaster so what's your story
oh streamer mode okay okay guys so what do you think I should do here honest I think
it's a good it's a really good play discreet not so sure about that one
dude I'm gonna be discreet for the same reasons as everyone else you're kidding me
that's nick fucking romeo wait i feel is it who you didn't watch the mikey lizard
what are these people do I hate the least I wonder are you just trying to get the most
extreme streamer can well you can't get more extreme than this some say the first one of
these was sent on Jeffrey Epstein's island who knows we'll find out one way or another
Ari out participation at the edge of the drop zone don't we have should we have oxygen masks
I have no idea how this works guys I do too soon you're in the sea do too late well
you're about to jump out the perfectly good airplane how's real about that
so you have too much testosterone here huh move your cursor what if there's a decision
that's what they say about he who hesitates what a fucking loser what oh they the audience
is not on board with me right now all right so it's just it's you just whatever it takes
to win right I gotta sabotage somebody's parachute right wait hold on okay Ricky
pro gamer 32 000 followers why is he not pulling his cord damn son oh no we didn't even get to
hear that guy talk track how you're doing from the pause menu press escape tracker team morale
audience opinion romance strength and insight really okay let's go he dead he'll live
unlucky for us then I'm very confused why don't we just meant to use your parachute
how come we're not just killing each other I did from like right now
immediately that's this is a pub G doesn't work like this everybody runs around finds like a
fucking frying pan starts killing each other instantly it'd be over in five seconds someone
runs around till they find a gun and just start shooting everybody I take it back Mikey
you did all right one down 49 to go really we don't get disqualified for this right
listen on us yeah hey can you send me that we just qualified a hundred thousand watching now
I had last season's finale at over a hundred million concurrent viewers don't work it I'll make
sure a million concurrent viewers that's like five cut that out come on that's enough no way
look how many people are watching this kid watching this could be the season's first
fatality take the camera off they came with their chill this kid watching seriously let's
head to camp it's like five billion people watching at the end of the day you should head
in 100 million concurrent viewers is like billions of people watching over the course of a day
look sharp people you're on camera here we go kill stream 13 live re-streaming it post
framing it
kill talk extreme vloggers psychopaths and wolf boys have we got a season of kill stream in
store for you we'll be checking in with our viewers and getting your thoughts on this year's
contestants a hot favorite going in nick wolf boys sure he's a team player does he have
that's the funniest thing so far
our contenders will spend the night on the island before this so
grab a drink and settle in because the countdown starts now there's a category wrong
I was on this oh no it's it's good yeah of course you were blood sure
oh we have to spend a night seriously what is this this isn't the island that's different
there's different every time warm sandy beaches didn't we show up on a beach
oh you might want to be careful where you stand they're everywhere what did make light of the
situation kaboom they're smart minds they're using of course players close to each other
keeps the game interesting must be hundreds of thousands that explains why they couldn't
afford to send us to the bahamas so we have to stay close to each other and we all know
what it's like anything to get the views my agent's gonna hear about this who cares
we're not here for a vacation someone's gonna step on one of those probably really soon
what's this where's the beach house you're not catching on are you
if they die in the game they die in real life come on no dude it's not that bad
fucking paradise it's like vr spending six weeks in the rainforest with nothing
no shelter except what you make for yourself
why some of this food here at least it's four weeks in the amazon
what's that there there's no beds here you don't even know where here is he's right judging
by the foliage and i could give up fuck survivor man it's probably just a bird
i'm gonna be sipping water you check it out then fine i'll go look for i'll go see
i'm drinking water and i'm gonna be drinking i'm gonna eat and be in like cliff bars
our hero is it i'm not touching anything else hello motherfuckers
what took you so long care to join me where's the view count another no no i'm good no i'm not
i'm gonna have be as close to as i can to reality i'm not getting inebriated at all
hey nick what are you doing here like i mean you must have done all right after them movies
you're kidding there's all worked in years got fucked over by the studio
why don't you mind your own business sorry man i saw it on tlz
i betson who dies first okay uh here we go at nine a.m i need to get some sleep well they've
introduced the comedy guy they give the word and we go at it so he's absolutely gonna last at
least 20 minutes killing each other tonight comedy guy might die first in a funny way right
because they might go the comedy guy dies first funnily i'm saying comedy guy for the
early rounds watch each other's backs through the crazy part and then what we're still breathing
we'll deal with it then i guess like turning into the night yeah this guy right here he's
first well i mean teaming up i mean of course you are that's not for me i don't play team
games we can play team game all right let's let's get a team thing going the final 10
or go down first well like we said it's complicated we're gonna do we're gonna team exercise
it's common sense no one fucks with a group the bigger the better for now
what no way chicken dinner all the way no chance what you're gonna win yeah why not me who wins
okay um you can definitely not be me i'm because i'm the main character i can't win
they have got you all food i'll be making a sacrifice at the end of the game for me to die
and it's just the playground what on earth are you talking about paddy power it's all fake for
tv no one believes in god anymore i need another 10 minutes the new church opiate for the masses
allen core rumba the russians or the illuminati definitely the fucking illuminati
like just a bunch of fucking old white men making the rules whoever's the quietest person
what do you mean where was like a fucking clan rally uh hello wasn't the creator of kill
stream black yeah where is he now you're just paranoid you know there's lots of other
landing groups and now he's dead yeah he's dead first you know calling me paranoid he's
gonna say he's gonna step on a landmark baby of course you're gonna kill the fake news guy
first right you're going to there's no way he survives 20 10 more minutes
ah come on it's better than having a death wish i'd sleep with one eye open if i was
especially with Hannibal over there i mean you know the story don't it
what is a survival blogger he spent four weeks deep in the amazon bay this guy's
gonna last a while i think found themselves in trouble got separated from the support crew
we found dev alive and well should have starved to death would have starved to death
his partner didn't come back no exposition well that what do you think we were playing
apparently he came back three kilos heavier
oh he'll be so hungry when does the battle royale start they said that there was going
to be one night where they literally explained some of the characters
they can't just start killing people they need to give you some backstory of people one night
and then we start to go kill screen the jury's still out on who are these people yeah why was
there was was it a kid come in i've landed on the island location unknown you knew about this
who am i talking to location changes last minute nothing and now that i have do you
know where i am we are currently unable to get your coordinates gps on your device has been
blocked it's great and what about extractions you at least have a plan to get me out of this
place you have not seen squid game i want you to mute mute for a second i'm gonna prove that
i've seen this show my neck mute if you haven't seen squid game mute i'm gonna prove that i've
seen the show safe you don't even know where i am i need some goddamn proof you can help me
i am gonna spoiler for squid game turn stop listening for a second five four three two one
oh you've never seen this good game before i've never seen this good game before what about
the doctor just said what are you the doctor thing yeah what's going on with that yeah okay
so i've never seen it like this is what i'm watching right now out of here i've seen it
what happened all right everyone can come back it's now safe make a joke i don't i
don't i wasn't even listening what i just told you i'd have to kill you're being too vague i don't
want to be no i don't just spoil television shows okay what's that i need to get i want to give
like a full 30 seconds for the broadcast should we open it why open it it's probably
something i'm i'm opening it i want it whatever it is what's every in there okay
30 minutes to show time time to get dolled up oh we hit the show hadn't even started yet
where are the other starting soon screen he's gonna go step on a mine that's gone good that guy was
creepy af he's gonna step on a mine i'm telling you this one too i'm telling you what's up
like you'd luck with dev going somewhere yeah let's go around he's gonna go shit on a mine
is that what you do in war of duty what no he's a camper what's that he's a pussy
plans himself in cover and waits for the other way this is a camper
hope he dies first sounds like a pretty good idea to me it's bullshit i never camp
let's screw this i'm scouting the area oh yeah get to the weapons drops first more like
excuse me you heard me what the fuck is your they drop weapons do you think this is a game
guys go on then leave get out before i use your head for fucking target practice
fuck this i'm not staying here with this fucking psycho react uh i there's no way i'm
siding with a camper i'm just making that really clear if you're not gonna be a team
player i don't see this working dude come on fine totally fine team i'm a little fucking
bullshit look at me ouch react harder he didn't side with germa auto cool i'm practically
observing whoo react dude hurry up there's a weapon drop nobody changes channels this
fast you have to spend at least 10 seconds to see what it is doesn't you know the double
double double double double double cross the animal style double cross the animal style double
double double cross i need to make sure everybody here i'm not a threat to anybody
but i'm a threat to everyone i thought it was going to be the one with the uh ipad
the korean no that was uh that's it classic oh oh oh here come good morning island let's cut
to the chase you know why you're here 50 contestants split up into six landing groups
spread around the island your task is to survive oh wait there's more than us oh shit i was
about to kill all these people
i thought it was just us like six who do you think you're teaming up against
holy shit imagine not paying attention to the first five minutes in the plane
i would have picked a brick up and started hitting people in the head really last night
and tap out why not what does that mean what the fuck that's right you're all in it to win it
no rescues no tactical drugs this year you've got to give it your all this is insane you
will shortly receive your first weapons drops not too far from your current position so move
fast with half the planet watching you right now you're already a superstar now go put on a
show bastards they can't do that i signed a contract you'd be the first one to die did you
read it i mean i did it wasn't exactly binding on their parts fuck you i'm calling my agent
attempt to inspire the team let's all right let's come to bring it together no no guys come on we
got to keep it together this is just what they want panic ah they didn't listen whatever fuck
them you're all getting bricked tomorrow night anyways let's go get those weapon drops
what a loser oh they hate me now what's a loser what a loser
don't ever underestimate the underdog he can't surprise you tish call it camping but we should
do we lay low and ride it out did the weapons crates drop you know i just checked the map
we should be right on top of it why are kids watching this and why are kids analysts about
this yeah i don't understand the mr president trump lives this guy's dead first i'm telling
you i'm telling you he's dead he's dead instantly he's gonna he's gonna die very soon in less
than 10 minutes how do we know how to use these kill her now no i'm not gonna now that
i know that we're a team um wait which one doesn't work i don't remember is the one on
just okay is it my left or is my right um the the the thing i'm switching the poison on myself
i don't want to do this is it my gun on right like this one or gun on my left it's your left
so it would be this one is left and left is the one that does not work
so i'm gonna give her this one okay these are all pretty old
she'll only use them if we need to they're screwed that one works damn it that one works
i'm gonna give away a location oh shit i reversed the poison on myself i actually did the thing
from prince's bride i freaked out i thought it hurts me should we you know get back investigate
don't shoot i'm not armed where's your landing group i'm on my own or shit i overshot the
landing been out here all night where where are your bruises where are your scratches horse
shit shoot him shoot him yeah i shoot him seriously man you don't want to do this
shoot him shoot him no scratches no i probably shouldn't have done that should i have done
that i just oh i just landed no scratches no bruises oh yeah i just landed away from
my group yeah right look around they're out here they're probably hiding they did
yep and he had a gun thank you everybody wants to say i'm a psycho i just saved the
goddamn team this guy's fucking dead news guys this shit's fucking real it's fucking
real hesitation is defeat you know everyone's gonna come after you now in no time at all
now it's getting interesting no if everyone's look that's the thing if you landed away from
your group you're not going to hide behind a tree and approach another group choco boy 89
says it's a little landing not a chance in hell why would you sneak up on another group
that's not gonna happen i did what i had to do anything in camo camo's so in right now
really you never see it anywhere seriously though what is this shit these guns are almost antique
we should head for the center see that what about it it's got to be something it's not
in the muck exactly there's a bridge up ahead from there we can either go straight through
or we can go around i don't know straight ahead i feel like everyone's going to be going around
nobody wants to do the straight shot because as well it's too far in the open we don't want
to be too exposed but isn't everybody going to be going around i think it's straight on i say
we go straight through let's go see if we can catch someone off guard no we go the other way
yeah it makes sense we shouldn't say the risk are you serious i didn't just get telltale
did i have the trust of his teammates what's it gonna take to pull this back oh wait they
don't trust me it's actually a meter oh shit they won't listen to me that's actually kind of
interesting it's illusion of choice but it's not really an illusion of choice is this a team
morale meter and they would have listened to me if i if i didn't they didn't hate me or
something i don't know what's the difference between a liberal and a puppy a puppy stops
whining when it grows up landmine here comes the landmine or maybe they're gonna keep
them around long enough to like make everybody like hate him and then they'll kill him i don't
know i'm just gonna keep walking by the way let's talk strategy here if you make it out give me
a call why would you ever talk like that with your teammates in a life or death scenario where
you need to like have each other's backs but i i feel i feel like if you don't want your
teammates to like fucking hate your guts regardless of any of this right why would you
why would you do that everybody is like hating this guy and he's like i'm being like political
and i look like a dick isn't it ha ha look at me like why wouldn't you want to like have
your back with your teammates this is a life and death scenario with everybody here guys
did you not prepare for this at all whoa easy now just run out what the fuck did you find
any what's going on here i saw something up ahead like a building looks like some kind of
what's with the blood you're getting some trouble don't point the gun back at your face
that was really bad so fucking psychopaths out there one less now um i i what why do you
have blood all over your face i mean it's very very it's very very very odd that would
be that high like okay have you shot somebody like and they sprayed blood it would be like
here here here here she's blood like on her face up here why that's very that's that's a
little odd i don't you need to explain this here what you seem awfully eager to get us this
outpost what's waiting there you know what fuck you hey hey is this the doubt is this the
fuck you nick you're all fucked anyway good luck so what's the plan maybe we should camp
am i using that right aren't we supposed to be on the same team look is she working with another
team that was really weird you have blood on your mouth weird i don't know about that
if it were me if i had blood all over my mouth it'd be like look guys let me explain why
there's blood all over my mouth listen to me you're camping right now anything to fucking
nice oh what i gave oh shit it's the um that's that was the broken gun that was the broken gun
no i'm saying i'm not getting up i'm such a coward no i have to no no no no i'll do it
i'll do it i'll do it i'll do it i'll do it hold on wait wait wait i'm gonna get up
i'm gonna get up i'm gonna get up i'm gonna get up
oh fuck you here comes a team wipe hey what does someone with blue blood taste like anyway
this is easy easy you took the good you took the good gun and didn't even use it oh
oh oh man i feel really bad i feel awful this is bad i need to redeem myself right now
where the fuck did they go i stop oh i don't know oh thank god streamer mode okay guys so
we got three seconds left and i gotta be honest i'm really not so sure what i should do
i'm thinking that gav has experience with potential uh survival skills but tish had
a lot of big brain ideas i'm not so certain about this though she had some i think she's
probably it's probably to keep the smart person tish tish suspects me oh shit she does you were
acting sus you've been acting sus towards tish if you save her then she should trust you again
but tish had a headshot that's right that's right um what but i feel like i haven't heard
very much from from gav in fact people saying who is gav so just because of that
i think we have to that's it
gav is not the annoying guy that's a good job i followed you down
i could work on the bridge there you really showed them it's your lucky day
dev the cannibal has cornered his own landing squad and that creative reuse of minds means
gav sees his final destination tish tasker and nick romeo he did get a headshot that was the
deciding factor for me that's what put me over the edge i forgot about her arms skills
tish led you to the bomb trap though looks like the mines they must have figured out
a way to reuse them the heck i might be impressed with my
ears stop ringing oh shit she's injured see what happened to the others i didn't see shit
i think scarlet went down and you shoot out though where are we oh thank god we're five
miles inland you should have stayed with auto fuck yeah well look what is it he said he was
a camper he okay got louder i just turned it over this it kills me turn that off why
you are too though well if somebody wants to decide on taking me over somebody else then
you know not to take the camper you know it's great to be part of a real team i think you
made the right choice fucking jesus christ good woman what the fuck stop what's wrong with
everybody now you're a star you gotta shoot everybody over here sorry shoot everybody
is she's alive what's going on zombie what the fuck we hear a kill stream would like to
apologize to scarlet's friends and family let's take a moment now in remembrance of her life
moving on i'm glad i got the mature stream warning on this one holy fucking moly looks
that was fast we saw where his heart was right at the christopher that was fucking scarring yeah
that was fucking horrible like forever changed from that one let's stop watching tv you've also
broadened it out actually good effects though not very realistic but pretty good i mean that
was fucked up you want another drink yeah how many people are even left on our team
nick slow down let's take a breather there's something up ahead can we please stop playing
this um i mean there's only two of us left what what what are you looking for you need to tell
me what's going on that headcase ari was almost right throw for content i actually have not
about that but this game is fixed what do you mean winners picked out before the game begins
how guns are real the mines are real how could you possibly stop someone from getting killed
it's not a sure thing but from what we can tell what are you saying it's fake
i'm too speed i'm not here to win tish you need to stop i've been sent here by a group
called the alliance they've sent me here to expose the truth that the corporation used
deep fake technology to rig the outcome of kill street with a deep fake stuff computer
generated scenarios they can alter the broadcast in real time to make things play out the way
they want why why can't they just let it play out the winner's a puppet all the fame
and power that come from winning this thing can be controlled if they know who the winner is
alan corp are fucked they've been hemorrhaging money for years they're on the deep faking people
dying cost of running this meat grinder adds up the bribes the countries that host it the
jurisdictions that broadcast it the lawsuits from the contestants estates them with audiences
dwindling they had to come up with a plan so they started fixing it we're not sure when
but when the creator left their big changes behind the scenes the winners always became big
all the way up to the top and then all the way to the top man decided to change that
with the winners in their pockets they managed to keep things afloat for a while longer
but now they're getting desperate that's why the rules keep getting more brutal
so you were being serious about the no tap ups they're doing it to boost the ratings
and the puppet who is it i'm not sure yet it's him sure it's um it's i'm the bad guy
probably right it's me who's i talking to on the phone before on the walkie-talkie
it's me it's gonna be me you're here to expose all of this how why do you be like
not bad and send you let's just say i have a reason to hate alan corp we're all getting
deep faked the alliance knew this and it was a safe bet my this is the last thing i'm playing
before i'm starting streaming they gave me this device a payload that i need to plant in the
corporation's network if they can get in they can hijack the stream expose it all the deep fakes the
fix everything so why are you telling me this why isn't the alliance helping you who's the
no something goes up they switched locations at the last moment who's the known animal
last dream ever what no i'm saying just for today what about gps our phones blocked
this all signals in and out of this place go through alan corp's network
we're almost done ice was meant to be vulnerable to their control but the blast back there must
have knocked it out i need to find a way in the alan corp's network a comms tower maybe
i can find a way to get a message out we can find out where the fuck they're going to kill
you gotta be something i didn't say this was bad they're streaming from all these drones 24
seven let me see that even if the radio is broken we should be able to get some info from
the storage i'm not dying on this fucking island for nothing do i do i trust her what do you think
i don't know i don't think so i'm gonna keep hold of it for now they keep just doing the
double cross thing no okay it's getting dark if there is a predetermined winner it could be
anyone you have another tower then we know that so what if it's just her we should take it
in turns keeping watch and tell them to stop cursing please toss a point no need
you're concerned about cursing you sure and there was just like a gruesome scene with
somebody's like face like blown off may as well have the conversation how'd you end up here
that's complicated answer why not not much call for an aging child actor i didn't make the
transition you bleep the swears sure tv and film that all changed i will do that for you
reality killed the tv store while you're breaking my heart mikey
you blame the corporation for that you missed it you remember the other nick
nicky murk you guys do like a double f for one what we're doing on a shelf life
this hollywood chews you up and spits you out when you do anything you can to stay on top i'm
waiting i'm trying to get it so he did kill stream season six it's all starting to make
sense drinking drugs made him a different person made him feel invincible he thought
this was the only way out deep fake it is for some of us i'm sorry i didn't mean
someone tipping the scales so here i am
um the ad revenue for my channel since i've been in here that's gotta be something for them right
what do they think of all this i told them be hard for them to miss by now though
oh my god all right this i haven't had a complaint about this game until right now
this is way too long you're sleeping in the subway station i thought you didn't watch those
movies come on they were everywhere when i was a kid of course they were to those movies
don't wait don't kiss or kiss don't kiss or kiss we can kiss we can we can kiss i guess
are we going to both be kissing each other premarital kissing gross so what happens if
you have a romance in this movie game thing i don't understand all right don't we need to
don't do it put a sensor bar on okay oh there soldier let's get some sleep okay if it all right
if it was attempt kiss or don't i wouldn't have done that unbelievable tish tasker and nick romeo
are still in the game there's more than meets the eye with these two see i thought it was like
this is this will happen do not attempt in a what or this will happen
lucky son of a bitch slippery fucker kelvin you heard he's keeping on him
don't worry buddy i'll look after you hello how are you that phone was terrible
now this is why i did i mean what's going on here why what's up where were you where'd you get to
what that what was really suspect never mind that was weird we should get moving yeah oh god
damn it no i don't trust anybody calvin right you're not calvin biggs are you oh my god it
is you you were in america's most wanted right hey there was a crying shame what they did
goddamn lame stream media and their goddamn witch hunts i mean so what if you took a bus
out of school kids hostage you only killed the teacher you're sure you saw something
i thought i might have seen an antenna okay what's this about an antenna oh don't even think
about it no we were wrong i'm sorry i was very wrong six could taking you both down
then why didn't you douchebag the math like that just might auto i'm so sorry
hey can we start over you were listening we need to work together that's not what you said to me
last time we met look i'm so sorry you said you were a camper in um call of duty whatever it
was there's more going on here than you know lower the gun let's talk camping is a really
good strategy it keeps your kill death high you get to enjoy the game you can eat a
sandwich while you're playing you don't have to have two hands the controller i mean that's
a pain in the ass what's the difference between this island and a dead prostitute
uh auto hears me saying auto and is walking over here now hello auto well it's a different
auto not you this island still sucks now we get a new party why don't get is if they can
fake bits of it why not fake the whole thing why bother going to the expense of hosting it
in the first place so let's let's get auto involved here too many variables all the drama
power struggles randomness of people is hard to script plus i don't know whether you notice but
seriously cutting you want 50 auto cam 50 game that everybody apparently hates that i'm streaming
that and there's just too many people involved by the time i start fixing this shit
trust a handful of people at the top to stay quiet they've got the most to lose
the winner's gonna keep their mouth shut but what about everyone else
let's see if i can get it so who is it you know the puppet the winners ari seems to think it was all
fake you know he really believed it maybe he was onto something maybe it's you mysteriously
popping up after an explosion one foot in one foot out of the group seems a bit suspicious
could be anyone he needs something i've got my suspicions but he's hungry
no you hungry fingers it could be more than one for all we know
west i'm gonna take them out and give them a little snack and then that's where i saw the
building 50 auto my promise has to be something so you get to a part where i can freeze it
there you go all right uh this is gonna be the last brb of the night i'll be right back
and then we'll have a 50 auto cam let's see how if the auto cam will work auto cam okay um
if he sits down let's see i don't 50 auto cam okay well you want you can't see the game
okay can you see the game cooking down to the final 10 who cares about the game this tension
with a spoon nick romeo is still and what do you think in your party maybe there's still hope
maybe the pieces are just too small this is strange they're not showing anything
bullshit what the fuck is going on the show's really gone downhill oh the show's gone downhill
that's two clicks west just past those trees past the mines we're just gonna get through
the field isn't there another way around the river mines around the island is 200 meters
oh no i don't this open ground it gives us an advantage so you're on like a bright red blanket
how can someone who joined this is way too suddenly be so risk averse it doesn't contrast
well at all i don't know it's better than fumbling around in the dark just hoping to come
across something okay what are our options well there's one thing that i think might live
auto reaction go on well you said those guys use the mines to blow up the bridge
yeah that means one of those assholes has figured out how to rig those mines to blow
up on command that means it can be hacked if they can be hatched figure out how they're
itchy head so what we take a live mine and deactivate oh he's hitting his ear that sounds
like it's gonna take forever not only for the first one these mines are smart which means
it's probably part of a mesh network they send a signal to arm disarm from mine to mine
if i can figure out how to break one of these guys security i can maybe disarm the whole
thing at least the area we're in wow that sounds like a long shot okay then fuckers
why don't you go grab a big stick and get ready to prod and poke your way through the next 200
meters of open ground meter by meter i'm sure there's no risk there at all i haven't
been paying any attention to this what happened uh auto's plan i don't even i don't even know
what it is i'm just gonna do it come on then nerd his auto is here get your mind to play
are you fucking kidding me he's gonna blow himself up
fuck it i guess he wouldn't be that big of a loss anyway whoa whoa whoa what are you doing
it's auto's plan i was gonna have the mine i need a computer
don't want to make sure it's not sending out anything that can track us
here itchy what's around here itchy you're itchy here he actually um had an ear problem
i needed to put this stuff in his ears this is a bad idea
he's okay though i should do it how do we know if it works well if i walk over here
actually there's an ear for him everything within a three meter radius should be disabled
he had to get this little goo put in both his ears try it you fucking try it you're holding
it was 75 auto careful wait what if i was gonna go to sleep what the fuck was that
holy shit you're fucking idiot it didn't work oh really at least i gave it a go
you nearly got us killed not to mention wasted our time and the game in the corner
we'll have to move fast what's pan b again what's that keep the pace it doesn't matter
step on the mine we're just as dead concentrate on what we're doing 85 auto 10 movie five percent
face cam there all right hold on there's people like aiming at me
i'm sorry i'm like ruining this whole game i'm sorry i got out of that alive i didn't do
anything i told you that was gonna happen i fucking told oh wait what wrong person
it was literally the wrong guy it's the other guy don't go anywhere folks we'll be back in
just a shade yo you seen this on the subreddit thief face yeah i'm not buying it something's
not right they're saying that's why romeo is there it's all a fix
i think you need to go to see what's going on it's not far now really listening to him
oh you've come this far yeah but where are we going okay i was about to say i'm gonna
walk out of the theater but he said we've come this far don't fucking tell us like shit like
they're right tell nick about yourself come on we gotta keep moving he's not just some glory
seeking wannabe auto here is convicted of squatting another streamer well auto did not
do that no swatting called the cops and said there was a hostage situation at the house of
another player so they would send an armed response and what happened auto is killed
i didn't mean like i don't care about anyone's past the fact is we're already in this situation
and we have to keep going how do we know he's not the puppet how do we know you're not the
fucking puppet you want to fucking hey guys i'm because it's me i'm the main character is the
puppet it's me what's that i might as well tell them at this point you shouldn't be out
this far come on here i can't see it man i kind of want to just finish this movie so i can put
it back in the blu ray case and just put it in the closet must be close now you know i don't
want to have it be sitting in my ps4 after i just kind of stop watching it you know what
i mean i it's like i've got to complete it so i can put it in the case and put it in the
closet all right well this is difficult because she she woke up earlier before i did and she
i don't know what she she like was doing something behind the building and then she was like what
huh what and then we already like kind of betrayed auto but then auto it put auto at low
opacity and put the stream behind him all right well i'll go with auto because auto is the dog
name and if i don't click auto then everyone's gonna be pissed you don't like that guy you
my dog you like this auto oh well look at him he's so long and chunky look at his big chunky
butt he's like a seal what is it look i already told you i don't care about anyone's past no
earlier my phone fell out oh it was switched on or were yeah sure just before the drone came
look i know coming from me what if he's making this up here's the problem what if he called the
drone he's just putting it on her but it's auto we need to confront her dude i think we need to
get the fuck out of it we're not just ditching her okay is he right oh is he aiming at my head
he's shooting oh god he's aiming at me oh i thought auto is aiming at me give it up nick
let her go in the spirit of the game now would it i do need you nick you're outnumbered
anyway you shoot her we kill you you didn't think i'd come alone did you here come the
yeah remember us you and me we just need a little chat what the hell is going on
speedrun 100 auto run no i mean didn't i tell you that near the end i was gonna have to have a
sacrifice but here's the thing what if they're baking this up what if they're working together
this could just be an elaborate ruse this is an elaborate ruse they're working i knew it i told
you yep what are you doing we need him god damn it i knew it he won't get far no no
i know where he's going i've been looking forward to this we had the we had the redemption
arc too but you needed a helpful man to take me down this is the end for otto blakely
necro to his fans and now just plain necrotic to the rest okay so now what
what is the climax of this whole thing right
you're just at the beginning your face on autos he's using the webcam i can't do that
okay i thought he was just saying he wanted to take a bath i wasn't paying too much attention
okay so what happens here how does this end the acting that acting is not even bad was
that was like good acting that wasn't bad acting what are you talking about
i mean some of the acting is not good is not good
you know you think he's a bad actor i think that guy's pretty good where the
fuck have you been i got this so wrong i thought this guy was gonna die first and
they kept him through the whole game like comedy relief guy yeah stealth takedown
how do you do a stealth takedown if somebody's looking at you i don't know
how i got over here what yeah search where'd the knife come from i don't remember it was makeup
oh no i don't think so what do you mean it was makeup all right dad it's makeup yeah
go fast fast fast fast fast really fast oh he didn't even say anything what do you have
another gun upgrade nice go go get in there hurry nick let's talk we can still get on the
blur and get this all sorted you awake again okay but we're almost there the finale wait what
what chance do you think you had you fucking muppet see the decision's already been made
okay but i'm still alive oh the deep fakes are out there as far as the world knows you're
already dead i can easily just show up and be alive they can't let you there will be
survivors one survivor anyway oh my god i can't believe he just showed that what the fuck why
don't remember that happening everyone gets shot through their right eye by the way now what
put the gun down tish so we made it to the last two that's not true doesn't have to end
this what about what about the girl the blood in her mouth lived through this maybe she just
dipped out there are no guarantees what then this right here is the ultimate prize nick
that's bullshit you just don't get it do you you may have lost your fame your fortune your
friend but it's just seven times i never had any of that to begin with i came here for
my family and now i can have it all the hell with everyone else you can't change it nick
we gotta look out for ourselves there's a better way we can put an end to all this bloodshed you
are better than this tish you don't know me who i am you still have a choice i never had a choice
nick don't do it your move fine don't make me do it don't make me do it please tish never
point a gun at something you don't intend to kill oh you didn't intend to kill me okay well
never mind
the broadcast is out you're dead anyway not if i skip the ending cut scene i can do my own deep
fake chaotic laughter do i live do i survive that that's probably a really bad ending
oh it's gonna be after credits it's a battle royale you want but i didn't win though
because they fake the whole thing with cg characters like one of the characters was
saying earlier what is the point of even doing this show if you can just have realistic
completely uncanny valley real people cg of people doing this what's the point of doing
this in real life that might be the worst ending it could be it's probably at least
like five endings the full screen auto well hold on not yet in one of the other endings
you hack the stuff and release the deep fake info oh okay all right let's get the credits and see
what happens there's nothing there is it it's it no morale nobody likes me nobody loves me
but i'm strong and smart i guess no one likes me but i'm very strong and very smart
okay decisions made 54 scenes viewed this 294 scenes holy shit damn okay no romances all right
uh i'm gonna do one thing before we go there's a short video i want to watch it's a short
sorcery film about this stream and the sorcery game uh but the stream is essentially over
next time i'll be live will likely be next weekend probably on either friday or saturday
or sunday keep an eye on the sus likely sunday either maybe friday and sunday or maybe just sunday
at auto first oh i'm gonna pet you i'm gonna pet mr auto you have a scratchy bum do you
do you oh my goodness you have a scratchy leg it's auto it's auto it's auto showing you
his penguin stripe okay um i'm going to grab this video real quick give me one second will
i grab it but that's going to conclude essentially the gaming portion of the stream and i think this
video is like you two three minutes four minutes something like that those who have never seen
the sorcery playthrough is one of the first streams i really did on twitch when i went
to quote i'm a streamer now 20 what 2015 2016 link is okay
hold on no no no it was good look at the first grade
all right let me get this shit out of here first of all okay all right you ready this is
called zap the old man a sorcery tribute and here we go great the door of the stone building
is slammed and the lock turns over behind you is this gonna be a better movie a bench against
one wall is the only piece of furniture where an old man sits we're gonna go talk to him
it's a better movie greetings old man he ignores you he is concentrating hard on
something on the ground just in front of him you glance upwards to the stars and suddenly
the old man shouts her sorcerer i knew it you're mistaken you reply cautiously oh i don't think so
you'll get us out of here better yet i haven't played anyone for months silly not anyone smart
sit down sit down hey what oh i swindle stones of course swindle stones stranger in town
don't know how to play better and better he shows you one of his stones it is a strange
for value to die he pats the bench beside him with one hand shit play we can talk while i beat
you this is really really well made i'll go first show you how it's done the game is
simple we roll and bet on what's come up for instance i might start and bet that between us
we've rolled at least two twos how do i know what you have three twos didn't you hear my last bid
that was a clue at least unless i'm trying to mislead you four twos i think you're trying to
mislead me oh yeah he had fucking two twos so i get the i win when you win a round of
swindle stones the other person loses a die this game is so good by the way very well
two ones should do they're here for 20 years now hold on i need directions three threes oh yes
where two four threes that's not yours call so he loses another die and he's at even more
of a disadvantage so what do they get you for one one it's a mistake one two oh i
better watch mine was lifting from a red eye two buttons you can't be a very good pig pocket
call your stupid fucking old man what do you know about the north gate of the city
two ones it's wizard hunt with a spell normally the first noble knows it two fours this is
important so tell me everything you know three fours they say the spell is four lines and four
nobles know one line each four fours that's good advice call i win don't i there you go
that's swindle stones i was going easy on you of course rematch thanks for the game
i enjoyed beating you that's so over the door locked of course from the outside
oh really is it really well door you're about to get fucking zopped got his explosions
i wish i had a pebble just below the door straight up well you know we can do
what are the other options i'm just curious stop this pop zip cause teleportation i don't
have a green ring zap zap the fucking door cast the spell winding a powerful charge of
electricity inside your wrist ready to unleash zap the old man
no reason to listen to this old man's horse breathing one instant he is there the next the
room is filled with smoke and the smell of cooked bacon that's so fucked up
you settle down on the bench to wait out the night in silence
uh yeah i would definitely subscribe
the door of the stone building a slave yeah i would subscribe that video is fucking
unbelievable that was very very very well made that was exceptional here's the channel
oh yeah i would absolutely subscribe that was fucking unbelievable even the the zap in the cg
is after effects you know what you're doing uh swindle stones should be the new streamer
meta i feel like that would be a lot of content uh thank you for that video that's
unbelievable that was by uh dr masaki very nice it would just compare it to squid game
yeah but not if you had no it has to be no well i guess it would because the
you know you know all those that have those that have seen squid game we know
he doesn't get it i look i don't i i yes i do of course i do i'll see you guys later i'll
see you guys next week and have a great week uh i'm it's probably gonna be friday keep an eye
on the sus looking like it'll be friday afternoon play sorcery i already did though
i don't think i can go back and replicate that new era of sorcery i don't know i feel
like it's it sits in a place for me where i want to preserve that i had so much fun it was such
a it was so many fun streams in a row that i don't want to go back and remake it i feel
like it wouldn't be as interesting maybe sensory stream yeah i know i got there's a lot of
stuff that i'm going to be working on this week maybe i'll go tap into that too uh that
was a lot of fun all three of those games had um interesting things to experience although
holy shit man i still i'm like still thinking of that lady in her like mouth i'm gonna need
to go watch like baby sensory videos that was fucked up do i even have let me let me see my
steam i think i have like another couple of fmv games that i've just been sitting there
that death stalker game i've had for a long time let's see
i swear to god there's at least another two or three that i've not played
it's honestly i looked at this the other day at the games that i've got on steam and i kind of just
did some reorganization and one of the things i realized i was like what are these i i bought
these like years ago with the intent on doing like a video on them or streaming them i just
never did at least that one i bought that one i know at least six months ago when did
that come out on steam very curious yeah like i came out like almost two years ago like a year
more than a year ago i may have actually bought it last year like in 2020 like let's do it all
right i'll see you guys on friday and one of the things we might be doing on friday
is italics and i might be playing resident evil 6 it's very possible we'll see
we talked about it dark pictures anthology stuff yeah we i want to play like resident evil 6
more and more than i think about i'm like oh actually kind of like i feel like i would have
more fun playing that raid somebody you dork all right hold on let me see who's even live
it's talix is live right now isn't he let's see what is he doing playing rim world
i'm stealing that one that's mine i just stole it from you right now before you got to the
copyright office so you just got screwed uh yeah we'll write it's alex uh we're gonna be hanging
out with him probably this week anyway so go say hello it's been a while since we've rated it's
alex playing rim world if that's not your thing that's not your thing if it is then
he plays it all the time and i will see you guys later have a great week
take care of yourselves see you friday or another day take care good night and goodbye