What the hell was the name of this game? It wasn't Mario Yahtzee, it was something else.
What was it called? It was like Mario's Game Night or something. Mario's Game Time.
What the hell is this thing called? Mario Game Gallery? Yeah, it was called Mario's Game Gallery.
That's the one. Thank you. Let's play some Yahtzee Mario. What's that buzzing sound? I don't know.
What is that buzzing sound? Interplay. Along with Presage, proudly presented.
There it is. That buzzing. Mario's Game Gallery. I don't know why this sounds so harsh right now.
All right, let me get the bits from last night. What the fuck is happening?
Let's get this over here. Sorry. This is from all the way back. I think I can get them all on here.
Dun dun dun dun dun dun. I don't know if there's a way I can get this.
Because this is from earlier today, but how do I get them from yesterday?
Oh, the delay too. Yeah, you're right. I gotta get rid of that. It should be gone now.
Yeah, I'm on the German mustard side, but where um... how do I pull from yesterday? Minimum bits.
The restore button. Oh, okay, right. All right, here we go. So these are the bits from yesterday.
We're gonna start at the bottom here, and we're gonna play Mario Yahtzee.
I know you are, Mario. Just wait a minute. I know you are. Hold on, Mario. I actually
need to do this. Sorry. He's freaking me out. What is this one? I gotta pull the Chrome window.
I know, Mario. Just wait, Mario. I'm trying. Going from PS3 to capture windows. There he is.
Hey, Mario. There he is. I told you guys you'd see him. Hi, Mario. All right, so let's go back while
I do Yahtzee. Is it loud? It's not that loud, right? So we're just gonna go through. This is from
yesterday. Thank you to Walrus Incarnation for the five dollars. I say you're probably the only
streamer I'm going to cheer for, to be honest. Well, thank you. I appreciate that. I really
appreciate the fact that you'd give me any money at all. Thank you. For Fusroboto, thank you for
the five dollars. I say peepee poo poo butthole. Great. I don't have any way to respond to that,
other than what I just said. Let's go. Thank you C4G for the 250. With the release of the new
Hearthstone expansion, will we see the triumphant return of Germadon85 as the number one Hearthstone
streamer on Twitch? Looking forward to the comeback of the Chicken League champion.
Uh, no. I don't think I'm ever going to play Hearthstone ever again. Try to go for the sixes?
I could, I could just take choice right now. What do you guys think?
I'm just going to take choice. Or roll the fours?
Let's try the fours. What are the fives?
Those are not good. I should have just taken the choice. I should have listened to my gut.
Should have listened to my, could I get a straight here though? One, I need a two.
I get to roll the threes. Should I just roll the threes? It's not going to be fours. I'm going
for the threes. All right. That's good for me. Okay. No four of a kind. No, not with threes.
Three. That's pretty damn good. Uh, Sergio Butt. Thank you Sergio Butt for the 250. I've been sick
for the past few days and I had to miss work. I've been living off your vods to help me feel better.
Thanks. Get better soon. Thank you for the 250, Sergio. This was yesterday, but hopefully you're
feeling better. What'd you just do? I'm an idiot. 13. Killer Crocomire. $50 from yesterday.
5,000 bits earlier yesterday. Night. Straight. Two, three, four. Oh, no, go back. I'll go backwards.
Five, six, five, four, three, two. I need a four. I'm going for it. Four. Not a four. That's not a
four. Four. Shit. It's all right. Do I just take the two here? Two's are, uh, that's, I'm going to
take the two because aces. Why would I do that? About Killer Crocomire, thank you so much for the
$50. Some of you guys give 50 bucks all the fucking time and all I can say is thanks. He's going to
get six here, isn't he? Thank you, Demonic Cucumber for the 250. Hey, Jerma. Haven't been able to
catch a stream recently, so it's nice to be able to laugh along with Chad again. Uh, he's going to
get, he's going to get six. Let's not do it. That's all right. I'll take it. Uh, but they say, anyway,
seeing as Minecraft has made a comeback recently, wondering if you'd ever consider going back to it
for a playthrough. I genuinely would like to see that in a non-jokey way. Anyway, love the stuff,
man. Keep it up. I don't know. I don't think I'll ever go back to Minecraft. This is really, okay,
done. Um, no, VR was different because it was VR and it was VR Minecraft and it was something
I haven't seen before. He's going to get a streak. It's all right, but probably not. Not unless there
was a very significant reason to go back to do it. Just try to get some ones here, but thank you for
the 250. Uh, thank you, Life Pies for the five bucks. Should I maybe change this to four? Go
for a full house? No, that's a terrible full house. I might change it to four though, but that's
risky. That's too risky because I only have two. I'm just going to do the ones. Uh, but Life Pies,
thanks for the five dollars. No message, just five bucks. Thank you. Uh, chunky baloney gave
$50. I remember catching this one though, cause he said, uh, this is my kind of chunky stream.
I think that I talked about like, I don't know, diapers or something, whatever. We talk about
diapers like fucking five out of every 10 screams. Thank you though. Uh, Dead Medic,
thanks for the 10 bucks. Hey, Jerma, as someone who's never played Terraria before,
it's been a lot of fun watching your playthroughs and learning the game alongside you.
You're doing great. You should hunt down the flame lash. Yeah, I'm going to,
I'm going to try to get that thing. Is diaper still banned? Can anybody write that word?
Oh, it still is. That's funny. No, not anymore. Oh, is it as it should be?
Well, we've got a, I'm going for it. Give me a huge full house here. Give me a five,
give me a six. This is the best full house you can possibly get in the whole game. Let's see it.
Damn it. But yeah, I, Terraria is great. I've been having a great time with it.
I'm at least going to play to the end of the game. Star and I will continue to do it.
But it's something you'll see on the channel for at least the foreseeable few weeks. I think
it's fun to learn though. Also purple rose tattoo. Thanks to the five dolls.
Just wanted to say, I'm going through some substance abuse recovery
and your content has helped me distract me from the pains of DT and want to drink.
I'm really sorry to hear you going through that. I don't have any personal experience with
dealing with something like substance abuse, but I've heard it's very, very difficult.
Take care of yourself. Wish you the best. And if my content, if this community can help you with
anything, I'm fucking very happy that you can have a place here to relax. Thank you though.
Good luck. Keep at it and take care of yourself. Thank you. Purple rose tattoo. Thanks for the five
dolls. Okay. Where are we at here? What do I want to do here? Roll the two? No, I have to roll the
fours. No, it's a small straight. A big, a big straight would be, what's the difference between
small and a big? Oh, right. Because it's, it's only four. Five is the big straight, right?
How close am I to that? Four, five, six. I need a two. I could do it. I need a two. Come on,
Mario. Give it to me. What's going on with my life right now? Two, three, four, five, six. Okay. I
need a two. Here it comes. It's going to be a two. Told you. What the hell is shit?
Gold finger. Thanks for the 15 dollars. Gold finger. How much do you bench? I used to be able
to bench like 180, 200. That was like 160 pounds. It was pretty damn good. I could do like 180 to
200. Like three or four times. Currently getting my ass kicked. But thanks for the 15 dollars. Gold
finger. Uh, I don't even like Taco Bell. Gave 250. German, it's okay. I have ad block.
What do you want me to say? What do you want me to tell you? I'm going to lose to Mario? Actually,
I swept Mario last time I played this. At this stage in the game, I think it's time to go for
the full house. He only has a 13 for a full house. Or four of a kind. No, that's bad. Just four of
a kind with twos is terrible. Go for the straight? I need a lot for the straight. I already have the
twos. I need a three and a six. I'm dumping the whole thing. Uh, but thank you. I don't even like
Taco Bell, but the 250. Appreciate it. One, two, three, four. Ah, come on. Five. Okay. This is the
best two out of three Mario. I'm going to lose. I know I am. It's over. Thank you Sad Vega for the
250. German, I'm thinking of getting the WWE wrestling game. I saw 2k18 was on sale.
Have you used this one to mod make German rumbles and how hard is it to set up?
Which one is easy to mod? There's really no mods that are any, any real game changers for the
WWE games that are on PC. They're like costumes and created characters. Every WWE game after
2k14 is awful. They just kind of stopped caring after 2k14. Once it came to the new engine and
they started to really put it into like the game simulation, not the thing to do for fun. Plus,
I heard the drama of, uh, isn't Yuke's, didn't they break off? Yuke's decided to go make their
own wrestling game and 2k still makes, there's going to be another, uh, wrestling game made by
Yuke's. However that plays out, I wonder because once 2k really got involved in visual concepts,
started to kind of do some development on the game is when it really kind of, um, took a huge
nosedive as a franchise. Maybe the one from Yuke's will be more interesting. I don't know. I keep
getting this just shit. I need a, I just mathematically, I don't think I went, I need a two and there it is.
Okay, but I don't think I can win math. I need a Yahtzee to mathematically have a chance.
But thank you, sad Vega. I would say get 2k14, but it's also very slow and it takes a long time to
load anything you do with created character, but it has a much better character creator than the
other ones. Or wait for Yuke's to come out with their new game coming up probably in a year or two.
Maybe, we'll see.
It's going on the deuces line. Deuces. It's your turn. Thank you Drosophilia for the 250.
Hey Jeremy, here's a throwback to a recitier. Wanted to play the game myself before watching
you and I lost my house twice and reloaded before I finally beat the game on loop one.
Mario, you're like really fucking interrupting me. Finally beat the game on loop one. Only after
I watched you I did, I realized that you keep your items and levels and that losing is actually
a part of the game. Yeah, I got, I lost once and then went back and did some tactical video gaming
and kept my items and money. Or not my money, my items. I'm throwing a Hail Mary here I think.
I wonder, should I, I gotta go for a full house. There it is. I have a mathematical chance. It's
possible. Yeah, that was a great game. It was really fun, really interesting. 50 dollars from
La Cranda. Oh yeah, I remember this one. This is the peepee poo poo comment. There was like three
peepee poo poo, 50 dollar donations over the last two days. That's 50 bucks guys. That's a lot of
money. Don't get a Yahtzee, don't get a Yahtzee, don't get a Yahtzee, don't get a Yahtzee.
Thank you Favorite Sage for the five dollars. Favorite Sage says, hey Jeremy, you and Vinny
are my favorite people on the internet and I was able to meet Vinny today at the retro games expo.
That's awesome. Was wondering if you'd ever ever attend any event. Mario, stop it! I was wondering
if you'd be attending any events near New York anytime soon. Uh, I'm gonna have to say no. New
York is, there's no real conventions I don't think or anything I'd be doing in New York.
I didn't even go back to Boston for PAX East this year, so probably not unless there was some
reason for me to be there I guess. I've kind of been dialing back the amount of conventions
I've been going to. I think what really, I muted him. I think after, I went, I've been to probably,
I used to go to like three, four plus conventions every year.
Hey, what's it take you so long?
I, okay, I muted him, but it doesn't matter. I guess I have to do something else. I'm gonna
mute him here. I hard muted him. That shouldn't happen anymore. But after doing, I did a lot of
conventions, three, four plus five sometimes in a year, and it just takes a lot out of me.
Now more than ever, traveling is just, I kind of would rather just stick around and work on stuff
and stream and, you know, kind of just hang out and do my own thing. That's not to say that I don't
want to go to conventions, or that I think conventions aren't worth going to or anything,
but I started to really dial it back probably a couple years ago. You can still hear him.
You can. You can hear it through my headphones. But stuff like TwitchCon is close, so I will
probably always just poke my head around there once every year or so whenever it comes around.
Other things, probably no more PAXs, I don't think. I've been to a lot of them. Maybe E3
when it comes around again, especially next year because the consoles. But no, I've been
dialing back conventions. And then of course, Jermacon coming up in Las Vegas, but thank you.
I appreciate it. And thank you for even putting me in the same company as Vinny. He's been around
for a long time. I'm honored to even be put in the same sentence as somebody like that, so thank you.
He's got a great stream. All right, Mario, I'm going to bring you back. Are you going to
be good, Mario? Okay, he's quieted down. We need sixes. I don't have, I mean, there's no six here.
I'm going to have to go for a Yahtzee. Just throw the whole thing away. I lose. I need six, four.
I need four of kind of sixes. What is he looking for? Foures? He's looking for Yahtzee. C4G,
thanks for the 250. Also, thanks for mentioning Card Crawl. I just downloaded to check it out,
and this shit slaps. Card Crawl is the best mobile game you can possibly own.
There is not a better game that is a handheld game that is better than Card Crawl. It's the best
fucking digital mobile video game. If you don't believe me, go get it. I need a Yahtzee.
This is how it happens. This is the dream right here. Here comes the dream right here. Two sixes.
Bingo. Or four. Four of a kind. All right, I still have a chance. I need a Yahtzee. Yeah,
check out Card Crawl. It's great. I made a video on it like three or four years ago.
Hey, snoozingcopter, thanks for the 250. It's my birthday today.
Okay, thanks for Terraria and DOS stream. DOS is always a blast. Yeah, there's at least one game
that's an absolute highlight. That does happen. DOS is weird. Very extreme. It's either very,
very bad or very, very good. I think that's kind of the fun pick it out of a hat scenario.
I do love it though. And then they say, anyway, can I get a happy birthday message shout out
that lasts at least for five minutes? Thank you. See you next stream. Yeah, at least five minutes.
Snoozingcopter, happy birthday. Happy birthday. We're going for Yahtzee. This Yahtzee is for you,
snoozingcopter. Happy Yahtzee birthday. I don't think we're going to get a Yahtzee birthday.
We didn't get a Yahtzee birthday. Birthday ruins. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Happy birthday, snoozingcopter, for real. Let's do another one. Let's go again, Mario.
But yes, for real, happy birthday. Have a good one. Chunkybaloney, thanks to Chunkybaloney for
the five dollars. Hey, thanks for playing Museum Madness. Brings back memories of when I beat it
when I was eight. So I'm sure you can finish it. I would have finished it, but my computer
fucking crashed. My internet turned off. Fusroboto, thanks for the five dollars. Hey, Germa, I'm the
peepee poo poo butthole fart guy from earlier. Oh, hey, hey, it's you. This dinosaur skeleton
has triggered my backseat gamer instincts more than anything else you've ever done. Get good.
Your role. Imagine introducing yourself as the peepee poo poo butthole fart guy.
Nice to meet you, yeah. What's your name? Oh, my name's Jeremy. Oh, yeah, hey,
peepee poo poo butthole fart guy. Just call me, uh, call me Rick. Uh, okay. Hey, Lizard Boy.
Thanks for the ten bucks, Lizard Boy. Ten dollars from Lizard Boy. Hey, Germa, I wanted to give back
after all the laughter and joy you've given me over the past eight years. It's a long time.
Since I was a wee 11-year-old lad, I'm now 19 and have been suffering from severe depression
over the last three years. Sometimes when it feels all like it's going to come crashing down,
all it takes is turning on a water stream. If I wake up in time, stream start at 6 a.m. in Singapore.
Time zones are all over the place. They really are. To make me feel better, thanks for all the
great times. Here's to more. Thank you so much, Lizard Boy. I really appreciate that. Much love
to you. Across the world, if you had told like 16-year-old me that there was going to be a
scenario where I would be able to reach somebody that was that far away and that enjoyed the stuff
that I was doing that much, I don't think I would have believed you. Thank you so much for sticking
around. I really hope that you get through whatever's going on. Almost at the 10-year mark,
please stick around in this community. You're all fucking hilarious. Join the Discord if you haven't.
It's a great place. I look forward to saying hello to you at the 10-year.
Mario, you're gonna get muted again. I'm going for the fives.
But that was Lizard Boy. Thank you so much, Lizard Boy. For real. Four fives. Come on, let's see it.
Do I take the fives or do I take the choice? Five is the choice. 23 is not bad.
Three fives is not bad either, but 23 is not bad for choice.
I'll take it. Dr. Clay, thanks for the five dollars, Dr. Clay. I played that Museum Madness
game as a kid. There was a lot of puzzles. I often had no clue what to do. I still had fun though.
It was nice seeing it again. I appreciate the nostalgia. Take care. It was an interesting game.
And that takes us up to the current bits from today. Currently in a decent position here.
With three dollars earlier. Three bucks from SirK9. They say German is mad, part 69.
I didn't get that mad tonight. I got, look, I got visibly frustrated during the ice level.
Right? Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice. Why is everyone saying nice? All right, do I do,
I could try for a full house. Should I go for the full house opportunity with the, that's,
that's a decent middle of the road full house. Or should I go for a small straight? Two, three,
four, five, double the straight. Let's go for it. There it is. Thank you back in for the 250.
Watch that 180. Watch that 180. It'll creep up on you. Thank you back in though. Appreciate
the 250. Where's that, Demonic Cucumber gave two dollars and 50 cents. Thank you, Demonic Cucumber.
I find it weird that you've banned diaper, dia space per jokes in your chat. Seeing as
you had one in your old demo reel. By the way, I'm not a stalker. This is in chat. I know people,
that's whatever. I don't care. Don't forget the bits from yesterday. I already did. Um, no,
it's not that I'm banning diaper jokes. I'm not banning diaper. All right, yo, we're almost at
that last straw where you get muted permanently. I mean, like on the, like they have audio of the
stream. Audio of the stream. I'm going to make that very clear. Anyways.
Mama mia, yeah, I know. Um, it wasn't the fact that they would. It's going to happen. All right,
I'm rolling. It wasn't the fact that diaper jokes were in the chat. It was 50% of all chat was diaper
related for two straight hours. I couldn't even read. We were talking about Terraria and in between
stuff. I'm talking about Terraria was like diaper spam. Who's fault is it? It's my fault,
but that means I have to correct it. Are you so good now? But thank you. Demotic key coming
from the two 50. Uh, this person has smashed. It's a smashed keyboard name. It's just a smashed
keyboard. Uh, thanks for the 10 bucks. Hey, Jerma, are you going to play electronic super joy too?
It just released today and it's free on steam. I, I made a video on electronic
super joy like seven years ago. That is the right game, right? Electronic super joy. I did
somebody find it. It's there somewhere from like 2012 or something. I might give it a try. You
forgot. I forgot about that video too until you just said electronic super joy too. It's time for
slime. Thanks for the 10 bucks. Uh, the Jerma DOS video I made seemed well received. I made a second
one. Thought you and chat would enjoy it. Well, we're going to wait till the end of the stream for
this one. Absolutely going to watch this. Thank you. It's time for slime for 10 bucks and I can't
wait to watch this video. Thank you. What do I want to do here? Let's go with twos. I think
yeah, or one, two, I could do one, two, three. No, just the twos, twos. Let's get some twos.
Hey, look at that. That's pretty good. We might be able to get a Yahtzee.
Oh, don't get a Yahtzee.
I could feel collectively all of you sink down in your seat and like your neck stuffs into you and
just like, ah, I could feel it. There's like thousands of you that did that. I don't know
how many, I can't even see how many people are here right now, but I could feel it.
At least half of you guys just turtled down into your shoulders. You keep digging yourself bigger
and bigger hole with that joke. I know, but it's fucking like midnight pacific. You know,
what's the big deal? It's fine. Nobody's going to see that shit anyways. You guys,
you guys like the late night crew. That's a potential for a big straight.
Thank you spliceable spleen for the five dollars.
Jerma, I know you're suffering quite a lot right now, but honestly, the streams where you are
borderline meltdown or full on meltdown are my favorite. Please continue to get angry.
This is not a big straight. One, two, three, four, five. Okay. Let's go five. What do you think?
What's more, what's possible? A five or a five? I just need a five. Doesn't matter. It's just a
five. No matter what. Okay. Whatever. I'm an idiot. One, two, three, four, two, three, four,
four. It's a five every time. Just go. Shit. Come on. Yeah, but I don't like to go too far
and getting upset at stuff. Doesn't happen that often. And of course he like he fucking top decks
a big straight. Then he needs to roll. Thanks Mario. Cyrus Dexter, thanks for the five dollars.
No message. It's five bucks. Thank you, Cyrus. Thank you Espada Escarlata for the 250.
Here's some bits. Hope you feel better after beating or giving up on this game,
whichever happens. I beat it, but I do appreciate the fact that it was either way. Thank you. All
right. What am I going to do? Big straight again. One, two, three, four, five. One, two, three, four,
five, four. Please. This is so, I need this. Uh, thank you to Mr. Rad HD for the four dollars.
I love Jerma. He's a cute boy with a nice man face. Wow. Good boy. Thank you. He already has sixes,
right? No, he doesn't. Shit. Thank you, Mr. Rad HD for the kind of sixes.
Bala Koala, thanks for the five dollars. Hey, Jerma, just want to say thanks for all the laughs
and smiles. Your streams always seem to be able to brighten up my stressful day. My pleasure. Thank
you for the five bucks and thanks for hanging out. Without you, there is no stream. Collectively,
all of you. Thank you. How do I have a Yahtzee and still going to lose this damn game? Do I just hold
the six and just throw it all away? I'm getting the one, two, three, four, one, two, two, three,
four, five. Now what the fuck do I do? I keep getting this shit over and over again. You want
a two, three, a four, and a five? You want a five, a two, and a three, and a four? You want a four?
You want, uh, there's, uh, hair on the fly, on the frog, on the dog, on the dog, on the dog,
on the dog, on the seat. Here it comes. Oh, yeah. Enjoy playing with you. Okay. We had, uh, that was
Balakwala. Thank you, Balakwala. Halo Softboy. Thanks for the 250. Jerma, you're a great guy.
You're a, you're great too. Your breathtaking. No, thank you. For real. Thank you, Halo Softboy.
Uh, Colusia. Colusia, thanks for the 250. This stream is amazing. Oh my god, my stomach still
hurts from laughing. Thanks for always brightening my day and being my favorite content creator.
You've done so much for my mental health lately. Love you, Jerma. Thank you.
Amiya. It's always great when a game and a stream just kind of click together, and it's one of those
I was, I was laughing my ass off, at least for the first like four and a half straight hours of this
stream. And it doesn't happen every single time, right? You obviously know everything's the funniest
fucking thing you've ever seen in your life, right? But when stuff just kind of clicks together,
it's just, I love it. This is a great time. This is important. I need this full house. And there it
is. Oh, you're so good. Just need a big straight and I pretty much win the game no matter what.
I have to get the straight though. Uh, Bala Koala gave $50 and had something very important to say.
Again, this is another $50 peepee poo poo comment. What's going on the fours line?
Peepee poo poo. Okie dokie. Your move. $50. I could buy a PlayStation 4 Pro with the amount of
peepee poo poo $50 comments that came through over the last two days.
Mario, I know. I just want to make sure that everyone's with that. You guys are aware of that?
You know, you could have given me a $5 or a dollar. You could have just put like $2.50 and
said poo poo pee poo, poo pee pee poo poo, whatever the fucking thing is. That's a lot of money for
peepee poo poo. And I've said it, maybe this is the point. I've said it like fucking 12 times.
That's a telephone call. I'm going to answer that. It's going to be peepee poo poo.
I need, uh, I'm going to go four of a kind. Let's go. Let's do it. Four of a kind. Sixes.
One. Two. No. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Mistake. It was a mistake.
It was a mistake. It was a mistake. I'm doing fours. That's fine. I'll take it.
Come on, Mario. Let me get this win. I need to get this win. We're almost at the end of the bits.
Nooces. I need a four. A good look, a good four of a kind and a straight ends this.
Six. Five. Six. Five. Four. Three. Ahhh.
I need the two. Give me the two. Give me the two. Give me the two. Do it.
Maverick's — Thank you Maverick for the $5. Not sure where I get these bits, but here's to you,
man. Love your content and keep being awesome. Thank you. Thank you so much.
We had our ten bucks from not so crippling depression for ten dollars
Hey, just wanted to let you know you can build a sword that lets you go extremely fast into area called Snow White
You should also have all the needed materials really
What'd he do? Oh
No, he just it just don't get a Yahtzee and I win. That's fine
Cuz I'm not paying attention to him to me. Oh, he had four sixes. I wasn't even looking
Speaking of sixes, we're just going for it. I just gotta get some points
It doesn't matter mathematically if I get a leave I win. He just doesn't I don't care. Well, okay, that's um
Should I just take it? I'm just gonna take it. No, that's awful. None of this matters. I don't it doesn't matter
Yahtzee loses any I lose anyways, I
Have a fast item in down in terraria, but kind of just following stars lead
Thank you back in for the 250. Oh
Oh
That was a little scary but it's okay I went Mario you lose
But back and thanks for the 250
I never expected you playing terraria and honestly seeing you play this game the game made this year a little better than it is
I can't say things are getting better and honestly, I don't know if it really will but then again, you'd never know
you really do never know life is strange life is funny it has a
way of
Unexpectedly changing keep your head up
But I wish shadow lovely good night and wish you the best on that carnival stream
I'm sure you're gonna put in a lot of work much love and looking forward to far more
Yeah, I can't wait for that stream that streams gonna be so much fun. Thank you so much back and have a great night
197 points
And that actually perfectly brings us to we're gonna watch this video
No Mario you lose
Let's watch this video. Let's do we got two more bits here. We've got DC Pro one for five dollars. Hey Jeremy cakes
They'll pass few weeks have sucked. I
Changed majors from aerospace engineering to new media and film production. My family is so angry any advice on how to stay motivated
I really love making films and stuff that they kind of making me scared for this career
Well, here's the thing
you
You know what you want to do
And regardless of what somebody else wants to have you do or it was something that they decide. This is what's best for you
You know yourself the best the advice that I would give I give it
sometimes is
Just always make sure you have a few things that you're interested in so no matter what happens
Let's say you have like three or four things that you really think are interesting and you put some work into them
You're gonna be happy doing any of those things
Don't put all your eggs in one basket
Spread it out a little bit and try to be happy doing with you know, the thing that you're good at doing
Try to be good at a few things. Try to care about a few things. You won't be disappointed
Suchi P with $50. Should I read this out loud?
Thank you for the $50. Suchi P. It's pee pee poo poo again
Somebody just said it right there. Just do your thing. Do you
Don't let somebody tell you how to do you because they don't know you know
I wish you the best of luck though and then pink lawyer ten bucks. Thanks for streaming Jeremy
I don't know if you've seen the animated video of you telling a sad story, but it always makes my day
Yeah, we watched it. We did watch it yesterday
Yesterday the day before it was very funny though and Rektar five dollars pee pee poo poo wee wee
Wee wee. Okay. Thank you. Very cool. Very cool stuff. There's another $50
I'm gonna have to ban that word. That's another
5,000 bits Bala koala poo poo pee pee. All right. Why are you doing this? That's too much money for
Poo poo pee pee. That was Bala koala five fucking thousand bits
Where's the link to that video to it's time for slimes video?
Let's check it out before I go and I will see you guys on Thursday
We're gonna be gone for a few days. What are you guys doing? I can't even it's not even on the screen
that was that was a hundred dollars a
Hundred dollars pee pee poo poo sushi pee. Thank you for the fucking
10,000 bits. No, don't get on this you guys don't get on don't get on like pee pee poo poo
How I'm never gonna be able to pee pee poo poo. What I don't even know what even is that?
What is pee pee poo poo? I don't even it's just a it's just a gross-out humor
Sushi pee hundred dollars pee pee poo poo motherfucker. All right
That that's like hundreds of dollars from sushi pee sushi pee pee pee poo poo again
Poopoo pee pee. I need to stop saying this before I make this a thing
Thank you so much for the huge amount of money Rektar five dollars. They said what they say the line DC Pro five dollars
They're saying the line. Why is this not working?
Dermados to coming up sue GP fifty dollars. I hope it's not pee pee poo poo. It's not okay
But seriously, you're one of my favorite streamers. Thanks for streaming you rock. Thank you for the
Ridiculous amount of money. I'll try to put it to good use. Thank you so much. I really appreciate it
That was sue GP for with fucking two trillion dollars. Thank you so much
Let's watch German dos too. Here we go. I gotta get this in the right spot
Let's go. I thought that was money
Asshole
These are so good man, like seriously, is it fucking awesome? Thank you for that. That was great. And
Hey, look at this the stream over for the first time today. Thank you. What for each for the five dollars?
Not a pee pee poo poo joke. Well, it was
Creamy sensation five dollars. Oop. Oop. Eep. Eep. Dermis snort. That's right. It was in reverse. You got it
Sad Vega 250 it could all be explained. Check out this
Video of Yoda
He doesn't say that in Star Wars, I'm 100% 100% positive
Thank you
Thank you. Dino squad for the 250 germ
I really want to tell you that I love everything you've been doing for the past five or six years is another hundred
Oh my goodness guys
But Dino squad. Thanks for the 250
Love everything you've been doing for the last five or six years
I've been following you for a hot minute
Just want to say that you've been helping me with not stay as stressed as I should be
Me and my fiance just had our first child about a month ago and our son has gotten so used to hearing your voice
That he's almost gotten to the point to where he can't fall asleep without hearing you. Love you. Keep up the great work
Congratulations on your first child. That's a
huge huge deal and
I what I'll be a good I'll be a good night light
Except I say like fuck all the time
Don't leave me on past like 11 months
Otherwise that I say like fucking shit and like peepee poopoo all the time
to be careful there, but thank you so much for the 250 and
Congratulations again, then we had Zell Grote with a hundred dollars
I've been watching since the TF2 days and you helped me through the darkest times and you're the funniest boomer
I know I want to thank you for the years of laughs from Australia
Thank you so much for the fucking hundred bucks
Stick around I got more to show you. Thank you so much. It's my pleasure
Again pendulum Jen pendulum. Thanks for the five dollars. They just say pee
Saks a lot. Thanks for the 250. Hey, Jeremy. I want to thank you for being a great streamer and whatnot
I can always count on you to make me laugh
yesterday, I changed my college major from
Peepee to poopoo and my parents are livid
I know that peepee tends to be more lucrative than poopoo, but poopoo is my passion. All right
I'll see you guys Thursday. Have a great rest of your week
Alright, I don't know. I don't even know who gave those 20 subs. It was anonymous. Somebody just gave a shitload of subs
Thank you, whoever you were for the gigantic sub drop
Thank you anonymous. It must it must have been peepee poopoo. That's a lot of subs whoever you are. Thank you
Have a fantastic rest of your morning for some of you evening for some of you others
I'll see you Thursday
Get some sleep much love to you. Take care. See you real soon
I didn't do the credits. Holy shit. What am I talking about?
I'm like fucking tired. Apparently so much like money just came in. I didn't even do the credits
Get them up there. You guys spoiled the shit out of me. Thank you everybody
One more bit message came in this it was from for real dough 250
Don't know if you've seen this video, but in case you haven't the video is not mine. It's the sad story
We have seen it. It was fucking hilarious
But thank you for bringing it to my attention anyways
And thank you everybody all the community subs all the gifted subs
Community subs you are you are sub community. You're
Yeah, if you're a sub you're a part of the sub of community of subs
But for real is shitload of money comes through this channel. I really hope you still like it
I still hope you're having a good time. I'm still having a good fucking time
Stick around we got rats. Look at those two rats
They're beautiful
Look at all these names and people are still just subscribing at the end here. Am I gonna play classic Wow? Yeah
we'll do a thing where
for at least four I
Don't like the thing about it's a classic while only have like five or six servers. I
Saw that recently they posted. Oh, yeah, there's like eight servers. We're gonna I don't want to just ruin one
13 service for NA that doesn't seem like very much. There's only two PST servers
Maybe
I gotta be careful. I don't want to be I'll be careful with this
Because if there's really only gonna be two servers on the west coast
At least initially I don't hey, let's like dump
thousands of people in a server and
Camp ogre mar I do want to do something like that though
I figured it'd be fun, but I don't want to be people want to play and have fun and I
don't want to get in the way of somebody else's fun to just kind of be like
a dick or something and flood a server
We'll see though
Ford is better than Alliance
Well, that's your opinion. I have played both sides. I started my first account as horde
but the first character I ever made was a troll and
The character I played the most time on was a dwarf
Get the jokes out now
But thank you everybody. I'm glad we got to do at least
Eight plus hours the last two days
I want to do some chunky ones because I knew wasn't I wasn't gonna be around for the next few days. So
Good night. Get some sleep
Much love to all of you
I'll see you real soon