Hey. Yeah, I know. I know I'm late. I know I'm late. Don't make fun of me. Don't make fun of me.
Don't make fun of me. Don't make fun of me. Don't make fun of me. Don't make don't make don't make
fun of me. Please. Okay. Hey, how are you? Good to see you again. Hope you're having a good afternoon.
Today, we're going to play City Skylines. I downloaded the Nvidia graphics card update.
I decided to pick the day to install the new Nvidia driver update to play City Skylines,
which I didn't fucking even need it. And my computer wouldn't post to Windows for about
20 minutes. So I had to hard boot my computer. And that's why I'm late. That's why I'm not here
like 20 minutes ago. I come on. That's the reason. I don't know why I fucking looked at it too. And
I was sitting there going, oh, hey, this is, you know, this is an Nvidia graphics card update.
I'm like, all right. Yeah. What am I playing today? City Skylines game come out in like 2012.
I need that update right now. Yeah, sure. Get it. Anyways, I can hear myself talk again,
which is irritating. Let me get rid of this. They are going to play City Skylines. I've been
talking about this for about, I don't know, maybe a week or two on a whim. Somebody brought it up.
Hey, you should do City Skylines on Friday. Yeah. Okay. That's what we're doing. There are no
mods. All I did was purchase every single fucking DLC in the game. I just, I freaked out. I kind of
panicked a little bit. As you can see, as you can see, I got campus radio, downtown radio. I
didn't know if I needed any of this stuff. I just, I bought the whole thing. I just was like, should
I get it all? Does this matter? So you can't even hear it. Hold on. There you go. You need camp.
All right. Well, here's the thing. I'm going to be very real with you guys. I, I don't know anything
about this game. I've never opened it. I've never pressed jump one time in City Super Mario Skylines.
I have to do the tutorial. This is going to, we're just going to relax and just chill.
And I'm going to play this fucking game. I don't know. You know what I'm saying? I just,
I don't know what I'm doing. Oh, I can't skip the tutorial. That was a terrible joke. I made a joke.
What? When? What? Didn't I just tell you what I was doing? What did I say? There is no tutorial.
Are you ready? Am I ready? Campus radio is an OST. What about, what about this? Rock City
Jazz City. How much was all this? Rock City Radio. Concerts? Did I buy like a concert ticket?
Was this like $40 for the music? Oh my God. Whatever. I'll listen to it. We're going to put
it on auto principle. All right. Here we go. New game. Choose a map. Choose a scenario. Is there
like a here's how to play the game, sir? Choose map. Green Peaks. Why am I not playing Animal
Crossing? Eh, I'll do that later. I'll do that later. This was more interesting to me right this
second. We'll do that like in a day, a couple of days. We'll do that like, I don't know, like Sunday
or something. I don't know. No, it's not good. No, it's not good. I don't like animals. I just,
I was like, yeah, I, whatever. I wanted to do this. I'm going to play it. All right. What should I do?
Choose scenario. This scenario is all about making the small industrial city of Peachtree.
Dude, is it going to tell me how to play? I'm just going to do Marin Bay. Choose scenario. Yes,
just pick a map. I'm just going to do, I'm going to do, uh, this one. No, this one, the peninsula.
You want to set random disasters on. The setting is global. Yeah, sure. What does that mean?
Meteors? This is like, uh, like sim earth, right? So like a fucking, the sun can explode or something,
right? Is that real? What? What do you mean dinosaurs? How is dinosaurs a natural disaster?
Your town can get attacked by fucking 17 million BC prehistoric animals. It's pretty. All right.
Welcome to city Scott. Hey, let's start by building some roads and zoning the areas next to them.
Buildings will spawn on the zoned areas and you will unlock new city services and buildings as
your city grows. Okay. We need to build some building. We need to build, start by building
some roads and zoning the areas next to them. Oh, how do I? Okay. W A S D moves around.
So here's a road. Oh, it's just like rural coast tycoon three. Okay. Click on the question mark
button. It'll probably be with you. Sure. All right. Let's put some roads. How do I put like
the park thing here? How much does it cost to come into my park road? All right. Here we go.
Roads need to be built to provide zones for buildings and city services. Larger roads allow
faster traveling, greater amounts of traffic and big roads with decoration produce less noise
pollution. I need decorations on the roads. That's probably cost more money. I'm not doing
that. You just page up and page down to build elevated roads or tunnels. Tunnels? Road over
water to build a bridge. You just draw it? No, no, no. I'm not, I'm not pausing the game to look at
a picture right now because I need to learn how to play city skylines. I, I know, I, I know you,
you may have made my mouth like three times bigger and like stretched my nose up into my eyes and
like gave my eyebrow bone like 5% more density. I know. I already know what the image is. So
can I just learn how to play city skylines? We're going to be here all day. I promise.
No, you pause pause. I'm not pa, I don't, I'm not pausing the game to look at an image to change.
Wait. Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa. You're talking about in the game. Oh, I thought you guys are telling me
to whatever. It's not you. You're an egomaniac. Oh, all right. Pause the game. I'm in the middle
of the tutorial. Can I not, can I not just do the tutorial first? City skylines collection bundle.
What about, what about this? What are you talking about? Buy to save 9%. How much did I pay for this?
Wait, the price. I know, no, no, no, no. Hold on a second. This is important. I didn't buy the bundle.
I bought the DLC individually through like the DLC page. Did I do that? Yeah, I did. Let me see
if I actually just like lost out on like fucking $40 or something. Let me see. This is important.
This is actually important. Hold on. Where's my like, my purchase history activity. Yeah,
I bought them all individually, but I thought the bundle was like other games or something.
Oh no. How much did this cost? Hold on. Let me go to steam support and find out. I scammed myself.
Hold on. Let me see view purchase history. No, no, it's it. No, it's all right. It's okay.
It was still the same. How much? Wait, 179. It's so much fucking money. How much was it?
How much was the bundle? How much was the bundle? Did I save money? Wait, wait, wait. Hold on a
second. I think I may have deleted one. Yeah. All right. I know what happened here. So I
individually bought all the DLCs, but I removed like one or two, I think, soundtracks and one like
content creator pack. I was like, I don't fucking want this. It has like really bad reviews,
but I deleted it. So I think I actually did get, I got scammed. Most important one. So I, you know,
I know I did get scammed. All right. All right. That's fine. That's fine. That's all right. I
don't, this is, this is fine. So pound for pound, I got scammed. You only needed the expansions.
I don't know. Dude, this is like train simulator. It's like the Sims. I don't know what the fuck I
needed. I just bought all of them because like, here's the scenario. If I didn't buy every single
pack and I got to a point in the game, like a few hours from now, like maybe it's like, let's say
10 hours from now, like over the next day or two. And I don't have the dinosaur invasion. You guys
are going to fucking be so annoyed. Wait, hold on. He doesn't have like the, he doesn't have like
tree. Wait, wait, wait. The stream doesn't have tree 18. I, no, I don't. Oh, how could you not get
tree 18 pack? I'm, I got it all. Where's the music? I want to play the music I purchased.
Let me learn how to play the game. All right. Enough. Let me learn how to, I need to learn to
play the game. We have, we're literally at the bottom end of the popsicle sticks for the double
popsicle, which I mean like that. I wish I had those. Do they even still make those
split popsicles? I fucking want one now. All right. How do I play? Make a road. You guys just fucking
threw me off. I'm not even past the second bubble of how to make a road. It's been 13 minutes.
I need everybody to relax. How to make a road. Where's my road bubble? Okay. Roads need to be
built to provide zones for, yeah, and city services. Larger roads allow faster travel,
so just have a bunch of huge roads. He's molding already. I'm not, no, I'm not. I'm just slightly
agitated. All right. Roads or decorations have less noise pollution. People like it.
Okay. Page up, page down is to go up and down over a river for a river. Change the road's type.
Try the upgrading tool. Use a road type to click on an existing road. Click on a one-way road with
secondary mouse button to change its direction. Use upgrade tool to fix destroyed road. All right.
Where's the upgrade tool? Road construction, intersections, medium roads. What's the upgrade
tool? Road toll tools. This is locked. I'll go snapping. This is upgrade tool. Okay. Upgrade
road. I want to make sure I know where it is. All right. So you can change the road's type. So
this, these are one-way roads. I guess this is coming into the city. Toll booths must be connected
to road in order to operate. All traffic driving through the toll must slow down at the booths and
pay a fee to pass the tolls. This is when they come into the park. Air price can be adjusted,
but okay. So I want, I want a toll booth right at the beginning of the town. So this is like how
you pay to get into the theme park. All right. Here we go. This is just a regular road, right?
Two lane road. Pog. That's a fucking Pog right there. Okay. Nice. All right. So now I'm going
to do what like 95% of all of us on this website do is after I do 1% of progress, I'm going to
stop for a little bit and we're going to talk about something, uh, maybe the progress of the game
or potentially something completely unrelated. It'll take me about three to four hours to build
this road a mile up into the city. What did you guys have for dinner last night? I had a, I had
a fucking spaghetti. Wait, shouldn't this be, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I want more than,
how do I make more than one lane upgrade tool? You cannot upgrade this type. Why the fuck not?
Oh me. Oh shit. Okay. Large roads. Right. That needs to, this is what a bottleneck.
Okay. Wait, wait, wait. I need to make this bigger. Wait, what? Wait, why? How many lanes
is this? Is this two lanes? Six lanes. Okay. It's okay. It's all right. These are, I need a,
whatever, six lanes of road. Just, I didn't have a city go this way. I don't have enough money.
How much does this cost? Oh, it's an upgrade tool. Okay. Take the upgrade tool off. Straight road.
Okay. Here we go. How do I tilt it? Middle click. Oh, what? Middle click doesn't do anything.
I'll take the snapping off a huge fucking road. Uh, angle. Okay. Road length grid. So if I go like
this, how do I tilt it? I have to use this. Freeform road. Here we go. All right. Get off.
Make only road. Build 5G. I gotta figure out how to play. This is not a great tutorial by the way.
Okay. How do I get to like, how do I build a fucking road for the left of you? All right. Ah,
look at that. Okay. Cool. This is so fucking ugly. All right. So this is, how much does this cost?
Okay. All right. This is a highway. So we're going to have the highway go,
we're gonna have like an exit off the highway. Wait, this is a highway. Yeah. Okay. Thanks for
telling me how to play. Oh, wait, maybe that, what's the, what's the tweet say? Hello, this is
Cherper. Keep an eye on what your citizens are talking about and what's happening around the
world. Fuck you. Well, thanks, Cherper. Um, how do I build fucking roads? Okay. Why are you telling
me how to build a toll booth? Oh, should I have 55? Okay. Wait, wait. I gotta go back to small.
Okay. Now we're going to, how do I make like an, how do I zone this shit? Zoning. I didn't, what
the fuck? How am I supposed to know what the fuck this was? Zones determine what kinds of buildings
will spawn to the areas next to the roads. Areas indicated by gray grid next to roads can be zoned
using zoning tools. Okay. Why is there horror movie music playing? There are four different
tools for zoning. Fill, marquee, and small and large. Zone an area by clicking the primary
mouse button on it. Hold down the mouse button to adjust the square marquee size or continue
paint with a brush. All right. Residential zones are for houses for citizens. Commercial zones
offer shopping and leisure. Industry and office zones provide jobs for the citizens and produce
goods for the commercial zones to sell. So commercial zones, industrial zones, this is jobs
and producing goods for local businesses. This is his own, which is just another way to say
the zone, I guess in a cool way. Okay. So this is our city. I'm just learning. So let's make some
houses, I guess. Let's have, no, no, no, no. This is our highway. I'm fucking learning. This is just,
this is just a trial run. So I want this to turn. All right. So you come in, you pay the entrance fee
to the park. Right to the right is going to be the carousel. It's every fucking person that's
ever played this game has had the carousel right here. No one has ever played this game without a
fucking carousel being right fucking here every single time. It doesn't matter who it is. It could
be you, your parents, your father, your mother, your friend. It doesn't matter who it is. Hey,
I built like two fucking centimeters of road. Let's talk for a little bit. Welcome to Twitch.
Did the thing I made fun of. I'm just gonna happen. That's what I do. Whatever. I'm just
trying to see how the fuck this works. Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Is it, how many lanes is
this? All right. Here's an intersection. Do you have to put stop lights if people are going to
drive into each other? Okay. So you go. Okay. Cool. So I'm, let me just put houses here. All right.
Let's zone it for housing. So you, this is like, you come down here and this is the first street.
This is first street. This is residential. Like, can I just drag across? I don't have to click
individually. Okay. So here's residential. Terrible city planning. Sorry. Sorry. You knew
what you were getting into when you told me to play city skylines. You knew what you were getting
into of just being completely upfront. So I made zoning for houses. So how do you make houses?
I sure wish the fucking Twitter ripoff would help me. Okay. What's this? Um, it's zoned for
houses. What's this? Oh, you can pick the mark. Okay. You can drag. Um, what is like the build
tool? Well, this is just an ad. The game is paused. What? So what? I need, wait, I need
tutorials for the, I have to unpause the game. They build themselves. What do you mean they build
themselves? What? Wait, I don't have to go down. Wait, they building themselves. What? So this is
like a, this is like a, this is like bacteria. They just build. Oh, okay. All right. All right.
So now, um, we need commercial. This is one street. This street is going to go over here.
This is going to lead into, um, shopping mall. Okay. Hold on. You never, literally never played
a city building before. No, I haven't. Why would I have ever done that? We're going to have another
city over here connecting to here. Now what's snapping on? What does it say? Space one.
I told you idiots. He's going to get so lost. Space is already. Oh, it's because of,
I told you don't use free form, straight road, curved road, free form. All right. So I want
curved road and I want it to snap angle, road, length, grit. So all of it, right? So I can't,
you need water and power, but water, water available, human replicants. Excellent for
physical labor, Tyrone operation. Thanks for the fucking promoted tweet. I wish I could delete
those. All right. Wait, pause the game. Pause the game. Connect the water pumps and I love how it
just assumes I know what that is. Hey, connect the water pumps. You need like a fucking giant
arrow. Just like a huge red arrow, just circling this a hundred times for people like me.
Connect the water pumps and drains with water pipes. Draw the water pipes under your city
to provide bill. Wait, really? So small buildings. So like this is under the ground. Okay. Cool.
Note that the water pumps and drains need electricity to work. Water tanks store excess
water and supply the city automatically. Picture your water pumps are located a safe distance away
from any drain pipes to prevent people from using contaminated water. Okay. Sorry. I'm just chewing
on ice. That means I have an iron deficiency. Fuck. During the winter, heating is required.
Upgraded water pipes carry heat to buildings. Make sure your water pumps are located a safe
distance away from any drain pipes. Do I have to connect every house or does it not matter?
Can I just go like this? Is this work? Is this working? Do I just have to go?
That circle means it's working, right? Okay. And then connect the water pumps and drains
with water pipes. Okay. So now I need a water pump, water pumping station. Does this work?
Oh, this makes it. Oh, these beds is front and first backyard.
I'm looking, I'm looking at Zillow right now. This house is, is 215,000. This one's 220,000.
Honey, this, look at this one. This one looks like a deal. Why is this one $41,000? This looks
like a great deal in the water source. Oh wait, it has to be, this is a million miles away.
This is so far away. This is so far away. I have to, what? Okay. So it has to be connected to the
water. All right. How many of these should I have? 120, 120,000 M3s a week. Water consumption,
1300 M3s a week. I got plenty. I only need just one. All right. Now water drain pipe.
The water drain pipe pumps out water waste. Remember to avoid pumping sewage upstream.
Know that the drain pipe always requires a water pumping station to work properly.
Road connection not required. So I need to pump this like this way. Which, which way is it going?
Which way is down river? This way is the up river, right? I don't want to pump it into the river.
Don't tell him. Wrong way. Arrows. Yeah. The arrows are pointing this way. So I need to pump it in.
Wait, you just dump, you just dump waste into fucking rivers and shit?
Now, so this is current. This is pumping down. This would be pumping upstream.
This is pumping. Can I tilt it? Can I turn it? Is there a way to like tilt buildings? Like turn
buildings? That's wrong. It just flows with the water. Yeah. So this is going downstream.
So just make sure there's no like houses or anything right here. You'll get green options
later. Oh, music. Put it at the edge of the map. So like down here. So just, all right. Just
whatever. It's at the end of the world. Evil fucking music. Does this need to be connected?
Connect the water pipes and drains. So now I have to connect this to all the houses.
Holy shit. This is complicated. Okay. I wish the tutorial would tell me just how to fucking
basically control a camera. All right. So now we go like this. Okay. Here we go. That's correct.
That's okay. So now the water is here. Water pumping station needs to be connected to here,
right? Is this correct? That's correct, right? Done. All right. You got water. Water pipe.
Heating. Oh, it needs heat pipes too. Not yet. Water pipe with heating pipe. Okay. Sounds good.
And it kind of works. So that's that. That's the, this is like the shit drain where like all the,
all the pee and stuff goes. That's where all the pee goes. And then this is the water pump,
which is connected here, which pumps water into the houses. I'm gonna connect. I have to connect
these. What? Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Doesn't this like the shit and stuff connected? It doesn't
matter. Oh, so wait, the water is coming in here and like the shit is coming in here. All right. So
doesn't matter. All right. Time for power. I'll figure this out. Don't worry. It's gonna be a long
one. Don't worry guys. This stream is going to be like, this stream will be at least four to eight
hours, four to six hours. You know, that's going to be a long one. It'll be at least three to six
hours. I'll figure it out. Now I need power. Oh wait, should I? Hooray. The water pumping station
has been constructed. Fresh water. Mayo or rocks. Mayo rocks. Okay. You're gonna really throw in
your like mayo agenda at the end of that tweet. Okay. How do I build power? Isn't this right here?
Garbage and industry. Where's power? Oh, electricity. Okay. Power plants produce electricity
for all your m- pause. Power plants produce electricity for all your modern cities need.
Electricity will move from building to building over short distances, but to transfer electricity
over great distances, you'll need to build power lines. This is gonna be so fucked up.
When placing power lines, you can see the reach. So I get it. You build the infrastructure first
before you build any fucking roads. You do all this shit first and then you build the
two roads over it. You do, you go from bottom up. I get it. We'll do that next time. No shit.
I love how people are saying to me no shit when I've never played a city builder in my entire life.
I don't, I'm not a fucking architect. I didn't know you had to, I thought you had to individually
put buildings down like fucking monopoly style one by one on each grid. This is a new experience
for me. So I would appreciate banning that person for life. When placing power lines,
you can see the reach of electricity around the buildings. So here's a power line. You can see
the reach of electricity around the buildings is light blue area. Connect these areas with power
lines to move electricity between them. Power plants produce ground and noise pollution. When
placing a power plant, the circular area around the houses you fa- fa- whatever. So I, okay,
on all the streets I've ever been on, power lines are like here. Like they go like this.
Should I put them behind the houses? Okay. That's a street right there. Is that working?
And then I need to go to the power plant. Let's just look at the picture. Okay, how do you undo?
Is there an undo? Where's the undo? No, these are not just, okay, these are pow- I'm thinking about
in like it, when I, okay, listen, listen to me. This is important. When I lived in Massachusetts,
every road had fucking power lines and poles going across. It's not that kind of power line and poles.
Out here in Vegas, they're all underground. But you guys know what I'm talking about when you
drive- I didn't know. I thought, okay, I get it. There were power lines fucking everywhere in
Massachusetts, on every street. They lo- it looks like this. I'm just going on based on what I grew
up looking at. Those are telephone lines. I know. But like, I- I'm sorry. I don't- I'm not a fucking
ar- okay. I'm not an architect. And I never- I'm not a city builder. I'm a- I'm a- I'm a begging
e-clown. Did you get- I understand the difference. Okay, so let's uh, how do I remove this? Why the
fuck is this scary fucking music? How do I change the music? Bottom right, free camera, global
happiness. Wait, I can do wind. Don't tell him. No, tell me how to change the fucking music.
Oh, here it is. Okay. How do you change it? Classical. Rock City. All right, how about- what's
one of the ones I paid for? Campus Radio. Please note some of the radio channels have licensed
music and cannot be used when streaming. Let's turn it off! All that jazz. Hey, that's all right.
A little loud, but here, let's- no, no, I don't want you- this is a- I don't like when people see
your uh, my menus. I feel like you look- I feel like you look at me naked. I mean, this is- I
don't want you- this is like weird. I got- what's- what's- what are your settings at? I don't want
you to see this. Anyway, that's better. Increase the FOV. There is no FOV in this fucking game.
All right, sure. Here, I'll do it. Okay. Let's get V-Sync turned on. I don't think I'm worried
about frames in this one. It doesn't matter. I'm not playing like Counter-Strike with like a
fucking 240 Hertz monitor, guys. This is City Sky. All right. So, when placing a power plant,
so you just kind of connect to a power plant. So put a power plant like over here. Like right over
here. I get it. This is just a tutorial for me, guys. All right, just relax. Power plant. Coal? Coal
uses coal. Wait, there's a- there's gonna be a coal plant over here? Billy must be placed on a
roadside. What? All right, this is gonna be where the industry is. This is gonna be industry way.
Um, okay. He will learn. I will learn. You must learn. Learn what? Everything. Don't fucking give
me an opportunity to make a three-eyed raven quote, okay? I'll do it every time. I'll do it
every fucking single time. Do not let me do that again. All right, so now we build. Uh, just,
all right, here we go. On this side. That's good. Will this- oh, it has to be connected.
I have to be directly connected to a power line? Does that have to be directly connected? No.
Just to be in the circle? Yes. Look at the drawing. Sick. Okay. Right here. I don't want it to be
too close to the residential area. Fuck. Well, come on. I thought it was the circle. Not this
one. All right, it's gonna be moved. How do I- how do I undo? Why is it no undo? I'm learning. I'm
learning. I'm learning. This is a learning stream. Bottom right bulldozer. Yoink. Okay. Coal power
plant. Bright air should do it. There we are. We're now producing power to every citizen on
earth. Okay. When placing a power plant, the circular area around tells you how far the
pollution spreads. Maybe if you've read the text. All right, sounds good. Let's get the fuck out of
this. Um, this is not working. Why is it- this is broken. What's wrong with this? Why is it broken?
It says- it's like- it's like a severed plug. What does that mean? A local power plant is online.
Maybe I'll get my TV working again. Hashtag reality shows 24 7. I love the smell of burning
fossil fuel in the morning. Dino power. Pro-fossil. All right, I'm starting to understand
what's going on here. So what the hell is this? Is this how, like, to leave the city? Um, wait, what?
Wait a minute. This is how to leave the city. So, but you can't-
you can't go this way. Traffic is kind of- nobody can even go down this road.
Malicious compliance. Well, I said to build four lanes. I'm gonna do it.
Redditor. Oh, stop. Whatever, I'll fix it later. We'll fix it in post. Okay, so, uh, how's everybody
doing? We need more stuff. Let's go to, uh, um, um, no, no, no, I don't want any more of this shit.
All right, I'll delete these. Can I delete this? How much space is this? What was the emergency?
What was the- was that the emergency warning? I'm not sure. What the fuck is it talking about?
All right, so this is fine, right? I don't- I love Hey Arnold, but I don't want to hear
Hey Arnold music right now. How about, um, this one? So, I need to build the more industry or
something. Wiz tutorial part two. Reach a population of four- all right, we need more buildings.
Zone. Uh, here, let's add some neighbors. Give me a road. No, no, I don't want a huge ass road.
All right, this is gonna go like this. That's so ugly. I- uh, doesn't matter. Is it- how many lanes
is this? Wait, hold on, is this a one way? Hold on, is this two- wait, two- no, this is a two-lane
road. Okay, that's fine. Is it day-night cycle? Holy shit! All right, let's go, uh, more houses.
This is just one little road. There, look at that. Okay, now we need electricity to go-
how many citizens? He's running out of- oh fuck, I only have two thousand dollars!
Wait, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on. What the fuck are you talking about? City budget for 2020?
Wait, people have to park on the street? The local budget meeting for, uh, Wink Dink City
for 2020. We're building a new city. We are allowing $41,000 to build 12 power plants,
500 houses. It's gonna be anthills is what we- excuse me. What do you mean there are no jobs?
Holy shit, they're crashing into each other. There's people! Hey, look, there's people!
They need jobs. All right, well, we'll give them jobs! How do I give somebody a job?
At the water and sewage plants? People will work here? I need to build- okay, everyone needs to
work at the water and sewage zone. I need- wait, I need to do zone commercial. Load- oh, okay.
I don't have any fucking money! Let's have it just be businesses, like, right here. All right,
this is gonna be commercial. Why are they saying no water? Do we have to have a day-night cycle in
this game? What's this? Disasters. Incoming. What? Hold on, why is it saying disasters?
They don't have any w- what do you mean they have no water? Oh. Oh, you motherfucker. This
needs electricity. Okay. But how the- what? Holy shit! This is the wrong- okay. This needed to
be on the other side of the whole world! Take a lo- all right, I'm starting over. I'm starting
over. New one. New game. What do you mean no? How do I take a loan out? Budget. You can manage
your city's taxes. Oh, you can charge taxes? Budget and loans here. Majority- pause the game.
The majority of your city's income comes from taxes. Tax income is based on the size and
level of the buildings in each of the zones. High taxation will make people unhappy
and might cause them to move away. A bigger budget for a service means that facilities
work more efficiently, but also becomes more expensive to maintain, right? City service
budgets can be adjusted separately for day and night time from the slides in the budget view.
You can take a loans from different banks. The amount and interest rates differ from bank to bank
and there's a limited number of loans that can be taken simultaneously. Okay, well, let's just-
let's take a huge loan out. Income. Uh, okay. It's all loan. Loans. How do I get a loan?
I don't have enough people to take a loan out. You need a bigger city for a loan.
New game. I want a different map. I want, um, what do I want? Garden Rivers? Eden Valley?
I want a balanced place. Turn off in- turn on infinite money. I'm not gonna do that.
Sand Vegas? No, I'm not ready for Sand Vegas. Where's Sand Vegas? I'm gonna do- I'm gonna do
one of the easy ones. Like, this one looks pretty easy. Eden Valley. Wait, this is the one I just did.
Do dust- a dust ball. I'm not doing- no, these are difficult. Wait, Marble Canyon. This looks
pretty cool. No, it's too advanced. Too advanced. Too advanced. Too advanced. Garden Rivers. I'm
doing it. I still have to learn how to play. I'm not- turn off the day night cycle on the options.
Good call. Boo boo. I need to learn. I can't just- you should have played the tutorial. I just did.
That's what I'm doing. I'm learning how to play. Hey, you should have done the tutorial. I'm doing
it right now. That's what I'm doing. All right, options. Gameplay. Day night cycle. Yeah, I changed
it to Fahrenheit. Whatever. People are gonna be really bad. Okay, turn off the day night cycle. I
just want it to be light. Okay, so road. I want a medium road. You're not even gonna let me build a
medium road. Oh, I actually did fail the tutorial. Okay. All right, so let's go with- this is fine.
Go straight up. Okay, I gotta- I gotta- no, no, no, no, no. I didn't- no, I gotta plan this out.
Oh, I can't even do zoning yet. So, here we go. I want up here. We're gonna go into the city here.
Then this is gonna, uh, curve out this way. This is gonna be fucking residential area. Pause the game.
So, this is residential. Over here. Right there. No curves. No curves. Why? Invalid shape. Distance
too short. You don't need a huge fucking road. Okay, now from here, let's go- let's do a few
streets. Just two or three streets. Just like little ones. Just like that. This is just- just
little roads. Just little streets. Like that. Just little ones, not big ones. These are different
streets. What are you doing? I'm making- I'm doing a- I'm writing a big F for fuck you! For
con- con- controversially making fun of me! How does that sound? Oh, we had a raid right now?
Who? What? Uh, is that what the- uh, hi guys. Whoever you are. What do you mean? What do you mean
raid? I don't see a raid. Who? Where? Okay, that's enough. That's enough. That's enough.
So, this is the get in. All right, so you get in, and well, there's that street. Oh, look at all-
look at this nice place. Look at this cool place. This is to get out. This is like, oh bye, we're
leaving. See you later. All right, bye. I don't know. Do you not understand highways? I can't even
build a fucking highway. Yes, you can. What- what? Why is everything grayed out? Six lane- six lane
one-way road is what I should have done. Keep looking at the tabs. Two- it's the tabs, not the
options. I can't build a highway, guys. Like, I physically can't build this. I already looked at
that. It's fine. Ignore chat. That's what I'm gonna do. All right, so this is uh, cool. Cool,
let's go up here. And then, from here, let's have this connect. I'm gonna curve it. I know you said
don't curve your roads. Don't curve roads. But, I'm gonna do it. Looks like shit. Let's go- we're
gonna go out a little further. No, no, no, no, no, no. This is just at dead ends. All dead ends.
Fuck it. Only dead ends. We'll go one more over here. Okay, this is where the houses are gonna be.
There'll be like a fucking park or something right here. Relax.
It's not even. It's not supposed to be. There's gonna be a big park here. Okay, now let's go-
so this is like some, you know, houses people live here. And then we're gonna go this way for
some shopping centers. Sounds good to me. Shop- use shopping centers. So you turn- this intersection
right here will do. Like this. All right, and then we got some- there's a shopping unit over here.
Key. Let's curve it down here. And there's gonna be a bunch of shopping. Shopping. Perfect. Okay.
Now, what the fuck do I- how do- how the fuck do people leave? From here we got residential,
residential, residential. There's your water pump. There's your fucking, uh,
is where the water comes from over here. Power is gonna be right here as well. We need industry.
We need like a place where all the fucking stuff happens. Okay, so from here, this is gonna be
industry road. Look, it's- see, it's like a big intersection. I know what the fuck I'm doing.
Industry up here. Done. So this is where like power plants and the pump shit and they're gonna
be connected and then down here. Okay, I'm done for a little bit. I've got- no, I gotta make the
way out. This is how you get out of here. What the hell are you doing? Don't do a curved road.
No curved roads. Is that okay? Press E when building curved roads. That's all right, isn't it?
That's fine. That's fine. Holy shit, big bits. That's a lot of bits. That's too-
Freddy Dread, another 200 fucking dollars. 20,000 dollars in bits. That's technically correct what
I just said. 20,000 dollars in bits, which is converted into 200 dollars into, uh, into human
money. He just paid for the game. Thanks, yeah, thanks for buying all the game and the DLC and
all the music we're not listening to. Uh, what's- what's one that I purchased? Mars?
Concerts? Is this- Country Road, here we go. The ads?
Hold on, it's like GTA?
Okay, game's paused. Uh, Freddy, seriously though, hope you're staying safe, my boy.
I'm in day six of quarantine since I flew on a plane from California. I'm slowly losing my damn
mind thanks for streaming. Yeah, it's- it's happening pretty much everywhere now. Just don't-
just fucking don't go anywhere. Don't do anything you don't have to do. Stay the fuck in your damn
house. If you- if you're in a place that has, uh, currently on lockdown, stay in your house.
Don't go anywhere you don't have to go. Don't fucking go to- hey, no, I think it's a good time
for me to go, uh, shopping and go all over the place. Let me go to a fucking concert.
Don't do that. Stay the fuck in your house if you're under one of these lockdowns. And watch
City Skylines by Jerma985. Seriously, thanks for the 200 fucking dollars, dude. You give so much
money to this channel. It's unbelievable. Yeah, don't go into crowds. Like, just don't- like,
don't do it. There's no reason to do it. There's no reason to. Don't do it. It's not fucking- it's
not worth it. Because even if you don't- let's say you're on, uh, like a lockdown. Or let's say you-
that's the- you're in one of these areas that's seen a lot of cases, right? If you don't- even
if you don't get the coronavirus, you- you could give it to somebody else, you know? You- you get
it on your hands, you know? You don't get sick, but you could give it to somebody else. Okay, mom. I'm
just being- I just want- listen to me. Play the game. Listen to me, kids. I will be your mother
right now and I will tell you these things. All right, anyways, let's go. Oh, wait, no, no, no,
keep pause. Keep pause. This is in the news. I know. I know. I know. I know you all know, but we need
to make sure we keep talking about it so we can get rid of this shit. All right, here we go.
Residential. Residential. Residential. All this is residential. These are all side streets.
Not this. There we are. Okay. Actually, I don't think I want houses here. No, I don't. I probably
could have done that way easier, but whatever. Actually, why- why not? That's fine. Uh, do I
want houses over here, though? Maybe there should be restaurants and shops and stuff on this side.
Okay. So, electricity. We need to have electricity from here. So, I'm just gonna go from- this- this-
is this wide enough? Is it- how can I see the wideness? Like, how much this- this- what the
circle looks like? Can I see it? Do I have to put it down first? Oh, I don't need to do this, do I?
Let the buildings get built first. Right, right, right, right. Okay, okay, good call. Good call.
Good call. But I need industry, too. Wait, don't blow all your money yet. Hold on. I need commercial.
Over here. Let's just do this area here for commercial. Right? That's smart, isn't it?
That just- that's enough. Industrial needs to be zoned over here. So, should I- should I make
industry over here, or just do this, like, down here? Yeah, okay. Looks alright. All right, cool.
Now I got enough. Let's let this play out, and I'm gonna build some electricity. I provide jobs
for citizens and produce goods for local businesses. Industry uses a lot of water
and produces ground pollution to its surroundings, so don't put it near houses.
Safe distance away from residential, right? I had the right to do. Okay, let's go.
Pick up the houses. Let's get them built. We're gonna need power here really soon.
Okay, we got our first house built. First house that needs power. Wait till these are all built,
and then I'm gonna do the electricity. You just go maybe potentially one power plant, dumping unit,
power plant, and a dumping unit. There's no such- there's no such thing as down river,
it's all just a stale river, right? He's doing better than 80% of chat. Thank you.
I want that- Twitch, where's my gold medal I can give to people? Where's my gold medal?
It's not VIP. It's temporary, like, 20 minute gold medal you give to somebody.
Why? I want it. No, not Reddit gold. All right, it is- it is like Reddit gold,
but it doesn't cost any money. The streamer does it. All right, here we go.
All right, build. Hurry up. Hurry the fuck up. Hurry the fuck up. Hurry the fuck up.
Why are these not getting built? Game sucks. All right, here we go. This- can one power these?
Build hard- I need to build. Can I- speed it up. Let's go. Hurry up. Hurry up. Why- why is
the other- why is it not being built down here? Is there a reason why they're not being built down
here? It's just gradual. Oh, okay. So, start correcting me if I'm incorrect. If I go like this,
I just need one- oh my god. I just need one for here, and then one- I don't need that many, right?
Uh, pause it. That's a hundred community subs. Thanks for the fucking insane, ridiculous amount
of money. That's a hundred subs. It was 200 bucks from FreddyDread, now it's a hundred community
subs from Zyxia. That's so much. Thank you. Just one connects to the blue, okay? So, like, if I go
like this, out to here, and let's say for the power plant there, that's correct, right? Yes. Okay, good.
Good. He's getting it. Oh, I'm getting it. This game's sick. I'm fucking so excited. I'm wicked
happy. All right. So, let me build the power plant first. So, this is where industry is going to be.
This is the- all right. So, this is where it's going to be. Bang. We go right there, and would
you look at that? Electric. Very, very cool. All right. This needs power, too. Oh, shit. Okay. Well,
we'll wait for a second. So, this is powering everything. Okay, now we need- and it was water.
Okay, water. Same deal. Water pump, right here, and then a water dumping unit. Water drain pipe. Oh,
shit. This is- how do you- there's no stream. I guess, is it going- it's going this way?
Let me see. It's going that way. So, oh, I have to go- as long as I just do it right here,
technically, right? Just need to swap them. All right. Swap these out.
So, the pumping station needs to go here, like right here, and then the dump station goes here.
So, it'll be dumping that way, or even like here. That's fine. Dumping station here. That's better.
Okay. So, then they're pumping clean water here, and they're dumping dirty water there.
Sounds easy. Water pipe. Here we go. So, this has to hit all this shit. All of them. It's not symmetrical.
It's not symmetrical. It's not symmetrical. I want- ban them. Ban them all. Ban them all. Okay,
cool. Water pipe this way. Ooh, this is fun. This is like an iPad game with all the money.
I like this game. All right. So, that's water. They'll connect them. Okay. So, we're all good,
right? Do these need to be connected to this? Everything have to be connected. Everything.
Oh, the sewage. Right. All right. Sewage. So, sewage connects to here, and they just have to
be connected. So, as long as this is here. But does this have to go across everything as well?
So, this will take on the properties of this whole entire unit here, right? Like that. So,
this is now taking on the everything. All these units. So, should I go from here to here too?
Like this. This is taking on all these units. No. Don't have to do that. Okay. What you're saying
is I should be- I should be careful with using these units. Twice as much. I should be- I should
be double careful. Be double careful. So, be like BB. Like a BB unit. Let's see. I'm glad everybody
fucking hates it. Makes me so fucking happy. All right. So, we need power to everything,
which I need more than that. Well, I'm getting it. So, well, they have to build first. Let's
go build. TV working again. Nice. I can watch my reality shows. These need power too. Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. Oh, shit. Okay. Hold on. This is fucking cool. All right. Let's go.
The real germa just came through. They're not getting water? What is what the water works?
Showering with bottled water is expensive. Wait, what? It's pumping right now. Oh, is this not
pumping? It's not connected? Yes, it is. What? Wait, hold on. It needs- It does have power. Connect to
the- Pump to the side of the building. Wait, it wasn't connected? Oh, shit. I thought it was
connected. How am I- Is this connected? Okay. We're good. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. I only have
$17,000. Oh, fuck. They need power here. Wait. All right. You need power too. Everybody needs power.
Everybody needs power. Take it. Why are these not powered? All right. Let's go. But there's no
plumbing here. Uh-oh. There there is. All right. We're fine. Our first little town is working
completely as intended. This feels like I'm teaching my mother how to use her phone.
Well, that would be accurate if your mother has never used a telephone in her entire life.
If your mother woke up one day after using rock stones and newspapers to get all of her information
and you showed her a cell phone for the first time. Yes, it's going to take her a little while
to figure it out. It's going to take her a minute. Yes. That's- That's probably pretty accurate.
Cave mom. All right. What about- How do I start charging like absurd taxes?
All right. Wait, wait, wait. Why are people not using their garages?
Everyone's parking on the streets. They don't have garages. Yes, they do. But how many fucking
cars do you have? One, two, three, four. And that implies that there's at least two in here.
Everybody has so many cars. This person even has a clown car. All right. Cool. So we've got
$15,000 of things to look when people have people need jobs. All right. Looking good.
Tax them. They're too rich. All right. Let's look at the money market. Okay. 756 bucks.
How many people live here? 226. All right. Where's the tax button? All right. Power,
how much electricity should we be using? Can we drop the amount of electricity that's allowed?
I'm at a net negative right now. What happened? Oh, wow. Strawberries are expensive. Oh, but still
so worth it. Strawberry season. Shit. Okay. So why- I need more commercial buildings.
Well, this is- What is this? Denny's? Why is nobody in here? Why is nobody going to the store?
More housing is wanted. Hey, look. I got plenty of housing being built. Why is nobody going-
Is there no power over here? Yeah, there is. This counts, right? Look at the three bars.
No demand for commercial zone. Low demand for residential. Low demand for industrial.
Nobody wants anything. Okay. Let's do some more. Let's build some more on residential
road. Um, I can't- I can't just make a road go through somebody's house, can I?
What happens if I do this? Oh, it'll destroy that house. All right. That's not necessary.
We can go like this. A little bit more out here. Out here. And then we're going to connect them.
Not symmetrical. Fine. That's okay. It's okay. It's okay. Everybody stop. Here we go. Boom.
You still want houses now. Oh my God. I need money. I need money. How much money does this cost?
Millions. Tax, tax, tax. I hope it doesn't rain tomorrow. No rain. Wishing for sunshine.
Housing brings in money. That's true. That's true. Okay. So, uh, let's start by-
how's the industry looking over here? Are we digging? Are we constructing? Is it- now there's
a demand for houses. 400 people live here. More. All right. Is there a way I can delete the grid
and just look at my city without any, uh, like to immerse myself in what it looks like?
How do I do that? Click on the X. Oh, there we go. Ooh. This is- this is really ugly right here,
but it's fine. This is turning out to be kind of a little place, right? This is fine.
And then from here, we're going to go over this way. More residential. This would be like the hub
where the- how do I build like a fun park? I want like a- I want like a water park right here. Can
you do that? I want to build like a water park. And then up here, maybe like a curve this way.
Up here. More residential. All right. We need like little residential road. Lizard,
little red li- lizard road. All right. I'm making money now. I'm plus $72.
My weekly income is $88. I'm doing well. What's this say? We're good. Yeah, we're in the green.
This is good. Oh, right. Sorry about that. I want to apologize if I sound a little
overexcited. I've got this really exciting jazz show. Let's just say it's hard to contain
my enthusiasm. Oh, sorry. I'm sorry about this. Little Hamlet. For each population of 480.
Now I get taxes and now I get loans. New services. Garbage, health care, education, and campuses.
Kylo Ren wanted to say sorry too. All right. We can get a medical clinic. Elementary school.
Landfill. Cycling and community school. Oh, lock schools. I'm looking fucked up today. I'm sorry.
Okay. Garbage and industry. Health care. All right. Industry. Hey, waste management.
To manage waste and garbage, build a landfill site or an incineration plant. Wait, pause the
fucking game. Idiot. Relax. Waste management produces pollution so the facility should be
placed far away from residential areas. Garbage that piles up in residential areas also causes
ground pollution over time. Make sure you have enough garbage facilities. Landfill sites and
incineration plants send out garbage trucks to pick up trash. Make sure they can get around the
city easily. Good connections with large roads help garbage trucks get around the city fast.
Okay, we need big roads. We're placing a building. Observe the roads to see how large of an area
will serve efficiently. All right. This is a recycling center. Citizens can recycle more
different kinds of waste when the city has a recycling center, taking less garbage pile up.
The center produces small amounts of raw materials from the waste. Yeah, let's do that.
Oh, this is loud. All right. So this is... Let's do a recycling center. Not here. Not... It's
got to be like out. It's going to be like a garbage... All right. Up here on the hill will be like the
dump. It's too expensive. What do you mean? How much is this? It's $16,000. How much is this?
$4,000. Is this industry? Does industry not give a shit about how loud it is over here?
They do. They don't care. Not as much. I think I'm going to build another road back here and
have the garbage dump be over here. Yeah, that's the plan. Go over here. Like industry out here.
Let's go this way. This is where the fucking garbage is. Shit, I need a big ass road, don't I?
Big road. All right, we need a big ass road. Six lane road. A big ass road up here so they can get
up here easily. Wait, I need only one way. Six lane, one way road. What is... Stop. Don't, don't,
don't, don't, don't. Too big, too big, too big. How about one of these four lanes? Will this be
good? All right. Up here? No, no, stop, stop, stop. Why? Why one way? So they can all... Oh,
they can't ever get back in. One way trip to the dump. You can't... You stuff them all out in a
huge six lane road and they never can come back in. All right, that's good. This gives plenty of
room for huge dump trucks to come in and out of the fucking dump city. Oh, fuck. Stop going so fast.
Health care. Keep your citizens healthy. Make sure they have enough health care facilities and
the buildings have good road connections. Things such as pollution, crime, this crime in this game
and contaminated water will reduce the health of your citizens. Ambulances travel out to pick up
sick people and patients can also arrive using their own cars. Helicopters can reach destinations
without road access and are not affected by traffic jams. Your citizens age and eventually
will perish of old age no matter how good their health is. The living citizens wish to respect
their loved ones by having a cemetery in the city to bury them. There's a lot in this game.
Let's just get 50 dollars. Chris, thank you Chris for the 50 dollars. 5,000 fucking bits.
Jerma, we all know that with your age you could be the dad of most of your viewers. So the only
reasonable thing for you during these times will be to distract us. Start streaming every single day.
I mean, I could be, I could be your dad. It's possible. No, no, no, it's not. It's not. That implies
wow. No, I'm not. I, there's no chance I'm your dad, okay? I'm 90, I'm 100% positive I'm not your dad.
All right, I got it. I get it. People are sick. You gotta make, uh, health care facilities. So
let's make a dump right here. Dump activated. Recycling center on the other side and they can
fucking, they can be like the Twix brothers and constantly be in competition. Now this is too much
money, isn't it? That's too much money. Do I have more than one? Landfill storage. I don't think I
need more than one right now. So that's connected. So that is doing, that's fine. Okay, now we need
medical facility. Medical clinic. So it should be, they'll be like a little hospital center.
No, it's gotta be like on the, it's gonna be like over here. They don't, this is not like
noise or anything, right? Large building. So that's fine. It'll be like right here.
Is that too much? Is it loud? It doesn't say it's loud. Noise pollution zero. What are you talking
about? It's loud. Oh, it's fine right there. Look at how happy everybody is. Oh, the music is loud.
Turn it down. I don't want to listen to this. How about city radio? That's all right. Okay,
so we have our dump kind of play. Does this need power? Wait, wait. This just, this is a Spider-Man
PS4 theme song? All right, this needs power. Do you like jazz? So how much power does, can one,
okay, I guess I can look. So electricity consumption, 10 megawatts. Production, 40
megawatts. So I'm fine for a while. This is already occupied by what? Oh my God, have I been
delayed this whole time? No, thank God. I thought my voice was delayed by like a thousand milliseconds
because we played the weed last time. All right, this is good. Healthcare for everyone. Citizens
flock to get treatment for various ailments. Blue shots. Okay, cool. How much can one hospital
do? Patients zero to 100. All right, so did the garbage trucks see? Look, they're coming in and
out very, very effectively. How much can this do? Garbage trucks in use, two out of 15, zero percent
full. So when it's full, what do I do with it? This is too epic right now. Deep focus. That's
better. All right, so now we got any school. Education. Children need elementary schools.
Pause it. Teenagers attend high school and young adults can get educated at a university if one is
available. Education is complete when a citizen ends their age phase while enlisted in a school.
Takes time. A working school system produces educated adults who can fill high-level jobs
in industries and offices, thus raising the city's technology level. Observe the roads to see how
large of an area will serve it efficiently. Public libraries provide entertainment and a small chance
for us all citizens to become more educated. The chance to become more educated decreases with each
education level. All right, so we need a, we need an elementary school. This is a hospital. Elementary
school will go right next to the hospital. Okay, if I plan on having a bunch of more,
it's gonna have to be like back here. All right, the elementary school is gonna be like here.
Maybe two elementary schools. It'll be right here. This is gonna be, how much money does it cost?
10,000. All right, you're gonna be idiots for a while. I need more money. Let's go.
Yeah, you guys are gonna be pretty stupid for a little while. You don't have any water. How the
fuck is it? Oh, fuck. Oh, I hate it. I can't do anything about it. It doesn't matter. This is my
first time. Who cares? Whatever. It's my first time. Does this need water up here? Does this
dump need water? I mean, that thing looks like shit anyways. All right, I'm 52 dollars, 52 human
people dollars. What is this? Population. Okay, now I can do taxes. Here we go. Taxes.
Low density residential zone. Okay, tax on income. So, 724 dollars a week or a month.
Nine percent tax. We're gonna make, we're gonna make 12 percent. We're gonna do it 12 percent across
the board. 12 percent. All right, we're gonna lower the taxes on the citizens to seven percent. We're
gonna raise taxes on commercial zones. We're gonna lower the taxes on the people. Why is everybody
saying Bernie? I'm talking about lowering taxes. You're doing his voice. Was I? No, I was not doing
his voice. I was not doing his voice. No, I wasn't. Was I a little bit low? We're gonna lower the tax.
I was a little. I was a little bit. I, it just comes out now. Who's leaving? Who the fuck are you?
What are you leaving? Oil truck. Get back. We need that. Wow, this looks like shit. I didn't even make
this. This looks terrible. All right. Oh, let's make a tunnel. Let's make a, can I make a tunnel
over here? No, that's too much money. I need to start small. People are just leaving in droves.
What? Exporting. Oh, hot dog. Exporting hot dogs. Hot dog exporting is our number one export in
fucking Wink Dinkville. We export hot dogs. Imagine, imagine that's the number one thing
your city is known for exporting. That's an embarrassing Wikipedia article. Oh, what's the
number one thing that, that Wink Dink city is known for? It's gotta be infrastructure or maybe
electricity or textile. You're the number one exporter of hot dog meat. Oh, okay. Cool, I guess.
How do I get, what are those palm trees? Rename the city. Bottom left. Why is this place called
Las Vegas? What? I didn't name it. I did not name it. No, I didn't. You guys, you guys have seen the
whole thing the whole time. It just, it just pulls your IP. IP. Los Vegas. City skyline says
track your low. What's with this money? What's it saying? Money? Percentage. What does that mean?
Was a little bubble. Taxes are too high. Taxes are too, who said that? Oh, the quiet corner shop
says taxes are too high. What do you sell here? Unicorn jewelry? Unicorn jewelry. All right. Hold
on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Taxes are a little too, taxes are a little too high. Oh,
it's 15%. That's too high. Well, I want a 12%. There, 12%. Happy? You can sell your unicorn
jewelry store. Shit. They're like the four people that come in a week. Sorry about your taxes there.
Is that, that was toxic? What? What was it? Unicorn jewelry store. That's toxic. No, it's, what?
Wait, is this your truck? I will lower your taxes if this is your truck. Donut van. This is the
Simpsons. Where's the Simpson house? Where's Homer Simpson? All right. Stop paying, I gotta,
stop paying attention. Pay attention. What's going on over here? Bug spray van.
They didn't know what to do. They got caught up there. All right. How are we looking?
What are you doing over here? This guy's out for like a Sunday drive. No, this is the only
way to leave. Right. Hold on a second. Does the, does the, does the bug spray guy and the donut
guy work in the same building? I feel like that shouldn't be a thing. Why did the bug spray guy
and the donut guy both work out of the same shack? Okay. Let's keep going. What's going on?
This is pollution. How do I clean this? I'm making some money. What are the needs? More houses. Good.
Let's do some more roads. We're doing big, big. Okay. I need a highway. Correct me if this is
stupid. I can't even do a highway. I need 2,600 people. Okay. Two lane road, two lane one way road.
Road. Let's get some bigger roads. Let's go out here. Four lane road. No, this is a big hub right
here, right? I need, uh, I don't, I'm not very good at city planning. It's like a, I'm going to go
this way. Oh, this is like, yeah, this is a commercial. So we're going to go from here.
This is like a big, let's get out of the way here. Out here. This is a little town. Here comes
another town. That's why our camera upgrade road. Oh shit. I can't. Should I do this?
I can upgrade them while they're money. It's all right. Hold on.
Oh, what are they doing? Oh, how do I undo, undo, undo, undo, undo? Is there an undo?
Fuck. Control Z. Doesn't work. It's okay. Whatever. I'm, this is fine. This is like the
getting out of the city into the bigger city. This is just some little town. Okay. So I'm going to
go up here. The new one's being built. It's fine. All right. We need more houses now. Now, now, now,
now, now. I need to, oh shit. I need more power and let me think this out first. Hold on. I need to
small road here. If I bring this down here, because the garbage trucks need better routes,
right? Let me do a bigger road because the garbage trucks can't just have one fucking way. Do they?
I mean, they, they need to have like a bigger way to go or lane road. I'm going to go.
No, that's fine. Okay. Whatever. I'm just going to go. All right. So this is going to be residential
out here. Elevation. What did I just do? This is going to be all residential zoning. Residential.
We need more. Page up. Page up. Okay. This is all right. And we need a little bit more commercial
down here. We'll need a place to work. Yeah. This is like the shopping city center. All right. This
is fine. This. All right. That's a lot of stuff. There's still no elementary school. Oh, they're
just whatever. How much is an elementary school? Like a hundred bucks. Elementary school. Shit.
They're going to be idiots. Um, okay. How many do I need? Two. I'm going to need one out. I need
one here. Fuck. Damn it. This is going to be, all right. The people at the end of this road are going
to be exponentially stupider than the people at the front of the road. These people don't get to,
if that's not, that's not, I don't have any money. Okay. I'm out of money. Go live.
Would you just tweet? Mayor supports education. Citizens approve of this.
No more homeschooling. Good. Okay. Cool. Let's go. Hand food, water, flashlight, first aid kit. I'm
prepared for anything. Bring it on nature. Uh, okay. There's tons of houses. Wait, any, uh,
any debt infrastructure here? This is a fucking stressful game. This is a stressful ass game.
I'm, I'm prepared. Wait, what did the person say? The person did not like the taxes.
Would I live in this city? Yeah. What's wrong with it? What's wrong with living right here?
Is there a problem with living right here? School right across the street.
Get in the car, drive right down the road. There's a fucking Denny's.
There's a, there's a sky trust. There's a bank, diner, people hanging out. Let's go. Why would
I not live here? What are you talking about? This is perfect. I should rename this place. This is
perfect, though. I know you're looking for electricity. I gotta wait. Worthy village. Here
we go. I upgraded. New features, districts, policies, second loan, district specializations,
and services policies. New emergency. Oh, there's no police. This police, new industry specializations,
self-sufficient building, organic and local produce, new power usage policies, water use,
new buildings. Okay. I'm getting overwhelmed. Unique buildings. Have I unlocked any?
The statue of liberty. Okay. Let's put the statue of liberty here. How much is it?
$210,000. Should I get a loan to put the statue of liberty in the middle of my town?
Look at how happy everybody will be with the statue of liberty.
No, that's, that's me throwing this into the trash. I'm not throwing this away.
Okay. I need power. Uh, do you have another power plant? 20. No, I don't need it yet. Can I go?
Okay. If, can I go from here to here? Will it connect? As long as I go from here to here, right?
Okay. So this one plant is using a shitload of power. 21 MWs a second. All right. Cool. So that's,
wait, I could have gone from, oh, right. I gotta come from here to here or here to here
or here to here. Whatever. Android and Ginoid robot models released.
Sick. There's only 21, uh, mutatable watts, whatever it is. How much money do I got?
Now we make the taxes 98% for one day. I'm going to solve every, let's solve every world problem.
You ready? I'm going to make all taxes 95% for two days and then it goes back to normal.
There you go. There you go. I just fixed everything. I'll take in like $600 million
and then I can build like 300 schools up here and have like five more dumps,
two more electrical power plants, like 5 million more houses. Is that going to, will that work?
And then I can build a statue. What a waste of fucking resources. Like this, this is,
this is why the world doesn't fucking work the way it should. You know what I'm saying?
Cause like if, if like the governor of fucking Wink Dinkville got a check for fucking $800 million,
he probably would build the Statue of Liberty in his own fucking. Yeah. I decided that it was
the right thing to do with the city budget this week was to build the Statue of fucking Liberty
too. How does Mike, no, no, no, no. I got it back. I got it back. That's your Liberty to the sequel.
And what I, I've never been to the Statue of Liberty before, but I just, there's a sign on it.
I was, I'll just paraphrase it on mine. It's let's go get everybody over here and have a great day.
And bring on the fucking, bring on the Red Sox, whatever the fuck it's called.
That's having a good use of city money. Police officers small. Oh shit. I need,
I need a police officer. I need one police officer. Okay. Fires can occur in your city to
prevent, wait, the city can burn down. You didn't have a property. Oh, hold on. You didn't have a
fire department. It gets fired. The closest fire department building sends out a fire truck.
How long it takes to arrive depends on the size of the roads and how well connected areas in the
city are. So this is, oh fuck. Oh my God. How are these people going to have their houses are on
fire? Depending on the size, multiple, depending on the size, multiple fire engines can be dispatched
to put it out. Make a connection. So like from like here to here. Oh, that's a great fucking idea.
Oh look, who cares about this thing? We can go like this. Is it going to delete their house?
Yep. Oh no, you just got mad because the huge road came in. Is that what you were mad about?
What are you so mad about? What? That person does not want a big road. Why? Because it's a
busier street now. Oh, why? Well, you're on the main road. Okay. Well, that's, look at how much
better. Look at this new traffic pattern. Miller street. Wait, I can change the names? What does
priority road mean? Um, about, I don't know. Uh, how about, I don't know if I can just name roads
after presidents. Uh, Andrew Jackson way. Whatever. I don't know. James street. Uh, how about uh,
George Washington Avenue or other, what other like public figure? No, no, no, no. It's going to be
like Lord of the Rings and shit. No, fuck that. Yeah. Nobody. We talked about this like a fucking
year ago. Why I had no road that roads are always like presidents. Um, like public figure is, uh,
famous places, right? Why is it not like famous actors? We, we use the same street names. Why
the fuck wouldn't it be like Schmiegel Avenue or like Aragorn way or like the Khaleesi Boulevard
or something? I don't understand why we've run out of names for us to, why do we have to name
every fucking road after like George Washington, replace half of the George Washington avenues
with like, I don't know, fucking like Super Mario way, Garfield, Garfield court. I don't know.
All right. How do I get out of this? Zelda Boulevard. We've read, there's no more names.
We've used them all. He's a Redditor. What are you talking about? What does that have to do
with anything to do with Reddit? All right, let's go. Andrew Jackson way. Why isn't the local
government doing anything to stop the fires? What? What building is on fire? Wait, what's this?
Is this house currently being burgled? It's a fucking clown burglar. This, where's there a fire?
I need a fire device out putter unit. Wait, there's like a meteor response team. All right,
just put it. I need a firehouse. I need one. Uh, like it doesn't matter. Just anywhere like right
here. I need one. I need one. I have to have one. I need a police station. Pause. Police patrol the
city to keep crime under control. To maintain a low crime rate, make sure police service buildings
have a good connection. Okay, so how much is a police service building? Police cars are dispatched
from police station to patrol the city. 12,000 bucks. Okay, I have enough. Um, I have to kick
somebody out. Police station. Right here. Right here. This is right here. Look at that. Oh, right
there. Right on Andrew Jackson way. There everybody. No more crime. Long arm of the law reaches the
city. I feel safer already. Good. Now you're about to be in big fucking trouble. Okay, so,
uh, I need more houses. How are taxes doing? Let's increase taxes. Let's increase residential taxes
to like eight, nine percent. We need homes. We need food. All right, how many do we have?
I don't have enough money. I gotta chill for a little bit. Increase taxes.
World. Europe. Super Mario. What? We need children. Arrest him. Get in there. Why are they taking the
house down? Upgrade underway. Wait, wait, they're upgrading their house? They're doing...
Oh shit, they're doing upgrades to their houses. I don't know they could do that. What if they run
out of land? Okay, we need a home. Homes. Homes. Homes. Homes. Homes. Homes. Homes. Homes. Homes.
Um, fuck. This is commercial. This is commercial buildings. And then from here, uh, more residential
in here. Done. I'm a fucking, I'm a fucking goddamn genius. I'm the smartest person in this room.
You want me to prove it? You're the only person in this room. Yeah, you get it. Okay, I can't do
this because the power lines are in the way. We got a raid. A raid from Limealicious. What's going on,
guys? What the fuck's up? Thanks for the raid. Welcome. We're doing, um, we're making a city in
City Skylines. It's a fun game. We make your own city. He's acting normal. Oh yeah, let me,
let me just prove you. There's nothing, I'm not going to just fucking instantly react strangely
to something. Okay, here we go. Thanks for the raid. Welcome, guys. I hope you're having a good
fucking day. I know, I'm acting weird. Right here. Curve it. Come on. I can't, what the fuck? I gotta
replace this shit. I can, I can move this, right? I just like delete the shit and move it. They're
not going to have power for like one day. All right, what are we looking at from here?
Done. All right, sick. We need more high demand. Okay, let's go from here.
We're going to circle this back. I need a shitload of houses. So we're going to go from here,
a boink, and then we're going to, uh, no, this is, don't curve it. We're going to go from here
to, uh, yeah, whatever. It's like a little side street. Yeah, this is fine. That's perfect. Okay.
Uh, all right. Now we just, all these are houses and then there's gotta be like a fucking school.
What's this? Wait, what? Somebody living in somebody else's backyard? Wait, somebody's living
in somebody else's backyard? What the fuck? Whose house is this? Okay. Uh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry that
I have to do this, but I'm sorry. This needs to happen. I need a connection to this part of the
town. What do you mean stop? I have to do this. You're destroying, you're destroying a family
building a golf course and I didn't even do it the right way. I didn't even, I look, it's crooked.
Okay, here we go.
And now we've succeeded in letting you drive the unduly dementia
test drive one. Okay, here we go. What scientists for decades claimed was beyond the realm of safe
driving.
I made a better idea, better idea. Hold on. No, no, no, no, no, no. We're going to do the big one
going off the way across like this. There we go. That's smarter. Okay. Cool. Good. I mean, I can't
do this. I have no money. I have negative 88 bucks. Okay. Play, play, play, play, play, play.
There we go. I got 200. All right. Connect this shit. All right. That looks okay. Now I'm going
to build a ton of houses. This is all houses. Uh, delete this shit. It's unnecessary. Okay. There
we go. All houses, just, just as many as can possibly fit over here. Oh my God. That's not
a house. That's not a house. That's not a house. How do I undo that? How do I undo? How do I undo?
How do I undo? Pause it. How do you undo? How do I change that? How do I stop that from happening?
Right click. Okay. Right. Oh, thank God. Okay. Here we go. Beautiful. Beautiful. Beautiful.
Beautiful. Beautiful. Beautiful. That shit off. I can't believe it's taken me like 10 years to
play this game. Imagine having a commercial building be in your side yard. All right. Make
sure we got everything. All the everything we need. We need some elect. We need power. We need all
this junk. So this is going to go from here. Inefficient. I know probably, but what do you
want me to do? This is hopefully we'll hit the people in the middle. Hopefully we'll hit the
people in the middle. Hit the people in the middle. I need a thousand dollars. Hurry up. Hurry up. I
need a thousand dollars. Oh, I can speed up time. Hurry up. I need a thousand dollars. Going to get
shit. These people, this purpose, these people are going to have,
ah, it sucks. Is it okay? Will that work? All right. That's sufficient. Now we need electricity.
Electricity from here to there we go. And there it is. Cool. And there we go. What's wrong over
here? Tiny town. You're doing a tuber thing. Am I? Probably am. Oh, park. That's what I wanted.
Parks. 1500 people. Parks and plazas, industry area, multi-unique buildings, concerts, landscaping,
park area. I want to make a park. All right. This is, I'm going to need another power plant,
aren't I? What's, what's their problem over here? Not enough workers. Oh, we need more workers. I
need more people. All right. They're coming. More workers are coming. All right. I need another
medical clinic. We need another one of these, don't we? This will be all right. Police. We got
a police station. I need another school. Elementary school. That's going to be, um, over here. Oh,
these people are real dumb. Okay. Uh, fuck. I don't, I don't know what to do. I don't know
what to put it. I need a high school. Everyone has a fourth grade education. Yeah, I know. I
don't have enough money for a high school. Public library. Ooh, this will help. This is going. All
right. It's raining. That's all right. What about right here? We just have a public library
right in the middle of your neighborhood. Public library is going right in the middle of the
neighborhood. Yeah, sorry. It's, that's happening. Okay. Public library. That'd be sick to live right
next to a library. That would be awesome. How would that not be cool to live next to a public
library? That'd be cool. You can just go read books and shit anytime you want. Walk out the door.
All right. That's good. We now need more industry. Industry. Make a playground. All right. Park,
park, park. I don't make a park. I want it right here. Wait, this is all commercials. Shit, isn't
it? No, there's nothing here. All right. The park is going to be right here. Park. Decorative
elements raise citizens happiness, which is a key element in helping build buildings evolve. All
right. Small playground. Must be on a roadside. Oh, all right. Well, right here. Perfect. Look at
that. Perfect little entryway. Bingo. Playground. And a small park on a roadside. How about right on
Andrew Jackson Way? Yeah. Yeah. What about other parks? I don't have money for any of this.
I love the new park. Can't read. All right. How about you make custom parks? I think that's a
little advanced for me right now. How's everybody doing? We need more industry. All right. We need
more industry up here. Industry. Right here. All right. That's, that's all right for now. I don't
want to spend too much money. Wait, we'll get it. We're encroaching. How much? What's the, what's
the encroachment line? I don't want to get, I don't want to have it be too far over here.
Everyone okay? How's everybody doing? We're good. Global happiness is pretty good. Connect the
road so people aren't a thousand miles from the library. What? What are you talking about? How do
you need water? The one guy that needs water. You're right on the front of one fucking house
that doesn't have any utilities. God damn it. Oh, it's so stupid, but I am gonna do it. Whatever.
Connect the roads so people don't have to drive that far to go to the library in their backyard.
People in the southern residential area. Oh, connect the top. Oh, you mean here.
Honey, you want to go to the park? Yeah, we could go right there or we could drive across the whole
city and end up there. Just fucking walk. Take the, go out your back door and just walk there. What's
the problem? Well, this person's house is going to get destroyed. I don't like that. Okay. That's
good. No. Oh, now you're going to get punished. I'm putting the waste management facility right
next to your library. All right. That's better. This is looking fine. I bet you half you didn't
think I was even going to get this far. I'm certain that at least 20% of people in this chat right
now didn't think I was going to get past how to use the grid. Oh shit. What's going on? Oh,
any water. They have electricity up here, right? Yeah. Did they? Did they? Okay. Let me just take
a sip of my fucking nice cold coffee. Can I do some more crime? I think I should produce, I should
do some more crime. Especially like over here. I'm going to build up this way and then we're
going to do a little bit more crime. There's literally no crime up here. Okay. Um, it's all
residential. I'll get built. It's a library. People aren't going to be so stupid. Let's increase taxes
a little bit, please. Taxes are going to be, uh, 12% across the board and 15% for industry
temporarily for a little while. All right. Let's go up here. What do we look at? Let's look at the
grid. Uh, what's the, we need more commercial. Let's do some commercial down here. Get some
more commercial space. Uh, this is like the whole commercial zone in the middle. And yeah, right
here. Let's go. What a great city. I would think of dreaming if I didn't know otherwise. See,
everyone's so happy. All right. That's enough. I don't want to go too far up here.
And then in the middle, I want the Statue of Liberty. There was a paid actor. That's okay.
All right. More. What do you think? More paid actor. How's Trash? Trash is doing okay, right?
It's only 8% full. Yeah. That's not enough. City's not big enough. All right. We're going to start
going up to the mountain area. I need a high school. I don't have enough money for a high school.
We need to wait. It looks pretty efficient. Now. Now. Water? Is there no water going over here?
Ah, shit. Oh, there's no fucking electricity over here either.
It doesn't reach. It doesn't reach. If I go like, if I go from here to here, will it reach?
Oh no, we're at capacity. Okay. I need another. All right. Pause it. We're at capacity. A little
wind farm. Cheap and clean energy from the wind. I'm assuming this is high wind spots.
Dude, let's just make like five of them up here and then connect them. Does it matter how close
these are? No. They can just, they can be right next to each other. Yes, it does. No. Put them
really close together. Is that what you do? Does it not matter? One guy. Okay. All right. I'm out of
money. And now I have to connect here. These are just both producing energy. So then go from here
to here. Done. Right? That's it. Did it. Hooray for the mayor. More green energy.
Why is this one not spinning? Okay. How much? What are we producing here? This is working,
right? 56 MWs. They think the tax is too high. Tax is too high. Uneducated. We're all dumb.
Zero available jobs. What are they even doing? Oh shit. Okay. Let's turn the taxes down and turn
the education up. Turn the education up. Turn the taxes down. We need lower taxes and smarter
people. Okay. Good. Taxes. 12%. All right. Is that making you happy? Thank you. Where's my high
school? We need at least a high school education. High school. $24,000. Have you lost your wallet?
I found black leather wallets. End of PM. It sounds like a loan. I need a loan. I'll pay it back.
I don't want to do anything insane. Budget. All right. We're gonna, let's take a look at
the here. Let's take the button. All right. Schools, universities, and campus areas where
a high budget can teach more students. Here we go. This is where we do, we do our city budget.
Okay. Electricity. Uh, that's fine. Water is fine. Garbage. We don't need that big of a garbage
budget. 70% on the garbage. We don't need, we don't need that many people doing garbage.
Was this medical? Health care. Raise a budget of health care. Let's have more vehicles. I think
we're fine. Uh, firemen. It hasn't been a fire, it has not been a fire yet. Okay. Crime. It's
been two robberies. There's only been a few robberies. This is a safe place. Okay. Education.
We need more education. More education. A lot more. Okay.
Uh, our parks and plazas. Keep them clean. Keep them organized.
Okay. Good budget.
Where's that, uh, where's that, um, school?
Where's the school?
Elementary. Where's my elementary schools?
Come on. I got so much money going to the elementary schools. You tell me this that
night you can't get more students in here. Get a high school. I'm taking out a fucking loan.
All right. I need a loan. I need money. Loans. Silver. Okay. You can only have three loans at
once. Loans can be repaid instantly with no extra cost. Okay. This is $20,000 in 52 weeks. Pay it
back. 5% interest. There's nothing. There's no money. Or this one is $60,000. 10% interest.
Give it to me. All right. I want a high school. High school right here. That works. Time to make
everybody smart. Wait. Put it like right here. Right here. Right, right, uh, right here. Space
already occupied. It's okay. Right in the middle. Right there. Now we have an educated group of
people. There we go. What's this thing? Public library. I already got one. Community school.
Small safety school allows children to get education and grow into educated adults.
And just Institute of creative arts. I don't have the money for that right now.
All right. Now I need like an elementary school over here. Elementary school. Wait,
we need more houses up here. Fuck. This is hard. City building is hard to do.
I need another elementary school up here. Okay. Two elementary schools and a high school.
I'm going to, okay, build houses up here and then same thing with this way.
Oh my God. It's more money just came in. Uh, just gave 10,000 bits, a hundred bucks.
Who's ready for some free shit? Well, I am apparently not enough educated workers. I'm
going for it. I need some slight education. Thanks for the a hundred fucking dollars.
Appreciate it. Thank you. You have an uneducated city. I know, but we're working on it.
More fucking money. Thank you guys. All right. Where's the high school? High school is right.
Where's it? Right here. Operating normally. It's students. There are 392 students,
high school students in the city. Look at this number. Everyone's freaking out.
Get my kid in there. God damn it. My son is 16 and he still doesn't know how to cow past 10.
He's still eating Cheerios at a high chair. Fill out the application. Get him in that school.
Okay. Fuck. I should have thought about this. Oh, it's on fire. Oh no, the tennis is on fire.
Put it out. We're good. Uneducated. Everybody's an uneducated worker.
Finally, we get some educated people in this one. They've been so desperate.
It's like calling up the bank. It's all like third graders. Hi, I'd like to, I'd like to make a,
yes, hi, I'm here. I'd like to make a withdrawal. Okay. Yeah, I would like to withdraw a hundred
dollars from the bank. I guess. Can you do that for me? And then they turn the fucking screen
around and they point at it and then ask, can you, and as much as shit you don't know and you just
desperately try to figure out, I use the fucking app at the bank. Thank you. Thank you. Thanks for
coming in. I appreciate that. Thank you. Can I help? Can I help an expert in wine?
The third graders can speak. They talk like this. Have you ever heard a third grader talk?
They talk like, can I have some of that, please? I'll take, they don't all talk like that. What?
They talk like this. I'll take one dust, please. I want one too. Yeah, they do. He's smoking crack.
Think of every second, think of like every eight-year-old. Yeah, I am one hatchet.
Am I thinking two or am I thinking like 12? That's like a three-year-old. Oh,
where I got it wrong. It's free school. It's like a 16 month old.
All right. What do we need? We need some more out. Three equals third grade. You know the logic.
All right. Here we go. Library users 12. How are we doing up here? What do we need? Nothing.
I got $47,000. What should I build more? Okay. Roads. Can I build a highway? No,
I can't build a fucking highway. Almost can. We're doing like a huge highway system over here.
This game is so fucked up. Click on earth. Let me click on earth. Wait, people are doing,
who's giving out game codes? Were you giving out game codes for what? What game is that?
Areas. What the fuck? New tile. New tile. I'm not ready for this. New tile. What? Thanks for
the amazing work you've done for the city. I have access now to this shit. Oh fuck. What's
going on up here? Abandoned. The drugs store has been abandoned. I've got to get out of here, man.
All you're sending me is fourth graders. They don't know how to handle prescriptions. They take naps
at work and I got to put them to bed. All right, I need more education. All right,
let's just do all schools. Like just a fucking hundred schools. Oh fuck. What's wrong with our
garbage collection service? Trash is piling up and it's swarming with flies. What? Garbage is piling
up. Okay, we did that. Uneducated trash to you is taking the bag of trash and opening the nearest
window and throwing the trash bag out of the window. That's trash. Oh, okay.
Okay, I need to slow down. Pause it. Trash. This one is currently landfill storage.
What are they talking about? What's going on? I don't understand. Oh, it lowered the budget.
All right, you can have some more money. All right, look at this. All right, we'll go back
to 75% capacity of the budget. Take down the parks. More education. 130%. This is a lot of money.
That's too much money. Ah, that's a lot of money. Keep it at 120. Okay, we need taxes. What's this?
High density residential zone. High density? Low density? Oh, I can do high density? What does
that mean? Low density residential zone. What is it? Wait, what is this? Paint the part of the city
you want to become a district. New districts will be named automatically but can be renamed later.
Apply special policy by selecting and clicking the district. Remove districts by painting areas
with the secondary mouse button. District specializations allow buildings to be replaced
by specialized industrial and commercial facilities. Specialized buildings can benefit
from different natural resources or focus on tourism. Park area? I can make a, just paint in
here a park? Will this just be like a park zone? This is stupid. Paint district. It's too small.
Industry area. This is, okay, this is a little too much for my brain right now.
Let me just focus on like building elementary schools for a minute. I'll come back to this in
like a year. Okay, um, I need houses. Residential, I think. Yeah, we need another power plant, I think.
Okay, um, a road. Let's go with, I don't have highways yet, which sucks, but this is an exit.
It could be a new town over, let's do, um, all right. Fuck. Uh, I'm overwhelmed. Slow down.
Relax. I'm overwhelmed. Okay, I'm getting over, here we are. Just taking a minute here.
I want residential up here. Okay, I'm gonna build out residential down here, so it's nice and
residential. Connect the highway over here. New city is gonna go out this way. Sounds good to me.
Here we go. Looking to get removed, but what do you want to do? Shit. Build a tunnel, which is for
fun. Hold on, so, wait. Page down, right? Page down. No, this is stupid. This is like, this is
a secret base residential area. This is so much money to do, to build like a secret entrance for
a new residential area up here. Up in like the hills. Is it worth it? This is a secret
residential area up here. What's going on with the points? I can't be total fuckface right now.
God damn it. I did it. I shouldn't have done that, but I did it. All right, now we're gonna
get out of here and have these opening for like the private zone. Okay, now pull it up. Page up.
It's too steep. How do I bring it up? Page up? Why can I not get out of this? What are you guys
doing? Where's that road? How come I can't page up? I can't come out? Space is occupied. It's too
steep. What the fuck are you talking about? Where's that road? How come I can't see it anymore?
Oh, okay. Page up. Here we go. Got it. This is so fucking stupid. What a waste of like
$40,000 to have like the weird private entrance. What the fuck? Okay. Cool. These people are not
gonna be able to have any education. Wait, I can do this though. Space is already occupied.
Channel points. What the hell are you guys doing? We're selling. We don't need no control.
Further we crave. It's just a purple chat room. Oh, you guys are wasting your channel points.
For the next fucking channel point stream that's coming up, it's gonna be 10,000 channel points
per burp. And whoa, sorry. You're not gonna be able to get me to burp. Oh, sorry about that.
Ah, now it's cancelled. Why are they unhappy? What? I just did the same thing over here.
I just mirrored the exact same layout over here. Except it's a tunnel. Why did I fucking do that?
What a waste of time. Secret Batman entrance. Alright, whatever. Who cares? It doesn't matter.
It looks like shit. Do you think I care? It doesn't matter. It needs to be a slightly
different layout. There we go. And there needs to be a road connecting this to here.
Done. Fuck. No, this sucks. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I can fix it. I can fix it.
This is the design that your fucking three-year-old nephew does on the back
of the fucking Chili's children's menu card. And this is like, what are you drawing over there?
It's a rabbit. Oh, wow. That looks just like a fucking rabbit. That doesn't look at all like
a rabbit. Yeah, but I see it kind of. You're trying. I need the big road. Two-way road. Here
it is. Upgrade, upgrade, upgrade. This is the trash can get over here. Alright, now this breaks up
into residential zones. Buy buy money. It doesn't matter. I'll get it all back. I'm gonna put taxes
at 100% for one day. This is a, this is just a stupid idea. All right. I like plumbing.
How does it know? Okay. Plumbing. Here we go. From here. Plumbing. Good. From here to here.
Up here. Is this correct? Oh, I think I'm doing this wrong. It's not symmetrical.
It's not symmetrical. No, no, no. Fix, fix your discord server. What the fuck? I don't know.
What are you talking, I don't even know what that means. It keeps crashing. What's the, I didn't do,
I'm, it's not like I didn't pay the discord internet bill. It's just discord's doing that.
Discord's, what do you, I'm holding two cords that aren't plugged in together and they can't
be plugged in. What do you want me to do? What a waste to get this.
How much, okay. Water's going fine so far. I'm gonna have to need a new pump or something.
Turn this off. Wait, no, no, no, that's the one I can't play, right? That's the only one I can't
click on. How about um, downtown radio. Sewer, sewage production, sewage drainage. All right,
we're doing fine. Water reserve and tanks. None. I don't have any water tanks. Okay, so wait,
what year is it? 2021, okay. Now, any electricity. Uh, this is a problem. We're gonna fix this.
Now, let's let this play out so they can build up. Remember, this is all residential and a couple
of schools. I don't have any money. They're all gonna be idiots again. I have to increase the
fuck out of taxes. 20%. Imagine living here and paying 20% property taxes every month.
Vod mute. That's not, I didn't get the warning for this. Start building. No educated people.
I didn't know that was gonna be that important. I didn't know. I thought it was just build town.
I didn't know you had to make people smart and shit. Businesses are being abandoned because no one
is... Boomtown! Ooh, okay, I can do ferry, taxi, post service, a bus. All right, I need to make
money. How am I gonna make any money? Uh oh. Oh, one guy over here is not gonna have internet.
Fuck, I gotta build all the whole internet infrastructure to get over to this guy.
Okay, we're good. They don't like, I don't want these taxes. Holy shit, we're making a ton of
money. Just bear with me, everybody. Bear with me. We're just gonna have a bunch of taxes for
one or two more days and then we'll go back to normal, I promise. Okay, okay. See, now I'm
gonna lower your taxes to 11%. See, that's all we had to do. Not enough educated workers.
One job available. How many people are in the high school? Wait, I need like a college or something.
What does this thing mean? Not enough goods to sell. What? What do you mean not enough goods?
Any more industry? How much industry am I making? Everybody is an idiot. They're all gonna, they're
gonna start eating each other. There's nobody, and now they're driving. How are you driving cars?
They're all so stupid. That just, you just ran over four people. Consume, there's not enough boxes
from the box factory. What? Okay, hold on. I got money now. Electricity. Let's go here.
What the fuck? Here to here. Fuck. Got it. Good. Right? 55. Oh shit. I need more of these.
I need another wind. More wind. Good. Another one. Green energy. That's it. That's it. One more.
Last one. Okay, good. You must construct additional pylons. Not enough goods to sell, but
from where? Where do you really pull goods from? Our vacation was extended. Whatever.
Do I not have enough industry? Oh, okay. So we need medium demand for industry. All right.
Industry is going up this way. Let's go. Excuse me. Move. Excuse me. Move. Oh, two lane row with tram
tracks. I don't care. Okay, here we go. You know, upgrade. I don't want to upgrade. I want to
place it. Industry. So get it way the fuck away from everybody. Good. Now we'll have a bunch of
goods. I'm going to need more power plants and shit. Okay. We'll let that build out. We'll just
keep going. Let's just look. We need more industry. It's coming. I promise. Do I know what a neighborhood
looks like in real life? Yes. I just, I don't zoom out on Google earth and look at every neighborhood.
Every neighborhood. You know what? Yeah. Every neighborhood looks like this to me.
I don't look at my, I don't walk out my door and see this. I told you I'm not a fucking city planner.
I already told you that. I don't know what the hell I'm doing. I don't know what like
sufficiency and efficiency is. I'm just going with, rolling with punches and making houses and
making secret centers. Nobody even lives over here. I'm not anymore commercial I think soon.
All right. I built this shit out. We need water. Oh, you dope. I thought I could do it. I thought
I could make a, like a V. It's all right. I'm not a fucking city planner. Fuck it. How about electric?
This. All right. Pause it. This needs to change. This is terrible. Terrible. Terrible. Terrible.
Terrible. Terrible. There we go. That's good. Connected. Good and connected. Good and connected.
Good and connected. Looks good. Life church is going there. Plumbing is going here. Keep it going.
Add some city policies. What the fuck is a policy? Oh, wait, wait, wait. I'm trying to pause the game.
Where's that tool tip? Policies can be used to add some flavor. Adjust where certain citizen types
live. What they can do. What sort of industry is allowed. Set policies. It can be set citywide or
limited to districts created with the district tool. Okay. So power usage. Energy conservation
is important. The best way to do that is by installing energy meters in buildings. Moderately
reduced electricity consumption. I don't need that right now. Pet ban. Smoking ban? Make this
a smoke free city? The whole city is smoke free. All right. That sounds like not a bad idea. All
right. The whole city is smoke free. You cannot smoke cigarettes in this whole city. Prefer ferries.
High ticket prices. Park made. Free Wi-Fi. Free wireless access points for citizens and tourists
allow easy use of email and other internet services instead of traditional mail. This
reduces the amount of mail. Let's go. Yeah. Free Wi-Fi. I don't need the whole city. It's all free
Wi-Fi. Okay. And smoke detector. Recreational marijuana. Allowing recreational use of controlled
substances attracts more tourists but also requires more police presence. Increase police budget by 15
percent. Reduces crime rate. Moderately increases tourism. No. We're going to have free Wi-Fi and
no smoking. Sounds good. All right. Am I making an entire city or am I doing the policy that's
inside of a McDonald's? This is a city-wide thing. I don't fucking know what the hell I'm doing at
this point. All right. Let's go. I'm not legalizing weed. Not yet. Not yet. I can't have no, I can't
ban smoking and then make weed legal. No smoking allowed. And well, you can smoke but only no
cigarettes. But you smoke weed. You can? Who are you to say what I can't? What about how? Who said
that? Who are you to say what I can do? What's next? Ban sandals with socks? Not cool. I want
freedom. How's this look? Industry coming up. Industry coming up. You don't like this trash?
Garbage is piled up. 16 out of 16. Uneducated people. Time to do education. High school.
Get it over here. Right here. It'll get everybody in this new area. Right on the edge here. Right
there. Because I'm going up. That hits everybody, right? Right here? Right there. Go. For the love
of God. And it's going to hit every one of these educational areas around here. Good. Good, good,
good, good. Okay. How we doing? We need, how's the crime rate? Recreational use or we riot? No,
not yet. I need to, I, not yet. Raise the taxes again. Let's go. Why is this shit taking so long
to build? Riot, riot, riot. You can keep rioting. That's fine. Okay. Looking good. 9,000. What do I
need now? I need to start to expand. Is this high school full? High school students in the city.
Okay. What about over here? 850-1880. All right. Keep the education going. Do I even have an
elementary, there's no elementary school. Education. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Children need
education. Okay. Elementary school. There's not, there's not even one over here.
Educate. Educate. Educate. Educate. Educate. Educate. Educate. Educate.
Okay. No more taxes. No more taxes. They're too high.
Put more stupid people stores. I don't know. There's not enough educated workers. Not enough
goods. I need to just have, just build dumb people stores. I don't know.
Stuff like anybody can do. I need to put something in here too. Can I like just put
anything in here? Terrain. Modify the terrain. Oh no, no, no. I'm not fucking with this.
I'm not fucking with that. No way. What's this? Basketball court. Oh, sick. This would be, this
would be perfect. What does the green over here mean? Oh, that just, it hits everybody in that
area. Okay. But like right here, right in the middle. I don't want to bulldoze any house though.
Okay. Right here. There we go. Nice. Everyone's happy about that shit. Small playground. Small
park. Playground. Put a playground over here. Hit this area. Right there. There we go. See? Good.
Feeling full of energy after a jog in the new park. Right. Fuck the mayor. We want to smoke weed on
the basketball court. That's too bad. That's pretty cool though. Look at that. Do I collect money from
this? Wait, hold on. Ship? I don't have any ship. Tours. Just take a budget for the road maintenance.
Okay. Now what do I need? Got houses going up. How come they haven't built anything? Oh, I need a
plumbing and power over here. Is that why this isn't up? All right. We're going to come down here
and this is going to be more commercial. More commercial down this way.
Whoa. What's this? Bus? Four lane road with bus lanes. That's kind of cool. So you can take the
bus. All right. You can take the bus from here all the way down to here. There's a bus. Bus, a taxi.
Wait, wait, wait. Yeah. Bus. So the bus you can get. You can get on the bus in the middle of the
city. So let's say that you could get on the bus here. This is the good place for a bus stop.
It's going to destroy two businesses. You can't just connect it. You can't just make a new
exit for the bus. All right. We're going to have to delete that for a minute. How are people still
so stupid? I have plenty of high schools now. What's going on over here? Not enough workers.
What? Build churches? I don't have enough money for that. Health care. Build a university.
How much is a university? Public library. Institute of creative arts. Thirty thousand.
Come on. I can't. I can't build this. It's too much money. Okay. Hold on. We'll be looking
out on the grid. Still need to build this up here. Just go fast. Really fast. And make the taxes
fucking crazy. Just make it a hundred percent taxes. Right? Would that be a stupid idea for
like a few minutes? All right. Here we go. Just for a little bit. Just until I get to a hundred
thousand dollars. When you start seeing like, hey, hey, hey. I don't like this. Okay. I don't like
that. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. All right. All right. I'm actually getting
a letter in the mail on like a week to week basis. Hello. This is Mayor Albertson. Just wanted to
make sure everyone's aware that this week taxes are going up 12 percent. And then next week. Hello,
Mayor Albertson again. Taxes are going down 12 percent. You would not live here. You'd get
the fuck out of her as soon as you could. Not enough goods to sell. Not enough workers. 16
out of 16 workers. I need more people to build the houses. Ice cube factory. We don't need this.
We don't need an ice cube factory. Okay. What a fucking scam business. That's not even real.
This is a shell company. I need workers. All right. I need people. Where's my total population?
I got houses going up, man. I got houses going up. Income from residential zones.
Self-sufficient buildings. All right. Hold on. I got 3,800 people here. How many are not working?
We need more residential. All right. Let's go. I'm doing a ton more buildings. You got 29,000
dollars. Highway exit is going to take us this way. All right. You're going to get on the highway
and you're going to fucking go over here. There you go. From there we got.
I can just build this out of this way.
This is cursed. Instead of going on the highway, just build this road down here.
Just down and around. I go visit grandma. I got to go one exit on the highway. She lives
down the street from me. Everything is abandoned. Why are there no people?
Where are the firefighters? Where are the firefighters? What? Oh, shit. Hold on. I need
to go to the fire zone. Right here. Right here. Right here. Just kick them out. What was here?
What was this? This is why there's no smoking. There is no smoking allowed in this whole city.
You motherfuckers. Flick the cigarette. There's no. How do you start a fire here in a park?
A park. Give me a break. This is unbelievable. No fucking smoking. Oh my god. All right. Open
the budget panel. Can you put. How do we fix this? Oh, shit. Okay. Electricity. Uh oh. We need.
What is this thing? Advanced wind turbine? That's too much money. This is all too much money.
All right. One more. Just. Okay. Fine. Fine. Done. Done. Done. Done. Done. You got power. Good.
Is this done? All right. Just delete this. Who comes back and like replants the park?
Holy shit. This is depressing. Educated teen. Oh, I can't even. What's this?
Abandoned. Build something else. There's too much trash. There's too much everything.
They need more educated people.
Okay. Fuck off. Build something else. This is what I mean. This was trash. Trash. Trash. What's wrong
with the trash? I need to dump landfill storage. Garbage capacity. Garbage production. A thousand
units. Should I put this down? Do I need another one? I don't think I need another one. Processing
status. Why are people abandoning the town? Stop abandoning me. Who are you to say what I say I
can't do? You're going to smoke in the park and burn it down. Great. Thanks a lot. Big head.
All right. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. You can smoke again. Okay. You can smoke again.
And no more. You know what? No more free Wi-Fi though. I'm taking that back. No more free Wi-Fi.
Oh fuck. I have to delete this. Did I waste it? Delete. Oh, it's okay. I need the budget panel
right now. Budget. This is trash. All right. Put education down. They're all idiots anyways.
You're listening. There we go. Right. We got enough. How much trash are you producing?
That's not a historical building. It's just some guy's house. Okay.
Hold on. Let me turn the fucking music down. Wait. A little bit more. Okay. That's good.
All right. We're good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Hey, wasn't that funny when I fucking made
this and wasted $35,000? That does no use for it. There's nothing even happening here. They're not
building over here. Okay. How are we doing? We need workers. I need houses. Oh my god. I'm so
bad at this. I just, I'm too, my brain's too scattered to play this game. All right. Here
we go. We're going out this way. It's so fun though. This is a fun. Really. This is a really
good game. Out here. Um, yes. Tons more houses. We need a, and we need schools immediately.
It's okay. It's all right. Don't worry. All right. So
more houses he says evicting two households. No, those are two companies.
All right. We need more income. I just, I'm so scattered. I just can't, I want to connect
this shit. That looks all right. No, stop with the curve. What do you mean? What the fuck is that?
It's a bunch of residential fucking houses is going here. Okay. This is too scuffed. Just stop.
Relax. That's my first time. I don't play it. I don't play the city builder. I'm trying to go
for it. I'm going for it. It's the first time. This is my first time. We're playing a city game.
Um, need houses. A lot of them. And I'm putting, I'm putting the schools and shit in here.
Wait, can you live? Is this like dog house? I don't understand. Okay. Schools. Elementary school.
Right on the corner. Bingo. Right there. There you go. Beautiful. Community school. I need a high
school. High school. Right here. Power and water. They'll get that in a minute. Okay. Shit.
What happened here? What happened here?
Somebody sneezed on a blueprint. All right. From whatever. I have to do what I have to do.
You're teaching your mother how to use an iPhone. I've never fucking played this.
I'm just trying to fun. You know what I mean? It's, I'm actually having a good time. This is a fun
game. There. Is that working? Is it, is that working? Is that, is it flow here? Is it no flow
here? No flow. Was there flow? Was it a no flow zone? Unpause it. I thought I had like a thousand
IQ right there. What the fuck are you doing? Okay. We're good. All right. I don't give a shit. It's
fine. This guy's not going to have water, but fuck him. All right. All right. We need electricity
and shit. You don't even have fucking goddamn it or whatever. I don't. How much electricity do you
need? We need water. Fuck. I'm, I'm trying. Okay. We have tons of water. Tons of it. Now,
we need electricity. Which are we doing? What do we need? I need another. Okay. I need a real plant
now. Double power. Power plant. Coal power plant. Two. Double the power. Put it over here. This is
industry. They don't give a shit. Okay. Now how much is this generating? 40. Let's take a look at
our graph. Electricity protection. 136. We're good. We're connected. We're good to go. How does
nobody have trash? Do I need another one? I need a second trash facility. Trash facility. Pause it.
How much trash do I fucking have? Services. Transport. My trash budget. Isn't it? Didn't I
just put it up? Okay. What do they need? Getting educated. Good. Good to see. Trash gang. Because
my capacity is still fine for the dump. It's 38% full. Okay. I'm going to make another one.
I'm making another landfill. Let's go. Perfect. As these houses start to get made,
you are the dump. What do you mean poop ground? I'm going to put this over here. All right. New
plan. New plan. New plan. New plan. Sell this. Move it. How do I move it? Relocate. Come here.
Holy shit. What a 9 million IQ play this is. That secret entrance is not to another house. That
secret entrance is to the dump. Look at that. They go down into their own trash hole. See?
You don't have to see them. All the trash goes underneath your neighborhood.
I should do two of these. All right. 10,000. How are we doing? Good. Good. Good. Good. Good.
We need water. We need electricity. Someone's screaming at me for electricity. What's the
issue here? Not connected. Well, you will be in about five seconds. All right. And then you're
connected there. And then you connect. Just build house. Just build. Build. How do you not have any
water? What the fuck are you talking about? Wait. You don't know how. What? What happened?
Oh shit. I need another water pump. This is a water pump. Water pumping station. Wait. What is
this? Oh, that's the dirty water. Don't touch that. And go. Right? Is that correct? There we go. Yeah,
we're good. All right. Everyone's being a little bit more happy. Is it not connected? It should
be, right? Was it not connected? No, it is. That's connected, isn't it? No, see? 240,000. It is.
What about the poop? Drain capacity. Let's take a look. Sewage production. Oh, there we go. Right?
I don't understand how you still have all this trash. How many trucks are in use? 16.
I need another dump facility over here. I have to. Like I, I'm running. I'm running out of time.
I'm out of time. Busy town. More policies. Unique buildings. Sightseeing tours. Oil industry and
tourism. Hey, I was doing something. Back to back. Come see the secret dump. That's no fucking
electricity. Wait, whose house is this? Wait, is this like a farm? Is this the guy that owns
the dump? This is like, this is a farm. Okay. Uh, here we go. Now we connect here to here.
That's got electricity. This needs water too. Water is coming out here. What are you fucking
talking about? The secret poop farm. Well, you know, uh, some people, some people have,
you know, milk, dairy production. Some people have corn and maize and all that. Nah, for me,
nah, it's, it's all trash. Trash farm. What's wrong with our garbage collections? Trash is piled up.
It's flied everywhere. I'm 16. I need another, do I actually need more of these? We'll fucking
just make another one right here. I'm doing another one. Just stack them all up here and have
this guy have a farm. Imagine, look at uneducated. Should he have his own elementary school?
This is somebody else's house. Holy shit. Imagine in the summer. Imagine you're the person that
occupies this room during the summer. Oh wow. What a bright, beautiful sunny day that's outside.
I think I'll open up the window and get some air and cool off my room.
Nevermind. Holy shit, that'd be so bad. But the one good thing is you can just,
you wouldn't even need to pay for trash. You could just come out your door with bags of trash and
just whip them over the side. Honey, we still need this TV. No, no, we don't,
we don't need that TV anymore. It's kind of doesn't work, does it? Well, I'll get rid of it.
I'll be careful. I'll be okay. Hold on. I got it. I got it. Okay. Just go out the door.
I'm out the front door now.
That was easy. We have any more stuff? Hey, son, open up your window. Let's check the trajectory.
Check the trajectory. Yeah, if we get, son, if we take the sofa and we fucking go as fast as we can
and throw it out your window, we'll get there, I think. Okay, let's try. Tilt yours this way.
Tilt it. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. All right. No, no, push. Push. All right. Let it go. Let it go. Let it go.
Okay. Let it go. Good. Good shot, son. Good shot. Good work. You made it. I
didn't think we were going to have enough speed. It went into the street at the wrong window.
No, no, that's not. No, they threw it out here. All right. Well, fuck it. Who cares? They'll be
fine. You know, I own my own dumpster. I make a lot of money, so I decided to make the Statue of
Liberty back here. My own personal Statue of Liberty for me. I charge people money to come use it.
I have to take on with a loan to put the Statue of Liberty next to the guy's
dump farm. No, no, no. No, I need to work on this. How are we doing? What do we need?
We need more industry. More industry. How educated are people? We're good?
People are smarter now. What's happening? What happened here? This house is dead.
The house died. A dead person is waiting for transport. What? Nobody says dead in the house.
Oh, these streets are too small. Look at these, like, dump trucks and these, like, gas companies.
This fucking... There's, like, thousands of pounds of gravel going through here.
Like, oil and shit. There's nobody... This is not, like, a residential neighborhood.
Oh, I need to have, like, a different, bigger road to bring trash and stuff.
Oh, and I thought the clown was going to come pick up the dead person.
All right. How do I... What do you... I need a cemetery? Oh, shit. Okay. How do I make a
cemetery? Wait, I need police. What is this? Police headquarters. I don't know.
Put it next to the dump. No, no, no. People are dead. All right. I need... I need some hospital.
Medical clinic. All right. I don't have one over here. Okay. Medical clinic over right here.
In this new area that I've made. Right here. Right here. This is perfect, right? Two medical...
People are dead. People are dying. How about right...
Right here. And then one right here. Okay. And I need another doctor's office over here. Right
at the corner. Okay. We're good. Click link. What? Why? What the hell is going on? Is there a family...
Wait. Dude, this is a Daily Mail website. There's like 600 ads on Daily Mail. Hold on a second.
There's like 40 ads that are on Daily Mail. Why did you leave me a Daily Mail article?
Oh my God. This is unbelievable. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. There are seven.
Seven separate ads. Some of them are playing fucking music on this website. Holy shit, man.
That's unbelievable. And if you have an ad blocker on, they yell at you. They get angry with you.
If you have... Excuse me. I thought you had an ad blocker off. Turn it off so we could deposit
five fucking thousand ads into your face. Anyways, misery of the fam is living in a cul-de-sac
that's been stuck next to a stinking 18,000 ton waste mountain for three years. Holy shit,
this is horrible. Oh my God. It's the same place. What the fuck? Holy shit. This is terrible. This
is actually awful. Okay. I have an ad on the side of this page for a toilet, but it's a small toilet.
It's a toilet that shoots water up your ass. What? It's a little toilet that dad has... I don't
understand. It's a bidet. Oh, all right. I need some... You guys have to help me out here.
This is going to be a conversation. If you're eating, I would say probably stop for a little
bit. Just don't eat for a minute. Just take your last bite. I'll wait. Swallow it and just hear...
Okay, because this is going to be disgusting. Okay. Very important question. I've heard,
hey, I can't believe a bidet changed everything. Oh, wow. It's so much better with a bidet.
And I think about this sometimes. After you've used the bathroom, wouldn't shooting water into...
Okay. Wouldn't shooting water into your ass make... Like you just... Gross water go all over your legs
and your butt cheeks and stuff. I've told you this is going to be a fucking 18 plus conversation.
I'm just... I need to know. I'm curious. I've never... I've always... It just works.
Just sitting down. But I feel like it would be like disgusting. It's not a hose, dude.
Somebody said it's a drinking fountain. Can you imagine? Holy shit. That's fucking crazy.
I don't know. I just don't know. I'm trying to be educated on this. You don't need... You don't need
to use toilet paper. What? No fucking way. That's unheard of to me. That is unheard of to me. That's
no. I would never. I can't... No way. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. That doesn't work. That doesn't work.
It doesn't work. That doesn't work. That doesn't work. No, it does not. No way. No fucking way.
How do you dry your ass off? You just sit there and let water hit you all over the ass and you
put your pants and underwear back on? How do you dry off your ass? You don't use toilet paper
anymore. You're putting water all over your back and your body. So you have water clean you and
then you just pull your underwear back up. When you have like a big water stain on your ass,
what if it misses? What if you're not sitting in the right way? What if you're like shimmying
around or something? What if you like move in the right wrong direction? Just hit boom right on the
side and then oh shit. Now what? What do we do to adjust? Am I going to sit there and just like
power wash the whole back side of my body until I get it in the right place?
Dude, is there like an app that you open up on on your phone that you like aim the nozzle?
How does this work? Calm down. I'm not gonna calm down on this one.
Do it. You have to, you have to fuck. It's a button you press. Yeah, I know, but what if you're in
like the wrong spot? Is it possible that it'll hit you in like the back? What if it's not tweaked
enough? What if it didn't like hit you right like in the swell of your back and go like off your
back? It shoots you and like hits you in the back of the head. You guys are fucking cracking me the
fuck up right now. It's like, what are you doing? A handstand on the toilet? I need more industry.
Hold on. All right, I gotta go back to playing the game. Okay. All right. Seriously, how do you
stop people from dying? Where's the cemetery? What is this? A jumpy house? Oh, fuck that. I'm
doing a jumpy house first. It's going right here. Point. Cemetery. Botanical garden. No, I need a
cemetery. Is it fucking carousel? Oh shit. Come on. Right, right at the front at the entrance of the
park. Okay, good. Fix the streets. I can't. Oh, wait. No, fuck. This is gonna be like, all right,
I got it. Check this out. I need this to be two way, two way. There comes a fucking theme park.
Four lanes. This is both two ways. Here we go. Uh, it don't matter. That's fine. This is like,
I'll look anything be like a little amusement park. All right. What do we got? I'm on. Oh,
look at this. Oh, like a Japanese garden. Uh, and botanical garden. We're gonna put this up here.
Botanical garden is going to go right in the middle. Right. I want it like right in here.
Now that's already parked there. Right here. Botanical garden. I make all these people happy
right there. Boom. Jeremy, here's a diagram for a bidet. You motherfuckers. Oh my god. Where's,
okay. Where is a cemetery? Emergency services. Fire station. I need a cemetery. Health. Medical
lab. Medical clinic. Scrematorium. Sauna. Cemetery. Okay. Here we go. Cemetery. Cemetery next to the,
I can't. How about up here? No, they can only take those people. All right. We need, it's gonna be
away. How about, um, all right. There'll be a cemetery over this way. That makes the most
sense to me. We'll have two. One over here and one over here. Here. Excuse me. Here. Excuse me.
Excuse me. I'm trying to get over here. Excuse me. Fuck. Come on. It's too steep. What the fuck are
you, what do you mean it's too steep? It's a, you're going to be burying people, right? I don't
understand. What do you mean it's too steep for what? Who should I call if nobody comes to pick
the dead up? Oh, it's a mountain. I have to go all the way up the mountain. Oh, it's okay. Just get
it. Come on. Where's the terrain tool? Flatten this shit out. That happens really fast. What?
Oh, it's a volcano. What do I, what is this? It's shift terrain. Level terrain. Wait,
level area. Click the secondary mouse button to choose target height. Oh, fucking God. Really?
Dude, I'm trying to level this shit. I mean, refund. What the fuck? How do I make this circle
bigger? Here we go. Okay. God damn it. Hey, there we go. Come no more urns on the mantle place.
And it's way the fuck away for everybody. So we don't, that's a far way to go. It's okay.
Oh shit. They need water and electricity over here. Right. Okay. What about electric? Electric.
Ooh, I can go from here. No, that's too far. Let's go like this. That's going to be really
ugly if I do this though, isn't it? Oh, that's super ugly. Way too ugly. That's too ugly. That's
ugly. Oh, that's, that's ugly. Look at how ugly this is. Oh, it's ugly. I don't like it. Whatever.
Okay. So now there's a place for people to drop off dead bodies, but it's away from everybody.
It's not over here. This house is abandoned. Just delete it. See, they're happy. Get rid of that
place. This is, yeah, look at us. Get out of here. We need organic foods, not enough goods to sell.
Oh, poor industry. I need a lot more. Okay. We need another industrial area. Over here.
No, this way. Industry. A huge ass road. Highway with sound barrier. No. Wait,
I can put an intersection. Ooh, look at this. This is cool. I don't know. I don't know, guys.
I don't do this stuff. I don't know much about this stuff. I don't know.
I don't know about this stuff. I don't know. It's just, oh, shit. Oh, shit. I just put a light
on the highway. There's a light on the highway. As you go in 60, 70 miles per hour and you have
to stop the red light here. Holy shit, that's so bad. The Statue of Liberty in the middle.
Oh, my chest. This is just a drive-by. Okay, the Statue of Liberty is going right in the middle.
You just drive around it. That is shitty attraction. You just drive around the Statue
of Liberty in a circle and you get back on the highway. Coming up soon, the Statue of Liberty.
Oh, honey, we're going to go see that. And you get off and you just go around the roundabout
and you get back on the fucking highway and go back to what you're doing and surrounded with
stumps. What do you want me to click on? This is fucking funny to me. Oh, that's hilarious.
I'm glad I clicked that. All right, we need more educated people. Oh, this sounds so bad.
I need, okay, well, how much is the Statue of Liberty? $210,000. Come on, I can just put it on
the highway. Wait, I can put it on the highway. Like here. Holy shit, that's the stupidest thing.
I can't. What is this? A winter market? Is this an Eiffel Tower? I can't put a landfill
in the middle, guys. I can't. Fire, fire, fire, fire, fire, fire. Where's the fire department?
Fire, fire. Put it out. We're good. All right, what was I doing? Right, something over here.
I was deleting these two buildings. I was deleting these three buildings.
All right, let's make, I need more industry. Industry, industry, industry.
Over here. Industry, up this way. Industry. Let's go. Road. Industry. Out. Up. All industry.
Only industry. Industry only. I need more than that. What the fuck is this? I don't know. I'm
just trying to make it. Wait, they have to get on the, oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait. Wait, you have to get back on the highway. Oh, shit. Okay, you have to get on the
highway and go all the way around the whole fucking state. Oh, shit. Hold on. Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. I can fix it. I can fix it. I can fix it. I can fix it. I can fix it. I can
fix it. Pause the game. It's so fucked up. I'm right here. Okay, here we go. You can either
get on the highway or you can go check out our fucking industry. It sounds good to me. Good.
Okay, we're fine. Okay, then you go this way and you go over here. Go around, around, around.
I can't. I can't do it.
Oh, and over here. No, this is so fucked up. Okay, delete this. I could go from here to here.
Yeah, no, no, no, no, no. Just from here. From here to here. There. That's better.
Okay, now that makes much more sense. Put a road in the roundabout. Wait, what do you mean
put a road in the roundabout? Let's see if it uses it. This is so confusing. I don't even know how
this would work. So, hold on. If you go around the roundabout, you can go in here and go in and then
left. That's, I gotta delete this. It's too fucked up. The whole purpose of a roundabout is to
not have to have something like this. No one's using it. Oh, they will. They'll have to.
Especially if you lived there. Oh, we need, we need water. Help. Help. Help. I can do better than
that. Help. That's better. All right. I need, I need, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, we good. Oh, we good. Why can I not go down here? I mean, it's already occupied. What the fuck
are you talking about? This is stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid. All right,
let me go like this. There we go. Electric. How much electricity are we using? This game's fucking
cool. 136. I need to do more electricity. How about more wind farms? Ooh, what's this? Oil plant.
Okay, let's go. Where's industry center? This is industry over here, right? This is industry,
right? Yeah, this is industry. Let's put the oil plant over here. Can you do an American accent?
Uh, America is an incredibly, incredibly deep. It's a lot of different accents in America.
There's like 15. I don't know. What are you talking about? All right. I want power. Oh, power plant.
$50,000. Here we go. It's very loud. Wait, this is too much money. Check the traffic map. How do I
do that? How do I check the traffic map? How do I do that? Top left. The info of views. Levels. Prime.
Just wind levels. Transport. Cars. I'm leaning the fuck into my screen right now. I don't see a car.
Escape routes. Meteorologists have issued a severe tornado warning for the area.
What? Residents should seek shelter immediately if any is available.
What are we talking about? Where? About to hit the tornado is going to hit the fucking city?
Huh? 1.5 is about to hit the city. How do I help them? A tornado has touched down in the area.
Seek shelter immediately if any is available. It's going to miss us. It's all right. It's going to
miss. It's going to miss us. It's going to miss us. It's going to, it's, it's, we're just going to
get missed by the storm. It's going to, uh-oh. No, everybody get out of the way. Get your.
All right. How do we rebuild this? We don't. All right. Repair the road. Is she coming back?
Repair. All right. Everybody, everyone's fine. We're okay. All right. Our industry,
we've got to get some more. We're going to build that back. Okay. So I'm going to say where's the
traffic? Tours. Tourism. Road maintenance. Park maintenance. Traffic. Traffic becomes congested.
People have a hard time getting to work and back. Production slows down when resource and
goods sit in trucks. Actually pretty fucking good. Pretty good actually. A little bit of some
congestion here. I can fix that. I can fix that. Oh yeah. This is bad. This sucks. All right. Here
we go. Fresh water. Why are you out without, what are you talking about? What are you guys,
what the fuck are you talking about? What? I took out the power plant. Oh, you fucking motherfucker.
All right. All right. All right. We're good. What about the, somebody's complaining about water.
I got $110,000 looking good. Is this building on fire? No. Save the game. Oh, that would be nice.
Sure. Auto-save. All right. So the traffic ain't that bad. Oh, I got to fix it. This is a big
problem though. Uh, I need to widen this road with a super road. A six lane road is going to go here.
Free up some of that traffic. Look at that flow. Look at that flow. Now it flows. Yes.
Wait. Okay. That's better. Look at that flow. Not, not a good flow on this one though.
This is going to destroy any, uh, this is not going to remove any businesses, right?
But a huge fucking road. More. Here we go. Now this is what we're talking about. You're going
residential. You're going this way. Look at that big intersection. Lots of upgrading the ability.
Looking good. Okay. Now we don't have to go too crazy. We've got our big main road, our huge,
huge thing here. Very good. All right. This is pretty good. This is pretty good over here.
We need some more trash collection. $122,000. Let's go. Any houses going to get built here?
All right. LinkedIn city is doing pretty good. Good morning, everybody. What a beautiful sunrise.
Imagine rolling out of bed first thing in the morning. You just open your eyes and you're
groggy and you just grab your phone and tweet. Good morning. Good morning. Before even brushing
your teeth. We're awesome districts. Jerma face. I still don't really understand that.
Wait, we have some more city stuff. Prefer very hot recycled. Prefer parks. Book fair.
The local public libraries organize a book fair. City planning. Ban heavy traffic on an area.
Encourage biking. Bike ban on sidewalks. No loud noises in the night. Old town. Only residents
of business can use the area from motor vehicles. Ban of the motor traffic. Filter boost workers
union. No rebuilding. I need another police station. Police. We need one. There's one there.
We need one over here. Right there. Looks all right. And we need another one up here.
Around the corner. Right here. Right down here. We gotta protect the industry, right?
Can people rob industry? Or is it only residential? Both. Okay. Let's get this in a spot where like
what's over here? I don't want to delete too much shit. Okay. We need one over here. Just police.
Police. Police. Everywhere. Good. And down here. One police station over here. Good. Now we're
protected. Completely. And a police station down here. And a police headquarters. Okay, what does
it do? Police presence helps control the crime rate. Keep citizens safe. All right. The police
headquarters is going to be around the highway. No. Oh shit. This place needs water. They got
electricity though, right? People actually live here. It's just people constantly. Remove all
more police stations than schools. You're right. Wait. College. Institute of Creative Arts.
Institute of Creative Arts. Does the red mean that they're really stupid? Here we go. Right here.
Right here. Perfect spot for it. Right in the middle. Boom. The new Institute of Creative Arts
is going to implement new creative ways of teaching art. Wait, is it art school? Oh shit.
No, no, no. There's only one school and it's an art school.
No, I want it to be like a general college. Public library. High school. Another high school?
Where are the dumbest people located? Over here. Space Occupy. We'll knock it down. It's okay.
It's a college. They get a general education. That's fine. All right. How are we doing over
here? We need more workers. I'm working on it. Oh, we need the fucking industrial building.
Ugh. The industrial building's not going to... The oil building's not going to hire a fucking painter.
We're okay. We're okay. We're okay. They might. They might. That's true. All right. I've got
schools. More. I need hospitals. Medical helicopter. I need a hospital. How much? $65,000? Increased
tax. All right. Let's take a look at our budget here. Trash a little bit more. Schools a little
bit less. Police a little bit less. Fire a little bit more. Hospitals a little bit more.
Industry areas a little bit more. Zero dollars? Why are they getting zero dollars? Because they
don't exist. This is just throwing money into a hole. What's the bottom one? What is this?
What's the top? Is the top and bottom lever? What are they for? Day and night. Oh, shit. Okay.
All right. Taxes. Let's go. You got to pay a little bit more. Seriously. Come on.
15, 20% to industry. Let's go. Only for like a few weeks. Promise. Big town, campus area,
taxation policies, sports arenas, trade school. All right. That's 110,000. Look at this shit.
More, more, more, more money, more money, more money, more money, more money, more money,
money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money.
Take a blimp. What the hell would I need a blimp for? What's with the water works?
All right. Bring it down. 12%, 12%, 12%. Let's do 11%, 13%, and 14%. What is this?
High density residential zone? All right. 12%, 14%, 12%, 14%. I'm just picking random numbers.
Build high density now. Wait. Trash. I need another dump. How's Dump City doing over here? Oh,
they've expanded. Dump City has... Well, they actually are doing pretty well. Speaking of
dumps. I need more commercial areas. Right here. Whoa. High density commercial zone.
Department stores and supermarkets that offer citizens a wide variety of spending possibilities.
So this is big, big shit. All right. How about over here? This is a pretty good spot for it.
We're off the highway. All right. What's going on here? Oh, they're already going up. What's
happening over here? Oh, right. This stupid dumb thing that I built. A fun, like a dumb joke. Turn
it into a fucking mall. That's fine. Okay. Let's go like this. All right. We're good. Electricity
is already coming down here. How much do I need? I'm about to be... I'm about to need to do more.
I need a dump. Incineration plant. Ooh. Instead of collecting garbage, why not burn it?
And turn it into electricity. The power of steam turbines. Yeah. Let's go. Have it back here.
Right on the edge. Yeah. Whatever. You fine. Turning trash into energy is a win-win situation.
Yeah, it is. Chat. Chat. Hey guys. What do all the industries win ThinkCity? What are you fucking
talking about? I need... Okay. I need college. Here we go. Modern Technology Institute. Bingo.
I gotta put this over here. Where's that other college? Right in the middle. $90,000. Right there.
There you go. Now you're going to be fucking real smart. The people are going to be too intelligent.
Oh, I was about to delete your building. Cool. Look at that. That's a nice little view.
All right. This is building. Everything's looking all right. We need some more residential.
What's wrong here? I need more workers. I'm working on it. All right. What about the trade
schools, right? We need those. This is a university. Why did I build like this super school?
Earthquake could hit the area soon. Tornadoes and earthquakes? All right. Do it like over here.
Please do not do it to the fucking dump. Don't do it to the dump family. Come on. Oh God. Oh,
I just built this. An earthquake is occurring. Oh my God. I thought that was... Wait for help
if you are in the affected area. That was $90,000. God's wrath. What's this filling?
What's this mean? Sewage is backing up. What? Oh, fuck. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
What am I supposed to do? What do I do? How do I steal the sewage? Sewage is backed up.
Somebody's house is on fire. Do I have any police officers? I need another drain.
What? I don't understand. They're all here. They're all here. Pause it. I don't understand.
Sewage is backing up. Oh, it's because of this. Stupid motherfucker. What about the eggs? Okay.
Oh, these are broken and fucked up. No, these are all right. Okay. Sewage is backing up,
but I solved it. Did I solve it? It's solved. All right. Here we go. Okay.
Relax everybody. Just... Yeah. All right. So what happened? Some things got broken.
Oops. Come on, mate. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Hold on. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
What about my beautiful road? Six roads, six lanes. Shit. Wait. My beautiful road.
My beautiful road. Oh, shit. What the fuck is happening? There's a crater in the earth.
No, dude. Why is this happening right now? Hold on. How is sewage backing up? What happened? What do
you mean there's no electricity? What the fuck are you talking about? Oh my God. Pause the fucking
game. Jeez. God damn it, man. Okay. How much power do I have? Money. Okay. What the fuck?
I got to fix this road. This whole area is messed up. Look at this. People have like
craters in their backyard. Rebuilding. We're rebuilding. I can't believe they took out the
university of all the things. Just built the damn thing. How do you not have water? Oh, fuck off.
$90,000 just deleted. All right. I got to redo this shit. This is all messed up. Pause it.
The road's out here. Just demolish this. I need to... Okay. What the hell is happening?
This is... What happened here? I need to go from here. From here to here. Give me the terrain.
Haha. Yeah. Good. Yes. I want to... Isn't this flattened to terrain? What the fuck?
Flatten. Fucking God. It's on the mountain. It's on flattened. Level terrain. There we go.
There we are. Okay. There we go. Back to normal. Back to normal. Clap. He did it. Clap. Ehee. He
did it. Ehee. He did. What happened here? I don't care. Fix these fucking roads. Good. Bring this
down. I'm on my beautiful highway. Be fixed. Get off the upgrade tool. Here we go.
One, two, three, four. Look at this traffic that's going to come down here.
Okay. Welcome to Wink Dink City. Well, it's not my fault. The fucking earthquake destroyed
everything. What is this? Oh shit. Is this a life? Is this a life? Okay. Is this a life?
Oh, it's okay. Fuck it. Just put a roundabout in here and it'll solve the whole problem.
Here. Oh no. Oh, no. People live here, man. People live here. Well, this is like an exit?
This is such a piece of shit. It's unbelievable. No, it's impossible. Is this a way? Is this a
runway? Oh, highway. Okay. How about we... No, fuck that. Let's just go back to what I was doing.
All right. We need to... commercials. We need high density commercial zone. There. Rebuild.
Rebuild. Commercials. Industry. Up here. Good. Not too close to the humans.
Don't go too close to the humans. High density, you fool. That is high density.
All right. Now I got to rebuild the fucking school, man. I got destroyed with that. It's
going to go back here. Let's take a look at this traffic pattern. This would be so confusing.
Fucking road in history. Oh God. Wait. They can drive straight? Holy shit. That's so bad.
All right. Make it a toll road. I don't even know how to do that. All right. Increase taxes. Go.
What's this? Oh, more trash. Build, rebuild. That's okay. It's going to get rid of all the
broken stuff. Any more broken stuff? Right here. Broken. Broken. Broken. Okay. Any more
broken stuff? All right. Now that complaining about the taxes, it's time to shut it off in three,
two, one. Turn it off. Okay. Cool. Let's make our university again. That'd be nice.
Red light here. Turn right. Red light roundabout. Okay. I think we're doing all right. We're going
to get some workers. We need more residential areas. So here's what I propose. Highway off down
here. Oh no. Okay. Check this out. Are you, are you even looking at me? Are you even paying attention
to me? Look at me. Are you looking? Check this out. Span down here and have this all be houses. All
of it. All of it. You understand? Are you fucking looking at me? Are you paying attention? There.
Nice. And then we're going to go right down the middle. For the bigger road. Okay. Nice.
That's cool. That'd be nice. High density residential. Incoming. You want to talk about
population? Here it comes. What's going on over here? Oops. Is that a power plant? Fuck. Is that
a power plant? Did I delete a power plant? Is that a power plant? Is that a power plant? Was it? Was
it actually? Was it a power plant? Was it actually a power plant? No, it wasn't. Okay. Good.
All right. We need to do, uh, our water and material, water and materia. See? Okay. Now we
need electricity. We need electricity. All right. Shut up. Looking good. I'm going to get a ton more
people here now. I need an elementary school over here right now. Elementary school. I don't have
enough money for that. Cool. I'm going to sneeze. Is it finally going to happen? No, stop saying it
and just record it. Fuck. Why? Every time I say it, I out loud and I'm about to record it.
I get my fucking box ready and I'm about to press a button. It's gone. Pain in the ass.
All right. Let's go build it. Triple the density. 13,000. No more natural disasters for a little
while. No more natural disasters. Give me a little while. At least a little bit. You know what I'm
saying? Build faster. Yeah, man. I is going to have a spliff now and take it easy. What?
Oh fuck. Oh yeah, that's right. It's weeds no longer legal here. Educational blimps.
For-profit education. Fuck that. That's too much right now. Taxation. Tax raise for low density
residential. Tax relief for low density residential. Let go of leisure. Leisure specialized areas.
Stop generating tax income. Tax raise for office. Tax relief for, all right, tax relief for
low density residential. And then tax raise for high density commercial.
And then tax relief for low density commercial. And then tax relief for offices. And then raise
taxes on high density residential. And then lower the taxes for low density residential.
That should work out pretty well. How do you not have trash? Taxes not zero. Omega low.
Okay. You want to see what happens if you go to zero taxes across the board? Let's see what happens.
Let's see. I expected five days for the earth to be on fire. What if all of a sudden it was like,
just like a blistering utopia. It was like perfect and I have to like eat my words.
No taxes. Whoa, we're at a net loss. See, this is what happens when it takes fucking three days.
I'm governor Elbert. So let me drag the slider to zero taxes. Wait, wait, put it back, put it back,
put it back. How come nothing's building here? Why is nothing building here? Because it's, it's what?
What's wrong? What? It's, why is the, what happened? Fuck, fuck, fuck. We need, I think it's time for
oil. Oil. No, coal. We're still on coal. Coal. Coal. Producing. Done. There you go. Power
resolved. Build these fucking houses. What are you doing? Build parks? No. Okay, fine.
How about a dog park? Yeah, a dog park. Yeah. And then a picnic table. Picnic. How about a picnic area?
How about some picnic? How about a picnic area? Fix the traffic. I will in a year. How about right
here? Yeah, a little like a picnic area right across from the high school. Yeah, that's good.
Remember the link. Quick, the link. Click the link. Whatever. Yeah, everyone has their own,
everyone has an opinion. Everyone's got their own opinion. That's fine. How many people are at the
university? Only, this doesn't make it 4,000 fucking students. Where is all the, where are
the students? Taxes too high on the, on industry. All right. I'll alleviate some of that. There.
Happy? Now what? Commercial? Too high taxes on commercial industry? All right, fine. We'll,
we'll do some alleviation. Okay. All right. You got me. All right. You got me. You got me.
I'm on crack. Like, I'm, I'm on crack today. I don't know what's going on here.
How hard does it work to make a working power grid? Well, excuse me. You didn't exist up until
like fucking 10 minutes ago. Just relax. This is temporary. I'll fix it later. You don't do crack.
I know that that doesn't, that's not what I'm saying. I'm saying this is a crack string.
It's temporary. Just wait till they build up these places. How much money? Snines,
thousand dollars a second. Did I make a school over here? Nope. I gotta do that now.
I want to replace an advert on a blimp, but these educational posters. Oh, please.
All right. We need a elementary school. Two of them, one down here and then one up here.
Okay. The least they're not going to be idiots. And then I want a high school right in the middle.
Did you idiot? What do you mean? Why? Because no, I don't want them to be stupid.
Our commercials. It's our way of saying we hear you. So don't be silenced when opportunity calls.
Pick it up. It's for you. Accio mobile. It's too much harsh prison sentences.
Fire. Where I thought that was a whole citizens are sick. Oh, I only have one hospital.
Oh, why are they sick? That's a good question. Need more educated, not enough goods to sell
more industry. Make it a historical building. Does that even do? Not bad for my flaw.
You know, when you really zoom out, you start to understand that this is not really a town
as much as it is the current state of your headphone wire. You made a toilet city.
Oh, people are really sick over here. I need a hospital. How much? 23,000 hospitals. All right.
Hospital. Medical center. Medical helicopter. Sports hall. Community pool. No, I need a hospital.
Hospital. Need more money. Taxes. Only for a minute. Only for a few minutes. Only for a minute.
All right. All right. All right. All right. Everybody calm down. I'm doing it. I'm taking
it off. Take it off. Take it off. Take it off. Take it off. Take it off. Take it off. Take it off.
Take it back to home. Hospital. I still don't have enough money for this fucking thing.
How many hospitals are there? What is that? I already have hospitals. I already have hospitals.
What are you talking about? I already have hospitals. I already have plenty of hospitals.
Separated by the tunnel. So? So what? They're fine. All right. I got 71,000 dollars. It's time
to really go fucking nuts. How's this residential looking over here? I'm pretty good. Pretty good.
Pretty good. Pretty good. All right. Now we're going to do a little bit more industry up this way.
I want some more. I'm going to make a more wind. I'm going to make a more a wind farm.
Super wind farm. This is a super wind turbine and into the water. Oh, nice. Pretty cool. Are
these connected? They are. It's too loud. There's nothing over here. Why these houses keep getting
abandoned? My finger is getting sore to click on them. What's wrong here? I'm not enough custom
reason. What are you selling? I don't know what's in there. All right. We need more industry. We're
going to go out this way. More industry. Industry road. You need a super road. Six lane road from
here out. I'm not going to do that. Don't worry. This could be kind of cool. What could be up here?
Cool houses. This would be pretty cool. I kind of like this idea. Yuck. Yuck. Yuck. This is very
yucky. Very yucky. How about... Oh, okay. Well, first of all, let's just do what I was going to do.
We need industry. We need industry. Produce more goods and shit. That's all that's going to happen
up here. This is the industry zone. And then if I go... Oh, wait a minute. I have an idea.
Check this out. Hey, hold on. All right. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hey, hey, hey. What the fuck? Too much poop water? What do you mean?
Who is the ambulance? That was an illegal U-turn. What are these U-turns? Illegal U-turn.
How much do I do with production capacity? I got plenty of capacity. Let me keep doing
what I was doing over here. So hear me out. Now we're going to do like a big countryside drive.
Oh, yeah. Look at this. It's going to be all up here. Cool. All right.
Look at the poop. I'm not looking at poop. Yeah. Look at this shit. And then you go down to a new
town. This is like a scenic drive. Perfect. I could do, uh, not industry. What should I put up here?
Fuck. I should have done the scenic drive. Whatever. How about a few of these?
You fucked that one up. I can't like pick it up and bend it. Dude, just... Oh, I got it. Small
business enthusiast. Cable cars, monorail. What the... What? Replace this with a monorail. Done.
Replace it with... What else did I get? A train station. Ooh. Okay. I'm going to make a monorail.
Yoga garden. All right. Monorail time. I know you want water. I know, I know, I know, I know,
I know, I know, I know, I know. There's too many things. Just wait. Just don't fucking move. Good.
Shit. Okay. Hold on. Nobody move. Not enough fuel for the coal power plant. Not enough fuel.
Where do you get... Where do you get coal? Where do you get coal? Where are you supposed to get it?
Are you supposed to put... Wait. Oh, use coal to produce electricity. So what's the problem?
I need to show resources? Are you kidding me? The map has natural resource ability that can be
utilized by a law and industry specialized in forestry, oil, ore, or agriculture. Oh, fuck you.
Okay. Oh, up here. There's coal in there. Why is my city full of... What are you talking about?
Somebody died in here? A dead person is waiting in here. Wait, where's the cemetery? Let's go.
Where is the cemetery? Wait, is the guy... Is the guy that runs the cemetery getting arrested?
Volunteer at the sem... Where the fuck are you? It's too far away. All right. I'm putting the
cemetery over... Garbage is piled up in this... Ah! Garbage production. Oh, shit. Garbage
processing. I need more trash over... They're not going to be happy about this, but I have to
put it here. Here, please check the water pumps. What? Oh, how do I... How do I clean this? Eco
water outlet? Fresh water outlet. The green alternative, while the eco-wire is quite
expensive, it helps purify the water and let it... Will the water let out of it? How do I get rid of
this? Get the water near the intake. Shit. It's sucking up the poop water. I have to move these.
It's starting to suck up the shit water. Oh, no. These have to move up. People are turning
their showers on and being rained with diarrhea. I'll fix it. I'll fix it. Pause it. Don't worry.
Everybody relax. The mayor is on the case. Okay. We're good. Hey, I smell regular pipes.
Water in sewage heated... Where are the pipes? Am I stupid? What's going on? These are like heated
pipes. It's not the same thing. This is like a different thing. All right. Delete this shit.
I said, delete it. Delete it. All right. We're good. So now, was like the shit...
Okay. We're good. Back to normal. People are dying. A dead person is waiting for transport.
I need another cemetery. Okay. We're doing a cemetery over... I don't... I need one right
over here. I have to have one. Where are they? This is a medical cemetery. A medical... What
about this crematorium thing? Hospital. Cemetery. Medical clinic. Sauna. I don't have enough for it.
Whatever. All right. Whatever. Whatever. Whatever. I'm going to build a road right here. I'm just
going to build a road right here. Get off the highway and go to the fucking cemetery.
Fix the roads. You think I can fix this shit? It's over.
Traffic. I will in a second. All right. No, no, no. Right here. It needs to be like over here.
I think they're going to be pissed off that it's over here, but I have to put it over here.
I'm going to make another... Okay. Here we go. Make a little road. It comes out this way.
It's just a small one. It's great. I don't want a curved road. Okay. Cemetery. Right here.
There's only those people over here though. What the fuck?
Oh, finally we can bury our dead. Hooray. I got 75k. Trash is building up. All right. I need
another dump. How's the dump looking? How many dumps do I got? Go to traffic. All right. Fine.
Oh shit. My chest.
Where are you people going? These tiny roads. This would be scary to drive down. Especially
considering people can park on the street. People can park on the streets. I got to fix this.
Large roads. We need six lane roads here. Oh, it's going to destroy this.
Does it only shift the bottleneck? Well, what would you have me do? Leave it like this? What's
the alternative? Set it to upgrade. It destroys them. It's going to take out the whole industry
area. I have to do it. Okay. Wait, what? Oh my God. I have to mess. All right. That should be okay.
All right. Incoming economic collapse. I'm fine right now. I know you don't look. I'm going to
switch. When we get into residential, we switch over. This is better. All right. Better. That
should alleviate some of the tension. Just don't delete the university. Where is it? Over there.
Okay. Here we go. They will return. Businesses will come back. That's fine. Relax.
How do you need water? Oh, water consumption. What are you talking about?
You're fine. Can somebody go pick up this dead person? I need another cemetery. Just put it
next door. Seriously, I need it here. Look at how much this will address the problem. Connect the
road? I don't understand. You don't connect this road? What do you mean connect the road?
Wait, I have to make this smaller for one second. Why can't I make this bigger?
Oh, shit. I don't understand traffic. I don't understand. Okay. Make this larger. I can't make
it. Why can't I make this one bigger? I can't even make it a double. I can't even make it a double.
The ambulance is Austin powers. Where's the fire? We need to make one of the emergency vehicles.
Sitting in traffic. Two, three, four ambulances. They're going crazy. Where's the hospital?
Where are they trying to go? I don't know where they're going. I need to relax. Relax. Okay,
the road's bigger now. You can fucking move. Ow. Just make the whole thing. Six lanes of
Aden. I don't know what the fuck I'm doing. Okay, there. You can drive.
Make it space. This doesn't even work, man. There's so many ambulances.
But I don't know. Okay. I don't understand why there's so many ambulances driving by.
There's nothing even happening. It's fine. It's because of the car accident. It's because the
car accident. Why are they not using both lanes? Why are they not using it? Why are they only using
it? Because this one asshole is parked in the street. That guy was parked. That guy was parked
in the middle of the street. You see that bullshit? Why the fuck did you do that? Oh my God. I don't
know anything about fucking city design. I don't know anything. I don't know anything about this
shit. Tell me where somebody's fucking seeing this that like does this shit for a living and
they're like, holy shit, how did this guy get out of fourth grade? I don't know. Very, very carefully,
apparently. Okay, so what's happening here? Why are they only using one lane? Why are they all in
one lane? I don't understand. Are you all taking a right hand turn?
They're all taking a right. Oh my God. It's chaos. Okay. Just make the roads bigger. There. See.
I don't know. Just do it. Just do it to every road that I can do it to. All roads need to be
there. Okay. My fucking throat hurts. Jesus Christ.
Where's the fire department? Where's the fire department? Fire department. We need one
right now. We need a fire station. Fire station, please. Fire station over here.
Fire station over here. Put it out. How many fire? I need another fire station. We need another one
right here. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. You don't have to do. Get out there. Go on. Get out
there. Get out there. Get out there. All the traffic. It's okay. Why are you going this way?
Holy shit. Every fire department. Every single fucking county. Oh my God.
Why are you turning around? Stop here and put this out. Put it out. Where are the rest of them?
Holy shit. Okay. We're fine. We're fine. It's just, we just,
can we please just stop this and just clean this up? Where are they going?
There's not another fire over here, right? There are no fires down here, are there?
Oh my God. Wait. Why are there fires everywhere? I don't understand. What happened? What the fuck
is going on? Did I get hit by a meteor? I don't know. I don't know why this is happening. Is there
fire? This is still spreading. Guys, I need more fire. I need more fire.
Um, just built it in. It's going to be okay. It's going to be, it's going to be, we have plenty of,
we have plenty of units at this point. How many operator fire engines in use? Zero. Zero out of
23. Zero, huh? Zero? Get out there. Where are all the garbage trucks? I don't know. We're having
like a total city wide, like burning of our whole town for some fucking reason. What happened here?
Jesus. Okay. I think we're, are we, are we, are we done? Are we good? Oh Jesus, man. I have to,
did you see the blimp? Oh, my fucking head hurts. That was fucking outrageous. The traffic,
they couldn't even get through the trap. No, this is on fire. Guys, just how do I,
I can't delete this with my hand. 30, I only have $30,000. What happened?
This is going to spread over here. Okay. Well, that was interesting.
Oh, hold on. Oh, I'm like choking. All right. I need to clean this up and do what I was doing
before. Whatever that was. I don't even remember. I was going to build a monorail over here. Right.
Yeah. That's what I was doing. Okay. Monorail time. Wait, bus. Where's the monorail? Metro.
Train. Ship. Plane. Monorail. Monorail station. Monorail station with road. Ooh. Monorail bus hub.
A monorail station with a built-in bus stop so passengers could easily switch between the two
transport. All right, here we go. Wait, it has to be on a building? Wait, it has to be on a road?
Let's keep going. You have no money? I'll just raise taxes for five minutes. Okay. I need to
continue my monorail. First, I need... Where was the monorail? Who the hell was that? I don't
know what that was. Oh, here. Okay. Monorail. Where am I going? I don't know. I want to just
have a monorail go around the whole town and have those stops along the way. Can I do that?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Listen. Okay. I wanted to come down here and then
have the... Yeah, right here. Okay, good. And then we have them get out. Monorail station.
How do you make them get out? Monorail line. Click on monorail stops connected with tracks to each
other. Wait, monorail stops? How do I make it so we can get out? No, I'm not ready to do this yet.
Do I have to build a road? But I actually need a fucking road? Okay. When you go down, you get to
go like, whoa. And it's like a landmark. Stop. What? This is the dumbest city plan. Who voted
for this? Okay. So now have them get out. Okay. Right here. So now get out of this. How do I
connect this? Teach him. Stop. Stop it. Stop it. Stop. It's connected. What the fuck? Here we go.
Done. All right. I know I need electricity. I'm not dumb. I'm not dumb. See? I'm not dumb.
We're already connected here, right? Yeah. All right. Now we need to connect.
Ooh. Oof. Oof. This is right here. And then I'll make it in the cup. This is not ready to be used
yet. So don't worry. Okay. This way. Here comes the residential. Put it up this way. Over here.
Then you go over here. Okay. Good. Okay. This is like trees and shit. Okay. I'm gonna need water.
I'm gonna have to do some more pumping, which is fine. Electric. Don't have to be there yet.
Oh, I can connect it from here. Look at that. It'll work out pretty well. What's wrong? Oh,
I need electricity. How much do I have? I have plenty. What's going on? How do you have no,
how do you know, how do you have no electricity? Electricity production 252. What's going on?
Why is there a total power outage over here? I'm, I'm have way more production. How,
why they disconnected? I got plenty of electricity available. What's wrong?
Poop is clogging the wires. What am I missing here? Why would they be disconnected if I have
plenty of electricity to use? Oh, was it a bad connection? What happened? Oh, this is fucked up
right here. Oh, this is fucked up. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. It's fucked up. What is this even
connected to? Okay. So that is powering this whole entire spot. And now, but can I not, I fucked it
up. Did I, I did. Can I not go from here to here? Not connected to the turbines. Your wire to your
water wind farm. Thank you. That's connecting, right? Yeah, we're good. Should be. Yeah. Look
at that light up. How do you not have water? Do a production. Oh, water. Okay. We need more.
We need a little pump. Okay. I'm going to do the green ones. Pump, water pumping station.
Get it over here. Right. Okay. Good. Pump it up. Nice. Sick. Cool. And then we need a dumping
station. But this time I'm going to do the eco one. Eco water outlet. Cool. Look. Eco. There we go.
Please check the noise. Noise. Pollution. Everywhere. Fire safety.
Move. Prime. Everything's good. Look, crime. Noise pollution. That's very loud.
Oh, I don't like looking at this. I don't want to, I don't look at that anymore.
All right. Let's do, uh, let's get this connected. This is temporary. Temporary. Remember,
they have water. What else is wrong? Not enough educated workers. What happened to the college?
Why are there only 394 students out of 4,000 that are capable to go here?
What the hell's going on here? Public library. No, I want like a trade school.
There are three types of campus areas in your city can include only one of each type.
A trade school is just a path. Click the link. Ah, sure. They called me a madman.
All right. Speaking of that, let's get back to the fun stuff. New music station. Something else.
Okay. I need to connect this road and then this is open for business. What happened here?
Citizens are sick. A dead person's in here. Citizens are sick. I have like five of these things.
Isolated. Oh, they're not sick anymore. Why are these all abandoned? Why are these all abandoned?
Excuse me. What's going on here? Oh, there weren't enough people to work the job. Oh,
this whole street is going to get abandoned. All right. Well, now there's plenty more options.
Okay. Connect this road here so we can use the monorail. Here we go. Nice. Yeah, I'll fix it.
Don't worry. I did tell you that was temporary. I did say that. Yes, I did. You did not. Yes,
I did. Stop. All right. So who's going to use it? Can I adjust the speed? These are all houses.
Holy shit. There's a lot of people over here. All right. I need elementary school.
I don't have any money. Okay. Good. And then a high school. And then, you know, let's put a library
over here. A better library. You know, I only have one in the whole town, but we'll be a library
right here for all the people to come and hang out. Good. All right. Now let's increase the
fuck out of taxes and make it... Wait, somebody going to get on the monorail? This road doesn't
go anywhere. I need more people. I need more jobs. All right. Let's do some more residential.
It's already there. Good. I don't think anyone's going to get on this. Go on first person with
the monorail. How do I do that? Whoa, cool. You can click on the train now. Wait, somebody's using
this road. It's an ambulance. Where are you off to? Where are you going? There's no hospitals down
here. Good maneuvering. You went over the fun hump. Oh, hold on. Oh, somebody's sick in here.
Okay. Let's go. Get him. Get him into the back of the ambulance. Take him to the hospital. Quickly.
Stopping at a red light? Siren's not even on. There's another red light. What? Where is he?
Wait, what? What's this monorail doing over here? Oh, right. I forgot. This is too far to go.
I need to make some medical centers down there. It's been like 12 days. It's a road trip. How
come nobody's using the monorail? I want to see somebody in it. It's, you guys, a frost country
emergency. Yep. At least there's no traffic here. Oh, wait. Somebody going to get on the monorail?
Oh, fuck this. I don't care about that anymore. Yeah. Drive the guy through the smog with the
windows down. Why are you going on this road? Shit. You're going to let this guy... What the
fuck? He's right there. Why is it so loud? This window keeps moving. Dude, I can't follow it. The
window keeps fucking moving. I never thought about how much garbage piles up in two weeks.
Where's the nearest hospital? Hey. Oh, okay. We made it. Did he make it? I think he made it.
Any more trash pick up? Okay. What happened down here? What the fuck? I'm getting so turned
around. The city is so fucked up. Which way is the right way? Okay. This way, right? Okay.
Oh, man. It hurts to look at. Okay. All right. So, fuck. Let's... There's the fire over here.
We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. This doesn't need to exist. People are just going
down here. Okay. What do I do? What do I need? I need industry, but I need workers. I need trash
pick up. Fix the train? What's wrong with the train? There's nothing wrong with it. How do I
turn it on? It needs a route? This is not a route? It needs a route. How is this not a route? I have
to set up a route. Oh, okay. Routes. How do I make one? How do you make a route? Traffic routes.
Adjust roads. Routes. It has to loop? The monorail tab. Post service. Tours. Taxi monorail.
Routes. Where? Routes. Where are the routes? Wait. Hold on. You're talking about...
It has to do this, is what you're saying? No. So, why won't it work? Top left traffic menu.
Have I never been to a city? Yeah, but I mean, how do I get it to... Where's the add stops
to both stations? Metro train hub. Monorail station with road. Monorail station. It needs
to be connected to other stations of the monorail track. Traffic highway. The third icon.
Miscellaneous. Click on the monorail stops connected with... Create a new line. There.
Complete the line. This is a huge PogChamp moment right here. All right. There it goes.
This thing's fucking fast. This thing goes faster than the cars. Okay, I've never seen a monorail
before that goes more than 60. Whoa. Oh, cool. Now, what do people do when they get off? Let's see.
Okay, responding to a call at the broad residence. I'm in a big city. Okay, responding
to a call at the pleasant residence. I don't... I'm a big city. Nice. This is pretty cool. I'm a
big city now. How much money? I got $211,000. Fucking $211,000. I need more electricity.
Need more wind farms. Water wind farms. What's this thing? Hydro pump. Flowing water is an
infinite source of kinetic power. Find a strong current in a river. Wait, what? This is not strong.
What's this? Water treatment plant. Get this shit on here. Water treatment plant. Done. I'm not
gonna take out a fucking loan. Wait, I didn't connect it. Hold on. Done. Bingo. I need more
power. Shit. Right. I need more of these. Okay, we're gonna see those disappear in a minute here.
That is 281 production. Okay, let's raise taxes like crazy for a minute and then build... build
a nice Statue of Liberty roundabout. What's the biggest roundabout I can make? I need a little
road in here. Just small enough to put it on. Like right... right there. Can I do it right there?
I can't put it right there? Oh yes, I can. Don't tell me what I can't. I can't fucking do a game.
Where's one way? Where's one way? Four lane. It's the red layer. Yeah, because it's all... it's just
going around. Where's... where's one way? Two lane, one way road. There we go. Make a lull of road.
All right, it's time to raise taxes for like fucking two minutes. Give me money now. Go,
go, go, go. Deposit, deposit, deposit, deposit, deposit, deposit, deposit, deposit, deposit, deposit,
deposit, deposit, deposit. Two, three, four. Okay, I can fix it. Need a bit... need a bigger road.
Need a little bit bigger. Rob... wait, it's a highway. Highway. Highway was... wait. Come on.
I can't put it on a highway. Here we go. One way. Six lane, one way road. Come on. I don't want
six lane. Fine. Build the statue first. I can't. It's gonna be on a road. Oh, why? And go. Wait,
why would you come through here when you can already drive by it for free? I was gonna make
tolls here. How do you make a toll road? Pause it, pause it, pause it. I'm so fucking stupid.
Right click and switch the type. Okay, so right click, road tolls. Here we go. One
lar... one way large toll booth. Can I move this? Okay, here we go. Over here. Over here. Here we go.
Why is it this way? Oh, no, no, no. That's fine. That's fine. So you come in and you go.
But how do you get out? Do another one, do another one. Do like three. How do I spin it around?
It seems to go to three tolls. Wait, what? I'm so confused. Which way are the cars driving?
Okay, this way. Okay, so, so you have to go. Wait, I don't have any money. Okay, explain this to me
because I'm fucking stupid apparently. Well, I don't understand. Which, this arrow is pointing
this way and arrow is pointing this way. Which way do the cars have to go? It goes both ways?
Look at the ends. So it goes this way. Okay, good. So it goes this way. But this is the exit.
So it goes this way. So I have to... I don't have any money. How the fuck do I not have any money?
What? Wait. Okay, I fucked it up. Move, move this fucking thing. Move it. Just move,
move, move, move, move, move. Pause again. Relocate this. Get rid of this. Can I tilt this?
How do I rearrange this? How do I rotate? How do I rotate? I can't rotate. Which button is it?
Okay, good. All right, good. I have fucking money. How? All right, good to go. Okay, wait,
wait, wait. It needs to be connected. I need power. Pause it. Okay, power and water. Done.
Matthew, liberty needs power. Wait, how much electricity does this use? All right, what's
wrong with this? Multiple problems. No road access. Make sure cars and pedestrians can reach the
entrance. No water's going through here. Oh, is this to be connected? All right, come on in to see
the Statue of Liberty. Statue's not on a road? What does that matter? How do I do that? Can I
pick it up? Wait, what? How did I put it down the first time? Why the fuck is the city on fire?
The city's burning. Wait, why? It's because this shit's a highway? I'll fix it. You motherfucker.
Oh, just do it already. You piece of shit. I swear to God. Connect a road to it. I can't.
I can't. It's like... All right, there we go. There we go. There we go. There we go.
Now upgrade the road. No, I can't. My taxes. Make entrance cheap. Entrance, 10 cents. Exit is fucking
$4. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash.
Firefighters. Firefighters. Firefighters. Firefighters. Firefighters. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash.
Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash
Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash.
Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash.
Delete the highway. Delete the highway. Delete the highway. Delete the highway. Delete the highway.
Delete the highway. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa
Okay. Yeah, sure. How dare you go see the fucking Statue of Liberty. Does that work? No, I don't. I don't have any more money. I need, uh, how much money? How much fucking money does this cost? $12,000. This is 35 grand. Um, what? Alright, hold on. I need to make some money first. Wait, they're avoiding the toll. They're driving off the road. Two bucks. Thank you for an amazing vacation. See you next year. See you next year. See you next year. See you next year. See you next year. See you next year.
Wait, I'm not even getting fucking money for this. I don't even get any money for this one. Why not just delete this? I think these people are stuck here. Raise the price of the entrance. This is fucking diabolical. Make tolls going into the city. Speaking of the city, it's in shambles. These are all abandoned buildings. Why do I hear a fire sound? Alright, let's increase some fucking, let's go to the budget. Where's the trash? More money to the trash.
More, as much as possible. Taxes? Eh. Lawns? Eh. Okay, I need another toll. Uh, right about here. Let's pause it. One-way toll booth. This one's cheaper. Wait, hold on. Everyone's fucked now. I'm gonna take them all around this whole thing and then connect them. Today they have to pay it. Imagine avoiding this. Uh, oh yeah, I'm getting directions to, um, my grandmother's house. Would you like to avoid the toll road?
Uh, fuck it, I don't care. I guess I'll pay it. Are you sure? Yeah, whatever. I'm gonna make so much money, you have no idea. I'm gonna make hundreds of thousands of dollars. And I'll be, the next city will be so cool. This is gonna go fucking this way around here, this way down, then back down.
Make it go into the city? Make it go, like, through fucking residential areas? Okay, hold on. Yeah, that's funny. That's funny, I don't wanna do that. You get a whole tour of the whole city. Fuck, I'm out of money. Why are they disappearing? Hey. Hey! What's going on? It's not, it's, yeah, it is connected. It's connected. Hey! They despawned, there's no way to the destination. Ah, okay, I see. Well, they'll get there eventually. Can I take out, like, a monster lawn?
Listen to me. What's the cheapest road I can possibly make? Two-lane gravel road? Can I do one-way gravel road? How much is this? $20? Okay, good. One-way toll booth. Is that gravel road? There it is. Imagine driving by. Is this that you live in and you see people needing to do this? This is, this is great.
Okay, I need money. Money. Money. Taxes. Money. Money. Money. Money. Money. Money. Money. Taxes. Increase. Something stupid and then just immediately take it off. Nope. Stop! See? I'm, I'm good. Alright, alright, alright, alright, alright, alright. Wait. What if I just connect this? No, they'll be stuck forever. Hold on a second. If I just connect this here, they'll just have to go in this loop literally forever. But the issue there is, when there's too much traffic, it'll get stuck.
The plan is to go around here. The plan is to go here and then around here back connecting to the highway.
Okay, I've got $67,000. You know what I'm saying? Just, like, go all the way over here. I can fix this later. Okay. Make the toll go through here.
Oh, shit. Hold on. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Make a ramp. What is it? Page up? Okay, now we're gonna, yeah, make a, just a single road. We have to go ramp up. Okay. Ramp it down. Oh, wait. We have to go underground.
Okay. No, this is, that's too much. That's too much. Okay, now back to normal. We'll get a toll at the end of that, but I wanted to make sure this is connecting.
Wait, hold on. I gotta level this out. Taller coaster. Page up. I need to, what the fuck? Where is this, wait, wait, hold on. I need to, yeah.
I have to, holy shit, this is gonna take fucking forever. All right. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. Back to normal. All right. Again. So we need one here.
We delete this. Just delete enough space where I can put it in. It's two spaces, right? Okay. Delete. I should put houses here too. And then delete this.
Fuck. I wish you could just do one. Do two. Okay. Delete two. How much money do I have? Not enough. Hopefully this will fix the traffic in the city.
How much is that fucking money? I have to finish the road. I have to for now. We'll, I'll fix it later. What am I getting? I'm $55,000 a week. Is it, are the taxes still high? No, they're not.
All right. I gotta connect the exit. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Just connect it. I'll fix the rest later. Done. Okay. Action. I'll fix it later. I need, okay. I need power.
Power and water. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Well, at least it'll be here already. I don't have enough money to do this. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. No, I need one of these to be over here. What is this mess right here? What the hell is this?
Fucking money. Come on. Come on. Negative $217. Oh, what's going on? What's going on? Oh, this shit's not connected to anything. Right. That's why it was there. Okay. Just put it from here to here. I have negative fucking money.
Shit. Oh fuck. Taxes. Uh oh. Uh oh. That's enough. Okay. Power. Power. Power. We need power from, we need power here. That'll do it. That'll do it. I know that's fucking stupid. I know. But just trust me on this. Wait. Tolls. As much as I can do. This is two bucks per car, by the way.
Hey, dude. I'll just make taxes in the city zero. Make the city taxes absolute zero. Yeah. That sounds good. Okay. There we go. Enjoy the Statue of Liberty. Is this working now? Is this connected? Wait. Hold on. Is this not connected? Is that connecting people? Should be. Alright. Looks good. Very good. Plus $57,000 coming in. Everything's alright. Let's take a look at how this looks. Good. I'm going to let this play out for a little bit. I need to fix some stuff in the city. There's so much trash.
Oh fuck. Who cares? Fuck these people. Put a dump right here. They're going to get mad that they're driving by dumps. I'll put like five of them. What do I care? Floating garbage collector? Oh, an incinerator. Here we go. Does this hit everybody? I can't tell. Is this going to hit like a bunch of people? Where should I put it? Oh, the dump trucks will clog it. Yeah. Alright. That's fine. Up here. Incinerator. Power. Here we go. Pay tolls to dump garbage. Alright. Is this working? Two dollars. Four dollars. Okay. Two. Wait a minute. Wait. They're avoiding.
They're getting off at another exit. The one before. Oh. I don't want to pay the tolls. How the fuck do you get out of here? You can't get out. Can you? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Excuse me. Excuse me. That's not happening anymore. They have to turn. They can eventually get on this road and go this way. Not anymore. Wait, what? Wrong one? What do you mean wrong one? These are both going to attach to here. That would mean no way into the city. Yes, there is.
Because once we get to about here, I will connect this to this road here. No, I'll connect it to here. From here to here. If you want to leave, then you have to go through the rest of the tolls. If you want to stay in the city, then fucking come this way.
This game is so fun. I can't believe you can actually do this shit. Alright. Let's keep doing what I was doing. Do these people die? Okay. You can like leave this way. I don't know if I'm okay with that. Am I? Alright. There we go.
I have to go down there.
Oh shit. Okay, let's see. Does this work? Grand city.
Oh no. Oh shit. There's another way in. There's another way into the city. There's like three ways into the city. Oh no.
Not anymore. Keep going. Oh, what's this? Keep going. Roads closed.
Keep going. Good luck. This is going to be a bigger road. Upgrade. Oh, I can't upgrade that. Alright, so this could just be deleted. There's no reason for this. Okay, people can come out. That's fine.
Yeah, this is alright. And then we'll just connect this shit right here. Whatever. Fuck it. Go like this. Oops.
Straight dog? There. Look. Now you can fucking go this way. And come back into the city. Does it work? How are people avoiding this? Uh oh. What have I missed? What have I missed?
There's no way in? Oh shit. Okay, yeah. From here to here. Now there is. Okay, good. Now here they all come. Perfect. Beautiful. Beautiful.
We missed a road. People have to be able to leave. That means they can never leave. They're just always going to be constantly going around in a circle through my tolls. Forever.
What's going on with the power situation here? I need, okay, I need more electricity. Electric, electric, electric. What do I want?
Um, how about a, I don't know, this fucking solar power plant. I got money. Let's make it. Put it down here. Who cares?
Is this industry or houses? No. What's the industry? Oh, everything's gone up here. Wait. I'm still turned around. It's over here. Okay.
There we go. Bang. Tons and tons of fucking energy now. Very good. These need power though. How are they not being powered? There we go. Alright. Back in business.
Wait, where are these people coming from? Oh, yes, you can leave. Yes, you can. After you go through all the bullshit, you can actually leave.
The only exit out of the whole town is right here. Toll dodgers? No, they're not. That's not possible. How come I'm not making more money than this?
This is like six dollars a car. Is this counting? They're tailgating. I need more. Alright, here we go. Nobody's calling me a psycho. Whatever.
Cars charged last week. Here we go. A hundred and forty-five? Excuse me. Excuse me, this is bullshit. Um, how is that possible? Why is there not counting people?
Fourteen. Fifteen. Sixteen. Less people have been charged? This is the... This has got to be ten thousand cars going through here.
One-nineteen. One-twenty. One person got through. One-nineteen. Dude, there's hundreds of cars going through. One hundred and thirty-two cars. That's it?
That's unbelievable. It takes a day to go through the toll. Okay, this is getting bad. But they all have a hundred. So if there's a hundred cars per day...
I don't get this. This math. A hundred times two is two hundred dollars. Let's just do the math if it was just all cars. Two, four, six, eight, ten, twelve, fourteen, sixteen, eighteen.
That's two thousand dollars a week. Is that what we're doing? Better be. All this for two thousand dollars a week. We'll just wait until there's fifteen of them.
Toll income. Thirty-six hundred dollars a week. Toll income. You need seventeen thousand five hundred cars to pay off one booth. Are you shitting me?
It's a hundred and twenty dollars a week to upkeep them. Long term. Yeah, in like forty years this will be worth it. What's wrong with the Statue of Liberty?
The Statue of Liberty is currently being robbed. Some people are just getting out of their cars and looting the Statue of Liberty.
Oh yeah? You all think you're so smart, don't you? Oh, interesting. Replace the dirt roads? I mean, I kind of can't. Go arrest whoever's doing this shit. Where are they?
Oh wait, the cop can't leave. Oh wait, how's the cop going to get anywhere? He's trying to squeeze in. He has to pay the toll. The cops have to pay the toll too. I lost him. Where's the car?
This is an absolute mess. Most attractive city award. Thank you. Hey, stop. I think I'm done. I think I'm done. I think I'm done for today. I'm done for today. I'm going to save this. Game saved.
Okay, so. I kind of fucked this all up. So tomorrow, open the natural disaster tab. The bottom? What the hell is that? In landscaping? Wait, I can do this? Earthquake? Sinkhole? I didn't do anything. Meteor strike? Why is it not doing it?
Slider? What's this? 5.1? Severity? 10? More for it to go faster. Alright, I saved it. How come they're not showing up? It's coming.
Wait, another one?
Eh.
Wait, what is this?
Wait, is it a meteor?
What is this? Lightning?
The residents should seek shelter immediately if any is available. A meteor strike has occurred. Avoid the impact site and head to shelter if any is available.
A meteor strike has occurred. Avoid the impact site and head to shelter if any is available.
What is this? Deep freeze? Oh no, no. Collapse. What does this do? Where's the dinosaur one? Dinosaur? That's Sim City. Alright, let's speed it up. I want to see this next one.
I might play this again. Maybe I'll play this tomorrow. Again.
And we'll...
Either this or...
I feel like you kind of can't start Animal Crossing if you're in the middle of Fuckface City.
A thunderstorm is battering the city. Stay indoors until the storm has passed.
Get out of here! What was the next thing I did?
What a storm. I hope no one's hurt. Holy shit.
Didn't I do another one? I did like this one. Tsunami? Let's see what it looks like. Tsunami takes forever. Oh.
In the water. Tsunami with the poop water. Oh no.
Don't know how people... It's just locked down right there.
Multiple problems. Environmental activity is high.
I want to see the... I want to see it. This takes a long fucking time.
Still earning $3,500 a week. Somehow.
Look at the horizon. I don't see shit. I see it. No you don't. There's nothing coming. It's not even coming.
You don't see. I don't see anything. Alright, this is not even happening.
What do you mean? Wait, is this just it? No, that's a burnt forest. Turn around.
Oh my god.
The Coast Guard is warning of a tsunami approaching the area. Oh, thanks!
Residents should avoid roads and waterfronts.
A tsunami has struck the city. Take caution and avoid roads and waterfronts until the water recedes.
Alright, I'm out of here. I'm done. See you guys later. I'll see you tomorrow. No!
No! How are you supposed to avoid this shit?
The tsunami has hit the city. Take caution and avoid roads and waterfronts until the water recedes.
I did. Don't I already know this?
What's with their obsession with the blimps? Why are these people happy over here?
The tsunami has struck the city. Take caution and avoid roads and waterfronts until the water recedes.
Uh oh, it's mixing. Alright, I'll see you tomorrow. I'm done.
I'm done. Let me just double check. This is okay. Hey, we're fine.
Hey! Cool, cool, cool. Very good, very good, very good.
Alright, so I'm not sure what I'm going to do tomorrow.
We're either going to do this or more. I might. I don't know. It's up in the air.
I think this is fun. I'm either going to continue doing this, start Animal Crossing, or something else completely different.
We'll see. This was fucking hilarious though. This was absolutely worth playing at least once or twice.
We'll see. I'll be around pre-stream tomorrow. Thanks for watching. Game is saved, don't worry.
Uh, that was hilarious. But, we are going to say our goodbyes.
See you tomorrow. Thanks for watching. Thanks for hanging out, as always.
Doom? Wait, oh, Doom. Just Doom comes out. There's a lot of shit that's coming out, huh?
There is a lot of fucking stuff coming out, isn't there?
It's already out. Oh, shit.
Oh, that's going to be, I don't know. I'm going to have to, I don't know.
I have no idea what's going to happen tomorrow.
But, let's go do the bits and the subs and everything.
Thanks again for watching. See you tomorrow.
Uh, produces Asan. Thanks for the five community subs. I missed it earlier.
I think that was right before the stream started.
And with Wings, thanks for five dollars. Oh well, sounds like it's scuffed.
Guess you could just play Doom instead. Huh? We didn't play Doom? We played this?
Sam, thanks for the three dollars, Sam.
Dermot, you will end up building a maze of a city and I'm alright with that.
It's alright. I did a pretty good job, I think.
Ah, thank you Freak8 out for a hundred dollars over many donations.
I'm going to pre-screen your messages. I'm just going to make sure I pre-screen these.
Because this is the porn guy for Lizzie that don't know.
Wait, didn't I ban this person from giving messages? I think I did.
I did. I already did. Yeah, I did that, right? I remember that.
Alright, I'm going to scan through and we'll take a look.
Dermot, I'm watching for a few years now. Well, thank you Freak8 out for the hundred dollars you gave over many different donations.
Read them silently. I'll pick out some words here. Let's see if this is appropriate for stream. We'll find out.
I've been watching for years. It's been a while.
But due to the virus, I didn't get many hours in February when the news first started reporting it.
I was fired two weeks ago from Honda. It's because someone ratted me out.
I would use to make cocktails in the back room and share them with the guys at work.
Alright, one time there's this guy. I wonder how it all started. One time there's this guy named Fred.
Okay, he gave me some Jim Bean. Okay, I figured I wasn't going to drink it straight.
Okay, what's next? Okay, I shared it with the guys. About a month or two went by. It was slow.
Okay, I started to mix up something. I call it a new drink. I made 7-ups. It's 7-up and whiskey.
Okay, people liked it. I began to bring stuff every week. Sure, okay.
I thought this girl started working there. I thought she was cute. Okay.
I didn't know how. Okay, okay, okay. What's the point of this?
What's the point of this? This is going to be like an end here.
There's going to be an end here, isn't there? I'm going to read it out loud.
Okay, I started to talk to her. Okay, I brought her Long Island iced teas.
Okay, you name it. Someone ratted on me.
In two weeks, luckily, my tax returns have been helping out. Not many dealerships are hiring right now.
I hope you're doing well. I have bought towels. You dirty boy. I saw that you played Binding of Isaac and not well versed in the Bible.
Here's Arnold Schwarzenegger reading the book of Genesis.
I wanted to ask, can you talk for the next 15 minutes in a Boomhauer accent?
Okay, this actually wasn't even that bad. I don't think this story is accurate.
This story is not even accurate. This is not even a real story, I don't think.
Apparently getting fired for bringing alcohol to work. Don't do that. It's a fucking huge mistake.
It is accurate. I'm the girl. Freak out, you freaking me out. You freak me out, I'll tell you.
I'm the drink, it's true. I'm the guy that fired him.
Well, regardless if this story is real or not, if it is, you shouldn't be doing that. Why would you be doing that?
It's not real. It's not a real story. But I'm sorry about you getting fired in this story that I don't think is real.
But thank you for the fucking $100 due to a lot of money. Freak out, you're freaking me out. Thank you.
It's 100% real, it's true.
Opster Narwhal, thanks for the $4.
You gotta have at least five or six mascots dancing around. That's all that matters.
As long as there's at least five to ten mascots in the front door, it could look however you want it to look.
Good luck though. I mean, if it's real, you shouldn't feel bad.
If you're bringing fucking alcohol to work and giving it to people, you're gonna get fired.
What do you want me to tell you? If you start bringing booze to work and drinking on the job and giving it to all the coworkers, you're going to get fired.
The boss is gonna be like, hey, this is not like an old movie from the fucking 90s where the boss comes in, hey, what's going on in here? Are you drinking?
Yeah, man, we're drinking.
Oh, well, you think you're gonna get in? Let me have some, boys.
That's not how this works. You're gonna lose your job if you do that. Don't do that.
Jerma sucks when he spits the truth. What? What are you talking about?
Hey Wembley TTV, thanks for the 250. Jerma, thank you very much for streaming and keeping everyone entertained.
I'm from London and it's gotten really crazy here and more than likely a lockdown is happening next week.
A local hospital had to be shut down today as well, but I'm still keeping positive. People like yourself streaming is getting us all entertained.
All I can say, don't take risks at all and look after yourselves and love ones much love.
Yeah, I talked about this earlier. I'm not trying to be your mother. I know people made that joke, but you'd be surprised at how many people when they know they just do it anyways, they'll just go somewhere anyways.
You'd be surprised. If you have a lockdown going on, don't take any chances. Only get essential things that you need. Just ride this shit out.
Shut up, mom. I would be a very good mom, okay? I'd be a good father. I'd be like, hey, excuse me. What are you guys doing in here?
Dad in the wall. Nothing. All right. Good night, boys. I don't know. I'm not a father. I don't know how this works.
Take care of yourself, Wembley. Don't fuck around. Do not mess around with a city or statewide lockdown. There's a reason why they're in place.
Take care of yourselves. Take care of your loved ones. Take care of your friends. Just let's try to ride this out.
We also had a ton of money come in. Freddie Dread gave $200 in bits. Zyxia gave 100 community subs. Chris gave $50 in bits. Just a shitload of money. Thank you guys.
All in the same five-minute span here a few hours ago. BS88, thanks for the $3. Jeremy, this is exciting to see you play this.
The girlfriend and I had a great time building a city in this and we both love it. Awesome to see you play it. Be sure to check out Biffa. He has great tips and tricks, particularly on traffic.
Yeah, I didn't really understand that traffic was the thing. I thought you just built roads and I didn't know that was a real thing.
I wonder if people, these games, this game people can probably get so elaborate with it. I can imagine the obsessive kind of, you could make so many highways so perfect.
I can imagine how cool that would be if only I was capable. But thank you. Thanks a lot.
Ruta Miss, thanks for the $5. Jeremy, my 30th birthday was yesterday. Can I get Bugleberry to give some words of wisdom on getting older?
Yeah, sure.
Get the fuck out of here.
Okay. I believe that was good enough. Happy 30th birthday. Thanks a lot.
Hey, Swiggity Swanky, thanks for the $2.50. Your aging Boston accent is slowly just morphing into Bernie's.
All right, we're going to lower the taxes on the citizens to 7%.
Fuck yeah. I didn't think I was even doing Bernie. It was. I didn't even mean to. It just happened.
Hey, just some normal guy, 25, thanks for the $5. Jeremy, please build an elementary school for us.
The people here are too stupid and are parking out on the road instead of on their, of their garages.
They're all eating bug donuts and someone built a power line right outside my house. Help them.
Uh, Disorge Captiva, $100 in bits. We, we went over these, but insane amounts of money.
Snarbosus, I didn't even see this. How did I fucking miss this? 20 community subs from Snarbosus.
That's a shitload. How did I miss that? What was going on? That's a 20 drop.
Thank you, Snarbosus. If you're still here, that's a lot of money. Thank you.
Uh, happy Homeacademy points. Wait, he wasn't playing Animal Crossing. No, I wasn't. You're wrong, not me.
Thanks though. Maybe I, ah, fuck, what am I going to do tomorrow?
I'm going to have to like flip a three-sided coin tomorrow and figure out what the hell I want to do.
There's too much shit that's out.
Appleship, thanks for the 250. Yo man, I'm sure it's already been asked, but how's quarantine treating you?
Hope you're doing alright. My school's been cancelled for the time being, so I've been catching up on Vodswell.
Sitting around drawing, which is definitely a silver lining to all this.
Um, just been sitting around and hanging out.
We thankfully got, a few weeks ago, the last two weeks before, um, the, I mean, if you don't know, Vegas is now, the state of Nevada is on essential business lockdown.
Which is, grocery stores are open, and, uh, I think like banks and, uh, like hospitals and everything.
But all non-essential businesses are not open anymore in Las Vegas, so.
Following suit for a lot of other towns and cities in the world and in the country.
But yeah, I haven't really, I haven't left the house really.
I've had some stuff, I've had some really, really important, here's the worst part about this.
There's a lot of important shit that's going on in my like current life that is hard to take care of now.
For those of you that do not know, I haven't really talked that much about it because I didn't want to make a big deal about it.
I've been talking about it in a pre-stream recently.
But I am moving.
Kim and I are moving to a new place.
And it's happening very soon.
And it's just like, holy shit.
This all is coming at this point right now.
Uh, we're staying in Vegas.
No, no, no, we're not moving, we're staying in Las Vegas.
We're not moving back to Boston.
So with the, this is essentially the first year or two here was to see if we really liked it.
And then, okay, did, did we like this?
Did we want to stay?
We wanted to downsize a little bit and there's a lot of reasons as to why we wanted to change places.
I wanted to get better internet.
There's another one with the fucking people driving by, the vroomers.
That was like 75% off.
But that's happening very soon.
But I haven't really talked about it because I don't want to be like, hey, I'm moving again.
Everybody get ready or where the fuck is he going?
No, I'm staying in Las Vegas.
Just a different place.
Please keep a place where people will still vroom.
That's such a big deal.
I call up a bunch of, apartment complex number 15.
Hey, do cars like fucking drive by really fast?
Um, I don't think so.
I'm just sorry.
Not interested.
Okay. But yeah, but it's been the last few weeks.
We're trying to figure out the smoothest way to make this a reality.
And it kind of landed on the worst possible time.
So we still are doing it.
That and the medical shit that I'm doing right now.
I'm trying to stay on top of it and trying to, but I, you can't really, it's hard to do that now.
So a lot of shit in real life is starting to get affected by it too.
But you do what you got to do.
And hopefully over the next month or two, this will start to flatten out as they say and get better.
All we can hope is over the next two, three, four months that this starts to really be on the way out.
We just have to just try.
But that's kind of the way it's been the last couple of weeks.
But thanks for the 250 Apple shift.
Appreciate it.
Thanks for the three dollars.
I'd like to remind everyone that despite current events, my German themed birthday party is still scheduled for next week.
Oh, I'm going to burp.
So sadly, Nvidia will no longer be attending this year as Greg has contracted it.
We're making up for their absence with something even more exciting.
A sub-only ball bit.
And those still concerned about the spread of the disease will be providing essential oils free of charge.
Hope to catch all of you there.
A ball, no, it's a ball bit as it says.
Essential oils.
What? Why would I get?
Why would I want an essential oil?
I don't get it. Thanks for three bucks though.
Stripes Beast, thanks for 250.
Hey Jerm, just let you know that in your landfill neighborhood, people were building houses and getting sick and dying.
Then abandoning the house.
A new house would get built over the old one.
The cycle repeats.
You're laughing. Yeah.
What do you want me to do? Not?
That's stupid.
That's fucking ridiculous.
Why is that happening?
That's fucking terrible.
It's like a secret tunnel.
Thank you Stripes Beast for the 250.
Thank you Silent Serenity for the 250.
Jerm, you have some seriously boomer-esque city planning skills.
I love it.
That was so much traffic.
Fun fact, statistical evidence suggests as you saw that adding more lanes only temporarily fixes traffic.
The only true solution is to have a better design.
Cheers.
Actually, it's funny because rotaries are supposed to be the end-all-be-all best possible way to end all traffic.
A shitload of rotaries is how you fix traffic.
It's not more lanes. It's not more roads. It's rotaries.
It's true. Look it up.
Rotary is a Boston word.
Yeah, that's fine.
Roundabout. There you go.
Roundabout. Roundabout. Sorry.
I'm from a different part of the world than you. Sorry.
Let me apologize first and foremost.
He's speaking in code.
Anyways.
Castle Build, thanks for the $5.90.
Hey Jerm, unfortunately I will no longer be able to help out due to the end of my academic career.
And therefore the end of my student prime.
I've loved your work since 2013. Keep it up.
Hope you stay safe during these turbulent times.
Hope you do too.
Because here's the real...
I mean I don't want to get too far into the future on this.
But if everyone's having trouble, you know, it's harder to...
Like when this stream turns on and let's say it keeps going further, like six months from now,
I'm not sure if we really keep going harder and harder and harder on this.
I'd like to try to stay positive and try to have fun on these streams.
I just really hope it doesn't get there.
Like a year from now, six months from now. I hope it's really fucking over with.
I hope we can really get over this as a group, a global group.
Because if it's hard to get like water or something,
I'll be honest with you, I don't want to turn my stream on and be like,
Hey everybody!
That's unfortunate, but I really don't want it to be that like that.
I really don't want to get to a point where it's hopefully...
It's just every day we just keep hearing about this shit and I really hope it's on the way out.
I'll keep doing it. I will keep fucking streaming it.
I'll keep trying to have as much fun as I can.
But honestly, I just want to be honest with you.
Even right now, for instance, right?
If I'm having problems in my life, it's hard for me to come on here and make a bunch of jokes.
Especially if something serious is going on.
But I don't think we'll get that far.
I mean, I say I don't think because I really hope we don't.
But I'll be here.
Regardless of what we're doing, I'll be here.
I've got no reason to stop. I'm not going to stop doing it.
And I think that sometimes having laughing and having a good time and making jokes and making comedy helps with everything.
No matter what it is.
But obviously I'm overthinking what could potentially happen in the future.
But we'll see.
Making comedies.
Cease to review refuses to stop.
Now, you know what I mean, though.
Anyway, take care of yourselves, please.
Captain O.W., thanks for the $5.
Use this to go to city building school, Omega Lo.
That was pretty good.
That was pretty funny.
AllOfOneZombie, thanks for the $2.50. Great stream. Thanks, dude.
It was a lot of fun.
Flo, and thanks for the $4.
Watch you for so long lurking, but just want to say you're easily the only thing getting me through this whole quarantine situation.
Big love from England.
Take care of yourself.
All of you.
I'm trying to as well.
Off stream, I'm trying to do the same thing.
We're all trying to do the same thing right now.
Take care of yourself. Thank you.
Eggscramble, thanks for the $2.50. Eggs, milk, hummus, 97% lean ground, turkey, dried bay leaf, carrots, celery, sourdough, cheese nips, club soda for Uncle.
I have no idea what you're talking about, but all those things sounded good to me.
So, besides maybe the milk.
I don't really want that.
Turtle toenail, thanks for the $50, 5,000 bits.
Just a few moments ago. You should change the name to Toll City, then you'd get more, you'd get more German tourists and more money.
I don't understand.
Toll City? Is a EU joke?
Wait, does Germany have a bunch of tolls?
Toll means awesome in German.
Oh, I see. Okay.
Well, thanks for the 5,000 bits, dude. Seriously. Appreciate it.
Silence, Serenity, thanks for the $2.50. If you really want to play Animal Crossing on stream, I'd recommend you start it off stream.
If you haven't already.
The game is heavy, very heavily time gated.
And the first day gameplay is pretty much just putting your tent down and catching fish.
It would be a very slow stream. With that said, the game is very cute and relaxing.
Maybe I'll fucking... I don't know.
It's going to be a game time decision tomorrow. What I want to do.
We'll see.
Dinosaurus Rex, thanks for the 300 bits. Hello, Germa. I really enjoy your streams.
About a year back, I submitted some custom Guitar Hero tracks, one being the Pirate Marching Band mixed with Tachyon by Death Grips.
The other being Berries and Sterries.
After this, you suggested the idea of an FL Studio stream.
I fully advocate this idea and along with it, we'd like to suggest a green screen-esque stream where instead of video, it's audio.
And you make funny noises to be remixed for a whole stream.
Well, dusting off in the vault of ideas that sit behind me, once upon a time, maybe a year or so ago, I wanted to not do...
The FL Studio thing was like, oh, that's pretty cool. What a good idea.
That's a funny thing to do is make like just music on stream.
Scratch that. I want to hire a whole band.
I want to have like 17 people here, like trumpet players, guitarists and stuff and record our own music.
And they have like an actual studio band.
And just have them do like samples and shit and just make songs.
That was, I mean, that was a year ago now that I wanted to do that.
And some things took precedence over others.
That idea was around before the carnival was even started having any work done on it, so.
But, it's just, it's in a gigantic book back there.
It has not been cancelled, it's just dusty. That's all.
It is still in the mine.
Jude Minecraft, thanks for the 300 bits.
Jerome, I've been feeling bad because of fibromyalgia and anemia.
Streams make me feel better when I have bad days.
I have an alert on my phone.
Hope you're doing okay. Keep yourself safe.
Tell Otto and Kim I said hi.
Sorry to feel, sorry that you're feeling that way.
Sorry that you feel so bad.
Fibromyalgia is one of those conditions that it's just tough to treat.
I know this because it's been potentially things that might be going on with me.
So I feel for that.
It hasn't been diagnosed, I'm not saying I'm diagnosed that way.
But this mystery illness with random fucking just chest bone and like spine pain.
I don't know.
Costochondritis and fibromyalgia both, they both kind of are hand in hand in a lot of ways.
But I might not even have costochondritis.
I might have fucking rheumatoid arthritis.
This is why medical shit is so fucking annoying and because it's been like a year and a half.
And I still don't know exactly what's fucking wrong with me.
So I can relate.
Trust me, I can.
Sorry to hear about you having problems.
And I'm happy that you feel better when you watch this stream.
That makes me feel good.
Thank you for the 300 bits.
And then Desorge Catchfoot gave 1600 bits.
Say gamers, are you ready for some of that free shit again?
Steam codes in the chat.
What games have you given out?
It took me five to six years to get my neurological illness diagnosed.
I just got to keep trucking.
Yeah, that's the idea.
Is just keep eliminating things until there's nothing left to eliminate.
And that's here you are.
This is what you have.
It just, it's frustrating because I want to just go get it done.
Just let's go.
Do it all.
What codes?
What are these for?
I'm seeing codes in the chat from Desorge Catchfoot.
What are these?
Bad rats?
They're still going.
There's another like three codes.
Is it really bad rats?
That's so funny.
Well, thank you, Desorge Catchfoot.
Whatever they are.
Thank you.
And thanks for the huge amount of money.
To me.
Thank you.
Thanks for the huge amount of money.
Please.
Please, please live close to the dumpster, that italics will be forced to live in when you abandon him.
The kind.
They are.
Your KFC scraps.
And the residual bits of poop line to allow him to sustain himself.
I think he's staying here.
I think he's staying in Vegas.
This was a trial period for me and Kim.
There's also a trial period for him too.
Me and Kim was also a trial period for him, too. I don't know his exact plans, but I'm pretty sure he's staying in Las Vegas
This is fucking so oh man
I'm flying you are not staying in Vegas. No, I mean Kim is staying in Vegas
Why did he move in with you in the first place? Well, I don't know cuz
We had me and Kim were just like we're moving out here
You gotta remember when we first came out here like it we didn't know anybody out here
This is I don't know anybody in this area. I mean we do now
But it's way easier if hey, you know, what's your situation?
Like you you potentially may be looking for a place to live
I don't know you want to fucking go do this for like a year and see what would save you like it
Yeah, I guess sure and now that we have had that period
Wait, that's it. And we we've liked it. We both parties have enjoyed it and now we're kind of just going our separate kind of
ways, it's
Weirdest do you have plans to have kids? Whoa, that's a loaded quite Wow
Do you have fit? Is it because you're gonna have kids?
Whoa
No
Answer I'm fucking answering. I just said no. I don't know what I'm doing in the future
I don't know what I'm doing next week guys. You think I know what I'm doing?
I don't know what could be in the cards in the fucking future
I'm gonna stop answering these questions
I'm gonna stop answering the questions because the more that I answered the dot that the deeper the sinkhole gets
Let's go. Let's throw the subs. I don't know fucking camera, right? Okay, good. I'm naked
I don't know I'm not not in the plants. No plants
I know I'm turning like 35 this year and I'm getting a little older and it's at that point where
You sort of need to decide in the next little while if it's something that you want to do because
Yes, it's like the time to do it and for the most part
Okay, sure. And what no, it's not in the plans at the moment and I'm yes
I'm moving around a lot, but you don't I could you tell that this is not part of the plan. Okay, cool
Let's show the crap. These are all the subs today a lot of them stop tagging. Don't tag Kim
There's nothing to do with this conversation. She's not just you know, it's gonna say the same damn thing
It's gonna say no, there's no plans at all zero. No, we're not doing that
I know and that's exactly what she would say
Hey, this is a lot of subs tonight. Holy fuck. Thank you guys
Thanks for the massive amount of subs every stream
Happens every fucking day. Thank you. Hey, uh Dran Cree. Thanks for the 1500 bits
Hey longtime fans since 2013 first time giving bits ever. Thanks for the it's a lot
15 bucks is a lot
Just want to say that I really appreciate you especially in the difficult time
I've been cooped up in self isolation for about a week due to contact fears
And recently developed a cough. I'm going a little stir crazy and your streams have been such a great thing to look forward to and all
Of this you do great work
Thank you for the $15 again. I will tell you though
Self-isolating that's the that's the right thing to do. You're doing the right thing. You're doing all the right things
Just hang in there hang in there. Hopefully this all will be over soon
Hopefully we don't have to worry about
Getting this illness or spreading it around or something, but you're doing the right thing
Yeah, it's the right thing but isolation fucking sucks
Yeah, I know. I know I know I know we are we are humans we are meant to
talk and converse and socialize and
We're meant to do that. I know that's why hopefully this doesn't last that long. We're meant to pog
Yes, that too, I appreciate the 1500 bits though
J-rin, thanks a lot. You're doing the right thing
Morning may bone by the way, I wish you I wish that I wish you the best of health by the way morning maple
Thanks for the thousand bits
German thanks for doing what you do. It means a lot. This is related to the stream whatsoever
But I remember there was this British French kids show in the early 90s called Harry Jeremy. Here's the intro Harry Jeremy
Superhero doesn't drive a car stop motion
And I've never seen no secret hideaway and no all-seeing eyes just Harry
He's most definitely say the name
His name is Jeremy and he's Harry
Okay, if I was still doing sub sounds it would be this his name is Jeremy and he's Harry hey
Thanks a lot for the the sub there, dude. I appreciate it
Hey, thanks a lot of Mike three for the sub appreciate that two months in a row
Hey look at that we get another sub from
That's a sub so that's a sub sound, but I don't do this anymore. Thank you morning maple for the thousand bits
Thank you, sir enigma for the four dollars. Thanks for making us laugh and Karen during this shitty time
Helps take my mind off the world me too, so it works both ways
Sitting here having a good time takes my mind off this shit as well. So it's good. Thanks for the 400 bits
Internet internet Jorge or internet George. Thanks for the five dollars, Jeremiah
I wish the best for you and everyone in chat this trying time
It's important to remember our humanity and compassion for each other as long as we are
Compassionate and care for each other we can overcome this. Love you all. It's very true. Very very true
Just be diligent be aware and take it seriously pretty much all we can do
Silence Serenity. Thanks for 250. Hey Jeremy, can I ask you something? That's kind of been bothering me lately, okay
How did you find your calling in life? I'm in my mid 20s. And even though I'm moderately successful
I have no idea what my life goals are. How did I how did I find my calling? Um
To be honest, I've kind of just been doing this kind of shit my whole life
nothing made me happier in my entire life and just sitting around and
Telling fucking jokes making up scenarios playing video games and hanging out and just talking shit with my friends
I loved it more than anything and doing this kind of stuff
What you are witnessing right now when I turn these streams on is the exact same kind of shit that I used to do
When I was 15 16 all the way through my mid to late all the way into my mid 20s
Just with people sitting around on a couch. We would do the same fucking thing
So, I don't know if the calling is the right word, but I've always just had this I just I just love
I don't I don't even know if calling is the right word
I just love sitting around and just like shooting the shit is all as I love it
I love it more than anything. Did you and your friends ever say pog? Well funny story
You want to know where the inspiration for German rumble came from is exactly what I'm talking about. We used
we used to in
no mercy for
Nintendo 64 friends of mine would sit around and we would make characters and
It's gonna sound crazy
But we would all make our dads and just sit there and let the CPU dads fight it out
It was like if it was like we had so much fun
It was so so much fun and that's kind of like I told you that's what it just I've been doing it for so long
I've been we've been the same thing we do here. Yeah, all of our actual
Actual like CPU just our actual dads
we would make them all and they would all fight in like an elimination match and like when you're like dad got eliminated first it
Was like no, come on. What the fuck? Oh, come on, dad
Come on you'll be in next time that was just one of the many games we would play many many many games
We would play so long-winded. Where does the where do you get your calling?
It's just the thing that you the thing that you have the most fun doing the thing that you care the most about
The best fun in games is the fun you make yourself
Yes, that is absolutely
100 fucking percent accurate and not even to see not not just video games in general just the fun you make yourself is
The fun that you create is more fun than anything that anyone can ever make for you. Let's just put it that way
Hopefully somewhere in there. You got some kind of an answer, but thank you on
Zeroic thanks for the 300 bits. When's it? Oh, I gotta answer this first. When's German Rumble charity it got moved
Because the Boston Marathon got moved the Boston Marathon is on I think indefinite
hiatus until they know exactly when they want to do it the whole purpose of the German Rumble charity stream was to
Directly benefit the sponsoring of one of my friends running the marathon in September. Okay
Yeah, and that's so unfortunate that we have to you know
all the marathon runners all the charities is
We have to wait, but that's the plan still it is going to benefit the charity and sponsor his run
I'm gonna play Banner Lord when it comes out in a few days. Probably not you'll probably not see me play Banner Lord
Judging by how much I did not really do very well in the first one
So maybe but probably not but maybe but probably not but thank you for the 300 bits. Hey
Neuro wolfy
Thanks for the five dollars German. Look at this. It's me jumping around in my room
It says it says quarantined on it. That's fun. The fun you make yourself. Thank you though
So what are we gonna do tomorrow? I should probably figure it out right now. What are we gonna do tomorrow?
What are we doing tomorrow? I gotta figure it out now. I don't want to I don't want to sleep on this
What are we doing?
and crossing doom
Viva Pena dreams DOS games. Ah, there's so many things to choose from I got tons of shit over here, too
What do I want to do? Should I play doom? Should I play doom? Doom is do is it good? Is it a good game?
Doom sucks. What should I play animal? All right, here we go. Let's do like there's a there's a shit load of people here now
I'm gonna do I'm gonna do this poll tomorrow in the chat if I don't do it now with
70% less people so I I don't know I will do any of these things. I'm just so indecisive doom
Uh
animal crossing
new leave new new or was it called whatever animal crossing
I'm gonna say animal crossing switch
Okay, so these skylines part two, okay, this is I'm alright with any of these
Okay, here we go. It's gonna be one of these so might as well just do it. Here we go. Oh
What should I what am I doing tomorrow? The new half-life game? I can't really do VR right now as much as I would like to
It's it's one of those things. I just until I get this medical bullshit resolved. I can't really
Move that much around in one stream
Alright, what are we doing? Well, were you voting?
All the people that I sell people that I have have very very adverse opinions to what currently a could or could not be in
First place you've got there's only been 300 votes and there's 2,400 people here. Come on
pick something
Pick something this it's close. You're close
15%
I'm gonna I'm gonna close this in
10 seconds 10 and whatever it is at the at them when I stop the moment
I stop isn't gonna be what we're doing 10
9 8
7 6
5 4
3 2
1 we're playing Animal Crossing tomorrow
You did you did you vote no, okay, okay, hey
Actually, I'm like that
Babe, all right. Hey goo berry juice. Thanks for the 250 right at the end
Hey not to rag on you
But I just want to say that the amount the moment you started doing this shit
Was the moment the city started to be ruined like I was actually getting it was actually I was getting so loud
Because I'm drunk on a Friday night and I was going EU out loud to the point where my neighbors heard me and called the noise
Complaint. Anyway, I'm gonna go throw up and pog into the toilet. What the fuck are you talking about? What what is going on?
What if when I made the I made I made a road he did they didn't like the way that I made the road
They freaked out and I got a noise complaint. I don't what's wrong with the roads
Drunk all right. Um, all right. I'll see you. I'll see you guys tomorrow. I'll see you tomorrow. Goodbye. Good night
about it