Hey, what is going on everybody Jerma here with scare Saturdays welcome to scare Saturdays this week
I'm gonna be playing eerie and I'm recording this intro
After I just got finished with the session of me playing the game
The reason why I'm doing it like this is because I need to say this this is hands down the most intense
Terrifying scary game I've ever played in my entire life
If you are into scary games and you ever heard of eerie before go get it right now. It is completely free
It's actually a student project from somebody and oh my god guys
Just watch this video and see the complete true terror. That is eerie
So I'll see you guys all next time. Enjoy the video and take care everybody eerie. Oh
What is that noise? Is that a baby crying?
Alright missing personnel following partial meltdown and blah blah blah investigate whereabouts of missing workers
Locate sir, but I want to read that man
Hey, I want to read the rest of that note
What the hell I'm trying to examine we go locate survivors mitigate further damage
So gain entry to plant grounds and use spray paint to mark cap
I didn't you let me read the goddamn note you spray paint to mark casualty locations and danger areas
Okay, whatever. Let's let's do it. Where's my spray paint? Can I like go shift to sprint? Oh my god
This guy's superhuman. You can run like a thousand miles per hour. There's a spray paint
Thank you for the spray paint
Is it an unlimited supply? Oh
Wow, hopefully this is okay. I'm not gonna waste this cuz I know somebody's gonna say
Germa you you run into the goddamn can don't it's like lamp oil
Anyways, let's uh
Let's go. What the hell's that these pictures of this dude? Yeah. Yes. Yes. Yeah. Yes
He whips it up so fast
crawl
Get me out of this stupid little terminal. Oh
I hate when it's like this get me out of this tiny little corridor
God
No, no, you're gonna let me read it this time
What the hell is going on run
Stop that noise
Which way do I go?
I'm assuming I got to go this way that this stupid alarm is freaking me out right now
Well, I can do a running slide. Oh, I got a tag where I've been
A figure eight. All right, that's the figure eight. I know I've been here
Just shut up. Can I turn this blood all over the place?
Okay, what oh that was the glass
Is anybody in there? All right tag. Oh this guy like oh this guy like tagged this way better than I could
I don't like how fast my character moves. I'm not I'm not gonna use the sprint feature. The guy moves way too goddamn fast. It's like
That's that's that's
That was stupid I like that feature though, that's a really cool feature
You can mark where you've been so you don't get like lost be crying. I don't want to go down this hole
I'm crying with you, man
I'm crying with you. I don't want to go on this. Can I just take your like key card for a minute? Thanks
Another cat, where's the cat? I'll see if you kitty gotcha gotcha cat spray every way
It's play this spray this like alien neon green piss
It's getting really foggy right now. Wait a minute. Wasn't I already here?
Associate doctor I'm not reading all this subject was placed in truck project preservation would hold on
So something broke out of like cryogenic preservation. Let's look at that again, right?
They placed a cryogenic which suffered a power interruption all subjects on the series were
Dead or something which way
No, let's go down there first. I definitely have to do something down here sure thing
Yeah, any fish in there
Offline offline. We believe the injuries are due to the worksite proximity of the Inric of Fermi one actor reactor
reactors
Ladies and gentlemen, this is your principal speaking
There's a fucking monster right next to me right now, and I'm not gonna be in school tomorrow
Oh
I'm so fucked right now. I'm so fucked. Oh my god. Oh my god. This thing is for
Where do I start? Do I start over again? Oh, I don't want to deal with that again. Oh
For the love of God, I'm not going in this. Where is he? He's over here. I don't even forget where he is
Which way was he if I completely forget where he was he's right there. He's right there. Oh my god that guy's hard
I don't know. That's why there's a script feature
This is insane. Oh
I got the key. I got the key. I got the key
Sucks this this sucks. I already have the thing. I need to wait. Let me look at my inventory
I got the lab lobby key in the g1 key. Okay, so I am NOT go I'm
How am I supposed to do this
Women women's room women's men room women's men's room. Oh my god crawl underneath it
We're gonna know what he can't get in here Kenny
Can you please tell me he can't get in here? He can't get in here, right? Yes. I
Do it about I do it about
Run sprint
Get me out of here. Get me out of here. Is that guy still chasing me? Please. Don't tell me he's still like here
I lost him. I think
My god, I am speechless right I am speechless right now
I'm just running in random directions guys
This is the most terrifying game I've ever played
this is
The scariest game I've ever played if you want the scariest game on the internet. It's probably this one
Access granted get me out of here. I don't know if I'm supposed to be here or not
Please like electrocute the grid so he gets electrocuted and dies. Oh
Come here get in the can
I don't think I can play this anymore
Scariest game I've ever played
scariest game of
You son of a bitch
You're not getting me in here
This guy is like slender on crack. This is slender on crack cocaine
Cuz not only does he follow you like slender. He runs a thousand miles per hour. I have no idea where I'm supposed to go
Wait a minute what about through this door? Maybe I want to go this way. Where's the other generator?
I haven't been tagging anything. I don't even know where the hell I'm going. It's not that way. It's not that way
It's already been that way. Oh shit. I hear him. Oh my god. Oh my god. I
Haven't been in this room
No, don't read the note. Oh, I'm going into this room
Done done scare Saturdays is over. Goodbye. Goodbye. Thank you all so much for watching
I can't do this anymore. This is insane. This is ridiculous, dude. I don't know how far I got
I hope maybe I got like halfway through this game, but it's too much
This is too much. It's too much. Okay. Thank you so much for watching really appreciate it. Take care everybody. I'll see you all soon. Goodbye