Alrighty, how you doing? Welcome back. We're going to continue our journey through
Kare, city blood of traps. Got my tea here. I also have a coffee too from earlier, which gross.
He spelled completing wrong. I don't, I don't care. Where? In the tweet? Or here? Because I gotta be
honest, in the world of 2022, spelling mistakes no one cares about anymore. They really just don't.
Back in like the 40s, or like the 50s. It's like, oh, you misspelled that on minus five points on
your grade. Who gives a shit? Nobody cares. We all are talking to each other. We all know what we're
trying to say. Nobody cares about how you spelled a word right. You're not going to put a red pen
through it and put like, oh, excuse me. You know what I'm saying. We both know what I'm trying to
say. Am I going to delete the tweet? No, I'm leaving it. The tweet is staying as is.
If we all started not caring, we would make a new language. All right. But okay, I get it. If I,
if I was sending like a formal letter to something, to someone, I would want to make sure it didn't
say like completely. But hey, I'm just in a live stream. It's just me hanging out, tweeted again.
Yeah. For those of you that are, have asked about it or wondering about it, the thing that I was
talking about on Thursday has been announced and it's going to be a wild one. Uh, I did not know,
I did not know my team until an hour ago. Uh, this is going to be crazy. So myth is putting on
a black ops two event and I'm on one of the teams and, uh, I hope I do. Okay. I haven't played call
of duty in like eight years. Go look, go to myth's Twitter and look at the two teams.
I am going to be the worst fucking person on this team. I'm actually, I'm actually quite concerned
about it. I'm going to be, I'm going to download black ops two tonight and just play it all night
and just try to not embarrass myself in front of like a hundred million people tomorrow practice
now. No, I don't, I, I'm not practicing right now. Do you need some coaching help? I might,
I may need some pointers. Am I going to stream it? I don't know. I'll, uh, I got to talk to myth
and see what the plan is. I'm not a hundred percent sure, but we'll see that 6 PM tomorrow.
I believe that's six Pacific and let me check again. Yes. Tomorrow at six Pacific. I believe
it will at very least be on myth's channel. I would assume it was redacted. I don't know.
I genuinely don't know. I'm being serious. I have no idea. I need to, I look, all I remember from
call of duty is so hold hitting shift to sprint and then right clicking and, and then dying.
That's the only thing I remember. I don't remember anything else. I remember people just dropping
down to prone and then I remember dropping a grenade because I was one of those assholes.
What was that thing called again? Is whenever, every time you died, you dropped a grenade on
the ground and people wanted to band from the game. It was like, please ban this from the game.
Get rid of this. It's doesn't need to be in the game. And I would get kills
just because I died near like somebody. Yeah. I was, I was one of those people
and I was one of those people. And at the same time, I also was mad at those people.
I had, yeah, martyrdom. I had martyrdom equipped and I would kill somebody with martyrdom
and die from it and go, fuck that loser. And I had it equipped. That's my experience.
I hope I, I hope I do okay. I'll try. Dude, you're going to be comic relief.
Do I just bring a slide whistle to this event tomorrow? I'm going to go 0 and 15, right? I
might as well be like, I should make sounds and shit. Like I'm just going to be the jester.
Watch me play like crazy though. That would be fun. Happy birthday to my friend, please. Hey,
Montes's friend. Happy birthday. No one else is getting that by the way.
Do what you're good at. You're good at something. Never do it for free.
You see, but that's the problem, right? I've told you guys this before and I mean this.
Okay. If I'm, if I'm like the weird clown guy that makes sound effects with his mouth,
that's what I do over here. But if I go into an environment where I'm on a team with people
and I, and I'm just like, people are going to be like, shut this fucking guy up.
Shut this guy up. I don't want to hear this guy talking anymore. You know what I mean? Like you,
we can't bring that to somebody else's house, right? Usually that's how I feel. I can't,
right? I have to at least dial it back a little. And I'm not even that I don't do that that often
anyways. Can we give him, I'm going to give him some a little bit of credit. I don't do that
anyways, but I don't want to do that in a lobby with other people that might be streaming
and they don't want to hear my horse shit. You need to do it more. Why else would they invite
you? Oh, come on. Come on. Like myth is running the event. He's got like a clipboard. He's like,
it's been a bunch of time planning this. And he comes over to our lobby and he's like,
what the fuck, man? Dermot's not making fucking sound effects. What that's what he's doing here.
What? Come on, man. You're supposed to be doing sound effects. No, I'm kidding. It'll be a good
time. I'm really looking forward to it. It should be a lot of fun. I'm going to say,
I might surprise a lot of you. I really might the wrong discord. It's because you try to seem
normal in front of the other streamers. That's not true. No, it's not. It's because you're a vegan
furry. Yeah, but I actually think it's going to be a lot of fun. Obviously myth reached out and it
was just cool. That's a really cool dude. Really, really funny guy. So I'm honored to be invited to
the first place. So I'm going to try to bring it my all. I'll bring it what I can. And by the way,
this has just been going in my head the whole time. I've not heard anything else and I'm sitting
there going, this sounds weird. It's just cats. It's just in sorcery. Well, now they're not there
anymore and you don't hear them. All right. So again, we're going to try to beat part two.
We're going to try. We're going to absolutely get to the end of part two. Sorcery part two today.
Black Ops 2 event tomorrow. It's going to be a wild time. I'm going to do my best. And then green
screen part two movie night is on Saturday. Very cool. You guys ready? Cast some sorceries already,
man. I'm going. I'm going. I wanted to talk about that. This is a cool event. I'm participating
in tomorrow. I'm going to talk about it. All right. So let's let's recap on what happened
yesterday. If you remember, for those of you that are vaude Andes, I would watch that first
because you're going to get a big spoiler here. We got to the gate, North Gate of Carr, which is
the end of part two. But all these animals are just talking over me. When you get to the end of
sorcery part two, if you haven't technically completed the game, it gives you an option,
gives you the choice to either just go on and say, fuck it, who cares, or be able to go back
and try to get the rest of the spell lines. And that's what we did. So we are still looking for
one more line. And it's down here where we have not been down here at all. We have to somehow
make our way from here down to here or make our way from here to here and restart it one more
time down here. Are you ready? The last thing we did, we went to the council meeting with Flanker.
There's nobody there for the council. Bro, play something normal. Play something normal? What do
you mean? We're playing Black Ops 2 tomorrow. That's pretty normal. All right, the docks.
I would call that a pretty normal video game, wouldn't you? No, Call of Duty is not like a...
What would you consider a normal game? That's a genuine question. What would you consider
a normal game? I played multiverses. Multiverses was a few days ago. Black Ops 3, Destiny 2.
I don't want to play those games. Phosphor 2 is normal. Yeah, what's so abnormal about this?
All right, so we're at the docks. You return to the docks. You still need to find somewhere to
stay for the night, which if you remember... Oh, it's still nighttime. We haven't gone to bed yet.
Sleep in an alley. Sleep by the river. Sleep in the market. Or the meet and cleaver had that
musical act. It was there, right? We could head over here. That's where the musicians were.
We met the band down here. We shook their hand and it was like, yeah, come hang out at the
meet and cleaver later. So let's do that. All games are normal games. You know what a normal...
Okay, an abnormal game would be like... I don't know. How many times can you do a backflip in a
row? That's kind of abnormal, right? If we're playing... That's like Mew, who can do more
backflips in a row? It's not like a normal game. How many times can you do backflips in a row?
I don't know. None? That's just gymnastics. Well, no, that would be abnormal for me to just turn
the camera on and do that. Like, hey guys, I'm going to play how many backflips can I do in a
row? It's like, what are you doing? This is like a video game. This is like just a normal game,
but like normal rules. That would be abnormal. That would be weird, right? So that's what...
What are you talking about? All right, let's go. Let's go. I'm not talking about abnormal
games versus normal games. All right. We're in the meet and cleaver. The meet and cleaver is
a small, grimy place. It looks like it's been converted from a wood store. Rats run across the
floor and the customers at the tables look haggard and tired, as if just smelling the air is draining
them. Damn. By the bar, a stooped and hunched innkeeper wipes his beer mugs with a filthy
handkerchief. All right, Jerry the musician's over here, which is the person we want to talk to.
So, I mean, we're going to go hang out with him, obviously. How many backflips can you actually do?
I used to be able to do one. I definitely can't do that anymore. You look for Jira, but eventually
it is he who spots you, waving from a particularly dark corner of the inn.
Come and sit with us. We've got food to share and company. Sit, but don't eat. Sit. Reject the offer.
Why would I reject the offer? This guy's been nothing but kind to me. Why would it be like,
no, fuck you. I'm going to sit. Thank you. You follow him to his table and sit down with three
others that you recognized from the performance at the fair earlier. Their table is spread with
delicacies, fried hill fox feet, curried ball eye beans, and a thin green plant in oil
that might be stewed grass. You eat greedily. So, how have you enjoyed your day in Carré?
This city is filthy. Jira looks at his friends and they all laugh.
It is, but it is no one's fault. Everyone who lives here generates just as much mess as everyone
else. One of the dancers, a tall thin woman with a thoughtful expression says,
the problem is the poverty. Everyone is so poor. There's no one poor enough to clean the streets.
Jira introduces his friend with a gesture. This is Almira. She's a dancer, but don't let that fool
you. She's a thoughtful soul, if ever there was one. Almira nods her head. The only choice is
poop water. Yeah, they're pumping poop water from the river and drinking it and pretending it's beer.
That's not good. All right, greetings. Almira smiles once and then turns back to her food.
Jira crunches on a battered skunk bear toe. So, are you staying here tonight? Yeah, for free. Yeah,
I go, yeah. And then I look at him and I kind of cock my head to the side. For free. I just look
at this guy. I'm like, for free. The guy's like, come on, man. He nods. You're a brave man. I don't
know many as would risk the beds at the heated reaver or whatever this place is called. The owner
makes good rat bone fritters, but he's a few giblets short of a casserole. A few giblets short
of a casserole. Where should I stay? The other inn isn't bad, though I hear that Vic tends to scoop
up the drunks. He nods meaningfully. Oh, Vic's a friend of mine. Oh, that's what happened. Okay.
Yeah, that's what happened last time. Well, then I won't drink. All right, let's get some info.
Who is he? Vic? I wouldn't say Vic was a good man to know. Or rather, there's many who know him
and wish they didn't. Vic's a bad man. Head of the slave ring and looking to be head of a lot more,
or so I hear. Almir agrees. They say he intends to overrun the council. That's impossible,
but if he's planning it, I suspect he has a trick up his sleeve. A kind of trick. I have no idea,
but Vic is a very clever man, indeed, and not afraid to work in league with sorceries and the
darker arts. Jura tries to lighten the tone, raising a toast with his mug. I need to find
a blind beggar. That's what I'm looking for. This is accurate, right? Maybe they know where he is.
We're looking for Theda. I need to find a blind beggar, one of the nobles. Jura looks blank.
You might find such a man somewhere in Kaare. You might find a hundred such. Hope you know what
your beggar looks like, because otherwise, how would you know you had the right one? It's late.
We should be going. Almir nods and takes his hand. Arm in arm, they bid you farewell and leave the
inn. All right. Am I sleeping here or am I going to go sleep outside somewhere? Do I sleep outside
or sleep in here? I feel like I want to get attacked in here or something. I'm going to
get attacked in here. Should I go sleep outside? All right. What is it? How much does it cost? I'm
going to get attacked. All right. You march over to the bar. The innkeeper stands up as straight
as he can to greet you. How is trade here? The man peers at you. Trade? This is a docks and I
sell beer. Trade is the same as it's always been. I know the city is supposed to be going to the
dogs and falling apart, but I don't believe it. People are always saying that, but they're still
in here most nights drinking their beer. I need food. How much is food? We're out of food, I'm
afraid. He points to a group in one corner. Bo's lot ate everything. Musicians. They're always
hungry, but good for drinking. Oh, no, I did eat. I already did eat. Never mind. I ate all the food.
I'm sitting here going, oh man, I'm hungry. I haven't eaten anything all day. Like I just ate.
I literally just ate all their food and I'm looking for more? I'm the problem. I'm one of
the musicians. I was part of their group. All right, what about a room? Do you have rooms? The
innkeeper nods and smiles a wide, almost wicked smile. We do. Best in Kare, if I say so myself.
People who stay here never stay anywhere is good again. Oh, gold pieces. Yeah, that's fucked up.
That's a weird way. Why would you? That's weird. That was a weird way to say that.
Should I just leave outside? I'm gonna sleep outside. I'm gonna go sleep in the water. Yeah,
I'm out of here. No, I don't know. I was specifically told not to stay here by the musicians.
They literally said don't stay here. He was like, hey, don't sleep there. This place is fucking
dump. Don't sleep there. I'm gonna listen to him. I'm not sleeping here. You walk back out to the
docks. All right. Back to the dock. You're running out of options. Sleep in an alley,
sit by the river or sleep in the market. All right. I don't know which one. I don't know
what you want to do. First poll of the night. One is sleep in alley, two is sit by the river,
and three is sleep in the market. I get to pull up right here. One, two or three. Where we going?
One is the alley, two is by the river, and three is in the market. I'm not sleeping in that end.
No, fuck that. What do you feel? By the river. By the river? Isn't that like out in the open?
I'm just gonna be lying on the beach in the open. Isn't that bad? You really want me to do that?
Okay. Carré is a renowned city as thieves and villains and has not earned that reputation for
nothing. To sleep outside is to invite disaster. Instead, you seat yourself by the edge of the fat
slug-like Fubaji River where the air is by turns fresh and stomach-turningly rancid, both of which
should help you to stay awake through the long watches of the night. Oh, I'm not gonna sleep.
Hey, you sit watching the river as it creeps past. Today has been a successful day.
You've made progress towards learning the lines of the Northgate spell. After a while, you notice
a light on the far bank. Oh, it's because I'm staying. I'm tanking the whole day. That's why.
Okay. Let's watch it. It is a lantern. For a while, it moves forward and backwards, then is
joined by several more. Voices call to one another. They're looking for escapers, but escaping from
what you cannot tell. As dawn breaks, one calls, Vic will be pleased. Clear night tonight. That
name again. Glandragor's friend. The men disappear as the sun begins to rise. Your long vigil has
left you tired out, but still in one piece. I got the health back. I got the health back.
I'm good. I'm good to go. All right, the next morning. As the sun breaks over the rooftops
of Lower Kare, the city looks clean and bright, like a stone polished to a shine by a fast-flowing
river. The effect lasts for a beautiful moment, and then the people of Kare begin to stir,
opening their windows to throw out their slop, shouting and cursing at each other as they do so.
The word slop. That's one of my favorite words. Can I just tell you? The word slop is just,
it has so much weight behind it. It can be used as an insult. It can be used as a means of
endearment, right? Oh, you're going to serve me this slop? That's not endearment. That's
fucking horrible. That's really insulting. It's only as an insult. Oh, hey, yeah. Give me some
of that. Imagine calling something slop at a dinner. Dude, what the fuck did you just call
my cooking? Oh, so what I have here is I have a pan-seared salmon. Yeah, I'm a big salmon guy.
And I have broccolini, very lightly torched to a nice crunch on the outside. Yeah, give me some
of that slop. That's so gross sounding. All right, whatever. It's only used as something gross or an
insult. Okay, the effect lasts for a beautiful moment, then the people come out. The city is
stirring again. Now we're going to head for the bridge. The market traders begin to set up their
stalls fighting and threatening each other to get the spots closest to the ships. A few sly types,
probably pickpockets, begin to prowl the shadows between the stands. Oh, well, real quick. Should
I play that new horror game that just came out? What's it called? Some of the Assistant or
something? Yeah, the Mortuary Assistant. Yeah. All right, no spoilers. I'm going to play it.
I'll play it like the next stream or two. Yeah. All right, I'll play it. You're going to die
playing that. I'll play it. It's really glitchy and buggy. Well, maybe it'll be fixed in the next,
like, I don't know. Maybe they'll do a patch for it. Yeah, we'll do that in the next few days.
Okay, cool. You can do the next parts of sorcery. Well, here's the thing, right? I want to make sure
that it's not just only sorcery, because it's been pretty much a focus for the last couple of weeks.
So we'll break it up. If you want to watch the sorcery stuff, it'll probably be there.
There'll be some more stuff in between. So, yeah. Look, I would. I don't care if there's, you know,
less viewers here or anything. That's fine. This is one of my favorite games of all time. I'll play
this all day, right? That's fine. I get it, too. If you don't want to, like, kind of sit here and,
like, chill, like, have, like, essentially read a book together. I get it. I do. But for those of
you that do like it, then we'll keep doing it. But for those of you that don't, then whatever.
Maybe we'll see you on the next one. It's all good. I don't care. If there's 5k, 10k, 30k,
whatever. People like different shit. That's fine. Let's keep going.
The market traders begin to set up their stalls, fighting and threatening each other to get the
spots closest to the ships. A few sly types pickpockets. I already read this. I should buy
breakfast. You wander the stalls looking for something to eat and find a stand selling
bomba bread for two gold pieces. The smell is quite nourishing. I definitely need it.
Ooh. All right. Okay. You buy a slice of the bread. It is pleasantly filling with a sweet,
meaty texture. You thank the woman at the stall and head over to the river to wait for the bridge
to be lowered. After a while, a grizzled old man arrives and unlocks a small booth by the harbor
bridge. He goes inside and closes the door behind him. Meaty bread? Yeah, it means when you pull it
open, you get the steam that comes out and it's really chunky and, like, fleshy on the inside.
I know what they're talking about. All right. Should we go knock on the booth? I'm going to
wait. You sit down outside the booth to wait for the man to lower the harbor bridge. After a while,
something happens. The old man leaves his booth and goes over to a contraption on the waterfront.
He begins to heave and wind an ancient winch. It seems to be quite hard work. He's trying to move
the whole weight of the bridge single-handedly. Can I go help? Excuse me. Let me help. That's the
way that Hannibal Lecter would describe meat. You get to your feet and go over to help the man out.
Get off. You'll break it. Okay. Don't help him. You let the man struggle, happy to let him be
stubborn. Sweat feeds on his forehead and he heaves and puffs as he works, but eventually the bridge
clunks down into place. You salute the man cheerfully and get to your feet. All right.
Cross the bridge. You cross the bridge over the Jojube River, which runs like a slime trail through
the center of the city. Oh, that's fucking gross. Andy Funny Voices. You said that wrong. Andy Funny
Voices. No, no, no, no, no. Excuse me. I gotta correct you. That's Funny Voice Andy. Andy Funny Voices.
You flipped it. You gotta get, come on, you gotta get it right. Funny Voice Andy. Come on. Andy
Funny Voices. I love that. That's my favorite comment of the week. That's so, I love that wording.
Time that person up for five seconds. You've reached the banks of Uppercare. The buildings
here are not as grand as on the south side of the river. They're in much better condition. Fewer
people live on this side away from the fields and the hills, but those that do are richer. They are
also most likely more dangerous. But of course, it is on this side of the city that the north gate
stands. You follow the road away from the river towards the fork in the road. Okay, we need to go
down here and I don't know if we can get there from here. I think it's impossible. Maybe it's not.
If we go here and then down, maybe. We'll try it. Yep, the sun is rising over the streets of Uppercare.
A few creatures roam this way and that unaware that they have walked these streets in just this
fashion once before. In one corner, a spring bubbles with fresh water. Oh, I remember this.
Drink it. You cup your hand in the water and drink a mouthful. It is fresh and invigorating
as though the water was enchanted. Okay, move on. We gotta go down. There we go. All right,
let's make our way down to the ruins. Where's the water coming from? I don't ask that question.
We don't ask that question. Got a lot of stamina now. You turn right heading away from the city
wall. A sign points towards Fireview Square. You pass large houses that are the aspect of official
places of business. One is marked with the clawed fist of a money lender. An elven woman is just
leaving. She looks quite worn out already this early in the morning. You stop the woman with a
gesture. She looks up at you in some surprise. Uh, you seem distraught. What's this building?
The woman looks at you in some surprise as though she thinks your question must be a joke.
It's a money lender. The why they call themselves that I don't know. She gulps back a sob. They've
turned you down. They're the worst kind of thieves. What happened? Did they turn you down? She looks
at you. Her narrow eyes wide. Oh, stranger. You have no idea. I'll help you. What do you need?
She pulls a face. You? Why would you do that? I cannot pay you. I'm sure you can guess. I'm an
adventurer. I help people. Perhaps you can help me. I don't know. What should I say? Well,
wait, maybe you know some, I just love the information, right? Perhaps you can help me.
I'm new to Kare. Is that so? Then maybe, maybe you'll need a guide. I don't want to guide.
I don't want to guide. I travel alone. I don't want to guide. It's a dangerous city full of traps.
A friendly hand wouldn't do you harm, would it? No, no, no, I don't trust anybody. I don't trust a
single person. I don't want guys. I don't want to get like clubbed. You know what I mean? It's like,
oh, yeah, come this way down this down this alley. And there's a guy I get fucking clubbed in the
back of the head by some fucking thief. I don't want to do that. That's happened to us like at
least once or twice so far. It's like, oh, yeah, I bumped into you and took like three items. All
right. I'll leave it up to you guys. What do you think? Do we want a guide? Do we want someone to
travel with us or no? So the poll will be one for yeah. Oh, well, we're doing it.
I didn't mean to do that. Very well. She smiles the first true smile you've seen in her face.
Very good stranger. I'll be happy to help you if I can for a fee. Where do you want to go? Oh,
oh shit. She actually might help. I need to find a beggar in the ruins. She nods. The falling
quarter. That's very easy to find if you can avoid the traps. She nods clearly pleased.
Take me there. I'll kill you. Like I pulled a sword out. I'm not going to right now. I got
threatened. We can't be this like psycho that starts a car. This has happened. This has happened.
My last place where I remember this is getting halfway through a conversation
and then throwing a rock at someone like, oh, yeah, I'm new in town. I'm the Annalander.
What's your name? Oh, I'm the great sage of the of the of the Western ruins. Oh, interesting. Can
you help me? Sword comes out sticking to their neck at their neck. Like what? Why start the
conversation if you're going to just threaten to kill somebody? Oh, yeah, like I'm enjoying my time.
We're having a good time around this campfire. I'm going to craft a fireball and just lob it
in the air above me and then run. Well, we know I'm going to we're going to do what we did.
And how much do you charge? She sizes you up for a moment. Four gold pieces. Half now, half later.
That's the way we do this. Half now, half later. I'll give you up. Fine. Half now, half later,
you suggest. The woman shrugs. That's fair. She holds out a palm and you give her two gold pieces.
She smiles. Very well then. She gestures down the street. Okay. What's your name? Before we begin,
tell me your name. You can call me Mesh. She nods. It's good to meet you, stranger. This way.
She heads off along the street. I'm telling you, we're going to get clubbed in the head.
You feel the round, painful edge of a bowling pin strike the back of your skull.
I'm going to get clubbed. The alley gets wider and passing a long building on the left,
which seems to be full of children. An orphanage, Mesh tells you, full of ne'er-do-wellers.
On the step, a lanky man sits with his eyes firmly closed. Wait, isn't this the area where the people
they open their eyes? We gotta get the fuck out of here, right? Yeah, isn't this the group of
people that have the fire eyes? Yeah, we're getting out of here. Ignore. Yeah, we got a place to be.
We have a guide that's already walking. If we stop, we're going to lose the guide. We're not
stopping. We're not stopping for anything, by the way. You're back on the approach to Fireview
Square. You see that? Mesh says, pointing to the monument at the center of the square with a curious
gleam in her eye. That's one of the great treasures of Carré. If you step inside,
you're granted a vision of the whole city from above, so you can see where you need to go.
Once again, you stand in the plaza of the red eyes, the heart of this half of the city port.
In all directions, roads lead off, some no doubt to the houses of nobles and others directly into
danger. On the other side of the square, the main road continues on through a low arch.
A thousand other alleyways lead off in all directions into upper Carré. Yeah, we're not
sticking around here. Lead on. We're not doing this. Yeah, I'm going to get teleported.
No, we're just going. Lead on. You gesture for your guide to lead the way.
Through here, she says, waving towards the arch at the far side of the square.
Right? Here it comes. Here comes the- I'm going to- Are you sure? You ask, surprised by the
direction. The woman smiles. Of course I'm sure. Do you want to find the beggar or don't you?
I don't know. I don't remember. I don't remember. What is this?
I forget what this is. What is this thing? What does this do to you? Follow. You follow your guide
through the archway. You follow Miche between the narrow buildings until you reach a fork.
To the left, the road continues towards- Oh, I thought it wanted me to stand in the middle
and get- I don't know. Okay. While the right leads to the shorter street.
In the center of the fork is a great bronze statue with some kind of pot at its speed.
I remember this. Oh my. Look at how much gold there is. She steps towards the statue.
No, no, no, no. Don't do that. No, no, no. Lead on. Lead on. Don't go over there. Don't go over
there. This thing, I made a goblin go try to take money from it and cut the goblin in half.
No, no, no, no. Don't. Lead on. Don't. Do not. Let's go, you say, waving to Miche to start walking.
Of course, she says. But you can see she's looking at the base of the statue where a pot sits,
containing several gold pieces. She begins to head down the road to the right.
This way to the beggar. Is she gonna die? Was that a different statue? Oh, but this can't be
good either. Follow her. You follow her. But then at the last possible moment, she dives to one side
and grabs an armful of gold from the bowl by the statue's foot. That'll teach those moneylenders
to not pay out. She cries, stuffing nearly 20 gold pieces into her pocket. Oh, god damn it.
From somewhere behind her, there is a noise like thunder of something moving into life.
Put the money back. Put it back. We were just kidding. Yep. Yep. Yep. It was a joke.
Look for the noise. I gotta draw the sword. We can't run quickly. Put the money back.
She's an idiot. Leave her. Abandon her. No, this is a new party member.
Run, run, run. Pray to the ape. I'm pulling the sword out. You draw your sword, expecting attack.
But Miche only laughs. That won't be much good, she says, pointing behind her at the statue.
The guardian of the gold, she shouts over the noise of hissing pistons and grating metal as
the statue steps forward. Why do you think I led you here? With that, she sticks a single gold
piece into your money pouch. The statue comes for the last person to thieve. Good luck. You'll need
it. She races away but turns in the mouth of the alleyway to shout something. Here comes the club.
Listen. It's got a weak spot on one of the legs, she calls back. And to find the beggar,
you need to go to the wasteland, but beware the mill. And she blows you a kiss and rushes away.
Well, we did get some info. Oh, am I always left? Okay, you don't have time to be angry.
Looking up, you see the statue's right arm sweeping down towards you. Leap left. You jump left,
straight into the path of the club. We got clubbed. Actually got fucking clubbed. It just took
like 12 minutes to happen. Which sends you flying backwards. Picking yourself up quickly,
you see the bronze giant has leapt from its pedestal and is advancing towards you. You adjust
the grip on your sword. You rush forward, dodging the statue's stamping foot. But when your blow
lands on the metal, it only sends a painful shockwave up your arm and does no damage to
the creature at all. The statue's leaning back for another swipe at you. You'll have to find
this thing's weak spot, if it has one, or else you do not stand a chance. One of the legs.
In the milliseconds available, you scour the creature for scratches, blemishes,
as anything that might suggest a chink in the armoring. Left leg, right? You said one of the
legs. Left leg? Left leg. You race forward towards the creature's left leg and spy a small metal
plate. Twisting your sword around in your hand, you drive it into the crack and begin to lever
the panel open. The giant flails this way and that, trying to shake you loose. But you are determined,
and finally the plate flies open. A blast of hot gas ejects from the statue. It sways and then
topples face down into the street. I'm alive. You gasp with relief and take a moment to recover
your breath. You've survived, but your elven guide has disappeared. Will all the statues money?
You see, we don't care about spelling, right? Who cares? It's with all the statues. Who cares?
I told you, it's 2022. Nobody gives a shit. I know what you were trying to say. I'll just
re-say it. It's fine. I don't care. Who cares? All right. So we've got to go down here. Back to the
house. Oh, okay. So we're going to go back to the house of Vlada and then chase the gnome, right?
And then go down. Side street. Could we get there from here too? No, we definitely have to go straight
down. Uh-huh. You follow the short street towards the building with a sign that says the gambling
halls of Vlada. Lots of creatures are going in and the place seems quite busy. There's a short queue
to get in. Yeah, we have to go in and we have to chase the gnome out the back. You join the queue
and after a few minutes, you are, you are allowed inside. Yeah, guys, I'm, I'm not, I'm not, I don't
want to go to the casino. I have to go through the casino. I got to walk through the casino
and out the back door. So, I mean, I could, maybe I'll set it up. Maybe I'll put a 20 bucks in a
machine or something and that's fine. I'm just trying to, but I'm not staying here. I'm just
getting, I'm going through it. Okay. Yeah. Okay. So here we go. I'm just walking through. Uh,
give her my gold. All right. I'm just, I'm just going to play for one game.
Those of you that missed yesterday's stream, this is a casino. Uh, it is the casino in the game. So
we're, uh, I, we played yesterday and I did okay, but wait a minute. I got to hold on.
Am I going to lose my money? All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait. I gotta, okay. Look at the tables
picking up. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. No, I can't, cause if, cause the gnome, right? No,
I don't want to do this. I'll play one game of the high wager. All right. We're going to play the,
we'll do one 10 gold bet and then we're out. Let's go. First the innkeeper. This is one,
it's 10 gold. Just one 10 gold bet. No matter. Okay. So I got, let's start with two, two threes.
No two. Uh, it's, I have literally everything. I have like a, we'll do one, two, two ones. Okay.
Three ones. That means he has to have to do four ones. Say it. Oh, you are in trouble. That means
you call it. There's no way you have three ones. I mean, see, we're just going to play. I'm going
to just sweep this guy and then we're going to get out of here. I got two, let's say two threes
because that's what I have. No two twos, two. All right. You've got two roof, two fours,
three fours. Now he's done. Call it. Thank you. You need 40 gold for that blacksmith sword.
I'll be close. Remember you're ruining this guy's family. I am not. It's look, we, that's not what's
happening. What do you mean? Why does the four confuse you so much? Because on a regular,
on a regular six sided die, the five looks like this. It has that kind of same pattern. So my
brain just keeps saying, this is a five because it's got that same, you know, the, in the middle off,
you know what I'm saying? It looks like a five on a regular six sided die. Okay. So you only,
he only has three guys. So I can really make this, I can put this guy in a lot of trouble.
I'm going to say two ones. No two twos. Let's really just ruin it. Two threes. Okay. I'm going
to say four. Let's do this because the chances of him having one of these are pretty high. Call it.
You definitely have one. You have to have one. Yeah. You definitely have one. Whatever. Oh,
oh really? One? I think there are two twos. Oh, well that's interesting. I think there are three
ones. Call it. Yeah. Sorry. That's a, that's a horrible, horrible hand to have against you.
You lose. Stupid. I'm just kidding. Damn. That's another good one. All right. So let's do
two twos again. Two threes. Fine. Hmm. How many, he has two die, which means he probably has one.
So if I, if I have to call this and it's wrong, right. Okay. So that's assuming that he's saying
that he has doubles, which no way. All right. All right. That, that was unlucky. One, three,
two threes. Don't call it. Yep. I win. All right. And then we cash out and then we get out of here.
Uh, there was one, one, one, one, two. I think that there, there's two twos. Two is probably
the only thing he has. Three twos. I'm sorry, buddy. What? Oh fuck. Wait a minute. I didn't,
I didn't know I had two twos. I thought I only had one. I thought I didn't know that was a two.
I didn't, my brain just didn't make that a two. I thought I only had one two. I have to call it.
Cause I mean, no, I got caught here. I just have to hope he doesn't have it. I could just bluff it,
but that's impossible. Cause he'd, he'd have to call it anyways. I got to see if he's bluffing.
No, he wasn't. I, that was my fault. I actually didn't, um, realize I had that.
All right. What do you got? One, one, one, three. I, I pretty much have guaranteed to win this too.
Yeah. I'm guaranteed there's not, when you have one die versus two die, you,
it's almost impossible to win. There we go. All right. 10 chips. Change. Get out. I'm done.
Cash it out. Cash out. Bang. 26. Okay. So wait, how do, how do I get to the ruins?
Down here and up? Okay. I'm not, I'm not fucking with the statue again. So I have to go,
how do I get over there? Could I go up and then this way? Let's find out up and left. I think.
Yeah. Uh, leave the square. Yeah. There we go. Okay. Cool. Let's go in the alley.
Do you like flour or corn tortillas? Well, that's a very loaded question because it depends on what's
in them. Corn tortillas are good for, uh, carne asada. I love like a carne asada and a corn
tortilla and fold it up nice and small. Pick it up. Just a flour tortilla is great for burritos.
Um, yeah. Okay. You choose a random alleyway on the right hand side of the square and slip
into the shadow between the tall buildings. The houses either side are well built and well defended.
There are iron railings on the windows and some even have arrow slits and portcullises. One
household has a dug, a moat across its front door. Outside one building, a tall man stands with a
grappling hook. Okay. You hang back and watch as he swings his grappling hook twice aiming for one
of the windows on the floor above. The hook misses and clatters to the street below and the man curses
before gathering up the rope for another try. Approach him. It's Batman. You stride over to
the man as he swings his hook once more. Greetings. You begin with a respectful nod. The man turns to
you. Stranger, I'm in a terrible fix. The man gathers the rope for another swing. He's clearly
tiring. Uh, what's the problem? I've been locked out. This is my home and I've lost my key but I've
got a terrible throw as you can probably see. The man throws again and misses again. Um, where'd you
get the grappling hook? How would you believe it? I found it near an old well in the wasteland.
I was wandering about there feeling sorry for myself and I chanced across it. Bullshit. You a
thief? Are you a guard? Answer the question. You reply coolly. Listen, if I were a thief,
do you not suppose I would be better at getting this accursed thing to land on the sill?
To demonstrate his point, he swings again with considerable effort and once more misses,
ducking to one side to avoid the look at he as the ducking to avoid the hook as it falls back.
The man gives up. He winds up the rope around his shoulder and then cups his hand to his mouth.
Ask me, will you just open the door and let me in? For a moment, nothing happens. Then a bucket of
slop is thrown out over the man. He stands dripping in muck. Who is that? You ask from a safe distance
away. Take my advice, stranger. Never marry an elephant. They may have lovely eyes. They are
thoroughly untrustworthy. He stalks away up the alley. Time for you to move. Well, we failed that,
whatever that was. Okay, along the alley. Well, I don't know, the guy's out there with a grappling
hook thrown at random windows. But am I going to trust this guy? Hey, yes, let me see that. I'll do
it. And then I go, shoot the grappling hook out into the window, break the window and the guards
come and club me in the back of the fucking head. We've seen that song and dance too many times.
The street is falling into disrepair around you. Something has blighted this region of the city.
Even the trees and the gardens behind the mansions have turned black where they stand.
The only greenery is the moss on the stone walls. There are no rats scurrying underfoot
and only spiders roost in the rooftops. You pass a particularly grand house. It's doors locked with
a heavy iron chain. Look at it. There is a metal S bolted beneath one gable. Perhaps it's an owner's
mark. Perhaps it is there to stop the wall falling out onto the street. There's a ringing noise from
down the alley. A hooded creature with a bell around his neck is approaching in shuffling steps.
Oh boy. We could open, we could open the door. Doc? Oh no, I don't have any more. There's always Jig.
But we don't know what this is. I could do Sos. Why is it lowercase and uppercase? There's the
different spells. So capital D-O-P is open doors, but lowercase D-O-C, like lowercase D is um,
a different spell. I don't know. It's a spell. Who knows? Uh, it's either Jig or Sos. Let's do Sos.
Or Sap. Sos is probably better. Because what if it's not a danger?
Sense danger. You cast a spell and a calm voice enters your mind. It tells you that the house
before you is empty of anything important, even of ghosts, but that the creature approaching is
quite deadly and the voice fades away. Um, you want to scurry into the house? I could do another one.
You cast the spell pulling out your little flute and playing a merry tune. The figure in the cloak
stops suddenly and then in awkward and painful steps begins to dance. The sight is macabre
and cruel. And you hear the creature wheezing with the effort of every movement. Oh no,
this is like bad. Keep playing? It said that the creature was deadly. Does that mean that
they were going to attack or they're just actually, I don't know. Keep playing? You show no mercy.
Continuing the spell until the creature is quite exhausted, it begins to scream in a human voice
from its terrible injuries. When the enchantment finally fades, the creature can barely find the
strength to crawl away. The creature with the bell around its neck passes you without looking
up and shuffles away. Okay. But Suss said that the creature was dangerous. Open the door? Do it
again. It doesn't cost anything. You cast the spell pulling out your little flute and playing
a merry tune. The sound is cheery on the desolate street. Nothing more occurs. Now the creature's
gone. Let's go to the house. The door to the house is locked with a heavy padlock chain. You can try
to pry it open with the tip of your sword, but achieve nothing. Let's dop it open. Open locks
and doors. You cast the spell over the heavy chain and it tumbles to the ground and to the house.
You slip through the wide doors into the old empty house, an empty mansion. You push open the doors
and step inside the dark house. It is a mansion on a grand scale, larger even than the abandoned
house you explored on the lower side of Carré. There are at least three floors and two great
doors leading off to wings on either side of the entrance hall. From the back of the house comes
a voice. The Lord is not home. I know. That's why I'm here. I know. The figure shambles forward,
resolving itself out of the darkness into a tall ogre wearing the livery of a manservant.
His eyes are tightly closed. Lord Shinva is not at home. Please leave. Lord Shinva is dead.
Yeah, Sus said there wasn't anybody in here. Lord Shinva is dead, isn't he? Indeed. He will not be
returning for some time. Returning? Is he not dead? Not so dead that he might not yet be revived,
but I hold out very little hope. My service will continue regardless, of course. As he speaks,
you notice a flash of metal from his neck, some kind of collar made of a strange dull colored
metal, and the collar is covered up by his shirt. I must now ask you to step outside,
gesturing towards the door. Should I just try? What do I do? I don't know. What do I do about it?
Push past? Push past the creature. You elbow past the creature, meaning to explore the house.
In return, the creature opens his eyes, and a searing red flash burns your arm.
I regret to inform you that I am part red-eye. Then he grabs you by the burnt arm and hauls you
out of the house onto the street. The creature with the bell has gone. A narrow alley opens up
to your left, slipping between the buildings. God damn it. That's bullshit. Rewind. Rewind.
I can't. Dude, just start killing everybody. No, I can't just kill everybody. Remember Corga?
Corga hated us. Um, I'm gonna go down this way, because we didn't explore this. I wonder,
I wonder where the beggar would be. Down here, maybe? Who cares about Corga? I don't know. Um,
I'll stay on the road. The buildings are thinning out, through a gap between roofs you can make out
a tall, crooked steeple some way away, like a finger pointing up towards the heavens. A dark
shape sits at its very tip. As you watch, the shape seems to grow wide, then flatten once more,
as though it had opened and closed. A bird, perhaps? Or simply a flag, draping downwards
in the still air. Okay, we're looking for theta. We need the spell line. Once again, you're
emerging from the alley into a wide area of wasteland. Once, this was a busy city district,
but now it looks as though a hurricane has leveled it. Nothing stands higher than head height. A few
staircases lead to nowhere, and in some places a door still stands. Plants grow from every crevice
and crack as though someone had poured green paint over the whole scene. Things are constantly
moving and shuffling between the leaves. The road, such as it is, is quickly smothered by
piles of wreckage. There are lots of other ways to pick your way through. One possible route leads
up and over the side of a broken down house. Another passes by what might have once been a mill.
You would have to climb over the mill wheel to continue this way. We were told to avoid the mill.
Didn't somebody say, don't go near the mill? That was the guide, right? Yeah, they said,
go to the mill. Did they lie? Yeah, while she was running away she was like, don't go to the mill,
you're gonna get fucked up. Something like that. Look at the broken house. The house has been sliced
like a many layered cake, showing the floors that were once inside. Opened rooms have been
stripped of their color by the wind and light, and of their possessions by a decade or more
of scavengers. But there's still hints that this place was once a family home. The hooks in the
ceiling above the hearth, the marks notched on a ground floor pillar, that suggest the height of a
growing child. Children. Height of growing children. I'm gonna climb the house. Look at the mill.
Who would build a mill out here so far from the river? Still, there is a gigantic mill wheel
lying on its side in the path. Despite the state that the building next to it is in, the wheel
itself seems perfectly intact and has not even lost its perfect circular shape. Um, we were
specifically told to avoid the mill. So, um, oh it's a portal trap! That's right! That's right,
a perfect circle on the ground. Climb the broken house. You clamor up the fallen rubble to the
roof of the broken building. From here you get a clear view across the rest of the wasteland.
It stretches for a mile or two and will take about an hour to cross on foot. And at its far side,
a tall iron fence thick with ivy slices across the land. Perhaps to keep the people of the
wasteland out, or to keep whatever is beyond the fence in. In the distance you see dark shapes
moving across the sky. Climb down the other side of the house. You make your way down the far side
of the building and look back onto the path, which soon forks. All right, this is actually
really important because I don't know where this with where this person is. Lord Theda is in the
ruins. Lord Theda can be found blind and begging in the ruins of the fallen quarter of the city.
He's a beggar. I don't know, just said he's in the ruins. Does anybody, nobody told us where.
He could be anywhere. Let's try right. Okay, you follow the path to the right between broken
foundations and cracked streets. On one side a roof sticks half out of a sand dune. On the other,
front door lies flat on the ground as though leading to a hidden cellar. Then the path comes
to a building that amidst all this destruction is still standing. Its door is closed and its
stone walls seem completely intact. You try the door and find that it falls open at the slightest
touch. Go in the house. You might be in the house. The house consists of a single room with a large
table and a large chair and in the far corner a sealed box. Everything seems in good repair.
The wood looks waxed and polished and the hinges on the box are free of rust. Is it a mimic chest?
I don't know. From the doorway you stop and look around and that's when you notice the
foot sticking out from under the table. Look at the foot. You go over to look at the foot.
It is clawed and a dull shade of gray green. It is about the size of your head and sticks out from
under the low table. This house feels dead. Even the air inside seems not to move. Did I just kick
the foot? All right, I'm gonna, I'm gonna fraud the foot. Reaching forward with the walking cane
you found in the house. The one opportunity to use the cane is here. I take the cane out and go
poke poke. That's the only thing the cane has been used for. Nothing happens. All right, poke it again.
Feeling more confident now? You brought it once more. Still nothing. Seems like this creature is
either very asleep or very dead. Okay, go for the box. No longer concerned about the creature,
you head over to the box and lift the lid. Inside are a series of small round stones.
Carefully carved. Lift out a stone. You pick out one of the stones at random and lift it from the
box. It isn't heavy but it is exquisitely smooth. Not quite round with a dimple at the top and a
deeper pit near the top. In fact, you realize as you turn it over in your hand it is carved in the
shape of an apple. Looking in the box you see other carved food stuffs. Apples, bread rolls,
goat's cheese, a ham. Each has been almost perfectly chiseled into a shape. This is the
kit at the fair. You search through the box hoping to find something of value or else something to
explain the purpose of the collection but you discover nothing more. Turning away your eyes
fall on the other side of the table where the head of the creature lies. The face is clearly
stoned. The eyes are stone. The open mouth is stone. It is a statue of a spin or else it once
was a spin. In its hand you see it holds a stone shovel. You peer at the shovel. It is a wide blade.
Good for heavy digging. This creature was a gardener, perhaps or a farmer, or more likely given his
lonely outpost near the necropolis, the city gravedigger. But now he is solid stone. Such
things are not impossible. Perhaps he buried a wizard's lover. A day too soon, perhaps.
You step back outside into the dying sunlight. Interesting. I wonder what you could do there.
You make your way between blasted walls and weed encrusted rubble. There is a constant movement in
the corner of your eyes. Rats scurrying to hide under the stones and the cracks. The path turns
around a large stone fountain which has toppled over on one side revealing an empty well
leading down into the earth. We don't- I don't want to go in the sewer. Move on. I'm not going
in the sewer. All right the edge of the wasteland. Did we miss it? Oh hold on. After a while another
path joins this one. Looking back along it you see a toppled steeple. A track climbs the rise at your
back towards a low hovel. This is the far end of the wasteland ahead you make out a line of tall
dark trees. Okay I'm gonna say the hovel. So hey do all your jokes come from this game? I'd say like
maybe 10% of all the jokes I've ever made. Maybe maybe like seven maybe seven percent of everything
I've ever said has been directly from the text of this game. No maybe like four percent of everything
I've ever said. Such as? I don't know. I made it up. I don't know. It's not even true. All right you
climb the rise towards the hovel. It is merely a tent pitched into clearing. Guy ropes held down
by rubble. You stand and hold your breath but you hear nothing from inside. Perhaps it is unoccupied.
Certainly it can't contain much. It's going. Aha! Did we find him? You step into the shade of the
tiny hovel and your eyes widen. The room inside is lined floor to ceiling with trinkets, knickknacks,
brick-a-brack, and other miscellaneous stuff. Some is piled up on the shelves. Some hang from the
ceiling. Even more lean against the walls. There are weapons, pottery, jewelry, domestic objects,
magical items, and so on. Oh it's not the right person. Who is this? Sitting cross-legged on the
floor in the midst of all this mess is a small bearded gnome who rubs his hands and greets you
as you come in. I have come to rob you. You know what? You know what I'm saying? Should I? I've come
to rob you. I've come to rob you. You announce. Amazed that no one has done it already since he
lives out here clearly undefended. Very well. As you can see I can't stop you. But you wouldn't
rather trade. I'll trade your life for what you own. Trade would be acceptable. Imagine like hey
this is a stick-up this is a robbery oh but I mean we could trade too yeah yeah you know that's
works I I'm more into that you're right yeah that's acceptable to me taking mercy on the
tiny scrawny creature oh good I'm very glad to hear that as you might imagine he pats the ground
beside him let's see if we can do a little bartering as you can probably tell I have no
interest in money the gnome gestures around his little room there's clearly a lot to choose from
but the items which stand out are a pot of beeswax a bag of goblin's teeth and a compass
whose needle quivers in a direction which is close to but not actually north what would you
like no mast I don't want any more teeth what's the compass it's not a normal compass instead
it'll point you to where it thinks you need to go I'm afraid it has a mind of its own and it isn't
always correct and it probably won't work in the countryside outside of Kare either so I'd understand
if you don't want it um well we're but we're like on our way out of Kare it's Jack Sparrow's compass
it's not that's not gonna do anything honestly it's not gonna work I don't need any more teeth
I could use the beeswax he said it's not gonna work outside Kare we're at the end of our Kare
journey very soon here teeth or we riot you could be lying all right I'll take the compass
sounds intriguing you reply not putting the compass down anything else um do I have beeswax
oh no okay I have beeswax yeah guys I have eight goblin teeth I don't need any more um no that's
enough you say standing back all done very good you took one of mine so I've taken one thing of
yours I'm very quick you probably didn't notice me doing it good day the gnome gestures towards
the door for you to leave wait what did he take what did you take the gnome looks surprised well
really I have no idea I'm a kleptomaniac that should be fairly obvious and what's more I couldn't
see into your pack when I was taking it could I but I'm very fair and I took exactly the right
amount of things so we're all square what did he take what did he take am I missing something
skull cap wig bone sun jewel badge of the noble 26 gold tinderbox walking cane what did I what
did he take he took the chain he took the silver chain he took the flute no he took the chain he
took my silver chain a magical silver chain that acts like a snake for a fucking dumb ass broken
I'm attacking this guy give me my stuff I'm sorry that's really quite impossible
I don't know where I put it or what it is you should be pleased with what you stole from me
and be on your way oh that's why he's got all this shit because he didn't he doesn't even know what
it is take something I just start grabbing stuff no no no no no no that's not I actually probably
should get out of here because if I take something if I just start grabbing shit he's going to grab
stuff from me and be like well you took something of mine so I took something of yours I wonder if
should I just attack him threaten him give me my things or I'll squeeze you to death for a moment
you seem to see something move in the corner of your eye look here I can't help it and in all this
talking about it I've gone and stolen something else from you so really I do advise you to just
leave kill this might kill him you give into your worst intentions and strangle the gnome where
he stands but with him dead you'll never find your property you search of the you do a search
of the hut but nothing turns up while all the time outside the sun is setting eventually you
give and you head out of the hubble you return back along the path what the fuck hold on what
else did I just strangled him to death what did he take oh he took the wig no I need that
I genuinely need that wig I need it I genuinely need that that's the thing that lets me talk to
animals are you not gonna let me rewind that well and by the way why did I put my hands around his
neck I strangled him to death why wouldn't I just kill him with my sword why would I choke him to
death and put my bare hands around his neck and squeeze him to wait did I say that I did say that
didn't I give me my things or I'll squeeze you to death why was I in the mood to strangle someone
I have swords and magical spells and why I don't need to strangle someone there's no reason for
this I have magic I have lightning bolts and I run a poll can I rewind and just fuck this place
and literally just not even go in here it's got to be at least 75% yes can I rewind or do we lose
two items for no reason you have to live with my decision it's got to be at least 75% that's what
you get it's a free rewind I know re-winding is I know it's polarizing I know right do you live
with your decisions and just take it as the game goes or do you no no no my finger was still there
so I could still do it I think there's an equal amount of both that make the game fun right because
there's been a lot of cases where I have not rewound it's like no we gotta fucking live with
that it is fun though to play this game uh and you have to live with every decision although
it's really hard to win I will say it's very difficult to win the game without doing it all
right let's go back uh we're just should I do what I did to get the compass and he takes the
chain right wait wait it might be random though maybe I just don't even do this what is I'm gonna
leave I'm not going in here no don't even bother okay uh we're going to the steeple chat's a bunch
of rewind Andes hey by the way we got him this is definitely him you make your way through the
wasteland towards the church most of the building is in ruins but a tall steeple still reaches for
the sky circling the steeple are two dark shapes that look like enormous birds at the foot of the
church a man dressed in rags is curled up asleep look at him you stop and peer down to look at him
could this be theta the blind beggar that you were told to find his face is curiously familiar
you've definitely seen it somewhere before since you arrived in care although you have not seen
any other beggars as filthy and smelly as this one is this the guy from the very beginning we
could have killed this person from in the beginning thomas yeah well I think we could have actually
killed this guy uh let's wake him you reach down and wake him gently at first he doesn't respond
and you wonder if you are too late but then he sits up sharply who's there I'm under attack I'm
under attack he rubs his eyes then reaches out with a dirty fingertip to your face um all right
let's take let's take it let's take it slow one voice andy no sorry it's andy one voice get it
right or don't even say it um wait wait okay well should I give him something introduce myself
greetings you say the beggar groans and grumbles what did you wake me for I can see in my dreams
you know I maybe that joke from the first game for the first time you played I'd rather stay there
you are theta noble of care do I jump this on him immediately you are theta noble of care
you round on the beggar you are theta seventh noble of care are you not the man looks absolutely
terrified by the accusation he begins to curl up around himself and scream it seems quite a
strong reaction then you see he is not looking at you but past you oh shit look up you turn
your attention skywards to see the two dark shapes are hurtling downwards beating wide leathery wings
they're the creatures you saw flying around the steeple god cursed harpies they come for me every
time every coin I get every apple every stinking crust of bread they come and they take it from me
what did I do to deserve such torment step in front of the beggar you push the beggar back and
stare up into the sky terrifying looking the harpies are screaming down towards him ugly
dark-skinned creatures with sharp talons and their arms and legs coming to tear out what's
left of his let's go okay this is important I don't have a pebble shield can I do cats
what would cats do I could do giant giant would help gob we got I got plenty of goblin teeth
I got eight of these let's get a goblin friend you toss a goblin's tooth into the ground and
cast the spell a plume of smoke forms and then moment later a goblin warrior stands in front of
you the beggar begins to shriek and scrabble back through the dust no what why would it do
turn the goblin on the harpies you turn the goblin about to attack the harpies the short
creature jumps up and down trying to stab the flying monsters but they cackle and laugh before
one finally snatches your little warrior into the air they lift him high well above the ruined
steeple then let go thankfully the enchantment that has created him breaks before his body hits
the ground and he simply vanishes in mid-air they're so fucking useless you know what gob
is really good to test stuff right you go first sending a goblin into a room and they just get
like instantly killed by a trap and then you just walk around it that's we've done that a few times
uh there's such dog shit though this is so bad at everything else all right they come
screaming for your neck uh they only got five stamina though so I'm gonna go full blaster
got it it flexes its long talons as it turns in the air once more it's still fighting all right
I gotta hold back I think you think he'll go more than five yeah he will oh come what the
fuck was that 0.1 look out they never give up these harpies they never give up full blast
oh that's fucking that's awful that's truly bad I might have to do I'm gonna do it again
that's actually terrible the beggar holds onto his hat as his head and the creature swoops low fuck
I'm dead oh my god this stupid thing it's over it's still defending I oh I can't hit it okay
we're gonna do 5.0 fuck you we're going full blast 6.5 one damage this is so stupid because
they're in the air I should have just thrown a goddamn grenade in the air definitely coming in
hard yeah okay now I'm gonna do light because this you don't have enough stamina to do anything
we're gonna do two point we're gonna 3.0 you got to be fucking kidding me huh it's gonna okay it's
gonna defend it circles out of reach defend again it flies up to the roof of the old building okay
defend again it wheels high into the air screaming to the other what what the fuck I thought it was
high in the air I didn't know he was down what it said he was goes high into the air
the harpy's eyes are on fire yeah come in 6.5 that's a huge that's a huge hit huge huge hit
it's gonna go for another strike fine do it 2.8 I swear to god man all right fuck you we've got one
what's happening demands the beggar but you order him to silence as an opening appears you cut a
side blow the harpy hits the ground it is a huge creature as big as a bear but the savage light in
its eyes has gone dark the beggar darts forward to jab it with his stick but there's no time for
celebration the second creature is already searing down from the sky oh god damn it this is such a
this the ape thank god for the ape this one has a much bigger stamina pool I gotta defend yep that
was a good play don't let him get you yeah thanks okay you just used a whole bar I'm gonna go like
the creature hovers just a little out of reach this is a defense scenario right or just a little bit
like 1.2.0 okay it wheels up and turns about ready to strike look out he's going for your head
eight got him okay now we pull back because he's coming in with like probably like a five or six
I could have done it but sorry I got a bigger stamina pool now it hangs in the air a short way
back claws grasping what do you think all in 5.7 got it two come on it's gonna drop down
defend I that was the right play all right now we go all in I get the kill writer
got it thank god that was a lot suddenly you reach out you cleave the air with your blade with a
final turn through the air the harpy barrels over then tumbles striking the side of the church as
it hits the ground a wall collapses and the creature is buried beneath a slide of masonry
the beggar cheers it begins to dance all right well I'm glad we got a goblin like just like
snatched up and dropped the beggar creeps out from his hiding place and thanks you two or three
times over give him back his badge wait what this is his badge the one that we got from the I don't
know where we got this but this is his badge uh I okay I forgot we had this you got it in that
hidden room from the mansion oh yeah it was it was his house right all right here take your badge
I have something of yours you dig into your pack while theta waits caulking his head and listening
to the sound of you rummaging through your things finally you produce the badge and place it into
his hand he smiles as he accepts it my stranger thank you but he feels over the surface trying
to work out the shape then suddenly he drops it as though it were scolding hot that's not mine
not anymore I wish I'd never taken it in the first place I won't take it again he kicks at the badge
and skitters away into the debris of the fallen church talk to him lord theta I'd like to talk
to you that is my name I don't deny it I'll talk to you I'll talk to you happily ever since the
blindness struck me down I've been tormented by those demons and now they're dead you've saved me
or as much as I can be saved that's his cane dude we are ready for this conversation by the way
this is the most prepared I think I've ever been for this conversation give him his walking cane
here I have something for you you take his outstretched hand and place the walking cane
into his grip his fingers find its familiar shape and he leans quickly onto it with a sigh
my old friend this saw me through the worst times when my eyes were failing I hardly need it now of
course to demonstrate he spins around on the spot gets his legs into a tangle and sits down
sharply laughing but thank you stranger you are indeed kind the beggar shivers against a sudden
breath of cold the afternoon is waning evening is approaching already days are growing shorter
it's like that here near the backlands tell me your spell line for the gate just cut right to
the chase that was a willy wonka moment tell me your spell line for the gate please happily
I'm glad to be rid of it it was uh no my memory is not as good as it was let me see it was uh
he racks his brain thinking for all he is worth shit um hit him no I'm gonna wait I'm gonna wait
wait wait got it by corgas grace and something's pride oh but I can't remember where the something
was I'm starving I'm so hungry but you have no food you could offer him oh come on dude try to
remember the rest of the line he shakes his head it's gone I fear it's gone like my sight
it was the name of a god one of the old gods the god of pride no less and maybe you can find out
elsewhere you could ask corga the god of grace for his health he lives in a temple that way
he waves roughly northwards shit corga is not going to be happy that you killed the gnome
wait I did does that still count that doesn't still count right I have I killed anybody no be
let's be honest I strangled a gnome I did I strangled the gnome with my bare hands and then
cut off his wimp height until he died but we rewound that have I killed anybody in this play
through here I killed the council guards fuck no but was that in defense no that was flanker
went in and I went into no I need to feed I have to feed him I need to defeat him where can I get
food do I have that part of the line already that's a good question I don't I don't have it
we'll hold on we'll see at the end of this conversation tell me the order of the lines
the order of the spell lines do you know it no no idea although I know my line came first
okay tell me about corga corga sees all and knows all suddenly the beggar grips your wrist
and squeezes what you risk your life if you talk to him remember please the left eye that's how
you start the left eye what happened to your eyes you take a moment to show some sympathy what
happened to your eyes a black eye curse and I know who cursed me it was sansis once he was a good
ruler fair and honest he ruled kare like a kind father looking after a cherished daughter nothing
was too much effort but he began to fear his other counselors he thought we were plotting against
him ready to overthrow him were you mulas was as soon as sansis gave mulas one of the spell lines
he wanted them all he wanted them for himself if he could hold the city to ransom mulas used to
be a blackmailer while I was loyal and sansis repaid me like this he was weeping you curse the
beggar for his useless half-help then you look to the track ahead and take your leave of him
your clues have been updated god damn it I just needed to have food where can I get food I need
to buy food where can I get food I need to rewind to get food corga's not gonna help me I kill
somebody in this rewind god damn it check the sewer check your notes on the spell order where is it
corgas grace wait I know it I know it I know it I know it I already know it corgas grace
no you don't he gave you that part what did he do why did he not give me
like corgas grace and someone's pride shit who's pride who's pride the god of pride is who we need
to find out who the god of pride is shit oh no is it can we get it here corga no corga's not the
god of pride corgas the god of grace you need to get it from corga could I ask someone ask the
dead noble in the crypt uh let's try that let's try that over here right the fence is a slang
shit fuck doesn't know damn it we're so close I need literally one word to complete it I've
I've never completed this the path ends at a tall and ancient iron fence overgrown with weeds
through the dense leaves you can make out a wide area dotted with stones and small buildings and
straight somber trees it's an acropolis of mausoleums and tombs slang's the god of malice
maybe check the tombstones yeah that's right there are nobles buried here all right I'm
gonna uh let's cast spill wait I look at my health try the sewers what is big big is one
stamina is anything free zip it's not free what parts do you have I have everything besides the
name of the god of pride that's the only thing I don't know uh hopefully this doesn't kill me
I'm gonna climb it you test the ivy seems tightly wound about the railings wedging one toe between
the metal bars you grip the cords of the plant and haul your way up and the second foot is up
and you are climbing so you can feel the plant tearing under your hands keep on ow you keep
going hoping that if you move quickly you will clear the fence before the ivy comes away you
don't manage it near the very top you feel the sap leaking between your fingers as the cords of the
plant snap then you fall painfully back onto the rubble strewn ground however all is not lost where
the plant has torn away from the fence a foxhole has been revealed leading underneath the fence
something a rat perhaps scurries through the fence and back into the wasteland
all right we're going to the hole you kneel down and wriggle your way into the foxhole
it is so narrow that you have to keep your arms out in front of you and drag your pack along
behind but thankfully it is short coming up on the other side of the fence less than two strides
away you pull yourself up from a hole in the ground into the graveyard all right where's the
i need food i need to heal do i have do i have nothing
fuck try corga again last time they answered you still they just didn't bless you i remember him
standing up and saying um i'm going to destroy you how dare you take a life of somebody i'm going to
kill you how dare you okay you're once again standing in the city necropolis in the shadow
of the ewes and gravestones okay the sun is setting behind the wall look around the gravestones is
there anything we didn't get here you step nervously off the path and walk between the
nearest tombs somewhere ancient headstones tilt to the crazy angles others are fresh neatly carved
okay we were here we were here is anything here wait grave goods shit all right oldest grave
lorag all right no we lorag doesn't know we already talked to lorag don't argue with corga
look elsewhere we just need the god's name you were rude to him last time somebody said there
are two ways to get the final part of the spell line the second way is a bit eccentric
i love how you put that that's great it's a little eccentric go to corga you don't need
the corgas blessing all right we'll go to corga let's go to corga okay you return to the path
beside the is it his the well all right wait is it is there food in here pull up the bucket
yes drink it thank god thank god i'm so happy because it on like you can rewind right but if
you have one hp one hp one hp throughout all of your rewinds you're kind of just screwed all
right we're gonna we're gonna go talk to corga again we'll see if he says anything different
okay here we go up to corga you will not get the line from corga you need to go into the sewer
should i go in to the sewer is that the way it's all right all right okay i'm going is going to
sewer all right we're going in we're going in we're going in we're going in sewers the way to do it
we're going in there probably is another way but look down yeah the wells lead to the sewer i hope
you're not lying to me throw a coin in can i not climb in this way this is the rise is not it
throw a coin in stop throwing coins in how many coins is what i have to throw in here
throw how many coins do i have to throw this is what's happening back it up back it up i
thought i could go in this one i can't go in this one i can't go in this one i can't go in this one
drink from the bucket and let's move on okay corga oh god you walk for half an hour through thick
trees along a narrowing track until you reach a fork in the road to the left the track gets narrower
to the right a massive shadow looms yep okay so this we've been through here before we're gonna
make a move so wait wouldn't stepping in the circle in corgas thing is a teleport trap and
it puts me into the sewer doesn't it yep that's what we're doing uh okay let's make a move no no
no what okay look for an opening uh oh yeah we pay we pay the gargoyle right drop in a gold piece
and look into the eyes and we get health yep very good climb up uh we're gonna do cast spell
we're gonna probably gonna do big because or should we do float big works float works
they're they're all they're all ones dammit yep we scale it scale it scale it halfway up here
we are look at the view it's beautiful up here walk around to the north face look at that isn't
that cool watch the torches they're going crazy climb higher okay here we go i'm just literally
gonna walk in i'm gonna give the double middle finger to corga i'm gonna say hey fucking suck
my ass and then i'm gonna fucking leave i'm gonna walk directly into the trap i'm gonna make him so
angry i'm gonna be like hey fuck you you're a piece of shit piece of shit piece of shit piece
of shit piece and then step right in the circle he's gonna be like oh why did i turn that on i
should have kept it off yeah we're gonna follow me i could learn another spell too right should i go
learn another spell that would work wouldn't it i get another chance to learn a second one yeah why
not let's do that before i um before i get out of here uh let's create a new spell for people that
didn't see yesterday's dream i'm sorry i'm kind of blowing through this but uh we did already do
all of this very slowly and very methodically so um if you haven't caught up yet i suggest you do
look to the stars you're a mage and not a mere sorcerer who knows what spell you could weave
at a spot like this it's the best place in the city let's try to make a new spell we did purr
last time which is summon a thousand cats tack is really good tar uh puke puke exists
luck i'm imagining luck is probably a good one too black is really good i think we can just
create whatever do tack tack what's litter luck lure tack is the best you should do tack please
tack all right let's do tack you fashion the stars into alignment and an enchantment is created
you feel a tingling sensation in your wrist and you look down to see flashing sparks in your palm
that flicker different colors for a moment gold then white then black um close my fist
you flex your fingers ready to grip the sparks which begin to flash faster and faster perhaps
the shade of the spark is important will you grab a certain color or trust to chance i don't know
gold just grab gold black is gold gonna give me money just grab gigachad um i need to pull
because i i genuinely don't know which one of these i'm gonna do uh one two or three i could
not make a decision if i wanted to yeah one is uh wait for the black spark two is wait for the
gold spark three is just grab whatever it looks like it's gonna be just grab so you want me just
to close my eyes and just gigachad who cares okay why would you guys do this right this is
not my decision so if i explode when i do this then it's not my fault all right just grab you
have no way of knowing the spell how the spell will last so you waste no time you close your
fist tight the sparks are hot in your palm but the pain fades quickly and when you reopen your fist
you found that you are now holding a wooden face mask of black wood the sparks in the spell
itself are gone you found one of the secret spells of the temple of corga the icy wind
chills you to the bone that is a new spell that i can do that's fear right where is it it's gack
isn't it fog mud niftel yak terrible fear within another's mind brave creatures will suffer a cold
sweat while cowardly ones will be reduced to powering jelly gack well i love y'all but i'm
so glad we have so many opportunities to use it go use it on the gnome all right it's time
then head back down and just go right in try to steal something what is tack though what does
that do is tack on there now uh no it's not because it's not known it's an unknown it's not my spell
book it generates one of five magical items that's awesome okay here we are seems that
this is the ziggurat of corga the gracious go inside oh shit i forgot about the snake
i forgot about the snake no you dick oh my god rewind i forgot about the snake get out of here
minus four minus four minus four full blast again kill him kill him kill him we cheat
we cheat we cheat we cheat all right corga you're a little bit of a dick there's corga
uh up there steal something yeah fuck this place the temple is cluttered with so many valuable
artifacts it is hard to decide where to begin there are sculptures plates candlesticks and
shields of solid gold a table covered with a silk cloth holds a crystal decanter and four
golden goblets in another corner a fountain showers with an endless stream of diamonds and jewels
take a handful of fucking jewels you go over to the fountain gazing in wonderment at the
sparkling splendor that issues from its spout you could simply put your pack underneath the stream
open and make enough money to hire an army to take with you to mampang you take a fistful of
the jewels but then you freeze the humming sound in the temple has become louder and you have a
strong sense that something is watching you turn around and look you turn your gaze up and see
nothing but wait a moment weren't there four stone demons up in the rafters above the altar before
the gargoyles are flapping in the air above you they are still stone but now their jaws are working
and their teeth snap in the air in front of their faces you begin to ready a spell but the creatures
know a sorcerer when they see one in moments one has dived for your right arm and with a single
bite severs it clean away what you look down in horror you will not be able to cast any more
spells now or wield your sword well the gargoyles hover back a little perhaps hoping that the
punishment has been suitably severe i can never cast the spell ever again that sucks um we we
ain't living with that i know i'm just i'm a cheating andy so bad right now whatever whatever
whatever i don't care i don't care whatever it's fine what else can i do here should i just zap
the statue should i just cast lightning and put it directly into corgis head it's three stamina
though that's bad do hot and just burn this place down um doesn't matter i mean i i'm trying to get
to the sewer because the sewer is where we can apparently figure out this last word maybe all
right i'm just walking across let's go nonsense and superstition you stride across the carpet
towards the idol but along the way something happens although you cannot be sure of what
one moment you are in the temple of corga and the next you are in the sewer this is where we want
to be let's find this goddamn line you've landed in a disgusting pile of unbelievable filth slime
excrement sludge dung and dregs all the way up to your neck you are evidently in the sewers of
kare wait you wait a moment as a nearby chute ejects a torrent of filth and pig swill then
you get yourself to your feet and wipe off the sludge as best you can oh we just got elden ringed
by the way where am i you stand in a cavernous sewer tunnel filled knee deep with slow flowing
stench filled water it is pitch black you could be standing on a mountaintop or inside of a coffin
except that is for a single speck of light somewhere in the far distance you wait and
within a few moments the tunnel is filled with goblins there are not one or two but a whole army
led by a tall stocky elder goblin enchanting a weird guttural song they pause a short distance
away from you and the leader steps forward you should not be here this is the domain of the mad
king end of us fuck you gack or god damn it i could be the new god uh hot that's too much stamina
though i need to i need to do the things that are not stamina gack would work pop would work
i don't have any pebbles though uh god would work but that's stamina i think gack is good
let's try it it doesn't cost any stamina gack you cast the spell whipping out the black face mask
the goblins shake and quiver with fear you are clearly a powerful being we will not trouble you
and with that he waves his army on they march off into the tunnel jeer at them you call and
jeer at the goblins as they pass but they are well trained even the grunts at the back ignore you
at the rear are two goblin generals how many more soldiers does the mad king want thousands
they don't get what he gets that he will the two walk on still talking in muttering voices like
this one didn't see that there were no quotes the goblins are tramping away up the sewer all right
head the other way follow the goblins i mean what does this go this goes down here potentially up
this goes up and potentially over here i'm going to follow them with the face mask on and just be
like
jim carrey from yeah i'm gonna be running around that's exactly what i was thinking of
do you know what i was holy shit that person you that i didn't even say it but that was exactly
what was in my mind jim carrey from the mask when he's in the office and he's holding it up to his
face and it doesn't work and he's just going like
he's making all these noises and jumping around that is what i was just doing as well that was
in my head i just didn't say it i didn't know how many people were going to understand that
that was the sweetest chef hey is the mask in the library of congress is it because it better be
that's like has to be right can somebody look that up is is jim carries the mask in the library of
congress if why no not the mask itself like the movie prop i'm talking about the the movie
like people in congress like want to go look at it yeah if this one movie somebody said it if
there's somebody said they shot it into space if there's one movie they should shoot into space
it's the mask just confuse the fuck out of all the aliens there's only jim carries the mask and
and a wheel we're like a car tire like what the hell is going on with what what is this
just that would be crazy right what the fuck even is this thing a car tire with the hubcap on
that's all of our inventions oh we found this strange thing siya look what we found we pulled
it into the beam it's a wheel that's what they put in their uh the thing in their time capsule
a fucking wheel at the jim carrey movie well we aren't going there they would never no we
would never get invaded we would never be invaded why would you invade this place why would you ever
care no no no we can just skip that planet they just they sent out a wheel and a jim carrey movie
we don't have to worry about that place don't shoot any interesting technology there right it's
like oh man we should share our technology are you kidding me don't send an iphone up there
send a burnt torch and a wheel they're going to skip our planet that's isolationist would you
want the aliens to know the technology that we have i don't want oh yeah let's make sure the
satellite communicates no all right anyways where were we um it's not did uh jim carrey the mask is
not in the library of congress but shrek is yeah i don't put i send up like a stick with a like a
cloth wrapping around it and like a shark tooth on it look yes tools we have tool we tool oh poor
earth no no no no no no we just leave them okay here we go send up a stick yeah the fact
the fact that it would be in a rocket ship means we have the technology to have a rocket ship
communicate in the first place that would be even more bizarre right why we're not fooling anybody
why would they put this in the we have rocket fuel but they're showing us that they have primitive
tools that's stupid uh yeah never mind what i said was dumb we have the technology to throw
that shit on whatever all right let's move on i fucked up i fucked up you trail along behind
the goblins like a shadow can't move on yet that was really dumb i don't know for some reason i
was thinking about in my mind i'm thinking about a tool with like earth carved in it somehow being
shot out of a cannon into space like it's not a rocket we just have a bag floating around in space
it's not on a rocket ship there's a bag in space that they come across and it's shitty tools and
a wheel right that's what i was thinking of like we don't leave a rocket ship it's just a bag
these like primitive cavemen are just taking their tools and throwing them as hard as they can into
the air it'll get we'll get soon strong reach space imagine if we did kind of what ellon mustered
with the car but instead slingshot on a metal box with sticks and shiny rocks yeah who cares
all right all right i'm done with i'm done we're gonna move on it's just too stupid to not at least
spend five minutes on it what if wood was rare to them that's true too like shit we gotta be careful
what if trees what if wood was an unbelievable resource and the aliens are like wait a minute
they have wood on this planet liquefy it and take all the trees don't send anything to space
they can come find us okay we don't send anything to space some people might see it as a threat
uh boss there's a metal box here that has earth carved on it and there's an ax in here shoot the
fucking beam at it that's an act of violence that's a threat please move on i have an essay do
well go do your essay you're assuming that aliens are as stupid as we are this is a declaration of
war the aliens finally show up one day the president goes on camera uh ladies and gentlemen it's the
president i just need to make sure everyone understands that the aliens are arriving on
tuesday and they think we're all primitive cave men and cave women so for one day only at least
everybody don't speak in any languages everyone crawl around and save noises and grow your beards
out as long as you can we keep up we gotta keep up like the the actual thing here we could keep the
personas up the aliens land everyone just kind of like throwing rocks making sounds grow a beard by
tuesday yeah some people can do that not me you do it in the bernie voice all right let's go
destroy all the cars yeah unfortunately ladies and gentlemen my fellow americans
all cars need to be destroyed or not destroyed but hidden there'll be government issued tarps
to put over all your vehicles and all your houses uh everyone is to dig a hole five feet deep in
their backyard and hang out in there for just six hours while the aliens walk around and uh survey
the planet how long would you have to keep that up what if they wanted to hang out oh this is
beautiful what a wonderful planet and they're so primitive i think we'll stay here for uh two or
three uh parsecuens oh two or three parsecuens was that a week oh on your planet that's three
thousand years oh well well let's do it for a little bit longer and they know right these
motherfuckers know ah yeah i wonder how long they're going to keep this up they know they want to see
like just how long we'll do this for i feel like you came from an alternate reality i'm from this
reality there what do you mean look just because the marvel movies came out and we're like look
there's this spider-man and there's another spider-man we don't know shit guys it's just
us and the cockroaches okay i'm sorry it's just us the cockroaches and like the the bunny rabbits
there's nothing else it doesn't matter that's a big spoiler a spoiler for what i don't know
look i okay i get the theory but the fact that okay so this what there's like an infinite amount
of me sitting in this chair having an infinite amount of rants about the alien joke no it's just
us and the bugs there's nothing else it's just us and the fucking earwigs who is he talking to
i know i'm stalling all right all right i'm not stalling though this is just an interesting
conversation what if they came down and they were large sentient earwigs i get to stick around
because i they will look at all my history here and they'll be like this guy was talking about
earwigs and he talked about how they were cool and they were an awesome group of uh beings and
i they would i would become an ambassador to earth sorry guys would you ever eat earwig meat
no all right you trail along behind the goblins like a shadow god we've been sitting for like
10 minutes the vaclands tribes are ready the first goblin general hisses second goblin makes a
chittering noise something close to a laugh ready to run through the city like a river of molten
steel that her word from the king a few words but i have learned a few of myself
hey what was that freeze or keep up i probably get high right right over here freeze you freeze
the goblins keep walking away out of earshot not stopping they do not look around but continue
talking in low voices catch up you hurry up and catch up with the goblins i thought i said a corpse
the tunnel turns a corner something glints from the side of the sewer i gotta keep up i have to
keep up i missed it you missed the spell line what i missed the spell line no i didn't keep up
i'm gonna run right into them keep up i heard nothing the other replies you heard a key pace
just behind them in the dark further on you know one of the lines one goblin is quizzing the other
the goblin spits an agreement i ever had the mad king whispered to himself in forger's pride
you can't believe your luck it's the second half of theta's spell line i got them all now
i win got it we've got all the lines we just don't know the order but it's okay this is the
first time i'm ever going to complete part two truly actually getting the good end and not the
bad end every single time okay something let's look at it you stop to look at it losing the
sight of the goblins it's a vial of it's a vial of potion sniff it you uncork it and sniff it it's
blimbleberry quaff it i should probably quaff it yeah i quaff it you unstoppable the blimberry
potion and knock it back quickly you feel a little better and all traces of hunger are gone also
the goblins disappear so does that actually mean that i know everything do i know the whole thing
i got the whole thing by corgas grace and forga's pride one lock made of golems hide tumblers to
seal deep inside i bid you portals open wide got it that's definitely the order that's the rhyme
okay i can turn back or we can keep going as we'll just keep going if the king knew you even knew
that much tell him and i cut your throat ah stay quiet and maybe we'll get out of this oh wait stay
quiet maybe we'll cut his throat just then you see more lights up ahead it seems the sewer is opening
out into a wider space the opening all the lines rhyme do they one lock made of golems hide
tumblers to seal deep inside like corga oh they all rhyme they all whatever
you slip into the hall it is warm with the fetid breath of a thousand creatures
who drink and laugh and clash swords down in the muck on his throne their king seems to be sleeping
or else they have killed him by accident he's a man not a goblin how does he control this rabble
you wait transfixed by the strange scene the king coughs suddenly the effect is bizarre at the noise
every goblin in the great chamber freezes and looks up interesting the man is thin as if he
has not eaten in months and pale as if he has been in the dark just as long his hair is long and gray
and he slumps over the side of his throne as though desperately ill his clothes are long soiled robes
that perhaps were once quite fine on his hand is a ring a diamond ring which he gazes at periodically
and on his head he wears a gray circlet of a dull silver metal you cannot quite place the king pushes
on the arm of his chair attempting to stand then shivers and falls down silence the chamber is
suddenly quiet look at his face you peer through the gloom through the grime and dirt and the
thickness of his beard trying to see his face there's something familiar about it you've seen
it somewhere before the king fingers the circlet on his head as if scared it will slip my creatures
the time is almost on us as the night draws in we will rise up and open the gates we will rub this
filthy city clean he's broken off into a fit of coughing you keep waiting wanting to see what
comes next the long journey is nearly over the process i began when i blinded lord theta
and left him a beggar finally the council will be destroyed and the city will be
cleansed it's not dumbledore so this is this is sansa's yeah this is the first noble uh i'm
afraid if i keep listening you stay hidden a goblin close by by your elbow murmurs how much
longer do we have to listen to this his companion silences him with a talon to the arm shut up wait
and listen you stay hidden and wait the king finally gets to his feet and raised into wise an arm
into the air i will open the gates for you tonight and we will make this city pure the king raises a
cheer and the goblins as one cheer back throwing their swords up in the air a thousand blades flash
and the confusion when they landed extreme every goblin cowering for cover and then squabbling to
retrieve their blade all right let's go move now it's time to get the hell out of here creep to a
ladder or return to the sewer well i think we can get out this way sticking to the shadows you begin
to creep around the perimeter of the hall aiming for one of those long ladders that disappear up
into the darkness you get about halfway before the goblins nearby turn pushing at each other
and you are forced to freeze the king calls for silence but the goblins do not hear him they are
still in a mess with their swords go go go get out go just leave just run run run run run run
keep going keep going no no you creep further around the edge of the hall the king calls a
again for silence clutching his circlet with one hand this time the goblins fall silent you realize
with a heavy heart that you've missed the best opportunity you will get to escape the chamber by
the ladder what look at his face all right i'm okay you know who it is familiar all right go
andy rewind that's fine uh yep keep going make a move we get out the long journey is nearly over
the process i began when i blinded lord theta left him a beggar let's go and we're out how much
longer do we have to listen to this make a move they raise a cheer hooray make a move we're out
get out leave quick taking advantage of the confusion you scurry quickly up the ladder
for a few rungs you are in the open it must look like a strange oversized rat climbing the rigging
in this underground cell but you climb fast and quietly and are quickly lost into the shadows
overhead once more you climb the ladder into a narrow stone chimney which climbs at an angle
after a while the ladder gives out and there is nothing but stone above you in the distance
a circle of light god i'm gonna fall right back down on my back gum raz sharpen blade
with oh i can probably stick it in the side force field float in the air float would work
yeah let's float float in the air you cast the spell making your body featherweight
you then paw your way up the stone chimney pushing off the walls with your hands and feet
as if you were dancing up towards the light you emerge in a grateful heap to the fresh air of the
outside world it's oh it's right here we're i got the let's go let's go go go go go you've emerged
from a well house in a clearing in the shadow of the city wall looking around you realize how far
you've come on the other side of this clearing is the north gate itself wasting no time you stride
over to the gate we gotta go now you reach the other side of the clearing unscathed and stand
below the enormous doors okay what's the the north gate spell i know what the first line is
here it is something that the corgas grace one lock deep inside i bid you corgo lock deep bid
let's go recite the spell you knock firmly on the door until you wake with the voice
you knock firmly on the door until you wake the voice within do you know the spell to open this
gate you close your eyes and try to recall the scratched poem in the sewer chamber of by corgas
grace and forgus pride one lock made of golems hide tumblers too sealed deep inside i bid you
portals open wide you stand back to see what effect your lines have had the voice has gone silent
you wait impatiently to see what will happen then the gate creaks the tumblers drop and the
wooden panels begin to move the door is opening booming out the voice declares the gate is under
your control but it is moving slowly looking over your shoulder you see an army of goblins
emerging from a well shaft and they are racing towards you oh do i just run i've i don't think
we've ever done this do i just run through go go go go go you rush through the gate into the back
lens okay just go go go go this i'm not waiting beyond the north gate in the darkness around you
figures are moving pouring towards the gate into the city inside you see the goblins still coming
close it on him gate close the gate obeys immediately swinging shut like a trap
from the low hills around red-faced marsh goblins are springing up and pouring towards the sealed
gate like flies into a fallen ox they begin to scramble on top of one another trying to
bridge the wall with their own bodies destroy the goblins the goblins must be destroyed
as though on command a ghostly figure forms in the air before you it is lorag you control the gate
use it uh you do it uh i don't know how try it is hopeless how can you use a magic you do not know
you close your eyes feeling your anger and frustration rising the hated goblins this
meddling specter the long and difficult road behind and the ones still to come all seem to
bite into your very soul like wolf teeth there is suddenly a terrible sound and a smell of burning
open my eyes you open your eyes there's not a goblin in sight just blackened grass around the
gate and black soot and piles on top of the wall the ghost nods slowly to you
i'll keep it on fuck it all the hatred of the whole city of thieves and liars and murderers
stored for centuries a little leak towered into the red eyes the rest was waiting for this for one
strong of hard enough to use it go be safe the long road is long huh he gestures to the path ahead
be safe you're not in turn to go so what so i burn the city so that's my i did it no just the
goblins though this is getting intense all right here we go outside kare into the back lands
from a short distance away you look back to see the plane outside the gate is quite empty
not a single marsh goblin remains but a single short sword or hooked pick it is like they have
been wiped from the surface of the earth and inside kare something similar must have occurred
as where there was the sound of flashing swords there is now only silence
you have saved kare a foul city perhaps but not one whose citizens deserve to die by a goblin
sword but it has been at a cost to your strength you turn your back your own road lies ahead
through the plains of badubak and on towards mampang the back lands await you remember the
words of the site master sergeant as you left the outpost settlement once you have crossed the city
port of traps you will enter the backlands they say that day and night are controlled by forces
other than the sun and from kare too your progress will be watched to badubak your journey across
kare is complete in the course of your journey you committed murder and saved the city port of
kare from destruction you played 11 games of swindle stones winning nine and losing two
you learned the truth about what the crown does a riddle about the sleepless ram
and that silver weapons harm the undead you collected a fantastic number of magical artifacts
large lump of beeswax a cloth skullcap two giants teeth seven goblins teeth a black face mask
a green-haired wig a bracelet of bone one sun jewel a bamboo pipe also you found a bottle of
poison a bottle of bark essence a bottle of snake bite antidote and a tinderbox you're very happy
considering this was your grocery list and it is now complete you're still armed only with your
original sword and have no rations and 25 gold pieces and a spell book the adventure continues
in sorcery three the seven serpents out now it is out now so there you go there's part one and part
two uh what we're going to do here i'm going to take a brb i'm going to p refill my t and i'm
we're going to you i'm going to we're going to at least start uh part three i want you to see the
map i want you to see kind of the mechanics uh we're going to keep going so i'll be right back
go grab a refill go to the bathroom we'll continue but that was car this is probably my favorite of
the three if i have to rank them it goes kare seven serpents uh part one and then part four
and it's not that i don't like part four it's just there's part four is awesome it's just it's very
very hard part four is very hard but no spoilers if you know the game if you've played it or if
you watched the last when we did this years ago but i do love uh part three i think part two and
part three are the best okay i'll be right back go get a refill see you guys in a minute brb okay i'm
back i am back but i need to make sure i can get this to work key dokey did you fall in no i made
another t yeah i know we're we're effing right now it's fine because i'm i was downloading uh
something downloading the episode okay dokey make sure i can capture this i can't hear anything
can you guys hear anything hey there we go okay the spongebob wait i find it so why did i read
it as spon i don't even know if you were writing i don't care i thought you were asking me a
question about spongebob okay so we're gonna do part three part three incoming here we go night
falls wait make sure everyone's here we're good night falls on this the eighth day of your journey
from manland to the east mighty mountains claw at the stars you stand on the edge of badu bak
wild and evil place beyond lies man pang fortress the archmage the crown of kings the path has been
title update we will in a second leaving the hills you journeyed into kare and saved it from
destruction by goblins you brave the deadly portal traps of the city ancient cruel magic
designed to trap the unwary and you faced an army of enchanted werewolves as they sought to
overthrow the first noble i fought one werewolf but you know i could say an army i fought one
werewolf that's fine one werewolf attacked me on the road and uh i killed it but the backlands
are different but the plains of badu bak will be different once long ago this land thrived
prospering in the warm shadow of the fortress of sorcerers high in the zanzunu peaks then
something changed they say the last refugee to reach kare declared only they are all gone
the north gate was sealed and the backlands left to die now the gates stand open they say the land
beyond the gates is cursed no one from the young country of aniland has ever crossed this wilderness
before you will be the first the old world is counting on you but already you have no food
this stage of your journey will be punishing but you cannot turn back ladies and gentlemen
inkle presents a story by steve jackson steve jackson's story part three the seven servants
is the gate of kare again let's take a look at this here you go it's very large it's like five
different world of warcraft zones and something else happens here too that's even more ridiculous
and you'll find out if you don't know and if you do know don't tell anybody because it's cool it's
cool and we're gonna let everybody figure that out no spoilers here we go the stones of the old road
disappear under a layer of dust and sand at your back looms the great wall the city port of kare
ahead there is nothing but an empty waste and the night you cast a glance at the city port even now
vic is taking control the baying of his wolves echoes across the plains that's a storyline
we did not do but um the city's there and vic apparently has taken it look up at the stars
you turn your gaze from kare to the stars wondering what fresh secrets they may hold
this far from the walls of aniland into the plains every step along the broken road takes you further
from safety and into the unknown something the ape perhaps sets your senses tingling you're not
alone out here is that the screech of a bird you hear or a distant scream we could talk to animals
we could uh just throw a fireball into the air we could sense danger let's talk to animals all
right let's try it it doesn't cost anything you cast the spell and pull on the wig in the distance
you hear the screeching of birds but as the spell takes hold the sound resolves into words
there's one he looks like a tasty morsel i claim first strike a moment later a ferocious
nighthawk has plunged from the sky talon's outstretched for your neck worse voice shut up
shut up that's how you do a bird that's a bird voice what do you want me to do all right i'm
gonna uh i'm gonna roll you hurl yourself to one side just in time and the sharp claws sweep
past your neck to rake the dirt i will shred you to your gizzards tasty one the bird wheels up
into the sky to rejoin its group take his eyes take his eyes you count four birds circling ready
to attack shout in defiance try to take me i have killed a manticore we will take your blood all
right bad enough are they stupid i think they're intelligent aren't they oh that would be all right
i don't think they're magical well they don't talk i can i can understand them because i have
the wig on i could put up a wall i can't do anything expensive because i only have what seven
stamina um i'm gonna say wait a minute i could i float up to them i'm floating up to them and
i'm gonna okay let's float you cast the spell and feel yourself lifting gently off the ground
as your weight is reduced to that of a feather the nighthawks do not pause one swoops talon
spiking your shoulder knocking you sprawling to the ground i prick you i'm dead you stay down
hoping the bird will leave you for dead but nighthawks do not attack for pleasure but for
food lying still makes them bold and soon all three are diving for you then quite suddenly
the nighthawks break formation something else is shimmering into visibility in their very midst
you settle back to the ground as your spell wears off wait what so wait they hit me in the
in the air midair and i'm lying down but pretending to be lagged out of the server
i'm just floating there falling slowly on my side all right i'm running crawl you belly crawl
up to higher ground while behind you the strangest of battles ensues the wing of one nighthawk snaps
upwards like a broken branch a second is ripped into feathers by invisible claws the remaining
birds scatter there's nothing left but your mysterious savior uh i'm gonna stay hidden you
stay low hoping the creature will not see you but there is a rush of air just in front of you
whatever it is has landed you hear the movement of unseen feathered wings and then at last you
understand this creature is a gold crest eagle from the king's own eerie in aniland the eerie
is deep behind the shumantanti wall it must have flown for three days to reach you but why the
creature slowly becoming visible sees you have recognized it it tilts its beak bow you bow your
head to the eagle it opens its beak in reply and something falls to the ground it is a message
cylinder whatever it contains must be of vital importance or the king would not have risked
revealing your location like this to deliver it to you take the tube you reach down and pick up
the tube inside is a rolled parchment sealed with the royal seal of the king of aniland
but you pause for a moment and sigh the king has accidentally sent you his letter to santa claus
it must have been some kind of mix-up okay let me read this we trust these tidings reach you in
fair health but must warn you of impending peril your mission is discovered the man pangs eyes have
spied our plan and word is on its way to the dark fortress too late we discovered our unwelcome
eavesdroppers and news of your quest is being carried towards high xamen by the seven serpents
the archmage's most trusted servants by now they will have reached the backlands
and here they will divide to complete their journey separately if you are still able seek
them out for they must stop to rest and eat destroy the creatures before they reach their goal
else the archmage will prepare a deadly welcome for you find shadrach the hermit for advice
for not moves through the backlands without his knowledge our hearts are with you the seal
fucking george washington thank the eagle you look up but the goldcrest eagle has already
rendered itself invisible once more you feel the rush of air as its great wings lift it from the
ground and you are alone destroy it or keep it i feel like maybe keep it because this might be
proof like hey i've got the king of aniland has the seal here maybe it's i could use it for help
that's possible right or destroy it because if somebody finds it on me then they know what i'm
doing here keep it to show the hermit yeah i'm not sure either way how this would work um yeah
we'll do a poll should i destroy the message or hold on to it in case i need to use it it's pretty
50 50 on what would happen i need food and i need to sleep this is bad one or two what are we
thinking oh let me run it one two there you go ah there we go cool starting off pretty strong to
keep it yeah it's one and two one destroy to keep isn't paper edible um not really yeah two is keep
yeah one and two come on what are you talking about all right we're gonna keep it you roll the
message up and slip it into your pack it would seem the backlands are not as deserted as you
had supposed you must find these seven serpents and destroy them or your journey will be for
nothing two new clues what are the clues seven serpents seven serpents threaten your journey
for they carry a message that will warn the archmage of your coming uh shadrack the hermit
can help you only silver weapons can harm the undead you are given a clue about the backlands
for sleeping of the sleepless ram seek the one they call the sham okay still have all my shit
right yeah all right back to the road the stars turned in the sky overhead taking the pole as
your guide you rejoin the old road and make your way north before you the backlands stretch away
to a dim horizon how can you hope to locate seven serpents in such a wilderness my spirit will guide
me the ape my spirit will guide me you will no doubt require the ape even more than ever before
out here where nothing else can be trusted and the ape has told you to walk off of a cliff so you do
it no decision is permanent rewind at any time that it was that was that wrong after about half
an hour you see a deep black line across the earth up ahead and catch your step just in time
you are one pace away from the edge of a sheer cliff a few loose stones disappear over the edge
and clatter away into the dark look for a way down rest until daylight uh i need stamina
stamina sun what would that do here how what would that do sun jewel oh so i can see down
oh i'm gonna do that doesn't cause i don't want to do anything that costs stamina looking to the
stars you craft the magic and the sun jewel in your back begins to pulse and throb with a brilliant
blinding light with the light from the jewel you look over the cliff and make out a set of
worn carved steps leading downwards it seems there definitely is a path here or there was
many hundreds or thousands of years ago climb down you creep towards the stone steps and begin
to make your way down okay that that works the cold night lingers on using the light from your
sun jewel you feel your way forward but halfway down the glow on the gem begins to fade you begin
to curse your decision to come this way throw the jewel no what i don't want to throw it this thing
is very very useful keep going you focus on placing your feet carefully and continue to make
your way down the cliff face like a goat the glow from your gem fades and you are plunged into
darkness once more the ground is closer than you realize and when the staircase runs out and turns
into loose scree it is a rough but thankfully short slide to the bottom you land with a thump
at the base of the cliff why would i have thrown the jewel you've reached the bottom of the cliff
the sky is already beginning to warm in the east the rock wall rises behind you cutting out half
the sky the staircase is now invisible just shadows on shadows in the craggy rock in the
near distance across the plains and away from the cliff you can see a dark shape jutting up from the
ground like a gigantic sword rest here out in the open in the dark zen hmm zip i don't have i could
teleport and get whatever the green ring is uh i might be okay that's one stamp anything free
what do i have that's free heel disease this is three this is a lot isn't it um i'll do how
because yeah let's do how i'm gonna die if i'm not careful you bind the starling to shape around you
and a familiar calm voice begins to speak voice tells you that the stairs are long since destroyed
and will never be rebuilt okay thanks i want safe passage not the history of the stairs i'll rest
let me look at the cliff you gaze up the soaring arc of the cliff barren rock dusted by what little
scrub can cling onto its sides it is as if some great clawed hand had scooped out the earth the
foot of the cliff is pitted with shadow holes no doubt dug by animals you peer through the gloom
trying to make out more details whatever the structure is it does not appear natural
but equally it does not appear to be intact seems to be sliding into the earth strange
the backlands were said to be uninhabited i i have to sleep we have to i have to rest here you find
an old fox hole and scramble inside at least you've eaten already today so do not need to
eat again to avoid hunger though more food will make you stronger you'll eat to eat once a day
all right close my eyes nothing bad nothing bad nothing bad nothing bad nothing bad you close your
eyes and let your tiredness overtake you the silence is loud in your ears slowly you're
understanding the true loneliness of this place you long for human company even the withering insults
of flanker but there is no one here you feel quite safe and you do not dream cliff face during the
past day you've become weaker reached the pit of the backlands and found four new clues you pull
yourself out of your hole and stand up okay i got two health nearby is a stone tower the only stone
structure in the whole barren landscape it is the shape you saw here at night look at the tower the
tower stands some way across the plane almost in the foothills of the ridge it lists to one side
but appears not to have crumbled into ruin move on this then is the plane of badubak an endless
expanse of dust broken only by the thin outline of an ancient road no one from aniland has been
here no one even knows what happened to this place once it was the archmage's country his fields and
paddocks and now it is too barren to even be a place of death what do we do this is quite this
is quite the early decision he just came and said what the fuck is happening all right uh i'll get
a poll going because we're either gonna go because let's let's give it a big picture here
where are they going this way right this way or this way so i'm it's going to be four choices but
i imagine yeah so ready pay attention one two three four again follow the cliff one into the
plane two follow this cliff three the old road four one two three four one two three four got it
again one two three four one two three four one two three four one two three four one two three four
one two three four you got it two four three one four four three four four four two four two one
did i get it right did i get the code right where are we going baby sensory hey wait what was it
again i wasn't paying attention oh that's easy that it's four or you get all you get one or it's two
you go four or four or four or three all right let's go four you leave the shadow of the cliff
for the road that cuts across the plane the air stirs a little still cold but at least fresh
from here the path is uncertain badubak is a wasteland and there is no pass through
the great ridge that forms its eastern border the forest of snata is uncharted the zanzunu peaks
and mampang seem remote the forest of snata to the east of the ridge is uncharted and the
clatterback steps are said to be home only to under evolved half humans no tracks climb the horns
of ilk lala no tracks climb the horns of ilk lala that lie beyond the forest and there is no bridge
across the great lake beyond that there may be no road at all when the archmage sent his birdmen to
steal the crown of kings they flew but you must walk lala there is no alternative the future of
the old world depends on you finding your way across this lonely dust bowl jesus christ um
well we're okay strike out north the blasted tree along the road okay well we're going
we're not going this way you've already decided to go this way we're not going from here to here to
here you had a choice to go from here to here and you didn't choose it so we're going this way so
you do get a choice here though you get a one two three lala you didn't choose to go that way you
chose to go this way one two three one two three three two one two two two two three three three
three three three three three three three three three two two two two two two two two two two two
one two one one two one one two one one three one two one one one sick fucking beat hey dude i just
joined what's happening he said i actually just joined and i thought my computer was actually
glitching i got you i got you i got you all right we're going one and then i'm going to start
making some decisions you know what i mean we're going to the blasted tree you leave the road and
walk across the desolate plain a few clouds scut across the sky after a while of walking you see
something to break the monotony too tall and thin for a skewer of rock or a building you cannot
place it until you get close it's a single tree leafless and dead tilting from the desolate soil
climb the branches that seems the tree must be the last remnant of an ancient forest
the why this particular trunk has survived when all the others fell is not clear and that is not
all a rope ladder hangs from one of the higher branches of the tree okay climb the rope ladder
this is like a tree house you scramble up the rope ladder to get a view across the lands
but the branches seem to be alive twisting and bending as you climb they're closing in around
you like a trap untie the ladder it's like a three stooges routine okay untie the ladder
the knots holding the ladder to the branch are thick with age but you manage to work them free
the branch underneath seems to lift in relief that is as it is removed a moment later another
branch draws backwards behind you and releases knocking you painfully to the ground for a moment
you hear a sound almost like a laugh who's there stranger stranger show yourself there is no
response surely this land is a desert you're entirely alone are you not we'll find out
hmm to burn the tree i could burn the tree i could read minds which would be interesting
uh sense danger i think that's all we have i only have four hp so that would be bad let's read minds
it's free you weave the enchantment pulling on the cloth skullcap as you do you reach out with
your mind but what you find is not what you expect there are no humans or even any creatures in the
vicinity instead there is an intelligence something heavy and dark and thick the thoughts like ancient
oil talk or listen let's talk you reach out further trying to connect with this strange other presence
you seem to make no progress and then the spell fades and you open your eyes to find yourself
staring another pair formed by the curved twigs of the tree itself a face stranger
you are lost what makes you say who are you what are you be warned i will not be played with i am
a spirit and an old friend okay well how are you a friend can you guide me the branches flutter
and break in a sudden gust of wind the face disappearing for a moment you seek the whereabouts
of a shard rack of badubak uh yeah where where is he turn like a leaf in the morning
through the fish tail rock he is expecting you another strong breeze catches the branches and
disturbs them and when they settle the face has disappeared fish tail rock come back get back here
you mother fucker uh wait you wait a short while but it's no good you walk away from the shade of
the tree all right we got a clue fish tail rock all right let's keep going this way we're not
going back this way you've already made your choice east along the road i told you that was
a major decision can you pray to get healed i can i don't want to use it unless i have to though
you walk on across the plane until you meet the edge of an old road as the morning moves on the
wind begins to rise the road snakes across the dust bowl in the nearest in the near distance you
make out something through the haze not a tower but a spire of rock seems to flicker strangely
from behind you a voice says excuse me turn around you turn around to find the road deserted
there is no one in sight in any direction where are you you call half expecting flanker to
materialize up from the dust to greet you there's no reply the cold wind whistles around you the
planes feel suddenly far emptier than a moment before you continue along the ghost road okay
you get a choice one or two one two one two one is towards the cliff two is head up east this way
and go so one is to go down probably here over here two is to go like here one is cliff two is
head east what do you think what do you think what do you think what do you think what do you think
what do you think please can you hit the two button a lot again uh no um no sorry no uh it's close
very close can you please hit the three button three i'll give you that i mean i'll give i'll
give you this too right like two no yeah i'll give you one a lot of you guys don't want to go to the
cliff interesting okay i don't remember what this is i don't remember what this is either i of all
the games forget these next two parts more than anything kare is my favorite so i obviously
remember a lot of stuff but i don't remember very much from this very much gone from my brain
all right we're going east you follow the old road the sun is hot now the road forks here with the
main path snaking up the mountainside of the east rocks have tumbled down the slope and all but cover
the road you cast your gaze east toward the towering badu back ridge the main peak is lost
in the haze at the end of the long winding road that climbs up the slope looking north the road
winds along the rocky edges of the foothills our particularly impressive stone stupa stands out a
little way along stone shift and move underfoot as you walk i mean two was cliff we talked about
two is the road all right i'm gonna make this decision this way heading towards the clatterbox
steps or up here into more of this kind of plains area let's go up the ground underfoot
turns into rocks and scree the sun has reached its highest point now out of the shade the air
is baking hot you pause to rest in the shadow of a large rock spire that sticks out from the dirt
like a claw through cloth the rock is a single shattered spire perhaps once part of the mountain
range to the east or perhaps driven up through the ground by some geological quirk at the base
of the rock is the mouth of a cave perhaps stuffed with buried treasure you approach the cave with
one hand on your blade the cave appears to go back some distance into pitch blackness someone
seems to have scratched a message into the rock inside the cave it is only just legible and must
be ancient in the thin sunlight falling into the cave you can make out the ancient scratch message
with some difficulty stranger i am waiting very long ago summon you call my name to the skies and
i will draw the message on the cave wall suggested calling out a name but what name should you call
flanker where are you shadrack jan well imagine calling jan's name here i mean we're gonna do
this right because that's shadrack you cry the name across the plains and the echo of it seems
to set off a distant avalanche the ground begins to shake and rumble and you stagger to your knees
the very earth is moving as though it was splitting or merging back together you reach down to steady
yourself only to find that the grass is growing between your fingers you pick yourself unsteadily
to your feet feeling sick and unwell everything around you is the same but everything is different
the rock has two spires for one thing the cave seems smaller and darker and in a fire pit built
into the scrub is its mouth is a fire burning from inside you hear the gentle sound of singing are
you guys starting to understand why a part three is cool and you will soon you guys just got elden
ringed yep there it is you got elden ringed again let me take a few guesses okay uh we're
gonna listen you stop and listen the singer is a man with a voice like gravel moving over ice
he sings in a language you do not recognize what its tune feels at once arresting an ancient and
the melody seems to soothe your soul you approach the fire call out for shadrack shadrack i am here
the singing stops abruptly there's a coughing and a wheezing sound and then an old man hobbles from
outside the cave limping on a stick this must be shadrack himself but you recognize the face as
that of the tree spirit you met earlier ah it's you i have been expecting you he waves a hand
around the landscape welcome back welcome back just so you have come a long long way my anilander
i know your mission of course i know all about you and you know about me i hope my name is shadrack
oh i i it was worth keeping show him the eagle's message you pulled the message from your pack i
was given this it mentions you hmm the diviners are most impressive or perhaps our meeting has
simply been remembered yes that is more likely then his eyes narrow on as he reads seven serpents
yes now i see why they have sent you to me can you help that depends hmm i know you journey here
from clare tell me how fares that city it stands still the same as always it stands still same as
always you have to call it the same as always right i've i've it stands sad track nods deeply
i watched an army of marsh goblins scale the cliffs armed with swords and axes there should
be smoke rising at the horizon but i see no such thing he grabs a handful of dry grass from the
ground and tosses it into the fire pit where it blazes for a moment into flame he appears to
change topic i must warn you that no one from aniland has ever crossed the backlands alone
and survived the serpents yes but not only them the very rocks and earth here are lost things
become unstuck and you have now become unstuck yourself i i don't understand he demonstrated
with his finger as he speaks twisting them together the old world in the ancient world
have grown together like thorny bushes to journey through one is to journey through the other you
have any do you have any food the ancient world you ask looking about yourself with the fields of
grass that have appeared to replace the desert istara the place that was my home you are most
welcome unexpectedly shadrach stumbles he smiles at you weakly oh are you unwell this whole land
is unwell i will not be able to stay for very long please ask me what you need to know and then
leave you play swindle stones you come all of this way to speak with me and you want to do it by
playing dice why don't we talk oh you're just afraid i'm gonna win i do not think so and what
do you think you have to gain playing swindle stones against a telepath is beyond even my
cogniz do you have any food my my three wishes right i asked the genie asked the mage the
questions i'm hungry i want a car and um replace the toilet paper in my bathroom because it's low
why could i ask for anything worse i could get the answers to the universe do you have any food
that actually is important i am too holy to eat but if you can reach karyama north of the river
you may be able to eat well there if it still exists in your time most likely it does not
shadrach is shivering slightly now his face is pale beyond the ruddy beard how did this curse come
to be the land was cursed by the archmage to be forgotten and so it has been and so it will be
not long now and then all you will see will be gone only timeless desolation will remain but why
because of you the archmage punished this whole land to make a trap to kill you before you could
kill him he is a dangerous enemy and he is quite desperate uh i understand he has sent seven
serpents to kill me the hermit nods most seriously the serpents are most terrible i have often seen
them but they are no mere snakes do you know of their legend tell me i don't care just tell me how
to tell me yes i can do that better it is said that thousands of years from now a few years ago
for you perhaps the archmage of manpeng often slew a mighty hydra which dwelt in the caves of
high salmon so formidable a foe was his creature that the archmage took its seven heads back to
manpeng where he used his dark arch to resurrect them as seven winged serpents they became his
personal messengers his assassins his force in a dark place thousands of years from now indeed so
look about you i fancied this valley was not green with grass when you entered it he's right
it is the same valley and yet not the same i don't understand what has happened how much
you ever lost on swindle stones i need to get a better mic guys there are no other mics that
are better than these you understand i'm not talking through like a fucking $40 desk microphone
there's no there are there are no other mics that exist that are better than this they don't exist
they genuinely don't it's my room has loud sounds because the ac is always on because it's a hundred
fucking degrees in vegas you got one guide yeah of course i'm gonna i'm gonna dip i'm gonna defend
myself do you have a fancy mic what i use for a mic is not of your concern okay what matters is
can i do this and can i do this or and the answer is yes okay quiet you will i don't understand what
has happened you will but you will learn that for yourself i must tell you this each serpent has a
spirit to sustain it and grants a great power but also a powerful weakness discover these weaknesses
and you may be able to defeat the serpents shadrack shivers and coughs friend i wish i did
not have to go but i must if i am to close the circle he gets a stick and pushes himself up to
his feet they hear the background noise and they think it's your mic crackling no they definitely
don't it's because i i have this background noise on this mic and i have to get rid of it because
it's like and if i don't get rid of it then it's gonna sound fucking 10 times worse it's hot in
las vegas it gets hot in here i don't want to hear what you have to say i don't care if you think
it's a bad mic all right we're now we're doing john oliver a good mic wouldn't do that because
the mic that i had before was seven hundred dollars and it did the same thing it was a seven hundred
dollar mic they don't they don't get better than that do you understand get better ac what are you
talking about i used that mic for like six years it was a newman t l2 whatever the hell it is
and everybody hated that mic too to stream out of the fridge i'll stream up the fridge microphone
from now on it's a skill issue buy something good all right now you're all just fucking with me now
i'm getting fucked with he's a rich fuck guys i bought that microphone i bought in 2015 i got
seven years out of that mic that i got a lot of time out of that mic and i might go back to it
it's it's possible i used that mic for seven fucking years all right we got one guide and
i can't wait it's derailing everything are you sure you don't think my voice just sounds like
dog shit it that's what it could be i'm gonna go you know i'm gonna buy one of those okay they
look like they look like steam engines they have like these dials on there with like compressing
like it looks like gas nozzles and shit i'm gonna plug it into that and see what people say no i
have a mixer i plug this mic with an xlr into a mixer and without a noise gate you would hear
all the horrible sounds coming out of my mouth hired audio professional and just to tune your
shit for a day yeah just get in there and fix everything the ac is going a lot and so it's just
like turn off the noise gate no it's i'm telling you we want to hear the horrible sounds i'm going
to turn the noise gate off and then see what people say it's off how do you feel how you doing
how do you feel that's a huge improvement it really isn't it sounds nice and crispy it's
you know it's not it's not crispy you're not idiot there's nothing you know there's no crispiness
that you're hearing try screaming ah it's exactly the same chat is coping go plug in the all right
i'm moving on i'm not going to let one guy do you look everybody's audio sucks okay everybody's
audio sounds like shit everybody if you turn the volume on the web and you put your headphones on
you put your and you just go what what's that so what does it sound like i turned off the campfire
is that what you were hearing i don't hear a difference well this is this is it without the
did i just get fucked with for 10 straight minutes because they thought it was that then
there's no there's no way right i just i just i got fucked with for 10 straight minutes did
that just happen because you heard this and you made a joke about how my mic sucks because it's
cracking like this and then wow you really hit a nerve because he went off on like a 10 minute
tirade about how about how the microphone sounds bad it wasn't just that yeah i'm gonna turn this
back on let me turn my settings back the way they were all right we're moving on okay here we go
you guys ready nice sorcery stream prove you aren't naked i don't have to prove anything
all right here we go go go go go relax relax relax relax relax nice rice crispy mic shut up
come on man you understand it doesn't okay even if i i okay i'm gonna do this i'm not gonna say
i'm going to hire a audio professional i'm gonna pay whatever they ask i'm gonna literally get an
audio i'm gonna say hey i will pay anything you say come in and make it professional and make it
unbelievable and i guarantee i guarantee the day after that there will be a shit load of people
in this chat going hey this mic sucks why it sounds like you're inside of a bathroom dude a
nice nice microphone you are you taking a shit i guarantee that happens and i'm not gonna tell
you that but i'm gonna do it and i'm gonna i'll pay him whatever he wants what he could write down
a number and hold it up embarrassed being like i can't say this number out loud because it's so
much and i'll go yep sit down sit down and do it hey by the way that's the number you wrote down
double it i'm gonna double what you wrote down their eyes are gonna widen and be like what are
you talking about i mean just do it just do it make and this is making this the best audio setup
you've ever done let's go and we get it you're rich no that's not the point i'm good the point
is the point is you guys are dicks that's the point your noise gate's too aggressive no it's
the art i'll just quiet and wait till when i hire this motherfucker i just called them a motherfucker
but i'm very i want to i'm gonna be their friend i just said it because like i you've got me you're
in my head and now you're in there rent free and i gotta get you out of here we gotta get back to
this now you're in there rent free and i gotta here we go i'm i'm removing you from my head
flexing money no no what are you talking about who is he talking to i'm talking to the one person
that said hey your mic sucks punk and i was like hey you know what you're calling a punk too and
that person got banned they got permanently banned that's a mean thing to say to somebody anyways
where were we dude i can do it for a hundred thousand dollars and that's not happening that's
not how much that cost uh see the problem is if i turn off the noise gate if i turn off all the
compression it it's the microphone if i scream into this mic it still does it with zero uh mixer
zero compression it still does it you said anything no i said i would double what they wrote down
700 this is this mic's not 700 dollars all right silence i have had enough i've had enough of this
we're gonna move on i demand silence from everybody here i demand it here we go oh you
will but you will learn that for yourself i must quiet everybody's silence i must tell you this
each serpent has a spirit to sustain it that grants a great power but also a powerful weakness
discover these weaknesses and you may be able to defeat the serpents
friend i wish i did not have to go but i must if i'm to close the circle and get out of here don't
talk about my fucking microphone ever again he shoved himself up be gone old man i have much to
ask you we will meet again we have already met i think he waves a hand at his cave i have left one
more thing for you in there travel well remember when you walk through the fields of ishtara you
are safe from the serpents but if you do not return to your own time you will never defeat them ishtara
this land my land uh how can i travel between these lands look through the beacons if any have
survived in your time they will hold a little of our ancient light still there was one to the
north of here at least by the river go there reaching over he places his hand on either side
of your head you feel a great lightness entering your body that done he turns and stamps away across
the grass and stamina let's go ds mike ban the word mike from the chat ban the word mike from
the chat i don't want to see it ever again m i see ban it from the chat i never want to see it again
okay let him go he leaves heading west across the plains and fading into the hazy dust that
hangs in the air you muse on what you have seen it seems there is more to the backlands than
there first appeared you are left alone by the cave mouth once more yeah well take some stuff
from the cave you look into the cave again and this time find a strange horn hanging from a hook
on the wall it is ordinately carved from strange twisting shell for the height of leather it is a
gale horn one of very few in existence you lift it down with great care what are they saying over
here are they saying that word that i said not to say how dare they i can't believe they're
actually saying these things m i c k e y m o u s e blow the horn you place the horn to your lips
and blow a note it is a clean and mellow pitched and makes the air stir with echoes it is both
powerful and likely to be valuable should you decide to sell it you pause to look around the
plane then scrub grass stretches away north and west to the east the mountains are shadowing the
sun the whole world seems to have come alive around but surely this magic cannot last you make your
way back to the old road that runs past the rock to the north you catch a glimpse of the tower
shadrach mentioned covered in green ivy west you notice a young tree that surely wasn't there
before sick so this is the tree that we were at before let's go see it now you head out across
the prairie the sun begins to dip heading towards the horizon you swat at pestering flies and
images the dead tree you saw here earlier is now a young strong sapling in its shadow a woman sits
cross-legged with eyes closed you watch the woman for a moment she's breathing in and out slowly
and murmuring under her breath perhaps she's praying around her neck she wears what looks
like a giant's tooth on a leather string i've got a few of those a fleet of long thin birds
swoop and career overhead snatching flies from the steamy air steal the tooth i have enough uh i
got two giants teeth no let's greet all the word oh yeah mike has been banned all versions of mike
good good forever you'll never be able to write that here ever again until tomorrow audio input
device come on give me a break you approach the meditating woman and kick her joe i want to kick
greetings the woman opens one eye then shakes her head sadly you're meant to be over there she
says pointing a little way to the east what do you mean no matter they tell me i will get better
at divination with practice she offers her hand um sure you shake her hand and she laughs how very
formal well met stranger my name is elthira welcome to ishtara the land of peace and plenty
yes will you sit with me a while you sit down on the long grass opposite her she smiles at you
i need to practice my third eye she says tapping what appears to be a small gem stuck to her forehead
perhaps we could play and reaching into a pocket she produces a handful of small stones swindle
stone she looks amused swindle stones my teacher has used that name before but that is not what we
call them here they're mind stones i try to read your thoughts as you try to read mine will you
play you begin to cast upwards to the stars when elthira catches your arm please this is not a
game of magic but a game of inner sense but you can read minds that's unfair no no i am learning
but the sense is weak with me please help me practice what do we what are we putting up stakes
here perhaps if you win i will give you the dice how is that okay okay elthira counts out four
dice each and waves at you to bid scammer uh let's just do something wacky two ones
two fours three fours i don't have any so actually yeah i do four fours do it for people
head north to karema for magic in a view there are the beacons the towers but the real wonder
is lake elclala itself i'm gonna try call this that means you have to have three call it mods
are punishing us dude so one guy has so much power you do just so much power i will i will
look over there and just see like three words think about that think of you just typing
into a keyboard just like three or four words in a row and just pressing enter and it shows
up over here and it derails the stream for like 25 straight minutes you know what i mean think
of the strength you have think of the power that you wield okay two twos uh let's go three twos
and let's call it well you have to have three of them so good luck you're not very good at
seeing the future got two left so you live out here oh i didn't read this part okay you've come
through kare two twos i have three twos it's such a small place chadrak says it will be important
but i doubt it or twos i would not recommend that you visit call okay it might be a cosplay
it's not a cosplay uh two twos three ones um i'll call you on that i don't think you have two ones
you do shit okay it's fine where did the table come from i don't know it's this wood here oh
wow like should i just start with three ones and just have a call yeah three ones call it yeah
sorry okay let me see uh one what do i not have one four impossible wait it's not impossible
if you have that shit i have to call it all right whatever whatever whatever it's easy to win a
two v one it's fine two v ones are simple it's so easy one one shit shit one one three two ones
all right well you have to have a one three ones why would you do that call it yeah unless you're
lying the whole time would you hope you're not you're not i win i win i win don't i althera laughs
you are a challenging mind maybe play again um no i'm done you are a feeble opponent she nods
gathering up the dice she drops them into your palm here take these you'll have better use of
them than i i foresee as much i already have dice though why would i i already have dice
this is for i'll take them you drop the dice into your pack without another word she nods and gets
to her feet i must be going travel well come and visit me if you will she waves in the direction
of the cliff you came down when you enter the backlands but quite why is not clear then she
hurries away the tree is relatively young fresh and strong as though it has been only planted a
few minutes before it is hard to believe this is the same tree that you saw before so tall and so
very dead but the position is the same with the woman gone you look around the plane south and
west the great fault line of the cliff shields out the sky and at its top it seems as dark as
night north the grass stretches away towards a distant flashing line that seems to cut across
the land you turn your attention back to the landscape sweet create a paradox all right so
where are we going back to the road let's go up north i'm gonna head north you walk on across the
grassland until you join an old road the sun is sinking and the sky is turning bruised purple
it will be night soon again already away from the road to the northeast the curious stone tower you
saw earlier stands alone overlooking the river towards the tower towards the tower the road
north uh go yeah the tower i we i'm gonna go to the tower because i want to show people something
interesting you step off the well-paved road and cut across the grassy fields that have somehow
replaced the plane that was here before the sun is now in the lowest quarter of the sky soon it
will be dark you reach the shadow of the tower you spotted while climbing down the cliff its sides
are too smooth to be natural and that there are no stones or brickwork like a gigantic game piece
carved from a single block of stone thick gripweed curls up and around the tower like
wool round a bobbin beyond it a river pushes past look for a door tug the gripweed look at the river
what's available please my father the sweetest chef demands your opinions on cast iron or he
will flame you on twitter okay cast iron is a okay here's the thing about cast iron it's probably
the best cookware but it's kind of a pain in the ass and it's really heavy and it's annoying how
heavy it is to do dope to do zen if i had the jewel i don't can you put it in the dishwasher
i don't think so we can't hear you laugh anymore it gets cut off yeah i'll i'll eventually fix the
cut off thing i have no idea why that's happening that's what that's this mic problem that didn't
happen with the other mic so i gotta figure out why that's happening um what do i do what do i do
what do i do what do i do do do why don't you we're gonna cat look for a door you walk a full
circuit of the tower hoping to find a doorway but there is nothing to see the tower sides are made
of solid stone if indeed it is a tower on the very top something metal glints in the sunshine
listen now you agree well i think the mic sounds fine it's just sometimes i get cut off when i make
a loud screeching noise i think it sounds beautiful right now don't you agree don't you agree agree
with me don't you agree uh tug the gripweed you give the gripweed shoots a sharp tug the plant
is tough as rope and seems to be firmly anchored into the stone of the tower uh look at the glint
craning your neck and squinting against the sun you try to make out what the gleam is
some kind of brass fitting seems to jut out over the side strange to see worked metal and stone
out here wasn't this place supposed to be barren you pause for a while watching the river rushing
past the sound is calming even though it is on the far side that the plains continue then somehow
you must cross climb up climb the gripweed quickly you grab the gripweed and scramble up the outside
of the tower the roots of the thick plant offer plenty of footholds and the ascent is easy enough
soon you are hauling yourself over the battlements onto the top of the tower at the top of the tower
you stand atop the tower the wind across the prairie whips at your hood and the ground seems
like an endless green sea far below remember this game has screen shake don't interrupt me
but the top is not empty indeed there is barely room to stand most of the floor space is taken
up by a large brass contraption that has been built into the middle of the roof look at the
contraption in the tower this tower was clearly built to house the brass contraption in the center
of the turret you look it over with curious interest a large brass cylinder it is set into
the bearing in the center of the tower and protrudes a short way over the battlement it
is rather like one of the chief mages telescopes but why would anyone set such a complex device
out here in the wastes you crouch to look through the cylinder but find you cannot it has no eyepiece
the near end disappears unbroken into the brass mounting of the device the bearing underneath the
cylinder looks as though it might allow the contraption to move furthermore set in the
central dome is an impressive looking blue crystal the blue crystal is not a gem you recognize
it pulses with a small interior glow as though something lived inside you touch the crystal
but as your fingers brush the glass something happens and you feel yourself whipped up into
the air as though catapulted for a dizzy moment you seem to stare down at the entire land of
badubak then a moment later you're back on your feet head reeling but feeling curiously powerful
touch it again you reach out to touch the crystal again only to catch yourself the blue crystal on
the contraption is flashing brilliantly and then suddenly the cylinder ignites with a thick beam
of syrupy light the beam floods across the landscape cutting through the mists and warping
the view like a heat haze the land in the light of the beam has changed it seems the magic you
witnessed earlier is happening again birds wheel and tumble in the air a short distance away
ladies and gentlemen welcome to why this is the coolest potentially of the three episodes it is
two maps on top of each other one in the past and one in the present and you can traverse them
however you see fit get elden ringed so the question is where do i want to point this
down in the water over here to the bridge so i can cross over here straight down over against this
thing uh i could also make this back to normal what do you guys think the cave this is a flop
episode come on it's a flop well let's put it over here first right or we could try to cross it
without it without the water and without the bridge and aim it this way or go across here first and
try to get over there back in time cave cave cave cave all right we'll do the cave i'll point it back
here you adjust the beam around its track sweeping light over the land below the view is now partially
lit with the beam from the tower and a different land appears in its light birds fly gentle wind
stirs pollen in a haze the various towers across the game you aim them that's how you do it there
we go with the beacon blazing away you swing yourself over the battlement once more after an
uncertain moment you find the grip weed and clamor swiftly down back to the tower's base you scramble
down the tower and drop the last few feet to the ground and you leave south of here the grand road
runs from west to east across the plain so that is what we have opened back up is over here this
road is now back in time i think it was a thousand couple thousand years ago let's go back uh the
road west i think we can cross this now you return to the road night falls you should find somewhere
safe to sleep if you keep going through the night you'll be weaker for it especially after so long
walking with an empty belly uh i'm if i can make it i think i can hang out maybe in the cave
you abandon the road and walk across the suddenly grassy field the moon rises filling the world
with thin silver light you crest a low rise and look down across the grass offering something of
a view looking north a wide river splashes spray into the air south you can make out
elthera's tree and east the road makes a loop past the foothills of badobak ridge passing an
unusual double spiked rock formation and that's all there is to see so we're gonna head back
towards the cave and it's really really sweet all right here we go you make your slow way across
the virgin grassland this then is the pit of the backlands it is not as fearsome as you had expected
or maybe the sludge and grime of kare has toughened your resolve indeed in this strange magical light
it is almost pleasant east of the badobak ridge lie the clatterback steps which you must cross
to reach the lake return to the cliff once more you enter the shadow of the cliffs that surround
this place the stars are flooding the sky the grass meadow ends by the cliff base and the
carved stone steps that lead away from the backlands i do need to sleep you find an old fox
hole and scramble inside you've not eaten today but you have no rations so you're gonna have to
just deal with it you lie back and try to forget your troubles you're protected here
and your rest is untroubled by dream you gain considerable stamina and met shadrach the hermit
all right here we go you pull yourself out of your hole and stand up the grass meadow ends by the
cliff base and the carved stone steps that lead away from the backlands go up the steps you haul
yourself onto the first of the gigantic steps that leads up the cliff face halfway up it's been two
days and you're exactly where you started yep but just like a thousand years in the past you clamor
up the carved rock it is painstaking work as every step is about the height of your own body
then about halfway up you pause to rest near the entrance to a cave the cave is clearly inhabited
a cloth hangs across the opening let's go you push back the cloth hanging and enter the cave
inside welcome murmurs a voice from the shadows at the far end of the space who's there i am armed
or greetings don't we we know who lives here didn't l theorist say it was her cave i was
gonna say it um you're enabling him yeah i didn't say it who's there you call waiting for your eyes
to readjust so you can see you hear footsteps patting forward over sand and then a shambling
figure appears a woman with crazed white hair wearing rags of animal skin you i had no idea
i would see you again her voice is familiar from somewhere but you've not met anyone so old since
the witch above the waterfall in the shuman tanti hills do you know me of course you've not changed
a bit or i was so young i was rather in love with you as i recall wait with that she steps
forward once more coming into the thin moonlight at the entrance of the cave you gasp though this
woman is old beyond imagining you recognize her face it is l thera with whom you were playing
dice only hours before how is this possible you demand afraid of whatever curse had befallen her
she laughs it is this not normal where you come from with my people we change this way as time
passes it's quite normal how long ago did we meet you ask horrified by what the answer might be
when we met i was barely 16 and now let me see i suppose i am 113 if you don't count the year
i spent as an eagle she shrugs sadly but welcome all the same perhaps you are thirsty from a corner
of the cave she produces a jug which has been catching water dripping down the stone thank you
she pours you a cup and you drink gratefully and quickly feel thoroughly refreshed it's been
barely any time since i last met you can you tell me about the serpents do you have any provisions
how can i cross the backlands eagle fursona yeah the last time i met i was in oh yeah the last
time we were at that fur con and i was in my fucking eagle costume weren't you a gopher yeah
i was a gopher i thought i knew i knew you from somewhere uh all right can you uh it's been
barely let's get let's get some some lore here it's been barely any time since i last met you
well then the curse on this land affects me but not you perhaps you will be able to leave unlike
the others what others the others all the others that survive the new crown they wander the
wilderness and circle is lost endlessly repeating themselves quite unstuck any provisions uh i do
not eat i sustain myself through passive thought it is a pure existence can you train me if you
have 50 years to spend in practice but i do not have so long i fear
you're a sorcerer are you not i'm a student of magic she nods there is a secret known only to
the most powerful sorcerers in this land the sorcerers of the fortress know it i am sure
but they've tried to keep it a secret would you like to hear it yeah uh if there are nods in
return it is said you see that sorcery is unstoppable powerful the sorcerers tell us
that magic controls the world's very warp and weft that once woven a spell cannot be unwound
the claim is bold but i have learned it is also untrue magic can be undone magic some magic perhaps
all magic can be countered just as the parrying blade can stop a sword i have discovered one such
counter spell already the spell of the healing opposes the enchantment of the fireball i believe
if one can recognize the spell being cast and one knows the form then one can prevent that spell
with the cast of the other counter spells what about the most powerful spells i have not tested
it but yes perhaps even the most powerful spell can be undone as she speaks she draws a shape in
the air a horizontal line a diagonal another line it is the letter z interesting what does
z can you tell me about the serpents seven serpents suddenly her face is alive with activity
and she hobbles back into the depths of her cave returning a moment later clicking her fingers
i have seen this i have seen this in the stars about the seven serpents turns the fate of man
and about that turns the fate of the world i thought the seven serpents were stars
up there the seven serpents are real they are most powerful they're all but indestructible if you see
one of these serpents stranger i believe that you must run i have killed many serpents this is
definitely going in this voice acting sizzle reel true i have killed many serpents not such
as these each of the seven serpents is sliced from the head of a hydra each is bound to an
element of the world fire or air or earth or time she waves a hand that sort of thing and each only
has one weakness what weakness a different weakness in each serpent you must know them to kill them
but to know them is to be killed by them and the whole land turns on this so the whole land must
surely fall woman sits down quite suddenly in a state of some despair they all have pokemon
weaknesses yeah you approach her hoping to console her but she does not react to your presence she
does not even blink the woman murmurs softly to herself look around the cave you glance around
the cave althera has few possessions to speak of but your interest is taken more by the dust
that covers the floor stone dust can be very valuable for magic you scrape together a handful
is worth of stone dust between your palms and slip it into your money pouch for safe keeping
the woman's third eye seems to glow momentarily you step away from the old woman and look about
for where to go next then quite suddenly she grabs your leg but it will take some time to search
come back then her eyes roll up into her skull keep going stepping carefully past the catatonic
woman you make your way further into the back of the cave after a narrow passage it opens out to
reveal a wide space lit by a torchlight the walls are covered with scratched writing curious symbols
and glyphs all in the same shaky hand a little dust trickles from the ceiling be careful here
sus rock turn to stone how probably sus right yeah that's definitely play consulting the
constellations above you bind the spell and a quiet voice enters your mind it assures you
that the cave is quite safe and the woman who lives here can be trusted but it advises you
she will have nothing to tell you until long after she is dead that strange message delivered
the voice fades some of the glyphs on the walls are split you notice like cracked crazed cracks
in the stone you look more closely at the cracks in the walls it is as though the cliff itself is
slowly shearing apart one crack in particular spiders the ceiling and threatens to bring the
roof down looking more closely you see why it is filled with a seam of some soft metal
which is slowly wearing away intrigued by the writing you look over some symbols they're a
mixture of star signs letters numbers and shapes you do not recognize there's no order it is as
though their scribe was desperately trying to capture as much as possible of a dream before
it was forgotten the results are quite indecipherable especially in the near darkness
and barely any space is left only one patch of blank stone near the base of the wall um
probably sun get a closer look right it's free you wind the stars into order around you the
sun jewel starts to give off a magical white glow the glow picks out details in the glyphs
and carvings of the wall letting you read several more clearly the bridge will fall
and the river become a chasm reads one the blood candle must not be lit do not eat from the larder
of a frog okay sounds important uh look at the blank stone you squat down to look at the blank
stone but see nothing it is natural rock only remarkable because every other surface has been
etched or carved above the blank section is drawn a rude outline of a snake followed by a hand and
two vertical lines a son again will this kill us both dig out the metal seam you dig at the metal
seam with your sword it is worthless tin and comes away easily there's a noise like rumbling
thundering the stones above shift perceptively quickly you put your sword away before you bring
the rocks down on your head what else can i do summon darkness so why would i do that no rock
can do sun again uh what does this do you craft the spell and billows of black smoke emerge quickly
from under your cloak the back of the cave plunges into thick darkness the torch on the wall
disappearing completely from view you wait and after a few minutes the spell fades and the fog
dissipates once more it's there for no reason i may as well just have put my back up against a wall
standing straight up standing back flush to the wall heels against the wall head against the wall
and just tilt my head down and then throw it back fucking hard and hit my fucking head against the
wall i just did the set that's what i just did i did the same thing and then just leave i just
took damage for no reason all right you head back out of the cave avoiding a cascade of small stones
from a crack in the ceiling as you go you return from the rear of the cave the light from your sun
jewel pulses twice and fades althera is still here squatting in one corner and rocking quietly
what do the symbols on the walls of the cave mean she shakes her head too much to see not enough
space enough space okay um can i make the space bigger i'm going back here uh how can't do far
log i don't think this if i could i but i don't have the right turn to strike do it turn to stone
i wonder what this does how much stone dust do i have i don't want to waste it i mean i just
picked it up off of her ground i'm gonna use it here all right i get a rewind if it doesn't
do anything i'm gonna rewind if it doesn't do anything
reaching up to the stars you create the magic across a handful of stone dust
and you feel the potential of magic entering your palm you have a few seconds to decide what to do
with it toss the stone dust onto the metal in the crack or toss it into the air you toss the stone
dust at the soft metal that fills the stone crack it bonds instantly and soon the cracks themselves
have turned to stone healing the join whether this will be enough to protect althera's home
you cannot be sure is that a good thing was that good did i prevent her roof from caving in or
something i'm gonna live with that uh althera is still here lost in thought okay all right let's
get out of here the view below is quite giddying you're one step from plunging to the pit floor
okay so we can go we'll go up through here maybe maybe i'll should i go no i'm gonna go check this
out in the uh in the present uh this is this will be the present so we'll go up i could also come
back here in the present time let's do that uh move on so let's let's let's see what happens i'm
gonna take the thing away we'll go back again you carry on across the grassland enjoying the
soft chirping of the insects the mid-afternoon heat floods the valley from behind you a voice says
excuse me this happened already just ignore it you ignore it another mirage like the one you heard
before excuse me are you deaf all right you turn around to find a small boy holding a black face
mask in his hand he pushes it towards you where did you get that you dropped it the boy says
thank you you nod your head and thanks the boy smiles puts the face mask into your hands then
he steps back and waits for something um what do you want like a reward offer him a reward
you look in your pack for a suitable reward um here here's three gold okay the boy smile grows
wide at the site thank you by thruff i'm glad i followed you i mean that i was here you know
what i mean he puts the gold into his pocket you squat down onto your ankles to be more at
the boy's level he's clearly local and is likely to know a lot about the area where are you from
you ask the boy kare but i run errands all the way to tin pang sometimes where's tin pang across
the marsh over the bridge near the lake you can run there in almost a day the idea that this boy
can cross the entire of the backlands is startling this is the most dangerous land you know the boy
is starting to look twitchy what do you know of the seven serpents nothing sounds like one of
shadrach stories the boy hops from foot to foot so you know shadrach of course i do everyone knows
shadrach he's a brute and beats children if they make too much noise near his cave um he seems most
ferocious he hates children he says they're all thieves and villains i have to go now i have to
go where i'm going back home before they close the gates with a final nod he in the other direction
across the gates with a final nod he goes in the other direction across the grass it is only later
you realize he somehow swiped the claw well guess what why did you do that if you i that skull cap
is so important do we live with it and just not have the skull cap anymore do i have to live with
some of these things and he took three gold i gotta stop being nice to people and just if it
says punch in face immediately punch in face if it's just oh a punch person in face done punch
person in face i'm going this way yeah fuck that i'm going over here i know rewind rewind rewind
rewinds when he said he was from kare that should have hinted that he was a thief yeah that's true
i forgot i haven't played it in a while okay you carry on tramping across the endless waste and the
grass turns to dust as you go the mid-afternoon heat floods the valley the sunlight turns the
dust of the plane to a bitter yellow as you walk you come across an open area dotted with 20 or 30
small holes you pull a goblin tooth from your pack and throw it on the ground casting you spell
across it the tooth erupts into a column of smoke and a moment later a goblin warrior is standing
in front of you go investigate the holes you direct it to investigate the holes in the ground
it salutes waddles over to the nearest and peers down a moment later a jet of hot steam vents
through the earth knocking the goblin high up into the air it howls in pain as it flies up and then
winks out of existence a moment later the jet also knocks something free from the hole which you
pick up it is a single polished giant's tooth with a hole drilled at the top part of a pendant perhaps
you pick it up and put it in your pack a flash of something catches your eye but by the time you
turn your head whatever it was has gone uh uh well i nice job goblin i ain't looking in the holes
that not doing that gob for yob got an extra tooth all right onto the bridge the sun is beginning
to lower the air begins to cool you journey across the open plane approaching a curious
black stroke that seems to have been drawn across the land as you get closer you see it for what it
is a gash in the land thousands of fathoms deep the road comes to a stop at the edge of a wide
fissure in the ground and the ruins of an ancient bridge the wind roars along the crack in the ground
in front of you like a mockery of a river look down into the crevice you creep to the edge of
the crack to look down into it it seems to drop for miles besides plunging like a waterfall of rock
the bottom is lost in mist and the rock walls seem quite sheer i wonder what will happen
oh look at the bridge there was once a bridge here the road runs up to it and a few stones push out
over the yawning abyss but as long ago tumbled into ruin and now it does nothing but give you
an impressive place to look down suddenly you see movement at the edge of the fissure
some kind of long spike reaches up over the edge bends and hooks into the ground closely followed
by another whatever it is kill it a nap speed stench talk all languages all right we're going
to toss we're going to talk all languages it's an earwig grabbing the wig from your pack you pull
it onto your head and weave your spell but nothing happens this spell works only on intelligent
creatures and not animals wait wait no no no no no go back i want to talk i want to talk to the
earwig i actually i really genuinely i want to talk to the earwig okay okay okay all right it's
not it's uh it's a different spell yap is all talk with animals there we go not languages yap
grabbing the wig from your pack you pull it onto your head and weave your spell the creatures
clicking legs and rubbing jaws are suddenly transformed into words soft flesh don't run from
me come to me i am beautiful as it talks the creature keeps coming it is a long six-legged
bug with hooked jaws and a deadly looking sting the size of the one you sliced from the back of
the manticore only days ago so just run run for it you waste no time but turn tail and run but
the creature whatever it is is out of the crack and the ground and coming for you well i wanted
to go back here anyway i wanted to go this way anyways you hurry your way down the old road and
the bug scuttles along behind you running along inside the inside of the fissure to keep up
it must be able to run much faster than you across the rock as it appears a moment later
directly before you jaws wide open the creature raises its long sharpened jaws and seems to
thicken its armor plated hide you steal your courage at the site this is a lynch bug a ferocious
creature that will be hard to defeat in battle it climbs inside of your ear yeah i could do law
fireball i don't have access to jig wall i'll do law law is expensive but it usually works really
well you weave the constellations into a pattern around you reaching out to take control of the
lynch bug's thoughts its legs lock up and it stiffens it is waiting for your instructions
walk the bug into the fissure or ride the bug's back ride the bug you bring the bug close to you
and clamor up onto its back it is uncomfortable but affords a tremendous view of the landscape
order the bug across the fissure or ride the bug south we gotta go go across right you order the
bug northwards to the edge of the fissure and ready it to jump but although you control the
creature's will you cannot override its most basic instincts instead of jumping the fissure
it leans out over the side and begins to climb down the rock face into the depths of the canyon
hold on you cling onto the bug's antenna for life as it turns vertical there's no way to get off
oh god down the canyon side the bug continues it's inexorable climb down the canyon side
it is approaching a large gray brown mucusy something built onto the side of the rock wall
it's a lynch bug nest and as you approach you see it is crawling with hundreds more lynch bugs the
thought occurs to you that these ones will not be under the influence of your spell uh should i hide
order to climb up or crouch low against the sides go in the hive and hang out that's kind of funny
all right i'm gonna crouch you hunch low against the lynch bug shell hoping to perhaps go unnoticed
meanwhile the bug reaches the nest and squirms its way in through a tight sticky entrance way
inside the nest everything falls into darkness except for the echoing clicks of a hundred
thousand lynch bugs and they're young this is fucked should i pray to the ape or just wait
but wait you cling on and wait the bug squirms along a narrow passage almost scraping you off
its back there's nothing you can do but wait the bug enters a wide chamber presumably burrowed deep
into the rock itself you hear these sounds you're in a wide chamber chewed out from the rock of the
canyon wall and the center sprawls the vast corpulent body of the lynch bug queen your spell
has now entirely worn off uh it's the time for the ape to come and help wait you hold on
hoping against hope for some means of escape the bug you are riding bows low to its queen
and one of her majesty's 300 eyes settles on you she reaches out a clawed limb and strokes
the side of your cheek we have to bow bow to her you bow your head low to the queen's gaze
but you cannot tell if she understands the gesture the queen raises two of her arms and
intones a few words a moment later the clicks and rubbing of her front legs transforming
impossibly into human speech greetings you are the anilander uh i um what if that's bad no
um i am you reply surprised by this turn of events good my enchantment will not last long
you stare in disbelief the queen's raised arms make it clear what is happening she has cast a spell
a variant of the rap spell no doubt um your majesty is most powerful should i cast something
what can i do if this bug can cast a spell then that must mean you are able to as well
you raise your arms to the stars only to have them pinned by the lynch bug you rode on i am pleased
you have come i have expected hold on let's do this i am pleased you have come i expected my drone
to eat you by accident your drone was sent to get me i am pleased it did not as am i but you are the
one the serpent slayer of legend serpents what do you mean what do you mean serpents you ask
wondering at what this creature knows the seven serpents of the archmage from an orifice in my
underbelly i'm going to pull out a claw and a gob of goo this is monarch oil smeared upon the serpent
of water that swims in lake il klala and it will shrivel like a burned creature she drops the goo
into your hands holy shit really uh thank you you nod and place the goo into your pack the queen
clashes together her antenna which you understand as a nod one more thing do not forget there her
remaining words are lost into clicks and scrapes and wet squirts as her spell fades no i gotta
remember do remember what your majesty i can't cast all right i'm gonna i'm gonna bow once more
you bow your head to the queen the lynch bug who brought you here scoops you up and clamors out of
the nest that's pretty cool where the fuck are we oh it marks it on the map um i gotta be really
honest with you i don't think i've ever seen that that's the first time i've ever seen that
i've never seen that happen that was cool all right out of the out of the fissure the bug clamors
up over the canyon's edge and drops you into the dirt with a final nod it turns and strides away
call a thank you you call out a thank you to the bug but it is already gone you look around once
more a few birds swoop in and wheel in the crevice turning circles that are way below you and yet
still high up in the air we got earwig friends right that was cool all right um we gotta see i
i'm gonna jump across this right this makes the most sense to me or uh teleport but i don't have
the item um create a force field i guess i get hurt floating is definitely it makes the absolute
most sense look you cast the spell lightening your body weight to the mere fraction of normal
jump you eye up the width of the gap cautiously it is a long distance made harder to judge by the
featurelessness of the far side you'll probably be unable to make it at least not without aid
so taking a short run up you race for the edge of the fissure and hurl yourself out into space
your feather lightweight means you hardly fall but it also means the speed of your run-up is
quickly lost you fall gently and calmly for a long long way into the featureless chasm
then with no warning the spell ends and you speed up nothing else happens for some time
and then when finally something does occur it is mercifully brief so i wily coyoted off the edge
come on how far is this chasm all right well i think this gotta be a way to get over there
i could fix the bridge with the tower there's no way for me to get over there from here
cause slowness i have an idea i'll cast slowness on myself you cast you cast the enchantment but
without any other creatures around the only target is yourself you feel no different once the spell
is taken hold but the clouds overhead seem to double their haste jump across you eye up the
width you're probably unable to make it without a let's go taking a short slow motion run-up
you stride for the edge of the fissure and hurl yourself out into space the chasm whisks away
below you at a comical speed and the wind that batters at you is not enough to slow you down
a moment later you collide into the ground on the far side in a pile of scratches and scrapes what
i made it wait the slow motion jump works that's so stupid i was just in slow motion the whole time
the world moves faster around you okay i did an action movie jump well shit i'm kind of stuck over
here you slowed your own physics down i lost a lot of health and after crossing the bridge that is
where we're going to call it so i'm going to ask you the question the question is do you want to
keep going with this you still want to go through sorcery i'm going to put it in a little i'm going
to put it in a box for a week or so though because there's a lot happening obviously in the next few
days uh let's go over a little bit of schedule here i don't know the details of what's happening
tomorrow i will obviously talk about them but at six p.m tomorrow at the very least on myth's
channel i'm going to be doing a black ops 2 event with a bunch of people go look at myth's twitter
i i don't even want to spoil it for you i want you to go see the teams
so i may be live tomorrow at six i may not be we will see
call of duty black ops 2 that's right and then saturday i won't be i will not be live on friday
saturday's green screen movie night part two and then we'll do the mortuary assistant on
maybe one maybe monday or tuesday i still want to play more multiverses as well
and i i this i gotta do a sponsor tweet for multiverses today i don't want to forget to do
that but i want to play multiverses i just want to play it it wouldn't be sponsored it would just be
me playing it play stray i don't know maybe but yeah that's probably the plan is we got this black
ops 2 event tomorrow um i don't know the exact streaming setup but again at the very least go
to myth's channel uh myth i myth is on youtube now so go to myth's channel on youtube that's
where uh it will be when is baseball august 19th stop bossing me around yeah uh i'll see you tomorrow
black ops 2 i'm going to get my ass kicked it's going to be hyper embarrassing but i will try
green screen movie night saturday mortuary assistant monday or tuesday
and then we'll go back to the backlands uh at some point next week after we do that after this next
week here baseball i'm going to get ready for baseball so it's going to be a lot of lead time
that i need to do up to that that's going to be fun a lot of cool stuff going on yeah we'll keep
going because obviously 97 98 percent of you said yeah there's a lot to see still and that's it
thanks for watching everybody we'll see you tomorrow maybe if you're not going to
check out the black ops 2 thing and we'll definitely see you on potentially saturday
if you come to the green screen movie night part two that's going to be starting probably around
four or five pm pacific i want to do it at night because i think it's a movie night it's better
that way and that's it are there is there a chance for a third movie night um i'm not going to say
yes but i'm not going to say no either it really depends on how much we can get through
it really depends on how many submissions i want to show because after saturday night we'll have
probably have gotten through about 300 or 400 of them probably 300 something of them and it
really depends on the quality of the submissions that are after that how many how much time i want
to give to it right but we'll see we'll see yeah see you tomorrow goodbye thanks for watching see
you good night good luck to whatever you're doing call your mother you know the deal see
you for more sorcery next week take care guys see you soon