So what is going on everybody? Welcome to FaceCamp Fortress Team, Face Fortress Camp 2.
This is something I did a while back and I want to do it again just because I feel like it.
So let's see, let's see, what do I got right now? Default loadout. I'm just going to run with whatever I got.
We got the back burner, the flare gun, and the default axe. What? Why is that on?
Oh, where you going? On blue, this is on bad water as well.
But yeah, I just felt like doing this again because it's been quite a while since I've done this.
I think it was like Thanksgiving. Yeah, it was like Thanksgiving since I did this last.
FaceCamp Fortress 2. Oh, this guy's got no idea. Back burner, back burner.
Let's go this way. Get that crate, get that, get that crate. Oh, no!
Oh my god, I'm still alive. They have two sentries like stuffed in one little area down there. That's ballsnip.
You know what? F the pyro. We're going Demoman. I'm going to take that stuff out right now.
Hey, ready? If I don't take this out right now, if for some reason I don't kill all those sentries, I will...
That's a spy. No, it's not. I will swallow a whole egg.
A whole egg I will eat if I don't take those out like right now.
Like I'll crack the egg and then crack it into my mouth. What? What?
No, I don't want to eat an egg. I do not want to eat an egg. I got to eat an egg. I got to eat an egg on camera now.
I don't have any eggs here with me, so we'll have to do that in a different subscriber video.
I shot five stickies down right on that sentry. Oh, it was a glitch. It doesn't count. It was a glitch.
No, I'm just kidding. I still haven't gotten that haircut I was supposed to get a long time ago in my last vlog.
That just didn't happen. Get out of town, buddy. Get out of town, buster. That's a spy up there.
Alright, seriously. Come on now. Okay, it goes down then. I shoot five stickies down there and it doesn't go down.
Come on. Oh, he's trying to build another one, huh? Nope. Oh god, they're spamming up here right now.
Is there another one down? Aww. Come on, let's cap that cock. Cap it, baby. Cap it.
So let me just hold on. Break. You know, I'm going to medic. Let's go medic with the...
What do I got? Syringe gun, critscreek, and the ubersaw. Take the damn critscreek off. Let's go with the medigun, baby.
I think we're going to cap it. I want the medigun. What the hell is going on? There we go.
I don't even think this is necessary. I think we're going to win. Maybe not.
Excuse me, sir. We got a cock to push over there. Mr. Jokester. Oh, we did it. We won.
Oh my god. Hey, we won. Maybe I'll do like another round.
So I have something to talk about in my next commentary. My next real sit-down commentary.
It's about something very, very important. Well, not really important. I just want to get your guys' viewpoints on it.
I'll save the topic for... I'll probably do it in two days. So what's today? Wednesday? Tuesday?
So yeah, it'll probably be up by like Friday or Saturday. But it's a very important topic.
And it's something that really made me very, very sad in the last couple days. And we'll discuss it when that comes up.
But in the meantime, I'm going to uber this pyro. And we're going to do absolutely nothing, probably.
Get him. Get him. Get him. Get him. Flame thrower. Flame. Flame thrower. Oh yeah. Denied. Denied. Denied.
Oh god. Woohoo. Run into that. Run into it. You bastard.
What do we got back here? Spencer? Sentry? Good. I can build it up on you, dude.
Come on, come on, come on. Only a minute and 47 seconds and we win this damn game. I refuse to lose. Come here. I got you.
You know what? For the remainder of the time, I'm just going to go battle medic. See if I can't do something fun.
Get out of town. Where is he? I'm bumping into him. There he is. Come here, you bastard.
Oh my god. I'm sorry. I'm being a terrible medic. I know. I'm sorry. I apologize.
You don't have to eat that sandwich. You got me, buddy. I'm your friendly neighborhood pocket medic.
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. All right. Fine. You want to do that? I'll just smash you.
Oh, now I got a crits. Now I got a crits. All right. Drop it like it's hot, man. Down here. Here we go.
Shavoink. Get him. Ah, damn it. Oh, it's over. No, no. Do your right.
I can't talk over chat because if I do that, my game crashes because I have like three things going.
I got the webcam going. I got my microphone going and I have wraps going.
So like my entire world just takes like a dump on itself if I hit V. It happens all the time. It's not cool.
I think we got this in the bag, though. I think we do. I think this is all she wrote.
But yeah, thanks everybody for watching. I think this is going to be it. I will see you guys all next time.
Hold on. I actually can't say that yet because they just got two people on the car. Oh my god.
I'm here to save the day as a doctor. Get back out there. Over time. This is not good.
I was about to say my outro. We did it. I didn't get on the scoreboard. That's a bunch of baloney.
But yeah, guys, thank you so much for watching. We really do appreciate it. I will see you all next time.
So peace and take care, everybody.