Hey what's up? What's up? Today's the day. Final Fantasy 16 is out! I've actually been waiting
for this. I had a lot of fun with the demo. I'll give you a quick little update of what the plan
is before we get started. What about where's the smurf report? Well, what the fuck is that?
Why did somebody just electrocute the chat with one... was it a euro? What was that?
Is there... why is there money? Wait, what are these different...
is there one euro at the top? Is there a new money thing? Do you see this? What is this?
Hype. Derma Go. Why is it gone? When are you gonna take the dino quiz? What on earth is happening?
Okay, this is weird. I feel like I'm... I feel like I'm playing a like mobile game and I have to like
press these to get them. If I don't touch these at the top, I feel like I don't get them.
And then they disappear. So if I don't click them, do they go away?
Okay, I just to make sure everyone's aware of this. I think you're giving real money.
Just to make sure you're clear on that. You guys are giving real money right now. I don't know.
I don't know what this is. But just be aware. This is you're spending real money. What is it?
Okay. Well, interesting. I think they know. Play Kingdom Hearts. Hold on. Hold on a second.
I think it's bugs in your brain making you see things. If this is... If this sticks around,
I'm gonna have to... I'm gonna make... I think I might have to make a few changes.
Does it... Can I... How do... All right. Well, this is interesting. All right. Anyways, hello.
Welcome, everybody. Today, I'm gonna be playing Final Fantasy 16. Sponsored stream. Thank you to
Square Enix for sponsoring this stream. I'm very excited to play it. I don't know if it was...
Probably wasn't hard to tell at the end of the demo, but I genuinely think this is gonna be
really fun. And here's the best part. The best part is we don't have to do the demo again.
You start right from where we left off in the demo. Are you gonna do Next Fest? I am. I'm gonna...
So here's the thing. I was thinking about doing half the stream Final Fantasy and then half the
stream as the Next Fest. But I'd rather just do it this weekend and play Sorcery this weekend.
And okay. Hold on a second. Let me just do one thing real quick. Where the hell is your face?
My face is hanging out. Sorcery needs its own stream. We'll figure it out. Don't worry. Don't
worry. So wait, these are pinned... These are pinned messages and they stay up longer depending
on... Well, I just want to make it really clear. I am not clicking on any of these. So just to be
aware, they stay up longer depending on how much money you give. I just want to make sure
everyone's aware. I'm not... I haven't clicked on any of them. I think the point is like I'm
supposed to click on these and be like, oh, this person has a chat pinned up here. They're all
gone by the time I click on them. I'm not gonna click on any of these. I just want to make sure
you know that. Well, I'll click on this one. This one says the CCO of Offbrand calls hype chats.
What? So I've said my thing. I'm not gonna click on any of these.
I'm sorry, but like maybe I don't know. Let me... Let's just go through today and I'll figure out
if I want to keep that or not. Okay. Okay. Streamers, you can't tell how much they're really
spending. Yeah. Some of them are just different currencies. I feel like I'm like Forex trading
in my chat room. Like a Canadian and then we have like English pounds and we all... I feel like I'm
trading up here like Forex. Well, all right. So that's a feature now, just so you know.
Let's make it really clear. I just said it. I ain't reading any of this. So just to let you know,
I know we have this policy where I don't really read anything that comes in monetarily, but that
also applies to here. I'm not gonna read any of these. Just to let you know, I have to be
consistent and I got to be transparent with you. There you go. Okay. I appreciate it nonetheless,
but thank you. But let's, let's go. Let's go. I ain't reading all that. No, not an,
I ain't reading all that. I just, I ain't reading all that. Wait, wait a second. Hold on.
You cannot opt out of hype chat as we wanted to, but you can set a minimum. You can set a minimum
of a hundred dollars. Okay. Well, let's just, I'm just going to leave it as it, but you know,
make it like, I don't know. I can't make, I, you know what? We're going to have to, I think.
All right. Just, it's a new feature. It's there. Let's just play. Let's play. I got a sponsorship
for you to do right now. You know what I'm saying? Set it at like a billion dollars. So nobody can do
it. You must read them. No, now run ads. No, I'm not doing anything. All right. I'm, I have a,
let's go. It'll, it'll play out for a little bit. It's all right. I appreciate it nonetheless,
but I ain't reading all that. All right. There you go. If, if, if we need to make it a little
higher, so it's not spammed, we will, but it's a new feature, I guess. Cool. Okay. Anyways,
Final Fantasy 16. Wow. Wowee. Here it is. Get to pick up right where we left off in the demo.
I'm excited. I cannot wait to hear that battle music like a thousand more times. Yes, it is an
ad. This is hashtag ad. This is sponsored by Square Enix. Keep that in mind, but I'm having
a blast in the demo. It seems like I'm, I don't know. I, I'm, I think this is going to be pretty
gosh darn fun. All right. You guys ready? Let's go. You want to, you get a face game if you're good.
You'll get a face game if you're good. Only if you're good. All right. So I'm gonna,
it's probably this one here. What about the Super Mario RPG remake? Huh? What are you talking about?
What are you talking about? He's making stuff up. It's real.
I like when people make up. It's real. Uh, no, that's cool. I'm glad they didn't just
port it. Uh, I'm excited. Hopefully it's really good. I'm looking forward to it. That's, I mean,
I feel like collectively everybody that has that in their top 10 favorite games of all time,
I think everybody just kind of had a sigh of relief when they did that first little intro
when it was like, okay, this is a port. And then they did the, wait a minute. Here comes the
magical star that's flying over and turning everything to 3D. I think everyone was like,
oh, okay. Oh, okay. This is real. Yeah. Uh, I would, I would be lying to you if I didn't tell you.
I was not excited for that because it seems cool. All right. Ready? I am excited. If you don't know
the story of Final Fantasy 16, uh, you probably have to go watch the VOD, but the game is officially
out. It's out right now. It launched today. PlayStation five. Let's freaking go. Additional
content is now available for redemption. These items can be claimed from the system tab. Ooh.
All right. Let's do it. This should pick up right with the demo left off. Yeah. It'll pick up 13
years after the demo. Wait, wait a minute. Wait, wait, wait. Is it correct? Welcome back. Sorry.
What's our situation? Let's just say Shiva and Titans little spat hasn't made things any easier.
Lord check. No, wait. Good call. Let's just get a quick little rundown. Wait, what? Lord check.
Wyvern. Oh, that's okay. All right. I remember. I remember. Yes. Yes. But at the very end,
we were, we were a soldier now. All right. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Okay. All right. Good thing.
This exists. I swear. I'm telling you. Slave soldier for the Holy empire of Sam Brickay. Now
in his 13th year of servitude, drafted as a frontline infantryman, the magical might granted
him by the blessing of the phoenix quickly saw him promoted to an elite squadron of assassins.
He was assigned the moniker by which he is now known. Interesting. Okay. I am really glad this
exists because I was going to just ask why the fuck is this guy's name not Clive? I was like,
what happened? Oh, right. Bastards. Okay. Unit of Imperial army assassin tasked with taking the
head of the iron kingdom's dominant warden of ice and vessel of the icon Shiva. Got it. Go. And
it's as you thought, the crusaders have sounded the retreat. Then we follow.
We need to change your title. Well, if we return without Shiva's head, our fate will be no different
from Beasts. I'll take my chances with the iron blood. At least then I might die fighting
after you do. That is the misleading title right now. No, it's not. No, it's not. When I get
control, I tweeted that too. Not today. Then it's settled. No dying. Now, if you don't mind,
we have an army to chase. Go. All right. A chance encounter. The iconic abilities,
scarlet cyclone and heat wave for the phoenix are now available for acquisition and upgrade
on the abilities tab in the main menu. Do not forget that once acquired new abilities must
be equipped on the gear and icons tab. How do they expect us to kill something that can do this?
They don't. Only the girl holding its leash. They now it's not misleading anymore.
I have to make sure my tweet and my title makes sense.
Should I keep the, um, this control scheme? I feel like if it now is time to learn how to
do the other one or go to the, um, what is it? Type B, right? What sprint does sprint, right?
Ooh, do type B. It's going to be way better in the long run. Uh huh. So I want to do
type B. It is on type B. Okay. All right. So that this is circle is evade. I'm going to take a
little bit of extra getting used to it because I did the tutorial with type A. So it might take
me like a little bit to get used to it, but it's probably better. Like you said, in the long run,
we have a face game. We've been good. No, no, not yet. What is sprint or run? I could lock on his
Elvon cycle. Icons is triangle. R2 is magic on this one. Square is ready. Iconic ability.
No face game. You have to wait. I'm waiting for your birthday. Your birthday is in like 20 minutes.
Your birthday is in 20 minutes. Okay. What's your iconic ability? Being able to go like this.
For a long time and hold the note. Titan has knocked the fight out of our iron blood and
the rest of them can't be the main host. Wait. Our fortunes have turned sergeant. It's her,
the dominant. Are you certain the crystalline orthodox is a backwards faith for a backwards
people in the iron kingdom? They teach the dominance are unclean aberrations born of
blackest sin. Only their priests are allowed to perform the rights of priming.
And I see many. Change it live to Wyvern if you want in the title.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Let's go.
Holy shit. Nobody messes with the bastards.
Okay. Hey, what? Wait, what?
Understood. Should have done a lower check. I got to get the controls down. So there's like a
parry. There's a parry. There's a, okay. That's the magic. Magic is if I want to do the,
sorry, I am, I am hyping up right now. Okay. So that's if you want to do the combo
and then holding instead of it's where and then what is it? What button is that? Is it up?
What button is that? Okay. That's our two. That's our one. All right. How do I do this
phoenix shift when it comes to the new control scheme? Lock on. What? Oh, okay. L2 is phoenix
shift. All right. Got it. Oh, shit. What does that say? Shit. Shit. What does that say?
What? Why did that happen? They're having an auto update. Whatever. I'm going to get like
ticks from mom up there apparently. All right. I gotta, I gotta learn, I gotta learn to get my
controls back. I got a whole new control scheme. All right. You know what? You know, you know what?
I think I'm going back. I think I'm going back. I got used to it. I'm going back. Yeah, I'm going
back. I know. I know. One's like, no, no, no, no, but I got used to it in the demo and I got to use
it. Yep. She's not even fully primed. Shit. All right. It's square and triangle, square and
triangle. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. It's just a good warmup. It's a good warmup.
Do I have enough heals? Yeah, I'm good. Oh shit. All right. We're good. Okay. I went to type A,
then I went to type B and I went back and I went forward. I got it. I got it. I figured it out
quick. Can you dodge roll? It is a dodge. Okay. Frozen tier crafting. Very nice. I probably
shouldn't lower check. Moves are cool. They are. I want to look at the upgrade tree. Is she dead?
I don't think so. Well, what are you waiting for? Oh, we, okay. We don't need to lower check. I know.
What are you here? Bloody do it then. What the? Jesus. Company Wyvern. You've dodged that? Yeah,
a hundred percent. What the hell are you doing? Get your ass over here and help me with these
bastards. We're the bastards. Which ones do you mean? Sorry Jill. All right. Let's go. What is
wrong with you Wyvern? Dominant. I know her. All right. It's L1 is lock on. Yep. There we go.
That's what I'm looking for. Is there a better way to kind of flick between? Okay. It's bright
stick. Let me get the dodge down again. That was my kill. That's done. Won't ask you again, Wyvern.
Take her head so we can be done with this. I can't. I won't. We have to fight? Betray the holy empire?
Betray? I don't recall ever pledging allegiance to your emperor. My service may have been bought
with this brand, but not my loyalty. I just fight to survive. Really? We have to fight you?
Are you dead? Wait, what is going on?
All right. I gotta, I gotta, I gotta play now. I gotta play.
You're not going to hit me. You'll never hit me. Top it off.
Did you think you'd get tired of just wearing it that many times?
I've always had a name. And I've not forgotten it. It's Clive.
Oh. Oh.
Oh, this is fucking fun.
Cool. All right. See, I got it. Need to take a vinegar. So
level up. Nice. All right. You've been good. You've been good. I'll turn it on.
You've been good. Although I didn't do this. Ooh, the whole crafting system.
Actually, let me, let me turn this off for a sec.
Got seen. Your mom did a nice job with your hair today. Okay. Okay, dude.
Damn. Constant conflict. And dog.
We need to lower check. We actually kind of do. All right. This is great because we actually
really need this. Uh, let me, let me, I need to do something very quickly. Give me one second.
I need to. Okay. That's actually all right. Oh, there we go. So make sure that looks all right.
I need to make sure my webcam is delayed a little because it will not be synced up with the game.
Now it should be. Hi. Hi there. Uh, where's a good place for the camera? Like up here.
I'll just gonna be tiny camera. And by the way, it's going off unless you're good.
All right. So we got, let's see. Right. Dominant Shiva and Clive's childhood friend
in the depths of the Nysa Defile. The two came to blows at the orders of the armies that enslaved
them. That should be good. Too much. Delay is too much. Really? Shouldn't be. Should match up pretty
well. That's not, that's bad. It's really badly desynced. Wait, what? Really shouldn't be. It's
not even close. How about now? If I go like this. How about now? No? It's by like 500 milliseconds.
Well, the face cam's going off. All right. Okay. I remember this. Holy empire. Tiamat is the leader
of the elite assassin squadron to which Wyvern is assigned. The bastards. I'll figure it out at the
break. Or in like 10 minutes. I don't know. Just, just, just hang out. Just chill. I'll fix it.
Okay. And this is Branded Soldier. Bears forced to fight for the nations that enslaved them.
Able to cast powerful magics yet entirely disposable. They're often placed on the front
lines in battle or assigned to highly dangerous scouting or assassination missions. All right.
You put the ice queen on her back. No doubt. But you'll have to work harder if you're to claim
this price. My lady, the thunder. We'll be hearing more soon enough. Always worth
fucking snakes it. Gather the men. We have work to do. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. All right.
Yeah. Cause I have to delay my microphone by 800 milliseconds to go with the capture of the
PlayStation 5. So I have to delay my webcam by 800 milliseconds, but apparently that's not matching
up. Why is your setup so bad? It's, it's fine. And who's this fine hound I see before me?
A fine hound who saved your life. That's who? Toggle. Hi. His name is Toggle. You two acquainted?
Well then, you won't mind taking him off my hands. Funny. I'd always pictured you as more
the chocobo type. Clive Rosfield. Can you do this voice? No. Come now. Fleetus flame,
fierce as a wildfire. That there was the blessing of the phoenix.
I'd heard rumors that you'd survived, but I never paid them much heed.
You could definitely do it with filters. And if I drop my pitch down. Calm down. I didn't
come all this way for your handsome mug. Now her on the other hand, she seemed worth muddying my
boots for. None the worse for her. Still might be best to get a second opinion. Crack her up.
Who's that? Not another step. I mean it. Well, I'm not about to leave her here.
Not one with a warm bed waiting. It's all right. You're welcome to join us.
You do want to help her, don't you? Lord Shack, we know who these people are.
Sid, if we aren't back soon, Nana will have our heads. I'll explain everything once we're back
at the hideaway. Come on. We'll get some more introductions.
You should lore check your microphone and see if the delay can get fixed.
Okay, cool. The hideaway. Don't worry. I will lore check a million more times.
How much further now? But we're in the middle of it.
Keen eye. The blights suck this place dry. Meaning no trees, no birds, and no magic.
But it also means no neighbors. The last place anyone would think to look.
That was weird. What just happened in the corner? Are we good? One, two, three, four.
What are you hearing first? Do you hear me and then my movements or do you see movements then
hear me? It's very important. Your audio is coming in a second or two before I move.
Okay, then let's fix it. This place. These are fallen ruins.
Is this better? Two, one, two. And it keeps the black from our lungs.
But how do you survive without magic? How does anyone? You must be starving.
We grow them here. Believe it or not.
Suit yourself. You're back.
It's a little bit of a big bite of an apple. This is the dominant.
How cold since we found her? I was hoping you might give her a look over.
All right. Good. Get her upstairs.
Don't fret about Karen. I've taken care of her fee.
All of it. She's the best healer this side of the belt.
You have nothing to worry about. Have a look around.
So do you ever think about getting into voice work?
You should probably say, do you ever think about reading some of the plays that we have
in front of an audience? Hide, hide away.
All right. So we get a map. Detail map of your current area.
Main scenario destinations are marked with that. That's a map. Cool.
Oh, and I know exactly. Is it? I know exactly where I need to go.
Oh, I can just mark it too. How are we doing? We all right?
One, two, three. Better. Perfect. Yeah. All right.
And he's a soldier then. Be surprised if he wasn't.
I'd have some around here. Blacksmith?
That is not perfect. I'll get it better.
Is it still are you hearing it still or is it are you hearing me first and then
my face moving or is it how is it? How bad is it?
It's fine. It's fine. Just working on a pet project of mine.
She's not about biting the hand that feeds you. All right.
I was hoping we might try and solve the mystery of poor Clive Rusfield,
a bearer of the San Brecois Imperial Army sent behind enemy lines
with orders to wait until it turned into a brawl, then slip the dominant throat in the chaos.
I didn't know it was her. How could it be?
And so to save her neck, you slit your sergeants,
then set your sights on the hills, conveniently forgetting how the Empire deals with deserters.
Because with that on your chop, my friend, we both know you won't be getting far.
Without you, I mean, you're going to help me, though. Of course.
You've fallen a long way, Rusfield. You look like a pickle today.
It's fine. A lot of it said that I'm a poor host.
What do you mean to do with her? Do with her?
Why nothing? Her life is her own now. If I wanted to use her, do you think I'd be talking to you?
All I want to do is help. Dominance like her. Branded like you.
Of course, the realm doesn't approve, which is why we live in a cave.
I want candles like that. And it's also why we need help
from Branded who know one end of a sword from the other.
What say you, Clive? Will you join us?
Sid, was it? I trust that you'll do right by Joe.
But until my brother is avenged, I must walk my own path.
Avenged?
Are you typing? I'm I'm watching. I'm just I'm asking a quick question.
The phoenix's evil swing. Another room I've proven true.
I only stand here today because of Joshua.
13 years I've waited for this chance. I've slept in filth.
Junk from a gutter. Killed more men than I can count.
You're right. The Empire will not suffer a deserter.
This will be my best opportunity. My last.
Which is why you should join us.
I told you I'm not-
Interested, I know.
One of my scouts sent word there's a group of branded fugitives north of here,
in the Imperial village of Lostwing.
Among them is one he believes to be a dominance of fire.
Is he certain?
What say we go and ask him?
This doesn't mean I'm joining you.
Let's make ready then.
You'll find everything you need down in the main hall, as well as a few things you don't.
Sid's solar. Visit the main hall.
On this way.
I wonder, should I like, buy anything?
How much money do I even have?
Your hair looks red.
This is the full game. Full game came out today.
We picked up at the end of the demo.
On PS5.
To the forge it is then.
Do we actually get to upgrade stuff?
Oh wait, no, hold up. You'll be needing this.
Blackthorn won't take no notice of you otherwise.
Might not anyway.
Somebody said it looks like your room is upside down?
What are you talking about?
My room is not upside down?
Why would I even need to address that?
Of course I'm not, I'm sitting here.
I'm not here to talk.
I'll be accompanying you.
Imagine defending that no, I am not in fact upside down.
How do you even argue that?
For all I care.
Or lifting a finger for you.
Is that so?
Okay.
Some spirit, better suited to stripping oil from a painter's canvas than consumption,
grants overworked conscripts a few rare moments of sweet oblivion
on their long arduous sea journeys north from the continent.
Okay, here, take this.
Do you want that or not?
I can take it back.
Damn you, Goots.
All right, all right.
No need to be hasty.
Let's have a look at you.
Drop something?
Everybody just seriously thinks that I'm upside down.
I'm going to let this go.
I'll do what I can as a favor to Goot's mind.
We could barely see that.
It's hard when you're in a little cube over here.
There, I have to match it up that way.
Okay.
The crafting of new gear as well as the upgrading of existing gear
can be done at a blacksmith.
As long as you have the recipe and the proper materials.
Select a highlighted item from the list and hold X to craft or upgrade.
Looks like I can upgrade my iron belt.
Okay.
Fine, I'll stop vibing.
I'll stop vibing then.
Fine.
Okay.
Iron belt.
I can also read.
There's nothing to read for.
Sorry, I could do...
Okay.
Let's see.
It wants me to do it.
And the belt sees a square.
You want anything else, you bring your own materials.
I'll bear that in mind.
Thank you.
A word of advice.
Don't let Sid decide what's best for you.
Notices when something has changed in the hideaway,
a notice will appear in the upper right-hand corner of the screen.
In addition to stock updates for Charon's Toll
and new forging recipes for the Black Hammer,
there are also notices for new quests,
new missions, and many other things.
A icon will appear in-game
as well as on the local map to indicate recent updates.
Sorry, it's a little like side thing.
I suppose I should think it...
Updates.
A new crafting recipe is available at the...
Okay.
Let's just see what it is.
I see I'm busy here.
I'm a Sanfordian, dear.
Broad sword.
I need three Y-rite.
I could do iron bracers.
What do I have right now?
I'm wearing the broadsword right now.
Broad sword plus one.
No, I actually don't.
What do I have right now?
Why did I do this with my voice?
All right.
I can...
Should I make some bracers?
I could.
Why not?
Say...
Yeah.
Wait.
Oh, this uses a Y-rite.
I'll save for the sword.
I want damage.
All right.
So what else is unlocked here?
The fat chocobo.
Well, I'm going to see that.
There's no way I'm not going to go investigate that.
All right.
Where's this fat chocobo?
Oh, that's the name of the restaurant.
I thought there was going to be like a big chocobo in here.
Can I eat something?
Auto.
All right.
Well, let's just go.
The gift worked.
You have my thanks.
Your face game doesn't line up with the header in the game,
and it's torturing me.
Come on.
Nearly there.
You.
Blankets.
Quick as you like.
All right.
We're making comfortable while a bed's made up.
Can you guys test the command?
Can you guys do exclamation FF16?
I'm just going to stand there.
Someone face some water.
I'll get the bucket.
You can't see if what I need's out.
Oh, wait, me.
Well, not all of you at the same time, but it could be working.
Is it working?
What the hell have I got myself into?
Nurseries in 864 P.
Who are they?
It's got a 30 second cooldown.
They're freed imperial bearers.
Who the hell are you?
Shit, at this rate, you won't make it through the night.
Then you can find your way up them stairs to the infirmary.
We need Taya.
Well, go on.
Shift your arse.
Let's tell you the one looking after Jill.
All right.
Speak with Taya in the infirmary.
What's all the commotion?
I think we should go and help.
It sounds like we've got some new customers.
Auto.
R1, R1, R1, R1, R1.
Your friend needs her rest.
There'll be time for tearful reunions once she's recovered.
I'm not here for Jill.
You're wanted downstairs.
There are injured bearers in need of attention.
Well, why didn't you say so?
Can you explain the lore of the last 16 games?
Well, that's the beauty of Final Fantasy.
You don't need to know anything
about the other Final Fantasy games.
You could start at Final Fantasy 16
and you are golden with its own story.
You don't need to know anything
about any of the Final Fantasies.
It's a perfect place to start.
He's going to be all right.
Thank you.
But I'll need to examine them both in the infirmary.
Yeah, but nobody said that.
Yeah, they did.
They just asked it.
Another fond day of the Heideweide.
To many of the bearers who come here arrive in this state.
It's no easy thing.
Cast me off your chains.
By the time most pluck up the courage,
they're all too far gone.
Can we get a lore check?
These two here are the lucky ones.
Sedolphus Telemann, cornered by a battalion of iron kingdom crusaders
in the depths of the Nysa Defile, Clive thought his end was nigh,
until Cid appeared and spirited him and Jill away
to his secret hideaway in the Deadlands.
Pretty fucking sick.
The name's Otto.
You need anything?
You asked me.
Well, Otto, I do need some supplies.
Do you now?
Then Lady Karen over there will be more than happy to help.
Can buy some stuff.
Right.
Oh, and thanks.
Be seeing you.
Not likely.
I won't be staying.
Is that right?
Well, for as long as you are.
This guy does not sound like Otto.
You helped us today.
And we won't forget it.
You have to stay and we won't forget it.
Thank you.
It's a pleasure to do business with you.
My name's Otto.
Yeah, you're right.
Doesn't sound the same.
Side quests have been unlocked.
So green icons are side quests.
After accepting quest, quest objectives appear in the to-do list.
Okay.
Red is a main scenario and then you can have up to three green side quests.
Any quest can be prioritized.
Right.
Okay.
The Thousand Tomes.
An ever-growing compendium.
All things Velystia.
The Orchestrion.
Jukebox for all the songs collected through the game.
Cool.
They're in the Fat Chocobo.
Who are these people?
Oh, all right.
Does anybody want the little M&M crunchies in my ice cream?
I kind of just want the ice cream.
You don't want the M&M's in the ice cream?
What do you mean?
You eat around the M&M's?
That's...
Really?
It's like the best part.
I need supplies for my journey to Lostwing.
I'm talking...
What else can you provide them?
What's that?
Does the newcomer think it proper to make demands
of a poor old matron before even introducing himself?
It's Clive.
M&M's are gross?
No, Clive.
M&M's are gross by themselves.
I hear that dog is yours.
They're amazing in other baked goods or ice creams.
Since he found Sidon one night, I've seen to it that his
chin's rubbed and his belly fed.
Though I suppose that's your job now.
Unless you lose him again.
M&M's and cookies?
I won't.
S tier.
M&M's and ice cream?
Not again.
S tier.
Handful of M&M's?
Thank you for watching him.
C.
So, were you gonna buy something?
C plus maybe.
You didn't think I'd shower your lordship with my hard-won wares
while you swagger about with a pocketful of gil?
Life doesn't work that way, lad.
Now, let's see some coin.
All right.
Shop stock changes as the story progresses,
so be sure to check frequently.
So, I can buy a broad-
Wait, I can buy a broadsword?
I'm gonna buy a broadsword,
then I'm gonna take it over and upgrade the broadsword.
How many I f-
Four.
I'll get another one of these.
Wait, how much-
That's 200!
It's 500 bucks for the broadsword,
and it's 200 for potion?
Seems like a lot.
All right.
I'm getting the broadsword.
Yeah, I'm gonna-
I'm gonna go upgrade it.
You're robbing me blind, you know.
Just don't get hit.
I'll be fine.
That's all.
Why, you're barely a girl to your name.
Just don't get hit.
You're taking his side now.
And after all I've done for you.
All right.
I can make an exception.
But just this once, mind.
Me stores are getting cluttered,
and I need to make room for the next shipment.
You're-
You're broke now?
Thank you.
Thank me?
Thank your dog.
Wha- wha- wha- wha- wha- wha- wha- wha- wha- wha-
What button do I press to get off?
Camera.
That one.
All right.
Collect the supplies.
Wait, did I just buy a broadsword for no reason?
I swear to God there's a broadsword in one of these sacks.
I'm gonna be pissed off.
Virtual Battlescape provides Clive a safe location
to test out new abilities
and train against all manner of enemies.
Oh, it's like a little training zone.
All of virtue.
That's cool.
I guess it wants me to do it.
Do I?
Yeah, I guess it's like go do it.
I'm telling you, I'm gonna-
I'm gonna be-
I'm gonna be the guy that has the big bump on the-
on like the- the uh-
the official source of this music.
I- I'll be the bump on YouTube, you know what I mean?
Okay.
Ooh!
Wait, you can see what I do over here!
That's kind of- I don't like-
That's weird.
You guys are gonna try to judge my movements.
The YouTube video hump.
That's what I'm talking about.
The thing that says the most replayed part of the video.
I'm gonna contribute to that.
It's gonna be bad.
Why does he move so weird?
I'm just fucking around.
All right, this is really cool.
So I can do invincibility.
I can do an action log.
I can do enemy invincibility.
I can probably change the tar-
Yeah, all right.
That's cool.
So I can-
Oh, you can practice against bosses?
Is that how that works?
So not attacking currently.
Oh, enemy aggro.
Here we go.
Interesting.
It's a good place to practice dodging.
Ow!
All right, cool.
I might practice here with some encounters.
The person really wants me to know that they ate a bunch of bread.
Even already, are ya?
It's you I'll miss the most, Lady Karen.
It always is.
Doesn't stop you going, does it?
This should be fun.
When's the BLT stream?
Soon.
There's fast travel.
You use the world map.
Instant travel between unlocked locations.
New locations are unlocked by progressing through the main story
or discovering waymarks known as obelisks.
World map up and automatically upon leaving an area.
What?
That was a weird way to say that.
All right, collect the supplies, which were right here.
Come on, get us off.
Clear this.
There we go.
Make for the Great Wood.
Oh, world map.
There it is.
Which button is that?
Ah.
Okay.
We're going over here.
The Great Wood.
So deep and vast as the Great Wood,
it serves as a defensive barrier between the Crystal Belt and the Holy Empire.
Are you gonna finish the game?
I, streaming-wise, if you guys continue to like it,
I mean, I'm invested.
I might finish it on my own time,
like just kind of hanging out on the couch or maybe I'll play it here.
I don't know.
We'll see.
We'll see how you guys feel because I'm into it.
When are you gonna do a live audience stream so we can throw tomatoes at you?
There we go.
So here's the party.
Let's go.
That sound is huge.
I suppose not.
Okay.
Banning embers.
Torgl has joined the party and will fight alongside Clive.
So use the d-pad to talk between item shortcuts and pet commands.
Attack, heal, and launch an enemy into the air.
Oh.
So I gotta go boom and then up.
The accessory known as the Ring of Timely Assistance removes the need for giving Torgl commands.
When this item is equipped,
Torgl will attack and heal automatically based on the current battle situation.
Did I mention there'd be deadly beasts?
I don't need to put that on.
There'll be deadly beasts.
Nothing a trained assassin can't handle.
How reassuring.
You're welcome.
It's very pretty.
For that and his shortcut.
Can you walk?
Walk, walk.
I'm walking.
I don't think so.
I thought he was on the ground.
I was like, oh shit.
Sid's like dead.
Where is Torgl?
Oh, he's already up there.
I want to upgrade this.
I like the magic.
Is this for sponsorship?
This is.
This is sponsored by...
The stream is sponsored by Square Enix.
Come on, Thanos 16.
What do you think of the PS5?
It's...
So I use consoles as like a complete multimedia box.
And PS5 seems pretty great for...
Hold on a minute.
Wait a minute.
He hates it.
I just thought I'm about to explain to you why I like it so much.
I didn't even like say two sentences.
What in good Grieger's name is he doing this far south?
Looking for food.
No more wolves where he's from.
The north was one of the first parts of storm to fall to the blight.
Oh sod.
I'd invite him over for a cup of tea if I didn't think he'd eat the dog.
You said on August 2nd there'd be a bald cam for your birthday.
I'll just put my head down and you can laugh for five seconds.
Let's try and stay out of its path.
Okay, stay away from that.
Oh, I have the charge move too, don't I?
This one here.
Here we go.
Down.
Ooh, level up.
Eleven Gil.
Is it Gil or Jill?
Gil?
Oh, I got...
Why right?
Maybe that's enough to upgrade the broadsword.
Do I even have the broadsword?
I have it equipped, right?
Yeah.
After you.
It's strong.
Thank you kindly.
Like, Gil?
The ruins.
They're everywhere, aren't they?
Some say there was a time they blocked out the stars.
Down was the only way for them to go.
Do I not have the broadsword equipped?
There's probably a lesson to be learned from that.
But it can wait.
Come on.
I'll check.
Actually, I have points to spend too in the abilities.
What do I want to focus on?
Journal tab has information.
All right.
What I want to see...
Items.
You can assign shortcuts.
Uh-huh.
I think the shortcuts are fine.
What is...
Wait, I want the strength one, I think.
Increases attack bar by 10%.
Yeah, let's put this down here.
Just don't get hit and just do more damage.
That sounds good to me.
All right.
Gear and icons.
They have these.
I don't think I unlocked anything new.
No.
All right.
Abilities.
Here we go.
All right.
What do I got?
115?
Should I upgrade Scarlet Cyclone?
Probably should get all these first.
Magic Burst?
Oh, actually, I use this all the time.
I use this all the time.
This is my move.
It's either that or...
I'm doing it.
This is my move.
You see me do it a lot.
All right.
Now I'm gonna...
I'll get this.
Put this well in the air to slice down.
Cool.
Taunt?
R2 plus that button to pull an enemy?
Swift Recovery.
That's important.
Stomp.
Kick off a nearby enemy, increasing jump height.
Yeah.
I mean, just all the cheap ones.
I'll just get them all.
Okay.
Cool.
Do you believe in dolphins?
Do you mean, do I believe that the animal, the dolphins, exist?
Or do I believe that the dolphins will win the Super Bowl eventually?
What do you mean?
Like, do I believe in the dolphins
or do I believe that a dolphin as an animal exists?
I feel like you mean, like,
do I believe in the dolphins, like the football team?
Which, not a great season last year.
Not a good season last year.
What did they do?
Fucking...
What was their record last year?
Dolphins did, like, they were all right last year.
Nine and eight?
Jeez, could get a little better.
Jesus.
The dragon?
Wait, wasn't that my name?
I'll get, I'll hit you with the Precision Dodge all day.
2300!
I'm gonna hit you with,
I'm gonna hit you with Precision every day.
Ow!
Torgl!
Dude, Jerma is so precise.
That's what I like to hear.
Dragon Talon?
Ooh, using it in crafting.
No one said that.
Go look at the logs, yes they did.
Must be a nest nearby.
Keep your eyes open.
Can I have a heal, Torgl?
Insufficient inventory space, potion used.
Oh, I'm out of room.
It appears we won't be going this way.
What is it, Torgl?
Got something!
Why trust in your own animal instinct
when you now have an actual animal at your side?
If you're lost, hold down L3,
and let Torgl point you in the right direction.
Ooh, you're so smart.
No!
Okay, here we go.
There we go, that's what I was trying to do.
That's what I was going for.
Oh, a treat!
My mouse is on the unsubscribe button.
You better be careful.
I was careful.
Hovering over it.
New enemies approaching.
This is stupid.
All right, give it to this thing first.
Cool.
You're so precise.
Did you give your thoughts on the Mario RPG remake?
I did.
It went like this.
Just make sure you take that image
and like blow the contrast up times a thousand.
Make my eyes wicked blue.
What a wicked blue.
Way blue, more blue than they really are.
And then superimpose that on top of any other topic.
Yeah, I'm very excited about it.
Like one of my favorite.
Yeah, no guys.
One of my favorite games ever created.
Ever since I was a child.
No, I don't.
You know, whatever.
Whoa, whoopsie, whoopsie daisy.
Whoopsie daisy.
I'm very excited for it.
Boss fight.
All right, make sure you get your...
Look at how precisely his comments ready.
I'd like to see them very soon.
All right.
Ow!
All right, all right, all right.
We just got real here.
Oh, shit, that really hurt.
Oh, it takes a little bit longer.
Oh, look at how precise he is.
Shit, I could have gotten it every time.
Nobody said that.
I did.
All right, let's go.
That wasn't bad.
Oh, my God.
What?
Oh, God damn it.
Oh, I thought I dodged it.
No, I wanted to...
Charge it.
All right, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
See you later.
All right, I'm gonna end it like this.
One, two, three.
Goodbye.
I will never stop spamming caps.
Well, you're gonna get timed out.
Pretty good precision, I think.
Move your camera.
Where do I go with it?
Right here?
Phase two?
That was actually pretty...
That was pretty crazy.
Oh, bloody Rome of strapping young lads.
And it was this sorry sack of bones,
Rome, who saw fit to home.
He's so cool.
Sid.
Did he like that with...
That's a good image.
But I don't want to put it on screen.
What's in it for me?
The same as for all of us.
What we want and deserve.
Save for our knack.
Dominance and bearers are no different from anyone else.
The ability to use magic or summon great beasts
should command respect,
but instead has left us outcasts.
Our kind are used and discarded like tools,
yet we are men.
So why must we die as less?
I see.
So what you're saying is you want to start a war.
You flatter me, lad.
But my days as a firebrand are long behind me.
No, I only wish to offer our kind of choice.
A place where we can die on our own terms.
Hey.
Take a big shove.
How do you feel, good boy?
Can I give him a treat, too?
Mejmer was like, here!
He was like, anything I'm missing here?
Damn.
Okay.
Let's make sure I didn't miss anything.
What exactly do you plan on doing
when you find this dominant of fire?
What do you think?
I'll show him the mercy he showed my brother
and cut out the tongue of any man
who tries to talk me out of it.
All right.
Forest Dark enough as it is.
I'm just taking it in.
Level 11 Hornets.
Yeah, the soundtrack is so good.
I love it.
Yeah, you know when I'm asking for OSTs?
Like, oh, man, I was here.
OST, you guys want to do?
I already got one.
I'll put on this one.
Put it over here?
Okay.
I'm going over here.
Whoa.
Okay, easy, easy.
I thought I dodged it.
My Wounds Boy.
Not bad.
All right.
Bloody hides.
Ocean.
Actually, I need to.
Okay.
Something in this cave.
Meteorite.
Dude, epic, Jerma.
Great job.
Thanks.
Yeah, I'm off.
Stop talking to yourself.
That's literally a live streamer.
You don't need to lower check.
Excellent.
We move.
Dude, I forgot everything.
Please.
Can I have a lower check?
I don't understand.
It is true.
My leech values loyalty above all else.
But where are you not quick to betray your countrymen
for the promise of coin?
God.
Damn.
Benedicta Harmon, commander of Waluld's elite intelligences.
We can capture her.
What did you do that for?
You.
She was showing off.
If you could make magic come out of your hands,
you wouldn't just show off randomly to your friends.
Imagine the birthday parties.
You'd be able to make so much cooler.
Let's get this over with.
At least they're not giant lizards.
Let's go.
You're already dead.
That guy was lying on the ground when we got over here.
Ow, that hurt.
Oh, it's rank time.
Oh, my God.
You're clear.
Get up.
Big damage.
Oh, my God.
Cinematic clash when the screen flashes orange like this
during a pivotal moment.
Repeat it.
Don't even tell me anything else.
I'll never fail one of those ever.
That hurt.
Ready to go.
Everybody get up.
Buton?
What's Buton?
Oh, I'm going to die.
I'm not.
Tap.
Again.
Oh, shit.
The boss fights are so fucking fun.
I'm just telling you.
Badge of Might is an accessory.
Oh, it is.
Okay.
Attack by seven.
Look at how precise that was.
That's not even a boss either.
Really.
I'm sleeping right now.
My dreams are kind of weird.
Are you typing?
What's the face you make when you hit a cinematic slash?
This one.
They thought we were Imperials.
You do look the part.
Fight like a true shield of Rosaria.
Blast by the phoenix of that.
What's wrong with that face?
Speaking of which, I wonder.
Does the other icon of fire give blessings, do you think?
You don't believe me.
And lo, the creator did make of the elements eight icons
to serve as keepers of the one roar.
Not that I've ever set too much store by holy doctrine.
But on that point, it's clear.
Fire has always had just the one warden as of all the rest.
A new one can't be born until the previous dies.
And even that can take years.
Thank God the face game is too scary for me.
You don't strike me as a liar, which leaves but one person
who might be able to shed some light on the matter.
And they're in a lost swing.
Oh, son.
What game are you playing?
Can you catch me up on the plot before I walk upstairs?
What if someone discovers the bodies?
Well, they'll be sorely disappointed.
Stage replay in arcade mode.
Is it an arcade mode?
In the hideaway.
So you can just kind of do just wonder what arcade mode is.
So this is Orbel Downs.
All right, so there's new missions back here.
I kind of want to upgrade my weapon.
Or should I just keep going?
There's a new side quest back here.
I think I should upgrade.
I want to check it out.
Hey, you do you?
Yeah.
New crafting recipe is available.
Longsword.
Longsword's better than...
Wait, okay.
Longsword, how much money do I have?
I got money.
Is it worth spending 700 right now?
I could craft a longsword.
Or I could do this broadsword plus one
as good as just crap.
Maybe I should craft a longsword and upgrade a longsword.
This does take a dragon talon, though.
I would probably just go buy it.
I'm going to go buy it and then upgrade it.
Wait, do I?
No, I don't have one already.
I don't think you have the longsword equipped.
Oh, I don't think I have the longsword
because I bought the broadsword.
And then the thing I started was the Imperial Infantry Blade.
It's just the starter weapon.
I have the broadsword on right now,
but the longsword looks like it's just better.
I'm going to buy...
Is this you own it?
I don't think so.
All right, I'll buy it.
I want to save the materials.
I'll sell the broadsword back.
I think that makes sense, right?
Because crafting this, I have to use a gnarled scale.
I have two of those.
With this one, I...
Oh, yeah, see?
I have to use a gnarled scale for this.
Why not just use it on upgrades?
I have the money.
Let's go for it.
I could do it again.
I have three meteorite, so I'm just going to go again.
You can find me later.
I could do it again.
No, I couldn't.
Cool.
All right.
Keep going.
I think that's all I can do.
So let me...
What about other stuff?
Iron racers?
I think I have...
I could do iron belt plus two.
Although what about...
What do you...
Okay, wolfskin sash.
28.
28 versus 26 and two health.
This one just gives 28.
28 defense versus health.
Just don't get hit.
That's true.
I'll take the health.
This is just better, though.
All right, I'm going to...
All right, here's what's happening.
I'm going to make this sash.
Then I'll upgrade it.
I do say so myself.
Okay, so this is going to be good before health.
Yeah, see, this is only two, even if it's plus two.
Okay, yeah, we'll do this one plus two.
You can find me later.
Trophy earned.
Okay, cool.
Can't really do any of these.
Do I...
I have iron burses on right now, I do.
Okay, we're good.
I should buy some heals, though, right?
Kind of low.
Installed.
Why do you look like a gigachat right now?
I think I look like gigachat.
What do you got?
You got a mission?
Damn it.
We'll be needing more wood.
If I step away to fetch any,
this lot will be down around our ears.
Ah, you there.
Perfect timing.
I couldn't persuade you to fetch me some timber, could I?
Ooh, what do I get for it?
I'd be happy to.
Oh, thank you.
You'll be helping me and the hideaway both.
Side mission.
Let's go.
More than we can manage, if I'm honest.
It certainly looks like you've got your hands full.
Ah, you can say that again.
The fallen knew their craft, make no mistake.
But not even their handiwork lasts forever.
This guy looks like the kind of person that...
That's why the walls need shoring up.
...always finishes top three in the arm wrestling competition every year.
...for our first harvest now, can we?
No, I suppose not.
Where can I find this wood?
Ask over at the white ads.
They'll point you in the right direction.
Thanks again.
Okay.
I really appreciate the help.
Yeah.
Let's prioritize this.
Let's do some good stuff.
Hashtag add.
Oh, yeah.
Square Enix sponsored this stream.
I think the game is fantastic.
I really mean that.
I am going to finish this game.
I'm going to play it all the way through.
I really like it.
Yeah, it's out on PS5 right now.
You can also get the demo.
The demo is still available too.
Coin purse weighing you down.
Okay, I want to sell some stuff.
I'm going to sell the broadsword.
It's probably a bad idea, but somebody will scream at me.
I reckon I can find a buyer.
I'm getting rid of the infantry belt.
I know, but what about just for drip?
No, it's fine.
All right, I got to equip this.
Come again.
All right, I don't want to put these ones on.
This is the rings that give you much more damage and power and stuff.
I just want this one, the one that I found.
There is my sword.
That looks good.
Okay, yeah, it's only on PS5 right now.
Only on PS5.
Can you see the chat's donations things?
Yeah, like I said before, it's a new feature.
I don't really know what it is, but I'll look into it.
I'll see what it is, but I can reiterate.
I do not read donations or subs on stream.
I'll say I've had for a long time and could tell you why.
But already, you know, let's go.
Excuse me.
The man working over by the garden sent me to fetch some wood.
Do I have to cut the wood?
Ah, that'll be Jeffrey, master carpenter.
Luck would have it.
We've just finished cutting the timber he's after.
You take as much as you need from the stack.
Thank you.
So let's just grab it.
No, not at all.
We appreciate the assistance.
Collect the planks.
Here we are.
Okay.
You better get this to Jeffrey, was it?
Hold on.
Let me help you here.
Ah, fuck if I know, man.
I don't know either.
I've fetched in that wood.
Wasn't too much trouble.
I get money for this.
Will this be enough?
This will do nicely.
Thank you.
With a bit of luck, the walls won't be falling in on us just yet.
That sounds ominous.
It's not as bad as all that.
And it's a damn sight better than the alternative.
We're safe.
We're warm and we're hidden.
What more could we ask for?
Now stop fretting and take this.
You've earned it.
Welcome to the fold.
And?
There's no need to.
That's not a matter of need, my friend.
You're one of us now.
What do I get?
Meteorite.
That's pretty good.
And a gill bug.
Contrary to popular belief,
this small insect does not get its name from its appearance,
but rather from the fact that it is highly sought after by
fizzickers?
Fizzickers?
For use in brewing medicines.
In summer, when the beetles are most numerous,
children across the realm will spend nigh every waking hour collecting specimens
in readiness to exchange them for a handful of coppers.
As children have tiny hands, however, this amounts to fewer than one might expect.
Rate this bug on a tier list.
I don't know.
B?
All right, so I can sell that.
Should I sell it?
What if I get more stuff?
Oh, I'm curious about the arcade mode thing.
I was supposed to see it.
Replay any previously cleared stage and be awarded a score based on performance.
Restrictions on level gear consumables are applied.
Gameplay mode will default to action focused.
All right, that's cool.
Play a little challenge mode.
Go see...
Can you go see the moogle?
Where's the moogle?
Yeah, sure.
Why is everybody doing mag?
Over by the board?
What board?
Why is everybody doing mag?
What happened?
Because they want moogle.
I gotta find moogle.
All right, let me sell this first.
Just said to sell this for a lot of money.
Heal bug.
Valuable can be sold.
200?
Would you eat a bug, be honest?
I don't know if I had.
Maybe.
I wouldn't be happy about it, but it would be like, whatever.
Do I have to eat bugs?
I don't know.
No, I don't know.
All right, let's go.
Wait, quest.
I want to make as much money as I can.
Ah, a new face.
And, dare I hope, a willing pair of hands.
The fat chocobo is a demanding mistress, and we are too few to keep her on her feet.
Might I persuade you to offer a meal or two to souls in need of sustenance?
For your trouble, I can offer you the contents of my strong box and my enduring gratitude.
There's not going to be anything in there.
Oh, there's 500 bucks in there.
And I see why not.
Marvelous.
And who exactly do I have the honor of addressing?
Clive.
Delighted to make your acquaintance, Clive.
I'm Kenneth, and mine are the weary shoulders upon which the weight of this fine establishment rests.
Now, I have three hungry customers awaiting their vittles.
Take these, if you would, and be careful.
They're hot.
I would eat that right now.
A meal.
Long as it been.
Can I just eat them all?
There you go.
Your food.
I was hoping it might be.
Well, doesn't this look fine?
Thank you, lad.
You're new, aren't you?
Kenneth's running your ragged already, I expect.
The old rascal.
Very hot.
Be careful.
I didn't say he'd give me something for my trouble.
And so he should.
We're not slaves anymore.
Well met, lad.
And keep up the good work.
I'm going to get 500 bucks.
Yeah.
Fully clad in armor, bringing your food to your table.
I hope you do not think me lazy for waiting to be served like a lord.
I mean, it's like a bunch of themed restaurants do that already, don't they?
Did not use me kindly, you see.
You left me half lame, truth be told.
That Sid took me in nonetheless.
Precise.
The hideaway is the home I never knew.
And a mighty fine one at that.
Enjoy.
Any crusty bread?
How can you have stew and no crusty bread?
Well, there's so much more to farming than just seeds and soil.
I'm talking bread that you have to like.
Your food.
Just a moment.
I need to finish this.
I won't be a burden.
I'm of no use to anyone as I am, but maybe if I can master this.
All right, but see that you eat it before it gets cold.
Of course.
Thank you.
If I had a restaurant, I would name it with crusty bread.
That would be the name of my restaurant.
With crusty bread.
It'd be such a really hearty.
Everybody knows you're gonna when you come in.
When you when you're here, you come in here.
Your family in here.
You know what I mean?
Wait, did I not feed them?
Oh, no, no, no, I gotta turn it in.
All done, I presume.
Splendid.
They were bearers.
Stay away from my family master's pleasure.
But I'm waiting to be fed like equals.
Indeed, equality is the very cornerstone upon which our little community has found it.
You know, everything's gonna be warm.
Beyond these walls.
Gonna be like candles and shit.
Speaking only when spoken to.
Eating only what scraps our masters.
We have the best crusty bread.
The first hot meal here in the city.
First, many will have known.
In the hideaway, we are free.
Truly free to speak as we please, when we please.
And to eat what and when we desire.
More than reason enough to trust in Sid's vision, wouldn't you say?
There's no utensils.
Now, I promised you something for your trouble, did I not?
This bread is gonna be so hard and so shit.
You're gonna have you pull it apart and you're gonna use that as utensils
to eat your soup and stew and stuff.
The bread is your utensil.
And why, right?
That's pretty good.
And 500 bucks just, that was all right.
The table is made out of bread.
That restaurant would be open for, okay.
First of all, that restaurant's open for one or two days
before the whole thing gets closed.
Everything is edible.
Somebody's dog is gonna get, you know what I mean?
An animal is gonna get, like a bear is gonna get into that restaurant.
It's gonna be a fucking nightmare.
They'll be like, hey, stop eating the post to the table.
Oh no.
Rats, yeah, they'd be all, it'd be animals.
They'd be just animals all over the place.
It'd be like a weird cartoon moment where you'd be sitting there eating.
Oh, did you know that the table is edible?
And it just cuts down to one of the posts of the table
and there's a rat just gnawing on the very bottom to have it fall out.
And it just, the whole table falls
and my grandpa's soup goes up in his face.
The whole restaurant is edible.
The bathroom would have to be normal though.
The bathroom, it's a normal bathroom.
We can't have edible fucking urinals and edible toilets, guys.
The bathroom is a normal bathroom.
That does not work.
Why not?
All right, let's go.
That was fun.
I got my upgrades.
I'm ready to move.
Let's do the next part.
No one was thinking that except for you.
I was thinking ahead, actually.
I was thinking ahead.
Go back and get the chest.
Wait, what do you mean the chest?
Didn't he just deposit it into my fucking account?
Any idea what that is?
They built the village around.
Get the chest.
The Fallen Ruin.
I've heard someone call it an airship.
Though its flying days seem to be behind it.
It's a shame, that.
Do you truly think her dominance waiting for us in that village?
My scout has never given me any reason to doubt him,
which is why I think we should hurry.
Come on.
Just give me one second to go back.
A tuning with an obelisk allows Clive to travel quickly to the location
via both the world map and local map.
Louder than words.
Let me go back to the...
Are you guys messing with me here?
Is that for real?
This isn't the first time I've seen one of these.
Perhaps I can use them as waymarks.
Are you guys being for real?
Is there actually something in here?
Is there a chest I didn't get on the table?
Do you think we should go and help?
Oh, there is.
I thought you guys were lying to me.
Okay.
Hold on.
It's important.
Thank you.
That was badge of metal defense.
Yeah, we're gonna put that on.
Of course we are.
Let's go back.
Guys, your face came weird.
This is my face.
And you can say my face is weird.
I mean, rude.
But that's your opinion on how you feel about my face.
I also have an opinion that your opinion is...
No, let's just play.
Why is it so small?
It's not...
I want you to focus on the gameplay.
Definitely, foe.
I don't know, Sid.
It really depends on if you start hearing music or not
when we walk up here.
Do you hear it?
No?
They might be friends.
Yeah.
Let's go!
Damn!
Dude, you're blocking gameplay.
I am not blocking gameplay.
I'm going to purposefully spot.
Combat looks so fucking fun.
Combat is so freaking fun.
No, it actually is.
You're in the center of the screen.
I think I'm in a perfect spot.
This is right over the stuff down here.
I'm not blocking anything.
No sign of the Royalists.
Else for that matter.
It's too bloody even for this hour.
What do we do now?
First, we look for my scout.
You start here.
I'll circle around the back.
How do I let you know if I find him?
Good question.
Shout?
Subtle.
The combat director of the game, Ryota Suzuki,
which, uh, Devil May Cry and Dragon's Dogma.
I'm curious.
You're like, wow, that combat looks really great.
Combat director of the game.
So the village can't be complete.
Very, very cool.
All right.
This looks like I have to pay attention here.
Very cool.
Okay.
I hear music.
That sounds like a child.
Everything all right?
It's all right.
We should play Dragon's Dogma sometime.
I'm not one of them.
My friend and I were.
I saw Sturve.
We did Imperial Army.
Sturve made a video on it.
We've come to help.
It's funny.
Do you know where your parents are?
In the church.
Then I'm going to find them and make sure they're safe.
Can you stay hidden here until then?
To the church then.
Go.
But not yet because I want to see if you have any, uh,
hidden gil anywhere.
I feel like it's a lot more urgent than this.
What is he doing over there?
Is he mocking this entire situation?
Just skipping around.
I think I don't think I missed nothing.
Stop skipping.
You're breaking my immersion.
The church.
I know.
I'm one step ahead of you.
True.
Can you speak in a British accent for that entire stream?
No, but 5,000 of you will leave.
You hate when I do that.
Everybody hates when I do that.
More than anything.
Everybody hates it.
This man's gonna die if we don't get into a healer.
Enough of your barking, dog!
That was fucking awesome.
Didn't even...
That was...
I loved that so much.
It was just right on cue.
Enough of your barking, dog.
Boom.
Not even a small second.
It was right when he was done talking.
Just right in the back of the head.
He's with me.
Is this everyone?
No.
There were others.
A pair of royalists came for the bearers just before you arrived.
Was a dominant among them?
Maybe.
It's not like you is old in a sign.
Oh, shit.
This is great.
We're just chasing this guy?
We actually have to chase this guy down.
Oh, shit.
The really good part of the song is starting.
That means I'm dead.
I'm dead in like 10 seconds.
I gotta run as fast as I fucking can.
As long as I don't hear those fucking trumpets, mate,
I'm gonna be just fine.
That big turkey leg.
Will you join me?
My thanks.
To our lady of the wind.
And the king.
Imperials drink this piss?
Well, it would go some way to explain their breath.
You are disgusting.
Everybody back nowadays were gross.
We had disgusting breath and smelly bodies.
We all smell.
And instead of killing them,
you lead the rats straight to us.
Mercy.
This poor guy.
This poor guy had to run into...
Oh, I feel bad for this guy.
That was just so...
That was so bad.
An imperial bearer.
But I was getting bored.
Recruited that guy.
What is that thing?
Torgl!
I have no potions.
I have to actually be really careful here.
Let's go!
I love ending it like that with a charged shot.
This feels so good.
You have the worst face cam out of any streamer I know.
Uh, all right.
This is a cam, whatever.
Turn it off.
They don't appreciate it.
Don't recall you complaining, Benedicta.
So.
Sedolphus.
Remind me.
Why was it that you betrayed your kingdom?
I asked you a question.
Lord Commander.
Why'd she keep saying that, Cid?
Cid, what's going on here?
Why?
Because I've had enough of you and your king's antics.
And yet here you are, stealing my branded.
What are you plotting?
As if I'd tell you.
This wasn't in the lore, check.
I looked at it before I even started hanging out with you.
Did you lie on your resume?
Lady Benedicta!
We have secured the dominant.
Who's that guy?
Okay!
That's Gav.
That's Cid's faithful scout who puts his legendary nose to work
in tracking the movements of slaver soldiers
and any other object of interest to the hideaway.
The ever-agreeable fellow only too gladly delving behind enemy lines
if he can get a good story out of it or two.
Okay, good, cool.
Let me just, remind me again.
Commander of the Kingdom of...
Okay.
All right, got it, got it.
Finally explaining the lore.
I told you last week when we played the demo.
I unironically think that is the best,
one of the best features of this game.
I want more of that.
Trust me.
Especially for a game that's, you know, you come back,
you jump back and forth, jump into it.
Sometimes I play a game and I'll come back a week or two later
and it's just like, I don't even know who the fuck any of these people are.
It's very helpful.
Unironically, I mean it.
So, it wasn't about bears at all.
They, unironically again.
Everyone with a brand.
And then everyone without one and all.
And locked you in the cellar, hoping sooner or later someone would break.
You know, things might have been different if you'd accepted my invitation.
Oh, don't remind us.
We were all saying the same thing.
This is our own, isn't it?
Don't mean we won't help when we can, though.
And that, I'll drink to.
I just wish one of them would keep dying.
Yes, I'll drink to that.
Because like,
Let's do something weird.
Like, who?
But people still think it was cool.
13 years ago, I watched the dominant kill my brother right in front of me.
And I did nothing.
But now I can.
I can kill the son of a bitch.
And bring peace to my brother's soul.
After that, whatever happens, happens.
Wait, you're content to be a slave, then?
That's what I'm saying.
That's what I was...
Like, Sid, there's nothing in that cup.
Sid, there's nothing in there.
That cup has been empty for like, 40 minutes.
He did the thing!
This radiance would have us believe the Imperial host invincible.
Yet here we find the Empire's cornerstone teetering on the backs of a handful of cowards and cutthroats.
While the Hamid may lead a hundred full legions.
Could it be that the young prince defends a house of cards ready to topple at the slightest breeze?
But I recognize that guy's voice.
He's in Game of Thrones.
Pretty big part in Game of Thrones.
Ow!
That's not a good...
You're literally, like, hurting me.
Why would I do that?
Why didn't you want to make it seem like this...
What you were doing was like...
Like, hey, I'm gonna...
By the way, here's like a full steak dinner.
And, like, you know, you want one of these swords?
We can make one for you.
What's your favorite movie?
That we can get it on an emblem on the handle for you?
Or your favorite play?
Whatever.
You know, what's your favorite book?
Yeah, I get pulp fiction on the emblem.
It's like the...
It's freaking Gav.
I hope Gav is a party member.
What about Gav?
Aww.
I like Gav.
I suppose I better scout ahead for any surprises.
Don't you let him down.
I won't.
Wait, we're sending him ahead because he has a...
He can smell things better than us.
Not so fast.
We wait until tomorrow.
He's right there.
And if we leave now, we'll arrive just as the sun comes up.
Maybe join the guards in breaking their fast.
Come on, Clive.
They only just took the place.
They'll be there a while yet.
I bet you cannot name Gav's accent.
Welsh.
Thank you.
What were you going to give me?
No.
Even close.
Dude, I'm very precise.
Okay, cool.
New stock.
Let me upgrade first.
Is there a blacksmith here?
There's a shop, but...
What do you got?
What can I interest you in today?
Give the best voice of the entire video again.
Can I get you to talk more?
Like, way more?
What does that get you to talk 10 times more than you already have, Button?
I have the longsword.
I need potions.
Yeah, I'm kind of out of these.
These are expensive.
Ah, yes.
I hope it's to your liking.
I trust it's all here.
Okay.
I don't need more than this.
$40,000.
What is this?
Adds a new song to the hideaways orchestrion.
40 grand?
Oh, that's a gold sink right there.
Good day.
I have like 3,000.
Quentin, my good man.
It seems we'll be spending the night.
I thought as much.
Where do you find that one?
What, him?
You won't believe me if I told you.
Quentin here is an old friend, one who is sympathetic to our cause.
Grind forward, or we riot.
And he knows about your little sanctuary.
I would never have guessed so many people were bent on setting us free.
When last I checked, the mere thoughtward only would trip to the gallows.
I am well aware of the risks, as I am of the rewards.
And what could be more rewarding than your very own dominant of fire?
A dominant?
Here?
Now that I would like to see.
Meaning you haven't.
No, but nothing passes unnoticed in Lostwing.
Take your brand, for example.
People will see that at once.
And I need hardly tell you how they will greet the inquiries of a bearer.
You are afraid your words will fall on deaf ears.
As they have ever since the moment you were marked.
Okay.
Happily, I can provide a solution to your dilemma.
As a favor to Cid, that is.
Take this.
You will find it has the uncanny power to loosen tongues.
Seal.
You accept the hanged man from Quentin?
May the mothers guide you.
This might be Imperial land, but here in Lostwing, it's his word that's law.
But how?
You don't need to worry about that just yet.
Trust me.
Everyone in Lostwing knows what that seal means.
And what it means if they don't take note.
We can sit here counting our blessings or put them to good use and find that dominant.
Your choice.
Hey, I guess I'll use it for finding the dominant.
Let's see if this thing really works.
Gather information from the villagers.
Okay.
But is it to walk up to them and be like, hey, what do you know?
That's all you can do.
All right.
What do you know?
Master Quentin took a liking to you, I see.
And there I was thinking you were in bed with Cid.
Wonder what Gav will have to say about this.
Speaking of whom.
What?
You see him.
Tell him thanks for looking after us.
Now, what can I help you with?
I'm searching for a dominant of fire.
Gav seems to think he might have taken refuge here.
We see a lot of bearers around these parts.
But I do seem to recall one who commanded the flame.
Now whether or not that makes him a dominant, I can't say.
But the Waludas certainly took a keen interest in the poor sod.
Did you go look at him?
Didn't have a chance.
One of the other bearers might have died.
Thank you.
Okay.
I don't know.
What is this?
What is this crystal?
That thing's kind of cool.
Get over here.
I can't.
This is a genuine laugh.
What do you know?
About a hanged man, I see.
Master Quentin must think you're important.
It was a good thing you done today.
Getting rid of those bastards.
If you hadn't come when you did,
I'd be on my way to Ashby now.
Along with the others.
Poor buggers.
These others, was there a dominant among them?
A dominant of fire?
Might have been, yeah.
Royalists seem to think there was, anyhow.
You know what?
I'm in an NPC dialogue with another NPC
and that character was the playable character coming to kill me.
Only that you weren't alone.
Was a young maid who went wherever he did.
Including the church.
And wherever the royalists dragged them both off to before you got here.
I see.
Thank you.
I wonder if Sid's found anything.
I want to bite your head right now.
I can relax.
All right, speak with Sid.
All right, I got info.
Tell me that scowl means you've got good news.
Sorry.
It's all right.
A shady lad.
Just relax.
And it's equally shady lass.
Not much to go on.
But.
I've been thinking.
If our friend is a dominant,
why not just burn the royalists to a crisp?
There's a reason he's holding back.
Burn the royalists to a crisp?
I reckon it has something to do with his partner.
That's such a horrible way to...
One of the villagers I talked to said the two were separated.
If the Waludas have her,
our dominants like to think twice before starting any fires.
Whoever he is, he's shown himself to have a level head.
He's careful, cunning, and he doesn't want to be found.
This could spell trouble for us and the royalists both.
Still.
It'll be a whole lot worse if we set off after them with bleary eyes and empty bellies.
There should be a pair of pallets waiting for us back at the inn.
Shall we?
Let's do it.
Your party makeup has changed.
How come you're not skipping?
I...
I forgot.
I seem to recall your request being to spend the night.
And for that, the floor will more than suffice.
Better than a wet rock, I suppose.
My thanks, Quentin.
Next time you're at the hideaway, our floor's all yours.
No need for thanks, Sid.
This isn't an act of charity.
You don't say.
I do like the voice work, though.
In exchange for my floor, I shall be requiring your services.
Even like, the side characters are great.
...to barricade across the road south when they occupied the village.
And failed to remove it when they left.
I expect it to be gone before you leave.
As you wish.
Following evening.
Uh oh, we're not gonna get...
Well, that's all longer than expected.
First time dismantling a barricade?
It gets easier.
Dude wants a favor for letting somebody sleep on the floor?
If we leave now, we'll arrive at the care when the shadows are at the deepest.
Yeah, what the fuck?
Well, I should rather wait.
No more waiting.
The road's south end.
Unless...
I know of another shortcut.
You should be so lucky.
I have heels, right?
Yeah, I do.
I have a potion.
I have three?
Uh, the high potions over there?
Oh, yippee!
I'm gonna collect potions, and I'm gonna collect materials,
and I'm gonna get...
I'm gonna get status effects!
Just you wait!
Just you wait, Sid!
Everything all right?
Yup.
If the royalists were looking to take the care
that have posted centuries to prevent any unwelcome surprises,
at least I would have.
Well, you should know.
Make for Care Norvent.
Five bucks?
Let's go!
Wait.
I probably didn't even need to buy the potions now that I'm looking at it.
What are the royalists thinking?
Why take a stronghold they've no chance of holding?
When they've no intention of holding it,
the king is up to something.
The king?
Well, you don't think they're acting on a whim, do you?
This is one of his majesty's cunning stunts,
and he's sent his best to execute it.
Back over here.
Item.
Two pinches of magicked ash.
Ooh!
What is this?
This is like a super chest.
Did I get a lore check?
I had to shave.
Yeah.
We're going to Care Norvent.
It's an imperial stronghold located along the southern fringes
of Sambricoi's territory,
far from its capital of Oriflame.
Shatter was wondering.
It occupies a key strategic position adjacent to the Crystal Belt,
and it's suitably formatively fortified as a result.
Within its walls there are living quarters,
a church, a jail, and sufficient storehouses
to see the occupants through the lengthy siege.
Hope you had a good shave.
You're going to do another Halloween week this year?
Yeah, of course.
Play at least a few scary games.
There's quite a few that have come out.
All right, check over here.
Can't go this way?
No?
He won't do it now.
He just said he would.
Now he won't do it.
You should wear a cardigan again for Halloween week.
All right, hold on.
Getting attacked.
Oh, I should have jumped up there.
Level 14?
Can you do a minus two stream where you tell bad jokes on purpose?
We did that three days ago.
I feel like I do that every other stream.
My plan for Halloween this year is to get a full elaborate vampire outfit.
I'm doing that.
I'm going to be in character the whole night.
I'm going to pretend like it's 1100 or something.
When do vampires rain?
I don't remember.
Well, they didn't ever.
When are vampires supposed to exist?
Somebody said 2008.
Fourteen hundreds.
Okay.
Wear a cardigan as the vampire?
The best and worst decision I ever made.
Your estimator, Clive.
A fight with her icon is not one you're likely to walk away from.
Garuda, warden of the wind.
Yeah, I'll just drink like a bottle of wine on stream.
Let's play scary games.
New location.
I think this is that part in the demo.
Is that correct?
This seems like the place for it.
I think this is the part from the demo.
Yeah, it is.
The land has fallen.
The eastern territories all but belong to the orcs.
I'll have my men ready to depart by noon.
Don't bother.
But what of the mines?
Without Adamantite, the light would have engulfed the mines ere long.
Besides, you already have your orders.
Yes, my liege.
The dark swallows more of the realm with each passing day.
The land starved of the ether that gives it life.
And as the fringes fade, the people flock to the mother crystals desperate for their blessing.
For we wage for possession of that blessing.
It breaks us from within, hastening us to our own destruction.
And so you do what must be done.
I unite the dominance that we may bring an end to the strife
and found a new order to see us unto tomorrow.
The world must be restored and I will see it so.
You might have already had Sedolphus not betrayed us.
Last fight.
Him again.
Lost you still for his embrace.
But worse not.
My liege.
I serve you and you alone.
I remember well the day you first entered these halls.
Your pale hand pressed into his as if it would never let go.
That that was a long time ago.
Sometimes it's like, hey, man, you're going to like play Breath of the Wild like next week.
Soon my hand that is that keeps them from falling into the darkness.
Hold me, my liege.
Never let me go.
That scared the shit out of me.
Well, our sentries has failed to report, my lady, your orders.
Pull the men back inside their care, Geralt.
He is here, then.
Have them lead Sid and his little pet to the chapel.
I shall entertain them there.
So you've come for me after all.
Yes, I have.
Yeah, this is the demo part.
Well, the part of the extra demo.
Yep, this is the same part.
Headwind.
To teach me some time.
Oh, yeah, I forgot how do I turn this back on?
Remember, I had to turn the brightness up on my game because I didn't know how to turn it back on.
I was like, I can't see.
We should start with the dungeons.
Where is that?
Oh, yeah.
In here.
They're all empty.
And you're going to give up.
Sid, this gate needs some help.
We just cast a headache curse on me.
Let me help you here.
Should be gone now.
I did my I did my best.
You made it worse.
Oh, you just made me dumber.
No, you don't.
You can't even prove that, by the way.
Did you hear that?
What are you in the middle of a math test?
Now you just don't know how to do it.
Hi.
Kind of loud.
I know.
But I mean, you got to get pumped up, right?
You got to get pumped up.
Oh, that was cool.
Where to next?
I don't know.
Ask the dog.
Wait, let me check it.
I don't want to miss anything.
This door only leads to more Royalists.
We can take them.
Find another one.
Oh, snap.
It's the goofy guy I keep seeing on my YouTube feed.
Welcome to the stream.
Hope you enjoy your stay.
OK, now here's how I actually am.
Well, we found the Imperial garrison.
Right where the Royalists left.
I feel like I'm one of those living, like, AI paintings.
The ones that's like, oh, look, we can make grandpa blink.
You know what I mean?
The ones that are like, they're everywhere.
Let's go.
Get them all in the same zone.
Is it zero?
The same zero?
I think so.
You.
You're the healer.
You need to die.
That was cool.
All right.
Can you heal me?
Because I don't want to use a potion.
I really don't want to use a potion.
I don't know.
Whatever.
I'll use them.
Fine.
Oh, bloody hide.
Bloody fangs.
Thanks for the...
Oh, shit.
And then one big one.
And then one of these.
There we go.
Oh, you went fast.
God damn it.
I keep forgetting he does that.
Kill.
All right.
I need to heal.
Would you consider yourself a junk food streamer?
Can you sing Billie Jean?
That one?
Oh, do Billie Jean without without any emotion at all?
Sure.
After them.
Well guarded.
Attacking the opponent from the front while his guarding will deal no damage.
Go to the back.
Hey, yeah, they can break through.
Yep.
Okay.
New enemies approach.
Four.
Caster, hold on.
I'm hungry.
Well, you should.
Get a snack.
You didn't even do the...
Now I did.
Don't miss a chest or anything.
I don't want to...
Yeah, see?
I don't want to miss anything.
I got some pizza here.
You want a slice?
Oh, I'm good.
What kind of pizza though is it?
Pepperoni?
What the hell?
A little late for prayer, isn't it?
Do I seem so desperate as to grovel at the feet of a false god?
This is gonna be much harder because I don't have all the things...
I was waiting for you.
All the accessories were on last time.
For too long, I hope.
All this for a midnight chat?
Well, let's chat then.
Where are the men and women you took from Lostwing?
You mean where's the dominant?
Well, Luke shall be requiring his services indefinitely.
Come back to me, Sedulphus.
I need you.
Think of all the things we can create together.
The world that we can build.
You need me?
Your king needs me.
I'm all for building a new world.
Just not his.
That bastard's dreams are as twisted as his promises are false.
And I want no part of him.
King Barnabas saved you, and this is how you speak of him.
Have you no shred of loyalty?
What?
To a leader who'd use me?
Like he uses you?
You know nothing of me, Sedulphus.
You're right.
I don't know who you are anymore, or what you want.
I only know what you used to say.
That you were tired of running.
That you just wanted to be free.
Free of it all.
You weren't lying to me then, so what changed?
What made you think you had to sacrifice who you were
to get what you wanted?
Sacrifice?
I used my talent to my advantage,
and you would tell me there is shame in that?
If there's no shame, then why do you feel so sorry for yourself?
Arousing speech, Lord Commander.
I was a fool to believe you might have changed.
The only person I feel sorry for is you!
I can't do this anymore.
If you would stand between our leash and his dream,
then you leave me no choice.
You're gonna do about it.
Goodbye, Sedulphus.
I'm back.
Did I miss anything?
And don't forget about what I can do.
I can get rid of your headaches.
Keep going, Sid!
I'll make sure you're clean of all pain in your upper region.
You are gonna wake up with fresh tomorrow.
Head's not gonna hurt.
I'm just the migraine medicine guy.
I don't want any part of this.
Finish them.
I don't even know how to use a sword.
I, uh...
Well, Sid, the beast is not three against one.
Watch out.
Cinematic evasion.
Oh, they crashed into each other.
I didn't even pick that up last time.
Get in here!
All right, this one's done.
Shit!
Sorry.
Okay, I'm getting hurt.
Shit.
8K, that's not bad.
How come you look really interesting today?
I think it's just...
I have a beard I haven't shaved.
Mom instincts kicked in?
Mom instincts?
We're not done.
Sid.
Do I look all right?
Does he actually make it?
I mean, in the demo, doesn't it kind of just end?
Benedict II will be on her way to collect the Domain if she hasn't already.
You can't afford to let them leave.
Remember, she has wings, you don't.
What about you?
Before or after I catch my breath?
Sorry.
Come on, Toggle.
Oh, he is...
Yeah, he is there at the end of the demo.
Okay, let's keep going.
Give him a potion?
Oh, they're mine.
He had a lot of opportunities to go to the store and buy three high potions just like I did.
Wait, they might be just over here.
She must be here somewhere.
Yeah, I'll just throw this over at the favor of fire.
What was that?
Did I just get something?
Oh, forget about the defense.
Let's put these both on.
I'm going to open the other door that was down here.
Can you equip the dog too?
I don't believe so.
At least not at the moment.
I'm not sure maybe later.
Good.
Meteorite.
We want to go this way.
You need to equip Otto.
Kind of sounded like Homer Simpson, didn't it?
For like one second.
I need to get rid of you.
You too.
You need to die.
Good dog.
Any more Cheshire Trests?
How do I get over there?
How lazy wants us gone before sunrise?
Oh, this is okay.
You go down from here.
Is there anywhere else to go?
I don't think so.
Can you pronounce something funny?
Give me a word.
Give me a word to pronounce.
Lobster.
There you go.
Oh, hold on.
All right, get everybody near the table.
I didn't hit anybody.
Oh, you got a good one.
Shit.
Oh, my hair's getting in the way.
Starting to like this game more and more.
It's just it's fun to play.
It's fun to play.
My mom made macaroni and cheese.
Pog.
This won't be easy.
Get him.
That fire breathing gets me a little like.
It's the first video game you ever played.
Super Mario Brothers for the NES.
First game I really ever played.
Same, yeah.
I remember because.
So me and my siblings would play and we were terrible at it.
You've heard this story before.
That's lame.
All right, time that person up for fucking six weeks.
All right, so I've told the story before.
So siblings and I would.
So my dad would be like, all you got to do.
You just get to Bowser with five lives and I'll beat it.
He's like, as long as you get to the end of the game.
As long as you get to Bowser with at least five lives, I'll beat it.
And we would be desperately just trying to get to the end of the game with five lives.
Because we couldn't beat Bowser, but he could.
And he'd be like, Dad, Dad, we got six lives.
And he'd be like, all right, let me get in there.
And he'd die like five times in a row, but he would actually do it.
He would do it every time.
Good memories.
Because my dad knew that if we didn't have at least four or five lives.
Oh, I don't know if he's confident on doing it.
Oh, get your dad.
Yeah, we'd be cheering.
It'd be like, yeah, he did it.
He beat Bowser.
And he would just be like, that's right.
Okay, I'm going to pay attention.
What door did I knock on?
I just opened like five doors and I don't know where I'm going.
Okay, it's this one.
What are you going to do?
You coming?
How's the job going?
Start with off brand.
It's going awesome.
I'm starting to work on some projects.
I'm going to get some, you know, writing days in.
It's going great.
I'm really, really happy.
Trying to get the workflow, you know, different days that I'm going to be doing stuff and
meetings, meetings, meetings.
Is Ludwig a good boss?
Oh, yeah, I would say Ludwig is a great boss.
I confess I expected more from the old man and less from you.
This is the second time you've bested my sisters.
Men of your talents are rare indeed.
Did you get a new planner?
Why waste your lot with such undesirables?
If it is the hearth you long for, you will find more than enough warmth under my wings.
You know exactly what I want.
Hand over the dominant and I'll leave you in peace.
You would dare to make demands of me?
Know your place, little lamb.
Fool is the shepherd who heats every bleat of the flock.
And I will suffer yours no longer.
Must I spell it out for you?
See how the chief creative officer of off-brand does in this boss battle.
To the slaughter with you.
You brought it up.
I'm just.
Let's go.
That hurt a lot.
Oh, I don't have anything.
Yeah.
Headache on.
Cry all you.
There's no one to save you now.
Oh, it hurt.
Just charge it, charge it, charge it.
This time.
Shit.
Hold up.
3k, that's nothing.
Ram will fall.
I always press the L1.
Oh, go.
Oh, shit.
What does this mean?
Deadly embrace.
I will say it's much more difficult without the accessories on.
Come on, dog.
Get her.
Go.
Get her, Torgo.
Get her.
Shit, I'm in a combo.
Okay, we're good.
I thought it was crazy.
So this is as far as we've seen.
What's the difficulty?
The action.
There's two difficulties.
This story and action.
We've played your games.
I'm on action.
Tell me where he is.
Where are you?
What are you doing?
Why, why did you do that?
What the fuck?
Enough of this.
Oh.
I took it.
Now you really are only useful with birthday parties.
She's gone.
Give her back.
Or is she?
Where is Garuda?
Have you done?
Did you hear?
What the hell is going on?
Her power.
You took it from her.
How'd you do that?
And I'll take yours too.
You don't cut the shit.
That magical purple electricity.
I hope the bearers found a way out.
Looked cool.
This place is ready to collapse.
If your dominance started this fire,
and I'm betting he did.
What the hell is going on?
I thought that was us for a second.
We did not make it.
We didn't make it.
Oh boy, that's bad.
That's a bad thing for us to cut into being killed.
What was that?
I created a diversion as commanded, your grace.
The villagers escaped in the confusion.
As should we.
Yes.
Cutscene isn't over.
Basecam boy.
Yeah, I could do some upgrades.
I have a lot of points.
Come on.
If the catcher's leaving a burning care,
people might jump to conclusions.
Right.
Wings of change.
How can we remove basecam for cutscenes?
It makes it easier to pay attention to.
So you don't watch me pull boogers out of my nose and sneeze and stuff.
The power of wind.
Clive has claimed a portion of the icon Garuda's Essence.
Tuning with Garuda not only changes the elemental aspect of Clive's magic spells,
but also allows access to several new iconic abilities,
such as Gouge, a deadly flurry of talons
that can tear into an opponent for multiple hits.
Ability details can be found in the abilities tab in the main menu.
Garuda's Feet.
Garuda's iconic feat, Deadly Embrace,
can be used to draw smaller, lighter enemies toward Clive.
The action can also topple larger enemies and that, you know,
become partially staggered when their will gauge reaches 50%.
Toppling an enemy in this manner can deal significant damage.
So use it wisely.
This is called Deadly Embrace.
By the way, press L2 to cycle between currently attuned icons in real time,
allowing for more varied assault.
Cool down times for iconic abilities are displayed around the corresponding icon
in the ability widget.
Ability availability for all attuned icons can be confirmed.
Let me go like this.
So I have Deadly Embrace as this like hole.
I can feel it.
Okay, I'm back.
Inside me, the flames.
Gouge and Wicked Wheel.
Of course I want to try it out.
Let's try it on these people.
Pretty cool.
Come here!
What do you got?
That's not going to help you.
Hey, I think you'd like the Final Fantasy 16 battle theme.
I think so.
Thank God you have CC now.
It's helpful.
The pole is helpful.
All right, we got a big dragon thing here.
Oh my goodness.
Oh my God, I forgot how to play.
What is the actual just default magic with this leg?
Pretty cool.
7K.
You watch the Smurfs movie yet?
Nope, I will.
I will this weekend.
You have Lego hair?
That's fine.
I don't want to move it because it'll...
I don't want to touch it.
If I touch it, I screwed up.
I need to go upgrade my weapon.
I have materials to upgrade this.
Don't just avoid all the items.
Five bucks.
Okay, let's take a look.
Abilities.
Garuda Channeled.
All right, this is where I got to figure out what I want to do.
Because there's at least three plus icons in the game.
There's at least three.
What is this one?
I don't know.
I like the pole.
I like the slashes.
It's gouged.
This is good too.
What's down here?
I use this a lot.
Does the pole just upgrade the damage?
Ah, that's a good question.
Range.
Looks like range?
Range is pretty good.
I'll go with this.
I like this one.
Follow up strike speed.
Jump back then deliver a punishing counter.
If the jump evades an attack, counter potency is increased.
So is this just a regular dodge?
But backwards and then I press...
How do I do the move?
Or is it a new move?
I'm upgrading this.
I use it all the time.
All right, what do I got?
Is it a different ability?
It is.
Okay, I would probably replace this.
So I really want to try to evade with this thing.
So you want to go wham.
And if you get a perfect evade, it's way better.
What's the cooldown?
Hmm is very pretty.
It is very pretty.
I want to practice that move.
Cool stream.
You can use this in IRL.
Wait, Gav is here.
I didn't know Gav was going to show up.
I'm not going to...
I'm going to stop talking.
Who was it?
Good question.
Someone who didn't have their hands full
fighting a bloody harpy, I guess.
But what matters is they're safe.
Something they wouldn't be had it not been for you, Gav.
Just doing my job like.
So what about his dominant?
Gone.
And after we were so close.
I can track him.
Who are you?
Sir told us about your family.
Lost mewing to imperial steel.
Sometimes vengeance is the only thing that keeps you going.
I'm biting my lip off camera.
I know.
You would be scolding me if you knew it.
Go safely, brothers.
Raggedy likes you.
She's gone.
My lady, you have to hold on.
We're going to get you.
Gone, gone, gone, gone.
What am I going to do?
How long to the coastal road?
At this pace, we won't make it by sunset.
No, he'll cost me up like all the others.
What am I going to do?
My lady.
Just pretend you still have it.
Oh, my God.
What the fuck?
I was waiting to see what that guy's story was,
but we're not going to get it anymore.
I thought that was going to be a major boss battle,
but no, he's just gone.
What are we out here?
Goodbye.
Thank you.
Jerov.
Second in command of Wayload's Royal Intelligencers.
Serving under Benedicta Harmon.
Killed by footpads while attempting to evacuate
the stricken Benedicta from the collapsing we just got.
This is just what happened to him right now.
This is the eulogy.
This is like the two sentence of what just happened to this guy.
Wiki page updated.
That's so funny.
What does this one say?
Huh?
No more powers.
Her love for former Lord Commander Sid
was deep and true and left an equally abyssal hole
in her heart when he fled Wayload.
Just pretend you still have the powers.
Who's going to question you?
We'll be doing the slavers of this service
if we didn't appraise our worth.
Stay away.
It's all right.
They can't hurt you anymore.
Let's go home.
Is this at Sotophis' punishment for not listening to you?
This wretched world.
Still got power?
Huh?
No.
Do we not have the power?
Sid.
Do you feel it too?
By the flames.
The harvest is hungry.
Been too much, Aether.
She can't control it.
Rude isn't stopped.
That vortex will swallow this whole forest
and us along with it.
And I'll stop her.
You'll stop her.
I heard it again.
Someone is calling me.
Come in, lad.
That doesn't mean you have to listen.
Well, I should have gone with you.
Yeah.
Best character in the whole franchise.
Okay.
Clyde, I don't think you understand.
That's not just windy weather you're wandering into.
Benedict's rage knows no bounds.
And that's on a good day.
I don't want to know what's waiting inside that.
But I do.
I have to find out.
That's all you have to say.
And I'm not turning back.
That's the only thing you have to say is,
I don't care where we're going.
Okay.
What is this?
There are so many.
I won for every fragment of our mind.
I'm just trying to get items.
Three bloody finds.
All right, let's go.
Yep.
Oh, that looks good.
I'm always late on that one.
Everybody in?
Have you learned the parry system?
I have.
But I'm a dodge Andy.
And I'm way more comfortable dodging frame.
Um, invulnerability frame thing than I am Barry.
It's cool that you can do it though.
And understandable.
Have a nice day.
What?
Have a nice day, I guess.
Barry is hard in this game.
It did feel like it was tricky to pull off.
Hi.
Oh, that was like perfect.
Wait, this is an item right here.
How long is the game?
That's a good question.
I want to say probably,
I don't think anyone's beaten it.
It came out today.
Let me try doing this move.
See if I can get it perfect.
It's not quite.
Sick of Torgl.
Yeah, we finally got to hear it.
All right, I want to get the item that was over here.
And do that thing with your face.
So what do you want to do?
This?
Yeah, thanks, dude.
You look a bit sloppy today.
I was, no, I was going to do something weird.
I feel like I'm having a dream watching this.
Why does I have a beard?
Oh, one of these things.
Who the hell are you?
I feel like this is going to be a pretty,
it's going to be a milestone of the video game.
I think come on up here.
I am going to go back because I think it's time to upgrade.
Detour Danny.
I mean, yeah, I'm not going to go with just broken up shit weapons.
What do you got?
There's now a bastard sword.
So sell the bastard, sell the long sword by the bastard sword
and then upgrade the bastard sword.
It's a good sword for you.
It's okay to be scared of birds.
You can be, I love birds.
Do you know how badly I've wanted a bird to land on my finger?
Do you know how much I want that?
There's hummingbirds all over Vegas.
They're everywhere.
And I would like nothing more than to be able to put my hand out
and just Disney fucking princess have one land on my finger.
Do you understand how important that is to me?
Do you know how important that would be to me?
It'd be a huge deal.
It would change my whole life.
That would be life changing.
That would change my entire life.
I'm not, I ain't going to hear anybody tell me I'm afraid of birds.
Okay.
Do you even try?
Yeah, I have.
Do you know how many times I've thought like, wait, is today the day?
It's today the day because the outside and you'll hear them.
You'll hear them.
They sound like massive hornets.
So for the first spot, you have to be really aware of it.
Hummingbirds have been like, just kind of just hovering in front of me before.
It's just like, and they're gone.
I just, I just like did, I just did the guy's voice for one second.
Jeez.
All right.
We good.
Yeah. You know, how many times I've been just,
and I was imagining one landing and just doing this, doing this,
you know what I'm saying?
This, you know what I mean?
Like, who are you?
Who are you?
I'm just like, you're looking at me.
I know when you turn your head to the side, you're looking at me.
You would be a toucan.
Definitely.
What a cool bird.
What an amazing bird.
That sounds awesome.
What a cool.
Oh dude, you'd be a toucan.
That's fucking cool.
What a cool animal that is.
Your webcam looks really crusty today.
I think I look crusty.
You just don't want to say that.
All right.
I'm buying the bastard sword and I'm going to sell.
I'm going to sell the long sword and then upgrade the bastard sword.
120.
All right.
So it was the right idea.
Oh, well now I have two.
It's all right.
I got 130 damage now.
Better than what I had before.
I guess I can.
Torgl doesn't have an inventory.
I love this down here.
This is great.
It doesn't seem to have an inventory.
This seems like it can be upgraded though.
Okay, actually, it's probably better stuff to put on.
Dark sash.
Steel crowns.
This is way better than what I have right now.
Iron belt.
Can't do.
I'll put dark sash on.
Bastard sword plus two.
And then steel crowns.
Now let me sell this other stuff.
Oh, I actually do.
It's just different.
Doesn't it look different from my mind?
Hey, I crafted it and made money.
That's how I see it.
I don't want to sell any of these.
I'm not buying potions either.
All right.
I'm good.
Let's continue with what we're doing.
New weapon upgraded.
Let's go.
You'd be a screeching owl.
Count based.
Oh, that's what we saw when we were...
I was under the impression that we did that.
I thought we did that.
Maybe not.
Lost our party members.
Awakening.
Where did he go?
Oh, shit.
Oh, do I have to dodge?
We cut the shit.
All right.
So what's the deal?
Is it us?
Is it you?
Is it her?
Is this...
Is this Joshua?
This is Joshua.
All right.
Let's go.
She's huge.
Holy shit.
Okay.
We got to go.
Holy shit.
That hurt.
Take down.
Larger enemies will become partially staggered
when their will gauges are reduced to 50%.
Using Garuda's deadly embrace
on a partially staggered enemy will topple it,
leaving it vulnerable to follow-up attacks.
Okay.
So deadly embrace.
I don't even have that equipped.
Oh, yes, I do.
It's in mod chat right now.
What is in mod chat right now?
10k.
Let's go.
Oh, jeez.
I think I just have to avoid it.
Oh, that hurt a lot.
Oh, pull her down.
It hurt.
Goodbye.
Perfect music.
Oh.
Oh, it's over.
Pause.
Damn.
That was cool.
Music's...
Honestly, music's probably my favorite part.
There's so many different ups and downs.
There's so many different...
Yeah, it's great.
55 fangs came out of that.
Dude, I have to show you what they put in mod chat.
It is fucking crazy.
Some of these are fucking insane.
What even is this supposed to be?
I'm gonna...
Hold on.
Just watch the cutscene.
I don't want to fuck this up
because this is like insane.
Wait.
Uh-oh.
It's me, right?
That's what I...
That's what I was thinking.
Yeah.
It's in emote now.
Oh, shit.
I think this is gonna be a big deal.
All right.
That's really funny, but I need to pay attention.
No way.
Do I get to play like this?
You do.
Okay.
Ifrit.
Melee ranged and evade.
Charging enemy covering great.
This is a short period of time,
as well as dealing damage if the enemy is struck.
All abilities available while embodying Ifrit
can be obtained and confirmed on the abilities tab.
Let's go.
Monster battle time.
Oh, that was good.
Holy shit.
85,000 damage.
Punch.
Skyfall.
Tap.
No.
Uh-oh.
I'm now losing.
Oh, 30k.
Oh, shit.
That's better.
You stink.
Oh, my God.
Jesus.
Is this an arm?
Oh, shit.
Holy shit.
Sid right now is down on the ground floor.
Just like, I can't do any of that shit.
Gonna be up to you for the rest of the game.
I thought lightning was cool.
Not really.
And we're both throwing back.
This is awesome.
What?
Oh, am I ripping the arms?
Hellfire?
Hellfire!
That?
That sequence took like four months to animate.
That was crazy.
That was really cool.
Wind shard.
Is there any more or is that it?
Control Nick Clive.
It is you, isn't it, Clive?
Oh, here we go again.
Now.
He's not gonna activate into public.
No, he's not, right?
We're doing this again?
What the fuck is going on in this game?
What?
It's like a giant wizard.
Does he shrink back down to?
You're too nice as your problem.
Tells you to quit it, dude.
Yeah.
That's this.
Okay, well, so do I, can I get electricity out of my hands?
Because that's what I'm into.
Lorecheck, please.
The Warden of the Wind who Benedict had transformed into during her ill-fated flight
from the Empire takes the form of a fearful harpy,
summoning storms and tearing into the flesh to prey with hawk-like talons.
Such is the icon's frenzy for destruction that even allies of the dominant of the day won't.
And let's try that again.
For destruction that even allies of the dominant of the day are won't
to begin fleeting the battlefield when dark clouds gather over.
Wait, am I reading this wrong?
Am I reading this wrong?
I feel like, why can I not read this right?
Well, that happened.
All right, well, I love how it's like,
you have like 10 notifications about Sudolphus.
You have a lot of notifications.
He's been DMing you about his fucking wizard form.
That picture.
The ghost you've been chasing was inside you all along.
This fucking picture is ridiculous.
Who even made this?
I'm going to try to look like that.
I'm going to just grow everything.
Just turn the camera on one day, I'm going to look like this.
And there has to be a part during one of that stream where I laugh like this.
And my teeth are like black.
Why did you have to listen to him?
This can't be what you wanted, can it?
Dad.
Some time later.
How much later is this?
Who the fuck is this?
Who is this?
That horse is giant.
Oh my God.
The king is bold, desperate.
Will you engage him personally, your highness?
Of course.
Am I going to engage him personally?
Of course I'm going to turn into a giant whale.
You don't think I have the giant dolphin power?
Griegel's breath fill your wings.
You know what the fuck you're talking to?
Yep.
The Hombet.
The prince is with us.
New music track too.
Am I going to have to fight all these things eventually?
Precision?
Yeah.
Reform the cohorts.
At once, your highness.
I can't get over.
I can't get over the germa that drank the chaos potion.
You know, I've got powers but I'm all fucked up now.
That was cool.
No, I don't want to lore check.
I don't want to spoil myself or anything.
You plan on streaming the whole game?
Let's figure that out.
I'm going to ask you that very question.
Ah, you're awake.
Because I really like it.
I would.
You're just full of surprises.
I think it's fun.
First that trick with Geruda, then whatever the hell that other thing was.
Didn't know you had it in you.
Do it.
Hey.
It was me.
I killed him.
I killed Joshua.
I killed them all.
I'm a monster.
And I deserve to die.
So end it.
End it.
Please.
I reckon I can take you.
If that's what you want.
But first, I thought I'd give you the benefit of my timeless wisdom.
It seems to me-
Take him in a fight.
But since you're still breathing, you might as well make yourself useful.
I don't know about that.
Get dressed.
Pretty as you are, you're not my type.
I'll see you in the hole.
I don't know, I have uncontrollable demon rage.
He's a cool wizard, but I mean, gigantic demon.
I think I can win.
He just beat you.
Yeah, but I wasn't prepared.
What are you going to do now?
Plus, I was fighting Garuda, who was also one of these icons.
Wages of guilt.
There are certain times during the game that side quests will become temporarily unavailable
until progress has been made through the main scenario.
Okay, so I have to focus on the main story.
There's, we'll hear what he has to say.
Don't go making me throw you back in there now, eh?
Hello, Doug.
I think I'm just gonna upgrade if I can.
So, what'd it be?
What is that?
That's the, okay, this is, this one's purple.
Storm Cry.
That's way cooler than the Bastard Sword.
Does it have any properties on it or is it just, they don't get it?
No scratches, right?
Can't reinforce it.
Anything else?
Ooh, cool looking.
Can I buy anything from you out here?
Look what the curl dragged in.
Coin purse weighing you down?
This is just better.
Call my guy.
Hold on, can I make anything new besides the sword?
I'm not much bothered either way.
Play it quick.
What do you want?
What am I wearing for a belt right now?
This one, right?
Plus two.
I need a plus one, but don't I already, oh, I have a plus two.
I just don't, I can't upgrade any more plus, uh, pass plus two.
Okay, well, I have the new weapon.
That's all that matters.
Anything else?
Hi, can we, can we get a poll in chat?
Do you want me to continue to stream Final Fantasy 16?
It would probably be on the, just chill nights.
Probably turn the cam off, play it and just hang out.
What do you think?
Can we get a poll?
I really like it.
So I'm going to play it regardless.
So I'm either going to, I'm either going to turn it on and just play it
for fun, just chilling out on stream or I'm just going to play this
and just with my mouth open on the couch.
That has to be 85% at least since you gave that same number
to Strawberry Magic.
Strawberry Magic is not Final Fantasy 16.
Final Fantasy 16 is a little different than Strawberry Magic was.
I would say.
I think that's a little different.
I mean, most people are into it.
Then I'll keep playing it.
I mean, that's pretty overwhelming.
That seems like it was almost 90%.
Yeah, I'll, I'll just stream it more.
Uh, I'm going to do this next mission and then I'm probably going to call it.
So whatever happens at the end of this, that'll be it for tonight.
I'll see you on Saturday.
Uh, the sponsor is obviously Square Enix, sponsor of the stream,
but I kind of kept going.
Very, very fun.
What are you going to do with the demos?
Uh, Saturday.
Gav.
Gav's gone through a fair bit of trouble for you.
The least you can do is hear the poor bugger out.
He's going to meet us at the King's.
Yes, we'll play SOS 3 on Saturday and we'll do some steam demos.
And then after that, after Saturday, I'll probably come back to this and just play.
Oh yeah, I Square Enix, thanks for the sponsor.
Um, the game's great.
It's out on PS5 right now.
Came out literally today.
It's very good.
The demo is available.
You can just get the demo and play it if you want right now.
You've seen it already, but if you want to check it out, maybe see if it's for you.
I think it's great.
I'm having a lot of fun.
I'm going to continue to play it.
I'm going to keep streaming it.
So, but for now, let's, um, let's finish up this last mission
and then I will call it and see you Saturday.
Uh, I don't think I need any other items.
We waited 295 days for a half a stream of sorcery.
Dude, you're a booger streamer.
Yeah, I'm not just getting half a stream of sorcery.
You're getting us getting back into sorcery.
Plus you're getting, I'm going to do voices.
German does voices, right?
It's so funny when German does voices.
You'll get at least two or three different tones and two or three different pitches.
Someone's going to sound like this.
Isn't that cool?
Isn't that weird?
And I'll do the dinosaur quiz.
What dinosaur are you?
Please think about it.
Clive, the rumors all point to that was an Imperial signal.
There shouldn't be here.
The old force been abandoned for years.
Our little chat can wait.
I need to see what the bastards are up to.
For those of you that didn't know, I know we talked about it a few times,
but you liked Final Fantasy 14.
The producer and director of Final Fantasy 14, producer of this game.
I know that a lot of people really like that game.
So you obviously got the devil may cry, Yoshi P, Yoshi P, Yoshi P is a legend.
Honestly, I wait till he's done talking.
I was never really into Final Fantasy.
I was a big, I liked the old ones,
but I didn't really pay that much attention past like six or seven.
Really?
This is good.
This is really good.
I'm very happy with it so far.
Oh, there's a giant enemy.
Spiders have a follow up to that, don't I?
Cool.
Yeah, the composer and sound director of Final Fantasy 14.
That's soaking.
Don't know.
Also on this game.
Somebody said this is like a dream team for Final Fantasy,
which that's really cool.
Is that a Minotaur?
It is a Minotaur.
All right, let's go.
Pull him down.
Oh, I'm having heels.
Oh, that was perfect.
Oh, cool down.
Oh, I did not time that right.
All right, don't blow it here.
Don't blow it.
This time.
If you do Torgl buttons mid-dodge, you'll get precision.
Cool.
Pet Torgl, oh, we're going to riot.
I did already have.
I love how he's just kind of like, yeah.
I need to heal.
Potion.
I need way more of those.
He's never going to check the lore ever again.
Hey, dude.
The hooded man.
A mysterious man that many believed to be a dominant of fire.
Clive first saw him at Phoenix Gate on the night of the Imperial invasion.
And for years believed him to be the dominant of the icon that killed his brother.
But to Clive's eternal chagrin, he has proved otherwise.
Pretty bloody hides.
What does it mean?
Oh, that's a good move.
Awesome music.
I just keep biting my lip and it's going to cause me stress.
Still making a little clay guys.
I actually haven't in a little while, but I'll get back into it.
Another minotaur.
Okay.
Well, I beat one.
I could beat the other.
Oh, this is not good.
I saw him come from a mile away, too.
Stop hurting these poor animals.
They don't deserve this.
You're saying true.
Is a minotaur an animal?
What is a minotaur?
Isn't a minotaur like a guy with horns that's like a bull?
Minotaur is like a mythical being.
Half man, half bull.
Humans are animals.
Yeah, animals can be mythical, too.
You're an animal.
I'm an animal.
Stop the violence.
There's no way I'm going to let Gab die.
I'll be actually upset if Gab dies.
They keep killing characters.
I will be upset if Gab is dead.
Bye.
Your webcam is atomically...
Are we doing it?
No, it's all right.
What's his name?
Uncle Fester is here to help us.
Forget his name.
Sid!
That's it.
Okay.
Oh, let's go.
Do you have any heals, dude?
Do you have any potions?
Oh, yeah.
Shit.
Uh-oh.
I got it.
That's exactly what I was trying to do.
Oh, shit.
Jesus Christ.
I had potions.
I had potions and I didn't use them.
Get in.
That was really, really scary.
First death.
Level 19.
It doesn't matter.
I had to sneeze and I couldn't even do the fucking funny joke.
Come on.
My back is itchy.
Each fight in this game feels like it has a lot of weight on it.
It's like everything feels like you're in this and it feels fun.
Even fighting the spiders.
We need to save.
We got to save.
Yeah.
No, this is too much.
It's too much.
Shit.
He's not going to...
His eyes aren't going to turn like red and he's going to turn like a big goose.
Holy shit.
That was cool.
He's holding on to the rock, right?
Yes.
He's got the branch, the one branch sticking out from the rock.
Do not.
Thank God.
Gav has plot armor.
Well, I don't speak so soon because
remember the guy that got hit in the face with the axe
that we didn't even get an introduction for yet?
He seemed like he was ready to get involved.
My sniffing days will be over.
Thank you.
Truly.
Yeah, a lot of people have died.
That would be deemed pretty important, I would say, huh?
So, what news?
I found out where your friend's heading for one thing.
Gav, I...
Him and his mate are on their way to your old stomping ground, Rosaria.
You should have seen what they did to the Imperials who tried to stop them.
There's no question about it.
He's a dominant fire, all right?
He can't be.
Clive, I saw you turn into an icon before my very eyes.
And yes, there's a good chance it was you who killed the phoenix.
But we weren't alone, were we?
There was the fellow you saw enter the whirlwind.
I...
I saw him too.
You didn't dream it, Clive.
He's out there.
I don't know who this guy is, but he's chuffing back at that.
Who is he?
Ask me.
I don't bloody know.
But I do know one thing.
You're gonna find him and find out.
It's a cigarette Andy in chat right now.
We have a few of those here.
You swore you'd avenge your brother's death.
That you'd never rest until you'd hunted down the man responsible.
So, find out if this man's responsible and kill yourself if he's not.
Sid.
I...
Don't thank me.
Thank Gav.
Thank you, Gav.
Yeah, well, yeah.
Hot stew?
Crusty bread?
No birds returning this year.
The deadlands have swallowed their roosts like it's not.
We're running out of time.
That's definitely Joshua.
We'll be in Rosaria in a day or two.
It's a phoenix.
Phoenixes don't die.
That goes against all phoenix lore ever.
Back to where it all began.
Yeah.
Who's that?
Who's the girl?
He must be stopped.
We don't have the reveal yet.
Can't lorry check the non-reveal.
No updated wiki?
No, not yet.
All right, cool.
I think that about calls it for me.
That was a good time.
I will play it again.
We'll stream it again.
Saturday, we're going to do Steam Next, Best, and Sorcery.
And then after Saturday, I'll come back to Final Fantasy 16.
What are your overall thoughts?
I think it's...
So the boss fights are some of the most fun I've had playing a game in a long time.
You just feel like you're doing a good job.
The game does a really great job of making you think you're doing very well.
The dodge mechanic is really fun.
When the follow-up attack, the music that plays in all the fights,
they vary it up so it's not the same thing every time, which I really like.
I don't know how big the world is.
I think that's the one kind of, I guess, outlier is.
Is there an opportunity for me to go and just kind of play and go collect stuff?
I'm imagining so.
But as it stands so far, I think it's great.
I'm going to keep playing it.
It looks like there's quite a bit.
How long have I played so far, including the demo?
The demo is included in this, too.
So this is five hours and about five hours and some change.
Eight? Eight hours total so far.
Probably another island.
Yeah, we'll see.
I like it.
I'm having a good time playing it, so I'm going to keep playing it.
And yes, the stream was sponsored, but I think you all know.
I don't think I would come back to the game and play it again if I wasn't into it.
So we'll play it again.
You'll see it on this channel at some point early next week, mid next week.
It's a good game, yeah.
And I'll see you Saturday.
Thank you again Square Enix for sponsoring the stream.
Again, it's on PS5 right now.
You have a PS5.
I highly recommend you at least check out the demo because that is free.
And you can just play a little bit of the first few hours of the game.
First like hour or two.
Well, I want to make sure I save it, though.
I think it's auto saves.
Yeah, I think it's auto saves.
I'll be fine.
This is coming through my.
That's weird.
It's coming through my speakers.
They're supposed to be music playing, but.
It's just coming through my actual speakers.
Can you hear it?
Very, very faintly.
Well, it's playing to my right somehow.
It's only when you talk.
Well, thanks for sticking around.
Have a great night.
Call your mother.
Final Fantasy 16.
Go check it out.
Thank you for resuming sorcery.
My mother is back from her trip just in time.
Well, there you go.
Put it close to the mic.
I kind of can't.
My mic is connected to my desk.
Kind of bolted on.
Yeah, it's not going anywhere.
When's the next no cam chill stream?
I've been doing a lot of those.
I mean, just kind of base cam and high energy.
Just sort of whenever I have the energy, I'll do it.
But yeah, I mean, maybe next stream.
The next Final Fantasy stream.
Absolutely.
We'll just kind of hang out and just have my mouth open.
Just playing it.
What demos do you plan on checking out for next best?
I plan on just going to the popular tab.
Obviously, also, if you have a recommendation, put it in the Discord.
The Discord recommendation channel.
Give it a look.
If you have one that you think, well, yeah, you really should play that.
Then throw it in the recommended.
I'll take a look.
Add it on the list.
I plan on just kind of blowing through a dozen of them or so over a few hours.
But see you later.
Don't forget the BLT.
No, I won't.
I'll take at least one bite of a BLT on Saturday.
Probably starting around 4 Pacific on Saturday, 4 p.m.
All right.
I'll see you later.
Have a good night.
Take care of yourselves.
And goodbye.