What? What? What on earth just happened? I just got fucking headshot through the gate.
No, seriously, what? That's impossible. Not anymore. You sound like terrified. I am. Because
that was legitimate. You're not upset. You sound scared. It's not as safe as we once
thought. Go to like the top left area. Yeah. By that exit. There's a tiny slit on the wall
right in front of the, before the gate. So like to the right of the gate. Yeah. It's like on the
wall. It's not parallel with the gate. Oh, I see it. I see it. So I have to be like here. Oh my god.
Dude, how the hell, this is like so difficult to like do this. You pretty much have to wait for
someone to walk in like two precise spots. Yeah. Like on top of a rock out there and just maybe in
the hill in front of it. Yeah. Oh, this is the guy. This is the guy. Oh, oh my god. Oh my god,
I got him. Dude, what people don't realize. This is what people don't realize. When you're watching
this video right now, this is like this video was taken like a week apart from the last one. Like
this is unbelievable that I got that guy revenge on that guy like a week or two later. I can't,
I can't believe the same guy is here. Was it incentive phase? Yes. The exact same scenario
except reverse it. I got him.