What are we doing?
Oh yeah, that's what I like right there, yeah.
Can you like do it?
Hold on, hold on, not yet, not yet.
No, go further away.
You're not cooperating.
Hey! What the fuck are you doing?
Get in the car!
All right, all right.
Get the fuck in here!
All right.
God damn it, man.
That's that motherfucker. I recognize that face anywhere.
Get over here, you piece of shit.
No, no, I'm just dead, no.
I'm gonna catch up to you.
Come here, you piece of god damn it.
Get over here.
I swear to god.
I'll push you over, I'll get you.
I got a knife.
Oh shit, he's got a knife.
It's time to turn.
Please, I was just kidding, I didn't want to get...
No ambulance, I got time.
Come on now, come on, use those legs.
Hey.
Man, it just takes a lot out of you.
God damn.
All I wanted to do was go to bed.
German, stop, stop.
No, go back, you took way too long.
Stop it!
Oh, geez, man.
Sometimes I just rock out to Madonna in the car.
Holy shit, dude, this lady's face.
She's like...
Hold on, I have to move.
I have to move for a second.
Why can I not move? Why am I stuck?
You're in the passenger seat.
We're in the graveyard.
The graveyard dance party.
Alright, we need more, we need more.
It's going to crash the server, you know it will.
Oh my god, German, German, look.
Stand where I'm standing, and like look at them.
You see way in the distance.
There's other people dancing.
These guys don't give a shit.
We have to do more of this.
There has to be more.
Hold on, let me on.
Dude, that part where we just saw them
all dancing around, not even near us.
I want to go to a busy street.
Why are they still all the way out here?
Hey.
Well, yeah, that was a good day's work, boys.
Yeah, that makes a lot of sense.
Let's get the hell out of here now.
Okay, you can do it, Carolyn.
You can just practice your swing.
And you can get on that pizza.
What kind of person does that?
Da-da-doo-da.