Look at the people in the background. This dude looks like he's holding two cups that are just invisible.
Hey, can I get one of those soldiers you're holding, dude?
In your default position?
I'll just kill this guy. I don't know how much health everybody has.
This technique seems to be working pretty well. Oh, another guy. Another guy holding two cups in his hands.
Excellent. I don't know what I'm supposed to be doing.
Can I please get out of here? I broke his sword.
We've been fighting for so long, this guy's sword is broken in half.
Yet for some reason he still continues to fight me and I still can't bring his health down past 5%.
Like, I have to be doing something wrong, right?
I have to be.
Both of us wouldn't have arms or legs anymore.
So now both of our swords are broken, which means this is a candlestick fight.
Notice the design work on the candles.
Can we stop this, please? End the fucking tutorial. God.
This is sad. How do I stop this?
We're fighting with two broken swords.
This guy's wearing like a speedo.
Everybody is talking at once.
I can't understand this.
Can you please talk it one at a time?
Big battle.
Help, I don't want to die.
Whoa.
He actually did it?
Holy shit.
I didn't think that was that. I thought he was going to just yell it like a taunt, like a command.
Am I on the train tracks? Can I move?
Train's coming. The fucking train is coming.
No way. That's it? What happened?
I don't even know what to even describe what just happened.
Did I lose?
Hey, I'm allowed to kill you if I want to.
That's not too extreme end of the spectrum. I don't know what is.
Oh, hey, hello. I'm going to kill you if I want.
This guy's not doing so well.
Get out of the way. Don't you see him having fun making this guy stay standing?
What is she saying? Oh, fuck.
No, will you watch out?
Lady, if you don't see, I'm kind of busy right now.
Take another egg.
I'm not paying for it.
All right. That was pretty easy.
I just had to not pay for the egg.
These guys are on the case.
Crime rate? I've been arre...
You get arrested?
There's just an egg. Come on.
So I stole an egg. What are you going to do?
You're going to like slap me on the wrist?
I am naked tied up in a dungeon.
Other naked dudes are throwing slabs of granite at me.
I took an egg.
Excuse me, sir. Excuse me.
Can I ask you a question? Do you know where the nearest subway is?
I know I could ask one of the officers around here,
but you seem like a citizen that knows what they're talking about.
So should I take a right down the street or is it a left?
Yeah. Okay. So I should go that way.
Oh, no.
Somebody's hurt over here.
The dude with the...
You're telling me the dude with the fucking box on his head can't see?
No way. That's unheard of.
Again, like, what the fuck are you people doing?
What are you doing? Why would you do something like that?
You can't see or hear the thing tracking along the...
Hey, watch me! Hey, watch this! Hey, watch me!
Let's go fishing in the man-made moat with no fish in it.
That sounds like a plan.
Did you shake... That guy knew.
See, that guy knew there were no fish in here.
Oh, he was wrong. He was wrong. There's crabs in here.
Hey, old lady. Edge up!
No. No, no, no, no, no, no. That's not...
No, no, no, no. Ma'am. Ma'am, you okay?
Ma'am? I killed her.
I don't know who they're... Who is he cheering on?
Shoot him! Shoot this guy!
These guys all have guns.
Will you please light this guy up? Oh, my God.
Shoot him. Somebody shoot him.
The seven of you with guns, shoot this guy.
He's trying to kill me with his blade.
You guys are running around like cockroaches.
I just drank a beer.
This is so exciting. You just slashed me with a fucking blade.
I'm going to chug my beer.
This guy can do whatever he wants and nobody cares.
Let's see how long this takes.
Where is this guy's health?
Because I feel like this guy's taken at least 15 to 30 bullets into his body.
Like, that was a neck shot. He shot him directly into his neck.
That was in the head. That was in his face.
Is he dead? Oh, I think he's finally...
No, he's running. He's running. He's running.
He's running. He's running. Put this down.
No! Don't let him get away!
Don't let him get away!
No!