Hello. Good afternoon. How are you? Fresh water. Keep me going. We're going to continue playing
The Incredible Hulk Ultimate Destruction. Don't know what The Incredible Hulk is or what ultimate
destruction means. Um, you're in for a big treat today. And let me tell you, there are like 300
other Marvel characters. If you think The Hulk is cool, just wait till you see fucking radiation,
man. I'm sure he exists in Marvel. Let's find out. Okay. Uh, radiation, man. Marvel. They have a
database with like fucking 5,000 superheroes. Yes. Radioactive man, I guess. Radioactive man.
He's there. Marvel is the Simpsons of superheroes. Wait, am I following that correctly? It's wait,
jokes to the Simpsons are like Marvel to superheroes is what you're saying.
Okay. I get, I get you now. I get you. Wrong order. Jokes on the Simpsons are to like
superheroes that exist in Marvel. Howard the Duck is the best character. I mean, if it was a frog,
I'd probably agree with you. Why is there no frog Marvel superhero? Is there? Is there like a,
is there a frog man? Let's see. Frog Marvel. Is there a frog in Marvel? Yep. There is. His name
is leapfrog leapfrog. Cool. I have, why do I not own every single comic of this?
That's unfortunate. Here's to a good stream. Yeah. We're going to play some more Hulk.
I feel like I'm going to beat the game. I think there's only like another four plus five hours
or so left in the game and I'm going to, I'm going to beat it. If I don't beat it. Well,
then I'm in deep shit because if I can't be Hulk, if I cannot beat Hulk ultimate destruction,
but I will beat Simpsons hit and run. It's a problem there. Anyways, let's go. Uh,
we're just going to pick up where we left off yesterday. Is exactly right here. I just remember
the controls. A is jump. Good. You have to eat a Funko pop if you can't beat the game.
I don't want to eat a Funko pop. All right, let's get going. Show us your room so we can make fun
of you. No, I learned my lesson as of yesterday. Okay. Lesson has been learned. I ain't ever shown
myself on camera ever again. Good. We're sorry. Okay. Somebody just hit me in the air, right?
That's not even possible. That's not even possible to hit me in the air. The threat has dropped.
What that means is I can't see him anymore. Therefore he doesn't exist.
Well, you know, when are they going to innovate on that? By the way,
I want some real AI innovation. GTA six. Check this out. Holy fucking holy shit. I just figured
out the greatest system ever. You guys know the nemesis system that everyone loved and was obsessed
with in a shadow of mortar. Imagine in GTA six, there's like detectives that like, like will track
you down and like they'll do their little intro. They'll come in and like detective car and they'll
be like asking you questions. That would be incredible. It wouldn't happen that frequently.
That would be awesome to have like a nemesis system, but it's detectives in GTA six.
Can I just break the bridge? Can I break the bridge? Where's the star on top? Is it on top of
the bridge? Nintendo should hire you. Well, Nintendo doesn't, it hasn't been a Nintendo
grant of photos since ever. Has it ever been? Okay. I can make this jump. I promise.
Just break it so I can get it. The camera. Sorry. Oh, nobody was in there. Okay.
Hey, hey, let me, excuse me. Was that a missile? Don't worry. There's always a guy with a missile
launcher. Where is he? Find a monk. Come here. I want you to watch me do this. You're going to
watch me complete this. It's Chad. No, no, put me down. You're going to sit here. You're going to
watch me get to the star. No, please. No, you're so bad. You can't do it. Please don't hurt me.
I'm not going to hurt you. I'm not going to hurt you. The sharks might.
Turns out he hit the edge of the bridge. Sorry. Wait, what are you guys doing?
Why? What are you people doing? Why are you jumping off the bridge? Hey, why are they?
I'm not doing this. Am I? I have nothing to do with this. I can't. Well, cut it out. Okay.
Let's do it. Our stolen mainframe interfaces directly into the division satellite tracking
system. Viewers dropping. Oh my God. Get the fuck out of here. Secured research facilities.
Get out of here. Profilers are as delicate as they are there. So you're going to have to bring
the whole truck back. Oh, that's secured by a mechanized escort team and some sort of energy
defense field. If I had more time, I could get some data on this, but you intercept the truck
and bring it back. That sounds easy enough. But anyways, detective and they'd be named
and each person in a different game could have their own detective. That was like coming after
them. Maybe you could even be a detective. No, that would never work. Maybe you could be a detective
in somebody else's game, but no, the first person that was able to invade your game like Dark Soul
style and be a detective would just fucking fly a helicopter to where you were and just launch
missiles at you while you ran around in a circle until you died. And then they would leave your
game. This would never work. And on paper, it's a great idea. In practice, it's horrible.
Intercept. I have to take the whole truck. Jeremy, you're cool. Hope you're doing well.
Hey, thanks. Did I make it? I did. Forward. Dash. I think I made okay time here. That was
a nice sponsored one guy. How do you sponsor one guy? I don't understand. But did you mean I'm
paying people to write nice things about me? Is that what you're saying? All right. I'm going to
take it slow. Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Give me this shit. Shield. Okay.
Where's this helicopter? Oh, damn it. Oh shit. Oh, it looks like three detectives got in my game.
No. Okay. Yeah. Where's the nice investigation you got going here? Oh, there he is.
Oh, the three of you in a discord together. I think it's funny to like come in my game and do
this. How do I turn off online mode? Because that's what's going to happen. Anybody know?
I can't wait to read like the 50 fucking steam discussion threads about how to turn off online
mode. Thanks a lot, guys. I just got absolutely destroyed. That was insane. Okay. So lesson
learned. Got to destroy the helicopters first. If only you had a move that blocked missiles.
I know it's called play in offline mode. It's going to run down the road. Nice Funko pop loser.
Where were you yesterday? Are you watching the VOD and you think it's a live chat?
Wait, that doesn't make any sense. How would that be possible? All right. I'm going for it.
Here we go. There they are. All right. All right. All right. All right. Give me cars.
Where are they? They're up there. Get out of the fucking way. We go in three, two, three,
two, one. Launch homing car. Got it. Oh my God. Get over. It's still, that can't be still alive.
Right. Oh, fuck you. Health, right? No, I have to kill these things. Otherwise I'm in deep trouble.
Hi. Kick it. Backhand. Kick. Headbutt. Buy coffee. What? Did somebody just say buy coffee?
He's still talking about Funko pop. Am I ever going to get you guys to stop talking about Funko
pops? Am I going to, am I going to have to eat like, oh no, am I going to have to eat like a
live squid on stream for you guys to like, be like, holy shit. This is, I got to, this is boy. Okay.
Fuck the Funko pops ever. This dude's eating squid. Do I have to eat a cooked squid calamari
on stream for you guys to stop this? Here we go. All right. Yeah. I intercept it. Don't kill it.
I have to grab this and run away with it. But this tank over there has his items.
Great. Hank. Almost there. Oh fuck. It's almost there. It's almost there. Oh, I did too many
jumps. I did too many jumps. Don't let it die. Come here. Get it. He's on two wheels. He's showing
up. Wait, why is he electrified? What? I got to break it. Throw something at it. Who the fuck are
you? Okay. Get it. Is it electrified still? Wait, what the fuck? Locate division transport.
Retrieve division transport. Okay. I located it and I tried to retrieve it. What do you mean?
Read. Locate transport. Retrieve transport. It's, there it is. What else do I have to do besides
play city heroes? They don't even exist anymore. Why do I feel like I'm at like times five speed?
Help. No, don't throw the tank. What is? Okay. Like seriously. Honest to God.
Did you give me a break? Why are these tuned like this? And now I see. Yes, I just said tuned.
Okay. Why is this tuned like this? Fucking God. I'm about to die because the helicopters
fly around at 1200 miles per hour and they drive into the fucking ground and into buildings and
doesn't even matter. They just slam and skid all over everything. I was fucking tuned like that.
He's got a bus. Why do I have the bus in my hand? I mean, if you were in this bus, which okay,
if you could get across the whole city in fucking like two minutes instead of like 40.
Okay. Mission objective. Disable division transport vehicle by throwing things at it.
What am I doing that? I was throwing shit at it already. How many things? How many things
do I have to throw at it? Do I have to keep doing this until it's broken? Oh, I don't. Do I?
They're destroying the thing. I can't even, man. This is fucking ridiculous. This is made by the
Simpsons hit and run devs. No chance that it's not. No chance. It has to have been. Get. No,
don't jump in the water. How do I avoid the water? How do I avoid the water?
Mike, how far am I? Where's the nearest one? What? Fuck. I have to go around the whole thing.
That's not cool. Here comes a fall joke. No, I don't want to do this one again.
Can anyone count how many times? Okay. How many missions have I done so far?
I think I've done what? Like 10 missions. I think at every single mission at the end,
I've said, no, no, I don't want to do this one again. I ran by it. I ran by it. Fuck.
I'm literally not even paying attention to the game. I'm just speaking to you guys.
Jump out. But what I was saying was I don't think I've ended a mission and gone. Yes. Oh,
I wish I could do that one again. Shield grind. I'm going to get the shield grind.
I have 100,000 Hulk points. I was going to say green points. All right. Shield grind. Grind any
shield just like a board. I don't want. How's this going to even help me? What?
How's this going to help me? A club smasher, air sonic, missile punchback, reflect projectiles
with a well-timed punchback. I want to try this move out. Remember the shield grind is a full
letter grade. Oh, is that a car? That's actually all right. Cool. Try following the on-screen
instructions. We need to get a handle on these new powers. There are 30 missions. I'll see you
guys next week. I've already done like 15 of them. If you can target, see what if I just punch
wildly? Will it work? That is confirmed. I have it. You still get, okay, if they, if they fire
10 of them at you, you're going to get hit by nine. Well done. But also they die. That's true.
All right. Let's go. Oh, that is actually the same depth. I, yeah, I can tell.
Why do they call him the Hulk? It's the, what do you mean? You talk, well, you're talking about
like, why do, why do they call him the Hulk? Cause he's a big person, like huge hulking,
jacked, large, lots of mass. What do you, I don't know. I got to buy more shit.
Yeah. That's a mass. This is what it means. A critical thunder clap. No, no, no. It's too
expensive. I want like air critical atomic, air enemy grapple. Yes. Those guys are so spear impale
max charge a club throw and spear Hulk class opponents. Yeah. I don't feel like that sentence
I can't even comprehend this sentence. Max charge a club throw and spear Hulk class opponents
comprehending it. Max charge a club throw and spear Hulk class opponents. Yep. Running. Uh,
definitely bowling. Yes. Give me this. Create a spherical bowling ball. Nice. But I want bowling
cyclone skyjack ride any aircraft to its death or pummel it. Yes. Thank God.
Dashing ground slam dash into a classic ground smash, clearing a crowd of enemies from Hulk's
path. Yes. What else we got? Gamma quake. Use Hulk's, use Hulk size foes for an area of effect
attack. David, it's a superhero prototype also made by the Simpsons hit and run devs.
This is literally an RKO. Why did you read that? Like a restaurant commercial? I did.
I don't know. Cause it was like classic. Oh, turn this into a classic. They usually say that before
they say like their classic pasta or their classic breadsticks or their classic Italian
cuisine or pair it with a classic red wine. I don't know. That's what they say. Classic. Hey,
you posted cringe, bro. Thanks for the five community subs. Thanks a lot. We need a bunch
of uranium 235 from the nuclear power plant. Chances are Blonsky knows we're coming. Thankfully,
you know your way around fissionable material. Locate two fuel. All right. Get retrieve fuel
rods. That's all I have to do is get fuel rods. There's nothing else on the list of things.
It's just get rods. Found them. Those look really unstable. A couple of fuel rods. I want you to
know. I mean, nothing against you personally. And this should happen in the circumstances.
Homer working like this place. I'm sorry. Banner. I don't have a choice. Neither of us do.
Who is this? I'm different than all your other. I just, I got one hit.
Is there like a, how to not get hurt?
Get all of the guys. Okay. Let me figure out a fight. You know,
the boss fight, but then that just did a boss fight. I'm going to.
Worst gets going. Throw shit at her. Did you actually just say wrong? Where? All right,
we're good. Jump rope. No wrong move. All right. You can't do charge attacks on her. You got to be
quick. Call me a baby. What'd you say? First try. I think so too.
You're annoying. Stop doing that. Why? All right. That's it. You came to me this time.
You're the idiot.
What kind of jail is this? It's an interesting prison. No, no, no. I just tried to butt drop her.
Oh my goodness. All right. Help me. Critical mass is where I have to shine.
Oh yeah. Well, I learned this. I don't have it anymore. Nevermind.
I didn't learn it apparently. Turns out I don't know shit lady. Come on. Get over here.
Give me this thing. It didn't hit her. What? What's happening? I don't know. Stop.
Don't. Oh, come on. How did it just come to me?
You like it? Come here. All right. Now we act like a coward. Wait a minute. No, go in.
Don't go. Go on. Be a coward again.
Run. Nice. Can I hang on the walls? Can I just jump on the ceiling?
There's just so many. What the? Oh, I'm so mad by that one. Kick her. Kick her in the face.
This. Okay.
Do you see the placement on those beams? Get the fuck. No. But they're eventually going to get me.
See? No, don't jump at her. Okay. This one's not that powerful. Step on her head. Fuck you. Yeah.
Listen to me, banner. You don't understand. I had no choice.
It's Blonsky. He puts some kind of tracking device in my head. Never safe.
Don't you think you should have written that on a piece of paper and held it up beforehand?
You know what I mean? We could have saved ourselves an entire epic boss fight if you just held up a
fucking note that said all this. I do. It's got a tracking thing in your head. Just text it to me.
He can't read. He can. All right. Leave him a voicemail. This is before phones, but he can't.
Hulk has a phone? Yeah. Floor kick. Deliver instant disrespect with the floor kick.
I don't care how much it is. I'm getting it. Increase the power of critical mass. Yeah.
Elbow drop. What? There's so many moves. There are too many moves. That's all I can do.
Hey, Willakilla, thanks for the five subs. Five community subs. Appreciate it. Just dropping
those. Sick. Now grind around town. Don't worry, I will. Blansky's. It's all Blansky. Blonsky.
Thousands of people just left. Fucking Bugleberry decides to start talking.
Bye, guys. What's happening to me? My darling scientists aren't supposed to fear.
I should be just out of going. Oh, I just swallowed air. Sorry. Cool. Blonsky file detected.
I already bought all the moves. Let me try the, um, what was it? Disrespect. Let's go to the city.
Next mission is clean sweep. I can see it. All right. Let's try the elbow drop.
Oh, wait, do I have to? Oh, there it is. That's so stupid. I do it from the second rope.
All right. Let's try this on somebody. It works.
That move is so good. It's so good. I'm going to use that all the time. Oh, the grind. Right.
Okay. So get a shield, right? Okay. This is bad. This is, how is this? This is slower than running.
Can I jump like this? This is Tony Hawk. Why is it playing twice? Why is it playing twice?
Cause I haven't got, whoops. Hold on. All right. Hold on. Here we go.
I don't know when you can do that in Tony Hawk. All right. Let's get this. Hey,
thanks for the five community subs adventure MF Dan and five from Mandalore. Thank you both of you.
Play it like Superman. Oh, there's a place where everyone can be happy.
My fucking world. All right. Let's go first. Just give me one second.
Okay. Now I know why this game, now I see why this game is fun. They added an elbow drop.
Now I get it. What about the bowling ball? I need a big thing to bowl.
Out of mana. Can't do that. Out of mana. Fuck. I gotta get back in the portal. Fuck.
Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Okay. I'm all right. How many guys do I have left?
Two? Fuck. Okay. I gotta go grind again. Wait, who is that? Bruce. No, get. Come on. You're so
slippery and sticky at the same time. How? Blonsky is overseeing the deployment of gamma suppressing
gas pods throughout the downtown core. We don't have time to get into the quantum electrochemistry.
Bottom line, exposure to this gas will render you comatose in seconds. It seems the gas is a
blend of two slowly reacting agents, giving us a brief window for action. Throw them in the ocean.
You'll have to grab each pod, haul it to the coastline and toss it into the ocean before
you lose consciousness. Move fast. Have to move and get that gas pod away from you. It could cause
you damage. Just throw it into the drinking supply of the whole city. Locate military gas pods,
safely dispose of military gas pods. Don't drink ocean water. Where do you think your water comes
from? Ding dong. Comes from the ocean. Comes from water in the earth. Well, I located the...
There's a big guy here. Wait. Punch. Did it work? We'll be right back. Right? Somebody do it.
Somebody do it. Somebody do it. Somebody do it. Somebody do it. Somebody do it. Somebody do it.
All right. I could use my fucking secret technique on this guy.
I missed. Turns out it's a whole lot harder to get this. Punch the missile. I didn't get
jibated. I need to do a running uppercut on this guy. You bet. Here I'm gonna do the xxxxxx punch
combo. Hulk is a demon. Uh, no. I mean, he's not biblical in any way. That doesn't make any sense
to me. Grab onto him. I tried that. Are you gonna... Seriously? Are you kidding me? Look, grab.
I can't grab him. I gotta say grab him. There's no... I can't grab him. There's no grab. I got a
better idea. Did it work? Turn. Turn. I can't even control him anymore. All right. I'm on a Disney
ride right now. Whoa. Look behind you. Take a picture. Take a picture. Oh my God. Look. He's
right there. Wow. Holy shit. That was crazy. Where do they get the technology to do this shit?
Look. Here he comes. Oh my God. Whoa. Mom. Mom. Here he comes. Mom. Keep grabbing my fucking arm.
Hard. Ow. Mom. Let go of my fucking arm. I'm sorry, sweetie. Mom. Jesus. I probably marks here
now. I have a sunburn there too. Look. Here come the missiles. Oh, what the fuck. Don't worry.
They were not... What? Why did I come back? Why did I come back? Wait. Police. I need your help.
You want to go toe to toe? You can do that. You tried to grab me, didn't you? Whoopsie.
Got it. Finish him with an elbow drop. No. Why would I need to finish him with an elbow drop?
Finish him with a slash. Fuck. I shouldn't have done that that loud. Listen to my voice. Listen
to this. I have this in my air pocket in my... Right now, there's an air pocket in my throat.
God, I lost it. Did I lose it? Yeah. Fuck. You know when you're eating and your voice...
The food gets stuck in a really weird place where your vocal cords are and you end up with this
crazy voice that can never be replicated? I love when that happens and I try to keep it as long as
I can. I try to make phone calls when that happens to me. Calling people that I know. Like,
here it is. Here it is. Okay. Okay. Calm down. And I'll call like fucking friends and family
members and be like, hey, we're not just checking in. That's me imitating it, but it sounds insane
when you actually do it. People are like, ermy? Like, yeah. Fucking weirdo. You're a weirdo.
Oh, we got another big guy. Can I handle it? He can't even fucking drive. The psycho helicopters
are here. The camera can't even keep up with me because of the helicopters. What? Come here,
I'm grabbing it. I'm so happy I have that move now. That move is so good. 8 out of 0.9 out of 10
Xbox magazine. No, I would say this is probably a 2,000 for 8 out of 10. I mean, this is pretty good.
I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. Is there another one? Oh, it's this guy.
The missiles... I shit don't even work in this scenario. I'd rather just go up and punch him.
This shit ain't even reliable. What? Go the X, X, X, X, X combo. Yeah, it's an X, X,
pause. X, X, X, X, X, right. X, X, X, pause. X, X, X, X, X, X, X, X, X, X, X, X, X, X, pause.
You have to stand still for too long. It's not reliable. Get that fucking help, Q.
I'll be going the wrong way. I don't have time to walk around. Give me the help. I want
steel fists. Thank you. No. Okay, pick that up. Throw gas into the ocean. Oh, this is
the gas pod. Throw the gas pod by using Y and then rotating L counterclockwise. What?
No, I just, I thought you throw it in the ocean. You don't throw it into the ocean.
Got it, right? All right, next one. I'm coming. Action. Go, go, go, go, go, go. Go, go, go, go, go.
Action. Go, go, go, go, go. Wait, point. I got to get some of these. 10,000 smash points.
Bowl the burger. Bowl the burger. Bowl the burger. Bowl the burger. Bowl the burger. Bowl the burger.
Denny's. Fuck. You said the word Denny's. No, I want it. Shit. I wanted Denny's. I can't,
though. I can't get that. I'm going to bowl the burger. Just hold on. I need a good opportunity.
Imagine coming into the stream right now. Like, what were you thinking?
What's this cheeseburger? What the heck? Hulk with a cheeseburger?
This has got to be a mod. Stop, stop, stop. Come on. Come on. Let me, let me have this one.
You guys, all of you right now, you better do it. The one person that comes in here that we're just
going to, they're going to think it's like really funny. We're going to, they're going to really
think that's what we think. This is funny. Everyone has to be like burger XD, like laughing burger,
like what the fuck? Eat it. Yum. Like stuff like that. Like, oh, he looks hungry. Be as
horny as possible. Okay. Ready? And action. What? You wait for me. I've got a burger. Hey,
what, what do you want some? What do you want some? You can't have any. It's my burger. Only mine.
Man, I thought, I thought I was hungry. What the heck? What the heck is going on here?
Everyone's a piece of my burger. All right. I'll share it with you. Oh, whoops. Yum. Yum. Yum.
It's just so yummy. All right. Watch this. Hey, who ordered it? But this is funnier. This is
funnier. Oh, I'm using my burger head as a battering ram. Oh, watch out. It's me. Hope
burger head delivering up fresh beef. Okay. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop it. I demand
stop. Oh shit. I'm in trouble. It was horrible. That's enough. I just said it was enough.
Okay. So how many people came and left? What do you think? More than five. I would say probably
three. Hey, fucking relax. Oh my God. These helicopters are unbelievable. I think, you know
what? I think the worst part about that one was, was the like, I'm eating it like yum, yum, yum,
yum thing. I think that might have been the worst part. I, that, that's where I would have left.
Right. Where is it? I know it's here. How are you still even flying around like that? You have no
health. You're exploding. That was just showing off for the camera. Okay. Oh, I want the helicopter
that's flying. Where's the helicopter? You've got to be fucking kidding me. You guys didn't think
this was the finale of the 4th of July. Really? Okay. So what, how would you keep telling me that
of what I said yesterday was not accurate? I'd love to hear about your thesis on that.
Why can I not punch the missiles back? I gotta, I gotta get out of this. I'm just gonna grab the
thing and run. Like why even fight these things? It's just like not even, not even possible.
Not even possible. This game's impossible. Wait, did I not even? Come on. No fucking way.
What are you talking about?
I was right. I don't even need to do the stupid big long-winded animation. Just throw it in.
I don't have to do this long-winded Mario thing. Just, just throw it in. Yeah, make sure we get
her. Do a hammer throw. No, I don't have to do that. Let's jump, uh, king spot right here.
Good. All right. Wait, how is he following me this well? Like how is it possible you follow
me that directly? He's 10 times bigger than me. More than that. Like he's probably 25 times larger
than I am. Let's just skate. All right, I forgot this is the missile game right here. Make funny
burger joke. We already did it. Didn't you laugh at it? We were here when we all laughed at it.
It was very, very, very funny. So throw it into the ocean so I can just turn around and just drop
it in. Holds up burger. I mean, it holds up burger. Wait, is that you're doing the holds up like
spork thing? Did I make it? Yeah, yeah, yeah. Into the ocean. Got it. I win. Mission complete.
Okay, I did it. So now good. New Blonsky files. Well, I win. No, I do. All right. Next story,
a bird in the hand. Do I have 93,000? No, I didn't want that. Um, exactly what I wanted.
Okay, can I get a reset here? Can I get a reset of the map? Let's go back to the church where
it's safe. $50 came in from Goiki. Thank you Goiki for the $5,000. Sorry, I was doing a little bit
yelling there. $5,000 bits from Goiki. $50. They say everyone tweet hashtag burger. Get it trending.
I think it already is. I'm pretty sure all popular food items always have like
10 to 20,000 tweets a minute. It's not going to take very much. I'm just gonna buy moves.
But thanks for the $50, Goiki. Thanks for the ridiculous amount of bits. Appreciate it. A ton
of fucking money. And thanks for your hashtag burger. All right, 93,000. Air critical. How do
I not have? Don't I already have it? Super air dash. Yes. Really important. Hitchhike. Finally,
I can grab onto those guys. Critical mass, sir. Okay. What about health? Shield grind kick.
Wait, is it a kick flip? Definitely get the kick flip. Missile catch. Catch incoming missiles and
hurl them back. Couldn't buy that one fast enough. I want a burger now. Okay, go get one.
Well, no. Well, you can't. No, you can't. Make one. We need to get a handle on these new powers.
Just get one. I know. I just said that. I know. Well, I mean, if you could get it from a stop
watching. Why did you? Why? I didn't say that. Yeah. Why would you say that? Still get some.
Some drive ups here still are available. Takeout is available, right?
All right, let's do this. All right. Grab and then throw it back. Well, that was off the screen.
I couldn't see it. Uncle burger at home. Yeah, you can do that. To be in Ross's shoes. The
military's insurance bill is going to skyrocket. Wait, you just throw it back.
You're not supposed to do it like that, but okay. You catch it and then you hold B.
I just whipped it back. All right, let's go. Well, I can only grab one at a time,
so it doesn't really matter. Ash is much better though.
Hulk is a stoner. You know, I was thinking about saying the oh, I hold the missile and it's like a
big joint, right? I was thinking about it, but that figured it was that was going to put a lot
of minus twos in the chat. But somebody you said it so you can take the blame on that one.
No funny weed. I didn't say it. I told you I didn't say it. Holy shit. That's really far.
That's is there a level three on this too? I hope so. I smoked a bong today. Well,
I would really highly recommend not like breaking down glass and smoking.
I hope that's not what you mean. You know, I'm so hungry. I need a big burger. I'm so
hungry. Cut his mic. No, keep it on.
Wait for the cop. Wait, wait till the copter lands and then grab fuel rod.
Stop doing the burger. Funny thing. We did that already. You're scaring away new viewers.
47 seconds. Reap what you sow. Yeah, and I guess I did. I reaped what I sowed.
I pulled the plant up. We've cultivated it and it's gone now. I planted those seeds
and then the harvest came and we harvested that joke and now it's done.
I'm not even fucking there. It doesn't count. You can't just smoke the jokes without sharing, bro.
We gotta just bunny hop. Let's waste the time. Just do this. Only this.
Okay. That was, I made up so much more time there. All right. I made it. Helicopter coming in.
Punch helicopter. Good. Hey, destroy helicopter. He's going fast. What the fuck? I don't understand.
What is a jet flying around the building? What in the name of God? How did it even get over there?
Come here. Come over here. He's too fast. Think fast. All right. Now, thanks for giving me any
time at all that you can figure out what the hell is happening. Just beat these guys up. You know
what I mean? Just beat them up. I don't have a time limit. This guy's going to follow me the fuck
around for that. I don't think. No, don't do an elbow. I can't. I have to. All right. Now do it.
This is like fighting with like, this is fighting with hulk hands with like your little brother.
You know what I mean? Watch out. Oh, I'm going to get you. This is how you jump. I'm coming like
off the sofa. I'm so bad. I'm not. He's just so good. Thank you. Thanks. I humiliate him.
10,000 smash points. Okay. Now I'm ready. Wait inside the building. Oh, I got another 10,000
smash points. I meant to do that. Oh shit. I didn't get it. No, I don't get it. I have to.
Oh, you think so? You think you're in control? This fuel cell. Oh,
he called in. Oh, speaking of. Oh, wait. No, don't. Oh my God. I'm going to break this.
I don't want to break it. Okay. Give me this. Just pick it up. Get it. Oh my God. This fucking
just nestled everywhere. Where's that jump pad? Am I? Where am I? This thing's, this thing's gonna
crack. Pick up the hamburger. I'm not going to pick up the fucking hamburger.
Just missed me motherfucker. Added 15,000 smasher points. Be patient. Closer than we've ever been.
To break any moment. He can't keep the beast inside him.
Once we capture him, I'll transformation. I'm beginning to understand the appeal.
What was that noise by the way? Wrong with this guy. Yep. People say that every day.
Okay. Doesn't mean it's true. I have to get across the city, Bruce now, but we're under lockdown.
My division informant has a new decrypt code. I need that info. And he's not
by the roadblocks. I don't like it. Something's wrong here. Just worry about keeping me safe.
Keep Doc Sampson alive. What is he going to be walking around with like a briefcase?
Heck Sampson. He's going to be in a car. I feel like he's going to be in a limo.
Right. Don't you see that? I foresee this guy in a limousine. Nope. He's in an SUV. Okay.
Am I in that car? I just ran somebody over.
Oh, he's driving. How is this driving? Protect Sampson's car. From what exactly?
We couldn't have got a better car than this. Can't we get like an armored car? Why don't we get
like a Subaru Outback? You think we would get a fucking armored car with like bulletproof glass
and oh, the roadblock. All right. Go on. You go. Go. Full speed ahead. Oh, there's tanks here.
Nevermind. Stay there. I can't pick up the debris. Try this again.
Here comes a meltdown mission. No, not yet. You get the tank grab upgrade. I should get all upgrades
guys. So they're looking for suspicious activity. So instead of just driving normally, you decide
to run the guy over. Why didn't you just like just lie to these people? Excuse me, sir. I'm with
Uber Eats. Oh, okay. All right. Right. Good. I'm delivering a package. I'm working for the post
office. Oh, okay. All right. See you later. Package from Uber Eats. No, I'm just saying like
people that deliver stuff. Oh, that would have been so bad. I just dropped a fridge on him.
All right. Catch him. There's a psycho chopper. Hold on. Let me take care of this. No, pick it up.
Give me the help. Help. Oh, he's still alive. This motherfucker's almost dead. Where's this
other person? Oh my god. Burger. Let me have that one. Please let me have that one. Please.
I know you guys are thinking the same thing. I know you are. Okay. Let's block him.
I'll get in my car. We can drive around together. Wait, where's it? I get it. Fade away. I love
doing the fade away. It's the best. It's the most fun. Banner. Banner. Surrender banner. Don't go
right next to the tank, you idiot. Oh, he's left. He left. He left. He left. He's fine.
This is a pretty strong car in front of us. God damn it. Hit it. Hit him. Oh, this is bad.
Holy shit. I'm dead. Oh, this one's going to suck. I need the tank upgrades. Yeah. All right.
I'll give it one more go and then I'm going to get the tank upgrade.
The throw tank. Watch that same guy get hit. All right. We got to make this quick. He already
left. All right. Stay with him the whole time. I got to make it quick. Get the fists. Stay with
him. Keep it around at least 80% health if I can. I'll try. Where are we at? Right here. First block.
Am I getting ahead of him? I'm just going to get ahead of him. What am I even supposed to do?
I'm not getting hit by a thousand missiles. Okay. Well, when they fire 10 million rounds at you,
I'm getting a tank upgrade. We tried catching missiles. Well, the interesting thing about the
catching missile upgrade is you catch one while 60 hits you in the back. It's interesting how
that works. No, don't start that one. All right. I need, I want like 70,000 points.
Let's do a mission. Are you guys still on board, girl? Get the soldier into the air as many times
as possible without letting him touch the ground. All right. Let's give it a try. Can I use grabs?
Can I just throw him up and catch him and throw him up and catch him and throw him up and catch
him? Hey, juggle the soldier. Did I fail? I got one. Wait a minute. Is it X and like up or X and
do it away from him or something? Right. Okay. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Okay. I get it. So
go like this. Oh, you got to hit back and X at the same time. Give me a bit of camera angle.
This camera is terrible. Maybe don't even lock on. Should I not lock? No, you have to lock on.
Ah, shit. Lock on changed. Give me a 10. 10. No. Well, got it. Silver medal. I don't care.
That's fine. 4,000 points. Cool. This guy's a silver streamer. I'd rather have the silver
medal. Then haven't we talked about this? How second place is better than first place?
Because I was very, very good, but I don't have to, I don't have to be the best because then I have
a ton of expectations. You get in first place, then all of a sudden you're the expectation now.
I don't want first place. I want second place. In fact, I want like fourth place because you did
really good. You didn't like place, but holy shit, like how many people were doing that?
Well, there was like 40 people doing that. Got to like eighth place. That's fucking kind of high.
That's pretty good. Okay. Use your club to hit the soldier as far as possible. Charge the attack
to increase the distance. See how far you can hit the soldier. Now, by the way, fourth place is
placing if you go by Super Nintendo Mario Kart standards. And that's the standards that I go by.
All right. I can get, I can do like 500 yards. All right. No, no, no, no, no. Okay. All right.
This is fun. You got to get a full charge. Oh, I got it. I could have done it a little earlier.
279. Oh, you got to get under it. That was all right. That was pretty good.
300. 300. I got under it. 384. Come on. 295. 300. Get it. Jump and do it.
I threw it. That's me. That guy just died for no reason. It doesn't work like that.
No, I'm hitting them. Oh, my chest.
For no reason. I know. I know. I know. But wait, let me try Y. That's definitely over 300 yards.
Holy shit. That's like 400. It's Y, not X. Get one more. I'm going to do this one again. I can
give, I definitely can do it. They all are dying for no reason. I know. And let's go like this.
It's a lot longer. Come on. 400. Oh, I got him right in the toe. I got way underneath him. That's
probably going to be pretty good. Come on. That was perfect. Oh, right. X and Y.
That didn't work. I'm just making him fall faster. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Try to do it.
I'm trying. I'll get it. I'll get it. Hold on. Got it. That was horrible. It was fucking terrible.
I'll get it right here. I'll get it right here. I'll get it right here. One more after this. I got
to get to 400. That would have been it. No, it wouldn't have. Knock them in the air, then do it.
Wait. Hold on. Hold on a second. You're telling me hit them and then throw it at them. Not a bad
idea. You'd be bad at baseball. Only baseballs don't come from the sky. They come forward.
Let's try this. Let's try this. It might work. Hold on. Oh, I think somebody called the police.
You're a little late. I'll be honest. I've been doing this for like two hours. Wait, what?
Let me use something else. Oh, no. Fuck. I tried running. I have to get gold on this.
Holy shit. He just said look out on his radio. Fuck. God. Stop jumping. I have to. I have to.
I have to. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. I'm going to get like extra,
like if you jump and punch, like you know what I mean? No, it's the same. Holy shit. Hold on.
No, I didn't want to throw it behind me. Stop giving this to me.
I can do it. I'm going to want to do it with the pole. It's going to be 5,000 yards.
Can I just die? Retry. Restart. Here we go. I'm going to get the pole and I'm going to hit him
into the fucking stratosphere. Don't do it immediately. Just wait. Okay. Ready?
So like knock this down. I exploded. Oh, you motherfucker. That's going to be pretty good.
366. Fully charged hit won't go to 400. Why not? Throw it after hitting him. I'm trying that every
time. It's not going to make it. That was pretty far. 350, 360, 424. I got it. That's gold medal.
I just got it. All right. I can do better than that. It's right before you do the full charge.
That's going to be at least 400. Come on. One more shot. That's pretty good. That's going to be a
good one. And too bad it was the last one I just did. Oh, now that one's terrible. All right. I got
it. Gold medal. Now do a little dance. Yeah. All right. Jump to the church to acquire mission.
All right. So I want to do, I got $67. I want to do more. I like these little mini games. They're
fun. I'm going to do more of these. I'm going to do more of these. These are fun. Do a dance. I just
did because you don't see it. I'll do this last one. Then we'll do the story. I'm going to get
the tank upgrade. The one that makes it so I can kill tanks really easily. Oh no. I already did
that one. This one. Soldier seeker. Defeat as many enemies as possible before the time runs out.
Play the automaton. The automaton has a name. Kill everything. Get the guy up here first.
Where's the next one? On the building. Oh, that was not good.
Where is he? They're on the roofs. Where is he? Up top. It's both the helicopters. Oh my God.
Just forget to kill the guys on the ground first. You're going to fall off, aren't I?
I did let go. I didn't want to let go. Come here. How many yards? Okay. All right. All right.
Where's the last dude up there? That guy's fucking dead. One, two, three. All right. What's left?
He's alive. He's alive. He's alive. Oh, he's not. Oh, there's a guy right there. Oh, I got it.
Whatever. Bronze. Who cares? Winks are crashing. Sell. You can't even sell them. They don't exist
anymore. They've been delisted from the marketplace. You can't sell something that's
not even available to sell. All right. Let's go back to the church. We have 70,000 points.
We need to jump. All right. Here we go. What's the move called? The one that you're talking about?
Good one. It's called a wink. That'd be funny if it was. Okay. Sonic clap. Air enemy grapple. Yeah.
Got these. Elbow drop. Super air strike. No, no, no. Shockwave smash repeater. That's cool,
but I don't want it. Air critical thunderclap. Hammer toss. Grab and spin any tanks. There it is.
Okay. Grab a tank and then spin. Dirty ball and chain. Utilize a wrecking ball for wide
sweeping attacks. Air spike. From an air combo, slam Hulk's foes to the ground.
That's cool, but hold on. Target kick. Hulk can ride an aircraft and kick it toward the
target of your choice. I want that. I can throw one helicopter into the other helicopter.
Critical pain. Power surge level two. Oh, this is health. Running club ram.
Yeah, it gives me. All right. I'm going to save up now. Toontown. Isn't there, there's a,
I can't you play Toontown? Should I play Toontown? Isn't it like, isn't it like Toontown
reloaded or something or remastered? Sir Canine just gave $50. Thank you for the huge bit drop.
Thanks for the 5,000 bits. That's a lot of fucking money. 5,000 of them. And they say,
Germa, I've redeemed my Germa wank earlier for 10 million channel points and didn't even get one.
Can I get a Wink as a re recomp, recomp, recompensation? Why did you read that? Because
somebody gave me $50. That was a $50 donation. That was Sir Canine. No, you, there was never
any agreement for anything you're saying. Winks are delisted. They don't exist. Sorry. This is
the way it is. Where's this mission? Where's the mission? Isn't there a story mission here?
Scam. Oh, yeah. If you're looking for Winks, you scammed yourself because they're gone.
Very addicted to them. All right. Where's the story? Is this the wrong area or something? What's
going on? No burgers. Naked streamers scams viewers. I mean, another $50 from Sir Canine.
That's $100 in bits so far. That's 10,000 bits from Sir Canine. And they say that's a lot. Canine,
thanks for the hundred fucking dollars. That's insane. That's crazy. They say, does that mean
I can get a Germa wank because those aren't delisted? Also play Toontown. They were never
listed in the first place. Winks have been delisted. Wanks were never listed. So I'm sorry.
There is this. It was never listed in the first place.
How come this mission is not showing up? Soft low mega low. Oh, is the raw. Okay.
I have to get across this. Annoyings. Now, but we're. Thanks for the hundred bucks.
But I'm not. No, I'm not going to. No, I'm not going to do that thing. I'm not going to do that
on stream. I'm not going to do that. No, I'm not. All right. I'm done. We're done.
So here we go. Now I got the tank grabber move and I get a couple of hog champs for the tank
grabber move. Don't give in. There's no giving in. Are you talking? What are you talking about?
Don't give in. Protect whatever. I got the line wrong. Improvisation. Look it up. Captain do
anything. I knew you were sneaking up on me. You and your friend and I didn't even do the move.
Taking them into the ocean with me. I got them both. But that's a good start. Let me get. So
let me get this straight. We are doing. I'm getting the silent treatment right now because
you guys want me to let me get this right here. Let me make sure this is very clear.
You've given me the silent treatment because you are expecting me to masturbate on stream.
I just want to make sure I'm very clear about this. Is that really what we're doing?
How far have you fallen? Swing it. Swing it quick. Holy shit it works. Oh that's very easy now.
Did a boss that four days ago. Wait. Psycho coppers. Coppers. You know whatever. Got it.
Okay good. No I'm not going to give in. I'm not giving in. Why would I give in?
Why would I give in? This is not hog of you. Just standing next to the car. Just fucking run
them over man. I'm a not hog of you. No that's not going to happen. This hurricane I'm giving
another $50. Another 5,000 bits. $150 worth of bits have come in to try to get me to wink.
Not going to happen. Not going to happen. I'm sorry. It's not going to happen. They say a wink
would work. Not going to happen. I'm going to have to be honest with you. It's not happening.
I'm just going to crush them. Thanks for the insane amount of money. But I can't.
I can't. You can't relist something. Okay I'm doing this on my own. I want to do this because
I feel like doing it. Zit shut up. Shut up. How dare you say that to me right now.
Immediate. Immediate. Immediate. Zit. Immediate call out. The camera was on for a tenth of a second.
Zit. Oh yeah okay thank you. Nice room. Thanks. I think so too. I'm not. All right.
He's so far ahead of me. Oh shit. Is he all right? Okay. Why are you stopping here?
Why is he stopping? Oh my god the tanks. This wouldn't happen if you played Pathologic 2.
What the fuck are you talking about? Hurry dude. The uber food is getting cold.
Oh shit we're going to hit that guaranteed 25 minute delivery. Okay. Oh kick us up. Stop
driving. He's driving on the sidewalk. You're doing damage to yourself. Come on. We got tanks.
Watch this shit. Watch this shit. Somebody over here. Tank. Tank. Tank. God damn it. Watch your
fire. I gotta ball this. Into the tank. Ball it into the tank. Ball it into the tank.
Okay. Don't care anymore. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Done. Done. Another task.
Done. You can go now. Wait for me to get out of the way first. Fucking idiot. He is an idiot.
All right. He's an idiot. What do you want me to say? He's not an idiot.
And what he was doing right there was smart. You want me to not call the guy driving on the
sidewalk an idiot. Okay. Look at this. This guy's being controlled remotely by a shitty wi-fi signal.
Nobody even in that fucking car. Holy shit. What? Why am I taking damage? Oh. Whoa. Wow.
Wow. Wow. Wow. Wow. Unbelievable. Oh, there's a checkpoint. Oh. Okay. Here they come.
Come on. Drop. The Yeti's coming out. Fire is releasing.
How? All right. Throw it at somebody else. Thank God it works. I'm seeing F.
All right. F. I got zero drop frames. Why? Why are you guys doing this to me?
Don't tell them. Because you threw a tank at somebody. Oh. Why is it that I automatically
just assume that F means your internet's not working and your stream is dead? I think I'm
just so fucked up from having so many internet problems that I see FFF and I'm like, oh shit,
it's over. Internet says the stream's turned off. Stream's off. I'm so traumatized. All right. Let's
go. Pick him up and flick him. Ah, there it is. See you later. Not over. Wait. Oh. When are we
going to reach our destination? Can we get there? This guy's taking the shittiest route possible.
Watch this. Got a bolt. Why is he driving around like this? Come here. One of you. I'm catching this.
He got one off at the end. No, he did not. Give me your mic. Give me your mic. Give me your mic.
Hey. Hey. Streamer. Hey. Check your audio settings. Something might be wrong with them.
There's something wrong with your audio settings. There's so many. There's too many. I have to start
throwing cars, man. There's too many. Oh, that's his car. Wait. All right. Give me the tank or
something. Go, go. Please don't get killed. It's the same shit that happened last time.
What? Ah, give me help. Please. Holy fuck. I did it. That was horrible. The Blonsky file.
Big zip, man. You've been stressed. No, no, not at all. Not at all. My dog was just
in the hospital last week. Had to move during a global pandemic. It hasn't been any stress in my
life. Play Cities Skylines. Cry. Hey. Hey. Hold on. Hey. Hey. That was like a radio kind of YouTuber
hey. My other voice. You're at the peak of your power. Well, not yet. Not yet. Why does he sound
like that? I don't want to do the BB unit thing, but I will because I like it. It's fun. I might
just do it. I'm thinking about it. All right. This is called my other voice. Everything's coming to
fruition. Now I need you to strike at their heart. The division has set up a front in the financial
district and they're spreading their poison in plain sight. We can't allow them a foothold there.
What about civilians? There are no civilians in that vicinity anymore. It's just you versus them.
All right. I'm going to
defeat division forces. Destroy the fuel depot. Destroy everything.
As everyone. Germa gave out a wild to seven out of 10.
It's unfortunately untrue. I don't know why it's unfortunately untrue, but it's not true.
I feel like I just opened up G mod bond just 10 of every enemy and just put them all hostile
versus each other. You know, when you do that shit, see what happens with the total fucking carnage.
Oh dude, I wonder what happens when seven guys in suits fight 20 helicopters. This would be
interesting. And you forget about the tank that you spawned. It's just kind of there. Oh yeah. I
did spawn a tank. Fuck. I'm going to have to do this again. It's not, that's it. That's a bad
variable. This is not a good indicator. I'm going to have to get after the tank is gone.
There's just too many of them. I just, I really did just give that guy a diamond cutter. That's
an RKO. Yeah. How many of you guys remember? I remember being on a trampoline and having
to deal with these little wrestle buddy things that they were like two feet tall and they were
stuffed animal kind of things. It was like, Oh, Ted DiBiase and the ultimate warrior.
And I used to just do wrestling moves to these guys. You're supposed to, that wasn't a commercial
and shit. I would do wrestling moves to them on the trampoline. We would go over to a friend's
house and like, Oh, let's do wrestling moves. We would do shit like that. We'd pick them up
and give them like stunners DDT fucking exploded. Hi, please. I need your help. I need his help.
Explode. I can get the fucking help. Shield, please. Oh my God. You're kidding me. Run. Did I get
them? Okay. Run. Relentless. Oh, I want a coin. Why is this guy lit up? Dead. Hey, you little
fuck. They never stop. It never stops. Should never stop. Fucking headache mission. This whole
game is a headache. Yeah, I agree. Am I going to regen yet? What the fuck? They're gonna die.
It's just never ending. Insta 50,000 mile per hour helicopters just grind into buildings and
into walls and shit. Hey, look at this. I don't know what I'm looking at. You kids beat this.
Yeah, on because they put it on easy and they probably know they didn't bullshit. They played
on easy the first three levels and moved on to something else because kids have the attention
spans of fucking squirrels. Okay, that's incorrect. You're about I beat this game when I was a kid.
No, you beat the first level on easy and then you forgot it existed and then your mother
brought it to like a donation box. That's probably what happened before you sold it.
You're like dad sold it and he forgot about it and then 30 years later you ask your mom. Hey,
Bob. What happened to that? Wasn't there a Hulk game that we had before? Oh, yeah. I have no idea
what happened to that. You stopped playing that after 10 minutes, honey. Oh, really? Because I
keep telling the streamer on Twitch that like I beat every game we ever played and I just want
to like make sure that I have save files still so I can like fucking stick screenshot of the save
file and I got to the end of the fucking game and I'm gonna have a screenshot that says 2004
uh 4 6 0 6 p.m and it's gonna be the final mission of save file. Yeah, we don't have that.
No, honey. We don't. I need help. This is what it feels like to just put like a paper bag on
your head and just run around your room into fucking walls. It's the same thing. You don't
know what's happening. It's just I'm on like a shitload of drugs running around with like a bag
on my head or something. I have like a blindfold on on a bunch of fucking crack
circling the same room and this is what's going on in my head. There's mutants and aliens everywhere.
Oh shit we're under attack. I did catch this banner. Fuck you. I did it. My god.
It's sort of elbow drop. That's not it. Destroy all hulkbusters and then stomp them.
Go juggle and then he explodes and then we get help. One um what's it what they call busters?
No, punk punk buster. No, it's a hunk buster. One hunk buster. The incredible hunk.
That's definitely the name of uh that's the title of the porn. It has to be. You know,
that has to be. This guy like just painted green.
He's definitely like painted green like with fucking like I don't know like party store makeup.
It's just like streaks all over him. They didn't give a fuck. They didn't even try.
Like a third of the guy's back ain't even green. The hulk Halloween costume. Yeah,
but the hulk mask on. Oh yeah we're talking about one of those plastic hulk masks. The ones that
just barely cover the front of your face and aren't sized properly so sometimes your face
might be a little too big and your real chin cheeks and forehead bleed out on the edges.
I think I caught one. Huge one. Of course there's a big ass hulk buster. No,
fright him. Punch him in the fucking head. I can't even see. I'm gonna run this way for a
minute. Oh my god, I literally can't even. No, I can't even start crying Jupiter.
Break this building. How am I supposed to destroy this? Okay, I thought my head just got fucking
splattered on the back of that. Did you see how fucked up that looked?
Gotta get the fuck out of here. Gotta get the fuck out of here. I gotta get the fuck out of here.
No, don't go back. No, they're still fucking up my ass. Yeah, they're right on my ass.
Yeah, it's still behind me. Go, go, go, go, go. Keep regetting. Give me that health.
Oh, where is he? Sir, can I have my save file? I beat this game when I was six. I need to take
one final damage the whole entire video. Okay. Oh, I'm not sure how you can do this. Something
must be wrong with your brain. Your brain is not correctly wired or something. I don't know.
We'll be back in an hour to see if you beat this mission. All right, give me something to throw.
There's no way. There's no way. You would die five times to that without even the amount of
running that I'm doing. This is not even the Incredible Hulk. It's so fucking funny.
So how do you want me to? All right. All you got. How do you want me to do this one?
What move do I need to get to throw these guys? What move do I need to get to throw these guys?
All right. Thankfully, we don't have to do that whole thing again. Oh, that's fucking funny.
This is very funny. Okay. Stop throwing. All right. I know you're fucking kidding,
but imagine thinking at the extreme, extreme. I was trying to keep myself alive. Imagine thinking
the guy is throwing, but I was, I was trying so hard to not take it. Did I get a hit?
Thank you. What would throwing look like? Oh, that's funny. No, they're talking about
stop throwing stuff. Oh, all right. Let's go, Tony. I disagree. Throwing is pretty good.
Stay in the realm of possibility of don't. I'm going to, I'm going to skate through this first
part. Here it is. Take this guy out first. Do not move until this guy is dead. Take out the little
guys first. Okay. Give me one of those. Yeah. All right. I'm going to ram them.
Fuck. Grab me. Oh no. Reinforcements came in. That's bad. That help. Give me it right there.
There's two. Fuck the other ones here. I want to explode. Get the fuck out of here. Good.
Another one dead. Good. Oh, I'm ready. Let's go skate. All right. There's another big one here.
He's not aggroing 20 enemies. Pog. I know. I know, but use the critical mass. Don't worry.
I'm saving it for right now. Critical mass on the building. Do it. Yeah. Yeah.
Is it magnificent? How has there been 4,922 viewers here for the last hour straight?
That seems strange. Oh, okay. Destroy the armory and destroy all
unclusters. You can't look away. It's like watching a disaster.
Magnificent. Nice uppercut. I'm sorry. Is somebody shooting me from over here? I couldn't tell.
Not a bad idea. Except you're dead. Magnificent. And butt. And butt. And butt.
Uh, Mick Muscles. Thanks for the 10 community subs, Mick Muscles. That's a 10 drop. 10
community subs. Thanks a lot. Congratulations to those who got those fucking community subs.
Hulk in the chat. Critical mass. All right. Now we take on the big guys. Hulk actually in chat.
Maybe. Don't. Don't call him out. Let him just watch. Here, watch this one. We'll do a
simple little technique here it's called. Get grabbed and get thrown. I'll give you a fucking
technique. What's that? Okay, that's a street light. I thought it was like a jet. Good. All right,
they're both dead, right? Yep. All right, keep going. I want more, uh, I want my shield back.
Let's go. Here we go. Ah. Fun move to do. Give me those fists. Where the fuck are the jukes?
Where are the jukes? They're all, they're everywhere, man. Nope. Don't think so. Right
into my hands. Right into my hands. Right into my hands. Right into my hands. Throw them in the
fucking ocean. Oh, you have another DDT. Or a bulldog. You find yourself unable to cast sus.
The screen is live. Yes, it is. Apparently it is. Yeah, it is. I love doing the fadeaway.
You know, when I used to play basketball games, if I played an NBA game, I would, it didn't matter
if the shot was very easy. I would always jump backwards and fade away and shoot every single
time. It just was so satisfying. Everything about it. All right, here we go. Here's the building.
Holy shit. I thought the objects in the mirror are way huger than they appear in front of you.
What? I thought these are small. I thought they were the little ones. It's two huge ones.
Get it. I got it. Shit. You got a fire. That's just annoying. Wouldn't that be hurting me?
Wait, wait, wait. Frank, stop. Frank, stop attacking. He's hitting his fucking head into the metal
over and over again. He's just gonna die. Let him do it. All right, this is bad. I gotta run.
Yeah, I should have ran. I'm regenerating. That's a good thing because I can get help from you.
All right, here we go. Fight. I need that. I need that. I need that. I need that.
I can't go back there. What's even happening? I have no idea. It's almost impossible to tell.
It's 75% of the fights in this game. What is even happening on the screen?
I'm there with you. I have no idea. Where the fuck am I? It's because I have to keep running away
and I keep grabbing more of these fucking guys. Now it's like I can't beat it now.
There's like 30 people following me. I need to regenerate health. Kill one of these guys.
I can't even grab anything because they keep blowing it up before I can get it.
Go for the objective. They'll never stop fucking following me. He's gonna drop health.
Guys, I have to destroy the building and there's 10 people following me.
Running away makes you run into more guys. Yeah, so the two huge guys that were attacking me that
I couldn't kill. Just let them kill me on the bridge or try to fight for my goddamn life.
Should I just let them kill me on the bridge?
Can I buy something new? Yeah, I definitely can buy. I'm gonna get the health upgrade.
And also, it's kind of hard to tell what direction I'm even facing.
It's like, dude, why are you running away? I'm not even trying to. It's just
the game is flashing my life before my eyes. It's like if in Overwatch everybody's four moves
they had were all ultimates. Oh, itchy eye. Where's my tracer? Wait, did they make a tracer pop?
They did. But why don't I have one? Don't aggro anybody. All right, what's the... Oh my god.
I need to get like those dumb checkpoints too. I'm just gonna fly above the city.
I'm not gonna aggro anybody. I'm just gonna fly above. I'm gonna hide.
I'm gonna do sneaking from the top. So just sneak. Nobody will see me. See? No one's even
spawning. I'm breaking the game's spawn rate. Nothing can spawn up here because the game
prioritizes frame rate, right? So if it spawned a shitload of things right now, the game would break.
See? I land for a second and there's a guy right there. I don't know. Dead and dead. Okay, here we go.
And I just beat the shit out of these two guys. Should I race to the objective? Should I try to
spy cap this? All right, I'm gonna try. I'm gonna spy cap this mission. I land. Let's do it twice.
Do it again. It just fucking happened. Third one too. All right, let's help right there.
I might even have water in the game. God damn it. Don't aggro the other guy. I'm trying not to.
Are they smart enough? I'm gonna get the fuck... I'm gonna aggro the other guy, aren't I?
Do a move. Okay, stay back here. Just, I gotta be careful. Don't go the other way. Go the other way.
Watch this. Don't aggro anybody. Check this out. Oh, you fucking piece of shit. Give me a break.
It's gonna work. I got another guy here too. What the fuck? Does this guy even come from there?
What the fuck? There's no like, there's no strategy here. There's no fucking strategy.
It's just, it's just a mess. I have to buy the health upgrade. This is no way.
Unfortunately, we have to do that whole stupid goddamn mission again. But we'll have more health
when we do it. Well, I can assure you. Where is it? Okay. Thank you. Thanks for the health.
Double air dash. This is very fucking important too. Got that one. Okay, let's go. Just ignore
the bridge. Yeah, but I have to kill all the hulk busters. I have to kill the hulk. That's part of
the mission. Part of the mission is destroy all hulk busters. Dashing twice will probably help
a lot. The second one doesn't feel as powerful. Do I like this game? Yeah, I do. It's Caffa Faces.
No, I do. I do like this game. I do. Otherwise, I wouldn't be playing it two days in a row.
You're doing well, Bruce. Okay, let's try this again. More health. Get the jump checkpoint.
Oh, fuck. It's okay. Seven out of ten. Where's the jump point? Somebody spread it. All right.
Let's try this. I'm going for it. I'm going to try as hard as I can. All right. Quiet time.
Trying to be quiet. It's time to not talk about how much I hate this game. Okay. How the fuck are
these missing? Be aggressive. That's all you can do. I'm just spamming. I'm not like you. Well,
let me tactically think about this. I'm the Incredible Hulk. Let me play my chess. I'm
supposed to be quiet. I'm supposed to be quiet. I'm supposed to be quiet. I'm supposed to be
very quiet. Yeah, you walked right into it. Stupid. Here we go. Go. More aggressive. More
aggressive. Be more aggressive. I think the GameCube version had better frame rate.
It is? I have a feeling every game, every one of these had probably bad frame rate.
It's kind of hard to have a good frame rate when there's all this shit going on.
Where is he? Where is he? Where is he? Fuck out of here. Let's go. It's because you're on 723.
Turn it down to 480i. I don't think I can handle that. I don't think I really could do that.
Pretend you're fighting Chad. Okay. Fuck you. Ow. Hey. Ouch. You're hurting me. Ouch. You're
hurting me. Ow. Ow. Stop. That hurt? Bits. Come on, Chad. Kick his ass. Come on. Let's go.
Get off me. Why do they keep spawning? Aggravating. Here we go. It's the first
hunk buster. Get down here. Ask and you shall receive, Jeremy. These guys are so hard to deal
with. Especially when there's all these other little shits just fucking spamming around you
in circles. Throw shit at them? Oh, I would love to. If it wasn't this shit just spamming
in every direction. You're fighting a raid boss. But I am a raid boss too. I can't use that.
They really liked the missiles. When they were making this game, they were like, you know what?
The missiles are the best part of the whole game. Just do more of those. More of those.
Excuse me, guys. I'm not seeing at least 50 missiles every one minute on screen.
What do you think this is? How are we supposed to determine if Hulk is powerful if he doesn't
get hit with fucking 100 long range missiles every second? People won't even know he's powerful.
They won't even know he's strong. He's mad. Here comes another one. Let's go. Hulk is stupid,
but he's strong. That's all right. He adds a lot to the Avengers. He added a shitload to
the Avengers. He was like, he was not even the strongest Avenger, but all right.
Not the smartest Avenger, but okay. Not the coolest powers of all the Avengers. Oh, all right.
It's green. All right. I'm ready for it. Let's go. Angry, angry, angry.
Go get me down. Did you grab me after the buzzer? That's a bunch of penalties. That's fine. Do it.
When the match is over, I will win because you're going to get a shitload of penalties.
You're going to get disqualified. Ref, I'm not doing anything. Ref, I'm not doing
shit. Thank you. All right. This is where I got left off before. This is important. This is the
one. This is the important mission. Just flatten me. These guys are really susceptible to the
fucking flattening. They really are. Just get a shield and then just hit Y and flatten. Over
and over again. Just got me. Yeah, but that just got me. How did you write that? If you write that,
that means I have to say it. What did you say that for? Did you take it out of my hands? What
has happened to that thing? Oh, shit. Oh, but that just got me. Folks, right now.
No, why are you doing this? We may need to do emergency surgery in the studio.
I don't want to do these things. Let me grab me. Thanks. All right. We're almost there. So the
strategy is to go across the water. No, there is no go across the water. There's no go across
guys. Look, destroy all Hulk busters. They have to die. They have to die.
I'm giving up free trailers. I just put that on my expenses and put that on my expenses.
I'll put that on my expenses. I'll put that on my expenses. I'll put that on my expenses.
All right. I can fucking take them to the ground. That went much cleaner. Here we go. Let's try this
tactic. No, wait, don't worry. This is an invisible wall. Staff are asking for a raise.
It's an invisible wall. Why wouldn't there be an invisible wall? Hi. Flat. Flat. Now we just have
to kill two huge guys at the same time. One of your staff just died. Guy just got destroyed. Good.
Okay. Here we go. I have to win. I've got to win. I've got to kill both these guys at the same time.
I've got two stomps. Don't waste critical mass. How should I be using it? Critical atomic slam.
Dan, do I have any other moves I can use it? That's the only move I can do with critical mass,
right? Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Fuck. I'm trying to grab.
Grab one at least. Grab one at least. Get him. It actually kind of is. How the fuck do you fight
these two guys at the same fucking time? Flat. That's not working. Flat don't work. Where the
fuck did you come from? Actually, I need you. Come here. I need his help. I need your help.
They flattened you. Yes, they do. I almost got one. One's almost done. One's dead. One's dead. I got
one. Why are you not dead? Don't jump. Xbox turn off. What are you trying to get? That's not going
to work. Xbox turn off. Xbox go to sleep. That was stupid. Elbow drops to the fucking wind. There
it is. All right. Dead. Finally. Oh my God. I'm just getting so mad. I'm just getting so angry.
I'm just so pissed off. Destroy the armory. All right. It's time for a critical mass. Wait,
let me do the punch, punch, punch, punch, punch, punch, punch, punch, punch, punch, punch, punch,
punch, punch, punch, punch. Is there any more to do? That was a long, horrible mission. I don't want
to do that one again. How can I say that again? Out of this video. Ultimate destruction. I don't
want to do that one again. I'm a freak show. Sometimes you got to do what's necessary.
Mutation doesn't have to be a curse. Yes. Yes. It can be a blessing if I choose it to be.
You're addicted to the power. You're becoming an abomination. What did you say? It's not like
that. I promise. Now I'm going to use that name. I'm not afraid of the mutation anymore.
This kind of power. Turned on his voice changer. He's streaming right now and people think it's
funny when he does the bugleberry. Is there a jump pod over here somewhere? There probably is.
Oh, we all know. We all know you can do very good. I need to probably jump here.
The next mission is the final mission. What is it actually? No, it's not.
We haven't even fought abomination. Where's a jump pod? I'm so sick of you fucking guys.
Follow me the fuck around everywhere I go.
Do you just leave me the fuck alone ever? Or do I have to constantly fucking constantly just be
running the fuck away from you? Just leave me alone. Why is the aggra range infinite on these
guys? It shouldn't be like that. Shouldn't be like that. Yeah. F, F, F, F. That was a real F.
Oh, that was a real one. Oh, it was a real one. Oh, oh. Oh, oh. No, don't worry. It's perfectly
normal. Perfectly normal. That's perfectly fine. That's completely normal. I'll tell you what.
That might be freaking out about 300. As you know, on a typical stream,
uh, a typical stream that's between four to seven, like five to six hours long,
drops about a thousand frames, maybe like 600 to a thousand. That's pretty typical.
But also keep this in mind as well. I'm also streaming through a VPN,
so I'm not getting the full power of the fiber because I'm going through a VPN.
Why am I doing that? Because I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm whack as I want to.
No, it is not the one. It's not that one. It's not that one. Okay. I can be, it's not that one.
I don't know what this is. I don't just want to die. What are you talking about? Well, uh,
don't act like I didn't buy a service and pay for the year four months ago or so and, uh, moved and
don't need it anymore. We don't think I'm going to get my money's worth and continue to use though,
that, that the, the privacy and the potential routing of a VPN provider.
I'm gonna let this thing run out. Critical thunderclap. I feel like, wait,
are there any important moves? Critical pain. It lives a huge deal of damage to a single foe.
Critical pain. What is it? Max X and then, hold on, how do you press that on Xbox with your
Max X plus B. I have to hold it like my thumb and finger. That's kind of a weird combo to press.
Anything else? I can't air spike. I'll think I saved the points.
Good for the big guys. Yeah. No, I, yeah, I'm still streaming through VPN. So I've lost literally
anything less than a thousand for a full stream is that's normal. Cause nothing can ever be
perfect. No matter how good or how fast or how stable something is in that back when there was
no internet problems at all. I mean, you typically will always drop like at least a few hundred frames
stream. That's not, I'm not, don't worry. I'm not alarmed by that. We're losing our few remaining
chances. Our contact in the division has left classified material for me in a box at the army
testing facility. I don't get it. Why they're praising like fiber was the second coming of
Christ. Well, yes, because, um, this fiber line is a 1000, 1000 line or 400% less than what I was
paying for a 330 line at the old place. So yeah, I am going to talk about it like that as cable sucks.
This is Len. I need you to listen to me. I can't protect you anymore. We've lost control.
Both of us. If you don't let me help you, you'll destroy yourself and the rest of us in the process.
Actually very, very true statement. I don't like what you're saying. I don't grow a car.
Oh, it's bad. Looks like worse than a super villain. Okay. How many people has the Joker killed?
Oh, like what? Like less than 20 just today. The Hulk has killed like 5,000 fucking people.
I'm talking only today. All right. This is the frame rate boss.
Grab him. I got to get like up on his head. Grab him. The army's doing damage. Yeah, I know.
Oh, I think I lose. I need to retry this one. I'm going to be here for a long time.
I'm going to be here for a very, very long time. What did he say? What? What did he say?
What did he just say? What do you mean? I wasn't even paying attention.
He said mop up. I'm done here. Right? Like I'm done. What are you talking about? Hold on.
Let me hear that again. What do you, what do you, when the Hulk is confined by a special attack,
he can struggle. Yes. Okay. All right. Kill me. I want to hear what you guys are talking about.
Come and mop up. Now I'm not going to be able to unhear that for the next 30 times I die to this
guy. All right. Stupid. All right. Launch a missile. Incoming missile. That's not a missile. I want
you to do a missile. Doink. Tell me again to grab missiles and throw them back. I'd love to hear
you tell me about it. Tell me. Yell at me. You should be grabbing missiles. Grab the missile.
You got one. Where's that tank? Where are you? Wait. I died. This is going to be hard. It's not
that. It's come, it's coming mop up boys. Coming mop up boys. Coming mop up boys.
Yeah. Coming mop up boys. Coming mop up boys. Coming mop up boys. See it's coming mop up boys.
It's that's what he's saying. That's what he's saying. Why would I do that? I was trying to like
prove to you guys. What am I proving to you? You already know what it is. This guy's impossible.
Can I just do an elbow drop? Can I just run? Run. Oh it fell. I don't even know what the strategy is.
What am I talking about? There is no strategy. I have to take down four, five health bars with this.
Grab his foot. Tanks at him. Yeah but I have to stand still for the tanks and I'm gonna get hit
by everything. Like I'm, I'm already dead. I'm gonna try to throw tanks at him. Or is there a tank?
Can I just get a shield for the time being until a tank shows up? I mean what are you doing?
Okay here comes some tanks. All right let's go. I'm gonna grab one. See this is what I'm talking
about. Me throwing this tank I'm getting just killed. Did we throw it? Holy shit that was a lot
of damage. But I need you over here. Come here. No get this out of here. Attack him. Him.
Junior. Are you watching the movie with your dad? Like he's really hyperactive right now.
Dad's just fucking sick of his shit. Junior sit down. I'm trying to fucking enjoy the Hulk. Ultimate
fucking missiles on screen. That mist. Dad's reading a newspaper. Dad's not even watching
the movie. He just doesn't want uh little Timmy to be jumping around excited about the Hulk.
God. Okay I got the right strategy but I have to stay alive. Yeah I I ain't gonna show that on
screen. Uh I'm not gonna put that image on screen. But you are free to um to look at it on your own
time if you feel like it. You can do that if you feel like it. You can just on your own time. You
can look at whatever image you want as long as. It's nothing to do with me. Literally nothing to do
with me. Has nothing to do with me. I'm just gonna get away. Yes I do. Just run. No dad.
There's the first tank. Oh nervous. I used that one already today. I used that one already. Oh
nervous. Oh scared and oh I tried to. I already did that one today.
I'm gonna do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again.
Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again.
Look at what I was doing. What's this bullshit? Tank. Tank. Land so I can punch you. Okay we're
doing good. I'm gonna heal. Pick up the heal globe. Run. Heal. I wish I could see.
Destroy this whole entire place. Safe going up. There he is. Wait the energy meet me.
All right let's get him. Here is another tank. And shut up. Oh banner. Banner what the heck man.
Do it. Oh she's alive. Oh I need a tank. I need a tank right now. Right now. Come here.
That's it.
You spray paint your hair green to mock me.
Oh no. Is it hypnotism word? That's all we had to do. Can I buy anything?
114 000. Air cannonball. Wait I need super air strike. Damn it. Oh I want it. X in the air.
Air critical thunder clap. Oh that's actually kind of cool. Yeah I want it.
Oh I need air sonic clap. Chalk wave smash repeater. I'm getting this. Air spike.
Critical mass surge level two. Buy the missile pack.
Follow Blonsky and escape from the vault. Defeat the capture ward and smash your way through the
vault defenses and leap to freedom. All right. You can't just open his mind. It's like trying
to peel an onion with a chainsaw. You promised me he'd have the best of care. I said to the
best of my ability. It's out of my hands now. Wait I've been in VR this whole time haven't I?
Oh you can't just open his mind.
Tough you are to the nearest decimal point. I don't need to know how to become
like you. I need to know how to control it. Voice what are you? I'm Ahab. I know you get angry. It
makes you big green. We'll make sure we have so many protocols in place to prevent you from doing
that. Here's funny dog and cat compilation number 412 on YouTube. Here is guilty dog compilation
number six. No way you'll get angry at this. All right let's just stretch it in a little bit.
I'm not the devil. Okay all right I'm up. I'm up. I'm up. I'm up. Turn it off. Oh that was smashed.
Hey bye. Follow Blonsky. Oh why was that? I got critical mass. Run through.
Oh blood. Want to see more blood? You think the hulk should get more blood out of his enemies?
Text bloodbath 426442. Hey by the way how the fuck does that even work?
When you text like the five digits. I don't understand. It's not a phone number. I don't get it.
It doesn't make any sense. They don't do that anymore. Yeah remember it was like if you want
the funny cat wallpaper text funny wallpaper to like whatever number number number number right
and you how how I don't get it. Text money. Okay I need to pay attention before I lose.
This too many how many fucking people are in here? If you want funny family guy text Peter.
Whatever number number number number don't say numbers.
I need to burn away for a second. Hail him. I'm gonna play numbers go up.
I'm not what do you mean? Play numbers go up. We're good. We should play stock market simulator.
Is that a real game? Is that a real game? Is that a real game? Is that a real game? Does it follow
the SMP? I'm not Shrek. Different big green guy. I mean I guess we could I'm like a muscular version
I guess. I won't miss this. Suck. Hey what's the fucking timing then?
Seriously what's the timing on that shit? He just exploded himself. Haha Shrek wins again.
Is there a reason why we're hunting? What is this for? What is this for? Watch it. No the grab moves are so dumb.
Like what the fuck? Get this grab move shit out of here. Dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog shit dog
I'm available!
Nobody even did a move there.
We were both trying to throw at the same time.
We both have money on ourselves losing.
For a Jerma Rumble?
Hmm. That's a thought.
Yeah, it's just a big green guy.
We take very much development.
Quack quack quack quack quack quack.
What do we call ourselves? The Jerma Crew?
Yeah.
Sure.
Whatever you say, game.
No, just glue your hand to my head and kill me?
Oh, did you have to do it?
Oh, okay.
Fuck.
We have to fight in this little fucking corridor.
No, now you can't get in here, the gate's closed.
Fuck off.
Now I fight the huge guy.
I need to throw explosives at him.
Don't let him blow these barrels up, they're very important.
Just throw fucking, just throw dice in the air.
Whatever lands.
That's what happens.
D&D Hulk.
I grabbed one.
He's sure he's not pretending.
I'm pretty sure he is.
He has to be.
And he grabbed me during that
attack and stopped running and throwing.
But I'm gonna get grabbed and half my health disappears.
Every enemy in the game has a
You can't just open his
Get away from me, you pile of filth.
Just swing.
What happened in this room?
Did he leave a grenade?
Get away from me, you pile of filth.
Sorry everyone I know in there.
I dropped the grenade and ran out of the fucking room.
Speaking of running out of rooms, I'm just running.
Why even play the video game?
Alright, shut it on him.
Use new moves and what?
You see the fucking insanity
You see the fucking insanity that's going on on the screen?
that's going on on the screen?
X, Y, and then Y, Y, X.
This is not that hard.
I don't have any clubs. I don't have any club moves.
X and Y?
Let's try that.
Punch the missiles back? No, we've already shown how ineffective that actually is.
Get me out of here!
Why can't I just climb out?
Look at us.
What?
Alright, cool, yeah.
I don't know.
Pogs are
Pogs are for dumb idiots.
Pogs are for
Pogs are for your breath smells, I bet.
Dude, just X, X, Y, Y,
Dude, just X, X, Y, Y, man. Like Y, Y, X, X.
Dude, just X, X, Y, Y, man. Like Y, Y, X, X. Do you combo on these?
X, X, why are you not doing a combo?
Why, why?
It's just a game?
No, it's the lifestyle.
I am the fucking Hulk.
Don't you understand?
I can't even attack him.
I just have to throw shit at him.
I can't physically fucking swing at him.
I just have to throw shit at him. I can't physically fucking swing at him.
Damn it!
Crusted, I needed that.
I just goomba stomped that I needed that so bad.
What happened?
Alright, throw a broken car at him.
Just do your combo.
X, X, Y, Y.
This motherfucker just tripped.
I need a...
Fucking broken down, broke ass car.
Just hit him.
I can't, you can't just punch him.
Eat this shit.
I hit the fucking dumb asshole in front of him.
Is he dead?
Just get the fuck away from me.
This is what it feels like to be a bug in a room full of people.
Where's that mosquito?
There he is, there he is, get him, get him.
Please don't get me.
No, open up a window, let me fly out.
I promise I'll fly out if you just open a fucking window.
Fucking chance, stupid human.
Oh, he killed me.
What was that grab?
No, guys, guys, no.
No, I'm sorry.
I ain't gonna fucking take the blame on this one.
I ain't taking the blame on this one.
I'm not taking the blame on this.
It's like I'm not locked on.
And who is even attacking who?
This is, no way.
You can't even fucking determine.
Like I said, alright, give me
some life.
I did it.
I just want to see if there were a bunch of people behind
that door. Oh, no, there's somebody.
You're coming with me.
Oh, shit.
Oh, he found me. He found me.
He found me.
Banner, I have the stormtroopers behind you.
I guess still floating.
Wait, the guy's floating in the
jump pad.
That's kind of a cool move.
Get explosions on you.
Escape the vault. Oh, God.
Escape vault. Escape inner base.
Escape outer base. Return to the
church. Great.
This is gonna be hell.
Oh, they're
seriously blocking
doors.
Do I have to actually kill everything?
Alright, where's the tank?
Where the fuck did they come from?
Where did all these tanks come from?
Where did they come from?
Where are you guys being here?
Oh, they're coming out of the doors.
Stand at the door and don't let them come out.
Can I leave yet?
Wait, just leave?
Wait, this is not a force field?
I can't leave.
Guys, this is like a force field doing this.
I can't get out of here. I have to kill everything.
Can I finally do bowling?
Yeah, I'm Hulk.
This is like just Hulk
bored. Let it go.
Oh, they're killing each other.
They're just singing
in the rain.
Singing in the rain.
What a day
to be around.
Now fucking die.
Can I get rid of this?
Just throw it.
I don't want this.
Wait, come here.
Somebody said throw it through the shield.
Oh my
God. What?
What?
What the heck?
I can't walk through the shield,
but I can throw things through the shield.
What object am I made out of?
What is this? A water filter?
And I'm like the
thing. This is like the fucking dirt
that can get through the filter, but not me.
This is like a...
I taught you that yesterday. It's been a whole day, man.
I think I got it.
Hey, you. Later.
Are you drunk?
No, I'm not.
I am actually not. Sorry to say.
Although I really
probably should have a drink.
Maybe like a
few days.
Watch some public domain movies.
Wednesday.
Double hit.
Where's this other one?
Out of the tower. One more.
Turn, Hulk. Turn.
Here's to that. Thanks for
blowing my shit up.
Now I can't break it. I need this other one.
I really cannot hit this.
Get up there.
Don't shoot this out of my hands.
I'll be so mad at you.
Go. Thank you.
Try another.
Oh, you missed that one.
Drive by the jets.
I want to ride one.
That's not how a plane works.
That's not how planes work.
This is not...
They fucking
It's not
like a little kid
putting a little kid in
this fucking bedroom.
Plane flies around like this.
Why is there not a toddler's
hand on that? Why?
I need to grab this.
How do I jump over it?
Banner.
Banner. Don't do it
Banner. Banner.
Object.
You're making me fucking
bald.
Why would you turn that way?
I'm trying to aim down here.
That's so...
Aim the other
fucking way.
What are you doing?
Of course, here comes a toddler plane.
Can't wait.
This really is fucking
dumb as shit.
I need to jump over
the tunnel.
Let's aim.
Yes.
You know all the people that I'm facing?
You know the people that I'm
directly facing with my character?
Target them. Definitely do that.
Target the people that are behind you.
This is fun.
Didn't even work.
Fire a missile in here.
Don't come in here.
All right.
They did.
I want that
targeted, please.
The thing in front of me.
Ultimate Destruction. The thing in front of me.
It's right in front of you.
It's right here.
Oh my god.
It's a fucking ceiling.
There's a bunch of junk in the way.
Shoot at me.
I dare you.
What is above me?
Is it a toddler plane?
Goodbye. Pick up the truck.
And attack.
Three. Two.
One. Go.
Where is this tower thing?
Break the target.
I don't like gravity.
Movie too long. Too boring.
Give me this.
No. Stop.
He stopped.
He listened.
Freeze.
Return to the church.
Just do your combo, man.
Express x, x, y, y, y.
Okay.
I don't rage.
Kindergarten.
Yeah.
I don't like that.
Aww.
To the devil his due.
After this cutscene I'm going to go take a break.
I'm going to get a water and I'm going to take a small pee.
The devil hulk's going to emerge and there's nothing I can do about it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I gave up on you.
Don't you just want to make the devil mad?
I'm a liar and an idiot.
I'm Jerma.
And a thief.
This is the regulator axis.
Where did you get this?
Let's just say it fell off the back of an army general.
You know.
Just in case I had to go to a Plan C.
Apology accepted.
New moves are available.
Bonski files to be unread do this first
Can I just go up
No, our surge level three important double super air-dash air cannonball though
Game a grinder. What is that? Oh and chain was get it. I'll be right back. I'm gonna get some
Water and take a small pee. I'll be right back
start
four and a half hours ago
Bad joke what long pee I got a water, too. I
was next
Me this is called meme dot PNG. Oh
Going that one either strange cargo. I want that better dash
Is it a hundred something thousand?
Something like that
150,000
How far away is this? Oh, that's so whatever could have just done this jump pod
No, not Murius
We have very little time if Ross and his men realize I've stolen the regulator access
They'll move to relocate the other half. We can't control power to the machine without it. That's why I'm sending you back out there
I know it's a risk because of this emergent devil. Hope we had no choice
What they're going to be on you like ants on a free meal
Make sure the regulator stays safe because this is our last change
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, I have to go and retrieve and bring shit back to the church
Is there any other missions in the game besides get item and put items into item box back at church?
Apparently they're right here
Sorry, I get hurt by that
Lot of you here
Yeah, so I didn't want to pick you up
targeting with this
So this is where we run and we pick up and run pick up run pick up run and that's it
We don't do anything else. How would practicing my moves help when there's ten people doing moves around me?
like if I
I'm just gonna grab it and run you see how close the helicopter was
I'm just gonna do this. I even fight any of these things
Wait, did I not get it? Wait, hold on. There was it what it was. It was an inside. It was inside that truck
Let's wait for the heel bring truck to the military base. Oh
not the church I
Can't jump with the truck. So I have to just walk what's just left in this game. It can't be much more
Right. I took back the fucking secret serum, right? That means that's that where at the end of the game
Two missions. All right. Well, let's go
All right, I brought the truck weapon eyes. What what the hell are you doing? I jump. No, there is no jumping
I mean, this is is this count as plus one letter grade. I mean sure I guess I think it does
I'm Fred Flint stoning this car, but I am driving the car
It's just a car coming through, you know, there's no cars drive
Somebody's got run over wait. I can stop this. He'll see through my what did he hurt? What happened? What is this?
This is free. Wait, do I have to get it checked? How does this work? Hold on there?
Are they gonna pat the car down? Yeah, I can't go faster than this
Why wouldn't I punch through the front and drive the car?
You know punt my pull my feet up tuck my feet up punch through the front of the bed here and grab the wheel
I just drive what does this achieve? I can still wear the car but be driving it
Hope just drive the car. Why do I have to walk with it? Oh
Retrieve the cube now
Wrong thing
Yes, you're the cube
Football that was American football
this is American football, but the
The ball has greased up with oil. Oh
This sucks. I have to do that whole thing again
Holy shit. This is horrible. I have to walk the car again
There has to be a faster way to do that. There was no there is not a faster way to do this
Like yeah Patriots must be yeah, this is nice
Good guy
Did I die did it hit me? I think I'm good
No, that was nothing wrong
That was the right warp because I'm gonna despawn all those enemies come back ain't gonna be any enemies there at all
Rock will be right there and I can walk the truck back in
Well, these are all funny images you good
Was that just that wrong warped down there? Wait, what?
Okay, wait for a second. I thought that
Good run this back at full health
How do I have fuck all health of being so close to the end of the game?
It's only one more health upgrade. I have the first two. There's like three. I think what you're describing is
It's a decision that the developers made when they made this game. I can't Hulk have like 10,000 more HP
You know, maybe band length. I'll just turn them off
Hey, you know each of my lesson turn links off. Just disable links. You know, I'll teach him a lesson
All right out time to teach him a lesson
All right. All right
Mods if people's if people do a link in chat, I'm them up 10 minutes. Got it. That's gonna happen
That's gonna happen to you. I've just made the order. I just gave the order. It's gonna happen. I the order has been placed
It's gonna happen. If this if you do purple text with a link
You're out of here. Ten minutes. That's it purge purge them. Oh you guys are getting fucking destroyed
Tell you I'm a man of my word 40% of the time. This is one of those times. I
See you did there. You try to get a nightbot band trying to get a nightbot timed out nightbot has immunity
Why would I time out nightbot? He controls everything here. I
Tell it and slowly slowly the links begin to cease
Ten the ten minute timeout
It's got them all fucked up. Okay. Let's go
Hurry go. Where am I going? This is not even the right fucking way to go. It's only one exit. Oh
shit
You didn't just do that
Give me that. Give me them. Give me them. Give me them. They have so many things
So many things
Come on Bruce, come on deliver it into the end zone. Oh
That's done. I did it. I have to get another one. Okay. Here's a very important thing to ask
Well, I have to pretend to be a car again. I hope I don't have to
That would be down who just be ridiculous, right? That would be absurd if I had to go pretend to be a car again
That's just that's outrageous
Hey, here we go. It's up here
That it's a trap. Yeah, there's a trap. I mean, that's a pretty nice super computer. I bet that thing has a fucking 2080
It is a trap boo boo. Ah, whatever
No, I want to throw it at the thing. All I care about is throwing this shit
you deck things
Freak you freak you freak
5g noise. All right, somebody has to die. I need help
Did you die outside of the playing area?
Good. Oh, come on. They all have the grabby move
Use your combo. Oh
You know the words to say to get me going
There's the fucking 5g noises. I'm gonna mess with my brain
Alright, so here's the plan. Just kill just kill trying to get out of there quickly. I'm just gonna go
combo combo combo combo hit hit hit hit hit punch punch punch
Cuz I need help and I cannot fight
No, no, no, no, it's not gonna happen. No, he took the bait. Wait a minute. What if I just don't go in there?
Will they spawn outside?
Wait a minute. What if they spring the trap when I'm not even in it?
Oh
My ears. I'm gonna grab
Like I'm locked on over here, why would you even be turned the other direction?
What's the point of a lock-on? We don't even fucking lock on
So many people got timed out. Yeah, that's then the justice has been served
But it's sorry what you should have said was justice has been served. I have another idea and
It's dumb enough to work
It's gonna work. I'm gonna throw
Like seven or eight items into the arena the hardcore match now
Cuz I'm just gonna throw it at the 5g towers and that's it
I'm just gonna run come here. I'm gonna get steel fists
Tables ladders and chairs mad snow. This is a truck
street lights and
mailbox
Event let's go
They're all in there. Good. This is perfect. Perfect. Just get this shit done or of them
You didn't think I was gonna do this shit. Did you?
What you doing it?
You doing it again, okay, just a second. I'm not in a cutscene
That's not fair
There's two on top of each other here. Why did you stop hitting the towers?
We think because the games respawned them and while in the cutscene
Sorry cow. I got it grabbed and got killed and
What we were watching the same video
Okay, fucking come on get out of here
Yes, I know there it is
We got him tango to whatever he says service
Tango minus two my fucking god. Oh
My
fucking god
Probability to get grabbed here is like 85%
85%
You can't fight them. Have you tried the Hulk smash yet? Shit. I forgot about that one
What was it called again? What was called Hulk? What? Oh gently pet kitty cat
Let me just give five thousand bits. Thanks with five thousand bits. That's fifty dollars from Vilemi
What if I gave you a bunch of money to post links?
No, you can't and then I do they do asterisk asterisk asterisk that means that they link got timed out
Fifty dollars and I'm gonna buy you a link you're up
Thanks for the fifty dollars though. That's a lot of fucking money. That's that's too too much money
It's an insane amount of money. Thank you for giving it to me
I can't bring weapons in otherwise the game breaks and decides to respawn everything. I can't fight him cuz I get grabbed
All right, let's do
Run and grab and throw what I'm gonna do. You know, here's my strategy already
Run grab throw run grab throw run grab throw run grab throw run grab throw run grab throw run grab throw run grab throw
Run grab throw
Help in here. I don't even need to get it. What's the point?
Here we go. Oh shit. The cops are here guys. That means you're gonna stop, right?
God, let me do it
Helicopter who I have I can't go back in that's not fair. Let me the fuck out of here
Let me out of here. Let me out. Let me out of here. Let me out of here. Let me out of here
I did it
Let's go let me the fuck out of here. Where's there another tower? There's no tower
There's nothing holding this shit up. It's bullshit
It's nothing here
Right there women right there. Where what do you see?
Behind me. I don't see anything. It's hard to see anything
Right there right there right there right there right there right there right there
right there
Corner of the circle there is circles don't have corners
Motherfucker but to kill them. Oh, he's got one of our boys
Okay, all the 5g towers are dead. I just have to kill this one dickhead instead. Okay, let's go
So that no, that's a 5g air conditioner. That's not a 5g tower. What do I get the fuck out of here?
What on the street no, that's just a telephone fault
What are you talking about actually soft-locked but look what's going on over there like this explosion an explosion over there
Look up. Let me look up
Okay, I have a minute here to look keep one alive. Keep one. That is it's the air conditioners. It's the 5g air condition
Just kill me
The one that's on fire, but I can't target it. I can't target it
Oh, no, not one of our boys go back to the sewer where you belong. You have the 1.1 B version
Have to go
This is the Xbox game
This is the original Xbox game
What do you mean? I have to go get like a patch for this. It was no Xbox version Monka s
Be weird
Restart your system. Let me try this one more time
I need a patch. Wait, do I actually need to go download like an Xbox? I
May even do that on 360
On a backwards compatible game. Can you connect that exists?
That's not real, right?
Hey, there it is. Don't get trapped
Hey here comes do it put up the towers one, two, three four towers
That's it
right
Go disable the gamma shield. I
Can't even target the fucking thing
This is just getting all the keys
Yes, it is. I get it targeted. I gotta kill somebody
But now you target it, right? Oh
My goodness, um, I
Had it beat the last time too. That's what's so annoying
It's important. No, this this came out on Xbox and GameCube and PlayStation 3 right PlayStation 2
This cheat we allow you to all right, here's the deal if this screws up again, I'm gonna cheat
I'm gonna do an infinite help
That impossible. I
Didn't even want to do that. And now I've probably bugged it again. I grabbed a car on the way in here
Let's see if it works
Yeah, baby, right. We've got one of our boys
This is not a drill. He's got one of our boys
Ah, just give me that health pack
Give me out of here. I didn't I didn't go go go get this box quick bring I did I get out of the field?
I think I'm out of the force field. Did I get out of the force field in time?
I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. They pushed me out
These fucking idiots push
No, no, no, no, no
No
It's oh
He's got one of our boys, oh my god, I don't even have any emotions right now
How what what emotional what emotional thing can I even say? I just gotta
It's gonna fuck up again, isn't it?
There's no way this works. Yeah. Yeah. Oh get it. Okay, but look out a trap
Well, your operation seems to work very well
Go I'll fucking happen in this time. I'm grabbing that thing and I'm getting the fuck out of here
Second I'm able to I'm getting the fuck out of here. You know, I mean
emergency emergency
Come on boys
Just getting ready ready. I'm getting it in the right spot. I can just run and get the fuck out of here. Goodbye
the incredible Hulk
And
Out. Thank God. It was horrible. I'm still to deliver the coffee machine
This is I mean, this is a no. This is a science fair battery fucking go. I'm sorry for doubting you
Please forgive me. I mean, I don't think there was any doubt
That wasn't I don't think people were truly doubting me and if they were and just just shove it in their face that what I
Just did a cube. Thanks for the 10 community subs
216 thanks to the 10 subs. Seriously, I'm gonna I'm a buyer. Let's go. The cat just woke up and missed your stream
Can you start over?
Fucking cat
Yeah, let me start the stream over the cat. Here we go. Wait. No, no
I'm gonna save it for power surge
Yeah, save it for that. I'm not buying anything till power surge 3 a freedom's swan song coming up
Bruce they're closing in fast. Look just keep on the task of finishing the machine
I'll take care of the military literally roughly 10 minutes
It's gonna be a bumpy ride and minutes to stop them from destroying the church. God damn it
Okay, defend the church for 10 minutes
But last time it was a huge
Overestimation it's gonna be like four. It was a major overestimate last time. This guy's really bad with time
He just wants to make sure he's not
We you'd rather have a lot of time than a little right? Oh
No toddler planes
How much time how much time?
What come on? I gotta kill the toddler planes
They're the hardest things. What does that mean? How do you dodge that?
Goddamn it. I have to jump on it. They can just avoid it so easily. Where's the other one?
Give me a break
Just I'm gonna throw everything here at him just whip just whip shit at him over and over again
There's nothing to throw
Shit, they got one of my boys. Which one's gonna come in first? Probably this one
Yep, wait till they turn around
By the way, he just turned with
Stopped moving to turn. Get the fuck out of here. Hey, I killed your friend
Got him. Oh
Huh health? Thank you
Yeah, ah shit that was one of my boys
Like what's the move to do the super thing? It's X and B at the same time with critical, right?
All right. Oh, we are
I'm working
Yes, so
Draw another tank
Grab the fucking tank
Don't turn around
Turn around turn around just let it go. It's dead. Check this shit out. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go
Watch my ready ready ready ready ready ready. Here we go. Oh
Shit dead. Why is it sitting on the ground? Is it turning into a cannon? That's dead
Shit man
Okay, I win defeat the emerging devil Hulk this guy's the last mission. I think we're at the end
I'm about to be the game
Creature can you be certain? He's real. Trust me
He's as real as the Hulk is understood I'm going to activate the machine. I'm sorry Bruce
This next part will be very unpleasant
He's like vaporized me
Diablo versus uber Diablo and you're afraid also
Pay no attention to my giant glowing hit the boss in the eye weakness
Don't look at that stay away from that
Wait, I got it
Wait, what was that x583 2-0
Wait, why is there an error?
Dude, you can accidentally just press it a and it turn the console off. He said so bad the Xbox died
Creature
Alright, dude. Yeah, do not press that button. I got no I won't join you. I will never join you
Join me and together we can destroy this shit
Mine is to that
classic scene
No, it's one down. I don't know what that really means to third egg almost destroyed
Third egg defeat it. They beat him. I heard him now
Something I just got it off. Holy shit. I just did the super critical pain. I did was groin the hell
All right. Now what this is like phase two. Do these have health in them?
All right, just kick them in the tail
Don't go on the fire
But the eggs are coming back. Okay, all three eggs need to be destroyed before you can affect
Crocodile man, I feel like how I used to feel when I would play a game that I knew
My computer couldn't handle back in like 2002
But I wanted to try anyways and you pretended
To not care and you really did everything possible to not get annoyed at the fact that your computer wasn't good enough
Because you had like a fucking g-force like 300 M in your computer
It's hard to not be angry
Oh
All right that all of them one more
Shit, he just swiped me. There it is three. All right, don't fucking be stupid here the hell
Where oh
Just heal up pray for me Bruce. I don't know what the opportunities to go in. Jesus. I can't how do I you have my going?
I guess get killed. There's no he's got like this fucking gel. I
Did some damage I get some heels. I didn't want to go that way. What are you out of your mind?
This is hurt him by the way. It really should get out
Pray for me Bruce. I went to Taco Bell at 3 a.m
And it was kind of cold when I ate it pray for me Bruce
Hashtag shit my pants has to act diarrhea has to have Jocko Bell doesn't give you diarrhea
It was just say it because it's a funny meme
if you have memes I
Do I am you?
In fact Bruce, I can't tell you the last time I actually did have diarrhea
It had to have been at least two years ago. I don't know why I continue to say that
He's farming minus dude. He's farming minus tools again, didn't he?
Was this his health just stay alive
Get out get out get out get out get out. No, he's doing this stupid ice move
Regen, please. Here we go. Good sing something. Why?
Don't let him bite you. I can't have I've got a fucking move
You can't be serious
tear my head off
Just trying to get the help. That's all I wanted. I got it. Who the fuck am I?
Please no, I don't even know where the fuck I am
No, please. What the fuck? I can't even walk on
You fucking piece of shit. Give me a break. That was dog shit. Fuck you
Which health Oh effects turn them off. This is my this is my time. This is my time
This is my time to do it. This is my time to do it
Oh
Don't get greedy don't get greedy don't get greedy just run away
Save that critical mass
Out out out out out. What are you crazy?
Greed is unreal
Unreal the greed is unreal get out
That's it. He's dead. No, he's not. Oh, oh my god
Look at that
I win. Yeah, you got nothing you're dead. He's gonna get up here in his health. I'm gonna go to zero
Yeah
It's a terrible. I just died thing to say
No, this is the wrong way
Oh
There's no face too
Not gonna happen. It'd be funny. Let's face two
Save it and I can get the final upgrade. All right, give me one second. Oh what happened? Why is it dark?
This is what death is like
What happened?
Wait
I changed to the wrong scene
This is apparently this is a scene here
Oops, sorry about that. I pressed the wrong button
All right
Get the last health upgrade
I don't think that's the end of the game
That's probably very close power surge level three
Yes
Okay
Critical mass level two
Yeah
and
Missile pack weaponize
Yeah
Good any others
Air sonic clap sure imb in the air cool
All right. I wonder that that has that was definitely the big apex of the whole game that this has to be the end
Back to the badlands
The final boss wasn't patched into the xbox version. That would be weird
Where is it? Uh down
World one complete
No, this is this is called intercept
Do I actually have to intercept?
another convoy
Okay, your superhero duties are boring radiation signature coming from a cave near the vault
It looks like blonsky's undergone yet another transformation
The creatures headed back towards the inner containment area bruce reached the vault
Reach the vault entrance just get to the vault entrance. I'm just gonna run
I can't go in like this
I'm losing my mind
I thought I just killed him
Oh different guy
Let's go get him
Okay reach
Get to the vault entrance
The vault entrance is down there
I'm not gonna waste a second here. Let's go
I want to get some help
and
Fuck fighting a single thing
What who what superhero uses the front door
Pirate's elbow ain't gonna get me
You ain't gonna get me. You ain't gonna get me. You ain't gonna get me
No, you really want to try but it's not going to happen
Not going to happen
not
going to
Happen
Probably shouldn't have skipped everything
I'm gonna do the headbutt to this guy. It's the best move in the game
Although I can't do the cannonball. I don't have the cannonball. I bought the health and surge upgrades. Whatever they're called
All right. I'll just throw cars
Steel fist no throw car is more effective
How does that miss? Okay again
Again
Throw a car again. I'll make sure I get that thing. Don't worry
It's a secret and we're gonna well, don't we we'll look at those those those comics
Got a few more of these
Hey
What? All right. I need the
Move this way
Can I turn these into fists? Oh, I can't
Dumb why's it no longer damaging him? I think it doesn't hurt him
Um
Why am I getting diminishing returns?
You can't even avoid that attack it's unavoidable use the combo
Um, can I not fucking hurt this guy?
What is with this game?
You can't fucking avoid that attack
Use elbow drop play on how?
I can't grab on to anything. I can't grab anything. I can't i'm just gonna do this fine. Okay, I
That actually just fucking work
That's okay. That's
No other moves work on him though only elbow drop
Oh my god
Of course, that's the one that works
All right. We're good. I hope this is just a qte end of the game
The one time that I actually want it
That last boss fight was hell
Baby, i'm here blonsky. I should have come back sooner. Oh god
I've lost her
I don't understand
Is this mission directive? I only wanted to help her bet. That's all I wanted
She's gone
What's happening here? Emil? Who is she?
my wife
Nadia and my unborn child
They affected our job was to examine what we knew of gamma radiation and its effect on human tissue
It was a government sparked by your previous research
She was diagnosed with ovarian cancer
Emil
It's time to bring this to an end
No, you created gamma transmutation banner you did this to her there it is
Because of you and your damned experiments kill them you damn freak and now i'm going to return the favor
Can he swim kind of looks like a fish guy
Pursue and attack abomination
Bruce, this is samson
I know you can hear me. I need you to listen carefully
Okay, blonsky's headed out of town towards the hydroelectric dam above the city
You've got to stop him before he can do any damage
There's not enough time to evacuate everyone unless you can hold him
What the fuck is this dude? Do you hear me?
bruce
all right, there's one reason why this would be okay for me is if
You sent me this voicemail like an hour ago, and I just had really bad cell phone reception
Then you were trying to warn me an hour ago
the only
So much bigger than me
He's doing like a look at me. What?
Pursue I am pursuing him
Uh-oh the toddlers
Do we just have to
Why is he so?
Just use him as a shield. They'll just kill him
Just shoot the big guy. He's a bigger target
Shoot him
Just drove into it
Come on, let's get him guys me and all these kids
Here comes tank
If I shoot
That's right abomination me and all these children
They're gonna come take you the fuck out
Can't even fit in there. I guess you can
All right, get him shoot him
Come on toddlers
Let's go kids
No, come on planes. I know you can do it
Just drive into him. Nice
Did you just grab one? I think he just killed one. No, he's running away
Don't let him get the fuck away
I
Get him elbow drop
He's got me help me somebody
Don't need help
All right, get off. Let me go
Oh, you want to fuck with me? That's a big mistake motherfucker
oops
dead
Wait, where'd he he did escape?
Okay, give me the health. I give me the hell to give me though. This is ridiculous. Give me the help
You dick
How can they even fitting in this gorge?
All right, i'm gonna get a fucking rock
Just throw it at him. Should I throw this?
Okay, when when can we be done with this? Can I fight him now?
I need
His health up here his health up here his health up here. Okay help
Why?
You're doing that to yourself
Me and toad guy have not done a single thing
We haven't done anything
Maybe you shouldn't let toadless fly planes
All right, I gotta get up
What?
Holy shit throw the rock
Oh got a plane crash down here good I got more health
Wait, I gotta stay with him
Okay, man, man just stew
Can we stop?
I gotta get in front of him so he can take that fucking pain
It's both of us man. We gotta both do this
Oh shit
health
I jumped way too high
I gotta fight him
Oh, no. No. No, I do not
This is fucking stupid
This is this is stupidest fucking thing. I think i've ever seen
I don't we're not even fighting each other
Stop shooting the missiles at me
Well, he's just as irritated as I am
All right, should I go for a ball? Should I try to ball him? I'm gonna try to bowling ball him
All right, here we go. I'm gonna bowl him. I'm gonna get the last hit on him
Okay, here we go bowling
No, that's not
What the?
This is too much for my brain
This is way too much. I feel like i'm cheating somehow. Don't you feel like I did this that I turned this shit on?
Here we go again another fight
Okay, here we go fight
I brought all my friends
Jesus
I don't want to destroy any of them
I want them to be here. I don't want them to die
It's making this way easier
Is he regaining health? I don't think so
I think this is just supposed to happen except I don't think it's supposed to be like 10 planes fighting us
I think because I aggroed everything
I don't think this no, I don't think this is supposed to be how this plays out
What it is?
No, don't hit the plane. Fuck
Okay, let's keep going
He's headed for the dam
He's going for the dam. Stop him
Don't let him hit it
Oh, no
Why
No, it's gonna come back right it's not gonna do this
Please
I'm taking the disc out. All right, put it back in quick
Oh, you can't believe it. I can't believe he's the cutscene for him to break into the dam
Wait a minute. What is this bullshit? What is this bullshit? What is this? What is this bullshit? What is this?
This is the mission before that. Okay. We've got a weird gamma. Okay. We've got a weird gamma radiation
How did I not?
It's over. Oh
I can't go on like this
And this one sucked didn't it? This one sucked, right?
No, this one's not that bad. It's not that bad. Okay
All right. So I can't believe he crashed at the dam. I can't believe he crashed in the dam of all the places
He crashed at the dam
I can't believe it
Unbelievable
It's gonna crash again
No, it's not
Don't say that
There's only one way to that was seriously I had i'm so glad we played this game all the way to the end here
because that
last mission
was
Just one of the most ridiculous things I think i've seen in a video game
Like I can't even believe that's possible. Like this shouldn't even that shouldn't even be possible
But I i'm glad I got to see it
All right, kill this guy
All right. We're not that far back. Wait, what? How did you miss the elbow drop? How did you land on a wall?
How do you land on the wall?
I don't understand
Get down
Where's this guy?
Get crushed. I'm so glad this actually works
How sad would it be if I had to actually fight this boss again and potentially lose?
Huge one to end it. He's trying to do the same shit to me
There you go. Get the fuck out of here. I win. All right, save the game. Wait, maybe could I not even save the game?
Is that part of the problem?
Those coins are
All right, I got full health
We just have to do this shit again because it's the same mission
Are you sure I couldn't save?
No, it's because it was the same mission
Right. That's why oh, this is bad. Did raid come in? Oh shit. We did
Thanks, lazy purple
Welcome everybody. We're currently trying to do the mission for the second time. We got fucking destroyed
I
Can't save it. Yeah, this just can't happen again
Welcome guys. Thanks a lot. You guys had a good stream
We've had a good stream here
Check this out
You're about to see something real fucked up
Don't do it again. Let's go
Just move
Move with him. You don't have to die. I just have to do anything
Just heal when I can and that's it. Just grab health clues
Cubes and squares together health cubes
I don't know. I've known
Here we go. Where is he? There he is. Stay with him
Smash five see what happens. Okay
Gotta get back up to the fully kill me
All right, we're about 10% of the way there. That's so much more to do
We have to run
All the way all the way
In fact, i'm getting ready
All right with my friends
Get them planes
And then nice miss
Why would you even attack me at this point?
Always just hide. How are you all this bad at aiming? You hit me every time. Why can't you hit him?
Get him this motherfucker is gonna kill me
I don't know but probably pretty thick
Is this a missile? I need them. I need a missile launcher. I want to make the weapon
But then I can just walk around with them fire missiles at him
Over here, right missile launcher guy
Here we go right here
Make it missile pack. All right, let's go
Let's fight you fucking idiot
You dumb fuck you're supposed to fire them not
Oh, I don't need the missile pack. Who cares? All right, well, he's going he's going he's going he's running around. He's going
Yeah, we got that guy nice work missile pack. Let's go
Where is he at? There he goes
All right, two more of these and that's it
It looks like hulk made that noise
Guys, fucking leave me alone
There you go his two a lot more fucking people following us
Converve dead. No, i'm not i'm here
Oh lord, where is he?
Right. Okay. Here it comes attack
You guys are attacking me more than him now
Go after him. He's the bad guy
Oh, he killed one good. That's health for me
Thanks, get him guys. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good
Where is he?
Make a funny noise
I don't know what you want me to do
Is it better?
All right. Here it is. This is where it all went to shit after this part
Okay, here we go fight
missiles, yeah
Yeah, what about those?
About those missile packs
No, he made me drop my toy
Get away from me. Get away from me. Get away from me. What?
Give me that back. All right, can we?
Here it comes. It's the last part here
And I got the whole team here
I gotta get up there
Oh fuck
This is it. This is it. This is where he runs into the damn
I gotta get that health before anything bad happens
It's so hard to control this
This shit is fucking unbelievable. Like you don't understand
All right, here we go. This is it. Here it comes
Try kill some of the planes. Okay, i'm gonna destroy some of the planes. I gotta there's too many planes
This too is gonna happen again, it's gonna happen again. It's gonna happen again
Kill planes quick
I gotta kill the planes
for another rock
fucker
Got no one got one
Okay, fuck. All right. Just don't don't do it do it
Do it
Go into the damn forget about all the planes
Oh
Stabilize able
Stable stable
Yes, it worked
Thank god
Okay
end game
We're in the end game now
This message contains a coded subliminal. I'm hoping you can use it to track your target on the map
All right, this is end game. Do not allow abomination to destroy the damn
Don't let him destroy the damn
Sounds fucking hard
Defeat abomination
No, they came with me
Really all about batter
Firing missiles
Don't let him destroy the damn
Oh, I am trust me. I am
Fire fire at it. Whip it at him. All right, here we go. That's where I want him
Don't oh fuck. He got me
It's okay. Stay right here
Do not allow him to do this
Um, how am I how do I stop him? What is he doing?
Did I stop him?
Holy shit, I just electrocuted him for two full health bars
I need health get some health back
Do not combat run me, please
I'm trying to reach in health
All right, here we go. Shit got me top rope
Fuck out of here
He's going for another generator he's going for that I gotta get up there and I gotta top rope him
Line it up line it up line it up line. Here we go. Go go quick quick quick quick do it get on the jump
Shit
Got one more health bar this he was way easier than fucking safe
Of course, he would be easier than safe
Go to one of the generators dude, aren't you don't you want to go break one of the generators?
Don't fire me
firing on me
You're stupid
You're just dumb. You're firing at the wrong person
Wait, here we go. Oh shit
Get on top of it. I gotta get up there
Don't get electrocuted you fucking stupid game
It's such a sloppy fucking mess
Oh my god, what's with the nuke?
Kill him with fucking cards. Who cares?
I gotta what did I just catch?
Oh, it's a mess
It's a fucking mess, but i'm gonna beat him. I beat him. I win game over see you tomorrow
There's a phase two probably
Did you actually just take out the damn?
Wait, did he just accidentally kill himself?
First today releasing almost 20 million metric tons of water in a statement released this morning
General thaddeus ross blamed the hulk for their devastation
We had the cure
It was right there in front of us
Dreams always are len, but you can never reach out and take them now, can you?
We could start again and finish this time
Still helicopters everywhere to let me help you. I can't stay here
They're too afraid of the hulk to let you try
I guess this is me len
I'm not a person anymore. I'm the hulk
And I can't force people to understand
Even in cutscenes, it doesn't matter
This doesn't make any sense bruce
You don't have anywhere to go
I don't know people going to work in the morning
people going on vacation
we're going to
the funeral for one of the
500,000 people you've killed over the last five days bruce
Will you tell me?
Congratulations, you've defeated abomination and have completed the game
You've unlocked hard. I'll never play that one
Savage banner is now available
Enter villain to play the game as abomination. That's cool
Go check the comics. I will you can play as banner the human. That's so stupid
All right, what is savage banner?
I don't have access to savage banner
Where is it?
Wait, it was at the very top
I figured it'd be all the way at the bottom savage banner
You just play as just half naked guy
Well, that's funny
Why couldn't I have had that from the beginning of the game?
All right. Well, let's um, let's go to
Uh, let's go back extras
Okay art gallery comic book gallery gallery one. Let's see here. He is
Incredible hulk the original comic book was just a direct ripoff of frankenstein incredible hope the monster unleashed
banner the incredible hulk
They're smashing out and nothing can stop them. Well, it's the juggernaut
Side by side with the juggernaut
Incredible hulk and the wolverine
He's a bad guy hulk was a bad guy for like the first
30 years
That's the first comic that wolverine was in what's someone to star on it?
Who will judge the hulk?
Fantastic for mr. Mr. Slippery arms. It's like
I know he's like the smartest man in the world
His power is just goofy. He's like a clay fighter. Incredible hulk versus the rhino
Twice the rage
Cool with me and the boys
Funko pups
Incredible hulk. What is this?
This is a movie incredible hulk. I only have one here
so strong
I don't remember this
What's that hulk versus wolverine? Why do they hate each other so much?
nice
nice nice nice nice pretty cool sick
This looks like a goro render. I feel like this is like a mortal kombat render
That's pretty cool
These are nice. These are really nice
That's nice
Stay away from my coco puffs
Isn't anyone of those commercials?
All right movie gallery
In-game movies. Oh the making of this
This is the gym that i'm going to show you this is the tool the designers use
I'm a designer. I want to say okay. Well, what's it like?
to
To play a good game kevin too easy too hard
What is most fun to the player the gym allows the designer?
To play with these numbers and encounters in a very easy way as an example like right now hulk's max charge jump
He goes to a height of 20 meters
So in this tool we can take that number and say bump it up to 40 meters from now
Holy shit a max charge jump and should jump twice as high. You know how old these computers are
I could bump it up to six down to one. I could do that. That was a blurred playstation controller
I did do a lot of the effects basically kind of builds up an effects database
That we use to blow up our props basically or damage them or make them smoke or make them light on fire
Anything that blows up or has fire flame smoke debris dirt. That's me nice
Obviously hulk won every effect took up a chunk of
Wait, hold on comics found 20 smash point hulk attacks. I did
2589 attacks. I jumped
3122 times I died 55 times
I caught 19 missiles. I weaponized 126 things. I did 100. I did
12114 combos
I grabbed 27 things
I got juggled
1471 times
I killed 731 people 43 police 138 soldiers
104 missile soldiers
15 transports 76 tanks 74 combat vehicles
53 gunships 11 strike fighters
152 infantry destroyers three titans
12 mrls's two capture wardens
through 25 soldiers
Elected 1100 stuff. Very cool. All right. That was fun. See you guys
Tomorrow do villain. All right, what are some of these codes to put in?
What are we gonna do tomorrow? That's a good question. That's a really good question. Actually
What are we gonna do tomorrow?
toontown
I don't think I can get toontown set up tomorrow
All right. What was another one?
It's easy
It's so easy. It's so easy
You can do it. It's so easy
toontown rewritten is already set up
toontown
I'll try i'll look at i'll look into it tomorrow. Well, no, we're gonna like I i'm gonna like
We're gonna like crash the fucking server
I'm gonna open up toontown remastered and the servers are gonna turn off. It's not gonna work out
I'm gonna do like an 80 minute stream delay. What was the suit one?
Did I I don't did I unlock this suit fit?
Can't do it character abomination
All right chase, but no, what was it smash five? It's like almost seven hours i'm going longer than I should be
Remember I told you guys that I I wanted to have streams capped at like six hours five to six hours max
Supposed to be moving around
Uh-oh
Uh smash five doesn't fit. What does it smash? What smash one five? It just gives me points
um
Is there another one?
Is there a is there one that's even worth doing?
Oh canada
Okay, oh canada and then cheese five and then but there's also retro
Canadian flag shorts, okay. Are they on?
transit
Start up the game, dude. I'm I gotta put these in
mass transit, okay
Um now what toontown t o n t w n. Oh, i'm sure that works retro retro what is that fit?
Which are retro retro what?
Which are what retro 64?
No, no, no, no, no, no just just retro 64. What?
I don't care. Let's play with abomination for 12 seconds and then end the stream
It's me
Thanks for watching everybody. Well, wait, wait, wait, hold on wrong one. I'm glad we sat there for that long and did that
See you tomorrow. I'm
I'm gonna pretend to think i'm gonna pretend to play toontown tomorrow, but it's not gonna happen. I can guarantee it
One server or two servers
That are probably
Just being rented for like less than 100 people to play on that because people really love that game
We want to keep it going which is very admirable and it's great
Uh, we're gonna destroy the whole thing and it'll be shut down. It'll be shut off in 10 seconds
So that's not gonna happen
I'm willing to give it a look. We'll see
Anyways, uh, let's do the bits and the subs fairly quickly here because I do want to get up
Don't uh, i'm going against my new rule
I said
uh
More stream days less stream duration i'm already breaking it because we're about at seven hours
It's probably going to be about seven and a half hour stream
I'm supposed to be doing this doctor's orders
Anyways killcon. Thanks for the three dollars germa
If you had the choice between banning the top 1000 chatters or selling your funko pops, which would you choose and why?
I would sell the funko pops because I don't give a shit about them at all
They're interesting little toys and I think they're cool. I think they're interesting. I would just sell them
Like immediately like like today. I would just sell them. I'll put them on the market right now
Hey fitty. Thanks for the thousand bits. Hey germa. Hey fitty
The jewish bro. Thanks for 540. Are you not doing the movie stream because manos the hands of fate is public domain
And it's so bad. It's good. It would probably be a certified germa recommends movie tall streamer
Um, it's um
I think everybody's seen that movie
It was on the list, but ever I think everyone has already seen it
I want to I want to watch public domain movies that i've never seen before
like the gorilla
I guarantee you none of you have seen the gorilla and I haven't seen the gorilla
I don't want to put on a movie that we're just like rewatching
All right, remember this one manos. Yeah
They don't almost all of us have seen it, but let's watch it. No, no, no, no, no
I want new fresh public domain content that you and I have never seen before
And I guarantee you there's probably
Less than one person that's seen the gorilla
In this chat fresh fresh content
That's the reason why?
Peaceful haley. Thanks for the 250 germa. How did the move go? It wasn't too much trouble
Also, I finally got a car almost 23 years old and finally getting a damn car
Next up is my own place. I feel like i'm going in slow motion when it comes to being an adult
That's not even not even remotely accurate
Hope auto is doing well. Have a good night. You're 23
Let me just let me just stop you there
Um, I didn't become an adult really
Until I was like 20 fucking six twenty seven twenty eight
You got a lot of time. Don't worry
23 is not
As old as you think it is
It's still extraordinarily young
He thinks he's an adult
I am
Yeah, you got plenty of time
Plenty of time trust me
Uh, uh the movement good
It just was talking about slow motion
it kind of went in slow motion just because of
how
All the coronavirus stuff. It's hard to do a lot of stuff hard to set up a lot of things
Just because of a lot of people had reduced staff
It was a very slow move
It's okay
It is
Done. We are here
Yeah, thanks for the 250
Unkey
Phil thanks for the five dollars. Would you stream pac-man world for the game cube?
I mean, I love pac-man. So you you can't you don't have to do much to convince me
There's not a whole lot of arm twisting to get me to play a pac-man game
Even though I think I played one pac-man game in six years
Still you don't have to twist my arm that hard
And the one pac-man game that I played in six years was not even a pac-man game
It was pac-man was in the game. It was smash brothers for the wii u
so
Maybe you have to go even longer
Thanks a lot rick bilby. Thanks for the four dollars germany your streams are an escape and without them
I would be in a worse place
Please don't buy any more funko pops or i'll have to make a reddit account. Don't worry. I have bought I had
If I bought funko pops who gives a shit
But I didn't all the things on the shelf that you see behind you were purchased
As of about three years ago
Not purchased a funko pop in three years. It's time to get over it. It's time to get over this guys
Uh crump. Oh crumpo
Thank you crumpo for the 15 dollars
I think that burger joke should be on the nominations for best joke with more than five minutes to set up
As I feel like your entire life was set up for that joke
I don't I disagree
Does it I completely disagree?
It wasn't a worst or best
It was a setup. We were trying to we were setting up everybody
Thanks for the 15 dollars. It's a lot of money
Shibiririririru. Ah, thanks for the three dollars. See the secret is a great home cooked burger is a well oiled
Real hot cast iron skillet get your well seasoned meat. Hopefully 80 20
and stick it
In the skillet then smash it down with a spatula until it's thin
You cook in a few minutes and be extremely delicious. You forgot to say flip it
I didn't hear you say flip the burger. So I just didn't flip it and in a few minutes. I have half of raw burger
Not a good you got be specific
Thanks for the recipe mono cucumber. Thanks for 258 germ. I've been able to catch a lot more streams lately
Streams and videos really help me keep sane in the lockdown. So thank you
Anyways, I recently was playing around with some parts. I built a lego germa with multiple hairs for your variations
Those are included parts guide in case you or someone in chat wanted to build one for yourselves
With the nightwing shirt
Take a look at that. I'll show this one here. This is the most important one
This is the most important one for sure. Look at this
How would they both the bazooka image? I don't understand
I just saved it as this
Here we go
The hair is pretty accurate. The bottom right hair is perfect top left hair is perfect
Is that that's actual lego?
Serial numbers
I don't think legos do cereal. No like the serial number
This is such like a high quality photo. I feel like this should be a like a profile picture somewhere for me
But if you have a lego profile picture
I don't know if I want to do that
Oh look, it's auto
And down. All right. All right. All right. All right
You don't use twitter. Anyways, no, I don't
That's a very accurate statement
Thanks for the legos and there you go. You guys have the pieces if you want to make your own
uh lego germa
I feel like I don't know to like to burn or something to be like a voodoo doll and try to hurt me on whatever
You guys are gonna do with that
Thanks for the 250
Uh, sir canine. Thanks for the 250
Vocal and rage streamer takes out rage on us soldiers by playing mini games with their mangled corpses
As it's a home run game. It's in the game. It's a home run game
Soup gg. Thanks for the 250. Please. Let us give this guy money on cameo and have him make you a sub sound for one time
joke
For the purpose of not spoiling what this could be i'm gonna look at this first
No, no, no, no, no, no
Uh, you just gave I just got an idea. Um, I think all the shark tank people do cameos
What if I just pay them all a ton of fucking money, whatever their cameos are
And have them just react to my shitty shark tank presentation
Each one of them i'll just have yeah. Okay. Can you can you talk about like my new my new product?
And get them to give me like 60 seconds and like edit a bunch of shit so they I can play
On like a little device or something in my hand different clips from each one of the sharks while I do my presentation
And we'll just have like like six cell phones set up with they're like facetime
Forward, I know at least three or four of them do cameos. I'm certain of it
Pay them to pretend to love it
Hey, it's me. It's me kevin. I just gotta tell you about this great product
Let me tell you
I think it's fantastic. I think it's fantastic. In fact, no, listen, i'm gonna come for you with
25 equity
It's yeah, that's gonna be hilarious
That's not trump. That's kevin. Um, oh kevin o'leary
And for that reason i'm out
He talks like that
They cost a thousand dollars
I know i'm supposed to get through this quickly, but
What do you mean? They cost a thousand dollars
Meo.com
Okay, like kevin o'leary
He's not on here anymore
Wait, just did he does he not want to did he not want to do it anymore?
No, wait, he doesn't do it anymore shit. What about the other sharks?
Shark tank. Oh, there he is. Kevin o'leary. Mr. Wonderful. Okay
It's 1200 dollars to get him to do like a 10 set. Wait, what?
1200 dollars
To do about one one to two minutes
I'm looking for like five to ten minutes of footage
I would have to pay kevin o'leary
About ten to fifteen thousand dollars
To make me like ten of these
Who are some of the other sharks? Because I know there's a couple
Damon robert barbara there. Oh my god
Barbara's 600 robert is 500
Damon is 199. All right, damon
Seriously, thanks for at least being 200 not fucking 500. All right, so we got four sharks
All right, how much?
One of them should just be like a happy birthday and shit
Like excuse me. I'll just let me can I just hear from what can I just hear from kevin see if he has an offer?
Say happy birthday to you jeremy's very very important day because he was too expensive
So I just had him do one. I like this idea and it's in shitty dumb shit like this
Starts to get my brain going and then I get into it and I really want to do it
This is this is like a twenty to thirty thousand dollar project
great
Okay
Cool. All right. We'll take a look at that. Oh, yeah
Just get impersonators. No, they have to be real. That's be the real thing
If it's not real, I don't want to do it
You understand it has to be like that. Well, we know how much that costs
Thank you to
pixel mic for the five dollars
Thank you crons grow for the fifteen dollars jeremy. Hope you're doing well. Here's twenty dollars towards your boob enhancement surgery
Don't let your body defy me. What why would I need to get a boob enhancement surgery?
What they're just fine
This is what they're just fine
What?
Thanks to the fifteen dollars
Non-descript civilian give 25 community subs and I missed it because I was probably in the middle of getting angry like a child
At a game that came out in 2004. So thanks for the 25 subs. That's a lot of money
If you do the math do it right now. It's a lot of money
Thanks for the 25 subs
a brooding
brooding
chiroptera
brooding chiro teptera
Thanks for the 10 bucks
Remember the person who said to play pathologic 2, please don't actually do that
You'll get all my favorite characters killed
I i'm not gonna do that. That'd be for halloween
Anyways, I had a dream about you and your girlfriend the other day, but maybe i'll tell you that later
the monka s
Traditional monka s situation here
Thanks for the 10 bucks. I appreciate it
It is sky. Thanks for the two thousand bits twenty dollars
Hey wondering if you plan on streaming megaman legends 2 in the near future. It's behind me. It is sky
It is behind me
Just need to find the right
Time and reason to do it
We're having trouble counting to two recently on this stream
And it's got to change
Thanks for the 20 bucks though
Lost the music an anonymous cheerer. Thanks for the 250 and they do
the anon
emote
And on email, thanks for the 250
Hey lemon, thanks for the five dollars. I'm not sure how long you've been playing
But do you know that you can charge your nest jump while in midair, right?
Yeah, I i'll just hold it down
You hold it down. You let it go hold down. Let go hold down. Let go. Yeah. Oh, yeah
Yeah, I did. Thanks for the five dollars. Thanks for the tip
Peaceful. Haley. Thanks for 250. Hi again. Just notice the stream title. Please replace huge and strong with I am
Thank you
Everybody knows that already though. My friend just showed me the mega milk picture
unfriend him
for her
Hey sikilos, thanks for the 250. Jeremiah. I just finished watching the first eight seasons of caribbeanthusiasm
Thanks to you recommending it at the start of a stream a few months ago
Yep, you got any other suggestions for me lots of love mom
I'm so glad you watched it
What a fantastic show what a perfect every episode is perfect
Uh, sure. I have a comedy
Um, I haven't caught up with the last few seasons the last maybe two or three seasons, but silicon valley is was hilarious
It's a mike judge
Brand show mike judge if you don't know is the guy responsible for beavis and butthead an office space
And it's hilarious
really
Smart well-written show is really funny
Uh, yeah, people are saying always sunny in philadelphia. That's another fantastic show where almost every episode is perfect
The exceptions are maybe a few but you can't everything can't be perfect
We already went over that earlier
prairieland park boys, you know
I can't say yes to that because i've seen
Like six or seven episodes of trailer park boys and it was like it was funny it was
but I just
I didn't I didn't I didn't watch anymore
Not because I didn't think it was any good
But I I didn't grab me hard
The one thing that I didn't think was really funny and they stuck with this for from my understanding almost the entire show
Is the guy not ricky?
And not not not and not this guy either not bobbles. Who's the other guy?
The guy that just always had a drink in his hand julian. Yeah
julian
Broke the course of the whole show and they they ran with this forever
There's every time he's on camera. He has a drink in his hand like a whiskey and coke
Every single scene he's in every single fucking episode. It's just that's absolutely hysterical
That is by far one of the funniest things I've I you could ever do and to keep that going
It's just ridiculous
Why is that but he's so my purpose would be so painful to do after even one season
Even after a car crash he was in a car crash
Wait, he got he was at a in a car crash and then going to the hospital. What?
Uh, maybe I
Should I give that show another chance?
He crawled out of the wrecked car with with a drink in his hand
I can't believe that they kept that going and it did under any circumstance
Yeah, I mean it was I I chuckled. I thought it was funny. I thought it was smart and interesting
But I just never grabbed on top of it and grabbed it
I never grabbed me in the head
But maybe i'll give it another chance. It was funny
Hey mick mussels. Thanks for the thousand bits feeling generous. Love you germa and chat
And you you too
Hey lm man. Thanks for the three dollars germa gorge your hatred embrace your rage on chat. I already did
you
You had to have been there when I did the
The if you put a link in the chat, you're gonna get timed up in 10 minutes
That was unleashing a lot of people got timed up
And again lm man. Thanks for four dollars germa
I gifted 10 community subs yesterday because the day before that I promised to myself that if auto was better by tomorrow
I would give subs
Thanks a lot. That means a lot
He's doing good. He's actually doing really good now
His antibiotic stint is over
And he seems to be back to normal
But I am going to go to the vet
uh
A day or two from now probably on monday or tuesday
To just do a recheck
Maybe just talk to the vet again and say hey it's been
Been on the antibiotics for a week
He's better
Is there anything else you want to do?
But he is seems like he's fine. That's really good. I'm really glad to see that
Thank you. Hey yoda 985. Thanks for the 250 for your information. Mr. Streamer. My username is in a short joke
But i'll change it if it makes you upset is not
Yoda 985 is not a your short joke. That's i'm surprised by that. I'll be honest with you
I you know how many photoshops of yoda with my face green on it i've seen at least a handful of times i've seen um
mini me and yoda
At least a dozen times in the last year. So sorry for jumping to that conclusion
You keep that name. You don't have to change it. It's your name
a g m egon thanks to five dollars
Remember you can't keep moving forever. The police will find you one day and take you back to boston for the santa trial
Also, thank you for providing entertainment right now. I'm an essential worker and it's been stressful very stressful out there
Your streams are a highlight of my day and they give me something to laugh to
Yes
I need a new trailer
Lady for the rumble or ladder match
Because we got all right. We're gonna talk about this
We i'm going to hold
For the first time ever and this is a big change and a lot of people might not want to see this change
but a lot of people might be happy about this
I think we're going to do
a
Almost like a nomination
for characters
And not a nomination for characters, but like a wish list that a lot because i'll be very honest
The last time we did a rumble typically they would happen once every
Seven or eight months once every like once a year because it's been so long
It's been almost a year and a half or so since the last one right at least
13 14 15 months
There's a lot of characters
There's a lot of people that have been on streams and little jokes that have been made tons of them and
It's been a long time since the last rumble
So what i'm probably going to do
Is once it gets closer to the boston marathon we can actually really lock that all in and that it's
We're hopefully back to normal by september or at least somewhat normal normal enough to do the marathon
I guess i'm saying open up a wish list where on the discord or something
We'll have a channel where we'll just make a big list and then from that list
But potentially I will go through and pick out characters that I think I would like to make
Or we can even pick them ourselves on stream
But I don't think I want to do that with everybody because I think some of the fun at least for me is making characters
You don't know that are going to show up
So you guys knowing all the entrants to me in all the matches I think is I don't really like that
As much as I could so maybe at least a wish list and then
Maybe at least bring in five to ten people that chat really wanted and then i'll just make the rest
That's kind of the idea but thanks for the five dollars
And take care of yourself being an essential worker right now is very stressful. I can imagine thanks to the five bucks
Five dollars from tj the duke. Thanks for the five bucks
I used to watch your old tf2 vids back in 2012 to 14 got me through some tough times
That has recently looked you up for some nostalgia and it's good to see you're still doing your thing
Yeah, we're still going not playing really team fortress anymore, but still going still just hanging out
Trying to have a good time a few days a week. I see no reason to stop
Thanks to five bucks and welcome back killcon. Thanks for five dollars german
Did you know that plants while plants do not have nerves?
They have calcium gated networks that use glutamate to propagate information across their bodies
We've observed that this system is functionally identical to a nervous system and plants not only sense things
But also learn it's an entire rabbit hole of mounting evidence
In support of plant cognition where plants are as aware and intelligent as animals. Isn't that just quacking crazy?
What are your thoughts on that?
Uh, they terrified me. That's the scariest thing i've ever heard because if plants can become
Completely sentient and we're all fucking we're dead. That's terrifying
Imagine if the trees got sentient if they didn't want what if they didn't like us they would come up
They'd find some like fucking toxin they'd find. Oh, this is um, that's uh
Yeah, that happened today. Uh, I think that's a thing that happened piece of fiction
anyways, um
That was
Shit
No, don't listen to anything. I'm saying just blah blah blah blah. Look at me. You're super stupid
He's going off on a crazy rant again, and he's crazy
Um, yeah, that's scary though weird thought thanks four to five for the three dollars
No message just three bucks volemy five dollars on top of
Uh, fucking fifty dollars
Let me get five thousand bits earlier
This is 55 total dollars tonight from volemy germa. You scanned me out of a link
so I demand that you play the
You've been known video to make up for it band links. That's all you get
Hey atlantius. Thanks for the thousand bits since classes are online
We have to type out responses from math
One of the answers was negative two and I immediately thought the teacher made a bad joke and laughed way too hard about it
Thanks for making our lives a little happier. Even when you're not there
Oh god
Minus two
That's funny
Well, that makes me happy. I'm glad to hear that the stream can permeate
into other places in your life
Hopefully in a good way and not in a bad way. I hope nobody actually is
What do you say say something really bad from this stream?
We're having fun. All right. Hey genie boy. Thanks for the 250 germa
This is my second time watching your stream last one was yesterday
Hey, what do you think?
thoughts
Let's hear him. I've been watching the videos for a little over a year. Okay. All right
So you're you're fairly new
I just want to say that your videos and now streams are giving me so much joy and have helped me through some dark times
I just got my tax return yesterday. So i'm excited to support you in these crazy times peace and love
Thanks for the 250 really hope that you take care of yourself
Most importantly you got your uh tax return
Take care of yourself. Make sure you're taken care of
Be very very low down on that list
And if you get there
All right, i'll gladly take it
Thanks a lot
And welcome to the streams
video watcher
Thanks a lot genie boy plop one down. Thanks for three dollars. They say thanks man. Thank you
Get the credits on the screen. Let's roll them
Seven and a half hours. I told you this was never going to happen ever again. And how long did that last?
uh
Um a week
Yeah, this this was never this was never supposed to happen ever again
I actually said that was it was never gonna happen again. I said there'll never be a stream more than six hours ever again
I was wrong
But well, hold on this
Okay, hear me out on this
the reason why this wasn't like a four to five hour stream today
is because
At around the four to five hour mark on the stream. I realized
I probably only have another hour or so left in hulk
Am I just gonna
Stop the stream and not finish this game
Right, so it's okay. I did say that there was never going to be a stream again more than five or six hours
But there are some exceptions
Like wanting to complete a game that I know I can complete in less than six to seven hours. There's some exceptions
That won't always happen though. But thanks again everybody for subbing. It means a lot. Thank you. Thanks for giving me money
Thanks for paying me money
Thanks a million times
Immortal draculich, thanks to the five dollars germa. Do you have any interest in playing the prototype series?
They're also by radical. They have a very similar feel to ultimate destruction
Yeah, I actually tried to play prototype a long time ago
And it didn't work. I couldn't get it to work. So i'd probably just get it for xbox
And do that or xbox 360 or something eventually we'll go back to it knife boy. Thanks for three dollars. Do a hulk impression
Thanks to the three bucks
Hey bug smoke. Thanks for five dollars germa toontown rewritten supports over a thousand players
And the servers have player limits specifically so that people don't overload and crash servers
Be a really cool game to see you stream really i'll see if I can get it to work. I'll try i'll try it
I'll give it a look
I can get it set up and get ready and do it by tomorrow then whatever what i'll try it
Thanks for the five dollars bug smoke and for the good tip
Mostly lost. Thanks for 250 put a one in chat. If you haven't seen manos the hands of fate. Well, this is also
There's also a lot of liars here
Seeing at least one liar
Me, no
All right, but but for for trial period
I want to watch something that I haven't seen and that a lot of people haven't seen a lot of people have seen manos the hands
Of fate, let's just be honest
I know that people think it's hilarious and people really like it. It's such a bad bad shitty public domain move
Right. Everyone says that
But a lot of people have seen it not a whole by comp by contrast
Shit little people haven't seen
The gorilla i've just given you statements that are accurate
funny monkey
We'll see how funny
Thanks to the 250 and thank you sir canaan for the 250. I can't wait to see purple hulk in revenger's end war
The forever glove is pretty cool, too
Um for some reason I thought I thought this was just an absolute gibberish sentence
I can't wait to see purple hulk in revenger's end war. The forever glove is pretty cool
Wait, is it? Oh it is it's like a joke
Right, like the infinity gauntlet
The avengers. Okay, it is. I don't know they they name so much weird shit these days
Like ultimate zombie avengers. I don't know
All right. It's a joke. Okay
Hey, mitchell. Thanks for 20 dollars mitchell
2000 bits
Thanks for the 20 bucks. Thanks for playing a hulk ultimate destruction germa. Glad you enjoyed it ridiculous as it can get
I played it too alongside the stream and the completion time difference may have been double digits, but I really enjoyed watching you play
Double digits as in like, you know, that's 30 seconds. That's that could be 10 seconds
So you beat the game 12 seconds faster than I did
All right double digits faster if toontown does not end up being a game for tomorrow
Uh, if it does end up being it it'll be a blast take care and have a great night, man
I'll try i'm gonna give it a real try. Thanks for the 20 dollars. And yeah, the game was fun. It was hilarious
Uh, thank you cubite for the three dollars. I sampled the gorilla for my lo-fi hip-hop ep you uncultured swine
All right. Well, we haven't seen it. I haven't seen it
All right, you are like one of five people that have seen that movie here. Hey blackout. Thanks for the three dollars
uh
Joey zio and at toontown are their twitterers with the head dev in the server the server capacity is 10,000
And originally had 4,000 active users
Him the tat man with 12,000 viewers was able to stream the game. So you should be able to go tomorrow. Okay. Well, all right
All right. Yeah. All right. I I I was under the assumption that it was like an old
Like pieced together project that maybe like a few hundred to a thousand people could do. I didn't I don't know
Is that popular? I don't know. Is that popular?
You can help with any configs
Well tomorrow around like three o'clock
I'll be here
Getting ready. So if there's something wrong
3 p.m pacific, by the way
I'll try to over that like from like 230 to like 330 is when i'm going to try to figure this all out
if there's any problems or any configuration issues, then uh, absolutely we'll ask in the chat, but
No, I mean if if somebody like tim the tat man can do it and not crash the server then we should be fine
Yeah, that's because I have
More less than half of the those numbers. So that should be fine
Guillotine senpai, thanks for the 250 new emote promise. It's not bernie pog and it's uh, oh they got the link got removed
All right. All links are banned. I forgot. Hey, i'm sorry. Thank you for the 250 though
Barry pk thanks for the five dollars combine the shark tank stream with the webcam stream then get them to film interview ask answers
Get them to film interview answers and have your responses at different angles. Just food for thought
I want to get those gears turning bernie pog
No, we're not we're not making bernie pog a thing
Get rid of the bernie pog thing in your head. We're not doing bernie pog
I've is no we're not doing that. Thanks for the five dollars door farine. Thanks for five dollars
Hey bub, I would like to request my favorite character for the rumble door farine the wolverine door
uh ask uh
Ask visceral concepts to make a game. That's fun. We'll see if that's possible
Thanks for five dollars. Thank you, sir canine for 250 chat
Not realizing the minus and plus twos actually affect germa's life span hunker s
Kind of scary if you think about it. Hey genie boy again. Thanks for 250. The stream was great
Also bugleberry for rumble, please
You should play lego star wars the complete saga a bugleberry was in the last rumble and he
Actually lasted a pretty long time. I'm sure he'll be back. He's a staple of this entire stream
Now he will definitely be a participant without a doubt in my mind. There isn't evil four. I plan on it
Slom.com. Thanks for three dollars. Hey germa eight year viewer first time bitgiver. Love your work
I'd love a good old happy birthday. Happy birthday slom.com. Thanks for being around for that long. That's eight years
That's a lot. That's almost a decade. That's almost 10 years. The 10 year anniversary is actually coming up sooner than a lot of people think
june
2011 was when the stream when the videos the channel started
So if june 2011 was the first video then june 2021
Is 10 years that's a 10 year anniversary stream from inside of a cake
We'll see what I do for 10 years, but thanks for the three bucks and thanks for sticking around and that is the end
I'll see you guys tomorrow for maybe toontown
Reloaded if toontown doesn't work, then we'll figure something else out tomorrow is going to be where I am going to follow my rules
For tomorrow, we're going back to like the rules which are like four to six hours
I just wanted to finish the hulk right at the very end. We had 250 from goo berry juice. Thanks goo berry juice
Hola, gerbacola. I really need to talk to you about this voice you do but the actual it's a band link
What the actual fuck is it supposed to be dude?
I see people in chat calling it double d from ed ed netty impression
But that shit sounds exactly like cow from cow and chicken sounds nothing like ed
And there's no way you watched cow and chicken as a kid. No one did so what's the deal with that voice?
um just run
Hold on like it's been that's been almost seven and a half hours
I can't do it cow and chicken was an amazing show charlie adler is is a legend
Charlie adler did every fucking voice on that show
Did you know that?
Charlie adler did red butt guy cow
And chicken now you have to be the top of your game to be able to do something like that
Uh charlie adler is one of those inspirations. It's like
Probably like in top five like how it inspired everything that I do
I love charlie adler's characters charlie adler when he goes like this and he's able to care
Like nobody can do it. It's only only charlie can do that. I'm speaking like only charlie, you know my buddy charlie. No charlie adler
is
um ikis from our real monsters
He's he's
Ed big head
Uh, he's so good. I don't know how much uh work he's doing now
man
That guy modeled pretty much the whole way that I speak
jim carrey charlie adler
and um
My dad. Yeah, my dad
charlie adler jim carrey
um
who else bernie sanders
larry david
Larry probably larry david. I'm such a huge larry david fan
I would turn green if larry david walked in my room
I mean if I was at a convention and larry david was there and he's like, oh you want me to sign something
You i'd be like hi
I would just turn fucking green and be like
larry hi
I'm my seromy
I would it would be he's like my idol. He's like the I think he's the funniest person on earth
Anyways, don't put losers in the rumble, please. Wait, what?
Oh, you mean like the people that actually lost the rumble uh for a second
I was like, wait, I thought you're talking about larry david
I was like what the fuck did that what did you just say?
You mean like actually physically people that didn't people that lost
No, they have we have to have all right if if like john cena gets eliminated
As number 10
He's gonna be in the next run. That's like john cena. Nice job you
You know, you're one of the most popular people in the wwe, but sorry
You never get to be in another rumble ever again. You sit these ones out
No, you do like
five to ten
People that were in previous rumbles. They're the people that I really like characters
I think are really fun and interesting and then you do like 10 to 20 new ones
And then some people don't even participate in the rumble
It's probably like five to ten new characters that show up just in the matches beforehand
I really like that system
And finally the buzzer for real dough. Thanks for 250 germa. Wait, I got a link to some possible fixes for prototype
Is there a mod I can pass the link on so they can give it to you?
Yeah, give it to one of the mods if not, it's I probably will
Honestly, let me just we'll we'll we'll say this right now. I'll probably just get it for xbox 360 if it exists for it
Some of these old games are just so finicky and by old
Anything more than eight to twelve years old just it can be such a pain in the ass if it's on a console
I just have to put the disk in and it just works and it won't
Crap well this game crashed like three times this game had like two bugs and hard crashed. This is a disk
Thank you for forgiving me. Jeremy. Did I?
I'm that person up for 30 minutes. I can't like I can't like choke on water right now and spit it up
Guys, don't you understand the joke? The stream is about to turn off in like 30 seconds
I don't hold grudges, but welcome back and that's it. I'll see you tomorrow
have a
Wonderful wonderful rest of your night
Of course, I forgive them. Of course. I forgive you. I did just just
Just put the brakes on a little okay
Just put the brakes on
Hey gooberry juice. Thanks for 250 with the kappa face. Thanks for the 250. We'll see you tomorrow. Good night. Goodbye
See you around four o'clock tomorrow afternoon. Maybe for toontown reloaded