Hey everybody. We're gonna try a test. We're gonna try to do it again. Who knows if this
is gonna be functional or not, but I am, you know, I'm willing to give it a try.
All you can do is try. You guys having a good day? What is today? I've lost all track of time
has been deleted. What is today? Thursday, November 1st. He's, he's, there he is. He's
Well, it never really went anywhere, but we've, we've had some solid green
over the last 24 hours. So I figured I would try because we've been dealing with, obviously
Cox has been trying to get infrastructurally these problems fixed. And this is the first
time in probably two and a half weeks where we've had internet for more than like four
hours straight. So we're green for the moment. Let's see how, this could be 45 minutes or this
could be six hours. I don't know. I'm willing to give it an attempt though. And well,
we will update some information about the green screen stream. So you're gonna have to
stick around for that. There's some updated info. Here comes a 30 minute stream. All right,
give me, give me one second. Also funnily enough, there was, I turned on the PS4
because this is where I was Red Dead 2. And I don't know. I think the, the PS4 must
have gone into rest mode because we're at the same screen I was at like four and a half
days ago. So we're just here. I don't really remember what I was doing, but I know that I
exist here. I got to remember the controls too. This is gonna be fucking hard. Even the game was
waiting. Yeah. It's like nothing ever happened. You guys just woke up. We all just woke up.
And we're here four days later. We got 50, 50 bucks right off the bat from Pocket Pauling.
Thanks for the $50 Pocket Pauling. Finally, my dad is back from the war. Hey, Jerma,
how sad, relieved are you that you missed the Red Sox parade? Oh yeah, the Red Sox won
the World Series. That's right. That happened. What else has happened in the time that I haven't
been awake? I mean streaming, you know, Red Sox won the World Series. Super Smash Brothers
is coming out and they did a direct today. And excuse me. Excuse me. Where's my favorite
fucking character? Excuse me. Plant? Oh, I thought you guys were calling me a plant.
Well, I don't want to give any spoilers for people that haven't watched the direct,
but I'm missing somebody real important there, I think. Jerma's a plant. That's right. I'm
working. I'm working for him. Minecraft Steve. No, no way. What do you mean I wouldn't let
that happen? I don't work for Nintendo. No, I would never let that happen. This is not like
me playing Red Dead right now. What am I talking about? I would like I would talk to somebody.
Oh my fucking Jesus. Hold on. Thank you. Thank you. Jabba dab for your 10 community sub.
Thanks a lot, man. Thanks. Also, by the way, pocket Pauling. We didn't really touch upon your
$50 here. Like for real, thank you so much. Pocket Pauling for your 50 bucks and jabba
dab for your 10 community subs. And I think we I think we can go. You know what I'm
saying? I think we can just go. I got it. How do you ride the horse? I forget. Here we go.
What was I doing? Okay, I'm back in it. Is it x? I forget how to play. Do you just I just
woke up from a fucking dream. Okay, stalling. I don't remember how to shoot. I was in the
middle of the tutorial and I went into cryogenic sleep to get the train. You want to
head down? See how he's getting on? Okay. No, I remember. Okay, but I'm getting some
memories. Check on Bill. That's a gun. Okay. How do I take out the
doctor binocular? What was benign? Was there a binocular button? Do I do I go? Am I going
down? You know, I have to leave. I'm holding a knife. L one and R one. There we go. Okay.
Let's check on Bill. How's he doing? All right, put him up. Get on the horse.
This is I didn't even get to fucking do this. It's been four and a half days.
No, god damn it. Okay, zoom. Where are you, Bill? This is this what I'm supposed to be doing.
Guys, give me a break. There he is. Okay. Where's he on the hill?
Okay, there he is. All right, spotted. I gotta I gotta move my horse out of here.
Set up the detonator by those rocks over there. Okay, sure. Now just unspool the wire and then
attach it to said detonator. I'm going to explode here. Pick up the spool.
I'm gonna I'm gonna like acme this guy. You're about to get wily coyote.
How much slack do we have? All right, here we go. Attach it.
This is attach the thing mini game or what? Okay. Okay. All right. Now stomp on detonator.
What if I just jump on this? Imagine if it just fucking blew up.
All right, I'm going. I'm going. I'm going. Put the horse on the tracks. I just got this
horse. Why would I do something like that? I just bought the horse. All right, so I
have to detonate it. So I blow up the train. He says all fine. We'll soon find out.
Put yourself on the tracks. I think so. Okay, cover your faces. Train should be here any
minute now. Weapon wheel. So now we're looking for the detonator. The light.
I thought I had to like throw the fuse. It's not radio controlled.
Gentlemen, it's time. Good luck. All of you. You all know what to do.
I don't know. I actually don't because I saw the first part of this mission and story
almost four and a half, five days ago. Here we go. All right, that just didn't work.
Why are we getting off the horses? Wait, why would we get off the horse?
Jump on the train. How am I supposed to do that from here?
Okay, I've made it. Oh, running a train. All right, give me a Lenin. Pull, pull him.
Wait, oh, did he fall or did I fall?
Come on, this is what it's supposed to be doing, right? What? What am I doing?
Okay, I think I figured out what I'm supposed to do. What's the uh, okay.
All right, let's go. Stop the train. It's not TNT barrels here, right?
I like the repeater. I was going for a tackle. All right, quick. I got to need something.
Give me some cover. Wait, wait, no, we gotta go. What the fuck?
I just got hit in the face with a shovel. Reverse the grapple.
Is this Abe Lincoln? All right, give it the front of the engine car.
There's more. Right in the face. I have dead eye, so I don't know why I'm not using it
for some reason. What's the reload button?
Can I get like an ammo toss to me? That's it, right?
That guy. I need to pick up stuff on the ground. Down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down.
Is that a person in the back? Is that an animal? That's a person. Oh shit. Oh shit. Get behind
this little fucking slab. Wait, this is our guys? Oh, these are our guys. All right. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I need to. It's a rock. It's a slab. That's a slab. Okay.
Assume yellow tonic to fortify your bars. A fortified bar can be used for a short period
without draining. This tonic will fortify your dead eye. Listen to me. Okay. We don't want to
kill any of you. Any more of you. I give you my word, but trust me, we will. Boys,
okay. You asked for it. Five, three, two, one. Seems our friends have gone deaf.
I don't, I don't know what the, what the world war two plane sound was coming from outside.
Are we going? I can't rapid fire this time. Mr. Williamson, give Mr. Morgan and Mr. Smith
some dynamite. You two boys go blow that door open. Why don't we do that? Thanks bill.
Much to us, but you boys in there might want to take a step back.
Place dynamite. Seems good enough. All right. Here we go. Like the views. Here we go.
All right. Now step back. Unless you got a death wish. I'd step back, fellas. Yeah,
I did this. I did this. All right. Now go in and just start firing.
Blind him. Get on up and search that train. What's the punch button? I want to punch. It's
all right. Let's search the damn train. Look at this place. It's like a, it's beautiful in here.
You two got the safe. I'll search the rest. Oh yes. Should be easy as cake.
If I'm going to hide something, I would hide it inside the lamp.
Shut up. Me and Arthur did all the work. Yeah, kid did good. Didn't see you rushing to jump on
that train. He's king. I'll give you that. On receipt of funds, we proceed with phases two
and three of the project and present you with a detailed report of our findings within
the month. Yours, respectively. Okay, let's see if we can get this open. Now that wasn't part
of it. Getting there. What's in there? Cigars? I can't carry any more of this item. I need
to sell some shit then. Any codes? No, no codes. You can screenshot that and read it later if you
want. All right, there's brandy. I'm going to need to do something eventually here, food wise.
Can't carry any more of this item. Why not?
Can somebody else hold something? Money? That's money. Those are IOUs. No, it tells you. Bond.
Is it really a lockbox if it's unlocked? That's true.
What did you find? These. They worth anything? Oh, sure. Bearer bonds. I think we could probably
sell these pretty easily. Oh, wait, is that Ethereum? Well done. Now would you get rid of
all of this? The train? Yeah, get it out of here. What about them? What do you think?
I don't know. It's up to you. Kill them, leave them here. Take them with you on the
train. Wait, I get temporary party members? Okay. See you back at camp. What do I do
about these three? We'll be moving on. The rest are you. Let's ride. What do I do with my temporary
party? Guard. Deal with the guards. Can I pick who I threaten? Okay. Get on the train. Quick.
Wait, I gotta get you too. Oh, hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey. What's going on? What happened?
Why did that? What? What's with the boundaries? Why are the boundaries here?
Somebody gave 100 bucks. Mega Mube just gave 100 dollars. Thank you so much, dude. I haven't been
able to watch your stream very much recently, but still love every second of the VODs.
Hope this helps a little with settling into the new place. Thank you. Thank you so much,
Mega Mube. Well, you haven't been able to watch very much recently. I haven't really
been able to stream very much recently. So all right, so let's do this the actual way I'm
supposed to do it. Okay. Get on the train. Quick. All of you. Any bright ideas? I kill all three.
Yeah. Oh, I don't have, I don't have anything else. Well, I want this instead. Get on the train.
I hear so much as a footstep from this car. You'll end up like all your friends out here.
I have honor level? I told you to get on the train. Look, all you had, I'm not,
if you follow instructions, you're gonna be fine. How do I take, I need to go to the engine car?
What do they leave? What if they run away? I'm supposed to leave them back here? I don't know
if I want to do that. No, I'm not gonna, these guys listen. These guys follow directions.
Can I climb? What, what's going on? What was that? Okay. My horse is fine. How do I know
that they're gonna stay? If I'm that guy, I'm just gonna walk off the train right now.
No way to be found. They are running. What are you talking about? They're running.
No, that, where? No, they're not. They're gonna remember this. That's fine. I want them to.
One person said that. It doesn't matter how many people say it. Let's get this thing moving.
Why don't I stay on the train? If I'm one of these guys, I'm gonna lean out the window
and be like, sucker. I would throw a rock out the window at him. As you're gonna get,
you can catch the train. There's a bunch of heavy books in there. I'd whip a book
at him and try to hit him right in the head as hard as I could. I'd probably miss.
You ever try to throw something as hard as you can at something and you just,
you weigh off. That's what happens every time we get out of this hole. We're going to try
whether it seems stable. And we just robbed the Leviticus Cornwall train.
We got money. It's the worst is behind us gentlemen. I'm an outlaw. I know this country
a little tuck them into bed camp in horseshoe overlook near Valentine. We'll be able to
hide out there. No problem. As long as we keep our noses clean. Well, then let's go
clean noses and everything else. Arthur, you're in that one. I know you two like to talk about
the good old days and what's gone wrong with old Dutch tuck them in. Nice. Well, that's a nice
icy waterfall. I'm glad we're getting to the title screen song with lyrics because
that's definitely where we are. This just sounds like somebody that's a karaoke
and they don't know the lyrics to the song for a whole portion. And then she's
going to sing the chorus. I don't even know the fucking chorus. Wow. Get over here. Yes, boss.
You two ride up ahead. Make sure there's no surprises. We've had enough of those.
Me with the boy. Come on, kid. You can buy me a whiskey. That sounds pretty good.
No, it's too easy. That's too easy. It's too easy to dump them during the song.
It's too easy.
Oh, I thought the horse went through the earth. Hey, hey, go. Oh,
I thought that the horse went all the way through. That was a preemptive.
I'm laughing. What the fuck? How do we lose a wheel?
So what's supposed to happen?
Hey, Charles, you and me hold the thing up while you try and put the wheel back on that.
Okay, lift it up. I'm playing house slipper again. That's all it takes. Oh yeah,
this is back in like the 1100s, right? The wheel was just invented.
Of course they're going to have technical problems with it.
You think? Trouble? Uh oh. We wouldn't have seen them.
We're bastards. We really screwed them over down here. Come on, let's not push our luck.
What happened? Well, get in. I'll tell you.
Here comes the whole story. Back to the wagon.
You can switch between different radar sizes in the compass by holding that.
Yeah, expand. No, no, no. Regular is fine.
I'll keep it on regular. That's fine. The Indians in these parts got sold a very raw deal.
This is the heartland we're going to. Good farming and grazing country.
We're just browsing around right now. We can take our time here.
Every blade of grass killed or heard it up to the reservations in the middle of nowhere.
There we go. This is more scenic. Kangaroo, kangaroo, get the kangaroo.
It's a four-legged kangaroo. How do I take out my gun?
Hey.
Don't mean he knows a damn thing about what he's talking about.
I'm trying. I'm just going regular speed.
So what happened to your trap?
I don't even know. It's not that I can remember.
My father was a cousin. Yes, the southern kangaroo.
He told me he lived with our people for a while. A number of freemen did.
Moved from our land. Three of us fled.
You got to know a family of like four is going to drive by then.
They're all going to turn their heads and go, oh, no.
Some soldiers captured my mother.
Took her somewhere. We never saw her again.
We drifted around. He was a very sad man.
Where clothes appropriate. I'm 13. I just took off on my own.
I was about the age we found young Arthur here.
Maybe a little older. A delinquent you never did see.
But he learned fast.
I was fast as Marston, apparently.
Wait, I don't understand. What's the problem between you two?
Nice shot. Yeah, it's a long story.
Do a flip with the carriage.
We still heading the right way.
That depends. Are we still heading west in search of fortune
and repose in virgin forests as we plan?
No. Are we heading in the correct direction
on our desperate escape from the law eastwards down the mountain?
We're going the right way still.
Yes, I believe so. You know this area?
A little. I've been through a couple of times.
There's a livestock town not too far from here called Valentine.
Cowboys, outlaws, working girls, power kind of place.
Is this boring? Hey, we're doing the tutorial, man.
We're just trying to enjoy the game.
In this place we're going.
Wait, what's it called again?
Horseshoe Overlook.
I don't think I can even control this.
It's a good place to lie low.
It'll do for now.
I can't go anywhere because I'm straight.
How long do you think Dutch is really going to lie?
It's just, you know, maybe it's me who's changed, not him,
but we kept telling him that fairy job didn't feel right.
You and me had a real lead in Blackwater that could have worked out.
It just isn't like Dutch to lose his head like that.
When do we fight the wild west orcs?
What? This isn't like Skyrim.
Dutch, abandon this line.
We're still here, so I figure we must have got a ride to hell.
Who's eating?
Just some yarrow and ginseng.
Good for the health.
Better than that stuff you buy in the store.
Yeah, you can have all this.
I'm at the point where I can do it with my eyes closed.
Why don't you just wish sometimes that you could just eat this and be fine?
Eating sometimes is just a pain in the ass, don't you guys think?
I mean, I love food, but they're going to be annoying.
It's something you have to do.
It's like sleeping.
Think about your entire day.
Like 60% of your whole day is eating and sleeping.
Come on, man.
Like, where's the science there?
Let's go.
Oh, boy, this discussion again.
So just stop eating.
What's the big deal?
Okay.
Wait, what does it want to do?
Oh, stop the wagon.
Turn and stop.
Stop.
Do I have to back it up?
All right, back up.
Where is he?
He's right around this rock.
Telephone's ringing.
All right.
There he is over here, right?
Where is he?
Oh, my God.
Wasn't he right here?
Look at the map.
I mean, yeah, but wait, wait, wait.
Oh, there he is.
He got stuck in my shit, so he started walking.
All right, get on.
Can I beep?
Run him over.
No, I have to be like at least a decent person.
All right, get on.
Get on.
Where's the beep?
How do I peep at this guy?
Wait, did he disappear?
All right, we made it.
Home sweet home.
There we are.
Good thing that you made it.
He made it before we did.
I've never seen somebody fuck this section up.
Well, have you ever seen somebody do that whole section in cinematic mode?
Now you have it, now you have it, now you have it, now you have it, now you have it, now you have it.
I ain't got that long, Dutch.
I want folks safe before I go.
Me too.
And now we are stuck east of the Gritsleys and out of money
and a long way from our dream of virgin land in the west.
I know, my brother, but we are safe.
We make a bit of money here.
Then we move again, head out around the west of Uncle Sam.
That's really hard to do.
Buy some land.
I hope so.
Would you just look around you?
This world has its consolations.
Gentlemen, I'm going to head into the local town
and, you know, see if I can strike up a little business.
Of course, Herr Strauss.
I prefer robbing banks to usury.
Seems more dignified somehow.
Now, everyone, put your tools down for a moment.
Come on, gather round.
Quickly now.
We're gonna need a speech.
I know that things have been tough.
Frio coming in with five community subs.
Thanks a lot, man.
So it is time for everyone to get to work.
Get to work, but stay out of trouble.
Remember, we are itinerant workers.
Laid off when they shut down our factory to the north.
Now get out there and see what you can find.
Uncle, Reverend Swanson, no more passengers.
It is time for everyone to earn their keep.
There is a town a little way down the track name of Valentine.
Can you play?
I'm playing the game.
I've stopped down all mard and morons, if I remember right.
This is the game.
That seems a decent place to start.
And we need food, real food.
That means every day, one of you.
Now remember, whatever it is that you find.
It looks like it's from a different game
that somebody created and put them in here like a mod.
Gets, gets, slice.
Now be sensible out there.
Now the girls have your tent ready, Mr. Morgan.
Come with me.
So we have a donation box.
We put you over here.
I'm sure everything will be fine, Miss Grimshaw.
It should be.
Most of your stuff from Blackwater got saved.
Everything apart from my money.
Oh, don't remind me.
Well, we can always make more money.
We're going to have to.
Miss Jackson, I've seen shit with more common sense.
Sleep shame or change clothes at your tent.
Burz, I don't know why for a second.
I thought he was going to burn his clothes.
I'm done with these.
I think I'm going to get rid of them.
Horseshoe Overlook, chapter two.
That was chapter one.
How many chapters are there?
That's not how you guys change clothes.
What did they do before?
No, never mind.
That's a stupid thing to say.
What did they do before?
Laundry.
They just left this clothes on.
You rinsed it in a stream.
Dutch seems a little better.
His eyes are sparkling once more.
Funny guys, funny number joke.
I think we all feel a little happier.
So this is a few weeks later.
Despite of Blackwater and that.
Jose.
Quite a day.
Eat, drink, play.
Let's hope so.
At Dave and Busters.
There's a bunch of the boys already in Valentine.
You've got to maintain your course, don't you?
Half price Wednesdays.
Oh, by the way, half price is actually what it should be every day
because it's like four dollars to play one game here.
Don't come here.
What are you saying?
You guys don't have, you don't, you never played,
you went to Dave and Busters?
Cam, camera.
Your games can't be shown by a symbol on the map.
Eagle talent, talisman.
Okay, so your beard is getting long.
You can use the shaving kit beside your tent
or visit a barbershop to maintain your facial hair.
Nothing at all.
For the first time in weeks, nothing.
We're free.
Okay, there's lots of details here.
Hold on.
So you got permanently increases the time
that eagle eye can stay active for five seconds.
Crafted from rare legendary animal parts.
Permanently decreases the damage the player receives
while on horseback by 10 percent.
Okay, that's interesting.
You can make little charms.
A hundred and seventy eight animals.
What?
There were like four in the last game.
Deer, bear, coyote, and like rabbit, right?
Six gangs, 30 fish, 74 pieces of equipment.
This seems huge.
Hey, I discovered the deer and the bears.
Where's the bear?
How have I not discovered the bear?
I literally shot him in the face with an arrow.
It's easy to track them.
Okay, I see.
All right.
Bring Pearson animals to supply the camp.
He can use the meat for food and skins to craft satchels
with increased capacity.
All right, there's a lot going on.
Let me take a look.
Let me, I don't care what that guy has to say right now.
Let's like, let's do some shaving.
Now, is this like, is this like the,
you guys remember,
no one's gonna know what I'm talking about here.
The magnet face thing where you have the magnet hair
on the guy's face.
It was like a 14 cent toy.
Length.
Oh, you actually can do this.
Hold on, chin.
Oh, I think I doesn't want a dirty chin.
I don't know.
What do you think?
Just gigantic chops?
Hmm.
No, I just want the piece of hair for my chin
to go down as far as it can go.
Yeah.
I'm gonna look like an Amish guy.
Can I dye my whole like face purple and my beard purple?
Yeah, that's good.
Okay.
I like it like this so far.
I'm gonna keep that going as long as it can go.
The current stock levels are shown when near the tithing box.
All right, let's take a look.
Now, that's perfectly balanced facial hair.
Here's something to make a stew.
You can eat from the pot.
I'm getting a lot of info here.
Uh-huh.
They demanded to know.
It's like lore in case you want to see it.
Let me just like take it in for a second here
because here's the donation box.
How much should I, how much money should I give?
Contribute.
How much can I contribute if I don't give money?
Okay.
I did my, somebody's, somebody's slurping out of a big gulp.
What the hell was that?
It was a radio.
I thought somebody said like a giant soda.
Let's keep looking around.
Hold on.
Food, I want to get, let me eat some stew.
Yeah, that's less, that's less than a hundred bits.
I ain't gonna read it.
It's a stew.
What kind of stew is it?
It's not, is it not done?
I want some of that.
How do I get some of that?
Oh, okay.
I have to take, I have to actually pick the bowl up.
This is the one, two parts here.
I only get to eat once every few days.
I can just walk around and talk while eating.
All right, this is pretty cool.
All right, this is good.
Can I throw it like, like acid?
Can I throw it in somebody's face?
How do I, I want to talk.
All right, I'm gonna sit here.
Am I allowed at this part, at the lunch table?
What the fuck?
Nobody wants to talk to me.
I can't sit with the cool kids at the lunch table.
Hey, no, I wasn't done with that.
Sit back down and eat the rest of that.
Okay, I can talk.
That was a, that was as shitty as a conversation as what's the weather like.
In this, look at that weather, huh?
I only get to eat once every three days and I'm gonna leave half my plate.
What am I at?
The olive garden?
Okay, what's over here?
Oh, this guy, this is the guy shaving the turkey.
Crafting upgrades, donate.
Look, I'll give you some meat so we get a feather.
Here, you can have, you can have a, you can have a bird feather.
I'm getting money here.
Donate all, donate for provisions.
I think I want to do that.
Donated, springy meat, donated.
I'm just gonna give it to him.
This is fish meat.
Two pieces of meat and we got some venison here.
Can I like cook on the, I'm just gonna give them all.
Just take it all.
Don't say like I never gave you nothing.
Just take it.
Oh shit, okay, hold on.
Can I not give these?
All right, so crafting upgrades.
Let's see what I can do here.
Okay, so craft satchel, increase carrying capacity.
Tonic satchel, I can't do any of these.
Oh god damn it.
I need like person, fusion cannot craft this yet.
I can't craft any of these.
Okay, so I need to purchase leather working tools
and upgrade the medicine wagon twice.
I got so much work to do.
There's a lot of work here.
I can make my own house.
I need one perfect ram carcass.
Cleaned up ram skull to be displayed at your tent.
Drugs, I don't have anything.
Upgrade the main camp's campfire.
I don't have any of this shit.
I need to like play the game first.
All right, well, thanks for the money.
What about you?
Morning, Mr. Morgan.
There's a guy over here.
What do the exclamation points mean?
Oh, these are provisions or something, right?
Can I like, I can take certain amount of provisions every day?
I'm assuming they're not grayed out.
Right, that would make sense, wouldn't it?
Needs to be restocked.
Okay, well, I'm just gonna go.
Let's do a mission.
Where's my horse?
Do the mission, do the mission.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
How are we doing on our stamina?
You can command your horse to stay,
flee, or follow by focusing on it with the L2 when it's nearby.
Yes, I'm on it currently.
All right, so we got G, E, U, or R, S.
We're gonna go towards G, E.
Galloping horses cause stamina drain.
Hold on, wait, wait, wait.
173 bullets, 41, 173.
Okay, I have ammo, so I'm just gonna go.
Hold X to maintain the horse's canter and quench some stamina.
Sounds good.
The world has opened up now.
We're going to the first mission.
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait, an animal.
An animal I can take and bring back to the, to the, what is it?
It's a turkey.
Study the turkey.
Where is it?
There it is.
Study it.
Can I talk to them?
How did you, I ran it over.
All right, let's go study them.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
Bird meat.
When you skin or pluck an animal, you take meat from the carcass
and you can cook and eat this meat at a campfire.
I, we need to take this back.
Can I like throw it at somebody?
No, that's a gun.
All right, we're gonna take this back.
All right, there's another one over here.
Where's the other turkey?
Pick up and examine.
So it's a random wild mushroom.
Parasol mushroom is a health herb.
It can be eaten to refill your health core
or be crafted to as bait.
What can I eat?
What do I eat?
This is dangerous.
I don't know why.
I don't think anyone should do this.
Oh, we're fine.
Okay, give me the other turkey.
This time, I'm not gonna skin this one.
I'm gonna bring this back to,
but I don't know what his name is.
Who's that?
Who's this guy?
You think I got a problem?
He ain't getting eaten one of these turkeys.
I'm guaranteeing you that.
How many turkeys can I put on one horse?
What?
I'm just messing with you.
I'm just messing with you, dude.
Hold on.
You can...
How do I rob him?
No, no, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, I didn't...
Just stop moving.
Where's it going?
GE?
That guy.
Wait, that guy might have something.
Oh, there's a witness.
The horse is the witness?
It's this guy.
Stop.
Hands up.
Get your hands in the air.
Stop.
Stop it.
I don't want to have to do this.
Stop.
Stop moving.
Come on now.
What do you have?
Hey.
All right, I got to get rid of this guy.
Is this like Hitman?
Do I have to like bury him somewhere?
He's sitting in the trees.
No more witnesses.
We're good.
What was he doing?
Oh, this way.
Okay.
You can't skin a person.
What are you talking about?
Wait, we're going this way.
No, you can't just rob and kill every person.
There are turkeys over here anyways,
and that's what we care about.
Where'd they go up here?
I don't see anybody.
No, they got away.
That's okay.
Study.
Wait, I can study sheep?
Hold binoculars while looking at them.
I don't understand.
Does that work?
I don't think it worked.
Go eat them?
What am I, the big bad wolf?
Okay, slow down.
No, I'll get in trouble here.
Animals attached to your horse will decompose.
Sell them before this happens.
Oh, shit.
I need to sell these.
Flies.
Study quick.
Come here.
No.
Got it.
All right.
Let's go.
That was a shot in the dark completely.
Made it.
I don't know how fast I can like full sprint over here though.
There we go.
We're good.
Hitch the horse.
Now we're at the general store.
No, I need the turkey.
Turkeys.
I need both.
I need a turkey.
Okay.
I got fresh turkeys here,
and I'm willing to sell it for a moderate price.
Bring that in here.
Go.
What?
Hey, what am I, what are you, what?
I'm trying to sell you a turkey, man.
Oh, don't do that.
I'll kick you out.
You can interact with the shopkeeper
by approaching the catalog.
What?
I just got kicked out for bringing a turkey.
Where's the butcher?
Pardon me.
God damn it.
Come here.
Let's go.
All right.
Here we go.
Hey, I got a, you can interact with the shopkeeper.
All right.
Let's go.
I'm going to throw it down on here.
I got some quality meat here.
All right.
I don't, I, I don't have to walk it over here.
Okay.
Sales of turkey meat.
Salted beef.
I'm going to keep that.
Turkey feathers.
50 cents.
That's not bad.
That's pretty good.
To sell a pelt stored on the back of your horse,
take your horse close to the butcher.
Oh, I got to get the horse.
All right.
Horse cargo.
What does he got on there?
Ooh, look at all this stuff.
I have so much shit here.
I got two championship pelts.
All right.
I don't think I can sell any of these.
Maybe I can time game.
I feel like I shouldn't sell these.
I'm probably going to need them.
All right.
Let's go find a Mr.
Mr.
G E.
Clips indicate optional stranger missions.
Speak to the stranger.
Question mark flip.
Do you see a dude?
I don't see one of them.
Do you see a question mark flip?
I don't see one.
All right.
Let's just go.
Let's find this guy.
I don't think he's in the store.
Probably down here.
I need to close.
Oh, no, I, I guess it is.
He's in this saloon.
The psycho in me just wants to like throw a chair in here.
But I know not yet.
Come here.
Come over here.
I want you to meet our friends.
Pleased to meet you.
Why, you're just a toughest mountain man.
Oh, you be quiet, Anastasia.
Anyone can tell this one is a pussy cat.
Exactly.
Yes, he's a pussy cat.
Ain't that so, Arthur?
Whatever you say.
How much you cost, anyway.
Ain't that a nice way to talk to a lady?
Oh, I didn't know I was talking to a lady.
Excuse me.
Well, I must say, you gotta find way with the women, amigo.
They're dandy and a charm.
What's in there?
Chocolate milk?
Oh, man, I dread to think about it.
Hey, you motherfucker.
Barroom brawl.
This is where it starts.
This is what you came for.
This is for me to get my ass kicked.
What do you got?
Oh, what's that?
You just got dodged?
How do I pick up a chair?
Come on, there's gonna be something I can do here.
Wait, who's that?
Who is that guy?
Uh-oh, here's the boss.
Uh-oh, a chair.
Can I rip off the gas line and just throw a match in here?
Nice.
Pick up.
No, I want the, I don't want the hat.
I want the chair.
Hello?
Oh, didn't even break the table.
Come on, man.
Let's go.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ear grab.
That's not cool.
Come on, he's bigger than me.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Scripted, scripted.
Scripted.
You blocked everything.
Uh-oh, I'm in trouble.
All right, am I missing something from the tutorial five days ago?
I never remember.
Am I, am I not doing something right here?
I think I'm, you hold the block.
You can dodge too, can't you?
Counter attack.
But so you, what, you hold square and then hit like left to right right before he swings, right?
Remember, I did the first half of this tutorial five days ago.
I haven't turned it on since.
Just pressing the direction while holding the block.
Save the goatee?
No.
I'm gonna knock shower for the rest of the game.
Can I stay like this forever?
Can I just be the guy that got slimed the whole game?
He's being held by some bounty hunters.
Trying to see how much money the government will pay them.
I know he's in Blackwater, but there's talk of them moving.
We'll get a second here.
I'm going to update you guys on the green screen.
Well, then we're dead men for sure.
Well, we've been live for about an hour.
There'll be bankertons all over the place.
But if he's alive, we've got to try.
Updates on how that's going to happen.
Yeah, of course.
It's you they want, Dutch.
Always is.
Charles, go find out what you can.
Carefully.
Josiah, take Javier.
Arthur, go get yourself cleaned up.
Join them when you're ready.
What about me?
Well, exactly.
What about you?
What does that mean?
Oh no, never mind.
Okay, so let's talk for a second.
So if you missed the stream.
Let me just put the camera on because we're here.
If you missed the stream from three or four days ago or so.
My plan was because we were having a bunch of internet problems and we still are.
It's not completely fixed yet.
So wait, is this my my desync here?
I might be.
Let me sync this up.
All right.
Come on out here thing.
There we go.
All right.
So because the beard's growing, I haven't had time to shave.
It should be good now.
But anyways, because of the internet problems, my plan was if we didn't get it back,
I was going to desperately try to get the green screen stream done like tomorrow.
But now that they're actually working on the infrastructural problems that were in this area,
I think I'll be able to stream now.
I don't quote me on that, but like I did just say it.
This has been green here for a while.
No drop frames.
It's looking all right for now.
So the green screen stream, if you don't know what I'm talking about,
I'm going to get in front of a green screen for like an hour or two,
and I'm going to do a bunch of actions that you guys ask for and that we vote on.
But here's how I'm changing it though.
Because I'm including props, you know,
I'm only going to we're going to set it up properly in a couple of sections.
Like you'll be voting for props, you know, prop actions.
You'll be voting for regular actions because every prop action will just win.
And I'll have to spend like five grand on like two day Amazon stuff.
So we're definitely we're definitely going to have to split it off into different sections.
So you have to vote for your favorite one.
This is such a good idea.
It's going to be a lot of fun.
So we're not doing that like tomorrow,
because I need some more time to go through and section these off.
And I'm going to present in the Discord a series of polls.
We're going to vote on them.
This is not I'm going to I'm going to try to get this done from tonight into tomorrow.
And I'd say by this weekend, you'll have a poll to vote on,
but with three different sections in it.
And then I'll be streaming periodically, hopefully, if the internet stays fine.
Expect now that the streams are able to happen from here.
We'll push this forward a little bit so people have time to participate.
And we'll get that stream probably going next week,
like probably like six or seven days from right now.
I have a studio that I'm currently in contact with and working with.
So it is it's happening.
We just need some more time to get it prepared.
Because I know I'm going to need to buy props,
and that's going to take at least two days to get that stuff here.
So hopefully, that's a decent update.
It's no longer a secret anymore, by the way,
because I need to know what props I have to get.
So that this is the whole secret thing.
Like, I'm not going to know is that's not happening anymore.
So I'll be in there browsing and perusing.
And JabbaDab just gave five more subs.
Five community subs from JabbaDab.
Thank you.
Can't you just paint one of your rooms green?
Oh, I mean, well, I could.
But you have to remember something.
A green screen studio is like 50 feet up and down.
If I were to paint a room back here,
it would just be like by it would be impossible to do,
let's say me sprinting and sliding into home base.
I wouldn't be able to do that with an actual studio.
I'll be able to do large scale movements, full body, feet, everything.
It will be keyed out.
And thank Kazzy 101 just gave five community subs here.
Thank you.
Here's another one.
Thank you so much, guys.
Both of you.
Five in a row here.
Five in a row.
Yeah.
So like you'll be able to see full body,
complete green over like a 40 or 50 foot space.
It professionally lit.
It'll be perfect because you either go hard or go home with this.
You know what I'm saying?
Like, I don't want to put like just a green screen behind me
and like do five Fortnite dances.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Like, there's going to be a lot of shit
that I'm going to do in front of this camera.
But regardless, that's kind of the update with that situation.
We're going to do that probably next week.
Give some more time to get more suggestions
and for me to make some polls
and you will hear about it again over the coming couple of days.
Here we go.
Okay.
Back to John Marston.
Or no, Arthur.
All right.
Multiple missions are available in the camp.
These are shown as the, that thing.
All right.
I need to take, maybe I should take a bath.
Can we have a peek at the recommendations?
You can go look at it right now.
You got your act together.
There's a channel in the discord.
I don't need to warn you again.
That is, I don't have anything in my, okay.
Well, just please can I, I don't want to kind of aim weapon.
Browse catalog.
No more nonsense from you.
Here's the catalog.
There's a green screen discord channel.
Okay.
Ammunition, hunting and fishing, horse care, clothing.
Here we go.
Clothing department, outfits.
Let's take a look at the outfits.
No, 85 bucks.
The Valentine, 113.
It's locked.
Custom tailored apparel of distinction.
That one's not bad.
The Dewberry Creek.
I ain't going to stay patient forever.
Get down to business.
Uh, dude, please.
Worn flat cap.
Ooh, some of these are nice.
Big city hat.
Derby hat.
Duster coat.
Ooh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Can I, was they a blackwater possum skin hat?
Should I get the rat hat?
I got things to tend to, so get on with it.
With items from our sewing department.
Can I not select it?
You need to bring the rat.
No.
I need to go kill rats?
All right, I need one that's going to be cool.
I'm overheating, right?
Am I getting like the crotchless pants?
I ain't going to stay patient forever.
Get down to business.
Okay, these are just pajamas.
Ranch pants.
Thin and ranch pants.
Button fly.
Durable friends.
These are bargains.
But please go ahead and turn the page in an inconceivable active account.
Well, now I have to buy it because...
Got things to tend to, so get on with it.
Can I be like a big candy cane?
All right, I'm going to be a candy cane.
Yeah, Halloween's over.
It's time for Christmas.
Okay.
Which, what are the cheapest ones?
Well, these ones are 16.
We're going with the dog shit ones down here.
Worn, well, actually, riding boots.
These are probably, these are all right.
I ain't going to stay patient forever.
Get down to business.
I can't do green?
I mean, this is kind of green.
I can't do green boots for like Christmas?
That's as close as I'm going to get.
Anything else?
I mean, I have to get a different coat.
I got things to tend to, so get on with it.
Our special attention.
Okay, we got gloves.
There's a lot of shit here.
All right, these are big like cleaning rubber gloves.
Let's check these out.
Oh, those aren't Christmas.
There's so much shit here.
It's like overwhelming.
All right, hold on.
I ain't going to stay patient forever.
Get down to business.
What am I doing?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Open that back up.
Press square.
Square just reads.
Okay, here we go.
Coats.
Get the rat hat.
I can't.
This is a classic one.
Let's take a look.
Damn it.
L2, R2 for free pants.
I got things to tend to, so get on with it.
I just want a red like candy cane coat.
Shotgun coat.
Get square when you're looking at the clothing.
Square is read.
Like go like this.
I don't understand.
Like square, I just select the price and then it's like a view is X.
I ain't going to stay patient forever.
There we go.
Looks all right.
That matches kind of.
Oh, well, that, okay.
How much is this for 16?
I got things to tend to, so get on with it.
I'm just going to look like a cork jester.
It's going to have to be this one.
All right, now we're going to go back.
We're only going to do this once, guys.
Don't worry.
I need like a Santa hat on.
That's not really a Santa hat, is it?
I ain't going to stay patient forever.
Get down to business.
All right, these ones are already kind of red.
I'm spending a lot of money.
Is that it?
Is there any more red stuff?
Like striped candy cane stuff?
All right, vests.
I got things to tend to, so get on with it.
Oh, boy.
Here we go.
Okay, now I just need a shirt.
See what we got.
Maybe I don't have a shirt.
Maybe just no shirt?
I ain't going to stay patient forever.
Get down to business.
Does this make sense here?
Let's see.
Yeah, that's fine.
Blue?
No, no.
This is like the Union.
Yeah, hold on.
Is there another one?
Oh, this one's striped.
There we go.
I got things to tend to, so get on with it.
Kind of candy cane?
Am I done?
I mean, it's not really a holiday.
It's more...
I need gloves.
All right, I need...
This is going to get ruined anyways.
Oh, boy.
Oh, I just need a green horse.
All right, gloves.
Accessories, right?
Okay, all gloves.
I mean, that's as close as we're going to get it.
I ain't going to stay patient forever.
Get down to business.
You look like the cowboy Joker.
All right, so we've got spurs, too, right?
Gurdon spurs, leak, multi-tone, border stamp, leather bootstrap, and Paul's steel hay bed.
That's a run-on sentence.
Shank and 10-point Ravels.
I don't like those.
That's not bad.
I got things to tend to, so get on with it.
Hmm, those ones are big.
Ooh, these have jingle bells on them, though.
That's important.
Let's try these ones first.
No, that's not bad.
Are there any others besides those ones?
These are close.
Those are good.
I ain't going to stay patient forever.
Okay.
Get down to business.
All right, I've spent like half the money that I own, so that's it.
All right, my outfit is now done for the rest of the game.
Okay, well, I've got something to tell you.
From behind here, we just look like a grandma.
Especially with like the side purse.
Yeah, look.
Oh, Jesus.
Would you look at that?
There's a sale on flowers over here.
Oh, my aching back.
It's time to go to church.
Just wait, this is not my horse.
Oh, shit.
Is it?
Is this my horse?
It's not my horse.
Fuck.
Where's my horse?
He's coming.
Come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here.
All right, let's make it up.
You are a wanted lawman and I'm searching for you.
They ain't going to find me.
Because I'm almost out of the GTA circle.
All right, we're good.
Evade the law by escaping from the red search area, which is what I did.
Oh, not yet.
hold on not yet not yet not yet what am i stuck on
yep all right i'm out of the circle now right don't no no no no no
stay right here all right i don't know if that's fair
if i just sat on the horse and i didn't realize what i was doing
and i got off the horse doesn't that me admitting that oh i didn't sorry i
didn't mean to do that that's like walking out of a store
with an item that you didn't know was still in the cart and you turn
around and bring it back and go i'm sorry i didn't know this is the
bottom of my cart how's that any different
mister who's this that that's a fine horse you got there
appreciate it all right be well now see you
hey mister can i have a word easy there
give me your money now tough guy you're a dead man
you're gonna give me call to use this don't think i won't shoot you
i'll close you
fuck was he gonna give it to me oh it says a witness
oh god what do you have he moved too much you can't have a
fuck with a snake man no sudden movements he reached like
he went what is that thing
i can't i can't study it oh okay can i take them give me this one
too wait wait no no r1 r1 r1
squirrel what why does it keep saying squirrel is there a squirrel here
where's the squirrel did i run a squirrel over
oh well let's go back to the what we were actually doing
slow down slow what is this hey mister
uh he's like i'm not gonna fuck around no just like let me go
i'm not gonna rob this guy let's go to the mission
i need to get back on a path the one guy this is this red is this like an area
where they're gonna find me where uh where the where the hell is it
where did it go let's go it ran i ran i i ran him over
well stop getting distracted uh oh uh oh
there come the hyenas i'm gonna go back to camp
let's get this meat here no thank you for stopping me
down here no you can't get down that no he can't
pitch the horse don't kick me backwards please
you're fine i'm gonna pet him he's fine there's the path i want to go down
right here
he's all right i didn't know that was gonna be that far
drop special horse reviver okay let's go uh i'm gonna just trot
for a second although can i kind of make like a waypoint
did those do those exist i'm so far away
i'm all the way down here holy shit what the hell was i doing all the way
up there out of options eat the horse fast travel
should i fast travel or should i run feed the horse surprise all right
what does horse break is it like square like how do you
slow down r1 okay i think those are bad guys
by the way horses dirty then cause us healthy brush your horse or ride it
through water here we go all clean all right i'm gonna brush
it
sorry pet him he's nicely clean robbery in progress
there's a bleeding animal on his back oh fuck
what the fuck all right now how do i can i like
take everything satchel's full kind of wedding ring
two chewing tobacco does he got a gun maintain
guys hold on pick up carbine repeater open eyes provide half the benefits
of new items should i just leave these guys here
can i go in the back of this and i just take
seven repeater cartridges revolver cartridges
baked beans is that it why am i doing this
why can i just go in like a normal person just go in
why do you have the spider man around this just go in
what is the ground poison i don't understand get in there
all right this is mine now santa got his slave
i think i sell this what the hell is going on here what happened
i just get attacked by a random what come on horse let's go
is he coming he's gone wait okay i thought that was a guy running
i need to eat something what do we got dead eye tonic
baked beans can i throw it to the horses
yep turn off the fan what the playstation 4 fan
uh that's impossible that's that's the ps4 just
turning right now i gotta turn off the ps4 fan
just turn off the ps4 what are you waiting for
who's this i mean who's there what are you doing what's happening
i'm here what you're everything wagons to the camp they'll be available
again when you leave oh well i can't bring that in here
i still got my uh my fox corpus where hey
can i talk to him can't funds 30 bucks
don't give me ideas like that man i will derail this whole stream for an hour
and a half and i'm dirty too i got my new
santa suit dirty i can't even get on it they won't let me get on anymore
it took it away from me red's not a christmas color what red and
santa is red what he's a big red guy i've read that wrong i did
bring him animal supplies to the camp we can use the meat for food and skins
to craft satchels all right let me hold on a second
let's go to the butcher i want to where's my guy i got my wolf right
he's still stowed so then he should show up right
i'm gonna actually give some real money here good morning arthur
i'm gonna donate some money oh they said it is a okay give item
oh watches no well these are worth a lot of money
all right i'll give one clamp buckle all right that's fine
well they only i have more money than the whole camp combined that's not
that's not okay all right i'm gonna give some money
what do i get 88 bucks i'm gonna give 10 dollars
no i'll get 15 dollars 16 dollars that's gotta be worth something go to
the butcher thank you for the 1600 all right
donate we could really use some more meat mr morgan
okay provisions the coyote meat let me see
coyote pelt and some meat well i'll take what i can get
okay many thanks mr morgan so let me see what do i need to do to
upgrade my satchel my satchel sucks if you bring me the right materials
okay i need to purchase leather working tools and upgrade the medicine
wagon so i need leather working tools
and then donate five animal carcasses to pierce them
so i need to buy leather working tools where the hell do i get those
i reckon i'm gonna think about it where am i supposed to get that shit
all right uh i can eat from the soup right because i get one soup a day
all good but what if well what if i want an extra serving
not allowed okay well we got a mission right here this guy's like tied to a
tree
speak don't cry boy speak about your gang
i can't
i have to beat this guy up tied to a tree
it seems the uh cat has got our friend here's tongue
i was thinking mr williamson could have a word ready to talk boy
i told all of you h1 and his chief they ain't no friends of mine
i've just been ridden with them for a while you see we heard that part so how
about you tell the truth that's what you want me to do heard
him so the next time he opens his mouth it is to tell us what is going
on oh my kid one odriskel's boys
couldn't open his mouth but he'd tell a lie
screw it let's just have some fun well i
but you carve out his brain eat his brain
and then close your eyes and sleep and see if while you're digesting it you
can hear his thoughts
what are we doing here
they're not doing this right
and you're right he don't like you any more than you like
he's at six point cabin i'll take you there
serious i don't like him i mean i like him even less than i like you
none take him okay then partner why don't you take a few of us up there
right i got this dutch should be fun i was going for santa and i ended up
like willy wonka somehow
what did i get wild west wonka all right throwing knife a small knife with
straight blade design and balance so they can be thrown with ease can be
used to silently take down enemies of range
or use a melee weapon if required it can be purchased from some less than
reputable sellers to save a trip by recollecting the knife after
throwing okay come here we got a social call needs
making where we heading an underwear
what are you talking about john you take this to the rest
i mean like what are you talking about nonsense kill him
mount your horse okay horse let me pet you first good boy
okay let's back it up i'm breaking things
already i don't understand i just tried to move out of the
fucking way you sure look all right let me get
how many knives do i have just one
damn you smell like one too i smell like horse shit that's right
boy are you
i was asked to give them and i'm doing you the further courtesy of
telling you about it
willy wonka he's our man
hoping the opportunity comes up to mention it last goddamn thing was
fucking terrible
yeah no no no the gene wilder willy wonka was good
but johnny they're talking like this the whole movie was kind of like i
don't know why i think that you're doing
exactly
watch that whole movie it's just
beating the man to death would have been looking on
when we supposed to be laying low i saw your eyes morgan
you didn't go clever you went soft i'll take it
after all you are an authority on that's how you talk
excuse me this is how i'm talking right now do you hear
this does this sound do you think i sound like that
are you listening to me right now the question
yes that's what you hear is that
you sound just like johnny depp
all right speed it up this guy moves the muscle
brain save your horses we gotta climb boys
you know you know you all ain't that different from
hot knife through butter through brain
i've been watching you all day been tied to a tree
nothing about this game yeah well i i'd say you don't know much about the
old driscoll's but maybe i know more about you than
you know about them so tell us then dogs brain through
blood like them about to survive like you live rough
fighting the law i'm trying to fuck this up get back up there
free to the killer you're already too close man
that's just more like a teacher from where i've been
you just look the same as all then you looked but you ain't seen
shut that boy up here we go shut him up
does it like road rash this guy we're almost on
those of this son of a bitch we got with us is talking true
but if it's what he says it is and colm or driscoll's hair
we can end years of fighting here and now okay now now skid turds
what no no skid skid marks hold r1 and x while moving
try not to set things up but if we do
why did i go right to that quick and hold on wait wait i've unlocked hold
on settle this like we know how okay there we go okay so if you hold r1
just move around all right then it's a handbrake
that's i wish i had that an hour ago good thing i unlocked it
hey i'd leave your horses the other side of this clearing
i'll get my guns off my horse it's an ambush look out oh no
okay i got my knife out who am i gonna have to throw this at
the cabin's just the other side of this hill okay
off your horses mccall tells us on the ps4
you're gonna get them nice i said easy off the horses got the knife first person
all right it ain't far we might have shared a horse
we ain't friends remember watching you every one guy well that's interesting
isn't it how do i throw is this not
hold on is this not a throwing knife
cabin's in the clearing down there there'll be a bunch of fellers
hiding out there too are these fellas armed armed that's by the rope okay
where are you strangers yep he'll be holed up in his cabin
stealth mission incoming who's blind likely is not
and over there someone's coming so uh who's gonna tell away you got love
for the pot i'll catch up it's a good idea all right
so i got a throwing knife in his body's pain so you can tell
him yourself yeah yeah yeah if anyone's actually
going to shoot the messenger it'd be that
bitch okay what are we doing about the pisser
morgan by the tree wait
that's clean off how do you survive how do the guy to the right doing
about the piss how do you live through that man
take the lead throw weapon how do i aim this
does it have like a bunch of drop or anything
nothing else from you throw stay here
don't you damn move let me start it over
well i want to start i want to like do it correct what are we doing
about the pisser morgan all right so this is gonna happen you
uh bill he's yours bill you're going in okay
nice work no i don't want these on i want like the regular knife
close to these two make sure you're going left to right
i don't i don't know how to stab somebody in the back is it r2
i've not haven't done this yet oh god damn it i don't know how to do it
i was about to greet the guy why hello there
stab down the log don't shoot bill i okay come on john go for it brutal
all right so we're each gonna throw knives at everybody over there
okay let's do hold on a minute stay there john stop stop stop
should i
whoops it's on let's do it dead i time for jedi what happened with that
okay watch out john john get out of the way
okay john please kill him thank you who's left
i got a tomahawk ow i gotta get a better spot give me a better weapon too
give me this thing what i just pulled his head off
okay got him uh where's my shotgun oh that's even better
so there's a guy in here i'm ready i'm ready once this guy opens the door
i'm gonna tell him i'm right in the head
oh oh what i was gonna do to you all right browse the place
come here what you set us up no i didn't you did
como driscoll ain't here it was here i swear i
if i was setting you up i wouldn't have saved your life it's a good point
arthur that's a good point all right then go on get out of here
hey i won't kill you i didn't set you up
lost shit lost i'm letting you go on get out of here that's as good as
killing me out there without you como just was gonna lose his mind about
this so so
it's gonna it's the first full body shot we've had in like an hour come on
let's get the camp so you got the cash then what cash
here's usually some cash in the chimney i'll check it
the rest of you boys get the cab quick see arthur
i ain't so bad hey bill you tell dutch old karen ain't worth killing
just yet you're right you are all right cash in the chimney you got it
slugs shotgun shells some biscuits and all that stuff
kill that guy i'm not gonna kill him yet
possum pans what's in here kentucky bourbon i can't carry any more
kentucky bourbon well why the hell not now i can
just replace it chimney money clip how much is in there 13 bucks that's not bad
more money how many money clips are over here 12
there's another one right there damn is it going right into the
donation box no donation box box why can i not say
that word search the draw snake oil can i take
any more snake oil okay anything else box money in the
chimney oh double barreled shotgun
yeah i believe so oh man clean the double barreled shotgun
cleaning weapons with gun oil will improve their condition and
performance okay cool that's cool any more dust on it looks
good looks really good actually all right
let's put back all right search the chimney chimney
at least you got something six holy fuck
that's a lot of money six hundred dollars let's see mission complete
under the threat of torture kieran leads arthur john and bill up to six
point cabin where he claims old driscoll is holed up i got an f
now let's head back anybody actually like this up this body's to
check over here redo now we don't need to redo
we don't need to do over what is that animal
that's like a skunk wolf what is this no no what is that thing
hold on i gotta catch the skunk wolf study study
don't study oh i thought i could have had it
there he is damn it next time i'll get the skunk wolf it'll
happen i can't i'm trying to jump trying to jump
inside of his cabin oh shit it didn't work
hey why is it still going wait wait what is in here
why is it still yeah it's not a car when do i talk it's not like you're
stepping on gas seven repeater cartridges pistol
cartridges damn what else you got in here what
now let's stand on the box chest herbivore bait
predator bait shotgun shells that's a lot of stuff
that's it right it's a bunch of vegan food
what about the horses these are these look like they're good horses
can i what about this guy i can throw this guy off and loot his body
right what oh fuck oh oh fuck oh fuck
oh fuck oh fuck what if i pretend it's mine
hey it's all misunderstanding don't get confused about me
i'm gonna shoot you both next you got a dead fleece on them
hey wait hey what oh it's just too many people here now
who are these come here get up where's my force
where's my horse oh go go go go go go go
all right settle down wait i found him where where where is he where did he
there he's that's not it these are two different animals
sorry study got it i thought that just said threatened
almost got it okay we're fine let me pet the horse
you're just you're doing fine you're good i got i could loot that guy's body
when he was on the ground i thought it was dead
that's funny no i can't go this way it's not a car why can't it just be
what can the armor on his legs calm down everything's fine
i gotta go home new mission why am i dead eye
study big animal all right let's get a waypoint here
what the hell am i okay this is bounty 25 dollars
where did i end up am i i still have a bounty
so i have to do i have to pay these guys or get rid of these guys i
think i have to get rid of these guys
now i gotta get rid of these guys all right i'm gonna i'm gonna go pay it
off so i'm just gonna go this way can i talk to them or
is that a bounty hunter no i think he's just
oh well it is these guys no it's not
okay i need to heal let's go with uh let's do some more kentucky bourbon why
not your health core is empty oh yeah you
need to eat okay we got i of course i thought i
could eat the glove i'm hungry smoking cigar canned peaches
okay we're good would be one more of those all right
back to what we were doing health is fine stamina is not great
but now that my bounty is taken care of i don't want to work them too hard
don't work the horse too hard he doesn't deserve that how do you
feed the horse everyone's saying feed horse feed horse
excuse me oh i gotta get i gotta kill five rabbits on horseback and i gotta
unlock a super move here eat this why am i getting
the gun see he's fine rabbit meat uh i'm gonna
skip the rabbit let me do i want to do this let me
just get five rabbits holy shit okay i just revealed the
scooby-doo monster that was pretty wild all right
i want let me do um let me do a few more rabbits
i want to get the four more rabbits so i could unlock something
tell me if you see any rabbits just scream as loud as you can if you see
one i've seen a lot of people scream i
don't see any rabbits though unfortunately guys sorry i don't know
what the fuck this bullshit is that you guys are doing
i don't know what kind of bullshit you guys are running here
i almost pubg'd that guy that would be pretty crazy
that was not that far that was not far
that really wasn't that far that was maybe eight feet
is it gonna be like an rpg anytime i play a turn-based rpg
i'm so bad at managing everybody's health that instead of buying the
thing that heals a party member i just buy like
60 revives because they come back with full health just
you know let them die and bring them back
let's take this scenery in for god's sakes
he wastes all right wait wait i i i'm critical with stamina right now
let's see i got canned peas i need something more substantial than that
that's all right did i yeah canned strawberry did it
i can't use i can't eat strawberries when i'm on a horse what
why does the horse's stamina well then let's feed him
god come on man feed him there he goes he's fine let's clean him
wait i can i can clean him like this let's i can brush him from here
i can study him oh i learned about my horse
okay let's go not with a saddle on what's a horse core
because i don't know almost back to camp
no scenic route let's just go intel horse two duo pretty good pretty
close more things to study i didn't have a
stupid bambi on my back we're going downhill this is going
pretty fast what are these is it a pig got it
well i learned about it this is gonna be okay right yeah
almost back how many giga horse does it what's wrong
what bill we're fine it's me what they don't know what i look like
i guess everyone looks like they're in the same clothes
from far away these guys have been up binoculars though right
all right how we doing how's the land doing here
53 dollars we're doing pretty well not yet
let me bring the carcass to this guy is there no running rule in camp or
something why can't i not run i've got something for you wait wait
wait you know and bring me some material satchel
wool perch leather working upgrade yeah yeah yeah i don't
perfect deer pelt perfect buck pelt perfect elt el we can't
i need well let's bring it to him
good rabbit pelt that's not perfect poor deer carcass zero dollars
we'll eat it okay then i'm gonna keep that good job
arthur what i got i got 200 bucks i could give some more money to the
camp can i what do we have 53 bucks is am i doing this right 20 bucks
20 dollars 74 total i come i'm unlocking more things
right okay now big bits it upgrades the camp it
seems that way let's eat the more you donate the
better you're ending interesting just eat it quick before it goes
bad i don't need to clean that okay all right
where's the ledger somebody said the ledger next to the donation box is there
one here that's not unlocked yet okay all right
i'm gonna just go do there's a lot of missions here d
dutch or damn minimum just i'm standing right here i might as well do
it so shea well feels like we are
finally getting back on our feet you uh find a buyer for them bonds me still
not yet but jose is working on it when we head
in west soon i don't know feels like
things have changed the whole world's changed
they don't want folk like us no more we're being hunted
we are smarter than them only the feeblest of men take
jobs in the government audio decent i hope so
trust dodge mr morgan you have to they got mica
dutch what's going on they got mica he he's been arrested for murder he was
in strawberry it's okay son breathe they nearly lynched me
they they got mica in the sheriffs in
strawberry and there's talker hanging him here's open
arthur what the fool brought this on himself
you know my feelings about him dutch i think i can't see past his bluster to
the heart and side he is a fine man no i ain't saving
that fool i can't go my face will be all over west
elizabeth i am asking he would do it for you i don't
think he would but fine arthur you okay lenny
yeah of course i'm okay you don't seem okay you take that kid
into town valentine not strawberry get him drunk
and arthur no crazy business i'm giving that up
and you get mica out of that jail jailbreak
i think i can handle this i'll get to it dutch just can't drop everything
all right jailbreak who's driving both of us
hold on let me make sure all right all right i need someone let let break
this down for me for just a second here like just somebody human me
so what dead eye is both sticks together right at the same time
and then you move it around and then press r2 and you're done or
which how is it i remember i i don't remember
it's just r3 okay and then you just aim around you have to hold r3
r3 and then aim around and then press r2
so i have to hold in r3 the whole time would you okay just click it and then i
aim around then press r2 okay don't need to hold anything so my
apologies i just kind of threw myself back into the
game r3 set shots take shots cool all right let's go
run them over run these people over thank you thank you jack
appreciate it
i kept asking him what we was doing but he was
you worried too much kid just just some business practice on
animals and minerals you know how he is i see a rabbit i gotta shoot it
then we ran into some fellas one of them michael new
drink some more and this is supposed to be a dry town we're in too
man he shoots one of them i don't know how that goes
with the swiftness here man why would we be taking our time here
happened like the strike of a match the lord was on his fast too
practice dead eye up there and then but i got away
just about all right i got a host of this
we'll take care of it so you're gonna go get them
i'll come with you no you leave it to me for now let's
this game is about taking your time i yeah it is i don't know
that's true i haven't seen the train go by yet because you know if the train
had come by i would have i would have rode into it okay
and gone
for you me and a couple the other boy
gotten a bit of a fight last time we was here
what kind of fight we kept it clean we're all good
if you say so i'll do it what the fuck is that
no no no no no no put it away put it down oh my
study okay kentucky sadler kentucky sadler got it what about that thing
over there let's go nice work in fact i don't
want the bow out give me the carbine double barreled shotgun who am i kidding
i just got this so we're gonna jailbreak this guy
this is like a stealth thing here are we just riding in
should i holster this you guys are just in the way okay we can move a
little faster here weapon shop right here i will remember
that pitch or not or not we got a
different we gotta find a different parking spot that one doesn't work
anymore over here easy all right we're good
go to the bar surprise oh it's a surprise birthday
surprise all right this is this is what we drink
this is a drinking contest just one or two
right off of course just a drink can we get a couple beers please
you i don't want no trouble you'll get none from me
i was defending myself tommy he'll be fine
have one for yourself thank you all right
micah seemed to know a lot of people that was the problem
how you mean i mean i done seen a lot of crazy crazy stuff
like a lot of crazy crazy stuff will you shut up will you shut up be quiet
buddy oh there alert this guy's just being a
dick you man is dull
and leave this fool alone leave the fool alone
i'm bored with being alone
charming listen buddy you're a charming fellow
one of the best but me and the kid here we're trying to talk business
could you possibly leave us alone no offense intended
ain't no pleasing some coke with the telltale games choice
that's too many where'd my friend go
where's lenny tommy where's lenny yeah do you know where my friend is
all right not back here my friend you know where we went
hey whoa hey are you serious buddy you're lucky i don't have control
right now otherwise i would drive a horse in here and run you over
plenty okay i've got my wits about me again
what i don't understand what are you doing why did i end up back here
power of teleportation wait why what did i get luigi'd
i actually got luigi'd i think that's what happened
that's the thing you see
no dad lose him again oh my god oh shit go down the stairs
shut your mouth mr what is happening whoa don't look at the
dick don't look okay i'm in first person mode oh boy
find him in the saloon all right we're having like a great time
all lenny what
churg who's turk churg can i sprint
we fight each other it was gonna be slap contest
oh this is so stupid i love it friend of me oh cheers
oh we got tankards now cheers it's gone
i'm just dropping the guy drawing it why am i doing this
where are things in this game oh that's not good is this the law
i have control i have control how do i can i jump
got it it was blurry but i got it is that it do i get to wake up now
oh weather change it's raining now you missed a sex scene good job
not getting banned oh that's all right i did lose the hat though didn't i
do i have to buy another hat or do i actually get to put it back on
somehow i need to eat something jesus okay i need i need to eat
now let's see the details did i do this one all right i think i missed
indeed what do we got uh i need canned sweet corn hold triangle at rest
set up camp craft show co coffee requires a campfire okay hold on
wait let me set up campfire do i need materials for this
all right crap craft and cook uh requires a percolator
you don't have enough ingredients am i slowly putting my face in the fire
i can't make anything i can make health cure i can craft seven of these potent
health cure fully restores health and fortifies
moderately okay well snake oil is the foliar stores
that i and fortifies let's i'll get a bunch of these
can i fuck this up or do i just hit x
stow it make another one it's idiot proof
hey watch it hey watch it
um how's my health right now i guess it's
i'm gonna use it just drink it all right i'll make one more
nice gameplay thanks dude this is the game
you're still now excuse me elite red dead streamer coming through
when did i ever say that i need tobacco i'll make it i guess i
could just fortify it all right when you say this game is good or worth
buying uh yeah i would probably say so
because i mean i feel like i haven't even
scratched the surface i feel like i've gotten
maybe like 1.8 percent through the game what about i need to fortify
stamina potent bitters so i need a burdock root
all right well whatever just sleep well i just picked 20 hours of sleep
pc version yeah i wouldn't i wouldn't hold your breath on a pc version anytime
soon first one never came out on pc
you gain or lose weight up or down will be shown in your health
it's a tear camp down all right so where's my force
is this thunder and lightning when am i going to play with uh stir
uh stir and i are going to play lethal league eventually here
uh we've had no drop frames at all about three hours
so the reason why you know i don't want to be like oh hey man
ready to like stream lethal league it's gonna be so much fun
hope you're ready and then the internet turns off in 20 minutes and
it's just like okay well that was a waste of time
what's going on here i'm writing down slipped on a rock today
moss is slippery be careful back hurts throwing knives
even know i was up here like let's be honest
it's fucking raining right now hey i don't know if he's a reliable way for
me to get down here you have to go all the way around
i'm stuck here right here is okay i should be able to slide down this
right it's not that far that's like two
feet at least try i'll try and mitigate the damage man
okay where's my horse down here oh someone was on the ground there
pick and examine pick up pick and examine plant
my horse is in town well what how am i supposed to i have to have to walk back
to town okay hat pick up hat this shouldn't even
my hat steal somebody's horse alright it's
kind of what's gonna have to happen herbalist let's let's take a look
at the map here reverend swanson i can run here
he's gonna walk to reverend swanson uh let me take a potion
we're good this way oh god it's slippery up here
i've unlocked it herbalist challenge it's right here right
all right is this guy wait hello ain't you done enough
look there must be some that's not the river in this room
reverend reverend swanson i've come to meet you
then your god has finally deserted you what you're talking about
i took your advice sir i have removed myself
from morpheus's embrace no more shall i sink sir i'm free
i am free you don't seem free friend you seem drunk sit down reverend we
ain't finished you ain't finished knock down look at him he's finished none of
us forced liquor down his throat friend i just wanted to play
now firstly we ain't friends don't make no mistake on that subject now
secondly he can hardly see let alone reason
now reasoning ain't never been one of my strong points neither but seeing
i do just fine you want to step outside or do a
business here i just want them to finish the game why can't we all just
get along these are good men are to their children
of god they have children of god hands down
there's a pool of blood under his head
sure you want a game sure i'll play a few hands we're playing well sit
yourself down goldfish uther this is marvin
okay fortunate for you both will be in gentleman about this
so who has the best hand or bluff of the weaker one
so are you two know each other anyway don't seem like the likeliest of
friends you don't mind saying we go a long way
but has a queen and a 10 a promising starting hand
i guess it's something like that can we play
uh he can't be no real clergyman he committed about five cardinal sins
just in that chair you're sitting in i think he used to be he's
community cards it comes to flop and then and then there comes a river
oh look at that can you imagine him at the pulpit
get a pair queen pair on the forest day he turned water
whiskey and i don't remember much after that
here comes the turn and then we got the river card he's a decent fella
oh no no no no what if he has uh-oh
him again and you'll find yourself in a bad time too
all right all right just trying to have a little fun here
it is a game after all mister in your own time
i reckon i'll go all in oh i think you're gonna regret that
call come on queen river queen oh i win i win it i win three
dollars game over two pair i win check it's always it always comes down to
the river come on you've unlocked the gambler
challenge check your luck for more you lucky son of a bitch
we're doing this shit again all right well i'll do one more
that was kind of a shitty shuffle though i will tell you
look look at aces live with two pocket aces
yeah get out of here what do we got now you shuffle this time buddy
i must say you have a lot less stories than your friend did
are you lucky or not you ever considered that
all right give me pocket aces is it three four
nine queen okay
weak all right what do we got
well you should go all in what we got
now you're talking okay hold on we got queen
hold on do it again that's the way it goes excuse me shut up
yeah i didn't lose that much money this has been quite the eventful day
just not the same without a slurring clergyman is it
queen six no i'm not going all in i'll call
i'ma play slow oh come on this ain't kid poker
man we need the flop to happen here come on deal it out
five four what do we got what do we got six
we got four five six seven we need a seven
we need seven come on man sometime before we all grow old
let's be brave give us seven okay now
oh fuck okay give us a seven straight do it
we're off there for real no i'm not gonna shoot him
i'm gonna come all the way back nice didn't okay i didn't want to do that
okay go ahead okay king ball good let's start this low for now
14 give us a full house don't do this to me again
king yeah i know pretty pathetic ten ten ten
no forgive me it's all i can afford ten ah oh you want to check that
all in what is this no you fucking lose buddy
this ain't what you call finishing strong yes yes yes got the 10
not much i can do about that okay so we're back in the game now
see what do i got for money what are they coming here with are you
kidding me that's gotta win two more hands right
and i was gonna play it safe and i'm gonna just win two hands and get the
achievement the people we've met at this table
can you win without a straight friend still breathing
he's very quiet you can win with a pair if nobody has anything
210 no i mean they could get like a pair i give it two pair though
i just a little wager okay well if somebody has a six then
it's just i'm folding here that's too dangerous all right
this is just this is yeah this is it come on
jesus you play like my grandmother when you guys got a fucking six the game's
over well okay what about that that was two
pair that was two pair and i'm shouldn't
fold but if somebody has a six we'll see
that was two pair what do you got check
can't check i thought i was good sorry to do this
two three is he got a six see i would have fucking lost
i folded at the right time it was the correct play
if you were sitting at the poker table you would have had to do the same thing
hey back in it i'll give you i've made like
10 grand playing poker now granted i've also lost 40
grand but i've won 10 grand before on the inside of me we got queen three
well i just need to put a couple come on all right well that's fine
that's like let's fuck them up a little bit here let's break them up
yep give me give me a two pair here there's the three
that's a pair right there just need a queen or another three
i ain't too excited good just give me a queen or three come on
give me three i don't think i'm gonna win is the pair of threes
and another check why don't that surprise me
fuck uh come on river's gonna be like a three river's gonna be a queen
or three he doesn't demonstrate oh fuck now he
maybe does i could win this with a pair with three he's bluffing this is
bullshit 84 cents take it easy let's see then
he's high read him and wait pair threes pair sevens god damn it
you can't win with that oh i would have won i would have won
that would have been it keep him coming lucky son of a guy i just got
a look i can i can come back i can come back i can just give me a few
more minutes just give me like another hour or two
i can come back i'm supposed to be amused just i'm just gonna run to the
atm i'll be back like i'm just gonna get like another 400 all
queen six why do i have a queen every time is this rigged
seriously is this rigged do i have had a queen fucking every hand
good flip them you okay with that i'm gonna go
oh come on damn it all right what do we got
uh that's it you're trying to fluff them up
come on no
how do i go to the atm this is getting too rich for me
sit down i just i'll be right back i'm just gonna go to my horse
you get my debit card come on rip where'd he go who
for where excuse me gentlemen the tutorial ai never holds
who's the stranger excuse me i'm sorry you see a drunken idiot
priest wandering about i wasn't done i wasn't done
hey i'm just screaming for him no god damn it i'm not trying to kill
anybody jesus christ what he's with me
find him who is this who he's still alive
shit he's still alive this guy is a fucking superhuman
oh no okay oh no no no no no get the sheep out of the way
come here come here come here live spirit is he going to the train
what is he doing i can't jump that high
what the fuck is he doing it's just a simple mistake
you can still be saved the train's not coming we're fine
all right come here it appears to like this place
and what's the stay oh the train's right there
what the hell did you do man what's just the heavy from tf2
what the hell is wrong with you throwing me bridge like that it was
your goddamn train you crazy bastard
have i been bad again mr morgan i'm sorry
was yours different go down you for not doing the cheap
youtuber joke home yeah that's a wonderful idea
i've done enough stupid shit the last three hours margaret who's margaret
but yeah y'all thought by the way uh those of you that have very keen
ears i i pressed r2 try yeah i know
no drop what a classic it's a classic one you know one more time
dude it's a classic funny youtube joke come on
we fell off what the heck what the heck you have to do it for the for
the youtube joke okay no i'm not doing it
will you shut up i told you i wasn't gonna do it just bail in the last second
no no we can't do that anymore there's way more funny interesting things to
do than look i fell off the cliff again
you know wait for the train to go to the length of the entire map and then
get hit by it here comes another one don't need to do
this he's coming without him hey hey is he out cold i think he's
knocked out
he oh he he got an accident hello it's a fatty let's hitch
all right reverend what do you think where's it going where are you going
with him drop off in bed
i am babysitting this guy huh just leave him on the horse can i put
him on the horse and put the pores in bed
no drop in fire that's not gonna happen drop off cliff not gonna happen
you better sleep your way to salvation my friend
what happened just the usual poor bastard exactly well thank you mr
morgan i'll keep an eye on him comedy license revoked this time
real lucky all right who is not without satan completed
donation let's get it to 100 bucks a companion activity is available in the
camp talk to companions marked on your map
where companion activity it's now marked on the map
what which one opened up five finger fillet with lenny
not this shit again i couldn't do this before because it was an xbox
controller though remember i should be fine
lenny hey alpha that knife sharp enough ain't it
depends why you feel lucky do you oh but for me at least six
generations were born and changed and for the last three years i've been
running from every lawman and bounty hunter west of the lanahassee
river so yeah i feel lucky i'm the living
embodiment of luck that is one way of seeing things
but i'm also skilled and in this game i think i'll be all right here you got to
have luck and skill and stupidity the outlaws
trinity look skill it's just a dose of stupidity
come on like circus ringleader outfit shines
after you as you wish you know we should head back up that mountain
sometime and make jenny a proper grade
okay who's turning is this work just like the other one
oh he just cut his hand oh he's setting the time i have to beat
all right got it keep it loose what are the buttons here
okay it's x triangle so it's triangle so it's x triangle left triangle left
i'll do it like in five seconds check it out ready
the hell out of here what do you got now so this is x square x
okay just x square x square x square x square
no other uh variables here record time here watch this
now we're going round two so this is okay so this is
circle circle circle square square whoa whoa whoa
this is so boring so this is square square square
triangle triangle damn it i'm gonna do it again i gotta do it again
oh i'm freaking out another one try this in real life
okay i gotta slow down on this one this is circle circle square
triangle circle let's get paid attention
your turn let's get a beam in four seconds triangle circle
square circle triangle triangle circle square
triangle circle square circle triangle what was it
okay what's this next one let me see
square triangle circle triangle square square triangle circle
triangle square square triangle circle triangle square
square triangle circle triangle square
square triangle circle triangle square square triangle circle triangle square
square triangle circle triangle square square triangle circle triangle
square square triangle circle triangle square
fuck out of here everyone i'll take that be i'll take that very
drink it out here finally all right what's next
we do i want to do this guy's mission go hunting
oh i don't think so no i gotta learn some time right
you want to go hunting what are you hunting an elephant
i wish no i saw a huge bear one of the biggest i ever saw i
reckon nearly a thousand pounds my god get a good item from doing
this need me to come with you well i'm definitely gonna do it then let's
go where are we heading exactly up before that river i am gonna go get a
water too i could do with a break from this
me too has it it's been a rough couple of weeks you need anything
i don't think so i got all i need let's go then
so you still ain't replaced bo to see you no i miss her she was quite a
horse this one's okay but ain't no boat to see
i've been meaning to offload this big shire horse for a while now
unruly bastard where'd you get him some
big loudmouth bastard tried to rob it was that right
so i well you know how it is i see visible force
let's take him to valentine it's on the way sort of
there's a decent dealer there we'll unload him you could buy yourself a
new horse put your saddle on them let's get going
okay that horse is huge there's nothing wrong with two
horses look at how big this thing is
okay well i'm gonna take that saddle
and put it on the giant one don't be rude about this magnificent creature
i'm gonna study him first put your saddle on him and let's go
what's what's wrong be on the other side saddle up
promise you don't want to ride that one there okay
horse bonding achieved level one so what about this guy
okay see if you can get your leg over that group i want to pet him
all right just get on let's head into town all right hold on give me a second
i'm just gonna grab a water i will be right back
see in a second did he go to the store to buy water no i'm right here
ah okay back to it so how is no what stay out of the saloon this time
talking about yeah that's a good idea they got a good
range of horse attack at the valentine state is now your main horse
is represented as a horse on the radar i used to have a real nice
one yeah what happened to that what are you
doing got stolen outside that saloon in deer creek
welcome back from the store just about it was a really really quick
store run turned into a long day yes is that
noise in the background your ps4 fan yep went crazy
threatened to kill the whole town and davy was
passed out so cold and left him there came back in the next day and he woke up
started right back drinking again it's not even near the microphone either
it's across the whole thing it's just for some reason
it's being picked up bad girl it must be pretty hard on lennie
you could tell he was sweet on her lennie and jenny could never have
worked that's vacuum out ps4
oh yeah this is not i can't do maintenance on this is i don't know i
don't know
it's alex had a ps4 pro and i had my ps4
so we would have had three ps4s
mine sounds like a vacuum when playing this
it probably has to do it they're still very i don't know maybe how hot
your room is or a couple of leads i'm looking into
that big bastard get the better of you there aren't they
yeah yeah calm down calm down calm down
boy calm down stables are just up ahead your bonus horses it will be available
to collect in the stables all right go sell that big broom
sell it buy yourself a horse okay don't i want this
i'm going off to the general store i want to keep this guy to lure that
bear out with meet you back here in a bit
hey how can i help you i did buy that stupid 20 dollar package
you're in the right place i got some beauties in at the moment
what about this one here looking to sell
i show you you got papers no no papers of course that's gonna
affect what i can pay but thank you for that i got a fella
who's been looking for a decent workhorse like this for a while
no it's mine good price otherwise i can always stable them here for you
yeah take a look all right hold on a minute
stabling your horse allows you to store it in the stables so you can
access it later if you sell the horse you'll be able to you'll be paid
the sell price this horse is five dollars and 20 cents
what that's that is terrible i'm going to stable it okay buy a
new horse american standard bread
dutch warm blood thoroughbred and ardenis he's free
oh shit is this the horse that i got for
a pre-order the game for 20 bucks is this my 20 dollar i paid for this
like i get the fast one my horse i'm pulling up the keyboard
that's not gonna work okay uh gotta be good gotta be good
uh it's something about like a 20 like who's in the 20
jefferson who's on the 20 it's andrew jackson okay
chuck schnozwell no it's okay wait it's female okay
how about uh whisper oops track attack and surfaces okay uh grooming
mane who all right can i make it a christmas horse
again
natural regular short long braid mohawk
dreadlock i think i want long long and red okay tail
braid a big braided tail oh man big gold braided tail
i like i like it to the hair be gold oh that just looks
fucking this i don't want that red's fine
okay tack saddles do any of these is this just for aesthetic purposes or
does this do anything i mean this one this one matches my
outfit kind of so i'm gonna go with this one
wait no never mind now it does improved
oh i like that i just spent every cent that i own
did i yeah i did look at that extra speed what do i want for a joystick
the lizard or the enterprise i'm a star trek fan so i got to go with this one
blankets uh i guess this one matches that
kind of i can't afford anything else i don't have any more money
bed rolls all right i'm ready services horse care package
that is waste five dollars all right horse provisions i think i already have
some but i want an apple though i want
like a few apples all right partner you got yourself a deal
and a fine new horse i hope so well i don't sell
anything other than good animals you have my word on that
35 cents left it's all right i'm just going to go back into the
donation box and take my money up here are your papers i can do that right
new grooming brush and some treats appreciate it i can't just reach in
there and just pull it back out you treat this fellow well i know he's
gonna look after you just fine it's all right i'll sell i'll sell a
few things looks like a nice animal you got there
all right look at this look at this beautiful voice
boy i got new saddles i got new hair wait what was it was his hair in the
saddle okay hold on let me like let's start
the bonding process brush hop on up there let's go
i'm gonna brush the horse oh you're dusty
that new horse of yours or not hold on thoroughbred
okay here we go all right let's get going
you got quite a ride ahead of us lead the way
so like this i don't want this horse to die
but i want to test out its speed zero to sixty
this is quick i just hope i can remember how to get there
back into the mountains i sure didn't figure on that
but this time we're doing the chasing i fucking hate the tail
why so how are things with you and what's wrong with it
i mean it kind of looks like a scorpion tail but that's fine
i'll say it he ditched us for a goddamn
youth i've spoken to him many times he knows he did wrong
he just wants to put it behind the tail is fine
i'm sure he does it just looks like there's a snake up its ass
is one thing but there's a cold he knows that
he ain't trolling dungeon you pretty much raised
i know but it's done has been for a while now
if it dies i lose it forever well then that's
very good reason for me to keep it alive
long hair it's the color not the braid get
gold okay time to go i think we need to head right up here
we're gonna go up all the way up yes i remember
i'm not in control anymore am i
what's what's wrong with my golden tail red hair
do i prefer flathead screwdriver or phillips well depends on what the
scenario is we made it let's loop around the other side
you can't have a favorite screwdriver depends on how big it is you know this
this screwdriver is a phillips head i can't undo my table without a
phillips head might as well go get a flathead
no i mean phillips head definitely is cooler but
did i do cinematic centrist streamer is scared to take a side
maybe we should catch one to cook sure try and shoot one
you don't want to use anything too powerful on a small animal like that
just ruin the meat you can probably put a paint can with a flathead
you can probably put a paint can with a hammer as well
slow down well there they all are i did i thought that we were still in a
cut scene why don't they just i got one
not very smart rabbits i will say you are correct on that
that's it we should camp here oh i thought we were going home
now that's it get it set up well i'm finished
cook that rabbit then they're delicious on an open fire like this
just like monster hunter right to spin it however i've been in this menu
it's just teaching me how to be in the menu
and cook six of this plain game let's go can i burn it
i don't like eating this late okay after all that
so i'm gonna eat a whole rabbit myself i guess i probably could do that
i could probably eat a whole rabbit put this one away
rabbits are 30 pounds are you sure about that
no they're not 30 pounds is is like a medium-sized dog a rabbit is like
maybe two pounds this isn't a shibu inu what do they call
is shiba shiba inu a rabbit is how many
pounds is a rabbit siri how many pounds is a rabbit how
much does a rabbit weigh how much does a rabbit weigh okay let's see
ranging from adult domestic rabbits can have a healthy weight ranging from
two to eleven pounds two pounds eleven pounds that's huge
that's a hare that's not even a rabbit first like to find this
monster choose time to sleep until sleep until morning
he better be worth all this drama eleven pound
absolute unit rabbit five five you ready
oh give me a minute coffee sure there you go
so what's your plan well we'll see if we can track them
but we might need to lay bait to draw them out
i want one of those cups obviously but they all can you get one of those one
of those old school tin cups i'll drink out of that every day
shoot from the trees but i prefer to hunt on the ground
more dangerous but we'll have a much better chance of getting
good shot in and if he bolts we can start right off after
why is my author arthur santa because halloween was yesterday and now
it's christmas time tie it up in that rag when you're done
i hope you know what you're talking about i grew up in the mouth
predator bait it's like the potent predator bait recipe
who's arthur that was virtually weaned on bear meat
okay i think i got this done good pack up and we'll get going i gotta
shave okay let's go so how are we gonna
take down we're gonna bait him this is my horse
okay yeah i can always tell that's where i saw him last
okay how's that horse treating you so far so good
you know i was in this area with bessie
years ago really i don't i imagine you still miss her
every day did you two ever think about
fix the audio hold on is it really like an audio syncing problem right
now or am i getting yelled at for no reason
you should be hearing like dun dun dun dun dun dun dun
do a test with the gun this is a better test right when you see the
highlight it should go it's a half second behind it wasn't
it normal the beginning of the stream the audio is playing first hold on
let me try this that's weird tell me if this fixes it
already i wonder why that happened that's weird
because it wasn't doing that in the beginning i don't know why i'm
just desyncing after playing for like three or four
hours it's weird okay let's go now we did briefly
you don't remember guess you were still young i had my sound off
how would you know there was a problem she understood she knew what i was
i've been around for a while things were looser back then
truth is there's never really any getting out
audio is at the wrong angle i gotta like tilt my audio
but bessie and i made it work you thinking about getting out
me no of course not you can braid your horse's tail yep
dutch's grand plans work and you can paint it gold we can make enough
money to go someplace new really new maybe we can all have a new
start anyway for now let's try and chase
ourselves a bear shall we let's slip by the water here see if
he's been fishing again sounds like fred from scooby-doo yeah an old version
is it fred uh what's his name fred wilker what's
his name there tracks dung bones any sign of him
you have entered legendary animal territory follow clues distract the
animal you can find legendary animals throughout the world
all right we got like a stink bomb here
let's hope it's him can you there he is there's the trail which way he went
this way don't i need a much better gun we're down here
tracks go into those trees wait i gotta make sure do i have
that this is not gonna happen here man hold on just just wait a second i
need the horse oh yeah i need i need a like a
shotgun or something double-barreled shotgun thank you
and what else do i want from you a knife i have the knife sawed off
shotgun i wasted all this money on the
saddle all right well whatever do i have
anything else i need light i'm gonna bring the light too
okay now i'm gonna make sure i have this equipped so i can
shoot the bear's face off of his head let's go
am i crouched where those tracks this way this way follow me
sniff the ground just drag your tongue against the ground and you'll be able to
taste it clue over here happy
okay keep my eyes on it did i hear a bear
use the safety light tracks dead no there's another clue
looks real fresh reckon he's got to be close
bear is close can i stealth kill the bear
hold on hold on which way dead trail looks like the trail nc we lost him
for now how little optimism are there well we're gonna hear the default bear
sound you guys know what i'm talking about
split up and each look the one that goes like this
it's in every single video game let's bait here fine by me
let's leave the bag over there those boulders up ahead looks like a good spot
for it that was pretty that was close that was
kind of close i'm not a bear though so i can't make
it completely you know so uh we need the bear bait which is
this one sausages come on wait for the bear
more or less there's a bad view scar down his face
hey did that bait look okay to you i think so
you're the expert ready with your gun there i'm good
you're okay you seem nervous so do you
no get the fuck out of here i'm fine here we go get the gun
let's just take a look at that bait no he's gonna get
he's gonna happen only just said it i was there i know here it comes
he got it he ate it got your knife here comes
easy do it whoa he didn't he didn't do it
you're right you're fine old man of course i fight
thank you i think that was fun you know what arthur morgan i'm a little
old he did he tried to do the bear noise too he
was that's what he was going for what is it it's a map
a man in a bar gave it to me well i stole it from him but that's another
story he said it told him where to find
some real big animals thank you it's a pleasure
there's the map my life i think i'm going back to
camp to lick my wounds you coming or you're gonna track that monster
well you're coming or not i want to track it
i'm gonna stick around here for a while
i'll see you back at camp yeah i hear him
i hear him where is he did i shoot the horse i didn't shoot the horse
accidentally right wait what am i eating whoa all right
i want to track this thing i'm gonna kill this bear train
train train which way train train up here train what your
horse is agitated by a predator what predator it's okay
i don't see anything all right let's find the bear don't go that fast
well i need to open up the the thing here because maybe bullet showed on them
all right there we go okay so this is king bear territory
i i don't no no no remove those i just defined them up here
so where's that thing that he gave me i don't see anything
is it in the maps lure the bear into the train
not a bad strategy don't walk off the edge here
what happened what did i just get clothesline
it's okay whisper
get up you're smarter than me it's for sure
how much does it get up here to get i want to board the train
okay come over i'm gonna let me feed you an apple come on
up here come on come on up here go go go go go go go
see you're fine now it's time to feed you
later all right what do we got here we're kind of
all the way up into no man's land what's this
that's a bounty bear i mean but is that where he is
do i have to go just down here find the bear
i'm what i'm gonna try just punch this
i punched the horse in the head oh i didn't want to punch the horse in the
fucking head and like lost the scent of a bear
let's go back on a road crying out loud just go down
it's not as easy as you think
ah let's try to be a dick and get out of there as fast as possible
go back the way you came up
hey go fuck yourself turn around he's eating shit
what am i doing i'm going back i'm trying to get down
what i'm trying to go down all right where
where was it up here like here author down
guys i'm in the middle of the mountains i gotta go down the whole
mountain to get out of here all right we're gonna play hot and cold
you ready starting now it's ice cold warmer getting
getting lukewarm cold cold hot warm hot hot hot hot hot hot hot
hot okay hold on i'm on fire on fire this is where that's where i'm
going this is where i'm heading right now
that's where i'm going right now what that's where that's what the
waypoint is the what who let the simpleton out of the
asylum yeah i got away with that one just press o near the horse's head
i don't understand
i don't know why i don't understand i just somebody told me to do that
i'm not cold while you're cold i'm not oh no no that's just a chat thing that's
not i'm i'm hot right now with chat
no please i could have just been a crazy person
where the fuck am i now what what this is not the beginning of
wait hold on no no no wait this is this is the beginning before
no my horse is right here thank god oh you can tell by the tail
i made it it's right here fucking jesus fucking christ i had to pay attention
i swear to god okay you have to avoid the rocks
well this game i like this game this is fun game
slow down i'm this is where i put it on okay
i wanted to back in and punch that guy in the ear and fly him off the
cliff so bad your words can't even describe how
badly i wanted to do that i was holding x honest to god i was holding x
it's supposed to keep you at a steady pace on
the mountain right holding x keeps you on the road
get away from me that's only if it's in a cinematic
oh for the love of god well then fine fuck it
let's do it cinematic mode now i can like actually drive around on the
roads okay i think i'm getting close you
can ride as fast as you want in cinematic mode because it no i don't
believe that where are we at now getting close
i remember this slow down
where everything's fine you actually can
should i believe people in chat or should i just play the game
holy shit they weren't lying okay
all right so thanks guys all right almost there how much further
down do we have to go i don't know what to think about that
tail i got i'm reading reading chat that time
minute that's because i was looking at chat
hey stupid come on okay how close am i to killing the bear
oh yeah yeah see we have to go around the whole mountain
you guys thought i could just walk run up the mountain
that's not gonna happen all right i need to
heal a little bit here you know what i'm saying
get away from me what what was that somebody was screaming
i don't see anyway oh hey what is that thing
i'm freaking out the lasso you're right here take it what do i do
what do i do uh
what does he need wait everyone asked me i knew he was dead
i in my head i internalized like that and that i want to make sure it was
quick you know like i i don't want him to
you know be suffering there to me like i did that very quickly it was
like done okay i got some wolf me what
do you have on him oh did i just sever his leg with
that what do you got good rabbit pelt
just in case his brain stem was still spinning data you know what if he
wasn't dead completely burial let's see it you
know i don't want to be suffering in there
you missed his brain well how do you miss somebody's brain if their head is
gone legendary animal territory here we go
i'm ready him hey can i give it an apple
something else too like an apple no i don't want to give him any more
baklava give him a fucking apple there classic oat cake classic oat
cakes okay let's give him a nice little
rub there girl it's a she i forgot so you
just stay safe daddy's gonna go kill a legendary bear
oh i just smelt something freaking times a dead eye herb
okay what do we got nothing around here
what's this shit oh just eat it actually i need to take a potion or
something here yeah look at my health it sucks
we could eat like beans and shit i have my core is terrible
okay what am i dead on my daddy sucks too
slightly damages the dead eye core who gives a shit
all right i'm ready not quite any clues yet
do i have any bait i don't think i have any day do i
can i make any come on can i make bait here
this is where you hide this is his hangout here i have herbivore bait
i didn't see any clues of him being right here anywhere come on
if i was a bear would where would i be right here somewhere i need to make
master ba and that's how
we sing the song the thing that we're singing right now
okay let's go i don't see any tracks or anything
there's no point of interest on the smell let me actually see if i have
i don't think i do herbivore bait predator bait okay
so now can i just put it down here i mean the horse hat kind of has to get
out of the way move out of the way wait bear
no what does that sound i gotta go further back
i thought the shadow was the jib was the bear shadow behind me
standing up all right i gotta i gotta get the horse out of here
let me get that bait actually we'll see uh it's flee right
flee me is that that means he's gonna go back to town right
when i press flee what does that mean hey go free
and how do i make him go home this way come on
come on all right stay there stay over there
let me just pick the bait back up where is it where is the bait it's like
right here right what didn't i just drop it like right
here what are these stink lines is this me
oh that's my body all right i'm going back down here
let's go right to the x i'm gonna drop it right here
so am i pushing the bear away by smelling strongly
i mean right here i'm gonna put some bait right here or would that be a stupid
idea there's a clue i don't see i mean this
is this this is not a clue this is just
flowers on the ground i don't see shit the bear is scared away
so i can't get him to spawn again i can just come back later
there's activity in the areas the bear won't spawn
oh ginseng what is going on over here oh what's this
i think that's the elk it was just right here right
yes deer tracks yeah i'll come back later
let's go do another mission in fact where am i gonna go from here
i'm so far away from everything oh how do i how do i get over here faster
uh i'm gonna go across the whole world
what's this we're going this way
how are you gold
the guy's looking for gold hey give me some goddamn space here will you
easy jesus what uh does he have any gold
let's see i'm i'm waiting to see i'm gonna wait and watch
we're talking about one shot headshot if they if he goes gold
sure looks like another pile of shit
can you take pictures why can you do a selfie
i can't can i like help him do whatever he's doing or no
look at his face you found me some gold why don't you hand it right over
get away from me found ourselves some gold
gold nugget some hobbyist spying these cars to be
collectors items keep an eye out for more i'm just kidding i'm not gonna do
it can i have his outfit i want to dress
up like this guy can i look for gold with his stuff
i just saw a hat on the ground where is it writer
prospector hat pretty good look all right i can't i can't use this stuff
so gold nugget that's gonna fetch me some money you want it
i gotta get back over this way that was cool
let's go how much does that sell for a lot
20 bucks in this day and age probably you really get you
44 cents that's it force medicine hold on i need to
let's get this out
this could be iqybod praying what did i gain 44 cents
like a canadian bounty 44 cents in a spot in hell
no too many animals we're just going south i see
some light down there that's safe safe trek down here skip i can
probably slide here very gently nice very good all right
back on land is there a body of water right here there's not
but what's this new hand over what is
i've been a bounty here somebody wants to kill me here okay
so i should just go in there and just shoot them in a bit
hello well somebody already did it i don't have to do anything nice
halloween house there ghost in here this is fucked up inspect the letter
let's read this at the second hour under the half moon by the great love
and grace of our savior cocoaba voyager of time and galaxies we cast
off our corporal shells so his vessel can take our spirits to
the promised realm to live in peace and power until the
2000th year when we will return for the new chosen
worship once again at the peak of mount shan
and his love we rejoice always the second hour
is that it what time is it right now it's in the night stand
potent medicine what time is it 10 30 p.m hey i know what we're doing
we're hanging out here till two cigarette card oh i need these
dr hawthorne's poet card okay well whatever one of 12 cards gone
okay that guy has a thing on his head so he might just get up
snake oil i'm gonna heal up too i'm not having that happen
you kidding me i'm not gonna deal with that bullshit
he doesn't read chat rewrite what what
i hear something is it 2 a.m look up i don't understand what you are i got
pranked uh what the fuck wow
okay get the fuck out of here you goddamn aliens
i told y'all it was real i told y'all it was real
i've been abducted four times just save the fucking earth
well that was interesting is it even 2 a.m like what time is it right now
1 a.m it's 2 a.m is that mountain time eastern time
i don't know but we only have another check the chimney
all right right i did i could check the chimney all right what's in here
it's alien time aged pirate rum okay increasing stamina xp
that's pretty cool time check 149 here we go
i'm ready 2 a.m it already happened yeah but
but it's at 2 a.m okay all right give me a horse yep yep
it already happened why does it look like 6 a.m
it's probably not two cool things that happen at this place
you'd probably be right now it was pretty cool though
is that like harping back on the joke that there's always some kind of
ufo in every rock star game that's pretty funny all right we got
it's a little settlement up here i'm not going to be bad guy
i'm gonna be a good guy i'm gonna greet them with respect
i have a dump count there's a mailman here
what is this here for how am i casting a shadow at 3 a.m
that's a good question what's he doing what
oh this is the back door this is the back door never mind
hey uh hey how you doing pay bounties i'd like to pay my bounties please
i don't have enough money train tickets this is your fast travel
but i can't do anything it was nice talking to you
hello sir hey it's lonely out here sometimes don't it
uh-huh anyway don't let me bother you
see you around mister what you want how's things
worse sir is the day goes by nope i'm not gonna do it what's that
hold on people jump to wagon oh right
where's my mask i'm trying to jump to the wagon
what happened to jump to wagon yeah an option wasn't it
i just pressed it hey wait what oh i can't
why'd they get off why would i just get off oh dear
oh boy oh boy oh i'm sorry that was my fault that was my fault
that guy blocked like three punches it was like clap clap clap
my ear diary i got knocked out i fucked with the guy i ran over four
people okay we're gonna get that that's what
that is we're gonna keep going now
oh wait wait wait wait 30 bounty here i haven't i haven't been here i haven't
been here one time morning morning what did i do wrong here
well besides just trying to open that guy's door uninvited but
damn this is so big i gotta go back here
i have to wrap around here uncle okay i'm gonna put uncle on the map i'm
just getting too distracted there's too many things to do
dog yeah whoa hey the hell do you want here hey boy
hey boy good dog study can i can i have the dog
you bet the dog likes me let's go what you son of a bitch i'm petting your
dog right now just hold on well you've got such a beautiful coat
okay what did you need sir
no that's a thought what he got off this is championship right here man
oh that was championship level fucking jumping
i wanted to hit my head on it i was also so wait hold on hold on hold on
it's only like a 50 dollar bounty i'm gonna sell all my shit i gotta go i'm
going back to where i was i mean this is a long way but
like i have to get back here i'm gonna just stop and eat here though
what's going on over here is that our camp or is that something else
okay hold on there's people here okay mask on no no no mask on
i gotta i gotta straighten up here a little bit guys
we're gonna make a friend what's he up what's he up to
how are you sure hey thanks man thanks plain big game this dude is dead
i'm not gonna kill this guy
uh i'm good let's do some venison can i give him some
been traveling so long world feels much smaller now
need one more thanks for the fire man been quiet up till now
i'm just kidding what does it got in here though
nothing nothing really abuse well let me i want to feed the horse
hit him far away with the throwing up if you see me try to attempt that like
30 times now i can now rear with this horse i can do
this nice all right let's go
i was trying to yell them almost the camp what's the point of the rear
that's a good question i'm actually not sure
fuck i made it hold on a second here dead he's dead what am i tracking
unknown animal unknown animal interesting so am i going this way i
guess we're going this way still on the right path right yeah
is that it right there that's the animal
what is this thing is it a bug oh it's a rat
it's a rat okay well cool somebody else died here study the
rat i didn't kill this lady pick up
who died how did you guys die out here
i didn't kill these people did i i mean there's no loot option
you got anything in the buggy no okay well i found a rat
people die jeremy well yeah but there has to be a cause somewhere
what does this want me to do in here my control is vibrating right now
i'm not sure why follow the rat focus on why am i focusing on the rat track
i'm trying to catch fucking rat in the field and this bandit's about to come
stop and yell at me all right i was trying to catch a rat out
here mister where'd he go there's like
there's so many trails now there he is there i caught the rat just gonna
put him in my pocket okay there's another animal over here
oh it's is that my animal i dropped a few frames
well we've been going for about five hours now i'm so i'm actually
happy with how stable it has been i gotta keep going
does motor investigate at the body is there
it's definitely these people here the first one
no the dead guy the everyone over here is dead they're all dead guys
oh i can inspect that what am i doing my painting this
chapter show gang savings creeping time alaskan ginseng why did i want to draw
this dinosaur bone okay that's pretty crazy
your dead eye bars increased trick shots hunting grafting and other
survivalist related activities yeah you found a dinosaur bone look out
for more of these on your travels they might be of use to you at some
point one of 30 that's pretty sick i could
loot something here it was on the other side what could
i loot there it is this guy got letter from cornwall
inspect the document very regrettable that you've rejected the various
extremely generous purchase offers presented you by cornwall
i'd be very concerned about a company of your size being able to continue to
compete on a price of the state of new handover
to secure acceptable rates for railroad transportation
so they killed him that's unfortunate that's
not cool that's the guy that i robbed what
that's not a guy i robbed three horses huh
which one is fast he robbed his train oh okay
did he find the unknown animal yeah it was a rat it was really nothing uh
spectacular will they just shoot you oh look look who it is
hi john well glad you're on the man sounds good
crafting fire to the edge of camp we've got uncle
122 all camp funds let's go ahead and i'm gonna sell some shit
nothing to see what are you looking for what do you want me to do
rouse's business is not too glamorous but it pays
please son for me dad okay dad what's your
oh wait but this uh this reverend
perfect perfect perfect perfect pronghorns
do it rapid donate for funds uh yeah just take it make sure you get a
good price for rat meat many thanks mr margaret so this
is the little casino table is opened up here
poker so contribute no i need money morning arthur i need to go like a
heist or something let's go to uncle i do still only have 79 cents
i'm not gonna gamble with my last 79 cents
over here me too somebody over here oh hello uncle
careful not to work yourself one way to do it there uncle i was thinking
yeah does it pay well eventually so while the rest of us are busy
stealing killing wait this is the actual first mission
you get to think all day are you serious
where are we living arthur morgan now you want to head into town see if we
can find anything else sure i got some areas to run great go
check the horses are ready if you're gonna take the old man
into town you can take us too well what do you
got planned nothing we'll find something for y'all to do
we always do we're bored out of hydra i got a water right here
cooped up here for two weeks now karen's about ready to murder grimshaw
can miss grimshaw spare you can miss grimshaw spare you
was i just fucking off for the past four hours very young healthy women
want you to take them arriving you're going about house i was doing
missions let's go i was going to places i was doing
things it was
falling down a few times
let's go what's after bond hive them all off a cliff
almost just caused a wreck right there it was close
the ladies got whipped right in the face
letting the top left oh shut up i don't want to hear this anymore
slow down oh no his coach broke down
very serious so do it what's going on
down the cliff right there friend hello you couldn't help me get my other
horse back from over there could you
i'd really appreciate the help you can give me money
here will bolt on me too if i leave them i might make some money here
that'd be good thanks it's the white one over there
all that whoa easy easy back to the owner come here come here
come here this way see you're good come on
well it's a pet and then press oh standing behind the horse you're good
come on punch the horse i'm not punching the
horse you don't have to look at it i well i
just i'm trying i want to look at it you don't have to look at it here
here you go money you heard gentlemen sir a gentleman
ah trying to impress the women well anyway thank you so i did a good
thing see everybody thought all i do is bad
things i just like to shoot people throw people off cliffs and everything
that was a good deed
i was holding down r1 to make whatever oh my stomach
how do you fuck up dying by dying i don't know man
i went a little too far and i was holding r1 tipped over
at the last possible second and i i didn't i and i have to
say help that guy again no i'm just gonna run him over fuck me in a good guy
i already did it we know we we're not doing it again he didn't give me any
money
right before no we're gonna hear this again do it again to punish yourself
all right get over here i'm being kind i didn't even do
get the mission yet here here you go he was checking for the train
no i was just trying to impress the women
okay back at it again i thought i was gonna throw them off i'm just like no
don't do it you're turning into a regular old fairy godmother there arthur
what's that supposed to mean it means you got a heart a small deep and
silent trains not even here guys no just do the mission forget it
forget it yeah yes there there's the train
yes it's here i'm trying to hit the guy
god damn it oh i was trying to run away
oh i'm just i'm just driving by the guy again i don't even hit the guy
and knock him out like extract a tooth out of the train
we're going right for the fucking mission man no bullshit go
do it okay well it's not the end of it help the guy
bring the horse back right just go don't the train is gonna i have this one
track fucking mine get the fucking just hurry up and get
him calm down he's fine agitated horse
easy easy easy you're good study come with me is there a reason
why you're what the fuck was that get it
turn on the face cam why where did he go
here you go thank you you're a gentleman sir
a gentleman no not really i was just trying to impress the women
regular old fairy godmother there arthur
forget about the fucking train and you haven't you're hit the guy off the
train i'm not going to hit a guy off the fucking train
okay we're fine
stop it stop that see what we got
main street get some bounties
let me push the guy over that's i gotta push that guy over i gotta knock into
that guy no not in this boy
will you remember that though why am i in hell
i don't know what do you mean why am i in hell watch where you put in
that thing i'm not getting like arrested right
now am i why did i just whip the horse
just like i said cultural center of civilization
man at his finest okay here i'll change the i'll change the scenery here
self-respect the maniac does what the women do work with pleasure
we'll start of the salute okay just stay out of trouble don't get yourself
much we'll see at the general store when you're done
this is still on my phone come on so that's how you see yourself is it
it's a maniac follow uncle i used to be known as the
one-shot kid there blue no let me state that was better i'm not gonna ask why
this feels more western doesn't it sad man arthur morgan
desperately you're my favorite parasite
that's better no we look like we belong in the west
you're my second favorite parasite very funny
i lied it's too dark then rats with the plague then you shut up
i mean i i could turn on like the nintendo switch mode if you want
like i got switch lights i got xbox lights
i've got ps4 lights i mean which one do you think i'm gonna do here
come on i'm not on the switch though so why would i do that are you joining
me or not all right i don't fucking fail this
mission morning what are fortnight colors so
what do you need drop a whiskey for start
something to pass the time while we're waiting on the women
yeah that guy should probably steer clear of the saloon this time
yeah i got no okay wait for me outside when you're done
i'm going to wreck it let me know if you have any questions fellers
all right shopkeeper i need to sell i have i'm selling a ton of shit here
all right sell coffee what else i got a lot of random shit here don't i
you won't take any of these the rings and shit okay miracle tonic
what about the gold will he take the gold cigars
i have a couple of these what is milk what do you reckon
lamb or a sausage well this here's a sheep town the lamb's the best in the
state now i know what the smell is well that's
a ripe cheese health core moderately mr stamina core
you're actually buying for once 75 cents for one of these
horse medicine got no respect for their elders no more
go to a fence that's selling look at this a jaw harp
what is this list of yours i got a lot two bucks that's a full heel but awful
time in the mountains all done thank you kindly ah
this should do the trick yep that's fine whiskey
just keep one of everything let's go wait for the that's probably a good
idea ah i sold it okay back at 25 bucks
and then take the free money out of the register right
how did i fuck that up because i said two would i just i don't know
hair pomade what does pomade do slick back hair yes
i'm gonna take a bath get bath and i'm gonna slip slip my hair back
oh here's to your good health sir and to being down here off that mountain
absolutely it's a funny world you know this time my cell miracle tonic by
married to an heiress
like a servant girl usually works someone was saying her sister was
taking a trip from new york or some place
it's like too big right rich tourist heading to sandin and then cruising
off to brazil okay a train laden with baggage and
passing through a bit of deserted country at night
i don't like doing this in time for the tides in some place called scarlet meadows
yeah i know it yeah scarlet meadows right it's real quiet out there sounds
good we're still in care i think at the hotel
they were picking up some drunken fellas that they was gonna rob
why it seemed easy they haven't gone for quite a while
not here like in the game i'll hear too but there's tilly over there
does not look ideal excuse me sprint get in get your hands off her friend
who are you a friend of mine get off her
or what exactly you want to find out you're making a big mistake tilly
jackson just get lost i ain't doing
uncle mary best they're across the street
the kid i feel that that was a i i i sucker punched him he was being a bad guy
so i wanted to push the bad guy over
get your hands off her who are you the hell off a bitch
hey there's no problem here be if you don't get out of here right now
good timing you're make tilly jackson just get
stabbed face game is in the way of options
all right let's go to the hotel jesus holy shit that was an entrance
uh i'm looking for somebody
who came in here earlier with a drunk fetter mid-20s blonde you'd remember her
yeah they're in 2b upstairs are you uh a friend of his
a friend of hers friend of hers no the options move your face
how about i just get out of here completely what purpose no that's like
ammo and shit i can't be anywhere can i not i can't be up here right
can i be up here get the hell out of sorry wrong room
how did you lock it that quick bust through it
hey get out of here buddy i paid they paid the hitter
you goddamn animal come here hey i thought that guy was pathetic
trying to play him not very well okay fine you sure
yes let his face fucking smash into the ground
men but stupid bastard stupid bastard was boasting about the bank
sure i know small town banks are usually a waste of time but
desync is back stock town why okay keep investigating
i will okay he's a peanuts okay another nothing
i don't know why i look like dante from capcom series
dante uh devil may dante may cry dante devils may cry i can't open
this door i hope everything's okay up there after you dante may cry
thank you arthur i don't much like being saved but
when i have to be i understand you okay
sure he only punched me arthur punched him a lot harder
all right now hey who's that guy over there looking at us
weren't you in blackwater a few weeks back it's benny from
uh vegas you were well i definitely saw you
with a bunch of fellers me no impossible listen buddy come here for a
minute i saw you come here cool get
i don't like this me neither go get the girls home
i'm gonna go have a word with our friend be careful that's not my horse
where's my horse please not a horse man
okay well that's fine now let's lasso this guy
why are you telling lies about me no no i've got it wrong partner
i got it very wrong now please step on his fingers
i ain't never been in chasing me i've got an unfortunate face yes
me too now please pull me up please all right i'm gonna step on his
fingers all right come on i don't know what's
going on here you okay partner no no balls what
i literally like i've been throwing dynamite at people and fucking running
people over with my dude horse truck all day
i help one guy up and all of a sudden i'm a coward
i think it's best for both of us if we pretend this never happened
i agree you saved my life you're a good man and i uh
here you want a pen it's one of them steel ones
very kind of you that belt is not even on
that is four sizes too big jimmy brooks not usually
you see i kind of look like a clown i was in blackwater
i kill people and maybe i should have killed you
i definitely should have should i have killed you jimmy brooks
i never saw you no not now not not never
i think we have an understanding of course we do
jimmy brooks i will remember that i've got a good memory i haven't
haven't not not one lick not one since in this year old mind
come on come on you have a nice day now sir
i'm not gonna do it you can return the horse you stole
to its owner and valentine to gain honor i'm gonna do that
i don't want this thing this thing's where's my horse
all right i need i want to go back to valentine back here please 32
dollar bounty what is this comedy tragedy face here
show all right we're gonna do that first
show sounds like fun oh that would have killed the horse for sure
hello mr hey mr figured out a track real beautiful country
around this area
it's over in your homeland it's way back
got it there you are sir which one was the guy that needed the horse
you you whose horse is this you have trouble me
whose horse do i have whose horse is this
never too soon huh give me my actual horse please
i don't want this fucking guy do i have any more meat
no this is mine i can't fucking help it i'm sorry it doesn't
matter what game it is open if you give me freedom to do
whatever i want out of his mind i will never do the thing i'm supposed
to do it's it'll never happen i just i accidentally complete missions in
these games okay uh i got everything in
there was a bar fight over here at the saloon
this what is in here uh savings bank look out you've lost it
optional mission is available i can't have my fucking way
no okay the skull definitely gonna be a way to gain honor okay let's
let's run right here i didn't i i thought he was dead isn't
this back in the day you if somebody's
dead you they could take their shoes and shit
there were no rules is the guy gonna shoot me
i picked up loot on a guy's body who's this
what i've lost control i've lost control
i've lost control 67 dollars just die whose horse is this
just just come get me just come get me just come and get me just come and
get me how do i say i surrender who's screaming
but i know i'm not having a hundred fucking dollar bounty
anybody in here don't i coward i don't have any money to pay for this
this is how red i have to just die i had to just start punching the guy
don't just don't do it i did i started slashing people
okay i this is all because of the horse this guy but i didn't have my horse
they gave me this fake ass horse and then i saw the guy lying on the
ground dead so i looted his body and
apparently that's illegal why didn't somebody go pick him up
pick him up and if it's so illegal pick the fucking guy up off the street
bro that could have been a family member for all you know
97 dollars and then i got i got like panicked and i was in the bar and just
started blasting that old guy in the face
he was unconscious well okay there we go now i feel at home
whisper let's feed the horse the whole guy and then i just started
slashing people i can't help it like whenever
there's a scenario same thing when gta man i would just be
in on mission and i would just drive full speed and hit triangle and dive
out of the car it was so fun to me i couldn't do it
i had to do i had to now let's do this little side mission
sheriff's office let's do a bounty here for me
look here maybe this is our man you a bounty hunter mister maybe
make uh i'm gonna this is like the equivalent of when you go to a
restaurant and you just go there for some reason
you don't have any money and oh well you you owe 140 dollar bill to
the restaurant you're gonna go wash dishes now that doesn't happen if you
don't pay if you just sit there and you go to
eat for fucking free and you go well uh i could go in the back and wash
dishes and cut to you in the back of the
squad car tracks delinquents and reprobates like flies
and i'm not a feller to pass a quick judgment and i've been around
long enough to never sink to catch a sinner that's that trope
you're gonna be working in the back of the kitchen and i won't ask no question
there was no money so what is it you need why don't you
have a look at that poster on the wall over there
he's a low down huckster some poisoning folks with his miracle cure
from here to ansburg kill morton land in the rickets
without even pulling a trigger that's not the guy from the first game
sick satisfaction out of it filler over at the saloon says he thought he saw
him by the gorge straight north of here
you think you can bring him in the money's good
i need him alive though i want to make sure the women he just gave the
eyes like oh fuck i don't know what this guy playing
that's gonna be tough i'll see what i can do
well you know you're asking and we need him alive it's an important point
last on location of the bounty is marked with a skull
let's take a look he is far a 97 dollar bounty
let's go but before i don't have any money what am i talking about
buy some stuff i have a 97 dollar fucking person tab
because all the people i murdered is it worth buying a ps4 to play
this game well it's definitely worth buying a
ps4 in general because it has some of the best
games of this generation that is uh that is a fact
spider-man bloodborne i mean god of war list them list them all
two games i just named three games on the top of my head
i can't see that far good i can take this we can cut here
fortnight's on why would fortnight three those are three exclusive games
and by the way those three games i listed are arguably some of the best
games that come out in years bloodborne is the best game to come
out in like a decade you gotta get 10 years that's the
that's the one that's come out that's the one
the last of us oh god don't even get me started but bloodborne 10 years
all right hold on probably should get rid of the light get rid of the light
there's a guy up there does he match the description we got
here is that him that's him you benedict albright oh sir
huh kind of look like him i was told he'd be up here
no not me sir it's because i want to buy some medicine
and i heard him i heard good things don't be in gold i got gold you could
help me find him it's just my mother's real sick
and we could drop the theatrics and i could just punch him in the face that's
the case for a sick woman i'd be happy to help
i'm a healer you know a medical man finest medicine in the state
game's over mister put your hands up taking you in
taking me what for apparently that stuff you're pushing is killing folk
there's a price on your head i don't know it ain't my business
partner that's crap i'm a healer i got an aura i speak to spirits
i'm a scientist folks get real angry for no good reason
this this is he's gonna do the thing where he drops off the cliff and he's
fine they only want you for questioning
i have to insist that this is a mistake
don't be a fool
i'm slipping come on get up come on
what no he's fine he's fine fine fine fine fine i need that light i need the
lantern it's so dark where is he it's so dark i can't even see
where he is i don't go fast enough
is he live he's right over okay he's right there am i supposed to do
something about this do i need to let go don't don't drown
right i almost got away he's going back in the
water i'm healthy i'm not gonna be mad if i take
his wallet right three dollars miracle tonic and platinum
band back to the sheriff stole his wedding ring
riding through deep water where the hogtied pastor would cause them to
fall from the back of your horse and most likely drown
okay duly noted i will not go through the deep water
not gonna do that shit do i have to cross at some point here
i gotta cross over here is this deep how deep is this i just heard something
i heard the animal of some sort just stay on the road
i think i must be suffering from exposure
suffer a little longer i hear like wolves and shit
if i hit i'll kill him if i hit him like another
i don't not doing that again get him to the sheriff now
i'm gonna like scramble his brains
come here
no i don't feel so well yeah mr you know you know what i'm saying
i'm only in it for the money got him i wasn't expecting you back
and he brought him in
sleep it off buddy
are you enjoying this compared to the first game
yeah
and uh good luck it's been real fun you ain't much of a man you ask folks
for forgiveness you remember this partner
i've already forgotten now sure how much was you offered uh
fifty dollars here thank you madam please remember what i told you
not even enough to cover how much i owe the state that's
cool and what is this big puke stain here
what's up what's going on the map here hey you there
can i have a word what's up now this little craw don't look like one of
can i have a word oatmeal poor what i do i do
how am i supposed to fight three people at the same time i know
did i shoot myself did i shoot myself in the back of the head
no you suck at fist fights as four three people punching me in the face at
the same time that guy was that guy was going like
this all right let's try that again so
oh dread yeah oh dress goals are bad guys okay let's try this again then they
would all like hanging out in the front door
three goons
it's not a bunk mr calloway sir who's your friend there
put that in your fucking book play-doh this is gym boy calloway
the gym boy calloway who the gunslinger fastest left-handed
draw that ever drew breath oh then we're gonna do a uh
14 men in a fight at louisie hollow what are you waiting for
how do you mean well i reckon right now
kill him yourself i don't want to kill him i want to deify him
he's a god i'm trying to write his biography
how's that going i think i prefer the duel either i'd kill him and be able
to be baltimore's finest ever gunslinger
or he killed me and i could be set free from ever having to speak to him again
well you're starting to understand something very important what's that
the joys of gunslinger it's win-win freedom or glory
that's brilliant i'm gonna write that down if i may be my guest
where's your name i don't have it but you are a gunslinger
not really i mean folks who need shooting i try and shoot in the back
all that other stuff it's well bunk but you fought duels once upon a time
i may have and you ain't interested in fame
i don't think so strange but you like fortune
i need money sure okay and forgive me mister if i seem a little desperate
i am a little desperate this book money i gotta make a thing of it and
well there's a whole list of gunfighters legends
every last one emit granger flaco hernandez billy midnight
black bell never heard of them maybe you can go and speak to them
ask him about calloway any of them get up and eat
shoot him i can't believe i just said that but you want me to go and
find some sad deluded fools like him
ask if he was the greatest and then if they get
up at him shoot him does sound a lot worse than it did in my head
how much you paying well a lot half the proceeds of the book
if you help me get it written i'll see what i can do
oh get photos okay and there are notes on the back you got a camera man
that should lead you to him i'll see what i can find out i imagine
we'll be stuck here upon your return here are some other flop house
okay so inspect documents this is a whole is a whole can of worms
here married six times six gentlemen gamble
with robbers outlaws everyone last report citing uh bluewater marsh do
not approach too dangerous for mere biographer
all right well this is uh black belt all right so ladies and gentlemen
i believe we're going to call it a evening here
getting to be about 9 p.m pacific which is about midnight eastern
uh i'll give you my first impressions real actual real first impressions the
game's great i'm having a blast it's fun just
to dick around as you plainly see uh so what we about six
hours here we're gonna do bits and everything
so here's what's gonna happen over the next day or two
that this is the internet the internet fucking works great
right i'm at 6000 upstream stream looks good right
good bid rate barely dropped any frames the entire time
i think we might be in the clear here
um any okay anyways uh which one's mine
uh i so okay so i'm gonna see what star is doing
the next day and uh i think lethal league is probably gonna be the next
thing i play on the channel green screen stream if you haven't
uh if you don't know the horse the horse can die the horse can die the
horse can die hi quit the game okay um
so there's lethal league there's this again
i'm having a blast playing this you'll see this again green screen stream
is gonna happen probably within the next week
i'm gonna get a poll in the discord so i'm not i'm probably not
gonna talk about it too much more the next three maybe i'll
bring it up one more time but the recommendations suggestions for
all the actions for the green screen stream are gonna be in that discord
so uh if you haven't said anything or you want to contribute it's there
just you know that we already talked about the rules watch the vod from a
few days ago and that is gonna be it
so if the internet is working tomorrow
i'm gonna stream i'm gonna go as much as i can
so i'm gonna get in contact with some people we're gonna try to get some
streams together and then i'll see you when i see you
unplugging the console is the only safe way
you know that's that is true so uh let's move on to here
and let's go over the bits here is there oh there it is okay
because oh nice to see you stream
yeah i'm glad to finally get like an actual like full
five six plus hour stream it's been a long time
so it's good to be back hopefully we are actually back
and the internet does not fuck with us anymore over the next
couple of weeks it might i can't guarantee i can't promise that it's
going to be completely solved let's hope so because this is the
first time in a while that we've had a stable connection
so uh with that we're going to go back a little bit here
and we're going to do we'll do the credits last uh pocket pauline gave
50 dollars earlier thank you so much dude
it's a lot of fucking money 50 bucks in pocket pauline
devakitty gave a dollar hey germa your short stream of red dead
solidified my purchasing of a ps4 and i've been playing it ever since i
needed another exclusive on top of games like bloodborne and god of war
to justify it and when you blew that guy's head off
with a shotgun i figured i'd had to play it
devakitty thank you for the one dollar and yes
we haven't even we haven't even scratched the surface there's so much
shit to do but thank you thank you also to uh jabba dab again for your
massive amount of uh sub gifting tonight thank you man
kill ganon thanks for the dollar uh i watched three ads for these bits
i missed you buddy it is good to currently be back hopefully we can stay
live uh the cap david thanks for the one
dollar i was enjoying some mountain dew citrus blast
with a squiggly straw and i spilled it all off my desk and pants
thought my day was ruined then i saw you went live they instantly unruined
germa hart thank you i'm sorry about your mountain dew tm
trademark citrus blast i've never had it before
hopefully it's in it hopefully it's good uh devakitty again thanks for the
one dollar also good luck with red dead redemption 2 aka red dead 3
it's a shitload of fun also be careful spoilers ahead
dobby the elf from harry potter something happens to him but thank
you thank you after looks atrox for the
one dollar 25 welcome back sweetie it's good to be back
thank you for the dollar 25 mega move earlier gave
100 dollars 100 dollars from mega move thank you again what happens to him
and watch the movies or read the books but thank you mega move so much
uh just home boy thanks for the one dollar three weeks ago hurricane
michael hit my town county didn't have any power for two
weeks afterwards i called comcast to get
uh internet back but there's just a pre-recorded message saying to go on the
website to contact someone so someone would come out
but we couldn't do that because no internet
we still don't have internet i'm out of town and happen to catch you live
and contact them regardless happy to see you just happy to catch your
streams again and glad to see you safely in vegas
fuck comcast uh comcast i went from comcast to cox
and i'll be honest with you the what ain't much different unfortunately
like 80 to 90 percent of the entire country
is is made up of about three or four different companies
and it's just pick your poison of the companies that
actually care and give lightning fast stable service
they're only in little bits and bobs in the country
horizon files for example i will i will shill and praise the fuck out of them
every time they're only in a few places they're
only in like the northeast and then some sections uh out like
they can new york maybe uh google fiber that's you can't
nobody can i have this theory that google fiber doesn't exist
and everyone like oh yeah this place has google fiber
does it anybody have it no it's just there
it's in the middle of like texas somewhere you have it
well i'm glad somebody does but there are like a handful of internet
companies that aren't just the big box like best buy
internets but it's it's almost impossible to
avoid them when looking for places i've actually seen a quite a few
people comment on this about well why did you why did you move
to a place that has bad internet it there i mean it's not like it was an
easy thing to be like oh hey i'm gonna move into a house
and before i purchase a house or before i sign a lease agreement
i'm gonna buy internet install it and test it
that's just that you can't do that that's impossible
all you can do is just check speeds and check on
you know low where where location wise and how new is the infrastructure and
you can't like go move into a house and then buy internet and test it and then
oh you know internet doesn't really work that well
uh please tear by lease in half it's like what
you can't do that hey dude can i mind if i stream at your house before i
buy it ask the neighbors or something well here's the problem with that
because there's so many different packages
right your neighbor might not even have remotely close to what you need
so if your neighbor oh yeah like can i test your internet can i knock on your
door and test your internet i'm like i'm sorry i'm a fucking weirdo i need to
oh yeah we have 25 down like two up that's not gonna be a that's not
gonna work you just have to follow speeds and
the speeds i mean before we had all these
issues we had we had a gigabit line that's a thousand down it's just a
question of trying to fit with like okay there's a there's like a
problem there's like an infrastructural problem
in this whole like there's like five or six areas
that have like these major that they're being like fixed and maintained
and maintenance and uh it seems like it's done you know
what i'm saying we're this is the first time i've had
like 6 000 up green light the whole night
but uh italics and i desperately desperately have been keeping on
top of this every single day it's actually gotten in the way
of a lot of other things that we wanted to do
because it's been every single day we've tried to get it situated and
fixed and updated and uh it is not uh nothing to do with
us trying to oh this is not streamed for like three
weeks so cross your fingers it seems like
the problem has been solved i hate to say that out loud because
tomorrow i might wake up and it might be off but
you know i can hope right anyways uh that's the situation with that uh
ifs hey hey hey ifs thanks for the one dollar dude hope you're doing great
germa here's some bits well for being you missing for being
missing your streams dearly my friend i'm glad you're back
hope you didn't have to fight any stand users up
in that balloon stand users also your olive garden joke made me
audibly sigh what olive garden oh it's a jojo reference oh okay
uh sprio gave uh a bunch of gifted subs too thank you sprio
jab a dab again kazi gave five gifted subs earlier thank you so much
jason bromber loves cat girl thank you for the five dollars
i like vivio names barry jason thank you for that
thank you jason for the five dollars and the fact that you like video game
i don't understand what this is but thank you uh div usb thanks for the five
bucks cheer 500 no message thank you garf you're the monday killer thanks
for the one dollar my gosh germa garf hasn't donated to you
in ages garf has missed the germ in his absence ody was going nuts
without the funny boston man i had no clue balloon travel was so
stressful i drew you a picture of you in the balloon
for good fortune let's see happy trails happy trails and germa hart thank
you funny well i'm no longer here it is
i'm no longer a uh a boston man i'm no a las vegas man currently that
is but thank you as always garfield the
wombat from hell thanks for the one buck one buck it's my birthday today
cake and ice cream is on its way jerma thanks so much for that
advice you gave to my friend about not comparing themselves to you a few
months back it made a big difference and they're
tentatively streaming again happy halloween too will scary story man be
returning good luck with cox in the desert
are they true to caesar thank you wombat from hell and yes
there will be uh there will be a christmas special with bilou berry
he's been blowing my phone up like crazy he's so desperate to come back
on the stream uh he's gonna come to the christmas
special so which by the way there will be a
christmas special yeah that's pretty much that's that's
what you need to know uh but thank you wombat from hell and
of course for the advice to your friend thank you
house of noah thanks for the four dollar you've been gone way too long
i know i hope to remedy that thank you though
house of noah for the four dollars thank you lactose cal for the one
dollar another pirate game jerma pirate game are we talking about this
game thank you planet playstation for your
five six seven eight what eight or nine dollars in a row here
thank you planet playstation you can civil war
uh you can civil war reenactments you can civil war reenactments sell
them what was i talking about do the roar
ha got them will germa be the streamer to beat red dead redemption
two on stream use coyote piss to attract the bear
bear party boston maniac punches horse in face
local boston man falls off horse blames others for being incompetent
do the roar oh the bear i can't it's it
my i need to my throat it hurts my throat hurts oh what an excuse
and he's a very tender throat hey i'm in vegas now man the humidity is
like 18 every day sometimes lower
it's dusty but thank you planet playstation for your
almost ten dollars here appreciate it hunter with lemons thanks to the one
dollar here's some bits you dirty horse puncher
anyway have fun hey thank you hunter with lemons
i am having fun it's a very fun game uh nay mean nay thanks for the ten
dollars nay ten bucks from nay give your horse
a pet and a carrot she deserves it after putting up with all you shit
yes she does i think i gave the horse plenty of carrots what are you talking
about i gave at least two no i get apples
and like baklava i didn't give any carrots you're right i'm a bad fucking
father but thanks for the ten dollars nay for
real uh plasma player thanks for the five
dollars i was shopping at party city for halloween costumes when i saw a
picture of you on a liquid latex product liquid latex product that don't
that that don't even look like me come on this
that me that looks like me that looks like a
i mean maybe a little bit that's what i'm gonna be doing
in 10 years once streaming is over well i'm like
50 years old i've been streaming for 25 years i'm going into retirement i'm
gonna be the guy that's on the makeup containers at the party store
but thank you for that plasma player appreciate the five dollars as well
honey chain thanks for the one dollar germa watch out for the train
toe pack thanks for the three bucks i'm glad you're back partner i wish
you looked as good as this cowboy oh and he linked my my 500 subs curl
video 46,796 views
that video has only received views retroactively by the way
when i made that video and even a year or two later it had like
probably 600 views but anyways thank you till back
it's good to be back invictus 99 thanks for the five dollars please fix
your fucking sideburns easy easy i will thank you for the five
dollars hey e dragon thanks for the 10 bucks e
dragon great stream as usual save this from when you lose all your
money at the casino uh there are there are a lot of them
around here there are a lot of them i don't think i'll lose all my money
though but thank you so much for the 10 dollars
e dragon uh tyruku tyruku thanks for the one dollar love you germa you
made me smile during some rough times in my life
went away now i'm glad i can watch again i'm glad you're here
thank you for the one dollar and for the
kind message here thank you so much tyra much love to you
tingy thanks for the five dollars tingy resending the message i originally
posted on your first stream back again it's too long for twitch so here is
a screenshot let's see uh this is from this is
from tingy uh germa i've got some great news
recently just purchased my first house it's located in the boston area the
realtor told me it was used to be owned by a short old man who
used to yell a lot at his computer according to his neighbors apparently
just before moving out he also invited one of the neighbors over to
fake party or something he told me that he saw him outside as he got home
from work and invited him in offered champagne and made dumb jokes
i got this house for really cheap because it had
extensive deal anyways how do you move to vegas went smoothly
can't wait to see what streams you cook up in the future much love
yeah you had me for the first sentence and then i figured out what was going
on thank you tingy for the five bucks
thank you topac for the two bucks you gotta get one of your mods or
something to figure out why out the way to keep good vods from
getting deleted playlists or something it's awesome to have them saved
with chat yeah actually that um i just recently gave sort of the
go-ahead to that archive channel i talked to
the that archive channel briefly they've been re-uploading those
streams pretty much forever and while it's nice to have with chat
i know that i could probably highlight them and everything but
to be i would be completely honest with you here when you go to like
video the videos tab on twitch i kind of
i kind of like the fact that it's just the last like two months worth
of streams just because if otherwise it's it's
like just hundreds just scrolling down
hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of videos potentially
and they made an extension that you can save chat they're adding an
extension for it well i'll look into it and i don't
mean that as like the joking like bullshit thing that i say because
at one hand i know a lot of people already
go to that channel you know what i mean like most people are already
watching that channel and they're like oh hey by the way
like just don't even go there anymore i feel like that's there's a lot of
people that probably wouldn't even know that that was happening
and there's a ton of people that don't even watch this channel live
you know what i mean i i would actually assume a
a pretty large majority of people don't actually watch these live
or if you do you're here for a certain amount of time maybe you're
here the whole time however that may be but if you
only know about like oh i know that i can just watch the replays on this
channel and then you know what if i like just
randomly you just they just upload just stop happening on that
channel and then they just announce it like oh it's over
like yeah it's pulling back to twitch i feel like if it's not broke don't
fix it at this point right now and two months back with chat and then
after like the 60 days without chat
i mean i i just don't think there's anything i necessarily want to do about
it right now but um if there's an extension coming
out maybe it can be put on the side i really wish like
there was an easy way to do that without having to like
potentially like delete somebody's youtube channel that has like an
archive of hundreds of streams you know
and i would never do something like that we talked about it extensively
for a little while we'll see where it goes but uh
anyways let's let's keep going here we're getting to the end of this
section here just over midnight eastern time
but thank you topac thank you mazy kit for the one dollar it's probably a good
thing you didn't go to twitchcon because the line was so long that a
bunch of people didn't even get in also if you live under my bed or
something you can have google fiber what was i talking about i was talking
about uh vodz and how twitch deletes them
after 60 days and that there's a channel that has kept
pretty much all of them for the last couple of years at least
uh yeah i didn't go to twitchcon i had no plans to
i was in the middle of doing all this shit
there was no time to go to any conventions or any events
maybe twitchcon next year potentially i mean i'm gonna look close enough
we'll see i had i did hear that it was a little ridiculous though
and uh envious that you have google fiber thank you mazy
uh voluki thanks for the five dollars voluki hey jerma good to have you
back it's been super boring without your streams and
all i've done is dnd speaking of i showed our dm castle griffinstein and
he loved it so much he told me he was putting it in the campaign
we haven't gotten to it yet and i'm the only one who knows but we're
getting to it very soon our dm has sent me the actual map so
i could send it to you i've been trying to not look at it just
wanted to show you how much your videos have inspired others
let's see it's like really is the whole that's
that's so well i i don't want to spoil you here but
that's great there well if i'm gonna if i'm gonna put it in the chat
because this is like that's great the starting zone
into that little area i love how you even have the demon over there on
the edge one day there'll be another one one
day i hope you have fun i hope that's a lot of fun
you'll have to update us all after you do it
because i would be pleased to know that i'm sure a lot of people here would be
as well thank you for looking and have fun
keldos thanks for the one dollar imagine reading a donation that gets
worse and worse and two of the sentences structure and grammar
writ wit to a point of utter nonsense but
for real there's a halloween update for house flipper am i gonna play it
like that that went right to a question
that was just absolute nonsense and then like gotcha are you playing house
flipper again did it get actually get an update or is
it just you can paint jack o'lanterns you know
what i mean i'll look at that uh after the stream is over because i love
that game thank you keldos hey clueless sniper
what's going on thanks for the one dollar hey germa happy day after
halloween please enjoy this picture of my turtle
no what are all those what are those candies
those are interesting like i see that the kitkat i said by the way great
turtle kitkats marty's coffee crisp and that's
an orange did you put a candle in an orange
that's very very cute very cute how could you not like it
it has candies very true but happy halloween to you as well clueless
sniper thank you so much hey tingy again thanks for the one
dollar tingy i'm glad the internet held itself up tonight
but i might have had might have some bad news about cox
bad news about cox oh i love bad news let's see
all right what is the what's this oh let's see
a better internet um i bitched and moaned until i moved
that's all you can do yeah
cox in vegas is is hell it's terrible there's no fix you have to
get rid of cox that is the only cure
there was nothing we could i bought everything under the sun to try and fix
my internet new router new modem better service plans business internet
everything the only thing that fixed it was
moving if you're lucky and you have like
century link fiber or something then yeah you can switch to to a
different internet provider but if you have to use cox
you're screwed dude oh well
hey that's yeah
well i'm close enough to california now well it's just
what's another like couple hours the other way
this way hey we're green today that's uh unfortunate to hear that
from somebody else that also probably had all the problems
uh i was told with the utmost confidence
that they know what our problem is and it's
in the process of being completely resolved so
i don't know we'll see how the next few months go
we'll see oh that's that's um that's gonna be uh i'm gonna have
nightmares about that clip tonight anyways thank you for that tingy thank
you uh skull girls for the one dollar hey germ i made a donation for you to
see this on the first red dead stream but you got coxed i really spent time
on this and i want you to see it okay this is oh my god oh my god
why why is why is this a why is this a thing
really ladies and gentlemen welcome to episode
one of germacraft the series where i play minecraft
this is gonna be a single player let's play and when i say let's play i use
that term loosely because why did you fail
you're gonna see lots of triumphs at least i'm hoping so go grab yourself
this is 11 and a half minutes long i got apple cider right here freshly
game mode is gonna be survive survival that's the most interesting
war world options seed for world generator you're doing a really good job
i'm gonna name this something uh crazy to get hold on
gonna name it and see ah forever hold on sound has to be lowered
definitely we're going to explore it right now go
all right we're gonna try that again i don't know if you guys are actually
really home
remember this
now explain this to me all right all right i want notch to send me a personal
email and explain to me why there are cows
that are acting like mountain lions oh god each one of those cows in
just a minute at least four months wood got gino still
from mario rpg one of the best where the fuck is he huh
huh he better be a dlc character i'm gonna be real upset about that
he ain't dlc in the smash brothers game i'm gonna be very i'm gonna be
fucking sad as you could ever imagine
do
oh fucking god
i can't seem to reach this stupid piece of wood
so i gotta put some blocks down to get where i should i'm gonna chop
ah what is the whole fucking thing
speaking of like a pipe what for the rest of your life and i still am scared
when i like open my door to like go get the groceries i'm scared
that bully is gonna come get me i'm gonna make a little mine it's getting
late it's getting late and when it gets
late that's when germa starts to lose i don't think i've ever made it
past one in this game when people are watching
what are you over the age of seven what are you talking about i get the
hell out of here i kick your butt no the butt
sometimes it's just right on the edge of these mountains i am not pleased
by the way notice how i'm slowly trying to find a way to end this video
like hmm oh i'm not pleased oh where's coal
i need a sheep too i need wool being a real piece of crap
well there we go uh thank you so much for that
that was fucking like i what no no i don't know what that is
that probably took so long to make uh here is the
the full the full video uh thank you so much for that skull girls
i that was in 11 and a half minutes that took a month to make that
that took one full month of time holy shit
thank you so much for that just the fact that that that somebody made that into
that no that's that's fantastic man thank
you so much gondor lane thanks for the one dollar
this isn't book over adventures too germa i haven't forgotten
i'll play that in like in a year uh timmy tim tam thanks for the one
dollar hey germ my dog is injured right now so the stream really
brightened my day is there a way you can read the bits
from the past month worth of streams or they lost a time
okay thanks lots of love uh bye bye uh love you yep uh-huh love you
uh-huh bye uh well thank you timmy tim tam first of all
sorry to hear but your dog being injured
that does not that does not sound good hopefully it's nothing
too serious but i'm sorry to hear it nonetheless
uh to answer this second question uh there are all the bits are
recorded and saved but i i don't think i'm going to go back like a
month just because i don't think i i don't necessarily have the time right
now to do that they're there and i think with some
of this direction that i'm going to take the channel here
is uh well let's just let's just bring it up for a second
remember i told you guys about like the podcast thing that i want to do
where a one stream every like couple of weeks is
there's no game we just hang out for like three or four hours and just
chill talk about whatever the hell we want no no like oh i'm gonna have like
guests no just be us just hanging out every couple weeks
just that's all we do like a like a comb stream yeah
and portions of that comb stream could just
be you know going back and making sure i pick up the ones that i missed
that usually ends up that's usually what ends up happening anyways but
going into it without anything else uh it starts
that way and if we could like come up with
topics and shit to talk about i don't know i feel like i i like doing this
kind of thing but it feels this kind of there's
gonna be a lot there's gonna be changes
made to this channel uh not anything drastic but
i think i would much rather because let's be frank
the this is just the end of a stream right
very at the end of a stream the stream is over played red dead
and here we are doing like this whole thing right
i would much rather have this be a like a focus
like three or four times a month you know what i mean
instead of it being and i'm gonna use this word in quotes here
like tacked on at the end of a stream if that makes any sense
talking to chat comb cast comb cast oh god
but it wouldn't just be stream over sign there would be things to talk
about there'd be things to show and things to do
but i i much prefer that over oh how many how did i read that person
how did i read that i gotta make sure i read that you know i
it i don't i don't want it to feel like this rushed kind of tacked on
oh i got an hour to like blow through a bunch of people that gave me a shit
lot of money you know what i mean i'd rather it be
taking our time because people say dude when you do the bits man if you
just read right through them in 40 minutes it'd be fine but i like
talking about all this shit i like giving each one of these as much as
attention as i can and maybe we would make it a thing that we i just
we just did so a bit stream no no i mean like just
the hangout portion of the after streams is what i'm talking about
but that it wouldn't be something that would happen every other day it
would be you know once a week or once every other week
germ is designated give me money so i'll talk to you streams
and then on top of that there are i haven't really mentioned this
because i haven't really had an opportunity to be to be live for
more than like an hour or two but i currently all the all the
stuff that i've been talking about over the last couple of years
is is real now because at this moment right now i have a studio in vegas
that i'm going to be working exclusively with and it is a full
studio sound stages green screens and i've
already toured them i've already talked to them
multiple times so like all that shit that i've always wanted to do
is going to start happening so the stream is going to start to take
some different directions because that stuff is going to be available for me to
do and i want it i want something like
that to happen more potentially once a month or more
than once a month so dynamically we're going to have to
start to change how this stream is presented right
and we'll figure that out as we go it's not something that i i have no
oh yeah this is what's going to happen and this is this is final and
i'm never going to play red dead 2 ever again
green screen stream monthly we talked about this in
in depth about the direction that i want to take the channel and slowly over
time i'd like to make it a reality and the internet's
dying uh-oh oh we still live that was uh that was a
full-on that was a full-on drop there we're back
we're here uh just kind of shit the bed for about
two seconds there pause and unpause all right well uh that might that's
like that's like the curt that's like the curt why did i just the
first time i've heard that noise all stream
that's the first time i've heard that fucking noise the entire stream and it
just scared me uh anyways that's i think that's like
the curtain call here the cane is coming out to try to
drag me off the stage so let me let me get through the bits
quickly after we'll talk about this uh thank you uh
thank you to lucas for the 15 thank you lucas 7151
uh thank you 15 bucks is red dead worth getting an xbox or ps4 to play
in your opinion it looks incredible uh i mean that that's up to you
if if you think that it's worth i mean there are a lot of i don't know if i
would buy an xbox to play red dead but a ps4 at least has a bunch
of great exclusives so far uh i would i think it's if you
played the first one it's more of that and
much larger and much more going on but thank you for the 15 dollars i
wish you luck in your decision on whether or not you'll buy
ps4 has a lot of great games though and i'm sure there'll be some kind
of black friday sale like right there always is and that's
less than a month away but thank you dark star thanks to the dollar 50 dark
star 700 000 games i'm so glad you're back and that my
off-handed comment months back about a green screen stream has now turned
into a big community event love you vegas boy thank you
yeah and you don't think that people in this community come up with great
shit we've we've like talked about stuff
in this chat back and forth randomly that if that's
turned into whole streams i love it it's fucking awesome and i
want more of it you know what i mean it's 200 bucks
for ps4 and spider-man that's pretty great
but thank you dark star and thank you gold ruby productions
glad i escaped vinny's dryer thank you
uh eaves thanks for the one dollar i'm sorry for always saying shitty jojo
references all the time but i love you jeremy your streams make me laugh
a million times more when i'm absolutely sloshed off of screwdrivers
well screwdriver ain't a bad drink except i i love orange juice so i
can't drink because it ruins orange juice for me
but they're all good uh zaza salt thanks for the one dollar you're pretty
funny and cute hey thank you thanks for thanks for
that flathead or philip said philip said
for large projects flathead for small projects uh anti snowman thanks
for the five dollars anti snowman hey germa i'm a radio dj at a small
town radio station and we often have technical difficulties including the
internet going out tonight your original red deep redemption
stream attempt is one of my favorite streets because i could really relate to
the pain and stress be encouraged that even when things go
badly it helps others know that they aren't alone
thanks for the entertainment yeah mint i think
thank you for the five dollars first of all and
yeah it sucks it sucks being at the mercy of
uh here's and here's the problem being the mercy of a bunch of
companies that just as long as they get their
monthly fucking sign up paychecks from the
millions of customers and they don't who cares right that's the problem
it's unfortunate because there are like so many things that could just be fixed
if it wasn't just like quick quick quick quick quick how many signups did
we have last month oh 100 000 more dude i want 500 000
signups sir uh there's not even that many
people that live in that neighborhood double them up tell them they need
two internets and tell them that they need two tvs too
and how many signups is that that sir that's that's 1.2 million signups
how do you want to have to get more signups
um i did there's no more people we'll make some more people up
start putting internet in the fucking dirt and give it to the bugs
start charging the fucking ants for internet i'm confident that we'll be
fine hello i'd like two internets please
sure have one but what can you do besides you know hope that the cable
companies lose their insane darth vader grip on the
internet it might take a while it might you
know they might get to a point where you know
5g is coming out here but 5g 6g that shit's gonna be faster than cable
eventually when like the like the wireless uh cell phone tower
shit is gonna be more powerful than cable and then we get to do it all
over again whatever it is what it is thank you
too where we are now but anthony snowman
thank you so much we are all in it together in the
internet uh internet of stuff right we all have to uh have the
good stuff and the bad stuff when it comes to internet unfortunately
but thank you foot fungus for the one dollar topac for the one dollar
can you play visage i'm not sure if you talked about any halloween
specials even though we missed it visage is that what's visage
i've never heard of it internet of stuff
but thank you uh topac thank you also to mostly loss for the
one dollar here you say i'm gonna get through the bits quickly every single
time and it literally never happens but that's just me telling myself i have to
hurry up and then i slow back down right but
like i know at least i know and we're almost done because timmy tim tam
just gave two dollars how long you gonna stall till the
next mission of la noir you've been stalling with this balloon
shit for a month that is la noir is still it's uh that's
right that game is fucking funny too and
fun we got a lot of catching up to do let's put it that way
uh shoot man too thanks for the one dollar hey jeremy great to have you back
speaking of dumb ideas if you consider doing a 360 degree vr stream
where it looks like the viewer is sitting in your lap
well i don't think i don't think i don't think i want to do that
well this is giving me a headache coughing at that thank you shoot man too
uh maybe for some other purpose but not for
people sitting in my lap uh chore dungle thanks for the one dollar
i'm all with you jeremy on these cable companies who is with me in chat to put
ceo's these companies out of business so you guys they've
bad internet um it'll happen with 5g and 6g people people will start to
realize that you know like a two hundred dollar
a month internet bill you can eventually you're going to be
able to get that just through the air from a cell tower and
it's going to be like a hundred dollars less expensive we will see in
the next decade a like a absolute just collapsing of cable
companies just clip this and then like a decade
go man man that guy that was like as smart as socrates
came up with that thing about like the cable companies going down in 10
years oh here's like the exact uh clip of it but yeah thank you
toward uncle thank you tippy tim tim again
can i have my dollar back i only wanted to cheer once
i don't have the capability to to do that i can't just go
rebunded i'm sorry thank you be careful next time
thanks for the three bucks uh hey eaves thanks for the one dollar make
sure you also play delta rune at some point also you
taste like a liar when did when did you taste what
oh i'm really drunk oh okay thank you eaves hope you had a good night
take care and finally app key thanks for the one dollar hey jerma thanks
for all the streams the last streamer i watched
banned people for slipping up thanks for being you
uh like i've told you guys before i like having an open
chat here and yeah i just just just just do your best you know what i
mean just do your best feels birthday man
happy birthday and now we are going to end the
stream by like this hold on
uh is this gonna work uh-oh this might not work
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait hold on hold on okay and that should be it here come the
credits oh here they come thank you to all these
people that's up today all of you a bunch of people were
gifted subs and a ton of people resubs old subs
oh shit load of you that's fast uh mr comcast is up there thank you
guys so much i didn't set this up correctly
apparently in the time i had before the stream
but all of you rock we've talked about uh i see a lot of the same names
and i've seen a lot of the same names for years like and that that
that guy just came in for eight months
a ton of you guys have been paying me five dollars a month for
two plus years that's longer than i think i've had a netflix subscription
you know what i mean seriously you guys are fucking awesome
thank you for your patience thanks for bearing with the uh
all the shit the moving uh internet and i hope you stay
tuned because there's a whole lot of shit going on
over the coming weeks and months that i hope is worth it
and i've been saying that for a while but now i'm here i'm in las vegas
and it's real look at all these fucking subs thank
you i've seen you around so much it's like
seen a regular yeah at the giant bar let's hope this is the start of the
actual return of streaming i wasn't talking to you
shit oh holy you guys sometimes the stream
over the course of six or seven hours will pull like three or four
hundred subs that's that's fucking mind-boggling
that just it it blows my mind every time i see it
even if the internet's worse vegas still has
all the stuff that i want to do and also remember
by the way first thank you all of you guys for your either new support or
continued support it's fucking means a lot also keep in mind
a bunch of all these streams are going to be on location
so you know oh this internet problems here they won't be
where i am going to be making most of these things
i'm confident that we'll have a solution here don't worry it will be
solved and finally here wrapping us up uh topac thank you for the three dollars
cheering for you to stay i'm here and i read it
i am still here thank you topac thank you yep so for the one dollar hope i
get to see you at some point at some con
now that i know you're in the west i'll be around at least to the west
coast stuff i'll be the stuff that happens in los angeles i should be
around hey and then this self bar came in with the new sub
i'll be around foot fungus thanks for the one dollar
timmy tam thanks for the one dollar how much of my sub money have i gambled
away zero but that's gonna be it guys
i'm glad i got to do at least just like a seven hour like
actual full bulky stream you know what i mean
we are tentative and i've said that before
the schedule is out the window for the moment
i'm gonna make a new schedule i'm gonna update that screen that when
it's offline so tentative schedule we're out the
window we're not it's not oh tuesday there's a friday 7 p.m eastern that i
i'm gonna remove that maybe you'll see me tomorrow if not
then i'll see you very soon we'll be playing red dead
we'll be playing lethal league this still like this like mario party
and shit this that oblivion green screen stream another thing
like this i'm back baby and i'm ready to go
thank you guys so much have a great rest of your night probably see
you tomorrow take care hearty hobbit thanks for the
one dollar see you guys soon