Hello there ladies and gentlemen, it's Grandpa here. I took over the Minecraft series for
Jerma. So let's, um, I've never played this game before. I have no idea what I'm doing
so like you're gonna have to give me like a couple seconds to figure out what the fuck
is going on here. Okay, I got some slime balls, got some rotten fleshy to play with. So what
are you doing this game? What do I have to do here? So I have decided I'm going to build a farm.
So let's corral these fucking cows. Come here cows. Okay. That's not how you sing that song.
Okay, so you stay here. Get the fuck, get over there. I need to make a place where these cows
hold on a second. Do I have anything? Yes, I do. Okay, so let's make a farm. I'm gonna corral these
cattle and make them do my bidding. Okay, come on. We know you want to see the outside world,
but that's just not gonna happen. Get the fuck over here. Get over there. Get over here. Come
here. You're in big trouble. Your name is Bessie, by the way. You know what? Um, I'm just gonna
fucking kill you. Oh, hey, boys. How you doing? Nothing just happened over there. Just me and
Bessie. We're having a talk about her recent school studies. And okay, so get in the get in
the tank over here, George. That's your name. Your name is George. George, get in the tank.
Hey, Mortimer. Mortimer, look over there for a second. Fucking stupid cow. Okay, looks like,
hey, Mortimer. You okay? We're good here. I got you all set up. I got, uh, uh, George just had to
go to the bathroom, so that's why he left. You know what, Steve? You can have your own little
pen over here because you're like a, you're a nice cow. Shit. Sand. Okay, Steve, this is your little
pen here. Got nothing to worry about. Okay, so that's your pen, Steve. What the fuck? This
game looks like it's made out of Legos. What the hell is this? Like, look at this. This is beautiful.
This is a beautiful game. Why didn't I play this before? Look at how magical this is. Everything is
so vast and amazing. I want to go look at that over there. Hold on. Wait, I, I didn't know you
can fucking die in this game. You can die. I didn't, oh, I, hold on. So where's, where's all my stuff?
Oh, you piece of shit. Um, so what do you guys want to do? No, I don't, I don't want to go to the
playground. I want to go to see the new mountaintop. What do you want? No, no, I don't care about your
stupid door to door salesman thing. Get out of here. What are you looking at? So somebody told me
that Jeremy usually sings a song when he plays this game. So I'm going to try my hand at that.
Let's see if I'm a good singer like he is. I guess I could, I could talk about the bugs that
are in the water right now. There's a ton of bugs in here. Okay, so let's get a beat going.
The bugs look so stupid and they stink.
And then we go to the bug water fountain and I drink and then I fucking puke because bug water
tastes not very good. Oh, look at this. It's an underwater cave. This is beautiful. I wonder
if I could make it. What was that? What the hell was that? Oh my God, it's a spider. I fucking hate
spiders. Get the fuck away from me. I hate spiders. Oh, oh, that was intense. So see you later,
everybody. I literally have to go to the doctor so I can't stick around anymore.
This game's kind of fun though. I would like to play this maybe never again because I'm not that
good at it. I'm terrible, but I have to go to the doctor so you look at my colon. So see you later,
everybody. Have a wonderful day. Bye.