I look like shit right there. Can I take a better picture? Why is it the same picture?
Oh no, I got sucked into the comic book. Come on. Let's go. Come on. Come fight me.
Get fucking slapped.
Yeah, you want to see how we do a backflip into the devil slap?
I got two. I got to fight two of them. Just come closer. Come on.
I'm just going with the slaps now.
Got the kick. Oh, she just kicked me right in the face. What the fuck am I doing by the way?
Why am I like sitting on the ground? Got to use the uppercut.
Again with the power punch. I'm not kicking him.
Yeah, did you see that kick? Where did I end up? How did I get up here?
Alright, how do I get down? Like I got to jump over again, right?
Shit. Can I go down like this ladder? I don't think I can go down the ladder.
I'm stuck up here. What the fuck? Here we go.
I'm back up here again. What, the boxes?
Give me the box. Give me the trash can.
Oh, fuck it. I just hit my hand on it.
That's what I call the window washer. Get cleaned up.
Who's left? Oh, you? Oh, you? I saved the best for you.
Shit. This game's fucking hard.
Stay low. Dude, look at that. How are you supposed to beat this guy unless you stay low?
I can't even see what's going on on the screen. All I know is I'm picking his ass.
I literally beat him. I beat him. Victory.
Can I just say, I'm getting really tired right now.
Because unlike any other game that's like this, I really have to fight these guys.
It's not like I have to like pretend punch. I have to really fucking punch these guys.
I have to like actually throw swings, you know, and fucking ground pound.
Is this how fast I can fucking run?
I'm back. This time I'm brandishing a weapon.
This lightsaber or $4.52 grocery store Whipple Ball bat is going to help me achieve victory.
Just call me baseball player.
Did I die?
Even with a baseball bat, I broke something.
It was a lampshade. Don't worry.
See what I got? Out of here.
See what I got in my hands? It was a ball bat.
Fucking God. I can't use this.
Here we go. Nice and easy.
Just like you're hitting the ball up midfield past the second baseman.
And you can queue up a power attack in a second.
Right when he's at pretty much like low health, we're going to queue up a power swing for a home run.
Here we go. This is what we're going to do. We're going to step into it.
We're good. Hey, hey!
This is stupid. This is extremely dangerous.
Like what I'm doing right now could be the dumbest idea I've ever had.
Hey, let me go buy a Whipple Ball bat and like put duct tape all around it so you can see it so I can just break all this shit in my room.
What was I thinking? What was I thinking?
What was I thinking? Seriously, what was I thinking?
I don't even need that weapon.
See? I'm actually doing better without the weapon and my shit in my room is intact.
One more.
Shit, I missed. I got him.
What a dumb idea.