Good afternoon. Welcome back. Red wizard. Today we're going to be doing a few things.
First of all before we really get into that. Did you have a good sleep? I did. I said that really
fast so you may not have caught that. I didn't. Remember how they had that headache last night?
Well it evolved into a migraine overnight and I've taken a few Tylenol and I'm all right.
I'm good. I just can't laugh that hard. Although like what a what a bad day to have a headache
because that's not possible. I'm gonna have to. I wish there was a way I could put like a filter
on my brain. I wish I could like take in a video file and like have it pre-screened and
pre-rendered and then like drip feed it into a part of my brain. Green screen movie night is
tonight. So like I gotta be ready. So I'm taking in some caffeine. I'll be fine. I
think I've took a couple Tylenol. I'm good to go. I wouldn't be here if it wasn't. If
I wasn't able to do it. So don't worry. What is green screen encore night? Well that's why we're
gonna we're gonna wait a little bit. I'm not gonna do it right away. There are about 50 plus
videos. Some of them are like 10 seconds. Some of them are like three minutes. There
are a couple of exceptions from some community members that have given us some movies
that are a little longer. It's the encore presentation will be about an hour and a half
to two hours. No it is not. 50 JoJo videos. So if you're not aware of what's going on
back in four or five months ago. Oh a long time ago. We watched about 400 green screen
videos. Since then people have made some good shit. So I obviously want to show those
the high quality submissions. There are still some shit posts in here. But we had a system
we weren't going to show every single one. This playlist will be publiced so you can watch it
whenever you want after this stream. And we will be doing this in like an hour. Because I
don't want to just start right now and go. Because obviously I want as many people that
will trickle in that want to be here to be here. So after about an hour I expect
most people that knew it was going to happen for the last three weeks will want to be here.
You know what I'm saying? Makes sense. Trickle. Make a playlist with every video that you
skipped. That's probably going to happen too. So there'll be just like a here's everything
and then here's the stuff that was on stream. It should be fun. I'm looking forward to it.
But before we do that, we've got some Super Mario to play. Super Mario Sunshine. I don't
know why I just said that. This is Mario Maker. Let me warm up with a couple of levels and then
from here we're going to do the online stuff. This is not going to be the castle building
stream. I promise. Everyone's just like oh no no no no what the fuck. He's not going to do
like Mario Maker single player just story mode again. Well I am. But just for like five
minutes. So I also have to check this too. One two three jump jump jump jump. We good?
Good. Five hours. What if I just don't do the Encore Knight? I get so into this. We just don't
ever do it. March of the Rookie Toads. This is another Peach level. Ten Toads. I wouldn't do that
to you guys. Don't have to go all the way to the left. Oh shit what's this? One two three. How
do I get that? What's this? Can I like pull this up? I'm not going to do that. Yank it?
Can I wait can I yank that thing? No there's no indicator. I can't yank it. It's probably
to be lit up. Let's get rid of the piranha. I want to see what's down here. Reach the goal after
defeating all piranha creepers. You got it. You got it. So somewhere around I don't want to say
maybe like 430? Five pacific? 430 pacific? Oh I'm gonna know when it's been like an hour or
two because people are gonna be screaming in here. It's Encore Knight! I just I'm not
supposed to yell it. I have a headache. What does this want me to do? Oh shit that's what it
wanted me to do. Huh? Did it. First try. Yeah that was fun. That was a good one. I think that's
enough warming up. I think I know what I'm doing. I mean if I can do that I can definitely
like have somebody honk a horn in my face and scream while I go through 18 different doors
and have them open up and have like spikes underneath me. I think I can do that. This is
new. Oh I have this item now. I can do this. What the fuck is under here? Empty? What am I
doing? Oh this is a robot. Rebooting system. I'm sorry. Sorry. Well I turned it on. Interesting.
All right what's on the other side? Coins. Well I can't really leave yet. Hold on. Encore
Movie Knight's like paused for a minute. Hold on. Can I not break these? Beep beep. Rebooting
system. Beep beep boop. Reboot complete. Beep beep beep. Authenticating mustache.
Beep authenticated. Beep boop. You are Mario correct? No. Beep boop lie detected. Mario confirmed.
Beep boop beep beep. I'm a robot that plays videos. Which video do you want to watch?
Oh that's it? Beep boop beep boop. I'm going to play Encore Movie Knight. That's too bad.
Why am I even? No I don't want to skip this video. So 50 dollars came in from some guy.
Thank you some guy for the 50 bucks. They say hey Jerma I think I found a family picture of you
from a while ago. That'll be weird. Oh okay. Thank you so much for the 50 dollars first of all.
And oh okay it's a clown thing. And Jerma told the truth about X. What is it X?
Oh that was a juicy one. That was a juicy one. Anything you want it to be.
Well thank you for the five community subs and thank you some guy for the 50 bucks.
Now there's a picture of a clown. I don't know like here's the image. It's just like it's like
a family of the clown with like a kid in a clown costume. I don't know. All right I'm
ready for online. Course world. Let's go. All right so courses. Should I just do endless
challenge for a little bit? Just see what happens. Or should I do like one of the
popular ones? So this is hot. This is called jungle. It takes 23 minutes and 46
seconds to go through this level. Oh no that's the time. I told you I don't do military
time. Short and sweet. Let's do it. Play. Jungle. Do I have to jump up on this thing's head?
I can't touch this stuff. Oh I guess we're just riding this up. No but wait what? That's it.
I win. Short and sweet. Okay that wasn't fair. Well I need the key. So how the hell. Are you
gonna make a mushroom? Just like you. Aw. Thank you. How do you feel uh comic chameleon? How do you
how do you feel? How do you kill? What's this guy's name? How do you kill uh comic chameleon?
I have to wait till he's gone. Jump on his head. He's got a magic wand. And don't. Wait.
Wait. See he disappears. This ice. They're really. This is good level design with the ice.
Good level design with the ice. What? I couldn't. Oh it's a boo. Since when is boo like bright
fucking purple? Oh dear. Is there gonna. Hurry hurry hurry. Mushroom right? No? One of these
has to have a mushroom in it. Yes. Oh all right. I gotta go up and around.
Oh. Oh. Something gonna happen here. Here it comes. Watch out Mario. He goes invisible?
Oh it's a free one. Bingo. That was good. That was short and sweet.
I solved first jump. Yeah don't post anything. Yeah okay. Pretty cool.
Prexy cool. No. Well let me fix it. Prexy cool. Whatever. Pre plus plus cool.
Require course clear to view. Yeah you gotta beat it before you see that and put a stamp on it
too. No. What? No. Whatever. There it is. Now you see my name now. Oh well. All right.
What's popular? Switch x switch. It's a switch controller? Hold on. 12 percent clear rate.
Hey yeet. Boy. Why am I being bombarded by fucking pop-ups?
Do I have to? Why do I have to see these? You know that it's not appropriate for
Super Mario. Are these people chatting? Is this a chat room? Is this just a bunch of ads?
This is billboard city. All right so now I go. How do I turn that one on? I did it. Stop
saying series speedrun. Oh my bum. Oh it's very distracting. How do I make one of these?
I'm just gonna put an advertisement for my channel. Except it's not gonna be my channel.
You know what I mean? I'm gonna put like twitch.tv slash epic gamer 47.2.
Grill master. I need one of those hats. Cool idea. Wow. Wow. I think this is intentional
to have just be irritating because it's very irritating. How do I do? How do I do this?
Do I have to jump from here to there? What? Oh this is number one in the world right now.
This is what I was talking about. I told you guys. I told you guys we needed to wait like a
few days. Oh shit. Don't do it. Yeet. Yeet. Give me the hat. Give me the hat. Give me the
hat. Give me the hat. Go to settings, change your character. I was trying to see if there's
any more. Did I just leave? No. All right. Back to course. I'm not Toad. Why am I not Toad?
Turn off comments. Not yet. I will after. Remove display. Please.
I will turn them off after this. I feel like it's part of the experience.
Yeah. I will turn them off. See that person died down there and they're vote oof.
Secret. Hey thanks for the help dark souls friend. Illusionary wall detected. Oh get that coin.
What do the coins do in multiplayer? I mean and um what do they do? Do you like buy currency
or anything? Do you buy anything with this shit? Nothing. I don't get to build my own castle.
Oh they dropped the ball on that one. They introduced that in single player and I don't
have my own castle that I can build. Here comes a clown joke. Oh shit. Wait what?
I don't have to drop them. Come on give me another mushroom quick.
Holy shit. Okay I gotta be careful. I did it. Hooray. It's not possible to lose. That's
pretty cool idea. All right now I'm gonna I'm gonna be Toad and I'm gonna turn off comments.
I feel like I'm running like a YouTube channel. I'm gonna turn off comments. I'm
gonna turn off engagements. I'm gonna make it so like only one person can
do that. Whoops. I think I'm gonna. All right for the next one I'm just gonna start doing like
paid iPhone game reviews. You'll see what I mean in a minute. Only 12 percent clear rate.
Let's go back to popular. How do I go back from here? Popular. I want to go back to
like the. There we go. Self destruct activated. This is a speed run. Auto scroll speed run.
Oh this. Look at this one. Seven percent completion rate. I'll do this one.
My most popular course remastered. Are you ready to blast off?
They get to be Toad. That's cake Toad too. That's the best one. How do I turn this off?
No no no I want to turn this off. No I'm not doing pretty cool here. Here we go.
Oh my god it goes fast. Oh holy shit. What stopped it? What? Oh god. Should I get it?
No go. The music. That's too much. That music is too fast. Jesus what the fuck is hitting me?
I don't even know what's hitting me. There's the bombs. I gotta get the star.
Turn the comets on. No comets are staying off. Go go go go go go. I got both. Cool.
Oh come on. Go go go go go go go. Don't just go. Forget it. There's no reason to get it.
Did I win? Why does Toad have a fucking like beard belly? Big mushroom Toad has a dad bod.
All right over 20 seconds. Switch block blast. People really into the switch thing huh?
And then do infinite run. I will. I will. Oh we got. No it's not quite cake Toad. That's
close though. Holy shit that was kind of crazy. Oh oh I missed. I missed that. That
was right there right at the end. Oh got them all. Oh got all the coins. What was my 19.7? Oh
come on. What's that? World record right there? Damn it. Oh well. I like that. That was a good
one. You beat the world record. Oh I could be up there as world record. What was that? How
long was that? No I got caught up on that first pole and then I got caught up on the first
pole. Oh do it again. I'll get it. I'm gonna get it. I'm gonna get the world record on this
one. Start over. Start over. It's that first cut there. I'm gonna try. I'm gonna try it. Not
quite. You gotta get clean over that first pillar. Three nanoseconds. You gotta go
later. I get it. There it is. Oh did I? I think I fucked it up. No I didn't.
I think I fucked it up. I think I fucked it up. I don't know. We'll see. I know. I think
I fucked it up. That was frame fucking perfect. You can't do it better than that.
That was frame perfect. This is the one.
I can't believe it. I'll get it. It's uh it's when you go over the uh
this part here. Wait a minute. He how do you get? Hold on. I'm gonna beat it by a shitload.
I'm gonna beat it by a shitload. That thing's gonna hit the... Watch this. Dude I have to do
it. It's three nanoseconds. I have to be up there as Jeremy 4567. I have to do this.
I didn't even jump. What am I thinking? I'm the only person that's died here.
Oh man. I'm gonna lose my fucking mind. I have to do this. Moving height is cancelled
until I do this. I fucking lost it. I added that foot. That's I'm gonna I'm gonna see
point I'm gonna see zero point zero zero zero in my dreams. No. No. I'm gonna...
You gotta jump earlier I think to get over that. It's not gonna be it. You gotta go
earlier. Pretty good. Fuck. Nope. Nope. Nope. Not gonna be it. It's the treadmill.
Oh god damn it. Oh come on. That's gonna be close. No it's that. Mario has a bigger frame
hitbox. Luigi has a bigger... It's that little bit right there. Luigi's faster on the treadmill.
Are you serious? Is Toad just screwing me over here? What did I just do? What was it?
What was it for? What's the default? No. Nintendo. I want to press B.
I got to point three nanoseconds man. Pretty good. Oh my god. My god damn it. My god. What
the fuck am I doing? I was trying to hit the very last frame of it so I'd fall on top of
the axe. Pretty good. How did I get 316 before man? No. You gotta. You gotta. It's the treadmill
but how do I deal? How do I take care of that? Is it less jumps? One jump? Two jump?
Trying to get it in one jump? But how? Lightly tap? Lightly press? Fuck.
No time lost. This is as fast as you can walk forward.
Mmmmmmmmmm. It's gonna be not even close. You are 0.000003 seconds away from the world
record. You can move on. Chat won't call you a loser.
Well, I appreciate that. Thank you. That doesn't mean I'm not still hungry. The thing is,
how do I get that to happen sooner? You got it. Let's probably get a way you can
make him go fuller faster right? No, no. I gotta. I know what I gotta do.
Check this out. That wasn't running fast enough. This is the one. It's not the fucking one,
not the fucking one. It's over! I lost! I can feel it catch it on me.
Please stop. I can't help it. You can't get to 0.0003 to the world record on this level
and then not do it. Wait a minute. Can I get up there from not hitting the switch?
I'm losing frames in the start. I hate it! There's no such thing as bunny hopping.
Nope. I looked over and I just saw. What a loser. See? That was so close but not enough!
Short hop onto the shell. I'm never gonna do it. The world record is frame perfectly time gated.
Even if you were to... Wait, what are you talking about? What does frame perfectly time
gated mean? You can only match it not beat it. What? What are you talking about? I'm done.
This is the one right here. How do I get? Oh, whoops. Here. Sorry. It should be me up there!
It should be me up there! One more time. I'm done. I swear to god. I promise this is the
final one. This is the last time I'm gonna do this. That's not very good. I have to get out.
Just go. I don't care what this is. Toad's faster. No, he's not. I only know how to do
one thing and that's the... I don't know how to do anything else right now. I forgot
how to play every other part of the game. Honestly, let me ask. How do speedrunners
like brush their teeth? You know what I mean? I did that for like an hour. I feel like if I
did that for like six more days, I wouldn't remember how to fucking tie my shoes.
My brain like hurts right now. Wait, did I just mess it up? Oh, almost screwed that one
up. I like this one. I'm hearing more than one sound for an hour. Faster. No. No more faster.
This is dangerous. You only played that level for 15 minutes? I feel like I've been here for
like three days. Fuck. Puzzle. Epic puzzle. Hearts. Hmm. Oh shit, I was looking up at the...
Oops. Dude. Puzzle. Really. Don't do it to me, please. What the fuck am I doing?
Stop. Okay. That was cute. That was cute. Wait, what? No. Looking good. Movie night died for
this. Movie night's still happening. When? In like 30, 40 minutes? In like an hour? I want to
make sure that enough people are here to enjoy it. That's why I said I was gonna do... I can
do that. I'm kidding. That's hard. Sun Touch Sanctuary. Puzzle solving 1-1 homecoming hills.
It's been an hour. It's been 57 minutes. It's just another version.
Oh no. Oh no. Let me just get to the end first and let me see what it looks like.
I ran out of time. He ran out of time on a speed run.
GG. What did I get? 199929. I can do it. Oh! Thought I could make it.
Shit. Only a couple more attempts. Let me finish it like one more or two more times.
I gotta get to the end though. Last one. One where I get to the end. You bet $50 that I'm
gonna get the world record? You think so? I'll take that bet. Who's got that bet? Anybody in
here? Anybody betting? Anybody betting right now? Shit. That's what I have to do. I'm sorry
guys. Somebody's money, people's money is on the line. I have to make sure I try. Come on.
I thought I did it. I thought I actually did it. One more try. I thought I was on the right for a
second. That's as fucking clean as I'm gonna get it. Come on. 20 seconds. Pow block blitz.
Oh I like this one. Speed run. Short and sweet. Down $50. Oh shit. That's right. Somebody,
oh somebody get, speaking of $50, Phil. Phil gave $50 and I, hold on. This is like an
hour ago. Speaking of Phil. Thank you so much for the 50 bucks, Phil. Phil 25. They
say, hey Jerma, long time watch. Your first time cheer. It's been so fun lurking around your
content ever since 2013. Just got my first paycheck at my first serious job and I want
to give back a little. Also thanks for making me the one guy at last E3 Streams credits those
two weeks ago. Unfortunately can't catch many streams from EU so I rely on VODs,
but it's still worth watching for the best entertainment out there. Much love and hope your
life is going just as well. Jerma Hart. Thank you. Thank you, Phil. I do feel bad
about, I have to pick that up, about EU times ever since moving to Pacific,
but I'm at least glad that you can watch the VODs and can enjoy them if you, now that's gonna
take too much time here. I'm not gonna get stuck here. If you get world record on any
of these speedrun levels I will sub to you. It's a $5 bill. No, don't say that.
Fast switch thinking. Let's do this one. This one looks cute. Okay. Only 3% completion
rate on this one. And we'll get a cake Luigi. That's good. You see. How do I, why did I just
do that? Also if I get a world record on, if I get a world record on a stage you'll
sub to the channel. Like at least three or four people said that, right? Okay.
I'll have to beat it. I can't even get a world record here. All right I'm not gonna,
just, they're sleeping. Just step on their heads. What's the point of that?
It's a troll purpose. What is this for? I can take my fucking time. Who cares? Get in the car.
World record. Why would you, I can't. So get out of the car and just go in the tube.
No go, I'm trying to just get away from this. World record. Let me see some fucking
pogchamps in the chat. I think I got it. I think I got it. What are you talking about?
What are you talking about? Get it! A million subs. A million subs. A million subs. Let me
take a look. There it is. You set your first world record. I did it. These are all the
people that bet it against me. 10 community subs from Lexi and five community subs from
It has to be a speedrun level? Well that wasn't part of the plan.
I just said a million subs and now it and now it's happening. Thank you Bebraham for the 20
community subs. 20 from MGSFan. Thank you for the huge subs. But wait a minute. What about
the, what about the one guy? Oh my god, a shitload of coming in. Fine I'll do, I'll do a
speedrun course. Uh knock, Lexi another 10. Knock turn. Thanks for the five community subs
knock turn. Back in five more. Lexi 10 more. I lied because I didn't believe in you. Adventure
MF Dan thanks for the five community subs. Thank you Adventure MF Dan. Abjo five community subs.
I gotta get another. I gotta, I'm gonna just get world records of all the new levels.
ABjo thank you. Can, I think I can make it across if I just go quick. Anonymous
Gay5 thank you whoever you are. Rare Pepe Body Lotion thanks for the five community subs.
Fourth consecutive line five community subs. Thank you so much. Knock turn again five community
subs of the shitload just came in. I mean I know that was like a joke but like seriously
you guys don't have to do this thank you. This is a music level? How is it a music level? On.
How do I turn it on? What's on? Thank you Spygetti for the 10 community subs.
For heat of meat thanks for five community subs. That's not world record piss. I can do better than
that. I'm just going through and fucking dumping on the world records because let's be let's be
honest uh who's actually gonna play these more than once but then care enough to do world
record? I got another world record. Oh my god the Lemmy just gave 75 gold. Let's go play the
like the actual other mode because it's been an hour and I want to do the endless challenge
once. At least before we do the uh five more subs from AB Joe. Thank you so much AB Joe. Thank
you all you guys for the subs and uh 75 fucking dollars from uh Vilemi. Congratulations on the
world record Jerma. Why not celebrate by chugging down a not at all disgusting Mountain Dew throw
back. Don't think I've forgotten about your lies. Thank you for the 75 dollars but I
wouldn't drink a Mountain Dew throwback for 5 000 dollars. Thank you so much for the 75 super
expert. This is a bad idea but thank you so much Vilemi for the 75 bucks. Thank you for the 50
dollars from Timmy. They just say oh like the oh no face oh no it's like an oh face.
Why do I have 30 lives? Speedrun. What? Go backwards and then down but thank you so much
for the 50 bucks Timmy and Vilemi and everybody that's dumping huge amounts of subs. You guys
are too much. Oh fuck. What? I gotta do the spin move. Why did he just no no no this is not
like I only have 28 lives. You need to spin. Spin spin spin. No I got it. I can do this
Nintendo. Leave me alone. Don't Luigi me. I'm already playing as Luigi. Don't you get it?
Oh fuck. Shut the fuck up and beat the level Jeremy. I can go faster than that too.
You want to hear like some crazy shit? I could do it but I can't. My brain is so small that
I can only do one thing at a time. Oh what the fuck do I go? What the fuck? Where do I go?
I don't know where to go. What what's on? Backwards? Up? Forward? Where was I? Go back
and then to the left? How the way do I end up? Oh who cares? I just hurt myself.
I just like went to go drink my drink and the straw just like poked me like in the back of the
mouth because I leaned. I leaned. I like this one though. This one's well thought out. I'll get
this. And by the way stay tuned for the green screen encore movie night happening soon just
like every fucking event you've ever seen. Especially on this platform. It's gonna be
like six hours delayed. I have no idea what the hell to do after that.
Explain to me. I have to go back up that way. 20 omega lol lives. Whatever. I swear to god.
Super expert. I'm fine. You gotta just. I know I know what I have to do now. It doesn't. You
just hold left. You don't have to worry but you're gonna put that hat on. It's automatic.
This is not disqualified. Jeremy turns his face come on and reveals he was dressed as
Luigi this whole time. Even if I was who cares? What would that even matter? Hey guys I have
overalls today. Oh shit. Now what? What the? Okay uh I got freaked out when the thing came
off my head. I hurt. I got hit by something and he went. Oh you punk. You rotten kid.
You punk. I don't care if I lose. I did it. I don't know what the fuck was that.
I swear to god my brain was on slow motion. I got freaked out. I died but I didn't die. I don't know.
Come on. Super Luigi. Come on. Everybody loves Luigi. Did I really not make that jump? That's
unbelievable. What was wrong there? Was it not? Whatever. I'm gonna. I'll get through this.
It's not 100 lives Mario anymore. You just have to beat it. I've already gone panicking.
Slow down. Who cares if you don't get the world record? Yeah it's not gonna look good in a YouTube
video but I'll still get there. What the fuck is happening? If I didn't get like baited into
jumping into those coins. Okay so am I what? Am I understanding that? I'm fine. Go back. So if
you put out. If you don't do the swimmy arms then that. What is you doing? What?
Hold on. What is this? Hey thank you for the five communities. Never trust nanners. Thank you.
I swear to god I pressed the button. I did. I pressed it. I pressed it. I pressed it in it.
I'm get. I'm tilted now. Excuse me what happened there? What happened? Why did I
overshoot that? I did that every time the same way. Something must be wrong with the game.
You know actually no I heard. I heard about that. I heard about like Nintendo was patching
some of their control issues. Yeah I started like an article on Kotaku about like control
issues or something. I almost just fucking let go of the controller. Yeah Nintendo was like
saying at them like a press release came up from Nintendo saying like we're sorry about
the control problems. We just like didn't test them and like we're just really sorry about it
but it'll be fixed. So like when you guys buy this game you guys like get this game later
like you're gonna have like a different game than me. So that's why like I'm not doing so
good but you'll like do better than me because like the patches will be there by then. Essentially
what I have to do is I'm hold I have to queue up controls. There's like four or five seconds
of input lag. All right come on. I gotta jump like at the very last second up here.
What is the problem here? I'm what how am I not making this?
That was as far to the end as I possibly could. What's happening? Good thing I had 30 lives.
I did it! Okay hold on. Wait just I'm not going fast enough. What the fuck is happening
in my brain? I just I had to I put the I put the car in reverse. Oh my god. Oh my god.
You just have to keep moving and I didn't and I put the car in reverse.
You can never put the car in reverse in a speedrun level. Ever. Here we go. Now what? What?
Now what the fuck am I supposed to know? Um um does he kill him? What? Back again?
What? Do you have to go boy have to go back and then jump over the coins and then go back
down? Oh shit I'm gonna lose. This is it. This is the last chance. Oh my god what the fuck did I do?
Oh my god. I just I didn't mean to press that button. Like sir I just I just like bah
do it again. Fucking whatever. Oh my god I'm so upset right now.
I was pressing too hard on Y therefore every button on the controller is pressed.
Oh god damn it give me a break. I'm so fucking mad right now. I had that too.
I need to get like a pro controller not like the fucking side cheese it controller. All right
I'm gonna I gotta breathe for a second here. Why am I using like the mini hot dog bun
controllers? The hell? What? I'm so on tilt right now. Like you didn't just shake the
pinball machine. You took a hammer and just wound up and smashed into the middle of the
glass and just started stealing components. There's really a fucking troll block right
there too. Here comes the explosion. The spin doesn't work. Do I have to be big?
Oh that stupid block. I'm not cut out for this. I'm not cut out for this.
All right I got a mushroom. I fucking forgot again. I'm not going down. Super goddamn expert
give me a break. Fuck expert. Fuck this. Fuck the Oscars. What the hell is this for?
There's gotta be a reason for that. Now watch out for this dickhead that flies from here.
Okay I should just go immediately. What am I waiting for? I'm scared that thing's gonna
pop out and kill me. That's what you have to do. Okay I'm just going right in. I'm just
gonna go right into the bulb. Watch this. Ready? Just right in. Immediately. Go go go go go.
No don't don't. What are you doing? Get the heart. Whatever the thing is. I did it.
Now what? Now what's the rest of this? Movies movies. Hold on. Wait wait wait. Just wait wait
wait wait wait. Did I do it? Not yet. Let me at least beat. Somebody said if I beat one super
expert level they'll download. I'm gonna be quiet. Can I even beat this anymore? I don't
think this is not completable. I picked them all up. I didn't know that was what was gonna
happen. Dick. Get hit by it. Come on. Get hit by that. What happened to the- what am I supposed
to do? Just die. We're gonna- don't worry. The movie night's coming soon. Just hold on
and let me beat this. I have to beat one super expert otherwise I'm- I have to download. Why
do I keep saying download? Why do I keep saying the word download? What's go- what's wrong with
me? Those are all the word- that's that's the only word that's in my brain. I'm gonna
have to download. You guys I will be careful guys. You guys- I don't want you- you guys
I seriously I'm fucking so dumb that I- I've been hit by that every single time and I can't do it
because I need the mushroom. Hold on let me download. Don't get hit by the fucking thwomp.
It just comes out of nowhere for no reason. It's only- it's only there to make you angry
and it's working. Don't be angry by this. It's- it's- it's working as intentional.
He tricked us into watching him play Mario. No I didn't. I did not. Okay now I'm gonna do it.
I just need to leave the fire flowers out here. I just need one. I'm gonna get the one at the
very end. Okay so I'm ready. Did that- what? It hits you? Excuse me Bowser. Please get the fuck
out of the way. I got hit by the- I'm so angry. I- I better beat this or my whole day
is gonna be ruined. What? Wait! Oh god Bowser please! I win. Okay. I can calm down now.
I did it. I beat a super expert level. Somebody owes me 50 grand. I mean now I gotta- I mean
I- I gotta keep going. 50 downloads. All right all right all right all right all right all
right all right. Settle down. Settle down. It's time. It is time for some movies. Settle
down. Everybody relax. I need to change this to this. We're going to return to Super Mario
after this. A hundred dollars just came in from A- AB Joe. Not quite 50 grand but here's second
place prize for your 0.003 speedrun attempt. Thank you. Thank you for the hundred fucking
dollars and your huge amount of community subs. So without further ado let me just make sure
this is in the right spot.