Late, but early. Late, but early. Late, but early. That's what I like to say.
Hi, how are you? Supposed to start in like a couple hours, but I changed the plan a little bit.
I moved the stream back to 2 30-ish because I want to play more Monster Rancher.
And I'm here. And I don't want to wait till 4 30 to turn my stream on.
Because at 4 30 is the game awards. That's going to be a few hours, or at least a couple hours.
I want to be able to, I want to play. Also, very, very, very tragic news
that I need to report to everybody watching the stream right now. Unfortunately,
because I am not kidding. I was searching. Searching every corner of every room here
to try to find Precious Family Heirloom that I don't have anymore. It's just not the same without it.
I lost the bathrobe. Bathrobe, the precious plaid bathrobe is no longer here. It's because
I promised that I wouldn't fucking cry when I turn the stream on, but I left it at the dollhouse.
It was an accessory on dollhouse and I left it there and it's gone. So I'm sorry that I know
everyone's expecting me to be in that outfit. Trust me, I want to be, but I can't. At least
it got a good send off. It was on the dollhouse stream for an hour. I think I'll just get another
one. I know it's not going to be the same. It's not going to be the same. I know it's not going
to smell the same. It's not going to be the same. It's not going to be the same wear and tear. I
didn't wash it once. So it's not going to smell like rotten eggs like it did, which fuck. No robe,
no stream. That's not how this works. Let us peep. No, we're not peeping any horror right now.
Buy it. But we got a lot to do today. I really want to play Monster Rancher again. I want to try
to get to A rank if I can. Probably, maybe, hopefully before the game awards. I'll be streaming
the game awards when it goes live. What do you say? I look like a what? You're looking very
Fallout NPC today. Did your TikTok go viral yet? Doesn't seem like it. Not yet. Sometimes these
things take a while. Horror now. No, I don't, I don't want to, I want people to be alive.
Your skin's still red though. You're the orangutan. No, I, I can't replicate greatness. You can. You
can try. I'll always be the original. Oh, like hashtag orangutan dance. Hashtag replica. Hashtag
replicating Jeremy. Hashtag replica of Jeremy. I'll always be the original. Freshly shaved.
Actually, no, I shaved yesterday. Ecomaniac. Got my water. Are you guys ready? I'm not even going
to be, you know what? You're not getting face cam until at least 10 minutes before the game awards.
May have another few minutes. Are you even real? I don't. What? No, no, this whole thing can't be
a dream. It's, this is so cool. This is going so well. No, no, no, no. The whole thing can't
wake up. Hey, crushed lizard. Thanks for the 20 community zaps. No, thanks though. Seriously.
All right. Let's play. I want to play. I don't want to stall. Okay. Yes, we'll watch the game
awards. I'll make, I'll change categories. Don't worry. I've got too many things in the way.
I need a monitor that's up here. Like up here. There. I got to get some new monitors because
right now I have the monitor that's down here on a stand and then I have another monitor here
and you, Chad is right here. Like directly kind of like in this zone that I'm looking at right
here. Right. I have the OBS stuff over here. I kind of feel like maybe I should have chat here
like right in front of me above. Right. So I can kind of just go like that because for right now,
I get so distracted and I always have to look at chat and stuff. So going like this, it seems
like way easier than going like this. I mean, I like having it near the camera because I feel like
you're looking at us. People don't like that. Every time I do direct eye contact, people go,
stop doing that. I hate that. Let's get this on. Look at us. All right. It's turning the webcam off.
Whatever. It's time to play monster ranch or two. We left off. I'm, I'm coming back. Just give me,
I want to be, I want to be private for a minute. I like being private for a minute. You need to
come back and look at us. I will. I need to be private for a minute. This is exactly where we
were last time. Oh, by the way, if you missed yesterday's stream, I'm currently raising
apparently the worst monster in the entire game. I did not know that until I was too far ahead.
You need to keep the webcam. Otherwise your account will go down. If only German from
10 years ago knew that when it kept the damn thing on. Okay. So I also have figured out,
I researched a few things and I figured a few things out. Oh, by the way, I want to ask this.
Do you guys like the black bars or do you want the whole image with the little input presses?
Is this better for you guys? Do you like this more? I think we have to do a poll because I
feel like it's pretty split. We've got the black bars or kind of all the other random
shit on the screen. Let's run a poll. All the shit on the screen are black bars. Whole milk.
You're gross. I can't think of the last time I heard of somebody drinking whole milk. Well,
you're not, you're not gross. You're not, that was mean. I don't mean that. I mean that like,
I think that I would be gross if that were me doing it. I don't like whole milk. I think it's
like, it's like I'm drinking cream. I don't even like regular milk. 2% milk is like what I would
be okay with. I know that's skim milk shit, right? Like, okay. Skim milk. No, no, no. Whole milk.
No, no, no. 2% milk. That's such a happy Thanos balance medium. 2% is disgusting. Okay. And what
do you drink? Skim? Hey, I got, I got a bunch of bugs that are floating on the top of my pool.
You want to skim those out too? 2% is based. All right. What do we got? People want the
bars or not? I think I'm too big though. I think it's so the face game is aligned with the bars.
Kind of too small. Should I move the game over? Let's be a streamer here, right? Does that suck?
I feel like that's, I hate that. I don't like it. The unevenness makes me want to throw up.
Yeah, I don't like it. Go back. I thought I just like control Z to a point where I like the stream
is going to turn off. Cause that was like the first input, right? Can you do that? If I hit
control Z like five times, it will turn the stream off. All right, let's go. You want,
fine. I'll leave it on. Whatever. I put a fucking t-shirt on. Just don't make fun of me when like
boogers come out of my nose. All right. So last thing that we did, what was the last thing? I
don't know. Oh yeah. I did some research and I found out that I'm doing this shit completely
wrong. The, the, I looked up some, some, some tips and some strategies and the training regimen,
when they get to be a adult, you don't even really want them to rest unless you do a battle or
unless you do an air entry. So when I'm just doing training, I shouldn't be just resting two
or three times, like twice a month. I should be hard training, nut oil, light training,
mint, hard training, nut oil. I got to go back and forth. So I think I'm going to try that out
and see how that goes. It's meta gaming. I know, but I, this is the worst monster in the game.
I have to at least try to metagame this guy and no, maybe you should choose another monster.
It's too late. I'm getting 400 intelligence. So where, what am I doing? What's the next battle?
I want to try to at least get to like B today. Fuck the game awards. I'm going to put the game
awards in a cube this big up in the corner. Who cares? What do I care? I don't have my robe. I
can't even stream it properly. So I'm annoyed by that. So it's going to be a cube in the corner.
All right. So I can train. Let's do it. What, let's see how old, how old are you? All right.
Seven months. I think we're at that point now where I can start to do the, the heavy training
regimen. Let's go for it. Let's do, I need to go to, okay. Training, grill. We're going to do
hard intelligence training. I'm going to do meditate. I need to get to 400 speed and
intelligence. Go for it. Your monster sucks. Hold that thought for another few minutes.
Go for it. Meditate. Why'd he leave? He just fucking left. Don't do that. You're pretty tired.
Okay, fine. We're going to start the new training regimen at the beginning of next week,
next month. Rest, rest, rest up. This wall sucks. I'm getting this to 400 intelligence
and I'm going to get the, I'm going to send him on an errand tree. He's going to get the
intelligence move and we're going to laser light show every motherfucker that we find
that we see in the video game. You understand? I'm sad about the robe. I am unironically sad
about that too. Okay. So I'm going to just get him ready. So let's see, which one's the next battle?
All right. I'm going to skip this and we're going, we're just doing heavy training for two months.
You ready? What do I have? I need to buy items. How many do I have? Okay. I need more than this.
I need a bunch of mint leaves and a bunch of the nut oil. These are so expensive. Okay. Mint leaves.
I need at least like four. That's a lot. Three. And then I need three of these. All right. This
is better work. Otherwise I'd literally soft locked myself and I can't continue playing.
What happened to bug Batman? Bug Batman is currently frozen because he is about probably
like two or three months, maybe three or four months away from dying. I'm keeping him frozen
so I can combine them later. All right. Here we go. I'm ready. Rest up. You get double rest this
time. And then when you get up tomorrow, you better be ready. Rest two rests in a row. Let's go. And
we're going to feed. Oh, jelly boiled. Not going to be spoiled anymore. I don't need to worry about
that. Okay. You're actually running out of money. Don't worry. I'll be fine. Here we go. It's time
training. Real heavy intelligence training. Heavy intelligence. Begin. Please do it.
How does this make you smarter? Now we do a mint leaf light training. We don't rest. This is the
non rest strat. We go out. We do light training. So light intelligence. Go for it. Mint light,
nut heavy. Yes. That's precisely what we're trying to do. Now we take a nut. Use. Bingo. Heavy
training. I got to get them to at least 330 intelligence. Heavy school mattress. Nice. Good
increases. Okay. I got to do defense though. Okay. Three. It's a combined it's combined speed and
intelligence, right? It's a dorm room bed. I swear to God. Dorm room mattresses. Let me tell you
something. Okay. Or as expensive as room and board is at college. This is a shot at every fucking one
of these colleges, right? Listen to this. Room and board is so expensive. It's remarkable to me
that they have these like fucking twin air mattresses that are in all these places.
If you're going to have college be that expensive, you put, you put, you put Tempur-Pedics in those
fucking dorm rooms. You put, you put like Tempur-Pedic branded mattresses in there. I swear to God,
when I was in college, the bed that I was laying on was actually filled with air. It was like,
you know what? It was, it reminded me of a pool toy. It was a pool toy. I actually think a pool
toy may have been more comfortable. It was a pool toy with a sheet on. College is going to be that
expensive. There should be a flat screen TV at every one of these fucking dorm rooms. Complaining
because of your GPA. I had a 2.6 GPA. It was good enough. Okay. Now, wait, I just messed it up. It
was heavy training, mint, light training, nut oil, heavy training, mint, light training. I forget.
2.6. What's wrong with that? That's literally like, who cares? It doesn't say what my GPA
is on my degree. But Jerma, you didn't make the Dean's lift. The Dean didn't say my name.
I have this, no way I'm going to forget this. To have five, 10 years from now and not give a shit
about, I don't even know the Dean's name. Coping, cope, copium. Do your best. Listen to me. This is
important. All of you listen. I'm a lot older than a lot of you guys here. I have a lot more wisdom
and knowledge than you'll ever have until you get to my age. Listen to me. Do your best, but you
don't have to be perfect. Just try to do as good as you can. If you get straight F's, you got some
stuff to work on. D's, you got some stuff to work on. Don't worry about it. You're going to be
all right. C's, B's, B minus, that's good. You did good enough. I don't like the grading system.
I think we need to go back. Listen to me. We need to go back to kindergarten grading. It was like S,
which was like you passed. Like S, P, and like F, right? We need to go back to like first grade
grading. Did you, like you passed or you did like sufficient, right? What was it? What are they?
There really should only be three grades. S means like really good. P means you passed, but like
you might need a little bit of work. And then like, oh, you failed the class. Satisfactory. Yeah.
Why do we care? Why does that, oh, well, uh, we have it at a hundred point scale. Why, what's the
point of a hundred point scale if anything under 50 means you fucking lose? That's stupid. What's
the point of a hundred point scale? You're smurfing. Guys, I don't get a hundred point scale.
It's just like why anything under like 60 means you're lost. Under 70 technically. Get a
goddamn flat screen TV in those dorm rooms. Plasma. LED. Backlit. You're based. I don't think this is
just regular shit. I don't know why this is based. It should be like normal stuff. I'm saying like
normal, popular opinion things, I hope. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
What was it? Oh, popular opinion, Andy. That's me. You're a mad lad. What a popular opinion, Andy.
I just, a hundred point scale. I used to get so mad when it was like, oh, I got like a C minus.
That means you're stupid. What? No, who cares? What are you talking about? And by the way,
let me, let me tell you another thing. Retention is more important than memorization. And I think
that our current education system is based on memorizing things from a book, not retaining
things. I don't remember anything that I did in high school, especially like some of the random
shit that I had to memorize temporarily. Cause that's what you want to do. You want to temporarily
memorize something so you get a good enough grade. But in the long-term, you don't really actually
care to retain that information. You guys, you'll see, look, even, even some basic stuff that I
should probably know, right? If you ask me like basic science questions, I probably would be like,
I don't have any idea what you're talking about. Retention is more important than memorization.
So 2.6 GPA actually means 150 IQ. That was my long winded way for me to say that I'm not stupid.
I promise I had a 2.6 GPA. All right. Now we're going to take, so training. All right.
People help me out here. I think I screwed up. The last thing I did was heavy training.
So it's mint leaf, right? And then we do light, not oil, right? This is a Fortnite ball. Okay.
Training, light, intelligence. I'm just trying to stack intelligence, man. I swear to God.
Are you high? No, but I will be in an hour. 10 for light training. All right. I actually am
going to run out of money. Uh, I think I got to unfreeze the, I got to unfreeze that guy,
bring him out of retirement, have him win one tournament and then put him back in the freezer.
Okay. Now it's oil, heavy oil, then heavy mint, then light. I'm just going to work them. No rest.
Not unless we do an hour entry intelligence. Let's go. What the fuck is this thing?
Imagine if I said that about you, if you said that about me as my buddy, Dave, uh,
this, uh, just nice to meet him. What the fuck is that thing? That's not rude to you at all.
You know, you know, he has a name. Cosmic calamity. So now that's mint, light training, oil,
heavy training, and then we have to relax. I am determined. Actually he's doing pretty well.
Oh, it's okay. It's all right. It's all right. I am being a little too soft though.
All right. I need some, uh, monster rancher two lore masters. Even if they fail,
I still have to stick to the regimen, right? So that's, it doesn't matter. Like it's not like
they failed and they didn't, it still counts like to their stress and fatigue. Here's a 2.6 GPA.
The views on education really reflect his face and faith in minerals and rocks. Your views on
education really reflect your views on minerals and rocks, like black tourmaline. What's with the
black tourmaline thing coming back? I haven't worn that bracelet in probably a year and a half.
Why are people talking about it now? It was a mistake I made and I'm burying it. I actually
like that. I like that bracelet. I don't think it has superpowers. I think it's just cool. I like
it. I'd like stones and crystals. Uh, do you see that? And what, you don't think that I like
crystals and stones and should have a gigantic stone crystal right behind me. You were there
for that. You are on that stream. You are, you participated. I like, I don't know. I think they're
cool. Educational. Nice. Interesting. Loves getting stoned. Not yet. I'm just kidding. Just relax.
All right. Uh, I forgot the last thing I did. I just have to, just, that's why the face cam can't
be on. I'm so aware of my face. Um, what's the last thing I just did? Light training and he failed
it. Okay. So we still have to do the oil. Heavy training. After this, we're going to do a battle
because I am going to run out of money. You have Funko's on that shelf and they're worth about 14
to 15,000 dollars. Yen. Not USD. Uh, all right. Training. Real. This might actually put us over
the edge here. And then I want to send them on an air entry. I want nuts oil. I just gave it to you.
What? You just had one. You just ate one. You can't have two. You can't act like you can't be the dog
that gets the cookie. Right. Oh, I want a cookie. Right. Here's your little, here's the dog cookie.
And then just still waiting for another one. It's like you just had one. No, he wants more oil. He
wants to get high. You guys need to relax. All right. Officially over 400 combined speed and
intelligence. Now I can get that intelligence move. Is that a CBD shake? No, I don't. Well,
I have enough money to do this one more week, one more month before unfreezing and winning a
tournament because he's right now in the prime of his life. I have to be very careful. I don't
have, no, I can't, I don't have any items left. I have enough to do this one more cycle, I think.
Right. I have to enter this tournament. I can do this one more cycle. That was heavy. So now we do
a stress relief herb spices. I'm going to do heavy drill one more time and then we'll rest them.
Light drill tournament. Don't need the full 400 intelligence speed to get the ability. 400 is
just the point where it's a hundred percent chance to get the ability from the pop us air entry.
All right. So I just have to do the pop us air entry. That got 350 fucking XP. I'm good to go.
This is going to be huge. All the doubters here are going to get floored when I get to a rank.
Cup of jelly, do a tournament. I have to, I have to freeze them and then unfreeze. Um, I have to,
you're, you're a rank number one. Shit. It's going to be air entry, isn't it?
Thousand bucks for entry. Okay. All right. All right. All right. We got to put this guy on ice
and I, when's the next tournament? I just need money from, uh, from the old guy. All right.
There's a tournament right now today. That's three grand and it's C rank. I think I'm going
to just do the, should I, I don't know if he can handle it. Do you think he can handle it?
Unfreeze the retired guy. Do C. What if he loses? I need this money. Otherwise the game softlocks
and it's over. Oh, I'll wait till tomorrow. I'm going to put this guy on ice. Batman can do C.
I know, but it's not guaranteed. I might get one hit killed by something. This game actually
softlocks if you run out of money. Yep. You run out of money. You basically can't play the game
anymore. I'm an hour and 40 minutes into the last stream. What happened to Bonnie? Is he okay?
Um, just, uh, I would, I would watch. It's pretty sad. All right. Revive Batman. Let's go.
D rank. You can do jobs in town. I heard the jobs are really not efficient and they're really bad
to do. Let me see what it is. Do the job. Do you know what kind of work we do? No. I want you to
help sort out the materials for the industrial products. There is a set of two pieces of material
and each piece has its own number. First, the sum of the two numbers equals 10. Put them into
the above container. Second, if the two are equal, put them into the container below.
If not, so pick the higher numbered item. The amount of wages will be determined on how many
materials you sort out. 2.6 GPA. I'm not, I'm not doing battle $3,000. Only four entries. All right,
go for it. Let's do it. I don't care about how famous he is. He's supposed to die. That sounds
bad, but it's true. There's only four competitors. Bugbat, Sussbane. Uh oh. It's a mirror with a
different subtype. I actually can't fuck this up. So I have a higher power. It's just going to come
down to a hit percentage. If I can land hit attacks, get in there and start smashing. Bad,
bad start. Really bad start. Abysmal start. That's actually probably the worst start ever.
Do the same thing, please. Okay, come on. Again, again, again, again. I got plenty of guts. Go.
Again, again, again, again, again. Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick. 86% chance you had a chance
right there. Oh, who cares? What are you? What is this? Gotta win. Why are you into so many
weird creatures? Train a human. Just hair a little bit. Oh shit, we gotta go against this little,
the little owl guy. We actually have to go against the League of Legends character,
which is bad because he's really good. The speed is so awful, but I had to hit him a few times.
Get away from the... Get in. I'm holding. Double tap quick. Again, just do it. I have to just,
I have to bully. No, this is gonna kill me in one hit if I don't dodge.
Fuck you. What, why is this guy, what's this guy doing in C rank? What are you doing down in C
rank? You do 160 damage a hit. Why are you down here? Fuck this goddamn League character.
I, as long as I come in second place, I'll get a prize pool. I remember this guy. All right,
just give me the prize pool. Just give me second place. I'll get probably a thousand bucks or so,
and then that's all I need. I remember this character, this dude was just hard to hit,
but was, couldn't hurt anything. So let's just get in there. Same deal. Not yet. Don't waste guts.
Just stay in tight. Go for it now. All right. No, I'm gonna, I'm gonna hold it. Hold it, hold it,
hold it. Oh fuck. It's actually not that much damage. It's fine. All right, now I got way more
guts than him. Go for it. That should be enough. Stay in tight. Just holding right. I'll get the
prize money now. Thank God. AO would be great. No softlock. An adult sippy cup? This is a cup with
Sussbane actually beat him. I have a chance. All right. This just got, okay. I might get four grand.
Okay. I just have to get lucky. That's all it is. It's just flip a coin if I can hit him or not.
Rematch. Let's go. His intelligence move is the worst. He, I gotta just stay close. Don't let him
do this shit. Stay in there. Get in there. Please. Don't let him push me away. He wants to do this
fucking move so bad. Oh, I almost killed him in one hit. Nice. Oh, thank God. All right. There it is.
More than $4,000. I'm back in it. Now we go back to, uh, Flammity. Do the Arran tree because it's
on sale. Get the intelligence move and laser beam people and get to A rank. Good work. Arran tree?
Yes. 3,300 bucks. And I got a star prune. Oh, that gives you fame, right? I'm going to feed that to
the wall. Shit. I'll put you on ice. You did a great job. Thanks for the money. Back to the freezer.
Dun dun. Bullying lower ranks. I need money. I'm going to buy, I got to keep the training regimen
up after this too, by the way. All right. Back to the ranch. Arran tree time. Hoppus Arran tree.
When the game says you must be registered trainer to generate monster, it just means you haven't
unlocked that breed and each breed has a different unlock requirement. Oh, okay. Good enough. So I
need to do Arran tree. I'm going to do run out of rest. Arran tree. Yeah. Rest Arran tree.
I want you to be perfectly ready. That's your problem. Give me that intelligence one. You
guys saying go to the pop us is where I get tech sharp tech, heavy tech, withering tech,
sharp tech, withering tech, or hit tech. It's actually, are you sure? I said to go to pop us
across the chat, save the game. Let's go for it. Arran tree. Hoppus. This was speed. Actually,
I kind of need speed. There's some chance to require a new technique and we'll deal with this
loser. You can do it. Nice job. Got it. That better be intelligence or I'm going to be really pissed
and then we've got to get to over 400 intelligence so I can literally just spam that move. Nice.
Get that speed over 100. Why are you so early? Because I didn't want to start streaming. Oh,
holy shit. I didn't want to start streaming at 430 again and have the stream be like eight
hours and go to like midnight again. So I figured I'd start like a couple hours early,
get some time in here, do the game awards and do some time after and not have it be too late.
We'll see though. We'll see what I do. Very good. Polar bears. What the? Oh, I have to try to sneak
through the fight. Why don't we just go around him? This feels so out of place. Did I do it? Oh no,
he got me. Who's bait? Oh, was it bait? Or are you just, what is that smile? Uh oh. Very good.
Keep it going. That's definitely a victory. Nice job. What's that? What's that gigantic
thing? That big Griffin in the back. What is that? What is that? Wait, does he have the new move?
Will he use it? Use the new move. You just got it. Use it. It's probably, it's probably at medium
range. He's going to just keep doing a stupid shoulder tackle move. He's going to just not do
anything but nudge. Let's see if he really is such an idiot. Let me see. Let's see the new move. Do
it. Oh, wait a minute. Wait a minute. That was the move. That was the move. That was like the
galaxy beam. Why are you not hitting him? It's all right. You tried. That move looks sick though.
I'll take it. Now we stack intelligence and skill and hope I can like do 150 damage in that laser
cosmic beam. All I'm going for is like a 60 plus percent hit chance to do 200 damage and hope I
don't die. Nice work. Now we rest. I want to see that technique. I want, this has to be at least
over 400. There it is. Strange light. It's got a terrible. All right. We really need to put. All
right. Hold on. So physical attacks, your hit chances based on your, the hit percentage of the move
and your skill, right? Is intelligence also based on skill as well? Should I level up skill
to make this better to hit? Skill is hit for both kinds of attacks. Okay.
C scaling on intelligence means sharpness. What the fuck does that mean? All right. We're sticking
to the plan. Now I have enough money and we're going right for D by the way. Not yet. I'm going,
we're going to rest. I'm going to go to the shop. Sharpness is crit rate. Damn cursor. Sorry about
that. All right. This is, we're in prime now. This is where we have to really hammer down skills.
We are currently in, we are just, we just went into the prime stage of life. This is where we're
going to get like 20 fucking skill points. The training regimen needs to be done now,
at least like three or four mint leaves and at least four, not oil. I can only buy two at a time.
I can only buy one at a time. The number of your allowed items has reached its maximum.
Oh, she's given the star firm. Just eat the star firm. Will that be good? Is that a good idea?
Wait, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Hold on a minute. Yes. We're going to start that now. Star prune
become more famous. Now I can buy another one of these. Very good. Very good. Very good. Very good.
Very good. This is now very crucial. So now we're going to do, I think I so train heavy training,
right? Not oil and then heavy training or heavy training. Then just by the way,
if you want to unlock the ability, the least of unlocking the strongest intelligence ability
in the game, you need to have at least 500 intelligence. All right. Used a star prune
today. Oh shit, I did. I think I'll be all right. It won't be like completely ideal,
but I think I'll be fine. All right. Intelligence. We're just going for scaling here. Intelligence
and skill thankfully is the second one. I need at least 400. I want polish. What does he want?
You want to eat like nail polish? He won't wait. He wants to polish his wall.
Uh, should I give it to him? Sure. What is that? What is it? What did he want that for?
Okay. That means you better do a good job. All right. Plus 20 intelligence guys. I'm getting
this motherfucker to like 500 in tablets. All right. And now I'm almost broke again,
but it's okay. Stick to the regimen. I will wipe the floor with everybody on a tournament.
Okay. Now it's mint, like drill, intelligence, not oil, heavy drill. I'm telling you,
I'm putting this guy on the top of the map. Hell yeah. Today is Cosmic Calamity's birthday.
Are we saying something? Yes. Happy birthday Cosmic Calamity. You are my best friend.
Bro and be a strong monster. Oh my God. It rained on my birthday. Can we reschedule?
Here's a big cake. I like the sound effects that like
oil and be training. Do it. Where's this? This is a new place. What did he not know where to go?
Why was it in a cave? Well, you just screwed the whole thing up now.
You reached the next training level. Oh, get in that cave. Well, not in the cave though.
You made him work on his birthday. I know I'm running out of money. I'll be fine. Not oil,
heavy drill. Worst birthday ever. So take us over 400, which then it's time to start destroying
tournaments. I want to get this right. This is cool. Got it. What, what is this intelligence?
I don't understand. How is this intelligence? We were just in a cave. All right. Time for
tournament meditating. Uh, you have mail. It's going to be air entry again, isn't it?
Oh man. This is big deal. I got to buy a ton of these. It's a battle. All right. We're doing
this D cup tomorrow. Rest up. It's time. Mint leaf reduces stress. We're going to give you a nice
full week of rest and then tomorrow we're doing the D cup and I've got over 400 intelligence.
I will kill everything in one hit. Perfect. Go for it. I'll get disc chips. This is where it
matters here. This is very important. Incredibly important. This will determine if we can get this
guy to A rank. All right. What do we got for stats here? I remember Capella was pretty balanced
across the board. We've got 415 intelligence. What do you got? Nothing. I'll kill you in one hit.
Oh, it's pretty good. It's pretty good. That was an 82% chance you don't even hit that.
Dude. Okay. Swing at him. Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. What the fuck? I missed with an 80% chance twice. It's all right. I can lose one.
Okay. Now it's all skill from here on out. Shit. If I hit you one time, you're going to die. Just die.
Dead. When it works, it works. Yeah. 36% chance versus an 80% chance. Math problems are really,
really annoying, aren't they? Statistics suck. I'll get some money from this if I win,
which you have no defense. I just got to hit you one time. Look at the terrible speed. All right.
I should be able to land this. I can't. Come on. Call it back. I'm holding left.
That's a lot. Especially if I get that to like 500. That will do at least 150 damage a hit. All
right. Capella. Lose. Come on, Millium. Take him out. Still in it. We just actually have to land a
coin flip in our favor. Start building defense so I don't get killed in one or two hits.
Probably not a bad idea. All right, Millium. Here comes one hit Andy. And when it works,
it's really, really good. Just have to try not to die. One of the game awards, like 30, 40 minutes.
We're probably going to do like a pre-show, right? Pre-show of four and then it starts at 430. Yeah,
we'll just go with 430. I got to piss. Nice. Very good. I want polish again.
No, I'm sorry. Not this time. Why do you want a jar of pomade? You don't even have a hair.
Now we stick with the training plan and buy a shitload of items. Sales not on anymore.
I want to keep at least a thousand in case it's an air entry. Oh, I seem well. What's the calendar
look like? All right. So I'm going to do a light. I'm going to do a heavy training. Rest. And then
we're going for the official D there. Okay. Rest. Yeah. Go for it. More damage. More damage. Did you
do it? How do you cheat? Sorry. You still got eight. All right. Now we need to do stress and then
rest or light training. Let's see. Okay. Light training, defense or health or skill. What do
you think? I don't know. Speed. Maybe defense. I think it's too loaded. I don't know. I feel like
speed needs to come up a little bit. Speed or health. I think I'm just going to go straight
health. Health and speed. Is there one that's speed and health? Defense and life. That's actually not
a bad one to try. Let's just do life straight up because I can't have him do a heavy one.
Straight up health. Next heavy one I'll do is swimming. How long do they live? That depends
on how stressed out, how fatigued they are and how well you treat them.
Tablets. Keep the training up at least for the next two or three weeks.
Tablets are really expensive but they're just so good. So item. Use. Not soil. Heavy training. Swim.
This is defense and life. Is there a life one? No. I feel like this is a waste. This is a waste
though. Speed and intelligence. Leap. I think leap is far better. This lowers my intelligence.
I don't know if I want to do that. I think it's leap. Leap is the play. Because having less than
100 speed is probably the reason why I'm just so easy to hit. Hit chance is so bad. Or so good on
their end. All right. At least I got to get that shit to over 100. Stress mint leaf. You're easy
to hit because you're a brick wall. Well that's not really how it works. I'm breaking. I'm breaking
the uh. I'm gonna break this up a little bit. I'm gonna say screw it. I got the official
tournament. I'm gonna do another heavy drill in a row. Then rest. Then tournament. That's the play.
Go again. Do it again. Finally. All right. Leveled up speed. Rest. Now we have the official D cup
which after we beat that we'll be able to do the official C cup and this guy will be unbeatable.
Go for it. You know what? Let's use the nuts oil for the tournament. All right. Let's let's clear
it. Let's clean this up. Dare you participate in it? What do you wait? What? This is a higher
grade tourney. Oh I didn't even do E yet. From the game awards. It's not until 430.
I don't need to watch the pre-show. Yeah I'm going D. We're skipping a grade. Look I don't need to.
Let me focus on my what's important right now and that's getting this wall to rank B.
And then just farming money. All right. Palmer. I would rather just watch this than the game awards.
I don't want to rage quit the game awards but you know. All right. This guy's done. 135 damage.
Almost killed him. Again. All right. Now don't be an idiot. It's okay. Those moves are so bad but
it's a waste of guts to even do them. What about the smush? Smush is okay. I'd rather do smush than
the slap. Not a problem. Not a problem. Not a problem. I would like to have a chance to do a move
though. That'd be nice. Defused again. You know what? Let this guy just chip damage me until he
wins please. It's all right. Maybe I should just build speed for the rest of the time. I need 500
though. I need at least to compete in B and A. Like to compete in B rank and A rank. S rank. I need at
least 500 damage. 500 intelligence. Just nuke and stall. That's probably a good idea. I want
one of those dogs. So bad. All right. Sakura Art. What do you look like? I gotta just get the hit.
I have to just get the beam. Build some guts first though. Not good. Shit. Now I have to just,
I can't spend any. I don't want to go to zero guts. I won't hit anything. All right. Back it up.
Back it up. Push. Push. Push. Push. Push. Push away. How do you still have this much guts? What
the? All right. Just fucking hit him with one of these and burn him. What the fuck? I didn't get
one hit. Not one single hit. I need more skill. I need more everything. It's a 46 to 51 percent
chance every time. And you can just lose, you can get heads 10 times in a row. I'm not, I haven't
lost yet because everyone's lost at least once. So we're good. Your defense sucks. I just need
to land this move. All right. Well, I need to get at least 200 skill and stay. Look, look at his two
moves. He can only attack if I'm in the first two slots and just here's the plane. Just never let
him over here. Just hold left. Why is he getting closer? I'm holding left. It's not fair. I got
enough guts. Go for it. Please. You're doing six damage. I just need to hurt. Okay. All right.
Fine. Fine. Sure. Yeah, that's fine. Hump them. Oh my God. One hit. All right. He sucks. All right.
He actually sucks, but it's all right. We're going to make it work. This is good. This is good for us
to know. Cause now this means that I'm going to do, I'm going back and forth, intelligence,
skill, intelligence, skill, skill, intelligence, skill, skill, intelligence, intelligence, skill,
intelligence, skill, skill. The next two months. Don't let me do anything else. If in the next
10 minutes you see me go, Oh, you know, maybe like a little bit more speed. No, no. Scream at me.
I'm not going to do heavy drills. We're just going to go back and forth, back and forth, back and
forth, back and forth. If I hit this, it will do more, probably 200 damage. He has no intelligence
defense. Hit it. Thank you. I'll stay alive. Of course I hit this twice in a row on this guy.
It's such horseshit. There's a chance I'm probably not going to win, but I might get some prize money
if I win again. I think it goes all the way to third place. I got a P. Capella, what are you
doing here? You're supposed to be on E rank. You get prize money if you're not dead last. That's
good to know. I'm going to hang back. Stay back. He's going to, he has so much guts. I, it's so bad.
He hasn't even been able to do a move the whole time. All right. Just kill him. 40%.
I need a new intelligence move. I do, but I think somebody said I need 500 intelligence
to get it. It might be tricky to get because I think we're out of the prime age here.
So we have monsters who are tied. Wait, wait, we all worth three and two.
Wait a second. What? I beat this guy with no problem last time. I actually might win the
tournament. I just have to get the hits. Don't throw. I'm going to try not to. All right,
just stay back. I'm going to build up to like at least 70 guts as long as they stay out of the
second and first and second slot. He's getting closer. He pushed closer. Good thing. I dodged
that. Okay. Now we go for it. I'll do it again. Just wait. All right, go. Lock it in. One shot
Andy or he's useless. I know actually one shot Andy or useless. I can't believe I just won that
tournament. What even determines where you're placed if it's a four ways high? I went above a
rank here too. So I'll probably get some bonus fame for that because I skipped a rank, right?
Oh, hell yeah. Almost 50 fame. My sister-in-law is here. Please make her. My sister-in-law is here.
Please make her leave. You are on the TV. I didn't deny another potential adrenaline.
What are you talking about? I got some stats from that too, but very good. I want polish. All right,
we'll give you polish considering how well you did. Game awards is in like 15 minutes. All right,
I gotta pee. I'm going to come back. We'll chill till the game awards and we're doing tablets
because I still, I want to train a little bit more. That same regimen gone
because I want to do heavy intelligence. Heavy. C is the official. This one's F, but I'll lose
this one guaranteed. All right, the official C is in a month. I gotta pee. Leave. Hurry up.
Uh, I'll be right back. We'll figure out when the game awards actually goes live.
I'm like tangled up by this cord. How? All right, I'll be right back. Let's go. Now I know everybody's
about to leave, but don't leave just yet. I know you're, you're thinking of leaving, but just hold
on one second here. We've got another thing to check out here real quick. If you don't, don't
leave yet. We are ready to continue to go. We're going to move right now after the game awards.
Hey, thanks Jeff for passing it over here, passing the mic over here. Uh, welcome everybody. Uh,
we're showing this new thing that came out today. This is, I mean, we're showing trailer for games
that are already out, but what we got here is monster rancher one into DX. And now the cool
thing about this part about this game is you get to raise monsters, you get to battle them,
and you get to not, uh, drop 70% viewership in 11 or 12 seconds. All right, let me change the
category. You gained viewers. Did I? Well, not when I changed category. Was I, wait, wait, wait,
was I in just chatting? Was I supposed to be somewhere else? Uh, okay. There's a special event.
Oh, okay. Let me change this to, oh, discussing, discussing our top picks from the game awards.
How about just wall coming in hot? A rank. I gotta, I gotta hurry up and I gotta hurry up.
Monster rancher. There we go. All right. Welcome back everybody. What was my favorite thing in the
game awards? Cuphead DLC. It's actually really cool. That's coming out. Very excited about that.
And that's it. Elden ring. Yeah. All right. Here we go. So where we left off here. Oh, the Star Wars
game. That was kind of cool. Okay. So what the, I was going to be training minus 10 K views. Hurry
up and be entertaining. It's still here. People are still here. Don't leave. All right. So the
last thing we did was I ain't watching this shit ever again. Uh, I was in the middle of training,
I think. Yeah. Cause when's the battle. So I wanted to do this. Don't forget what I was doing. I,
no, I did this. Okay. See, we're going for this one. I'm going for C rank. So I was keep the
training regimen going. I believe the last thing I did was I want to do a super drill or I was
skill and intellect, skill and intellect, skill and intellect, skill and intellect.
Let's do skill. Sorry. I got to leave. No, I'm just kidding around. You got to go. You got to go.
We'll see you later. All right. I want this to get to 200. So let's do the stress leaf.
We're going to do intellect. Uh, just go back and forth between the two. I'm not going to do the
super powerful hard one. Maybe I'll do the hard one one more time on intellect. Try to get it over
500. 500 int. Why is the teacher a toucan? Good question. Shit. I don't have any more. Um,
I'm going to buy some more. I haven't blinked in four hours. What the fuck? Okay. By the way,
get McDonald's later. I've decided it's definitely a McDonald's kind of night. Have you tried
Popeyes? I still haven't. I have to take the plunge. It's very loyal. Yeah. Loyalist guys.
What about McChicken? No, no McChicken stream sequel. You can unlock beam. You got to do Papa's
Aaron tree again. I've got a pretty good chance to get it now. Papa's Aaron tree. All right. That's
what we're going for. Definitely need more skill. Least 200. Nailed it. Look at this crazy bastard
flying around. Now, thanks for watching. If you guys are just sticking around, I'm if you're new
viewer, we fucking around 90% of things I say are not true. Um, we just have fun. Backtrack everything
that was, I said that people didn't like this whole stream. Uh, we're going to do stress again.
Thanks for watching. Maybe we'll see you again. If not, happen to be your, your little home away
from home or your other streamers that you're watching. You better come back. Uh, intelligence.
What speed intelligence at right now? Speed is pretty low. Ooh, that was a big one. 456. Uh,
cup of jelly. Alison knock, knock, joke, knock, knock, banana, knock, knock, banana. Hey, knock,
knock orange orange. You glad I didn't say banana. I forgot to do my tick tock and whatever. Who
cares? Holy shit. I laughed so hard. I pooped a blood vessel. Have that happen sometimes when
you're hanging out here. It's fun and funny. All right. Skill again. I wonder what the success
chance is because right now I wonder how much, how old he is. There's a B cup here,
but no, I'm not ready for that. I'll try this. The actual, uh, see one. Maybe it's time to rest.
I need to do Aaron tree after this. Okay. Let's do skill. It's a 200. Actually I have to rest.
I have rated today. Let's see. Right. I mean, let's see. Right. So we got one,
so one, two, three, four, five weeks until they see battle. I can still train.
We should buy some more. Yeah. We'll do that. We'll do heavy train,
heavy skill. One doesn't exist. I'll go for this. We'll go for meditate. I should get up level up.
That was, that was great. Holy shit. Wow. Skill leveled up or 76 intelligence. Nice job. I need
to buy. I get to buy some more of those. I don't want to go broke though. Thanks your boy for the
10 community subs. Just one. All right. Don't go broke. What's this Hulk Hogan thing you're
talking about? Stop. All right. Now we do intelligence again. Hey Dorsalis. Thanks for
the 20 community subs, 20 community subs this time. Thank you. That's a lot of money. Thanks guys.
It's the lighting. You look like a monster. I think at this point I got over 200 skill
stack intelligence. So I can't train them anymore. Try to get to like five or 600
rate again. Damn. It's working hard. Always cup jellies. If you can't afford tablets,
cup jellies, the only thing that really reduces stress that well.
Official tournament. I'm fine. So the battle is, so we got nuts oil, heavy intelligence training,
stress relief, light intelligence training, rest tournament. That was good to me. Why do you have
a cosmic wall? I know it's weird meditate. Let's get another great 20, get it to 500.
I think he failed. That's not good. I'm not too soft, right? Are you training a memory card?
I could try and do it again. Try and do it again and we'll rest. Nice 500 intelligence. Now there's
no way I don't make it to at least a no way rest up today into this week, move into the C
tournament. I need to get another move. I do, but I need money. Our entries are two thousand dollars,
which I don't have. What do you think? I got 500 intelligence. Is that asking too much? I'll just
say that. That's this is a big tournament too. Would you ever wear Heely's? No, I feel like I
would be walking and I would slip and crack my skull on the back of a pavement. We just have to
make sure that we land attacks. This guy here is a huge problem and has really high intelligence,
but I have a lot more. Just got to land it at speed 375. This is going to be rough. 50%.
Oh, excuse me. It was a bad idea. I just melted his face off.
By the way, getting KO'd in one hit is really bad for your character apparently.
Getting KO'd is really bad, but I actually, this is not even a joke. This is like baked into the
game's code somewhere. I took like four months off of that person's life. Something like that.
Getting KO'd like that is really bad for your monster. Yeah, you can get injured. You can get
sent to the hospital and die. Let's get a cosmic brownie. All right, what do I want from McDonald's?
What do you think? I'm thinking there's a new German 985 meal by the way. It's a 10 piece nugget
with a powerade, sweet and sour sauce, honey mustard, and two double cheeseburgers without
pickles. That's the new meal as official at this point. Don't forget the apple pie.
I'm not so sure anymore. The McChickens are a single item. I get like one or two of them.
I used to get a McChicken as well, but I have to cut back. You can't eat that much
fast food. It's too much. It's going to be tricky, but I will have really high defense
versus all the things you're doing. That hurt, but 29%. Jeez. Oh, all right. The percentages
suck, but I have to try to just hit them once. 33%. Come on. Nice. What do I need? I have plenty
of intelligence. I need more skill. Another four months gone. Flash Royale taunt. I just beat
S-Frank with my pixie. Can I ask, what were your stats? What were your main stats and how high were
they? I got to figure out when I should slow down. Nice. Am I facing? I lost that person's name. I
found out who it was. I wanted to know what their stats were. All right. Yeah, I might not kill it
in one hit, but I will kill it in two hits. High speed, unfortunately. Eyes. I'm going to stay back
because the only thing you can do is this move that's not going to hurt me. All right. Now you're
in trouble. Oh, that's a lot. I don't think there's even a crit either. With a crit,
you're probably killed. All right. Slow down. Slow down. 275. Play that giggly sound effect again?
No. This character is overpowered. This character is built very stupidly. This is apparently one
of the worst characters in the game. The worst monster and subtype combination. But with
perseverance, you can get these two moves that you just have to flip a coin and win.
But later on, I bet I fall off horribly. 800 intelligence, 500 skills, 600 speed.
How'd you do that? What? How'd you get 800 intelligence? I'm struggling to get
600 before this guy dies. Okay. Again, intelligence only. Let's go. That's not good.
Just pissed you off. That's fine. All right. Just, just, just bump. Bump again. They said light drill
three times, rest on fourth with mint leaf. You don't do any heavy drills at all? I think these
are a really good base. They said never. Really? I've seen different, seems like the book is out
though. I've heard that alternating between heavy and light, heavy and light with nut oil in between
is a good strategy. These are like the four or five different ways to train. There's also drugs.
You can, you can get like tons of drug training, right? Which I have no idea how that happens. But
I know you take like a year or two off of the life of the monster and you just drug train them.
It's expensive though. So I think you have to do that once you're able to buy, you know,
win a bunch of money. They fixed the bug stats so this character isn't shit tier anymore. Okay.
Oh, yikes. Uh, okay. This character is just me, but physical because all he needs to do is hit me
one time, but it goes the same way. I get to go first. Oh, he's only got two moves right in the
front. Uh, have I secured it? I need to win one more and I win. So coming up next week,
when am I going to stream again? I feel like Monday, Monday and Tuesday. I'll be back on
Monday and I'm not done yet. I'll be done. I'm probably not going to stream for that much longer
though. Uh, but I'll be back on Monday. We'll probably do Monday, Tuesday or Monday, Wednesday
or Monday, Thursday. Uh, we can do baby sensory and you laugh, you lose. I want to set that up for
next week. So I'm trying to think of, I'm probably going to talk to the mods because I want to set
up at least some, you laugh, you lose stuff for next week. Also, I want to make this really clear
too. The nominations are still open in the discord. So if you want to nominate something for worst or
best thing of the year, um, go to the discord. It's the new year's eve discussion, new year's
eve nominations. It's still open. It'll be open till the 15th. So if there's a noise or a face
or a gross hair or a sound that you liked, you have still have about six or seven days to do it.
Stop. It's there. Let's win this tournament now. Discord. Let's win this. I'll be happy if I can
get to a B rank over, get to a rank tonight, which should not be that long after this. I think I'm
doing a lot of damage. I would like to get that skill up though. Maybe we'll focus on skill.
All right. All right. All right. Settle down. Where can I play this on steam right now? It's
on steam. It's on switch and it's on iPad. It's on iOS. Uh, I still win the game. I'm the only
person with one loss. What haven't I fought yet? Well, it says one loss. Is it gun burn? Okay. So
I'll have to fight him twice. I don't want to get that far though. Let's go. It's going to be hard.
I'm going to stay back. Try to get to like 70 or 80 guts. All right. Go bad. Really bad.
Don't get so confused. Come on, dude. All right. Get it. Stop. 36%. 33. Oh,
just stay back. Stay back, stay back, stay back, stay back, back, back, back, back, back, back,
back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back.
I got stun locked. Oh my God. My neck just cracked. Did you hear that? I was like,
uh, I'm tied for first. All right. Huey, Huey needs to lose. I don't want to fight Huey.
All right. Rematch for the championship. I just have to, I have to land it. It's just literally
percentages. It's just RNG. I got to land it. Why does this motherfucker could do three moves in a
row? Oh, all right. All right. This is now it's anybody's game. It's going to come down to the
last hit. Fuck. Dodge it. Dodge it. Dodge it. I'm over. I lose. So he's not ready. So I, I,
I wiped the floor with six straight people and I get this one dickhead that I'm not praising
because I want to keep him at even eat the tablets. Get back in the training field,
get back in the training zone. I got to get that skill up speed. I think is a,
is a lost cause at this point. You need to win a tournament item. Use that nuts oil crane.
Am I getting like, okay. Intelligence. Let's do meditation again. I want the skill and the
make it great. Great. Come on. 16. Nice. We'll do light skill oil, heavy intelligence. Nice.
You can skip the training cut scenes. I know I like to watch them. I think they're cute.
More intelligence. I need that discount for the air entry. So bad. Come on. Discount even 90%
chance to unlock Ray. Now from even 90% chance to unlock Ray from Korea entry air entry,
which you really, really want it. Don't do pop us anymore. Do do Korea. All right. That sounds good.
What item did I just use? What item did I just use right there right now?
Mint. And then what did I do right after that skill mint and then see what I just do.
I don't remember. I meditated. Okay. Holy shit. What's that? It's gonna be worth something huge,
right? I'll take it. All right. Another nut oil, heavy training. All right. I, now I actually,
this week I have to fight something. This is definitely air entry discount. Nice. Okay. All
right. All right. All right. All right. Right. When are the battles? Another male piece of male.
I got to pull. Um, I got to pull them out of retirement because I need to do like all of these.
We got to go get a bug Batman to do see. Yeah. Cause I need the money so I can send him to air
entry. Yeah. I'm going to go do it. One last job here. Okay. I'll do one more drill and then I'm
going to freeze them. Right. I think he cheated. It's okay. I loyalty too. Yeah. Let's go bring,
uh, bug Batman out of retirement. I need that money. I should fuse them. I actually, I looked
at it. It didn't look like I was going to get anything good as a tournament of the IMA versus
Fimbo. You need to win it and attend the meeting after to unlock four breeds. If you don't, you
have to wait four more years. Well, let me focus on a winning a B tournament because I don't know
if I'm going to be able to do any of that. How are you anyways? You okay? I need to place now.
I have to place. If not, then I have to keep this guy here and do this tournament just to get a
thousand. All right. We got a place because he's technically B rank, right? One's dead. What's the
strategy with this guy? Uh, I stab. This is a melee fighter and I got three moves and mainly
I'm just, you try to use this man. I unlocked this one in the front and it's all about just stab.
It's got a high hit percentage. He's usually does have to place. Nice. Stay in close. Don't go that
far away. Why did that do so much damage? Oh, fuck off. Attack who has more health. I think I have
more percentage health, right? Yes. Just win one more. I don't care about winning the tournament.
I care about his prize money. Good luck beating this guy as a melee character, by the way.
Somebody else has to beat him. I'm biting my lip. Stop. Stop it. Stop biting. Don't bite your lip.
I always do this. I'm sorry. The camera's off. I need guts. So let him just kind of hang out here.
Good dodge. Oh, he was confused. I had a chance. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Now you piece of shit.
Get in there. I have so much guts. Just don't care. The clock is counting down.
Okay. He said they're doing this big. Oh, I'm guarding now animation. So you got five seconds
left. Get in there and attack Jerry. You were winning. I don't think I was. He lost. Perfect.
Okay. I need to, if I lose this and it's, I have to fight this guy twice. Good luck. This is going
to be horrible. I don't think I'm going to win. No way. I just have to rely on this dude missing
a lot. So I'm going to pull back. Just bounce, bounce him away. Bounce him away.
I want a ton of guts so I can just stab, stab, stab, stab, stab when there's like 10 seconds
left. Pull him in. Push. Miss. Oh, yikes. All right. Here we go. Got all the prize money.
Oh, we got it. We got advice here. Both Ray. It goes into the four slot, both Ray and beam.
So Ray goes into the first slot. You really end up wanting both. You have to use the move 50 times.
Let's you unlock the upgrade. I definitely want Ray. That sounds like a death move. So we're going
to, we're going to call Ria. You did what you were supposed to do bug Batman. Thank you so much.
Excellent job. We get a little bonus too. Exactly. I'm just so just breaking even. Oh right.
Cause I dropped down a rank. Wait, this is okay. If I combine these two eventually,
something will have way higher base stats, right? If I combine bug Batman and calamity,
base stats could be monstrous. I would give you rest right now, but I can't. We have to go back
to town and I need to bring the other guy back so I can do the air entry. So you can take a rest
here. Come on out. Just let him die. He's come out of retirement too many times. We're not going to
need him again. So it looks like it's going to be rest and then air entry. This is still the same
month, right? Save the game. Rest up. You're going on an errand next week. It's time to spend all of
my money. Why these, why these expensive again? Wasn't this for this month? I thought it was for
the month. It's only for one week. Oh shit. That sucks. Do I give him this Nigel before he goes
on air entry? This is straight up drugs. Should I make him take these drugs? Are these performance
enhancing drugs? No, no, don't. Okay. What about a tasty mango? Here, have a tasty mango. All right,
here we go. We need to go to Korea. Korea? I don't have Korea. I don't have it. What should I do?
Just back to Papas and get the other one. Oh, I have to go to rank B. I can get an intelligence
tech here though, right? I mean, it's worth doing. I'm not going to. Yeah, Papas is fine. Okay. All
right. Speed and life. I don't want speed in life. All right. Fight a D level monster. All right,
how about this rabbit? All right, let's see it. Should breeze through this. I could skip it,
but I like the suspense. Got the skill. Hopefully it's the intelligence one. Awesome.
Mm. Ice quake. I think I failed this last time. I need 40 fame and 140 health. Does this guy not
have 100? Does that not have 40 fame? I play it higher than that. Yeah, I think I got it.
Then when he's, and I don't, by the way, I don't control the monster when you get the random fight
at the end. If I do it just happened. All right. You got it. You got a technique. You're good.
Easy. Were you guys betting on that? The Korea expedition is only available during June week one.
What? It's available for one. I saw I missed it by one, like two minutes. All right. Rest up
tablet. So I'm going to try to do that training regimen again. And this time I will try to actually
win the tournament. Try to go to B rank. All right. You're stressed out. I got it. I got it.
I got it. Remember, look at me. Let's take a look at this move. What is it? I got it. So this is,
takes a lot of mana, 24 guts, but has a much better hit percentage than this
beam. I'm just going to use this every time and it's max range. I can literally just sit back
and just be a camper. That's pretty good. Very cool. All right. Let's start the training regimen.
We're going heavy intelligence and skill, and then we're going to go light skill. You want to play?
I hate that mini game. No, I'm sorry. That mini game sucks. It's the snowball one. I don't want
to play it. I know people are going to think I'm a dick. I know. I really don't want to play it.
Now he's sad and he's sad because I wouldn't play with him this week and I was going to be pissed.
Reset. Right again. He's fine. 561, encroaching on that probably did 600 intelligence.
Now we're going to do skill. Oh, eat your McDonald's. I'm good. I'll be right.
Somebody has a guide for what I should do after B rank. Let me just copy that on the clipboard.
Nice. That's going to be at least a eight to 10, right? It worked. Is this game fun? This game's
very fun. Skill is your hit chance. So the higher my skill and the lower their speed, the better
chance I have to actually hit percentage on all my moves. Click the link. Yeah. I'll look at it later.
Actual good link. That's the guide, isn't it? Give me over 600. It's a picture of your face. Oh,
okay. There is no way I don't win C cup now. I feel like it's impossible. Tablets again. I need
to get to 600. His fame is at 69. I need more mint leaves. What do you think? If you like it,
get some. Okay. Then I got baited into buying and eating one of those and I don't even know what it
did. The link sucks. I'm not clicking it. All right. I'm almost at zero dollars. Don't fuck
around here. What's the next tournament? Oh, eat dinner. I'll be okay. I'm fine. I'm going to stop
streaming in like 2030 minutes. We're going to play this again. Don't worry. This is my new favorite
game ever. So I'm playing again. I, I told you, I am not going to stop playing this till I at least
beat S rank. Oh, this guy's dead. And what? Look at this. I'm going to kill this guy and actually,
actually one hit. In fact, I might kill him instantly. Oh, stay back. What the fuck happened?
What happened? You got to be kidding me, dude. What even happened? I couldn't even attack him.
I have, that guy has 43 intelligence. I have almost six freaking hundred. Why would he, I not
kill him instantly. Well, now I need the, I need to come in second place. Otherwise I'm not going
to get any prize money. See what I'm talking about? This guy just rolled that guy. That guy
just rolled that guy up in a burrito and ate his ass. Ate him. I ate him up. I swallowed him up.
I swallowed him up. And I killed him. Sussvane, you piece of shit. Now you're guaranteed to win.
Utter dog shit. That's what's supposed to be happening. I'm supposed to be drilling their
teeth out with a little teeth driller. There's no reason why I should have lost that. Tell me,
Sussvane, please lose. He's got one more fight. Can we kill Sussvane, please? So I can beat his
ass. Thank you. It's a rematch time. I'm going to melt his face off. That was such a fluke. Absolute
fluke. 43 intelligence. Give me a break. Let's kill him in one hit. Three, two, one, die motherfucker.
That's what was supposed to happen. And I don't know what happened, but I like must have taken
money to fall because there's no way I don't kill him in one hit. I got money again. We do
vigorous training. And then I'm going to go eat McDonald's. 3000. You ate his ass, bro.
Ooh, star prune. I'm about to beat a hundred fame. I'm going to be the most famous monster.
Nice. A seven speed. That's awesome. I want polish. All right. Yeah, sure. Then I'm going to have to
know what this is. He keeps asking me for this. I've spent a thousand dollars in hair cream for
this guy. What does it do? He eats it. But what does it actually do? It's minus stress. Oh, okay.
It's time to do training. When's the next official tournament? All right. I'm going to beat this
tournament. We're going to be rank and then I'm going to go eat McDonald's. Let's train. I'd like
to see skill at 300 and intelligence at like 700. I'll eat a salad. I'm not clicking the link.
You're not getting me to click a link. Do an IRL stream at McDonald's. All right, fine. I'm going
to click it. I'll click it and be done with it. I need a mod to link it to me. What is it? Click
it. I need a mod. There's no links in this chat anymore. You guys have used that for so many years
that I had to delete it. All right. What is it? This is what we've been fighting about. This is
what I needed to see. I had to see this. This is what I needed to see. Very, very important.
All right. This is the last training session I'm going to do before I get him to this tournament
and the gas. Then I'll see you guys again on Monday. Your audio is distinct. It's the camera.
It's because the exposure is high because I don't have enough light in this room.
It's because when my camera's exposure has to be so turned up that turn off your webcam.
Turns out you're the horror. Yeah, I just don't have any professional equipment.
But I don't want to ring light in my face. That sucks. I don't want to do that. What did I say?
What was rude? There we go. Tell me if this fixes it. I'm curious. Okay. Ready? Tell me
if this fixes it. Hey, hi. My name is German95. Good to see you. How are you? Does it work? Is it
better? You see? This sucks. Is it what you're seeing? Hey, does it actually work now? Is it
better? Because my exposure is way down. Yes. Is the frame rate better? Because I can't fix it.
It got worse? How would it have gotten worse? This is what it has to look like right now.
Maybe I'll get a light. Should I get a light? If I had a light that was like here. Like right here.
Or like here. Here. Maybe. Maybe. All right. I gotta go. Let's train. When's the tournament?
Now my eyes are blinking. All right. We're going to do. I want to do this one more time and then
we're going to rest. Fuck it. And then I got the tournament and I'm going to beat it. I do so much
damage. I'm going to just rock everybody here. Now I can rest. Tournament. Bingo. Very well.
Battle. C. All right. This is the big one. I'm ready. And after this, I'm like literally have
to run out of here. I gotta, I gotta get food. You're blinking a lot. Are you okay? I was just
holding a wicked bright ass light in my face. I see like splotches. I'm going to try to kill
everybody in one second. If, if it works, it works. And I'm going to annihilate everybody.
Like this. Good. Very, very good. Minus four months on that dick. That's suspene. Come on,
bring on suspene. You're in the tournament too. Why don't you play cookie run kingdom?
I mean, you're acting like I already haven't spent $5,000 on that game and I'm embarrassed to tell
you. I haven't. All right. Who cares? Oh, it's just a snap of my fingers.
That was so loud. Wasn't it? Let's make it eight. No, this is the only going to work until it
doesn't because when I get to A and S, I'm not going to be able to fuck around like this anymore.
I just want to unlock the new monsters because I know you unlock at least four or five breeds
when you get to rank B or after rank B. Oh, gun burn. Oh, hey, it's good to see you. I just
was curious if you wanted to potentially, my hands are so sweaty. I couldn't snap and it wasn't funny.
You, it was actually like slippery. No, this is not the B tournament, but what if when I
beat the B tournament, I will unlock some more breeds. We can go searching. I'm speed running.
I know I'm just hungry. Die already. Just pull back. Pull back. Oh my fucking God. I'm going to
lose. No, I'm not 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20. I got flaws victory because like this,
I just, I shot them. Like I shot like six beams and not one of them hit. I'm still going to win
the tournament and I'm getting outside. I'm slashing that Zambor's fucking tires. Okay.
It's a tournament. All right. Only two, only three more. I don't want to get too late.
I'm very, very hungry. All right, Nicole. Okay. If this fight takes more than three seconds,
I will piss my pants on scream one, two, two and a half, two and a quarter,
two and a two thirds, two and two fourths, three and four eights, three and four fifths, four and
three and two fourths, two fourths and two fourths, two fourths and three fifths,
two eights and one eight, two eights and four eighties, one and one two fourths, two and a half,
Two and two...seventy orders...and...two and two fiftieths...four and three-fifths...two and three...shit.
I can't...I can't believe I lost that. That was so stupid.
Now I'm not gonna win the tournament. I have to win the next two. I have to...this sucks.
If I don't win this in one second, I will piss my pants again. One...nice.
All right, who else has two losses? It's Nicole. I can still win the championship.
Let's go. Come on. Nicole lose to Suspain. What a...oh my god. Pathetic.
I won. I'm the only one with two losses. That's game over. I win. GG. Good job.
All right. I need to go get food. I gotta get some food.
I'm gonna make my own McDonald's. I'm gonna make the secret sauce. I'm gonna make my patty.
I'm gonna make the lettuce. I'm gonna make cheese and shit. I'm gonna make my own Big Mac.
All right. I'll see you guys later. I actually am gonna run away now,
but this is great because now I can probably do the same thing in B rank.
Excellent work. Am I gonna play more of this? Absolutely. I refuse to give up on this game
unless I beat S rank at least. If you were watching for the game awards,
uh, thanks for watching. I had a good time. It was really fun.
And obviously Monster Rancher is a ton of fun too. We're gonna continue Monster Rancher and
baby sensory videos next week as part of a You Laugh You Lose challenge. And we'll be able to
pick it up immediately on a half-off errant tree, which is awesome. Have a good weekend, guys.
Let me save this. Nice and saved. Awesome. All right. I'll see you guys later. Really
appreciate everybody watching. Take care of yourselves. I'm gonna let the end play out.
Take care, guys. See you on Monday, Monday the 13th. Good night. Thanks for all the subs. There's
a lot of gifted subs too. Here you all are right now. See you guys later. Okay. Good night,
everybody. Stream is ending. Yeah. Good night.