Hold on. I don't know what I did with my drink. My tea is the most important thing on stream.
My green tea or energy drink that I have here is my Spider-Man Iron Man suit. I- I'm sorry.
I need it. Be right back. Peter, if you're nothing without the suit, then you're nothing at all.
Peter, if you're nothing with- without the green tea, then are you really Spider-Man?
Yeah, I still am. It's a drink. I'm fine. Shut up. It's literally green tea. I'll be- I-
I am Spider-Man. Who am I even arguing with? Yeah, people- Oh, Popeye. When Popeye breaks
open the spinach can, he eats the spinach. Iron Man didn't walk onto the set and go,
hey, Popeye, if you're nothing without the spinach, you're nothing at all.
No, Popeye said it's a nutritious fucking thing and I can- I'm gonna knock your lights out,
actually. Who are you- what is he talking about? Do you guys not know what I'm referring to?
I thought you guys watched Marvel movies. What? You don't know? I think they're doing this on
purpose. Yeah, see, I understand. Somebody does. That's from Homecoming. Yeah. Wait, is it? What
movie is that from? That's from Homecoming, right? Yeah, it is. Okay. Anyways, hi, guys. How you
doing? We're gonna be playing some Slime Rancher 2 today. It came out. It's in technically early
access. I liked the last one. I thought the last one was great. So why not try the other one?
How was my birthday? My birthday was great. I had a really good time. Yeah, once you get over 30,
your birthday just is a birthday kind of- it's not like, oh my god, we're gonna- oh,
wear birthday hats. And there's gonna be like a bunch of cake stuff. Well, I actually-
Holly did make me a cake. So, excuse me. That happens at 40. That was a nice day. The big
everybody needs to show up is 40. If you're invited and you don't show up to my 40th birthday,
I may have to cross you off the friends list. Because I mean, really? 40. I don't care if you
miss 31 through 39. That's 40. And I'm gonna be doing it in the McDonald's fucking place.
Somebody just said in pre-stream, he's gonna be really sus today, I can tell. And like, fuck,
I have been. I've been like saying weird shit for the first like 10 minutes.
Why did you know that? Why did you know that I was gonna be really sus today?
You must- I don't know. Somebody must have had some vision or something. But yeah, 40 is when
I'll care. Every birthday from 31- okay, you freak out when you hit 30. And then it just doesn't
matter. At 31 and 32, you're kind of just, I don't really care. 40 is the next big one where
it's, you know, this is zero at the end. It's like, oh shit. Okay, this is another one. Another zero.
But I appreciate all the birthday wishes I saw. There's a lot of cool artwork and people saying,
at birthday, thank you. It surprises that many people on the internet who would
say that to some random guy who has gone on record talking about
putting baseballs up his ass. So, I mean, thanks. I appreciate it. I hope we can have a good time
still today. Here's to 39 more baseballs. But that's implying that I'm 39. I'm 37. You got
it wrong. Actually, I would much rather people think that I was older. I kind of pre-bake
my birthday. Does anybody else do this? Maybe you do this when you're after 30.
But I have been telling- oh, how old are you? Oh, and I'm 37. Even though I wasn't. Just because,
like, I need to prepare for being older. So now, maybe like six to seven months from now,
I'm just going to be like, yeah, I'm like, you know, I'm 38 pretty much. I'm turning 38. I'm
probably 38 soon. 38. So then when I'm actually 38, it's like, oh, I've been saying- it doesn't
matter. I'm prepared for it. I do that too, kind of. Yeah. All right, let's go. Slime Rancher 2.
Welcome, everybody. I do that too. Yeah, it makes it easier. It makes it more palatable for your
brain. Just say you're 40 now and prepare for it. I don't know if I want to do that. All right,
is this game good? How is it? This game good? Yeah. I've seen a few slimes and they're cute.
Okay, it's the same as one, but better. Okay, let's go. Tar? Oh, well, you can disable the
bad slimes. Huh. Okay, well, one time- how high can you go? One and a half times damage?
We're just- we're just playing the regular way. I'm not doing anything weird. Is there a cutscene?
After a long day of slime ranching, Beatrix Laboo was enjoying a cool glass of carrot juice as she
watched the sun set across the slime sea. Suddenly, a boat arrived at her dock with nothing
inside but a mysterious letter. You've explored the far, far range from the dusty shores of the
dry reef to the furthest reaches of the perilous glass desert. There are worlds yet uncharted,
Beatrix Laboo. Rainbow Island awaits you. Climb aboard if you're ready for a new adventure.
Beatrix excitedly boarded the boat and took it across the slime sea. Eventually, she saw an
island unlike anything on the far, far range. Mountains, trees, and grasses all in an array
of colors that danced and moved like a dream. As she explored, she found an abandoned conservatory
overlooking the rest of the island. Curiously, it was equipped with everything a slime rancher
like her would ever need to wrangle slime, start a farm, and build gadgets. That was- that scared
the shit out of me. And so, a new adventure begins. Beatrix tightened her boots, readied her
vac pack, and set out to explore Rainbow Island and uncover its mysteries. I don't know, it was a
loud screaming noise. How- it scared me a little. All right, sensitivity's way too high. Let's try
that. It feels a little bit better. All right, moving around. This game looks like the graphics
have increased a little. There's a lot of bloom. It looks pretty good. All right, vac pack. Yep,
suck in slimes. I remember this. Yeah, then you got to shoot them through the barrier, right?
So, is that- no, that's not it. That's not it. That's not- that's wrong.
Shoot through a cor- yeah, here we go. Then they sit here. They shit out money. Okay, so they eat
fruit, veggies, and meat, right? Cool. Okay, so then- oh, here's the marketplace, right? Just E.
Basic player controls. Okay, I think I got it. So, this game just kind of assumed that you finished
the first one and we're downloading the second one and it's like, let's go. What- let's go,
right? Like, that's it. Let's go. So, I need to feed them. What do I get the food? Don't you- don't
you plant berries and shit too? Is there a map? There is. Okay, so where am I? I think we're going
to get Elden Ringed. I think it looks like it, right? It kind of looks like it, doesn't it?
Put the cam in a different place. Okay. Oh yeah, chickens, right? Food like fruits,
veggies, or chickens. Hold on. I got it. I might be a weirdo, but does anybody else agree with me
that music in the background of a game? Just- I hate it. I just- I want it to be quiet and I'm a
weirdo. I've done this- um, I've tested this theory where if I turn the music off during, like,
Dark Souls or Elden Ring, I will play five times better at a boss. So, you know how the boss
musics are always like, if I turn that off, I will beat that boss fucking 100 times easier.
Okay, so I get to get food. All right, try shooting food at a pink slime. They'll eat anything.
They'll eat chickens? I thought they didn't- I thought they only ate berries.
Oh, how do I only pick up the money? When slimes eat, they make plorts. Head on over to the
plort market and cast your pillow. Okay, depends on the game. Yeah, I really do. I- you know what,
it's definitely like a concentration problem or like an ADHD problem, but if I turn all the sounds
off and I just do it visually, I will- I will first try every boss in Dark Souls. Here we go.
How much money do I got? 261. Get out there and explore. So, we're just going. All right, so now
I got- how much is it to do another pen? Happy slime makes for a happy- okay, this is two-
250. I have to produce food. I gotta do a garden, right? Prove it. Prove it. I don't have Dark Souls
ready to go. I'm doing a garden. Yeah, shoot a veggie or fruit into the depositor to begin
growing more of that type. Yeah, this is what I want because I gotta start- that was one thing,
was food was always a huge problem. Where's my wi-fi off? All right, let's go. I'm just gonna go
straight to the front door. Install it right now. I'm not- no, I'm not gonna install Dark Souls to
turn all the music off and beat champion Gundyr in one minute. It's- I don't- I don't- I'm not
gonna do that. Silent. Hold on. Just prepare it in a different window? That sounds like you want to
do it. Carrots. How many can fit in one pen? Pomegranates? Just do it. Just do it. I don't
have a save file that's at any boss. They would have to be the first boss of any of those games.
Slimes. Well, that's a bunny. Yep. Fog fruit. Oh, shit. Large slimes are large,
formed when slimy support- I'm like- I forgot. Right. All right, I'm going back. I'm going back.
I'm going back. Okay, there's the garden. I'll do a big pen over here. Stay right there.
All right. Oh, it's like incinerator. Pond. Okay, right. So I want to do this. I only have 11 bucks.
Never mind. Will you just hang up over here if I feed you? All right, should I do fog fruit or-
I'm gonna do carrots. All right, yeah. Carrots. And then we'll feed you- Here you go, guys. Going in.
They eat anything, right? Let's make some fucking money. He's gonna eat somebody. How do I suck up
just the money? Oh, I need to build that, don't I? I think I have to actually build it.
Okay, this is growing, right? Yep. Floor vacuum for the pen. Yeah. So what are these worth?
1.11? That's not bad. Cool. All right. The market changes too, doesn't it? On a daily basis.
I need to make a cabinet, whatever. A chickadoo? Shit, I don't have money.
What do you like that? That's what a chickadee does. And apparently that's only cute to your
girlfriend. Apparently. Apparently doing that on the couch going like, it's only cute to your
girlfriend. Okay. Oh, he's gonna be sus today. Boy, it's nighttime. You have to sleep, don't you?
You're nearly 40. So I'm 40, so therefore I cannot ever for the rest of my life
imitate a chickadee for the rest of my entire life. No, I refuse. Hey, dude, what's that bird?
That birds have like a pretty interesting, you know, you know that call, that bird call.
No, I don't. I don't. I'm 40. Oh, but you know, it's like, it's like,
how do you do it? I've heard you do it before. No, no, I'm 40. I can't make that sound.
Yes, it's a fucking bird sound. You're fine. No, I can't. I'm 40. I can't make sounds.
I'm going to be, I don't care. I'm going to make sounds until I'm dead. You understand that when
I'm in my death bed and there was rotten. Oh, no, it's just nighttime. When I'm lying in my
death bed and I'm connected to like about, you know, what it's I'm like 90 or something, like
a hundred and everyone's like gathered around the bed and everyone's like, oh, let's just say
goodbye to grandpa. Right. You bet your ass that I'm going to be like, you bet your fucking ass.
That's the last thing I'm leaving you with. All right. I need to make it. I need more money.
Yeah. And what they don't know, it was me making that noise. I'm all right. I got at least another
few days. Come back tomorrow. Can't make sound effects anymore. What is it? All right. So I need
more money. I need, when, how long does it take to grow? Probably a little while, right? I'm just,
I'm just going to go sleep. Death bed stream. You know how fucked up that would really be though?
How are you getting out? Stop. I got you. I got you. I got you. I got you.
Can you imagine if like, I, you know, I retire, whatever, and then you just don't really hear
from me at all. I fall into complete irrelevancy over the course of like 40 years. And then one day
you're a complete, you're completely grown up to, and you're like fifties or sixties or seventies
and you get a notification on whatever device you have. You're still following that. I went
live today and it's me lying there. It's like, I wanted to make sure I went out with everybody's
here on Twitch. I don't know where it would be. Would you guys be there if you were like 75? All
right. I'll get enough money to make those then. I don't know if you would. Okay. You'd probably
look at your phone or your, you know, holographic fucking eye cameras and just be like, nah, I don't
think so. Is that too much going on? Okay. 300 bucks. I need more food. That's, you're immoral.
I mean, I'm not actually going to stream the last moments of my life in a hospital. Like why would
I, that's, I'm not going to, when I'm like a hundred? No. Should I do a coop? I think so. Okay. I
need chickens in there. I think I have too many, right? There are too many. I need way more food.
I'll be back. Now you said immortal, not immoral. Yeah. I need way more food. Merch for your deathbed
stream. That's fucked up. All right. I need way more food. What is this? Is it oil? Get tombstone
shirts. Ooh. Okay. Can you mark anything on the map or you just have to kind of browse around?
I'm going a little too far. Discover map data nodes across the range to uncover more of your map.
These mushrooms. I need to upgrade. Honestly, I'm just trying to get as many carrots as I can.
And, um, get these too. You have to pay for the deathbed stream. Wait, there's a new, hold on.
Tabby slime. Oh, I remember these. Refinery. Refinery links conveniently transport resources
and ports to the, what did it say? I can send stuff from the world to the farm. That's pretty
cool. Okay. Okay. It tells you what they like. Favorite is chickens. It doesn't really have a
favorite. Favorite is blue ice cream or something, whatever it is. Water lettuce. Interesting. What
if they banned you right before you do? Yeah. Cause I would be dying on camera, right? Then
you're going to get the, not like this disconnect thing. Can you imagine they caught it right at
like, right at like the flat line. Okay. I gotta go back. Oh, can you mark stuff on the map?
Streams is going to lag. You drop a bunch of frames. We come back from a disconnect.
Community Jake like walks into the frame for a minute. Hey, hey, can you die again?
We, we, we lost a connection. I don't know what we lost. What do you see?
All right. I got 20 carrots. I'm ready. What's that? Ooh, that's the lettuce stuff. Don't touch
that. That's mine. Um, I want to grow that probably, right? Don't touch it. Water lettuce. I
want to grow this. This is somebody's favorite, right? Yeah. I got to grow this. Am I going the
right way? Yeah. This game's fun. This game is just like the other one. Okay. Here's the thing
about Slime Rancher. Starting over in Slime Rancher was always like, I don't think I really
want to do that. I think I've seen what the game is and I've seen everything I really want to do.
Would I have loved to have memory wiped myself and played Slime Rancher one again, because I
loved that initial kind of playing the port market and making money and making pens and stuff.
So this is, I just memory wiped and I'm playing Slime Rancher again. So this is great. I'm very,
I'm very happy. Hey, hey, sometimes people just want more and you just give them more.
What's wrong with that? I bet you this is probably some new tools and stuff. The map's probably a
lot bigger too. It feels like it. All right. Let's go. All right. I'm back. I've got a bunch of
carrots. Um, okay. Here you go. Well, don't jump out. You know what? You just, there's, there's too
many. So, but you should eat. I want you to eat something. All right. 20. Was it worth? I went
down. What the fuck? It was 11 bucks. Now it's 10. Okay. I can do another. I swear to God,
I thought this was Jerma in the casket. Okay. I think I've seen this before, but hold on.
Am I, does somebody edit me into this? This looks like I'm, am I edited into this picture?
I thought this was Jerma in the casket. I swear to God, I thought this was Jerma in the casket.
What is this? What movie is this from? No, don't vote. Hold on. It's so hard to do this.
All right. Get this off the fucking screen. I'm still alive, but this chin is way too big. Hold on.
Oh, I'm done. It's so, you know, it's like, it's, you know, how hard it is to make the adjustments
over here and be upside down. This is my soul. Look at, we're looking into each other's souls.
No, no, no. Wait, wait, hold on. Then I wake up. I have to go back into my body.
I'm the spirit flying in like, I'm in. And now it's me. I have to go back into my body.
How big was this webcam? Jerma ghost? That is like fucked up though. It actually does look
ridiculous. Make it mirrored. No, I'm supposed to like go fly down, right? You did this bit
three years ago. No, I didn't prove it. Hey, prove it. Don't you understand? Like,
it's a series of recycling a joke from five years ago over and over again.
You did? When? Oh, when I, I was going to say, when was I in a casket on stream doing like a
routine where I fly back into my body? It's like that never happened. Oh, okay. I know what you
mean. When I died on stream and I came out of the, okay. I remember. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I thought you meant that exact scenario right there. Okay. Yeah, I did do that. You're right.
All right. I want, I got to make, I could take some chickens over here. Let's do another garden
because I want to grow this water lettuce because it's the bunny's favorite, right?
When was that? 2018? 2017? Because then I'm going to put these guys over here. All right. I got to
get more food. There are definitely way too many, but whatever. This is before hit and run. Yeah,
I would think so. There we go. Come here. Nice. All right. I need to put these in the pen.
It was January, 2019. Oh, yeah. Close enough. All the viewers. This game is pretty. It is really
pretty. That's growing. I'll put the, who's is the favorite, right? Thumbnail, the thumbnail.
I don't get it. All right. I want to know. No, that's not what I want. I think I just have to,
I don't want to lose the whatever. I just got to get more food until I can grow up myself.
Let's go. Just more carrots, more fruits, more vegetables. I don't want to lose the cats though.
Suck in your cheeks, raise eyebrows and smile at the camera. I don't get it. Can I touch my elbow?
Who cares? All right. I'm just trying. I'm just getting food. That's all I want. I don't care
about ports right now. Just food. That's all I want. And I fold my tongue. No, I can do this.
I can't do anything. Oh no. Can you, somebody said, can you fold your tongue? And I said, no,
I don't think I thought I could. You can't. Does it work? Stop. What? He's left brain,
right brain Andy right now. What? Wouldn't that just mean a complete brain? Wouldn't that mean
that I go fine? Left brain, right brain Andy. What's it mean? You mean like one's taking control
for five seconds and the other one takes over for five seconds? Oh, they had a test in high school
saying stuff like you're left brained if you can roll your tongue and vice versa. It was dumb.
Oh, I see. All right. Let me get some money now. American education moment. I always forget which
one is which. What's left brain is the analytical kind of mathematics one, right? And then right
brain is the more artistic, whatever it is. Reverse that. Okay. It's crazy how we have all these
theories and is there, is there science to back that up? Is it like, oh yeah, by the way,
that is what it is. I wonder how much that gets refined in like another hundred years.
Like, is how we view the brain and kind of our bodies right now going to turn into how we view
people bleeding people because they had a cold? Like, oh yeah, you have the sniffles. Let's remove
half your blood. Do you think that eventually like in two, three, 400 years people are going
to look back and be like, what were they talking about? Wait, they thought they thought that they
had a left and right brain. I bet it's going to be, it's weird thinking about that. Just like,
what is going to be completely outdated science and education wise in a hundred years? Because
we are going to be that group that looks back and goes, holy shit. Yeah. Fuck in like 50 plus years.
It's possible. No, maybe not in our lifetime. Maybe like another two lifetimes. We, you're the
one that's 40 dude. That okay. I'm not that old. All right. I got 320. What's okay. It's time to
make a pen and time to feed bunnies their favorite foods, which is water lettuce. Let's do it. This
is where the money starts to actually roll here. Pretty, pretty, pretty big. Here you go. Look at
they love it. You're 20 years older than me. Dang. All right. These are, these are worth like 20 or
30, aren't they? You guys happy? Good. Remember you're as old as my step mom. Wait, these are
a good value. Yep. Seven. Oh hell yeah. Hell yeah. I said almost as old. Yeah. But, but how,
what do you mean? Oh, are we talking like 45? Cause that's, I'm not even close. All right. So now
I think it's time to go to sleep. How do I upgrade this stuff? Okay. Here we go. Nutrient soil
contains compost from the rainbow fields and minerals from Ember Valley makes crop always
yield the maximum harvest grow twice as fast. I want that. So we're going to save up for it.
I guess they will eat anything, right? So then, so now from my understanding, if I feed a, you,
you feed a plot of a different slime to a different slime and it becomes something else. Right. So I
take this and then I feed this to one of them over here. Right. That's what, if I remember,
except that they, what are they doing? They're trying to escape. Okay. Well, whatever. Well,
I'm not going to do that yet. I don't think I'm prepared for that yet. So I'm going to go to bed.
This game, I love this game. It's just as fun as the other one. It's just more of that,
but it's somehow new. Let's go. How's the audio? Audio good? Is the sound high enough? Low enough?
Nobody wants meat yet. So that's fine. All right. I'm going to go out and do another,
another poll. I'm just going to go out and just do another poll. You're not 40. You got plenty of
time. I know. I look, I don't care how if I'm 40. You think, are you serious? You don't think I'm
still going to, you don't think I'm still going to pull my pajama pants all the way up to below my
breasts, my leg area, my chest, whatever. And with super Mario pajama pants on and like put my hands
down and walk around. Like, I just have legs in the house. You think I'm going to stop doing that?
My, they're like chest muscle. What am I, my breasts, my breast or area, whatever this is,
my sternum. What is it? What is this called? My under my chests. My, what? I didn't even want
to kill that thing and I just did accidentally. Pectoral muscles. Thank you. No, torso is down
here. This is chest muscles. All right. Chest, whatever. Pectorals. But anyways, my point was,
I'm not going to just stop doing that, which I haven't gone over there this way. What about
down here? I don't think I've gone over here. Mushrooms? Me when the, oh, you didn't finish it.
What's this? Ah, all right. Hydro turret blueprint. That sounds pretty, um, pretty sick.
What was that? What just happened? That was weird. It was like a little rock that had stuff in it.
Nothing. Me when the, whatever. I wasted it. Yeah. Maybe more food. I mean, I'll just take these.
Why not? It's free money. Look at this. Look at all this.
Have you seen this? You can see this, right? What do they call it? Oven when you, hold on. Why do
they call it oven when you in of out the cold food and in out hot eat the food? I don't know.
I don't know what that means. They did it wrong. Why do they call it oven when you of in the cold
food of out eat? I feel like my head hurts. What is this from Garfield? Why do they call it oven
when you of in like put in cold food? It's an edit. Okay. Hmm. I need more food. Oh, I need,
okay. Yeah, this is, okay. You know, I'm, this is, I, no, I'm not going to say it, but like, man,
this is, this is the, this is my kind of game. This is my kind of game, especially, you know,
if I was sitting on the couch. Oh, this would be a great couch game. Just sitting on the couch.
Oh yeah. I think I'm all right now. I got 20. This puts me over the edge. Now I can do the
faster growing. Yeah, it was, it was made up. Okay. Look up Garfield, but minus Garfield.
I have way better things to do with my time than that bullshit. Okay. Like beating carrots to slimes.
The original comic is a fun comic. It makes John look crazy. I've actually seen it before and it's
very funny. Wait, didn't somebody do like Garfield, but as like a Lovecraftian monster? There was a
lot of Garfield material. It's all, it's all very funny. It's John just saying stuff to his pet cat.
You know, uh, but isn't that kind of already fucking happening? Isn't John just kind of
talking to his cat? Is it even confirmed that Garfield can even really actually talk? Right?
Like that's already happening. Like John is just talking to nothing. That's already a thing. What's
wrong with them all? Something wrong? Veggie diet. This is not a vegetable. Oh shit. Okay.
It's a fruit. You're right. Does anybody have their favorite example of the Garfield-less John comic?
One of the mods want to link me one? You guys want this. I'm just going to let them go. This is way
too many. Let me see this one. Oh my God. Stop moving other stuff. Why is this locked? Remember
the time yesterday when I almost ate a donut? These are fucking funny. Hold on. This one too.
Something wrong with my pants. I do this shit like every day. I like this one. Stop making toast.
But is he making the toast? What is happening in this one? What is happening in this one?
Yeah. This one's sad. This one's really sad. Oh my God. This is so awful. I'm going to throw
myself a surprise party. Gosh. I hope I don't suspect anything. Oh man. This is just fucked
up. He looks so happy in the second picture. I don't know. Poor John. Now those are fucking
wild. What? Oh, some of these are so bad. Some of these are bad. I don't. Oh, I don't like it.
Okay. Last one and then we're done. Yeah. Those are, those are, those are fucking classic. All
right. Let's go. You have some plorts and new bucks to spare. I don't get it. What do you mean
you don't get it? He's, Garfield's supposed to be on the chair. So they edited Garfield out of the
chair and Garfield's too lazy to get out of the chair. So he just drags the chair with Garfield
in it to the vet. But you see that he's been removed. So he's just dragging a chair to the vet
and looks, um, a little, a little weird. So you get it, right? All right. I got a lot of money.
I got to go to the lab underneath the conservatory. All right. Where is that?
I have to go in the conservatory. How do I get down there? Oh, feed them, feed them. I was too
busy looking at funny Garfield list comics. I'm sorry. This is what I'm talking about.
What does this do? I don't want this yet. Oh, right. You have to, you can make shit. All right. Um,
I need resources. Okay. When are you going to do Garfield shorts movie night? Um, I don't know if
what conspiracy you want to believe or what you want to look into or what, what it is about
Garfield, but Garfield has stayed around. He is the test of time has shown that Garfield is now a
super meme and people think Garfield's really funny and shit. Even, even unironically, right? Or
ironically Garfield, there was the meme stuff that came over the last 10 years or so. And I don't
think any other old comic strip like that has really stuck around in the mainstream kind of
meme world like Garfield has. I'm trying to think if there's other ones, not really Dilbert. I don't
know about Dilbert. I don't think so. The peanuts. Yeah. But the peanuts, kind of the peanuts are
sort of, they have that new show, right? On whatever it is like, like Apple TV or something.
But, but Garfield took on this next level kind of ironic humor. The peanuts don't have that.
Garfield's kind of turned into Shrek in a way. If either that, that comparison makes sense
or like Peter Griffin, like Garfield turned into like Peter Griffin with people just kind of
put them everywhere. If just as a funny joke. All right. I got to spend some money. Shrek is Shrek.
Yeah, no, I mean, of course. I mean, Shrek is in the Library of Congress. This is one of the most
important films ever made. But they've, okay, they're very hungry. All right. I got it. I got it.
Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Oh my God. What have I done? What's happening?
Oh my God. I'm sorry. How do I, what do I do? Hold on. Everybody hold on. Relax. Relax. Relax.
Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. If I sneeze, then I, if I sneeze,
then I'm going to come into 500 million dollars with no strings attached at some point in the
very near future. Okay. Not going to happen. All right. Eat, eat, eat, eat. It's in there. Come on.
All right. There we go. I was making, what do you mean? I was making a joke that if I sneezed right
there, like I thought I was going to, because it was coming, that I'm going to, if I sneeze,
I get a million dollars, right? The non sequitur. Irma hallucinates and thinks he owns a dog. Wait,
this is pretty much what you just were looking at. I'm going to leave him here. Come on. Turn this
down. Have I ever seen this video? Is this going to be like a Toy Story scenario where like I leave
the room. He doesn't know that this is recording. He gets up and starts walking on fucking two legs.
I'm not the dog. This is not like dog. I'm not the dog. If you just got in here, like a minute ago,
listen, the microphone's down here right now. Listen to me. I haven't washed my hair in two days.
I've conditioned it twice. I'd haven't done that because after VR, my hair gets wicked
fucked up and I'm afraid to wash it because I'm afraid it'll fall out. Why is, why are you,
why are you saying this? I'm going to do it today. Why are you saying this?
All right. So you're probably asking why am I doing this? No, I, yes, I am. I am asking that,
Jeremy. I fucked up the sus and the sus said there was a scream today for the last two days
and I didn't even know there was a scream that was scheduled for today until like a half an hour ago,
40 minutes ago. Oh, come on. What's this? Get up there like that. There you go. Now you look better.
I didn't know there was going to be a stream today, but now apparently there is.
I told you guys that anybody that was in the fake pre-stream chat that we were going to do an auto
stream. It really is John Artbuckle. This is literally going to be like 30 minutes. I'm just
doing this because I got guilt tripped by pre-stream because I, you know, this is a guilt trip stream.
Got me. Come right, go there exactly. Oh, here comes a full body reveal of the dog. Oh, no,
nevermind. Well, I know what it'll make me get up. It'll move for his favorite toy. Just you wait.
Flamingo. See? Oh dude, auto reveal. I didn't get the fuck out of the way.
What if he's just like shit on the carpet right now? Hey, don't do anything. Get daddy in trouble.
Just like spins around and just like dumps right here. Do you see the finger? Look at the finger.
Look at the finger. Oh, hey, hey, don't do anything. Look at this weird edited shit.
Just like spins around and just like dumps. Is that a fake hand? It's going to be like a
Toy Story scenario where like I leave the room. He doesn't know that this is recording. He gets
up and starts walking on fucking two legs. Oh, no, I gotta get the dog. I'm blocking the view of the
dog. Hey, did that just join the stream? Welcome. Have we seen this? Today's a subscriber. Uh,
what day is it? Tuesday. Welcome to subscriber Wednesday. He's going to get me. He's going to
get me. I'm not the dog. This is not like dog. I'm not the dog. If you just got in here like a minute
ago. I'm just putting this in my mouth. It's not rolling around. I know. I can't seem to move.
Oh, no, please. You have to rescue me. Oh, I can't get up. Oh, no, I can't. I can't seem.
I'm trying to do it. I, this is so sad. No, it's not sad when it was the John Arbuckle ones were sad.
This is a human, normal human behavior. Those of you that are wanting to eat that may have come out
of my mouth. That's enough of that. That's enough of that. That's enough of that. Completely normal
behavior. All right. All right. Okay. All right. What is that? So sad. It's not sad. It's a funny
joke. Oh my God. Look at all this cash. I can't pick up more than one slot. Really? Why not?
Prices are going down, but I need the money. Okay. Everybody good. Everybody has been fed.
Everybody's good. Head back over here. I'll go bring you guys some carrots.
What is happening with these two? Why are they fused together? Is that, is this a new feature?
Can they like fuse together? That's interesting. Okay. I need. All right. I got another nod. All
right. I'm going to come here. Okay. No, they weren't fused together. I'm going to get rid of
a couple because I don't, I'm running out of the ability to feed everybody. So I'm going to combine
because I don't want the pink, the pink florts anymore. We're going to do some combinations
here. I'm going to do, uh, there. Okay. That's too many. Just go, go be free over there somewhere.
Who wants carrots? Uh, all right. Cool. You can upgrade the, uh, yeah.
Yeah. I know. I don't know how they, that's how, okay. We're going to do one more poll and then
I'm going to buy a bunch of upgrades. All right. That's the last poll. Do the chickens have to eat?
I forget, or they just kind of exist, right? Do you have to feed the chickens? No, no. Okay.
All right. I'm going to upgrade this pen so they, okay, they can't bounce out. That's a good thing
to have, especially because it could be the bigger ones are going to be here. That one's pretty good.
That one's huge. Yeah. I want this one too. And then the auto feeder is, uh,
will be coming after that. All right. Everybody in. I'm going to make them, I'm going to feed them
these, right? And we'll make a bunch of big ones. That sounds like a good idea. What's this? Oh,
hello. Hello. I'm sorry. Beatrix, do you read me? Testing, testing. Hmm. Perhaps you're lost at sea
taken away. Oops. Nope. Just forgot to turn on the display. Nice to see your face again, Beatrix.
I've missed you greatly, my dear friend. And while I'm quite excited for you to partake in
a new adventure, I already have data that might complicate things. Last night I received a message
from some sort of artificial intelligence program written in code, but not one I recognize. I'm in
the process of analyzing it, but I'm certain this message was sent from where you are now. Okay.
Mysterious boat takes you to a mysterious island and is a mysterious code from a mysterious island.
Curious. Well, thanks for literally zero info. Take this home portal. It should make the early
stages of your journey easier. That's good. And teleport back the town portal. Okay. It's time to
make big pink bunnies. Will they still like the lettuce that I'm making? I wonder. Hello. Well,
there we go. Nice. They will. Okay. So I need some, I'm going to go to bed when I wake up. The food
will probably be ready. I'm so goddamn excited. Do bunnies and cats actually probably better. I
do. I need a place to put them though. I guess what do they eat? Could I put them in the same pen
or are they going to, is there going to be a problem? Are they eating each other? They eat.
Okay. Happy slimes eat meat. All right. Here we go. It's going to start to get crazy in here.
Oh, and lettuce is ready. Okay. They, I caught in Tappy Largo. All right. Veggies. They're going to
get out. I need to buy that thing. Oh no. That's bad. How do I, are there too many? Oh shit. Okay.
Hold on. Air net. I need some money. I got to get the air net. Is this game worth it? 100%. Yes.
If you actually, honestly, if you've never played it, how much content is in the early access?
425. A lot. Okay. Is it, is it almost feature complete? Would you say it's at least 15 hours?
All right. Well then yeah, then it 100% is worth it. I know I'm, I know I'm coming with some,
some food. I need more chickens. All right. I'm going to go on a chicken run. Elder rooster. Okay.
Well, okay. Tappy port. What are these worth? All right. Where's the thing that collects the ports?
There it is. Okay. All right. Cool. Let's go. 28. That's worth a lot. All right. Let me get a
roof on this. I think there's too many. Are there too many? Are there too many in here? I think so.
Yeah. All right. I need to go and do some exploring. Oh, the carrot's not done. I need to go explore.
I've got to get some stuff. I'm going on a generic food run. I'm going to head here and then to the
left. Food run. Has he done the beat box thing yet? I think so. Yeah. Chickens, fruits, vegetables,
everything. Anything I can get. Okay. Yep. Is this thing? I want 20 of each. I got to get ahead of,
uh, ahead of myself here. Otherwise I'm going to be in a lot of trouble. Just am. Pod decoration.
Oh, I'm in this area now. All right. Where's one of those map pods? I have a question. So
I get a very important question. I keep getting on my YouTube homepage. Just I open up YouTube
and there it is. Gatorade pod videos. What is this? What is a Gatorade pod? You should watch it.
It's Gatorade. These little globes that people like into this container. It's not a Gatorade.
It's like a Gatorade syrup that you put into a, I guess, a travel kind of sip thing. I'm trying
to figure out what, what the application for that is. It's a make your own Gatorade. Right. But
why not just buy a Gatorade? Is it cheaper? What is, what's, what is it? Oh, I have like the red
Gatorade syrup that I turn it upside down and like into this special device that has to puncture the
thing. Why not just buy a red Gatorade? It's less plastic. No, it is expensive. It is. Wait, those
are good. It's a reusable bottle and you can dilute it. Maybe less plastic. One bottle in small pods.
Wouldn't like powder with like a paper kind of bad, like, you know, a paper container be better
than a plastic pod. But it just, it wouldn't be, powder would be bad or something. I mean, it's
still, I just keep seeing these videos and I'm just like, what, what is it? This is Gatorade pods?
That word. So just Kool-Aid. I mean, yeah, but just wait, does Kool-Aid have electrolytes
or is it just like food coloring and sugar? I don't think, I don't think Kool-Aid is a Gatorade.
It's, it's like yummy, delicious flavoring and sugar and food coloring. It's what less waste
overall because it's a reusable bottle. All right. I get it. Okay. So it's a, it's a, maybe it's a way
for Gatorade to be like, Hey, look, we have all these plastic bottles and we're going to shrink
our bottles to like 10% the size and you have to turn it upside down and like, like load it.
It's, it's almost like a little, it's a little canister. It's weird. This thing eats fruit.
Oh, no, I'll come back here versus right here. There was a specific reason why I came out here
and it was to collect 20 of each food and I'm going to stick to it. All right. I'm pretty close.
I just need some more. I got enough chickens. That's fine. The reason he's getting it on
YouTube is there's a big marketing push for it. Should I try it? Do you want to do like a Gatorade
pod stream review? No. All right. I brought food. Oh yeah. This is going to be huge now.
Look at how much money I'm about to make. They seem to want you just to do Kool-Aid instead.
What was the, what was the tier list that I want to do when I'm just sitting there? IRL.
Oh, cheese. I want to do a cheese tier list because of all the goat cheese bullshit.
All right. Can I get in there? Yeah. I want to do a cheese tier list. I talked about this with
Holly. She was like, you're going to like shit your pants. I was like, no, no, no. It's going to be
cubes, little cubes of each one. All right. This will put me in. It's going to be a lot of money
here. This is going to be a big payday. I can upgrade this pen. This pen kind of sucks.
I surely you probably won't shit your pants. I mean, if I do it correct, I mean, I was okay
on the last one. I will say I felt a little odd after eating all that random shit. You need at
least two to three variants of goat cheese to get a real, I, I promise I will get real goat cheese.
I will get the good stuff. I had a big argument with the mods by the way. There was, there was a,
there was a blowout in the mod chat on the discord. I was told that my opinions were
absolutely fucking meaningless. That they were disgusted that I said that goat cheese tasted
like dirt and it was, it was a blowout. So I was told this specific goat cheese you need to eat.
Don't just eat the random shit from like the random restaurant that puts it on top.
So I agreed. I said, okay, I will eat a specific good one and we'll see how I feel.
And it's got to be a blind taste test. Okay. Okay. That's fine. I'm going to know when it's
goat cheese because I'm going to want to puke when I eat it. This is not a Coke versus Pepsi
scenario. This is a Coke versus, this is a Coke versus a can of creamed corn that I have to drink.
I'm going to tell what's wrong with creamed corn. It's just so different. And I'm so
get out of here. Get out of here. You're not supposed to be over here.
You know, I actually don't, when was the last time I had creamed corn for all the people in the chat
that are calling me, yeah, what the fuck do you, you, you creamed corn, your elitist creamed corn.
I mean, when was the last time you ate creamed corn? I don't think you even could tell me.
I couldn't. I don't. When was the last time you ate a can of creamed corn? Today. Was it good?
Never in my whole life. LMAO. Never in my life. I feel like I've had it. Okay. It's not bad. It's
just kind of, it's a little off-putting. Cream corn is good. I don't remember the last time I
even had it. Had it been mixed in with something else, like a casserole or something, like a
Thanksgiving casserole. I don't know. One of your subs is named creamed corn. You better be nice.
I didn't say that it was bad. I just said I didn't, but I said it was kind of gross, but it is.
It tastes fine. Oh, that's good. We definitely want to make this better. Music box. Cream corn tier
list. Everyone is pinging me. Omega lul. You put creamed corn in F tier during the Thanksgiving
tier list last stream. I did? Um, I should probably get this, right? Yeah. That's a 46
month sub and that's the treatment you're giving a 46 month sub. Um, all right. Money's going to
start flowing here. You guys are all right. I think I need to take care of you. Oh, you know,
they've been fed. They've been fed. You should apologize. I mean, I'm no, no, I'm not going to.
I don't like creamed corn. I would not eat it from a can. I would not eat it with a fan. I would
not eat it in your house. I wouldn't even eat it with a mouse. I wouldn't eat it here or there.
I wouldn't eat it with a bear. I can't rhyme any other words. I don't know. Pretend like I did,
well, like a little bit more and then I eat it and I'm like, Oh, you wouldn't eat with a mouse.
Okay. I need more of, I think I need to separate some of these out because they're, they're,
they're doing another pen. I'll get one ready. I would not eat it on a bus. As you know,
that would make me sus. Yeah. But you had time to come up with that. You had time to sit there and
go. I didn't have that opportunity. Let's get some of the nighttime ones. Maybe I should go to sleep.
All right. I'm going to go to sleep. Mods are saying that they're a good chatter.
I don't know. All right. This is really funny to me, but they're a good chatter. They've only
been timed out. Now think about this, right? Just think about this. The mod is telling me,
no, they're a good chatter. They're good. They didn't, they're no problems. They didn't have
anything fucked up or okay. Whatever. They've only been timed out 91 times. That seems,
that seems like kind of a lot. That just goes to show you how much you guys misbehave here.
Look at how much you guys misbehave. Most frequent chatters have over a thousand timeouts,
over 999 plus timeouts for a, for a, a frequent chatter here. That is actually an incredible
ratio. Wow. I'm sitting here thinking, Oh, if you get, if I got time, maybe if you got time
out like twice. No, a thousand. Some of you guys have been timed out over a thousand times.
I'm sorry. It's nightbot. Fuck the caps limit. Well, dude, if you get timed out for caps
500 times, you're going to get timed out of 501st time for a thousand times is a lot.
If I got timed out a thousand times in a chat room, I'd probably be like,
I'm probably going to get fucking banned. One of my mods has been timed out 999 plus times.
Wait, what? No, you, Oh, no, no, no, no, no. Okay. Okay. No, let's air it out. Let's air it out.
We've got 18 timeouts from one of the mods. Do you want me to tell you who these are?
Should I tell you who these are? Are you guys comfortable with that? Okay. Ooh. Oh,
VR Josh. VR Josh has been timed out 34 times. Dude, one was a personal one from you.
Wait, I timed you out personally. I'm interested. All right. Grump, what's yours?
How many times you've been timed out? Oh, wow. We currently have a leader.
We currently have a leader right now. Who's number one in regards to the timeouts here.
Okay. Kumakisu has three, three timeouts. Grump has never been timed out ever. Once. Ever. Ever.
In like seven years. Wow. That's actually remarkable. Wow. Not once. Unable to be timed
out. Immune. Not fair. You can't be timed out. Giga chat. Zero. No, wouldn't the Giga
chat be the person that's on my mod team that has like 900 timeouts, right? I feel like that
that's Giga chat, right? Like, I don't give a shit. I've been timed out a thousand times.
So that means, yeah, that means that, uh, I'm very curious about this. This is funny.
Is there a way? No, I don't want to do this, but this is kind of funny internally. Maybe
is there a way for the mods to know who in chat right now has the most timeouts ever
that's here right now? Cause like, I think that's funny. Who is, who is the ultimate
timeout Andy? Do we know? We can't see more than 999. There's internal stats on Twitch. Probably.
Oh, we can't see it. We can only see 999. Ollie's been timed out 11 times, but, but a thousand.
Those of you thousand plus Giga chats, you know what I'm saying? You've been timed out in this
channel over 999 fucking times. Oh, here we go. This is, that's so funny. Don't, uh, don't the
glowing slimes need to be somewhere else? The only need to be kind of in the underground or something
so they're not in the sunlight. That's how it worked in the first game. Almost all of it is
nightbot. I mean, I would imagine it would be. They have solar shields for, okay. Good to know.
Thank you. Oh, you're big. Uh, let's get a few of, uh, I don't want to do any combinations yet.
We'll get, we'll start with seven. Cool looking though. Cool looking. I think, isn't nightbot
broken right now too? Don't have a weapon to get rid of those. All right. I'm going to go, let's go
this way. Is water death? How do I get rid of these? Isn't there like a gun or something I
can use? It's water. I don't have it yet. Okay. All right. I, what do I want to do now? What do they
eat? What do you guys eat? They eat fruits. All right. I have fruits. I need to upgrade.
I need to upgrade my pens bad now. All right. Is that also that big guy down there? Right.
So let's do this. What kind of plorts of these? Oh, 34. Yep. I'll take it. Oh, they can jump
right out of here. Shit. It's okay. No guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, come on. Stop 425.
Your hairline is crooked. No, it's because this hair, look, my hairline is not crooked. It's just,
this is falling over this way. Uh, by the way, congratulations on your 998th timeout.
Whoever said that? Why are they? Oh my God. I forgot they're in the sun. I need the sun shield
thing. That's a lot. Um, oh my God. Okay. Hold on. I got a lot of stuff going on. What are these
worth? Only 19. That's it. I gotta feed them too. They're probably, yeah, they're hungry. 35. Damn.
All right. Hold on a second. Okay. Looking good. I need more plorts.
All right. I got money to work with now. Where are your eyebrows? I have a big brow bone and it messes
them up. 1600 bucks. Let's go. Let's go. This needs way, this has got to go way faster. Soil.
I'm going to have, I need fruits. So I'm going to do this too. I have two slimes that eat fruits.
Okay. So that's good. That'll produce much faster. Let's go. All right. Uh, right. Okay. I need the
solar shield sensitive to light and then let's make the height more too. Okay. All right. Now
you guys hopefully can't fly out. Maybe you can. Hope not. How you guys doing over here? Good.
All right. This is going, this is automatically doing it. Good. Okay. I don't think they can get
out. I think we're good. They're safe in there. Your wig is crooked. My wig? Oh, all right. We're
going to do one more pole. One more pole because there's a bunch of, uh, ports to get. All right.
Suck it up already. Let's go. Suck it up already. Let's go this way. So they eat fruits and their,
um, plorts are worth a lot, right? 34. I got to really start to get more of those. They're okay
in here for now. No one's having a problem. They're all fine. I don't want anything else to do. Do I
want someone else here? No, this is, this is the best pen that I have. Yeah. So I got to keep that
in mind. Looking for a pole. No, I think I'm maybe just said something that sounded like pole. Perfect.
This is ready. So this is a vegetable. I'm going to replace this with a fruit because I have
vegetables here and these are better, higher quality. Pull all the carrots out. I need a fruit.
I'm going to go try to find like a high quality fruit. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here.
It's foods in here. There you go. Yeah. Eat up. I tried to make it. All right. I'm on a mission for a
really cool, delicious fruit. Maybe backwards because I want to replace the carrots. Eat it up.
That's right. I cannot go this way. Nevermind. Because there's the pog fruit, but there's
probably something else too, right? It has to be. Qberry is probably the best thing to find in this
area. Maybe I'll look for it. Or is it? All right. Fruits. Fruits are chickens. Eventually I'm going
to need a lot of chickens, I think. I think I'm just going to head to the unexplored area.
That's probably the best idea. Just in case, I'm going to pick these up. There's a very real
possibility I don't find any fruit. And if that's the case, I will punch through my monitor as hard
as I can. Because like, I can't believe I didn't find any fruit. The people egging me on, by the
way. Come on, Quinn. I actually don't remember the last time I truly tried to break something
like that because of, I don't know. The only thing I can think of is when I used to play Super Nintendo
or some Nintendo game back when I was younger. And I told you this before, but you grip the
controller so hard and you try to like, almost like you're tearing it in half and you're just like,
and all you hear is like, just, just components crackling inside the controller. It's just,
you're like, all right, I'm fine. Just the crunches inside. Yeah.
But no, I like throw in a controller or something into the screen or into the wall.
No, my brain thinks probably five to 10 minutes ahead. A lot of times like that. And I just, if
there's a hole in your, I have to fix that. I like the drywall is fucked up now. That's a whole
project. That's a whole weekend project now that I'm making for myself. I have to, how do you fix
a hole in drywall YouTube video? Okay. All right. I need to go get like plaster. I need to go get
this material. I have to, I don't want to do, I don't want to do that. No. My rage is contained
by how lazy I am to do household maintenance. Sorry. If throwing a controller onto the ground,
boom, it blows up. Pieces kind of go everywhere. I don't want to do that. I mean, I got a dog,
right? I don't want to, what if like auto is nearby or something, right?
Oh, what if like a week later, I don't get all the pieces and I step on it. I don't, you know,
I'm not, I don't. Oh, trust me. There have been times. Oh yeah. There have been times
when I have just been like, I want to fucking eat this.
I want to smash this thing, but it's just, it's, it's built out of this idea that I don't want to
do the housework that required afterwards. I, you know, maybe I should get a, like a foam controller.
Do they make those? Do they make little like kind of squishy toy controller things for your
controller? Cause what if you just threw that and it was just like a, a nerf controller? Yeah.
The nerf controller is real. If I went over somebody's house and instead of just two or three
regular PlayStation five controllers, they had these foam made out of clay controllers.
And that's all they had. I'd be like, you, you, you need to work on your temper. You're like,
why do you, you own, why do you have these? I'm, I'm anticipating that that control is going to
get thrown tonight while we're here at your house. Okay. These guys, I mean, they're, they're, they're
at your house. Okay. These guys, I need, I, what did I do with all the fruit that I just had?
What did I do with all the fruit that I just had in my pocket? You, oh, I fed the big guy. God
damn it. I did. Didn't I? All right. It's time. It's time to set the pink slimes free because
they're not, the money is not worth very much. And I want to make room for the next group and
we're going to set them free. Good luck guys. Thanks for being the start of the business.
Excellent work. Okay. Over here with your friends and there's a big patch of carrots here.
See you guys later. Thanks for, thanks for coming to the stream guys. Appreciate it. Thanks for
hanging out. Thanks for the bits. Yep. Thank you. All right. One, a few more of these. These are
currently the most expensive. Should I do more than 10 or 20 in one thing? I don't think so.
Although that's a big pen. I can fit a lot. Might as well. And then I have to get fruits.
No bullshit. Fruits. There we go. Okay. Cute slime. Yeah. This is vegetable, but whatever.
I'll take it. Um, we're already, I already got, I already got a bunch of those. Ooh, what's that?
Fruits. There we go. Finally. Chicken. Uh, I don't need this lettuce. I'll take some more, uh,
chickens. All right. I have a ton of these. I have 20. That's probably way too much, but whatever.
Oh, that's a little, uh, what's that? Ooh. Okay. So there's this little area over here. I think I
got to go back. Wait. Cool. Just give me, just pick up the pink florts as well. Fruit. Oh shit.
Tons of chickens too. The right chickens. Shit. Um, I want the chickens. They're going to be so
important. It's very soon here. Once I need to actually start getting meat, probably make a
second pen. What's my favorite book? Um, is it a meme for me to say, um, one of the song of ice
and fire books? That's probably the last real book that I read. It's funny how that turned me off to
reading books like forever. I've read every single song of ice and fire book. I was so into it.
And then I just like, I was like, Oh, the other book is like just never coming out.
I'm never reading ever again. Okay. Time to go back and start building the fruit here. Of course
it's the game of Thrones book. Show teeth so we can prove if you have cigarette stains. I don't
think so. Your teeth are made out of plastic. All right. Let's put in. Ooh, wait. All right.
Pog fruit going in. Is this fully upgraded? I don't think I don't want to do that. All right.
So I got fruits coming. I have a bunch of chickens now. I have too many chickens,
so I got to be ready for this. All right. Good to go. Cool. Looks good. Let's feed you. Get some
good shit. And then what should I, should I combine the, should I make, I don't know. What
should I combine next? I'm not, I don't think I'm going to put these, the, Ooh, nice. Okay. I think
they could fit in here for now. I'm just going to go right to bed. Okay. Now I need a music box
and automatic feeder. All right. We're going to put a bunch of fruits in here. I think
showing your teeth is a threat. I got, I'm a dog or something.
I think you're a dog. I ain't doing it. I ain't doing it. I know the meme. I know I've read it
a thousand times. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it. And then I do like a snarl
into the camera. I refuse. I'm not doing it. All right. Come on, hurry up. New quest. What do you
know? Beatrix Labu off on another rival adventure. Rival adventure. Why did I add a word? I don't get
it. Why did I do that? Uh, and we'll, and didn't think to take her good pal, sometimes rival
and forever mentor. What is happening? Why did I, why did I go like this? Well,
what do you know? Beatrix Labu off on another rival adventure. Why did I go like this?
That was weird. Okay. Seriously. Next time you go off running off to dangerous uncharted territory,
could you at least give me a heads up? Okay. Help collect all those valuable resources that
seem to be scattered all over the island. Why you think I wasn't going to do a little recon
of my own? What good are surveillance statistics if they can't snoop on stuff? Why am I making
words up? Anyway, be careful out there. The island gives me a kind of weird vibe,
so I'm going to keep poking around. This is why I don't read. I, I have been waiting for
the winds of winter for 10 years. I stopped reading books and I've lost the ability to
comprehend reading. Okay. Since I know you're starting from scratch out there, take this
refinery link. Should you make things easier for you? I'll just, bro, I gotta be honest.
The only reading I've done is just reading the back of cereal boxes when I'm bored
eating cereal in the morning. You know what I mean? That's the only reading I've done.
It's just the what's on the back of the cocoa puffs box. Oh, it's another maze. By the way,
let me design those. Let me design those fucking things. Have you noticed that those have gotten
worse? Those, the back of the cereal box activity things have gotten worse. It's just an easy shitty
maze now. There used to be so much cool shit. There'd be a word search. There'd be a maze over
here. There'd be find the 10 leprechauns. What happened? There's just, there's don't,
they don't want to do that anymore. Oh, here's a mad lib. Those are for children. Yes. And I'm
saying they're not, they're not there anymore. No, I'm sorry. They're for children. And they're
also for adults in a bathrobe at two o'clock in the morning eating Honey Nut Cheerios out of a
fucking bowl because you're hungry at two o'clock in the morning. And I'm sorry. Who am I going to
talk to at 2 a.m.? What am I going to do at 2 a.m.? That is the box is facing me and it's, I don't
know, a little dark outside. Is nobody really around? It's just, it's me in the box. It's just
me in the box. So I'm sorry. Yes. I read the little activity thing on the back of if it's like 3 a.m.
and I'm eating Honey Nut Cheerios in a bathrobe. Oh, here we go. Don't act like you don't pick up
random shit to read in the bathroom. I'm not saying they do that with the Honey Nut Cheerios box,
but you know what? It's the same. It's in the same space. It sits in the same spot. It's just,
it doesn't, it's just shit that doesn't even matter that you're just passing time with two minutes.
Somebody said, dude, you realize the toilet bowl is not for the cereal, right? Like I'm
I'm putting the cereal into the toilet bowl and Captain Crunch still has puzzles on it.
He did it with coffee recently while I was asleep. I'm horrified. He talked about it on stream and
I learned about it hours later. Well, we talked about when I drank the espresso while I was taking
a shit. That was a little unhinged. I will agree. I felt like it. I felt, I don't care. I felt like
doing it. That's it. I felt like I just felt like it. That's it. That's all. I don't need to explain.
There's no explanation. It actually is not an explanation. People are like, dude, why,
why did you do that? There is none. There's nothing to explain. It's just, I felt like it
one day. I was like, I'm going to do this today. That's it. And it was, it was like, whatever.
It wasn't a big deal. It was, it actually wasn't a big deal. Okay. Let me explain. For those of you
that don't know or weren't here or whatever. I don't know. Like, like three years ago, whatever
it was, it was like, I don't know, like a few months ago, I was late to a stream and I like to
have a coffee before the stream. And I made an espresso. The espresso was just a little,
it's just a little thing. It's not even two ounces of liquid. So that's a lot of money, by the way.
So I make an espresso. I'm already like five to 10 minutes, probably late to the stream. So I'm just
like, okay, usually it's you drink the coffee and then, okay, I need, I don't really need to go
this far. Coffee is a, it's a diuretic. I, coffee in the morning gets me moving. Right? So I was
like, you know what? Like, I'm, I'm late to the stream already. I'm just, I'm just going to bring
this into the bathroom. Like, what the fuck do I care? It's one and a half ounces of liquid. I
didn't even care. And I sat there and was just sipping on an espresso while I was, you know,
getting prepared to what? That's not, is that really that weird? And I remember sitting there
going like, all right, I've only, that's only, I've done it once. I haven't done that ever again.
How are we doing over here? Good. It doesn't matter. That's kind of a weird vibe. I, I disagree.
It was something that I just did one time and I was like, you know what? Fuck it. I'm going to
do this once because I feel like it. And I will tell you, it was, it was not a negative experience.
It was not, I don't want to say it was a positive experience, but there was nothing. I got through
the coffee and I was done and I was ready to go. And I, I skipped like 10 straight minutes of like
sipping a coffee before the stream. All right. Let me go upgrade something. It wasn't only one
time. It was the only one time. That's it. Oh, I need ore. Okay. 10 of these. I feel like I need
this. All right. This is for any 10 of the funny lords. Okay. Okay. Let's do that. And I will load
this up momentarily. How are you guys doing? You all right? I think I need to make this go faster.
Yeah. People hungry in there. How are you? Let's do increase soil, faster growth. Looks good. Are
you at the age where you have a magazine rack in the bathroom yet? Um, no, I think I have to do
another. Yeah. I need more food. I just do. This is vegetables. I need root or yes. Okay. Did you
eat a three course meal on the crapper? I have not heard anybody say crapper in a long time. That's
impressive. Um, well, no, that's not true, but whatever. All right. I'm going to get this one.
Should I just put vegetable in there now? I'll be back. Um, I gotta get off this island. I feel like
I've seen a lot of the, uh, feel like I gotta go up here or this way because I've gotten a lot,
most pretty much everything off here. Are there any other slimes that are here? I need 10 of
these. I need 10 ports, 10 of the bunny ports. I need that. Okay. I need 10 of these. Come on.
Three or somebody else eat something. I missed a lucky slime. What does that mean? I've, if you
eat the veggies, they need them. That's it. One more. Where is it? When do you just please? All
right. 10. Good. I can now upgrade the vacuum cleaner. We're going to blink for like an hour.
I'm going to just do another, I'm going to do another pog fruit tree. I think it makes the
most sense. Oh shit. Look at this. Why was this one so fertilized or whatever? That's a lot.
Okay. 19. I guess I could feed this, right? Isn't there one down there? Anything else over here?
All right. This is the only area I've not been. So let's just take a quick look.
Hmm. Nothing over here. Actually there was, it was a hen.
I think that's good. Although I'd like a, I think that's good. I'll get the upgrade for the
vacuum cleaner. Ooh, what's that? You need to take a cold shower chat. Is there any data?
Isn't there science behind that? Taking a, like finishing your shower with like it not being hot,
hot, hot is actually not a bad thing. Can you play trombone champ? I actually, I'll play trombone
champ probably maybe tomorrow. Cause I want to do breath of the wild tomorrow. Is trombone
champ on the switch or is it a steam game? Yeah. I'll do breath of the wild and trombone champ.
Is it on switch? Steam. Okay. The, this has got to get an upgrade. Yeah. I got to feed the chickens
and shit. Okay. I need to feed. You guys are good. Holy shit. That's a lot. All right. You need food.
All right. That's good to go. Suck this up. It's just on steam. All right. Oh fuck. I already have
a lot of those. Probably have two grand after this. What's the price? The price, I'm going to go to bed.
Maybe the price will increase tomorrow. What about splatoon? I did want to play splatoon eventually.
No price change, whatever. All right. Sucking these up, right? Remind me to keep 10 of these.
Otherwise I will forget. I got this 10 in the, in the chamber thing here. Okay.
15. Okay. All right. Now pretty good payday coming out here.
Very nice. Okay. What are these worth? Like 30? These were 30 yesterday. Whatever.
I need whatever that is. He doesn't understand economics.
I know I'm flooding the market. I know. Okay. Cotton port. Oh, I have to shoot them into here.
Right. How do I do that? There we go. All right. So I can, now I can get resources from a node.
Shakes loose science resources from nodes in the environment. What does that mean? What does that
mean? A node? Well, I know a node when I see one. Yeah. Okay. Still have money. Hmm. The water
sprouts. Oh, okay. Cool. So I can actually use those now. That's pretty sick. What's down here?
Oh, it's just behind everything. Okay. All right. Time to upgrade. How much is it to go the, the
area over here? I want to go over here or down here. Let's see. I think it's like a thousand,
2000, 1800 for the den. Oh, okay. That's the place to put the, where the light doesn't get
in there. The archway, ancient ruins. Okay. How are we doing? No more ports, but I definitely
have an, I definitely have to play. Let's restock the food. This is going to get bad if I don't.
Oh my goodness. There's so many chickens in here. Um, what, what am I supposed to do? Feed
Vitamizer? There's a lot. All right. Feed, feed, feed, feed growing. Okay. Right here. All right.
Good. Go. Okay. There's way too many chickens, but I need somebody, something that eats meat.
They eat meat, but do I really? I don't know. Okay. It's time to, where should I go? Is this
boat? Can I use this boat? Let's check it out. Wake up, dude. I'm awake. The boat costs money.
I don't think I can activate the boat. I did get that node thing though. Let's check that out.
Why are you angry? What? I'm not angry. Why do you think I'm angry? Why is everyone saying wake up?
I'm looking for one of those oil nodes. Another one down here. Oh, wait a minute. I see one right
here. All right. Give me something new. Jelly stone. Ooh. Okay. Jelly stone. This is box.
Wouldn't, this is another one of those somewhere over here, isn't there? Veggies. Oh, okay. Here,
look. Eat these. That's a veggie, right? Oh, I got it. Okay. That's the cube one. That's when
everyone's like, you got to find that one. I got a cube berry. All right. I got to make sure I grow
this. I don't want to forget something. I'm thinking I'm just going to go back. Cue berry,
resident sleeper. Cue berry. Chat's on something today. To be fair, the entire stream feels like
we all shared a joint. Does it? So is this, is this a food? This jelly stone? What does it do?
Is it just like a, is it a buff or something? Oh, here we go. Don't touch those. Those are mine.
Deep brine. Not safe for drinking. Water from a slime sea that's been filtered by the subterranean
core below Rainbow Island. It's denser than freshwater and loaded with salt. Okay. What do
I do with it? Bong water. Nothing else over here. Oh, yeah, there is. I remember there was one in
the cave somewhere, right? Yeah. All right. I got a couple of new resources. What the hell do I do
with this shit? How hard is the jet pack to get? I don't know. Let me go look. I'll make some money
here. Put it in the refinery. Yeah. That's a good idea. All right. You are fine, but you...
Where's my second tree over here? I really hate to do this, but I have to delete this.
No, no, no, no, no, no. This one's not upgraded. I'll do to this one. There we go. All right. Let's
collect some cash. Cause I've got a lot of florts now. Yeah. I'm going to have this again. I'll be,
I'm going to have, I'm going to end up with like three grand. Oh yeah. You better believe it. Look
at this. I'm going to have like two grand or at least look at this. All right. It's time to
collect this pen. I need a new group of slimes. All right. Refinery. Okay. I've got jelly stones
in here now. So what's the, how do I get the jet pack? Jet pack is one, 10 radiant ore,
10 phosphor plorts. What's that? I can get those. Where do you get the radiant ore? Check caves.
All right. Let's do a collection here.
Okay. I wonder if I should upgrade people now. Like I should people, what's with my voice?
Should I combine the, the ghosts with the pink or something? Experiments.
There's food in the dispenser. I think it's garbage though. It is. Okay. I got a lot of money
and I do anything else with these. I think these are all fully upgraded, right?
Yep. This is fully upgraded. This is fully upgraded. It does have to,
I don't think I need that though. This, this is fully, wait no it's not. Safely and gently
moves elder chickens away from the younger generations and stores them in a collector.
Um, should I just do that? I feel like they're all getting old. There was only one elder chicken
in this whole coop. That was 1300 bucks. Okay. Well, this is good. All right. I'm going to,
where do I go? Where should I go? Southwest and down here. Cubes. So now we are going to do this.
Uh, yeah. Get rid of this shit. I just want double cubes. I have to start feeding
chickens to somebody because that this is getting ridiculous.
They eat meat, right? I think so, right? Veggies and meat. I'm just scared that I'm going to find
a slime that only eats meat and I'm going to waste all these. Is that wrong to think that?
All right. I need a, I need a new slime. I got this pen over here. I'm not,
just not being used for anything. What are you doing over here? Oh, you're just hungry.
Oh, okay. Well here, that's a special cube. That's cube fruit. That's just for you.
There you go. All right. Speaking of cube fruit, I should probably store this
or feed it to these guys over here. Yeah. All right. I'm going to the Southwest. Special dork fruit.
All right. Let's move. There's too many tabby slimes. I cracked the super mysterious code
that was sent to me. It was complex. I believe that AI, I believe that the AI that created
this code displays a comparable intellect to my own. So very advanced, almost alien.
What did it say? Okay. Hello. Who's this? Hold up, Beatrix. Are you there? It's me, Ogden Ortiz.
Are you off on a big new adventure on a mysterious island filled with secrets and danger and maybe
a few succulent fruits and veggies the world has never seen before? You know, I had to ask.
Ever since you got me a steady supply of Cucadoba fruits, I've been reaching for
even greater culinary heights, getting pretty tired of eating Cucadoba pie, Cucadoba souffle,
Cucadoba pudding, Cucadoba corn, carne, Cucadoba corn. You get the idea. I'm running out of ideas
and willpower. If you see something new, please tell me about it. Okay. Okay. Oh, I got this.
Finally. How do I turn that on? How do I use the water? Do I have to suck water up first?
Is that other tree upgraded all the way? No, it's not. This is democracy manifest. Oh,
that's a nice chokehold, sir. It's one of my favorite videos of all time. I mean,
it's a classic video. All right. It's in Southwest. I'm heading Southwest. A meal?
A succulent Chinese meal? Hot on. Farewell. Get your hands. What an outrageous video. Show it and
dump it. I can't. I don't, I don't think I can. I don't know. I don't know what word for word
fry. Um, I'll try. Is the charge eating? Can I have subtitles? It's going to be hard for me to do this.
Let me turn on subtitles. Okay. I'm going to, uh, let me see how this works. What is the charge?
Eating a meal? A succulent Chinese meal? Okay. Let me try this. I got to turn him off though.
All right. So this has been muted. Okay. I'm going to try. What is the charge eating a meal?
A succulent Chinese meal? What is this? This is not the video. Hold on. Wait, this is the wrong
video. Just skip to 15 seconds. Okay. I'm under what? Okay. Gentlemen, this is democracy
manifest. What is the charge? Eating a meal? A succulent Chinese meal? Democracy manifest.
I need, this is the wrong video. Give me the right video. He keeps cutting around. This is like the
news report of the guy. This is the news report. Okay. I'll do this one. Hold on. Let me do it again.
Okay. Let's put this one on. I'm ready. I have to really prepare for this.
Okay. Are we ready? Are we ready? Okay. Let's go. No, you don't want, we don't want audio for you.
This is, this is not even right. What? Hold on. I'm not showing any under rest. I'm, what? Gentlemen,
this is tab, tabock receive manifest. Ever look at the headlock here. See that chap over there
joined. Oh my piousness. This bloke who got me on. Chinese male. Eating a meal? Eating succulent
Chinese male. Succulent Chinese male. Oh, that's a nice headlock, sir. I see that you know that
you're cute. Alright, let me try this. I'll give it a go. Here we go. Just a short breather. I could
speak showing anything under arrest. I'm under water. Gentlemen, this is tobacco receive manifest.
Ever look at that headlock there. See that chap over there joined or by piousness is the bloke
who got me on the penis before. Well, what reason? What is the charge? Eating on the older succulent
Chinese male. Oh, that's a nice headlock there. Stop. I see that you know you're cute over here.
Wood and user. Are you waiting to receive my? I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't do it. I can't do it.
What the fuck? What the fuck? I can't, dude. I can't. I gotta go back to play the slime game.
That's in the video. I did not. I forgot that was in the video. I thought that was a wrong
caption. I forgot that he says that. It's like, holy shit, dude. What? I forgot that was actually
in the video. OK, we're going to go down to the southwest. Did he beat champion gundyr already?
Yes, I did. It was very easy. Is this a cube tree? Oh, the cash in there. All right, I'm down in the
southwest. What am I looking for? I have to open up one of those other places, right? I gotta,
I gotta hurry up. I got, I got money coming in. Bring the mustache back. I can't, I can't do it.
Is there an audio delay? There shouldn't be. Is it one of the other? I feel like I have to go into
this or something, right? This is what, like two grand? 1800? Can you do the ooh, ooh, voice? I've
been waiting a long time. No, I promised I would never do it again. If there's a reason to do it,
maybe I would. I kind of don't know where to go. I could feed the big guy. I could try to go this
way. Let me, let me look at what's over here. I feel like that's where I need to go. Wait,
there's a voice desync? No, there shouldn't be. No, there really shouldn't be. I turned all that
off. The webcam is late. Oh, it really shouldn't be. It's probably because of the low FPS on this
piece of shit. Yeah, this thing's a piece of crap. Actually, this thing's a piece of crap. But I'm
one of those people that complains about a product and, and never stops using the product. I just
complain about it every day. Have I gone up there? I haven't, I need the jet pack. Seems fine now.
That's weird. All right. I'm going to head over here because I feel like this is where I need to
go. I need to activate the boat or something. Because if I go this way, what, what, how much
is this? All right. 1800 bucks. All right, let's go. I can make that right now. I guarantee you,
I can make that right now. I, okay. I need to get rid of at least a third of these chickens.
I see you know your judo well. Where's my, uh, cabbage farm? Like the cabbages aren't even
ready. How is that possible? All right. Here we go. How can, how can it, is it possible that
there's no cabbage right now? Oh man. Okay. Yeah. I definitely can afford it now. What the fuck is
that? This is an AI prompt photo for a German enjoying a succulent Chinese meal at a,
German 95 enjoying a succulent Chinese meal in an upscale restaurant. Oh, I see. They fed the face
into the, it didn't generate the face. I was going to say this is weird. Let me, I gotta say,
this is weird. Yeah. I want you to, yeah, I'll show you. This is creepy. I thought it made my face.
Why am I putting it into my, what's happening to my hair? Why am I putting it in my ears?
Why am I putting, why am I going into my ears? These look like Tinder profile pictures. It
really does. Oh, I'm on vacation. What the fuck? Why do I look so weird? Why do I look so strange?
What is this from? This image right here. This is a toothbrush or whatever. AI is fucked, man.
It really is. The prompt for this apparently was, what the fuck is this? German 95 enjoying succulent
Chinese mayonnaise at home in his kitchen. Why do I have sunglasses on my head? What is this one?
What is going on in this image? Can somebody help me with this? They said Reddit shelf,
me with my Reddit shelf. It's so funny. Why, why am I so skinny? It can't do text. It's just you in
the Reddit shelf. But what's even on here? Why is there a sink? There is a sink on the Reddit shelf.
Look at this right here, right in the middle. What else is even on here? A toilet, an empty toilet
paper roll, a bunch of Funko pops, some weird Funko pops. These like backpacks, a bathroom sink,
a toilet. What else is it in this room? What is this? What's the shirt? I think that's a whee behind
me. RIR rims. JC Mr. JC. What is this? Dude, AI is so fucking weird. This shit is, this shit is
fucked up. It really is. What's on the ground? Unbelievable. Jesus. Okay. All right. There's tons
of money now and I'm going to open up that of the door. I, okay. The chickens are, this is better.
Okay. So this is good. That looks good. Looks good. Forty six. I need to hold more
plorts. I, how do I upgrade my plort holding ability? These are going down in price. Two grand
probably. I should be able to open it. Would you ever play super monkey ball? Um, I did. I beat it
already. Correct me if I'm wrong, but that was a melt downstream, right? I had, I had a lot of
problems with that game. Oh yeah. No, I, that was a, that was kind of a nightmare. I did not expect
that game to be as hard as it was. That game was hard. Like really hard. Lettuce. German 985's
gamer room. Then I added a details like Funko Pops. It's crazy. This takes forever. This, they're
being fed, right? Yep. Don't ignore it. Where's Lala? Where's Lala? You know, I would do it,
but I think a lot of people ask for it a little too much. We had somebody come in here and ask
for the, the ooh, ah-ha-ha thing. I don't know if people have been asking a little too much for it.
I don't know. I mean, people have been asking for it.
I'm not doing that again for at least three months. That's on, that is only three months
cool down. I told you three grand. That's exactly what we're doing. Three grand. Three thousand
dollars. It's going to be pretty close. Almost exact. All right. Now I want to buy the new area.
But I also want to see what I can do here. Utilities. Portable water tap. Warp tech.
Okay. Right. Decorations. Upgrades. Water tank. Extra tank. Tank booster. There we go. All right.
It's 10 tabby plorts and 450. So let me get the tabby plorts. 10 tabby plorts. And let's open this
up. New area. What the hell is that sound? Ooh. Oh, this is another. Ooh. Okay. Okay. Sorry. I
have coughed like in your face. So this is just extra space. All right. Is there anything else
I can do here? Whatever's down here. What's this? Tide pools. So this is all just expansion on the
conservatory. How do I get out of here? Like out of the island? Because I mean, look, there's
definitely at least another area or two to explore, right? How do I get out of here?
Do I have to feed the giant slimes? Okay. Where am I now? Which are the big slimes should I feed?
The vegetable one or the fruit one? The veggie one? Does the veggie one also eat meat? Which
one of them eats meat? Because I'm going to bring like a hundred chickens. No. Damn it. I don't think
I even have enough vegetables. The pink one will eat the meat. Because there's this one here and
this one here. One of them's fruits, one's vegetables. Pink is any. All right. So we're
going to feed the big slimes. That's the next. That's the next part. That's the next part of the
plot. I feel like these have taken so long. That's the deal. Okay. 450. I can carry 30 of each thing.
Okay. Cool. Jet pack. I don't have it yet. Dash boots. Power core. Don't really need these right
now, but I definitely wanted that. All right. Let's go. Do you remember why don't you say penis on
stream? I just did. And I have, what are you talking about? All right. We got to go feed people.
I need vegetables. I'm just going on a vegetable hunt. That's it. Just picking up a hundred of each
one. What's my take on kefir? I love kefir. There's kefir in my fridge right now. It's amazing.
It is amazing. Highly recommend it. You grow your own. Oh no. Grow my own kefir? Look, that's a
very, that's a huge process that I want nothing to do with. I just want to buy it and drink it.
It's not that hard. Yeah. Hold on. Is it like making your own kombucha or whatever it is?
We have to get like that weird circle alien bacteria thing and stick it in. I don't know.
I don't like it. It's not that hard. Scoby. Yep. It's this weird hockey puck of bacteria
that sits on top of the kombucha. It's wicked easy, dude. Just leave milk out in the sun.
Oh yeah. That's how you do it. Thanks for the help. Thanks for the tip on how to make kefir.
Just leave milk out in the sun. Cool. I guess that's how you do it. It's not how you do it.
Is it really that difficult to make though for real? It kind of is. It starts with kefir crystals.
Okay. My parents do it. It's not hard. I don't, it probably doesn't, it's probably not hard,
but it probably takes a while, doesn't it? How long does it like the fermentation process take?
At least a couple weeks or something, right? Or at least a week. No, I don't fuck with anything
like that. I don't fuck with fermentation. I don't fuck with making anything like that ever
because what you are doing, you are making a fermented product. You are taking milk,
which I mean, I don't know, man. Like I don't want to make kefir. Oh, I made my own kefir.
I made my own kombucha and take one sip and instapuke and go to the hospital. I don't feel
like doing that. Why do that when I can just buy it? Oh, it turns out you made it wrong and
there's a bunch of other bacteria in this and you just drank, you just drank. Now you're going to
go to the hospital because you just puked and it's like you instapuked. Wine is fermented. Yeah,
I'm not waking my own wine in the closet over here. Like people have like, you know, like the FDA and
shit, right? Or you, I don't know. When you buy kombucha at the store or when you buy kefir from
the supermarket or whatever, I don't think it's coming from some random dude's closet.
Isn't there like regulation on the milk? I don't know. I like FDA. Yeah. Okay.
I don't know. Well, I don't know. It's not, it's not like some guy like on the, I don't know. It's
not like the back of the carton's like, Hey, my name is Dave. I made this. My name is Dave. I made
this with my bare feet. Like, okay. That doesn't, no, it's made in a processing facility where
cleanliness and, you know, this is like, there's the process involved and there's even trained
employees and people that know what they're doing. I don't know. Maybe, maybe Dave's bare feet
kombuchas. I don't know. I'm afraid of products that are fermented. Dude, FDA is federally Dave
approved. You are full of shit. You would not buy, you would not. I'm looking at you right now. I
moved you. I put you over here. I moved you from over here to over here. I'm reading you up right
now. If you would not buy a product, if it was called Dave's bare feet kombucha, you wouldn't
buy it. You wouldn't buy it. I know you wouldn't. I'd probably try it, dude. You don't know me, man.
I guess not. What about the show called Barefoot Contesta? The show, okay. The show Barefoot
Contesta is not called Barefoot Contesta's bare feet kombucha. That's, that's, that's not the same.
The product is called Dave's bare feet kombucha. That's a huge difference. There's a huge difference.
What about wine? Moving on. Drinking wine. What about wine? No, it's not. That doesn't happen.
All right. I have a lot of vegetables that I need to prepare. They do that. What about the wine stuff?
You stomp grapes, dude. Yes, some small batch wine person place is, will do that. Maybe the, when you
buy the, oh, there's a wine called, isn't there a wine called like Barefeet? The most popular wine
in the world is like Barefeet wine or something, isn't it? Listen, I'm trying to say that, uh,
but if they don't, I was trying to say the big like corporate wine companies aren't like
Barefeet wines, but there it is. I'll take the, Barefoot wine. Wines. I lose. I lose. Sometimes
you lose. Sometimes you lose. I'm going to lose. I take a loss. I'll lose this one. I'll lose it.
Yep. I lose. That's a loss. I hate, I don't like losing. I lose. I don't want, I hate losing. All
right. Fine. I lose. Fine. I lose. Oh, I fucking hate losing. Okay. Now stop feeding it to, all
right. I got to deposit this crap. Yes. Hold on. But wait, I'm getting backed up by a mob though.
It's not, it's called Barefoot wine, not Dave's Barefeet wine. That it's, there is a semantic
difference here. Yes. There's a difference. Dave's, Dave's Barefeet wine versus Barefoot wine. One is
implying that Dave's Barefeet were in this drink. And the other one is like, oh, Barefoot everywhere
on the beach. Maybe we're, I don't know, relaxing at home or I don't know. You know what I'm saying?
There's a different, there's a different context. Dude, you're weird. All right. All right. Let's go
feed the big guy. Wait, hold on. I got to answer this. Somebody said really important. Oh fuck. I
missed it. Somebody said this is really important for context. Remember this will make or break the
argument. Okay. Does the packaging look homemade and does Dave have his picture on the box?
Um, come on, you have to give me some credit. Yes. I love this car. It's so stupid. I'm not buying it.
That's worse. No, but it's, it's not that it's worse. It's okay. Let me make some money.
But is it just his face? Okay. Is it Dave going like this? Does Dave have a big beard? Okay. Does
Dave have a huge beard? I feel like it'd be Dave going like, and he's got a huge beard. Then like,
okay, that's just Dave. And like, maybe that means like Dave is, I don't know, likes to be barefoot
and whatever on the beach or whatever. No, it's just, it's his, it's his bare feet. Then no,
then absolutely not. I don't want it. You guys are distracting the fuck out of me right now.
Guys, no one would do this with their marketing. No one would be like, Hey, I have an idea.
I'm going to make a wine and it's going to be called Dave's Barefeet Wine. And oh, by the way,
let me remind people that it's my bare feet that is crushing the grapes. And I'm going to put my
feet on the picture on the packaging. No marketing 101 would be like, um, I don't know if you,
I don't, I don't think we do that. Somebody typed this. I need to find out if it's for real.
Barefoot's creator, his first wine he made in his garage. It was called Barefoot Burgundy. What?
It's true. It can't be. Barefoot Wine. Was somebody named Davis? No, it was not. Wow. That's
unfucking believable. Take our very beginnings. California winemaker, Davis first created Barefoot
Burgundy in his garage. The unconventional name referred to what else? The free spirited method
of crushing grapes barefoot. Fast forward. Here we are today. His name was Davis. Wow. Oh, this is an
Omega loss that I'm taking here. This is like a huge L. You just watched me get absolutely eviscerated
on stream. Has that happened before? Have I ever been this eviscerated on camera? I don't think so.
This is an absolute complete and total incorrect statement. I've been making this whole time.
Wow. We told you now last week you were wrong about goat cheese too. I stand by that.
Apologize. I apologize for having no, I'm not apologizing because I don't, I don't know. I,
I don't know. Are you going to? No. Okay. Let's play Slime Rancher. I took the L. I lose. Um,
it was Barefoot Wine. Oh, what a loss. Okay. I got some fruits and vegetables. We're going
to go check out our buddy up here. But what if it was called like Davis like fart bread
or Dave's like fart wine? Would you still, would you drink it? Dave's saying like I farted. I farted
in the, okay, hold on. I farted in the room this was made in was like in quotes on the,
right on the, on the label. Would you drink it? It's just like, I farted in the room where this
was made. It's probably time to cease, Jerma. This is reaching now. Wow. This is, you're reaching
hard. All right. The mods are telling me to stop. Is this reaching? Yeah, this is reaching pretty
hard, I think. No, you can keep going, dude. Sorry. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. Don't, don't, don't 180 on me. Rain me in here. You can go. Pepe laugh. Do what
you want. Pepe laugh. Is that a no? Oh, all right. Where, where, where are you? Where's the big slime?
Where's the big slime? Where's the big slime? It's in a cave. Oh, oh, it's down here. Okay.
This is fruits. Ooh. Okay. So now we're under here. Watered yet? Um, this is a certain port.
Okay. Can I put this in here? No. Is this a cat? I think that's a cat. Okay. So we've got to come
back down here and that's a cat slime. I think does it count if I take one of the,
I think that counts, right? I do want to go to the, okay, this one over here because that's
the vegetable one, right? Come on, dude. All right. The other one is over here. Ooh.
Large pink bonza. More? There we go. All right. What do you got? What, carrots?
I feel like I just blew up that town in Fallout 3. Um, what does that do? Oh,
you look at that. Okay. All right. I got to go back and deposit and then I'm going that way.
Nice. Unlock. What are these? Like, what are these things you're pulling out here?
At 24 minutes and 20 seconds in the second German video, L.A. Noire, the German craft killer.
All right. Detective Andy. He holds up a bottle of barefoot wine to the camera. Okay. I'm not,
I can't drink it. Why can't I drink it? It's literally the thumbnail. All right. I got to,
there's a lot of money to be made here. I got to feed a lot of people. Hold on.
Dave's bread. Dave's bread is great. Okay. It's time to do a huge turn in here very soon.
This is going to be a lot of money. This is going to be more money than I know what to do with.
Look at this. Uh, how many of these do I need? The, that door. Just one? Just one? Cool.
I don't know. You're hungry. How are you? Hold on. I'll feed them.
Any more? I think we're good. Maybe we'll be at five grand. It's overflowing.
Make sure to save a tabby plort. Yep. 4200 bucks. What can I do? All right. Pink plorts
is more health. I still need the ore. I don't have any. Yeah. Okay. I have enough jelly stones.
Um, I don't think I can do anything. Very cool. It's time. Dude, I just banked the money. I don't
need it. What about tomatoes? I don't really need to give my tomato opinion again. I feel like it
been pretty clear about it. All right. I need a tabby plort.
Is this thing fully upgraded? I'm just going to buy it. Is everything fully upgraded? Uh,
this pen over here could use it. I need another slime. All right. This thing's ready. Do you
prefer a fast food place to wrap your burger in paper or foil? Paper. Something about foil.
I feel like I'm going to accidentally eat a piece and it's like, I just ate metal.
Monka S. If I eat some paper, I don't care. Boil will keep it warm. Boil makes it feel premium.
I didn't think about that. That's kind of true. That makes sense. Keeps it warm. Time to go open
that thing. Burger or burrito. Uh, okay. Let me, let me backtrack a little. Burger or taco.
That's harder. Burger or burrito. It's burger every time. Uh, I don't dislike burritos. I just,
burgers are better in my brain, but burger versus taco. That's actually very hard for me
because I don't think I could answer that. I really don't. All right. So it's down here.
Burritos have a tendency to get really messy. What about tacos? All right. But okay. How do
I word this? A taco is usually small, very small. And I can, I get through a taco and I'm like,
all right, cool. Did I got two more tacos? Sure. I, yeah, I'll take another taco. That sounds great.
But a burrito, burrito, unfortunately, is huge. They're usually big and stuffed full of stuff.
So you get, sometimes you might get halfway through burrito and it's just like, I don't
really want the rest of this. Tacos, you can kind of portion out what you want. Where a burrito,
a big burrito especially, you're committed here. You could wrap it back up and put it in the fridge,
but I don't know. I'd rather just eat what I want. And plus the street taco is sort of, I mean,
if you have the soft shell, kind of soft street taco, it kind of is a burrito. It's just a small
one. I don't like the big burrito. And things I don't, I like one thing, tacos to me, I like
because you've got the layers. It's meat, cheese. And then on top of the cheese is lettuce. And on
top of the lettuce is tomatoes, whatever, right? It's a layered experience and everything doesn't
kind of mush together. A burrito, everything gets mushed into this soup in the middle. And
I'm talking and everything turns into kind of this weird meat soup where it's just kind of
everything mushes together. I like it being kind of separated in the taco. Now, let me make,
I gotta make this really 100% clear. If you gave me a burrito right now and you said, hey, eat this,
it's a burrito. I'd go, yes, that sounds fucking incredible. It's not like an S tier versus D tier.
It's like an A plus tier versus A minus tier, if that makes any sense. So there you go. This
might take on burritos versus tacos. All right, where was that? Down here, right? Where's the
cave? I forgot where that cave was. I feel like it's right here somewhere, right? Where is it?
Can you guys help? It's over near the beach. Can you help? Thank you. I appreciate the help.
What about, what's your favorite Indian dish? I mean, butter chicken is just, you cannot, I can't,
it's just, it's just S tier. It's 10, 110 out of 10. How do I get out? How do I get, okay, I gotta
talk about, no more food. I need to find this cave. Wait, where was it? Like down here? No,
it wasn't at like here. I wish I could mark stuff. Was it up? Somebody help me. I genuinely don't
know. It was like a cave thing here somewhere down off the cliff. It wasn't over here somewhere.
The line on the map. No, no, no, no. I'm not looking for that. I'm looking for the place where
I can shoot this port. It was like up and then down and then I just honestly have no, I have,
I do not remember where it was. It's near the conservatory. Is it? Isn't it just like right
here? Yeah. All right. Here it is. Yeah. I was like, no, there's no way. There we go. Tank guard.
What is that? Pretty cool. All right. Now let's go to the next area down here. 37 year old
Jerma is whack. I turned 37 guys and now every stream is a crack stream. Have I ever had
octopus? I haven't. I don't like it. It creeps me out. It's a little weird for me. All right. So
from here, go. Even squid too. Squid kind of freaks me out too. Something about it. I really
don't want to ruin the calamari for anybody, but it looks very specifically like something
that I do not, I don't like. Here we go. Move. Although I do have a bunch of shit. Maybe I
should get rid of this. They look like spiders like lying on their backs with their legs in the
air dead. When you get like calamari where it's like, you know what I'm saying? They had the
legs. They're like this. What kind of 37 year old is afraid of calamari? I don't sit in the
restaurant and freak out when the calamari comes. Somebody orders calamari. I go, oh, all right,
cool. I'm not going to have any, but I hope you like it. It's not like the guy doesn't walk over
with the fajita plate like shh. And I'm just like, no, no, I have to leave. I'm fine. I don't
care. I might even eat one new zone. Let's go. I need a new slime and go. All right. I found
what I'm going to put. Let's make that sound. What did I miss it? I missed it. I didn't,
I didn't even know what I was supposed to be looking for. It looked like just a regular.
It looked like a cat slime beats. All right. It's just white. Okay. What do rocks eat?
Ed cheese. Really? You don't need meat. What has happened? That scared the shit out of me, man.
No, please make it. Oh my fucking God. What? What happened? What ever back? I'm gonna pee.
What the fuck? I, you die instantly and you lose everything. I was trying to bring it back.
Beer B fucking game is not even fun. Uh, I got a lot of cleanup to do though. I, so I was muted,
but, um, I might haven't cleaned my room in a while and I didn't clean my room. So I got to
clean my room. Um, so I, I'll, um, I'll be right back again. Okay. No. Why would I leave the mic
on and just smashing windows? All right. Um, all right. I'll actually be right back.
Modeling is a house. Oh man. I was muted. I was, I was dying over here. I just people like,
what is he doing? I was, if you look up smash controller sound effect, it's one of the first
two and this, this, whoever's doing this is really hitting it on something and it won't break.
It's not breaking. All right. BRB for real. Hello again. Okay. I think it's time to dial the, uh,
maybe a little bit of erratic stream behavior here. I think we're going to pull it back a little
and chill and relax the next part of the stream. Okay. Hey dude, can you reduce the bit rate of
the stream so I can finish downloading devil may cry five? Uh, just put it in one ADP or something.
You can do that. You can do that on your own. Put it in like 240 feet. All right. So what was
I doing? Right. Oh, I died. That's right. It's also funny that I'm not even using a controller.
Okay. Is there a way I can tell? I got to teleport. I have a teleporter. Don't I?
Do I have to buy it or unlock it? Cause I have access to this teleporting pod,
but do I have to actually make it? Oh, okay. I need 10. Perfect. I need 10, uh, bunny
ports and I'm good to go. Do I have any in here? No. All right. I can do it.
When you can play trombone champ. I don't know. Maybe whenever I stream next tomorrow,
the next day, I need just regular bunny ports
at more than 30. Damn. Okay. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming.
I'm 38. You're not old. Thank you. That's a nice thing to say. Appreciate it.
All right. So we got to get this one loaded because eventually there's going to be
some buddy in here. Okay. First things first. I'm going to do a one pole here.
There's a lot of ports I need to collect. Very important.
Okay. Okay. Okay. All right. Now I need 10 of the cotton floors. Let's build it. So now I can
actually teleport. Um, and I'm not going to get stuck somewhere and not be able to go anywhere.
All right. Let's do it. Build it home portal one. Oh, one way travel back to the conservatory. It's
T. I need to build it here. This gadget is installed permanently until demolished. Should
I put it somewhere else? Oh, okay. Let me put it. Where should I put it? Can I put it pretty much
anywhere? I can. All right. I definitely want it next to the house. Yeah. Without a doubt.
Right next to the house. Very cool. Okay. So this brings me. What did I, what just happened? What
the hell just happened? Don't I, how do I, it's a one way home portal, but how do I use it to go
back? I wasted it. It's one way. Yeah. But it's not like a town portal in Diablo where like, oh,
I'm going to leave and I go back to that. I have to build. Okay. All right. All right. Let me,
let me make sure I get this right. So I want to go here. Let's go one way to your home.
Fuck. I thought it meant like I could, I thought it was a permanent thing that just stayed there.
It's what can I take it back? You build it in the wilderness for a quick trip home. Yeah. But I
thought it was a permanent fixture here and I had like a town portal scroll that I clicked on or so.
So what the fuck is the point of that? I just wasted all those resources too. Didn't I?
How do I remove it? I get it back. I don't get it back. I don't fucking get it back. Well,
when I built it down here, it was like, Oh, I had to build it here. I had to build one of these down
here. And then it was like, Oh, make sure to go into gadget mode and put it down. I didn't know
it was, that's how it worked. I thought it was like a permanent like teleporter upgrade for the
wait. Why can I, I can still do it. I think I'm fine. I'm fine. I can still do it. I can still do
it. Yeah, we're good. All right. I want to go get some slimes here. Free food. Okay. Let's go. Now
let me get my stuff that I want to get. They were beats. They were, there was new slimes.
There was a rock slime. It was a, it was a stealth assassin slime. Let's not blow it please. All
right. There we go. Yep. There we go. Oh, you're too big. But I did get one of the, one of the
plorts. I can use that. Okay. Let me find just a little small version. What's going on over there?
Is that a beehive? Oh shit. Wild honey. All right. I'll take it. Honey slime. Oh hell yeah. Let's go.
Get the fuck away from me. I don't know what that is, but I kind of want it. Oh, I don't,
maybe I could get one. What do they eat? Veggies, right? I just want a blue one to eat a vegetable.
What is that thing? Look at this weird apple. Mint mango? Shit. Um, I think it's important to
have this. I'm not going back yet. I want some more rocks and some more. I think the wild honey
back too. Whoa. Angler slime. That's too much. That's too much shit. Look at all this stuff.
So I don't have it. I need a bigger inventory. Okay. I have to go back. I want a bigger inventory.
Let me see if I can find some more of these.
My whole life just flashed before my eyes. I can't believe I shit my pants in the fucking second
grade. Jesus. What is that? How do I get the first two? All right. It's time to go before I die.
What is that? Oh, this is, I need this ore. Oh God damn it. Um, all right. I know what this is though.
What was this? No, no, no. I don't want that. Buzz wax? No, you're more important. Kubrick's stare.
How do I get more slots in my backpack? I have to upgrade it. Is it even on the list of things
to upgrade? It was. I didn't even see it. Backpack size, not capacity. Okay. I wonder what it needs.
Okay. For a second, I thought everybody died in here. They didn't. That's just, there was
nothing in there to begin with. All right. So what are these guys like? Is it fruits? No,
they like vegetables. What about the honey slimes? Oh, you like fruits. Well, go on in.
This is ready for you. It's going to be delicious. Tons of plorts. It's going to be sick.
I believe it is time. I think it's time to retire bunnies maybe. Yep. Either that or I need a new
plort thingy. Let me just put this here. And these, they want vegetables. All right. So we
got fruits, veggies, a lot of veggies. All right. Let's go. I think I'll make another garden too.
Yeah. I mean, I need some more vegetables. Okay. Cool. So it's, do you guys like fruit?
Let's fill this other one with fruit. Veggies going here. I got you guys. This is probably
one of the last times I feed the, maybe not. I don't know. What should I do?
Clear some of the hens out. All right. Don't retire any. Keep them all. Yeah. I mean,
but they're not going to be worth, the plorts aren't worth anything. And if I have to keep
feeding a dozen of these, I feel like I'm going to waste food. Okay. So what do I want to make?
I still have this, is this got a pond one? Deposit this shit. Hold on. All right. What is,
what is this thing you talking about? Tank booster, 30 units, extra tank. So this is it here.
I don't have any sand. Well, let's do this. I'm going to store 30 in here, maybe more
because I, you want at least 10 to 20 of every single plort, right? Just in case
100 of every plort. Okay. I have so much shit here. All right. Um,
um, honey rocks, maybe. Oh, you eat meat. Perfect. Uh, you're going to be in your own pen.
Is there any more pens? You need water for the angler slime? Maybe it's a pond. Um, well,
I have some more room down here. All right. I think it's a pond. Is this correct? You look
pretty happy in there. You look kind of happy, right? Are you trying to get out? I don't think
so. Right. Eat this. Nice. Nice. Should I feed you a rock or something? Let him out. How much
do the honey ones go for? All right. I got to start. Let's go. I'll keep getting distracted
and overwhelmed. Um, I need so much more room. Blood on the floor of that cage. Okay. You're
happy. You're kind of unhappy, but we're okay. Kind of, I think. Okay. Yikes. Okay. I need to
feed this to somebody. Who should I even? I think I'm going to feed it to you.
One of you guys in here. Just fuck it. Go for it. All right. Yeah. You eat meat and vegetables. All
right. Cool. Maybe I should turn, turn them into rock ones. That might be smart. Should I do rock,
uh, phosphorus or rock? Um, honey, honey, phosphorus, honey, phosphorus. That's what
I was thinking. All right. Well, there's a shit load over here, so let's do it.
All right. It's time for you to grow up. Cool. So they eat fruit. Good to know. They're too big.
I think they're okay. All right. What about rock honey? Rock honey? They might break out. They're
not going to break out. Okay. Fruit. Let's go back to what I was doing. These are worth 58 each. Uh,
yes, please. Thank you. So you guys are good. I need fruits. I have a lot of fruit over here.
Okay. Um,
overstimulation. No, I'm all right. This is veggies and I obviously want lots of rock stuff.
Yes. You know what? Just kind of keep it in there. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming.
All right. Cool.
All right. Cool. How you guys doing? What do you guys eat? Fruits? Yeah. All right. I'm coming.
I'm coming. Cool. I'm coming. Fuck. Um, hold on. 33. That's all right. He's never cleaned any of
these cells. Let's go do this. Um, I think I'm going to remove some of the phosphorus ones.
They, it's going to get too, it's going to get too wild in here. It's going to, it's going to get
actually unreasonable in here. Okay. I think that's all right. Maybe like two or three more.
That's enough. Why are there veggies in here? All right. Go be free. They're fine. They're fine.
They're fine. They're fine. Oh shit. Box box raid. What's up box box. Uh, welcome everybody. How are
you playing some slime ranch or two? I think I'm doing a pretty good job. Hope you had a good, uh,
stream box box. I've got a lot of, uh, stuff going on. Trying to make some money. I'm doing
all right so far. Things are going good. Where'd all this energy come from? I'm saying hello. I'm
welcoming a bunch of people that just got here. What was that? It was okay. I'm going to show you
this one day. The ring light is right here. So when I look up here, it's kind of really
bright in my face. So I can't really look into the camera because it's so bright. Okay. I have
almost a hundred of these phosphorus. I think I'm ready to leave. I think I'm ready to continue
what I was doing. Right? Let it just collect. I want to go get one of those, um, assassin raccoon
things. Let me fill up some of the wrong side. All right. Let's go. The inventory upgrade.
Thank you for reminding. Thank you. Seriously. I actually would have just completely just,
just glossed over that. What do I need? What was it again? Someone fed the AI thing,
the image of the stream, but erased just your face so it would auto-complete.
This is fucking hilarious. You ready? That's insane. There's another one. This one, I don't get it,
but I do. I want this as an emote or something. This picture is so perfect. What's the, uh,
the Pennywise actor? What was his name? Yeah. Bill Skarsgrd. Bill Skarsgrd. So ridiculous.
It's ridiculous. It really is. Okay. But the real question is how many yellow plorts did I need?
How could there only have been one elder chicken? It was 10, right? Okay. So hold on. I got to take...
It's 10 rock ports, not yellow. Is it?
Is it really rock ports?
Shit. All right. What do they eat? Veggies? Fuck. I need veggies. Hurry. I'm going to bed. So I wake
up and it'll be there. This is a long time to be asleep. Okay. Let's do this now. Oh, something in
my eye. You get something in your eye and it just doesn't stop for like an hour. It's annoying.
Okay. Excellent. You guys need to eat too. Uh, shit. Hold on. I'll be right back. Hold on. I'll be
back. I'm back. End of the stream, boys? Um, not, not yet. Maybe in a little bit. So what does it
take? Silky. Oh, I don't even have the sand for this. Or distort. Let me feed everybody again.
I got a lot of people to feed here. You ever played the first game? Yeah. I, uh, I beat the
first game on stream, didn't I? I remember correctly. You guys eat fruit. You need veggies
or meat. I can do that. You guys want fruit. Chickens. Come here. I'm going to be overflowing
with these. Oh, the angler. I'm just going to bring the angler up here. He hates us. He's not
reading chat. What are you on about? All right. Store it. All right. Cool. Let me go get the
other slime that's down here. I'm going to bring them out. I'm going to put them in that, uh, with
the other rocks and feed it a rock. I think that's a great idea. And what's, do you hear my voice
right now? I don't know what, I don't know why this is happening, but it is. Hey, come with me.
And then I'm going to feed a rock to this. It makes the most logical sense, I believe.
Go ahead and eat one. I guess I'll pull it if it's not. All right. We need, um, did you eat one?
All right. There we go. Perfect. Perfect. Let's go. It's time to continue. I think everyone's fine.
I could refill some fruit. He's not ready yet. Nope. Not quite. All right. All right. I'm going
now. I need to find sand. I'm going this way. The inventory slots. I need sand. I need what,
like silky sand or something, which I don't have. Is it, maybe it's on a beach. Could NPCs have
feelings if they're programmed to? Oh, a thinking face. Let's go. Stop at Wendy's on your way back.
You know, that's actually not a bad idea. Oh, somebody said food. That means streams ending
in like 30 minutes. Actually true though. Didn't I tell you guys, like, if you want,
if you want a stream to turn off, just talk about food after like seven or eight o'clock Pacific.
That's the quickest way for me to be like, oh yeah, food, eating humans. I eat. I need that.
I want the beat. I'm looking for, I guess I can take more rocks. That's fine. I do want the
recommend though. Do you recommend eating any of these? I don't think they're edible. Not, not,
not the humans though. I don't think, not the humans at least. You can play breath of the
wild tomorrow. Yes. I want to bring this guy back. Jesus. I still have not found the map
fragment thing here. Just kind of surprising to break these or something. Oh, no, I don't want
the honey. Okay. Ooh, meat. I have so many chickens. What's better, Greek or Italian food?
Uh, that is very hard. Depends on the day. I want to say Italian because Italian, it's just
chicken parm or, you know, you know what I'm saying? No, I'll, I'll joke aside. Italian
food is like one of my favorite. Uh, Mexican, Italian and Greek are probably one, two and three.
Probably in that order as well. I'm a sucker for American food too though. Just like that,
hot dogs, hamburgers, turkey sandwiches. Just like the, the, whoa, give me a bunch of these.
Is that that like a barbecue? Brisket's one of my favorite things in the world.
Um, I mean that's kind of style. I like a lot of different things. I really do. Good old-fashioned
American food. Yeah. Well, I'm going to have a ton of these now. They're going to need their own,
uh, they're going to need their own pen. 24? That's a lot. French fries? Well, they're actually not
called French fries, right? Aren't they just called, aren't they called crisps? No. Oh man,
I got that wrong. What, what is it? It's chips, right? Chips are fries. Crisps are chips, right?
Yeah, so it's not French fries. They're, they're chips. Isn't that what a lot of EU calls French
fries? Oh, another L. Oh, another L. That's British. Fries are French. So what do, okay,
if you're from France, what do you call French fries? What are they called? Chips? Frites?
Just fries. Frites. Okay. Yeah. So I need this. I'm just going to farm over here for a
sec because I, I need this. Silky sand is over here on the beach. I need 10 of them.
Come on. How can there not be any? Any. Oh my God. Hey, what'd you do with my stuff?
What did my, where's my silky sand go? I just lost all of it. Oh my God. Get out of the way.
Sand? Don't jump that. I'm an idiot. I need a lot more than this.
I'm trying to think of some other foods that I like. I just like sat there. It was silent. I
just was, I just was in my own world for at least a full minute. I was gone. I was not even sitting
here. I was in my own head thinking about how good brisket was. I was like, oh yeah, brisket. Man,
that's good shit. And I forgot I was playing. I was just sitting here. Meat brain. Yeah. A good
brisket is you do the food dancing. No, I don't even know why I'm telling you guys this. Whenever
I eat something I like that I really like, I just kind of start going like, I just start punching
the air. I'm kind of just like, does anybody else do that? If it's really good. And I'm like,
oh, this is awesome. Yeah. I feel like other people do that. Stop shooting the fucking sand.
I think my body just gets bored. That's the problem. My mind is focusing so hard on how much
I like the thing that my body's like, Hey, how come I'm not involved? Why am I not involved?
The mind is having a good time. Let's throw some punches. I only, I still only have three
sand. It's bullshit. I think like over here, right? I'll give me this like another two minutes.
I can't replicate it or anything, right? There's no sand at this beach. How can there be no sand
on this beach? I think I'm ready to go back. There we go. Let's get the, how do I get up there?
Sand comes from the mud. Geyser is on the ground. Really? Okay. I thought they've just scattered
around randomly. How do I get up here? Ooh, no, no, no, no, no, no. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop,
stop. I want, I want, um, thank God. All right. Nice. Now I have, all right. Good. I haven't been
up here yet. Have I been up here? Yeah. I was earlier. I don't know. I'm going back. I have,
I can't get rid of any of this stuff. So I'm just going to get out of here. Tons of new slime. So
have I not found the map? What's your favorite Mexican dish? I can't answer that. I actually
can't answer that question. Some days I just feel like a wet burrito, just a wet burrito and eat it
with a fork and knife. Um, I love tacos. I love, I love everything. Yeah. Soggy, wet burrito,
just covered in the sauce. And you just like, you eat it. It's like a stew almost sometimes.
Favorite frozen pizza? It used to be Dr. Oakhurst, but you can't really find it anymore
the last few years. Where would you place plain cottage cheese on a tier list? Um, it can't be
plain. I would say cottage cheese with salt and pepper is, it's pretty high. I think a lot of
people sleep on cottage cheese. It's really good for you. It has a lot of nutrients, very dense.
It's really good, but you have to put salt and pepper on it. Salt and pepper. And that's it.
Just eat it like that. Just pepper. Pepper and cottage cheese need to be together. I don't like
cottage cheese. If anyone puts anything with sweetness or anything, no, no, no. All right.
I need another pen. I have so many of these and I'll do this and maybe, I don't know. Cottage
cheese is with sweet stuff like apples. Um, I, I prefer it with just pepper on it. Just salt and
pepper. No fruit. Nope. Salt and pepper. You already have the anglers with rock. Yeah,
but I think I want to do anglers and something else. Anglers and, uh, uh, ringtail. That'd be
cool. So let me go to the pen that I made down here. Hold on. Where is it? How am I even going
anymore? Cottage cheese and parmesan is good. I've never had that, but I had a doctor, not Dr.
Oakhurst. I had, what the hell, DiGiorno's, DiGiorno's stuffed cross pepperoni pizza.
That's very high. It's, it's exceptionally high. You guys hang out there for now. Um,
I guess I'll do another one over here. Should I not be putting the solar shield on everything?
I feel like I shouldn't be. They eat meat. Oh shit. The chickens. I put them in the wrong spot. Um,
okay. Uh, hold on. I'm going to transfer them here. Okay. I got to hold on. I'm going to do
a huge chicken transfer. Yeah. DiGiorno's stuffed crust pizzas. Phenomenal. Uh, the red Baron French
bread pizzas. That's like a high nine. All right. Now we can clean this out a little bit. That's
better. All right. Very good. Let's go dump all these in the other one. You've never had a French
bread pizza. Oh, it's so good. It's so good. That red Baron Supreme French bread pizza from the other
night. Jesus. That was, that was, that was close to a 10. That was like a 9.5. It was unbelievably
good. Where's the audio? All right. I got food. Maybe a little bit more. Those are going to be
worth a lot too. Those plorts. Do you guys eat meat, fruits? All right. Well here, eat these.
You guys good? Okay. I need to kind of sneak in here and grab these.
Cool. I think I should do, these two are going to be worth a lot right now, right? I think I'm
just going to combine these. Why not? Is that a bad idea? Anyone disagree? I'm just going to do it.
Don't they need light protection? Um, I don't think they do. Okay. Let's just do that. Cool. Whoa.
What? That was cool. So when do they, um, when do they stop doing that? It's dead? Oh, it needs to
be nighttime. Oh shit. Okay. Oh fuck. All right. I'll be back. I'll be right back. I'll be right
back. Well, the reason why I want to combine them is because when I feed them, I'll get both
ports, which is a huge deal. How much are these angler ones worth? 50? Oh yeah. All right. I'll
feed everybody. Hold on. I want them to feed. Uh, Oh God. They've been eating in days or something.
This is bad. Okay. Oh yeah. Okay. Oh, they say these guys eat fruit, right? Yep. Okay. Now who
eats the vegetables? These guys? What do you guys eat? Vegetables? Shit. I just used them all. You
guys eat fruit? Okay. Time to make some money. Goodness. All right. All right. All right. All
right. Um, hold on. You eat chickens or something, right? You guys are good. 61. Oh my God. Okay.
Uh, shit. Okay. I've got a really big overload here. Fuck. There's so many things to collect.
Okay. He's getting overwhelmed by a kid's game. This is not, I'm not, I, I'm going to stop talking.
I'm going to store the rest of these. Okay. What else is over here? We have these. Cool. All right.
Everybody good. If I took you to a casino and I gave you a hundred thousand dollars, what would
be the best game to triple your money in an hour? Uh, I would say do not go in the casino. Uh, use
that money to start like a business or like invest in, you know, skills or education or something.
No, I would not take that to a casino. I would, I would, I would walk out of the casino with that
money. That's probably a bad idea. Now you want to drop 500 at the blackjack table, smoke a cigar,
have a fucking vodka pineapple. That's up to you. I don't think I would do more than that though.
Lame vodka pineapple is, um, it's that that's the drink.
Everybody sleeps on the vodka pineapple till they drink it and they go, wow. Okay. Never mind.
Every other thing I've ever had is like, why would I ever have it ever again?
It's smooth. It's loaded with vitamin C.
Not pineapples. I didn't, that's not what I said. All right. Sell it. All right.
I have 3,600 bucks. I can, I'm going to bring the, somebody needs fruit. Who wants it?
Does somebody need fruit? I'm very simple when it comes to alcohol. Incredibly simple.
I don't want any, I don't, I don't, I'm not into like the marshmallow toasted almond vodka. No,
no, no, no. Just, just give me, I just want a vodka pineapple, a vodka cranberry,
or just like two fingers of whiskey. Like I got one that I like. That's it.
I only drink like a few times every few months. There's a never-ending supply here. Okay. Um,
load the, load this. Don't sleep on 1800 coconut tequila. I haven't, I'm not really a big tequila
guy, but if I'm ever in the tequila mood, I'll definitely, I would definitely check it out.
All right. Everyone's good. Everyone's good. Everybody likes tequila. Um, I'm not a big, no,
not margaritas, no. If you could invent a cocktail that would be named after you, what would it be?
Uh, Blue Gatorade. One, one, one and a half ounces of vodka. Blue Gatorade. Um, Jolly Rancher.
On the bottom. Um, two Green Apple Jolly Ranchers. And hold on. No, but I'm kidding. Are you serious?
No, my favorite drink that would be named, would just be, this is, it would be called the, the,
just drink it. Just drink it. I just feel like just drink it. That's it. And it would just be,
oh, what do you got? I've just vodka and pineapple. Just drink it. It's good. Just sip on it. It's
good. You don't need anything special. Why am I holding 25 fruits? Are they getting out?
Don't listen to German 985. We suggest the German 985. 12 ounces of rum, 12 ounces,
monster energy drink, combined in shaker and strain into a cocktail glass. That's,
I would not drink that. I don't know. The whole energy drink and alcohol thing to me is just,
just headache fluid. Uh-uh. It's just, I just, I'm just going to get a headache.
I never got into that. Too headache-y. Red Bull vodka. Yeah, but no, nah, nah, not me. I'm not
into it. It just makes me feel fucking crazy. I just don't like it. Everybody good? I think
everybody's good. Favorite subway order? That's a Meatball Marinara Sub. Large, no bullshit.
Just a large 12 inch meatball sub with just regular ass provolone cheese on it.
Nothing else. Don't put anything else on it. That's it. That's the one thing that I like at
Subway for real. Subway meatballs are F. That's it. They're okay. I haven't had one in a long time.
Sandwich tier list. Look, if you guys get me that interesting tier list, I'll do them. But I don't
want somebody to be like, Oh, Hey dude, do a sandwich tier list. Use this one. And it's like
a JPG's of like two peanut butter and jelly sandwiches, a ham and cheese, a meatball sub
and a steak. They got to be substantial and it has to be a lot on it. They got to be a lot of
variety. I got to do the, they got to be good. It has to be like a decent tier list.
All right. I'm going to feed the other over here one more time. I did a sandwich
tier. Yeah, I did one already. I think I've done pretty much all of them that you can do.
We're going to start reaching here. Yeah. Once we start reaching to, uh, what is Donald Duck's
favorite sandwiches tier list? You know that we're kind of past doing them anymore.
Sell this. That should do it for a little bit. Firehouse is solid. Firehouse is all right. It's
good. What's the, uh, the Turkey one? They have, uh, it's like a Turkey. I think it's called the
ladder. It's whatever the ladder is. It's like a Turkey and peppers or something. The engineer,
the hook and ladder. Yeah. What's that one? I think that's the one that I get.
It's Turkey and ham. Yeah. Whatever that one is, it's good. Firehouse is fine.
I don't have a problem. Firehouse is good. What slimes are those? These are, um, angler slimes
and I combined them with the tail ringtail slime. So now they are happy raccoon angler.
Well, they're very, they're very unhappy. It seems they're very angry with me. They want to attack.
It's okay though. They're cute. Yeah, they are. The person with the coffee pasta that ended like
40 minutes ago, dude, are you, do you have like 60,000 ping? That was just, it just came up again.
I look over and it's like 40 minutes have gone by and I see, oh, hey dude, I'm a big fan. But like
you cool ranch Dorito farts or something. It's like, man, we, we were over that already. Okay.
You're about, I'm drunk. Um, well, just relax, drink some water, stop drinking. Now you got,
I got to give you guys the strat here. The drinking strat, trust me, please listen to me.
Stop drinking after midnight. It's treated like gremlin shit. Stop drinking after like 1150.
No, don't drink anything else. You're done. Drink water for the rest of the night and you'll be,
you'll feel in the morning, you're going to feel way better. Do not sit there and stare at that
fucking 1245 AM shot. Yeah. Okay. Um, maybe not. Yeah. Nope. Put it down. Put it down.
Seriously. Put it down. That one AM shot of fucking Jack Daniels. Don't do it. You're not
going to want to do that. You're going to wake up in the morning. You're going to be like,
why the fuck did I do that? It was the shot of Jack. You're going to be able to rewind and go
the shot of Jack Daniels at 145 is what fucked me up bad and put me over the edge.
At about 1215, you should treat alcohol like you're a gremlin and just start doing,
start doing water. Cause no, what, what, what like happens at two o'clock in the morning?
Nothing. Fuck that. No, no, I don't know at like two, three plus AM it's no after midnight.
It's like the let's let's it's time to end the party here.
So if you're sitting there and it's like, you know, 1231 AM right now and it's like,
I'm on Pacific. So I don't know where you are, but 1230, one AM, no more. What happens at two AM?
I joined a stream and asked where the, wait, what with the nearest barbecue? I don't know.
I couldn't even read what he said. Drinking is for nighttime though. Yeah. You got a solid.
All right. If you, if you start, oh, I'm going to have some drinks tonight.
Maybe I'm going to go with some friends. What am I going to do? I'm going to go do something.
Right. There's been plenty of opportunity to do that. I do it. People come to Vegas a lot.
And it's like, oh, let's go do something. You cross that threshold of, you've got like from,
from like seven to eight PM to like one AM. You started about like six straight hours of drinking.
That's where you need, you need to be. That's gotten at that point. You're kind of, you're good.
What am I talking about? Talking about drinking after midnight or drinking after one AM or after
two, after one 30 boomer goes out at six and is what, no, I didn't say that. I didn't say that.
Okay. At midnight, you don't have to go. Well, fellas, it's 12 o'clock. And if I don't get home,
I'll turn it to a pumpkin, right? You don't have to do that. You just stay out. No, you can,
you can hang out still backtracking Barry. No, that's not, I didn't say you had to leave.
I didn't say you had to like, if you're, I didn't say you had to leave if, okay, if you're hanging
out with friends at like a buddy's house and it's like, you don't have to just leave, stay,
just don't drink after 12 30 after one 30. It's okay. It's like, it's like a calm cast guy window
between 12 and one 30. They go and take a fucking lift takeovers. Don't, don't be a fucking idiot.
For the love of God, for the love of God, please. All right. Why was he screaming at us? I wasn't
screaming at you. Drink some water for eight hours on a stream. I mean, I kind of do that already.
Yeah. I'm not going to tell you how you should drink if you're of the age to drink.
Just be careful. Look, I'm 37. Okay. Listen to me. I'm, I'm listening to me. I'm your goddamn
grandpa. Okay. I'm your goddamn grandpa. Listen to your grandpa. All right. So I've walked in a
circle for, you know, 10 straight minutes. That's how we know that time to probably turn the stream
off. I did the build the Minecraft wall and take the Minecraft wall down 10 times while we talked
about something. You're 37 omega low. Oh, come on. He's a rambling old man now. What? All right. This
game is really fun. We might pick this back up again. I definitely want to, I want to do Breath
of the Wild tomorrow though, between 12 and one 30. That's it. Vodka pineapple, vodka cranberry,
good whiskey, and just drink responsibly. It makes me old man. All right. I'll see you guys
tomorrow. Breath of the Wild will start probably closer to three tomorrow, not two. So that's what
we're going to do. Breath of the Wild. We'll continue playing it. I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Thanks for watching. This has been Slime Rancher 2. It's been, it's good. It's kind of just Slime
Rancher 1 again, but it, it feels like they, they just, they have Slime Rancher 1 and they're like,
let's just make that again and put a bunch of other shit in it. So, and that's not a complaint.
Like I said, it, it's great to get more of that game. So anyways, uh, hold on a second. Is,
is the Vinesauce stuff going on right now? Is Joel, Joel going right now? All right. Cool.
I believe, I think Joel and all the rest of the Vinesauce crew there, I think they're doing a
charity event right now. I'm going to raid Joel. Yeah. Let's, let's, uh, go say hello,
go support, uh, go support their, uh, streams and everything they do inside. It's called Stream of
Conscious, uh, for St. Jude's Children Hospital. And I believe he's doing Vine Wrestle. So, I mean,
like go enjoy that. That's always a treat. All right. I will see you guys later. Thanks for
watching everybody. Take care of yourselves today. It was kind of an unhinged stream today,
but whatever. Sometimes it just happens. It wasn't too weird. I mean, it was kind of weird
eating a meal, succulent Chinese meal. Yeah. I'll see you guys later. Breath of the Wild tomorrow.
Good night. Goodbye. 3 PM Pacific. Mark it on your calendar, even though it's tomorrow.
Take care of yourselves. Good night. And please behave over on Joel's channel. I will be very
upset if I hear that either you were misbehaving. I will actually be annoyed by it. Don't misbehave.
Be good. Be nice. Be supportive. Or I'm going to be very upset. You understand? I'm going to
be very upset about it. And I'll, I don't know. I'll be told. Take it easy.