Hey, what's going on, everybody? Germa here with Scare Saturdays.
Gonna be playing Stalked tonight, and special guest, of course, you see him in the background, is Shit-Faced Burger Boy.
He went to a beer tasting, a beer drinking competition today. He drank like 40 beers in 10 seconds.
Anyways, we're playing Stalked tonight, which we are recording this after we actually played the game.
And I do have to say very, very explicitly, stay and watch this whole video.
Because it is like the most hysterical friggin' game I've ever played in my life.
And just the- what are you doing?
Hello, wake up, follow me. Stalker's here. It will kill us.
This is Arnold Schwarzenegger.
Reach the elevator and get out of here. Never look at the stalker.
Never look at the stalker. Come on, we have to- come on, we have to get out of here.
Oh my god! That is the best animation I've ever seen!
Look at this guy's legs!
Wow.
Oh my god! That guy just died!
That was actually kinda scary.
Can I take his gun? Did I say the game was called Stalker or Stalked?
Because I think it's Stalked.
Give me your gun.
Come on, we have to get out of here.
This guy really is Arnold Schwarzenegger.
Okay, sure, I can't pick up the shotgun.
Oh, sick like meat.
Oh, that's like a person.
That's like half up a torso.
Oh, there's another one on the left and the right.
I think that's like both halves.
Geez, that's pretty gross.
He said never look at the stalker, so I have to like look away from him.
This reminds me of like Doom.
There he is.
Yeah, this really does remind me of Doom. It like looks just like Doom.
It really does.
Can I- can I go over here?
What?
No, it's just like a dead body rotating.
This is like- this would be scary right now.
What the hell is going on?
It's like claymation.
High fighter!
I'm not even sure what I'm actually supposed to be doing right now.
Specimen.
You know, in all- even if like the graphics are crappy,
they have like half torsos hanging up.
I know.
Even if the- it kind of reminds me of like NSFW.
What?
What was that?
Like blood stains on the wall.
Did you see like that flash of that like thing?
I got a feeling he's gonna sprint right at me right now.
No, there he is.
Don't look at him.
Do not look at him.
That's the goal, huh?
The goal is do not look at the stalker.
Well then how did you know he was behind you?
You freak.
I didn't.
I just saw him.
You didn't see him?
No.
Oh, I can act- I can sprint.
I can run.