How you doing? Doesn't this guy eat gravel? No. I don't. I don't recommend it either.
Dude, can you perform circus tricks on stream? If you do, I'll cash app you 50 cents.
You don't have to. You don't have to cash app. I'm not doing it. No, I'm not doing any circus
maneuvers. But hello, welcome. Today is Wednesday. Told you at some point midweek.
Just going to turn it on. Wednesday or Thursday is Wednesday. Here we are.
Gonna be just chilling out playing this game that I've had my eye on for a while. It's called
the Eternal Cylinder. It's a game where you have little alien creatures and their planet is being
destroyed and you have to save them and help them and it just seemed kind of interesting. So I was
like, you know what? Why not? Let's just do it. Gonna be kind of in the same energy level as the
plans for a zombie stream. Just going to relax, hang out for a little bit, chill. I love alien
creatures. Why do you hate pizza tower? I don't. I don't. Put it on the list. Is this going to be
seven hours? No, no, I don't. I mean, probably just a few hours, three, four. I'm just chilling.
I'm just here to chill. Bro, where is Frog Detective? Okay, I promise Frog Detective 3
will happen in February. If it doesn't happen in February, then you can be very upset with me.
If on March 1st you have not seen, if I have not streamed Frog Detective 3,
then I'm in big trouble. Anyways, let's go. Don't want to waste too much time. I'm very interested
in what this game is. It could be really crazy. It could be chill. Actually, I don't think this
is going to be that chill, chill. Cause I mean, we're avoiding the destruction of this species'
planet. I think. I don't think this is like, Oh yeah. Just like chilling out. I don't know.
It's kind of, it's probably going to be a little wacky. Yeah. The eternal cylinder. Let's just start.
Can you hear it? Well, maybe once upon a time in the age of the eternal cylinder, they lived a
family of little creatures called the Trebum. Trebum are not the strongest nor the fastest,
and they do not have sharp teeth. They would make easy prey for the terrible force that came to their
planet. But Trebum are loyal and resourceful and very, very stubborn. Okay. It is with such a Trebum
that our story begin. One clever little creature born into a cruel world who would be instrumental
in bringing prosperity to its kind. That's me. Is this like Spore? I don't think so. I think.
I don't know. We'll find out. Okay. I wonder what happened. Pretty. What an unfortunate place for a
beginning. Okay. And now what? Run. Something inside him said run. Run. This is a controller
game. What is that? Oh my God. There's a giant wave behind here. I, this is a controller game.
Holy shit. Okay. Don't stop running. I'm not. I'm going. I can't make this. Am I going to die?
Oh shit. Can I jump? What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? The great crushing
thing, the great cylinder had stopped. Perhaps it was safe here for a little while. This pub G?
How quickly it learned to use its legs and its trunk. But these things were not so much learned
as they were remembered. They were a gift from the strange voice it heard in its mind.
Are these evil? That too was a kind of memory. Oh, what did I just do? Okay. What? What? Oh,
that was weird. What did I just do? Okay. Choose materials you've collected. Okay.
And do what? Just eat it? Just when it was starting to get used to its legs,
the food from the jumping creature gave it new ones with the right substances. Oh shit. A
trebum can transform and adapt to many challenges. Okay. So if I eat, it's kind of like Kirby.
Shoot anything from your inventory. Try shooting water at the flying bugs.
Shoot. Okay. So I have water in my nose. Okay. We eat that, right? What? Do I like breathe this in
that face? It's kind of oops. Okay. I got, should I eat this? Well, oh, no, no, no, no,
come back here. Okay. I just shot it out. Hold on. How do I eat that? Okay. I cannot eat this.
Should I suck in more than one? I got mushrooms. Eat the mushrooms. What did that do? This might
just be healing. What is that? I can only hold three different types of things. All right. That's
good to know. This is technically a mushroom. Okay. How much can I hold? Should I store a bunch
of this? Like a gerbil? 10? 10 each, you think? We'll do it. Come on. Suck it up. Well, eight's
fine. The trebum was drawn to a bright light or perhaps to the creature next to it. A creature.
There is something over there. What is that? It's like a brontosaurus. Except for the grass growing
on the old one's head. They were very much alike. What? Surrounded by this light,
the trebum knew things it had not known before. It knew the older trebum had carried this light
for a long, long time. Oh, that's the same species. And it knew that now that responsibility had passed
to the next generation. Yes. This young trebum had to carry the light to those great towers in the
distance. It could have stayed here to learn many old things, but the cylinder would not allow it.
Is it going to start up again? Stanley Parable. Yeah. What makes that happen?
Run. The inner voice said run. The towers would not stop the cylinder. I can suck it up. Activated.
I'm strong. Roll to move faster. Okay. So I'd go for this thing. I'm going to just say I'm
legally drinking alcohol right now. The cylinder would not be stopped.
All right. Okay. Is it going to stop? Wait, what? Didn't it say this thing? How do I stop this?
Wait, I didn't listen. You got to get out of here. Get out of here. This is like mouth monster.
Oh shit. No, don't. No. The voice inside the trebum's memories assured it that while the
tower stood, the trebum would be safe. The power of the eternal cylinder was contained for now.
Okay. So you block it with this stuff. I want to get a look at this. Is this thing?
What are you doing? Relative tranquility gave the trebum a chance to think about its family.
I'm not meant to be alone. So where were the others? I wanted to make a friend,
I wanted to make a friend. I didn't know. We've both just survived that together. You'd think
that we would have sort of like a Wizard of Oz moment where it's like, hey, we both have the same
shit going on. I guess not. Okay. Well, checkpoint. Good. Thank God. The giant mouth is not a friend.
I didn't know everything was dangerous. Okay. The voice inside the trebum's memories assured it
that while the tower stood, the trebum would be safe. The power of the eternal cylinder was
contained for now. This thing is crazy looking. You want to share food gave the trebum a chance
to think about its family. Trebum are not meant to live alone. So where were the others? We're
going to find more. Okay. Ready to eat this stuff. I feel like there's a lot of random things I can
collect. All right. These are like eggs over there. This counts as water. Oh, I have like a water
meter. Okay. So I got to find more friends. This character looks like you. Yeah, maybe a little.
Our young friend had found an egg, a trebum egg with one of his siblings inside.
Okay. The egg had been abandoned, but it could still be made to hatch.
All that was needed was a source of heat. I'm going to break this if I move it. This looks like
kind of an incubator. Oh, put it down. I know. Okay. This is like the, oh,
Wugwool. Okay. Hey, hey, hey, don't just eat stuff. Don't just eat stuff. I don't wait. I can't
control Wugwool. Wugwool just has, has a mind. I like the pattern. Okay. So we got two now.
How do I make it so you have bigger legs here? Eat this like fucking turnip, whatever this is.
Oh, that's me eating it. Here. Try one of these. Eat that. You don't want that? All right. I'll keep
it. All right. So we have another party member. This is not moving yet. So that's good. Anything
else to do here? What about this stuff? Ooh, I think it's just food. I don't think it doesn't do
anything. I ate that grasshopper and I got legs. I can't really eat anything else. All right. There's
a mouth monster over there. I'm not going over there. I wonder how many, uh, like little people
you end up having. Do I have a life cycle? Am I just gonna die eventually? Oh, it's way too cold
over here. Get out. Can we eat something to make us have, I don't know. Let's see. Come on. Mutation
items have a lightning bolt next to them. Oh, so imagine that's just health. It's probably just
food. Health. Did I miss something? Anything else to do? I'm very intrigued by this game.
Drink some water. Actually, yeah. It's too cold over there though. What's that? These animals?
This is fucking Dr. Sue shit. Ooh, hold on. Ooh, what does this do? How do I do that?
That's annoying. Should we both eat one? Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Let's test it.
Yeah, that's what I thought. Spore two with fart noises. I think I just have to explore.
It's so cold over here though. Shit. No, this way. You're doing the auto voice. Yeah, of course. I'm
doing auto. Wait, how long can I, hold on. Are these predators? Wait, this is fuzzy. Hold on. Wait,
can we wear these? It's going to be like a sweater. Did you get one too? Now we're fuzzy. I feel like
this game is dangerous. I'm going to get, okay. Do you see anything else? Hold on. I'm going to
go this way. Oh shit. Don't die. Is there fall damage? Weird mushrooms. I need water. You just
die if you run out of water. You can swap. Oh, I can swap. Okay. Q swaps. Interesting. All right.
There's an egg over there. Can we sneak by this thing? Oh God. Is it awake? Get me out of here.
A new family member. Gui. Okay. Hi, Gui. Okay, so we're, Gui doesn't have any protection from
heat though. I mean cold. What the fuck did you just do? I think Gui needs fur, right? We need,
hold on. No, no, no. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. We sharing it? I think we, yeah, we shared it.
Why can I not move? Okay. I can't move with this creature. Why not? I can't physically move. That's
strange. Okay. Well, whatever. I got three. I need water. I have to find a pond or something.
Wait, there's water here. This is frozen water. Can we like break it? Can we drink out of this?
Come on. There's gotta be something I can drink. Get the water eggs. Oh, that's a good idea.
Why can I not control this guy? Oh, this is water. Okay. We're going to die. There's like a big lake
over here. Can I just stick my face in here? Just drink it? All right. Yes, we can do this.
Come drink. Make sure you get, yeah, there we go. I have lost control of this character. I can,
all I can do is drink. Satisfied? This thing hasn't started moving. Should I swim over
there or anything? It's all salt water. Where to go? It's too young to swim across. Watch for the
beams of light that come from activated towers. They will point you to objectives or areas of
interest. Ooh. It was hard for the Trevim to know what to do or where to go, but the friendly voice
suggested this was not the right way. Stream remote? To find your path, it said you must follow
the beam of light. I did not get Luigi'd. To the tip of the tower and stay away from the deep waters
where the old things dwell. I didn't get, I did not get Luigi'd. Wait, everybody should have the
little horn, right? Where's the horn? I just heard it. Or maybe not. Okay, so we need to go this way.
Did everybody have a horn? Why not? Yeah, might as well take one. I think this is my favorite,
like the blue. So everybody has access to that. All right, let's control. All right, this thing
wants me to go this way. We could probably fuck somebody up. Not that that's what I want to do.
I'm just making it clear that, what's that? Wait, the snail, that was just open. What was that? Did
you see that? What does that sound? That was a free, yeah, that's a freaky snail. What do we do
this guy? I don't know, I got him. I don't know. What should we do with him? Kill it? Why? What
if it could help us? Wait, that guy just attacked me. Get out of here. Just jump over. Wait.
He's like a little weirdo. Get out of here. What the fuck? I'm gonna play this instrument
ever again, I promise. Holy shit, that was crazy. Okay. Whatever that is, it's big and I don't know
if it's friendly. Something's loud. Will you go down water? Wait, there's an egg. A fish. I just
got a fish. Hold on. Get rid of this. All right. Get the egg. How do we get up there? We just suck
it up from here? I don't know. Oh my god. Get out of the water. Get out of the water. We think we're
dying. We're struggling. Get out of the water. We're struggling so bad. Please don't drown. Okay.
Oh my god. That was bad. Can I knock the, wait, come here. I have an idea. Fuck. That was a
gridded. That was a bad idea. Stack them up. Can we do that? Can I jump on top of one of their heads?
Maybe it's the fish that has, wait, the fish. This is part of the fish here. This is just food.
Yeah, it's just food. Wait a minute. This is something else. Back to the surface. Quick.
What does this do? All right. Not all, don't all of you eat that. Don't all of you eat that. This guy
just turned into a cement brick. I don't know if that was a good idea. Well, I don't know. What
about the fish? All right. This is an actual fish. What do you do? Frog? Swimming more quickly but
can form a high jump out of the water. All right. Cool. So we've got float guy, frog guy, and
whatever I can do with you, I kind of, I can't move for some reason. I think it's bugged,
but I can't walk along with this character. I think it's a bug. I wonder, can I tell people
to stop just to stay or is there like a command? Maybe restart it. Save and reload. Yeah, we'll
save it. Save and then main menu. Look at the tutorial. I, I mean, I, I just, I can't move with
that, that one for some reason. I don't know why. Is he too heavy? That's possible, but I don't know.
I think one of the incubators is over here. He's going to be in this one. This game's cute. I like
it. You just kind of get like friends. We all have a job. Okay. Okay. Or when somebody dies,
I'm going to be really sad. Ah, that's way more helpful. If I hold Q, I can just select the one
I want to control. This one's still bugged, but it's all right. All right. Well, what do I want
this one to eat? Reload it, save, and then just load the save. Use the broken one as cannon fodder.
We have to go over there and I'm, I can tell you, I'm not super thrilled about it. There we go. Okay.
I can control this one now. Stop sucking up random stuff. I feel like these guys,
I feel like this is going to eat one of us. Right? Who, I don't want, I'm not getting rid of the,
the big one. Oh God. All right. Should I just get up? This door had been built for Trebum.
It gave them hope that in this large and dangerous world, some places had been made for them.
Whoa. What's that thing? What did I just get? Some ingredients cannot be eaten until their
edible interiors have been exposed. There are multiple ways to break open ingredients. Try
experimenting with throwing them, crushing them, or feeding them to other creatures.
Items with a breakable exterior are marked with a yellow border. Oh my, I feel so bad.
We just like took that snails. I don't know what we did, but I don't, I'm kind of sad about it.
All right. Everybody in. I broke it. I don't, I don't know what that is. Who should eat this?
I mean, you've got like the big butt power. You've got the swimming power. I have jumping power.
The new guy here. Try this. This is going to snail power. What does, what would that even mean?
Whoa. Make some shiny, sparkly, and very attractive.
This is like the attractive one. Okay. Well, cool. Let's go. I wonder if this is like a little
hideout. Hmm. Have to quickly change the group leader. Hold to manually select. Don't worry.
If you lose sight of one of your family members, you do not need to wait for other TREBUM. They
will always manage to get where the group leader is. Okay. So you don't have to worry about them.
So they will always get to where you're going or better for us, I guess. It's like, Ooh,
what is that? To the top, right? I'm kind of resource. We should eat like a kind of like
alien watermelon. All right. Everybody eat these. I'm going to clear up the inventory.
Sell that one. It's rare. This is a family. Nobody low on water. I think everyone's fine.
What do you have so many mushrooms? Just eat them. Oh my God. I just ate everything.
Okay. Don't all of you do that. All right. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. You ate all the food.
Was that our, wait, I probably shouldn't have not. I probably shouldn't have done that.
Interact. Somehow this ancient statue transferred knowledge to the TREBUM.
This tells you what everything does. Inventory. Oh, he's got a way bigger inventory. Okay. That's
cool. All right. You hold all the snacks. You're going to be the snack storage. The map is here.
Very nice. It was as if a memory had been stored inside it, waiting for someone to absorb it.
And as soon as this knowledge had entered their minds, the TREBUM realized that there was a great
library of information hidden away in the web of their memories. But why was the knowledge of a
specific ingredient placed here in this TREBUM made of stone? I wonder. Oh, more of this.
Do you collect this dust? They're learning. Okay. Well, can we get it? Are we supposed to?
We did it. All right. Who wants to eat this weird cube? It's so stylish. The stylish cube.
So yeah, I can fit in here. Ah, it opens the door.
Garumo the Elder. I'm going to start talking. Wait, this is a, oh, this is an adult? Inside the cave,
the TREBUM found a living elder. It had been waiting in this chamber for a long, long time.
The elder told them it was happy to see some friends before the cylinder came. This is kind
of sad. It said, you are young. So you never knew the time when our people could shape shift at will.
We TREBUM are inheritors of a vast tree of abilities, abilities passed on to all future TREBUM.
But this power is being taken away. Beware the servants of the cylinder. They will seek to hurt
you at every opportunity. And they have the power to rob you of your abilities. Like a car? But if
you persevere, one day you will find a way to protect yourselves from their evil light. Farewell,
my brave friends. I fear I am too old and tired to join you. May you find a way to prosper
in this time of struggles. All right, so thanks for helping. Here, have a mushroom on me.
Okay, so we can go that way. Wait, wait, wait, wait. He almost shot it up his nose.
What is this? This is like a bath? It's like a little bird bath. Everybody,
should we get into the, this is like a jacuzzi? Easy. Oh, it's a place to fill up water.
You should make the fat one eat a cube. Maybe. Is everybody good? Everybody have water? Make sure
to fill up. We're not, we're gonna get out of here. Should the fat one eat a cube? I don't know if I
want another big cube. Should I? Yes. Okay. All right, so he's not, it squished him down.
He's not big anymore. It's a cube. So the power is, some of them don't stack. So now I just have two
cubes. I lost my, I had a bunch of watermelons. Turn him back. I can't turn him back. He's,
he's like this permanently. Everybody else want to be a cube? No, we are, we have two cubes. That's
good enough. Make him eat something. You can't have a double cube, right? Yeah, just need to
find another one of those fishes. That's fine. All right. Let's keep going. Load the save. No,
we have to experiment. Give them nicknames. I don't want to, because I know for a fact that
some of them are going to die. Like, I just know it. You know it. I know it. It was not easy to
leave the cave, but the elder had urged them to go forward. Suddenly they felt the weight of their
many tasks to find their trebum siblings, to restore the powers their people had lost.
They all seemed a little daunting, but even when they are afraid, trebum are stubborn.
You okay? How do we rescue this one? Food? Here, eat this. Can you eat that? What about water?
It didn't work. What? I'm trying. Grunk? What is this? What? I need four. Oh, okay.
We have to feed him for the of the. All right. All right. All right. We have to save this guy.
All that little stardust. Fuck. I just wasted so much water. Okay. Do I still have the indicator
telling me where to go? Let's get water first. Anything happen at night? Oh, fuck. Don't come
in here. I need the jumper. It did say, don't worry. They will find a way to you. I'm looking
for more of that stardust. The cave had more dust. Oh, is that right there? No. Checking to see.
What's this? Weird mushrooms. I don't want them. Whoa. What the fuck is this? These are different.
These are like different eggs. This is bad. Should I hatch this? We're gonna take more than one.
Here. Okay. Somebody grab that one. Grab that one. All right. All right. All right. All right.
All right. Where's an incubator? Break one? No, I don't want to do that. Incubator. Get the
stardust, bro. Hold on. Is there no incubator around here? There's one over there. Bro. What
is this stuff for? Exiting the blue energy dome that radiates from the tower you activated will
awaken the eternal cylinder. Warning. Not all towers have the same radius of protection. Some
may be weaker. Oh, when I walk. Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello? Get out of there. No, no, no, no.
Run, run, run. Is this their egg? Is this yours? You can have back. Take it back. You can have back.
You can have back. Yeah. Take it back. Take it back. Run. I think that was, was that their egg?
I don't know. Just run. Just get away. Get away. Get away. I don't know where to go. I don't know
where to go. I'm freaking out. All right. Where's the egg? Where'd it go? Give it to me. I'm taking
it. I don't care. Well, what? Oh, shit. The cylinder resumed its destruction. Nothing could
stop it forever. Yeah. They need to roll to safety to find another tower. Crap. All right. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. What? I don't know what this is, but I want it. It's like a weird
magical... Okay, go. This one right here. Oh, no, our... The friend. I forgot. I forgot about that.
Oh, no. That's not good. That's too bad. That's too bad. Grungo, whatever his name was.
You murdered him. Keep going. Come on. Oh my God. Go, go, go, go, go. Reload. No, it's okay.
I made the mistake. I'm going to live with it. Oh, that's sad. It's okay. Please reload. I can't.
I made the mistake. I have to live with it. The Trebem found themselves almost as lost as they
had been in the beginning. And where is the fifth? The most powerful of all the Trebems.
It was only natural to be confused, it said. They had been born into a strange, broken world,
cut off from the history of their ancestors. Everyone was a little lost these days. What
mattered was to keep going, to keep looking for answers, to keep carrying the light they held
within them. The light that stopped the cylinder. Why is this one almost dead? Okay. That would have
been sad. Water. I can't find any. You're kind of not understanding the fart dynamic. Sorry about
that. Let's continue. That looks like poisonous. I don't think I want to go in there. Is this over
here? I'm going to go in this. Okay. What's this? We're all making it out alive. The strange,
eerie temple. The Trebem felt something stir in their memories. There was a great power in this
place. Something from the days when even the elders were young. Perhaps it could help them.
A stir is here. What's up, dude? All right, this is a power. Who should have this? I think I'm
giving it to you. Eat that. I don't know what this is going to do. Hopefully it doesn't do anything
weird. Okay, so he attracts the flies. He's just cool hair now. This attracts these flies. Wait,
what am I looking at here? What is this? This is a human. This is a human. No, wait, what the
fuck is that? What is this? It's like a human in a human. All right. Well, what do I do here?
Get those. I think I have to bring them over here. Yeah. Wait, what's this? I don't know. What does
this do? I don't know. They're like little crystals. I'm taking them. The humans have mutations too.
That was very ominous. Uh, okay. So I think I just have to bring flies over here to follow me.
All right, here they come. Okay. Now can somebody take that? All right, who has a room?
You. No, maybe not. Oh, wait. Could not retrieve any helpful information from the Trebum memory
cluster. Whoa. So was that giving me? The Trebum were disoriented for a moment. It was like a
finished map. Something new had entered their memories and they needed to make sense of it.
It seemed to be a map. And on this map, a location had been marked. If they understood correctly,
there was some manner of serpent, a guardian, a greater being of some kind, somehow linked
to a safe haven. Could they find refuge there? Their ancestors must have created this map
for a reason. All right. So we have to go find the big giant serpent thing. So hold on. Let me,
how do I get to this menu? Can I press a certain button to get there? How do I get to that menu?
M escape. Press the map key. Hold on. Let me roll. Spit open inventory. Interact. I think it's I.
Yes. Okay. So a map it's marked on. It's now marked, which is up here. So we've got to go
out here through here to here. Good luck. So this gives you a map fragment piece. Wait,
hold on. What's that? You see that up here? I wonder if I can eat that. Can I grab that?
Oh, thank God. Tapioca pudding. Yay or nay? Uh, tapioca pudding is probably,
it's probably a nay for me. I don't hate it, but I'm not, I wouldn't order it. I know that a lot of
some of what Boba right is tapioca. That's, that's all right. Ooh, where did that just go? Oh,
okay. A little ball. I'm gonna pick this up. I gotta break it. Shit. What is, okay. We have
two cubes. One of the cubes is not going to be a cube anymore. Should we give it to the attractive
one or the, I don't know, give it a blue. All right. The attractive cube or the blue. Okay.
Well, we'll give it a blue. So much bullshit. Get rid of these stupid mushrooms. Get this out of
here. Stop eating and get rid of that. Let's see what happens. Plated body. Okay. I got a shell,
but this, this one's a fight. This one can fight now. Turtle. All right. Let's fill up.
Now we got to get out of here. I kind of want to see if I can get that.
You know what I mean? Can I break this shit? I feel like I can use this for some reason.
These little crystal things. I feel like I can get that. Should we water at it? Oh, it worked.
It actually worked. All right. What is this thing? I don't know who's going to eat this.
Dude, what is this? I don't know what this is going to do. Should I hold it?
I'm going to hold onto this. Yeah. I'm going to hold this. We have turtle.
We have fish. We have jumping spiky haired dude. And we have attractive cube. I think this is good
for now. I think this is okay. Let's keep going. Would you please, uh, project song void? I think
so. What manner of strange beast lurk behind the center? The trebum were deeply unsettled by this
new mystery, but though some part of them was curious, they were certain it would be best not
to find out. Where is everybody? Uh, yeah. Get me out of there. The narrative just cough.
They should not find out. There's an incubator here. Um, I wish I had one of them. What is this?
This is just food. I don't want to go yet. Holy shit. What's that? Oh my God. All right.
There's too many things. Um, just eat it. Water processor? The water processor mutation is
constantly processing ingredients found in its inventory slots, transforming them into water.
Note that this does not extract any nutrients from them. Be mindful of what you absorb with
this trebum as its body will automatically process any organic ingredients stored inside.
The trebum were excited by this discovery. This new mutation would allow them to extract water
from ingredients that were otherwise quite dry. Don't do that. But the voice cautioned them to
be careful. More water was useful, but this process would not extract any nutrients. They
would have to use it carefully and wisely. Uh, somebody just turned into a water filter. All
right. So let's go with this. I mean, maybe the thing that's 10, right? Maybe this too. Okay.
This is just going to be producing water. You put dry things in it and it just makes,
okay. So this thing, it just needs to suck up a bunch of junk, right? All right. Let's keep going.
Oh God. Okay. We need another egg. You gave him too many items. Oh shit. All right. I said,
you mean only give stuff to this character when we need water. Does that mean, all right,
when you're looking for an egg, looking for eggs, that's interesting. Whatever that is,
I want to go look at it. Does it show where we are on the map? It does. All right. We need to
go up here. So I, let me, let me investigate this. All right. Go, go, go, go. Do not aggro that thing.
I want this weird building over here. Is this, is this building, whatever this weird like big
piece of artwork it looks like. All right. What's this? Oh fuck. Everybody's cold.
We still don't, we don't have that mutation. I thought we had it. All right. I won't be here
long. What is in here? Nothing in here. It's like a cool thing. There's gotta be something over here.
Well, no, no, no, don't just pick stuff up. You're going to turn it into water. Actually,
that's okay. All right. We're going to get out of here. What's this? I don't know what this does.
I don't know. This is somebody take this. We're going to get, we gotta get out of the cold now.
Get out of the cold, out of the cold. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. How do I get out of the cold?
We've got to go this way. Back it up, back it up, back it up, back it up, back it up, back it up.
Come on, get out, out, out, out, out. We're okay. Get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out,
get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out,
get out, get out, get out. Don't die, please. Oh, wait, the thing's moving. The thing's moving.
It's moving. It's moving. Go, go, go, go, go. Eat this? What happened? Oh shit. Whoa, no.
No, no, no, no. Back it up, back it up. Back, back, back. Back, back, back, back, back,
back, back. This way, this way, this way. Oh no, that's awful. Oh no. We're all gonna die.
We're all gonna die. Follow me, follow me, please.
Go, oh I fucked up everything. I fucked everything up. I ruined everything. It's okay,
it's okay. It's alright. We gotta get over here. We gotta get this way, through here. We're safe.
Okay
Come on. Oh
Goodness, okay, so that was a little bit of a problem. That was a little bit of a problem. I have to activate it. Oh
shit
Was lost
There was no more pointed running. Yes, there is yes, there is under
Consume and I thought it was gonna stop it. I thought it was gonna block it. I thought it was gonna block it
I thought I was gonna block it. Is there no more of those things?
My god
Okay, I didn't know I had to activate it. That was terrible. I feel so bad
Okay. Well, did the auto save this is two minutes ago. Okay, we're good
We need to just go this way. I had it right just get out of here. I do want to eat though
I want to eat this
Because this thing makes water what the fuck did you just do?
Okay, we're good. So now this thing processes more water
So it's better
Here we go. Okay, everyone sit out here for a sec. I'm not gonna activate it yet. Please get away from us
Is there an egg here egg egg? Wait people say an egg. Is there an egg? Was there an egg? I don't see one. Oh
My god, everything is so dangerous
It's a big peach egg
No
Guys, that's a mouth monster
Hey
We're good. What about this thing? Do you do anything? Can we do anything with this or is it just a set piece?
You left an egg. I don't think I did. I got plenty of time. I don't see anything
Usually they'd be like a little oh no. Look at the distance gonna make it you're gonna make it. Oh
They're not gonna make it. All right, it's wrong. Oh wait, you're hungry. Does anybody have food?
Okay, the stomach meter represents your party's food and energy level
It's divided into two parts stomach and the energy pouch
I'm a calls all the food you consume and fills up depending on the nutritional qualities the ingredients you eat and digest food when
Resting or standing still which depletes the stomach and fills the energy pouch and you pouch is not only necessary
For your tribune to survive it's essential for replenishing the energy the tribune used to roll
Those energy you have the more slowly your stamina and endurance will regenerate. Okay rolling consumes a lot of energy
So if you plan on rolling to distant safe areas, you must be prepared as their fear faded
The trebum started feeling weak and tired with all the excitement and adventure
They've neglected their most basic needs the sound of an empty stomach reminded them that survival requires more than
Escaping from danger. Okay, you also have to eat
Luckily when the cylinder is the internal the trebum is the capacity to store food in their bodies
But they still need to digest it to gain the vital energy that gives them strength and for such small creatures
They do require rather a lot of food
I fortunately the Savannah was rich in flora and fauna which would satisfy their little bellies
without necessarily
triggering a
Mutation so I think you share it. It looks like it's when I eat it goes plus plus plus
I think it's for everybody. Alright, so they're introducing mechanics as we go. That's interesting. Whatever that is. Alright, I'm fairly safe right now
I'm looking for eggs. This is games really cool. I like it
So I'm imagining you probably can get anti poison protection or something. You should use that thing
You already have um, who has the turtle has it? I think I'm gonna feed this to
The attractive cube third I can use this mutation to look for specific ingredients by tagging them in the compendium
Okay of all the changes that trebum were experiencing growing a third
I was the strangest one yet and make things even stranger
This I seem to look in two directions at once
Into the world and into their memories like the eye icon
To find in the real world any element that was contained in the web of their memories
It was truly a remarkable mutation. What should I look for?
Where's the thing to make the big puffy one? One of these here look for this
Okay, if I do that, then how do I know where it is? I wonder looks kind of funny
Can you do eggs? Can you look for eggs? That's a good point egg yolk
Egg shroom, I don't think I can look for them individually all hail attractive cube seer of the unseen
There's a creature tab
Alright we need to find an egg. I need to find a fifth party member. Mm-hmm. Alright new friend. They need incubator
I don't see wait that one over here sacrifice the rest of them. You only need one. I
Highly doubt that here we go. What we're good. Once I get more than five or six of these
I feel like I'm gonna start losing track. Alright, what do we get? Come on out friend grew Temu. Hello grew Temu
What are we gonna turn you into? We'll figure that out. Alright, we need to eat who has food you do eat a few mushrooms
What about his mouth? But
Okay, we got a new friend. The goal is ultimately to go this way. Yeah, we're gonna go up here. There is another
Place there, but I'm not gonna do that yet. Hold on. I feel like there might be something else
Wait, yeah a lot of danger over here though. What is that thing? Oh
That's weird. Oh this thing pukes. What is that doing?
Goodness, everybody be careful. What is this thing? What the fuck? Alright, so what is this?
Bro, that thing is disgusting
Boy new fruits. Ooh
Wait, okay. Let's do it allows the treatment to produce a song that causes the click ball to follow them
Yeah, but I'm so even more than one. All right, cool. What is it? Glick Bowl? Can I go any deeper? Is that it? That's it?
Wow, what's that? Oh my god. What else do I need to do with this? Can I activate this or what?
What's this here for? I wonder why is this activated cube hole? Ah
That's right. Okay. I want that egg the things are gonna get out of the way is the big guy a Glick Bowl
Possibly, but I don't really want to find out
All right, the attractive cube in there
The trebum felt a great power flowing through this cave, but they were not afraid
The power felt familiar
even friendly
These glowing structures were the work of their ancestors
puzzle
They water any food too. Okay
Well, we're gonna suck up all this shit. I turn them on water storage increase your maximum water storage
capacity
These are upgrades cool. Okay
They all cost six right do this
I wonder if I should hold on to this to get another friend maximum health
It's two in the attractive cube evolve into the larger more attractive cube, baby
I don't know. We'll find out soon enough. Alright, so I have seven. I think that's all there is here. What's this one?
Oh the maximum number of Trebum how many can we have now like we need that?
That's maximum and have more family members didn't click on one. He's the size of the stamina wheel probably health
I want to blow through on my on my material though. You do it twice twice or save it just once
I'm happy with that. All right
I wonder if I lose access to this place because isn't this gonna get destroyed this thing's about to get annihilated water
Yeah, good water. How we on food who has food?
None of you have anything save the game. I think it actually is saving right now. Where's my fifth these crystals, too
Alright, there's this food there's water and then there are crystals
What the fuck are these for right? Like what is this for? It's got to be something to do with this
Is even in the compendium memory cluster contains a fragment of a story about a culture hero called
Naka who was cast into the underworld by Chris. This is is this it? Yeah. Okay. So does this really do anything food?
Creatures some memory cluster. I think it's just they're on
Or in the water, I mean they're cool-looking but I don't think they do anything. I think we're good eat one
I'm not sure you can that's right. You're not even let's go
You're probably gonna need 30 of those in the last five minutes of the story true
What's the objective of the game? The objective of this game is you are these little creatures and there is an eternal
Death wall that is slowly destroying everything and you need to outrun it and live. All right, we're good
Was that what the fuck is that? All right, I'm getting nervous. I gotta get out of here. All right, I got an egg
Check over here. How we doing on food? We're all right, but eat pretty good
Just checking just suck up a bunch of bullshit and make sure to eat it. That's the play. There we are. All right, the
Objective is over here
Where straight ahead I got plenty of water plenty food a cube is so attractive speed run the game
Speed run in the game is I'm sure there's a rolling speed mutation. You probably just run as well
Yep, a new friend. I don't activate it yet. Yeah, this I'm sure this I don't like that thing at all
There's two of them to that incubator was over here, right? It's way somewhere
You can't roll
Where was it? Where I think it wasn't this far. Was it this far?
It was definitely this far
Where is it you have a map are those on the map is it right there is that that one
Is that what that is on the map go to the bruhs, huh? What do you mean go to the bruh?
Listen, what is that? All right, there's something. All right. I'm getting overwhelmed. Hold on
We need to open this and then I'm going in that hole. All right, there it is. Oh
Oh
Go this way go this way go this way go this way go this way the monsters are fucking weird in this game
He's exactly in the area. I need to be in get out of here. Goon. Oh, okay. Goon. Oh, let's go
What do we have six going in this hole? All right, the hole is over here. Hope this does not kill us. It'd be very sad
You guys ready? Whoa
Don't wait for others when entering or exiting small caves jump pads a moving plant
They move on their own. It will follow you. I want to look at this though. There's like something up here
Can I touch that or something?
Okay, so this is a jump pad
Huh? Are you all right? We'll gull need more leadership. We're perfectly fine
What do you mean need more leadership? What does that mean? We're not smart enough need more leadership. What?
Ooh
Something new new shit in here. Uh you all right. This is just health nothing else in there the upgrade thing
party full need upgrade
No, wait this he's they're gonna die down here. What do we do about this?
Will you be able to jump higher and have the turtle show curious? I think this is the leader you need to kill them
I don't think so. I feel so bad. I really want this one. Um, how much was it?
I'm gonna buy it. I'm buying it. I don't care if it's a waste. I want this friend
This is kind of hard to get out of here. Okay, i'm rescuing that one. Oh, I won't have enough. That's right
It's gonna be like four to upgrade and then it's probably gonna be four or five to get them
It's four will I have enough to free them the question you have six
I don't know if i'm gonna be able to do it. I think I just have to move on this game music on
Yeah, it should be that better. Maybe we're just too low. You should just try. All right
What if I waste all my stardust or whatever the hell this stuff is? All right
Uh, fine. We'll do it. Why is this closed?
It's locked off now
We can't go back in
Unfortunate there's a hole in the ground
Wait, wait, wait, wait, what? What? No, I think I don't think I can get back in
Oh in the hole you jumped out of
the hole I jumped out of is where the
There's just a little cave with that pink guy
Upgrade rooms are locked when you exit. Oh
It's too bad
That's too bad. I'm sorry. And I mean are we willing to sacrifice somebody? I don't know if i'm willing to sacrifice anybody
Should we sacrifice the new green guy?
But we just got gunu
Gunu doesn't deserve to die
Kill gunu
What?
I can't believe i'm hearing this
kill gunu
Sack. No, we can't even get uh
I'm not gonna kill the sexy cube. Are you out of your mind? Um, all right, i'm making a decision here. I'm sorry. No
No gunu stays. I'm sorry
uh pink pink
Trebum, i'm sorry
I've made my decision
All right, we're gonna go this way left
over here
We yeah, we need water. I'm gonna eat and have water. Where's the water guy?
You turn this into water
Thank you. Okay. What else you got? You have like power shit eat that eat that
Uh eat that that was a lot of water. Holy shit. Okay
Turn that poop into wine. All right, I think we're good goal is over here. I'm gonna take the turtle
Hey, i'm gonna take hey big raid coming in from connery's pants. What's up connor? Welcome everybody
Thanks to the raid. We're currently playing the eternal cylinder. It's pretty fun. Hope you had a good stream
Just chilling out for a little bit playing it and I need to just get a uh, we gotta go now
We gotta go now
Go go go go go do not get picked up
Okay, we have to we get we're moving and we are not we're not looking at anything
I'm not gonna look at how scary that is and that i'm just crossing the path right now
Get away from puke
Everything is okay
Here comes the wall
Everyone is chasing us
Okay
Everybody's still intact. Yep. We're gonna be really hungry after this get out of there get out of there. I got you. Don't worry
Oh
What do I do? It is a car. It's a car
Is it gonna wake up? I don't want to fucking be here to find out
Don't wake up was this strange being
Half flesh half metal
The trebum felt an old distant horror as if they remembered their own destruction
Something about this creature was very
very
Wrong, so don't wake it up
The hand behind the car that is weird
I don't think we want to wake this
I'm not going to
Oh, it's it's the influence of the three fingers
Perhaps the creature would wake up with a loud noise
If we want that to happen, I don't really want to do that
I need oh wait. What is this?
There's a hole behind it, but just let me what is this?
I pull the plug here. Can we pick this up or something? I don't know you need to eat something. Yeah. Yeah. Yep. Yep. Yep
But anyways, uh, thanks for the ray conor. Hope you're doing good
Yeah, we're just chilling out
Just hanging out
Who told you to do that?
Who did that?
Who told you to do that? It's awake now. We need to eat first. What are you thinking?
Why would you blow the horn? Who did that?
Trapped on all sides by deep pools of poisonous gas
The trebum needed to find a way to escape this monstrosity
I didn't want that to happen to use the creature's own weight
to lower the bridge
Okay, first of all
So you need to run over here and
and smash into this
It was gunu. He betrayed you. What's wrong with us?
What what's wrong with us? What's wrong? What's happening? What's wrong with us?
No
I did it guys. I can't look behind me restart restart restart restart. Everyone's gonna fucking die down here restart restart
No, everyone's like coughing and choking. How do we get out? How do we get out of here? How do we get out of here?
What the fuck? It's so hard
God dang gunu. God damn it gunu. We were not ready
Gunu we weren't ready
You just wiped out the entire fucking family gunu
You blew the why would you blow the horn? I wasn't prepared
Okay
Ban gunu from the guild
All right. So the idea is we have to wake up the month. Wait, not yet
Let me eat first
Do not blow your horn
Just wait get out of here. Just trying to get it full stomach. All right, uh, I want the water
I want you to produce water
Take a bunch of junk
Okay gunu fight back. Wait, it wasn't gunu
Gunu doesn't have a horn
It was vu
It was this dumbass
Okay. Well, whatever
So the strategy here is you gotta wake up this thing
And have it run over here
That's I guess what i'm gonna do and let's try it
Won't wake up from this. Why not?
Go go go go
Trapped on all sides by deep pools of poisonous gas
The trebum needed to find a way to escape this monstrosity. Oh here
Perhaps there was a way to use the creature's own weight
To lower the bridge
Oh fuck. All right. We got it. We got it. Go go go go go
one by one
The oh light cruelly burned away the trebum's ability stop
How do I stop this? The elder had warned them about the evil light of the cylinder's servants the light
Now they knew what kind of creature to avoid
Get out of the poison. We all did we make it safely?
One two, three four. You guys all right?
All right. Take a break
Hold on. We need to take a break
So we don't have any more abilities
We don't have an attractive cube anymore
Okay
So we now we kind of start we start the process up again. All right ruin the run
No sexy cube
Attractive cube. All right
How we doing we need
Up here
There's still space to explore over here. So let's go ahead and just see what we have
That weird car is no longer over here
just scanning the field
See what's here
I wonder if you can eventually kill those things or fight back or attack or something
Interesting. What's that behind you? We're good. I mean, yeah, there's that thing but
We're getting out of here. What's this?
Revival shrine
These special ruins scattered around the world allow you to store or revive fellow trebum
Storing trebum can be useful if you reach the maximum party limit
Who would like to call upon some of your trebum during a later stage of the adventure?
Reviving lost trebum comes at a cost. The cost is based on how many mutations the trebum had when it perished
Okay
When the trebum stepped on the strange device
Interesting ancient memory came back to them a memory of long ago
Where the cities of their people still stood and the fight against the cylinder was not yet lost
So we got those days
A very smart trebum had found a way of cheating very smart trebum
Of stealing stuff in the cloud to absorb and to reshape and being uploaded to amazon web service
Revive their fallen friends or send others to a hidden place
And it was also by this device that a link had been forged
They have so many g names opened to the voice that spoke within them
Put gunu in the hole
Should we all right gunu is in the cloud, but that's kind of unfair
No, we don't want to store gunu. Everyone's safe
I think the whole point of storing is if they have a certain mutation that you don't want to lose
But nobody has a mutation. We all got it all just kind of gripped away. That's cool. That's how that works
All right, does that does that thing does it look like anything on the map?
Well, not much further to get to whatever that is. I wonder if there's anything else store someone away and save the pink one
I really hate to say this the pink one is gone pink one is over there far over there
Very dead get some water. Oh, hold on. Wasn't somebody supposed to be finding the fish ones. Here we go
All right, who do we want to be? Uh the big uh, big fat one blue
I'm not it's just storage. I think make gunu the fat one. Why it was blue before fine. We'll do okay gunu. Here you go
All right, gunu now gunu is everybody's favorite character all these like omega lows lol lol. Ha ha ha
It's not like that. It's not even like that funny. It's just like he's just a little bigger
It's not like he's a blobfish now. All right. Oh speaking of oh, we're not generating water anymore. Okay
Well, I think i'm ready to move. Yeah, I think so unless this is a hole over here. I think it's time to move
Huge poison chasm over here. So I need to go this way that dude's built like a Hershey kiss
Yeah, I see it. All right. I'm going for it. All right prepare. I need to go there. We ready
All right, everyone's had food. Everyone's had water. Oh, this one's moving a little faster. Nothing here. Good. All right
Oh catch your breath. Oh, fuck. It's actually kind of close go hurry up. Oh, is it all right get in get in get in all of you
Oh, thank goodness. Okay
Jesus
One two, three, four five
What happened?
What happened? What happened? What happened? Why did that happen? Why is still going cylinder roared with fury?
The voice of their memories spoke with great urgency
The trebum had to be very careful now
Oh god, um would lash out of the land, but it would not let them run too far
To survive they would have to stay in the eye of the storm, huh?
Where is that?
Stay in the what does that mean? What's that? I don't know. I I don't understand what that's supposed to mean
Stay close
The torso is producing electrical barrier that you cannot pass out running lightning strikes. It's not possible
What do we do?
You can't get far ahead of it. Wait, what?
And we need to eat something
Do I have to stay close?
You have to be between the lightning and the cylinder
Oh my goodness
All right. Eat quick quick quick eat eat eat eat go go go
Not that close
This is so much
God
All right. It's all right. Any more food
Who is that thing? What is that? Let's find out
plenty of water
Everything's okay
Uh
What is this? Can I do anything with this?
I don't think so. I'm just checking
This is so scary. They're not gonna eat us right? Not right now. That would be really really annoying
Sacrifice gunu and run to the cylinder
I wonder if this counts
Is this gonna shatter?
What do we just eat?
Lightning is lightning is striking me
Gunu must survive
Oh
Back up back up back. Don't go too far
I want one of these flowers so bad
As frightening and surprising as this enormous creature was that trebum felt a sense of relief to see it descend
From the sky what the holy shit a celestial being that'd been told to seek
Perhaps it held an answer to their troubles. Oh poison
Okay, I should give everybody one of these then. Yeah, let's all take these here
Everybody grab one. Oh shit. I'm sorry. I'm trying to give you this
I have to imagine everybody should have it
Hopefully it doesn't uh overwrite what gunu has already so there how many people still need it. We have one two three
I ain't fucking around anymore
Elf
As they approached the colossal creature
Their optimism faded why it did not seem to like them at all
What and now they realized what terrible danger they were in
If this creature guarded the way to some holy place, then that place must lie below it
And being so large
The creature most likely could not see what was in front of it. It just killed that motherfucker
All right. Hold on. We need so perhaps the size of the trebum was an advantage after all
Perhaps okay, they could reach the platform right under the serpent's head
Okay, okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, stop, stop, stop
The trouhalla has an electric attack that strikes if you remain in its line of sight for too long. It had to be in cover
All right. Everybody has to have the poison on
It's just the way it works
Come here gunu get out of line of sight who's in line of sight right now. Stop
Get over here. We need food. I'm not going over there to have food everybody have um poison gas mask on
Uh, you don't
Grutemu, okay grutemu. There is an egg
All right. We don't want that to happen to us. That was awful. So don't all right
uh
Shit
There's an egg over here, but I don't
Rotem need more leadership
Fuck okay
Move move move move move move out of the way out of the way out of the way out of the way
Let it get zapped. Okay, good
um
Gunu, I want you to take point here. Everybody has to follow gunu. We need food. We need to eat. All right, follow me
What happened?
Fuck. Okay. Hold on. This is something. What is this? Who wants it?
one two three four
Five
All right, you eat this
We gotta figure we need to eat we figure out this is electricity. Um, something about like, I don't know eat it legless
um
Well, this one dies
No
It's okay. It's all right. We will always remember you we will always
Remember all the jokes you told us. We'll always remember you. Um
it's been real
you're super nice and we all love you and
Make it one two. Where are they? Where are they?
One two, three, four five. Wait, they grew back
No, we're all here. Wait, it was you. Is it maybe it's a temporary thing. What are you doing?
Ah
Why is it targeting him?
All right. Everybody relax. I need to have a game. Why is it targeting him? We need to eat now
All right, you go get it. You're the one that's being targeted for no reason
You gotta collect the food
Gunu go for it
Okay, oh
We need water now. Where the hell are we gonna get water? Everybody can let's all right
We gotta go we have to go for it hide in the poison. I believe we can't get whoever's in that egg
It's just not possible. It's not gonna happen
um
Let's go down
Everybody should be safe down here. Okay, we need water bad
Can we go in this you can't find other trouble return to the platform from time to time other wandering friends
Might have reached it on their own
What does that mean what's the egg relieved at having bested the guardian?
I have a full party trebum now found themselves seeking the help they had been promised
Who would answer their questions in this place?
You ate the egg
Well, yeah, I mean it's I I I have a full party though. I have six um trebums one two, three four five
So yeah, I can't get any more even if even if I got that egg and hatched it. I couldn't
You're not gonna die from that right? Okay. What is that? What just happened?
Uh, i'm going down the magic crystals
interesting
Interesting what does this do?
You try it light. Oh you turn them into a torch
Okay, that's funny. I think we should only have one person do that
I don't think we should have more than one starlight. We're pretty good on food. I love this area. It's very uh,
What does it remind me of? It's like fraggle rock. This was what was this one again?
Oh, don't die. Yeah, don't take this. This is the you just like lose. This is like you don't have legs
All right. Yeah, I don't want that. Everybody got full water. Look at this one. We need more spots
All right, who's gonna get drowned? Save him. I can't I have a full party. What do you mean? What the fuck?
What the fuck what you need to put them in storage? All right, we are going to put the the
Lamp we're gonna put the lamp
Into storage because we're not gonna need the lamp anymore
Brutemu the lamp and anytime we need a light we will pull Brutemu out of storage
That's definitely what you're supposed to be doing. Wait, there's a lamp. We need to you. Okay, you gotta be the front anything else
Oh
Look up there. Can I make the jump when you have legs? You have legs you ate that weird shit just up here too
Do you have to have the specific? Oh, this is huge. Actually. Gunu is useless. Gunu is a backpack
They're definitely not useless. All right, what's in here? That looks whatever it is. It looks delicious. Oh, no
There you are over here, please. I got a few things for you to store
This I think is a full heel you can just open the inventory. That's true
So this is a full heel full water full food. What is this? Should Gunu eat the light?
I wonder will it is it will it take over his bigness or will it just be a will he just glow in the dark?
I feel like this one should be the lamp the biggest character
Okay, I actually like i'm not that happy about this because Gunu now is gonna look like this until he doesn't
Well, we got what we wanted and let's go even with the light the maze was difficult to traverse
Was there some clue in the structures on the walls?
I think was the part of sand on the ground meant to help them perhaps others had walked in this place long ago
And tried to leave a path for those who would one day follow them
This is an arrow, right? I mean these are arrows. They put arrows. They're very smart something here
I want more people to be able to jump. Let's get out of here. How we doing on food good
Yeah, how do we get out of here? This is where we came in
So why did it was like oh traverse make sure you know the correct way all the large arrows on the way
Didn't I do that? Oh, I didn't how did I follow them the wrong way something I can do. Yeah, follow the large arrows
This is a snail. What significance do the snails have? These are big chunky rocks. I break them. I can't all right
So that's interesting. What's with the slug? We don't have a cube
Unfortunately, maybe we'll get a cube in a minute here you get out of here. This is our territory somebody kill them
Well definitely wants us to have a jump power. I have a couple people that already have it
Uh, I guess i'll give it to more of you probably have it dude. It's so dark
Where is it? Oh, it's over here. I eat this get some legs. Can I give the legs to gunu?
I feel like it's gonna override. It's probably gonna override the um
Bigness I think it's legs not body
Save and try it. Well, it's worth a shot. Let's see if it is just like legs
Maybe it doesn't replace anything
That's not what I want. No, stop. Let me do this. Okay, so it is it's legs body
Skin and nose. I think of the different ones. Okay, cool. None of these
What was this one? I forget what this one does zero for me to see amber. Oh, it's the third eye
Give it to gunu. Do you want gunu just to be completely stacked?
Okay, if gunu dies, it's a problem like actually a problem. I think that's good
He just gets uglier and uglier. Hey, don't say that how dare you fill up on water
Yeah, so the reason why why cube didn't work is it's changed his body
So we gotta keep that in mind. I'm going to forget every single one of these. So please help
I think we should have a swimmer you swim. There we go crystals. I got a lot of these
I need to spend them. Should everybody just glow in the dark temporarily. They're not dying. Are they wait?
What's going on? Are they okay? I need light. I think it's all right. I'm gonna make a couple more people
They can't jump that eventually I can teleport them. I just can't see there we go. Everybody should be there
They are okay crystals. All right that way. Well, hold on. What's this? Oh, it's cube. It's a cube
All right, who should be a cube you boo. You're the cube now gunu can't be a cube. Okay. All right somebody else's
Uh, you're the biggest one. So just go now. That is not an attractive cube. It's just a cube
It was a place where somebody could go. I wonder if i'm gonna wrap around now. Yeah, okay
They're cool. Oh, it's a place where you could go
Where was it? Yes. All right cube get in there. Whoa
Okay
a moa
Ball now what encountering another elder was a happy moment the trebum asked how they might survive the cylinder and the elder replied
I can feel your fear little one ever since this cataclysm began
We have been seeking ways to stop it, but the cylinder is relentless and indestructible
It will consume everything in its path
So perhaps what we need to do is go behind it
I have discovered a mutation that allows us to rise into the sky
You must seek a weeping tree from which grows a special fruit that floats as it becomes ripe
It is the key to the transformation I have undergone with it
You can use geysers to float well above the cylinder's height
My only regret is that I have grown too old and weak to help you with this task
If you find any glimmer of hope on the other side, remember me
farewell
All right, so there's a I have to eat a special food. Now. The question is is it on the map? No, it's a special tree
Get us to float can we use this thing? Wait, somebody's dead who died?
Somebody's dead
This is hurting us
No, guna's not dead. He didn't just die somewhere. No way. Where's everybody?
Show gunu on cam. Hold on. All right. Yeah, what the fuck is everybody this guna?
Um, what are we doing? I can't float through that
But I found this tree. Well, where's it? We can't go up that way
As we just go out this way
Sadness and fear filled the trebum's hearts as they left the elder's cave
Stand by their only path to salvation was full of uncertainty
I know I could go out the door. I just didn't know what someone wanted to get here
They had seen lurking behind the cylinder casting a dark shadow over this glimpse of light
Okay, so just a big log rolling
Interesting the trebum had never seen this mysterious tree the elder spoke of
They would have to keep moving forward and hope it lay somewhere ahead
The cylinder would give them no other choice
all right, let's get
and the
Big dragon is gone. So that's a plus
Everyone just coming to the stream right now. What would it mean big dragon? What the fuck? What are you? Yeah, man
Should have saw it and I actually might sound like i'm being sarcastic, but it actually was really cool
Okay, there's some what is this it's pointing over here. So there's that way
It's pointing over here though. Still good on food. Maybe somebody should be
tanky
Yeah
you
Wait, oh wait, I forgot. That's not the right one
Well, it's okay
You just make water
Is this food?
I wonder can I eat anything up this?
No
So correct me if i'm wrong
and
This I think this is accurate
This is made by the same team that did xeno clash. Do you remember xeno clash?
Do you remember that game?
That game was wild
They're actually making another xeno clash game. Aren't they coming out soon? I think
but same team
it
I mean that would
I mean all the character designs it looks very much like xeno clash
Whoever is there whoever is doing the character designs and the concept work for uh ace team where the xeno clash team
It's it's like next level. They're they're they're unbelievably good
Um, all right, i'm gonna go touch that wait didn't I already see this? Am I crazy?
The new xeno game looks actually really cool
Yeah, it's like a dice game
But then it turns into sort of like a third person action game after you play a game of dice or something
I'll probably play it. It looks really interesting
Did I touch this already?
Oh, yes, we're gonna store people right right right right
All right
We are gonna store
one of our
Yeah, we need to we're gonna store a lamp
Who do we want? Yeah, we're gonna store
Store gru temu
Makes sense. All right gru temu you're getting stored in case we need a lamp who knew it stays
Gua stays boo stays wog will stays. There he goes. Okay, so we have
It was kind of everyone kind of has a purpose at this point
One two, three or five. Okay, that wasn't the lamp. Yeah, it was who knew is the most important
But yeah, the most important one has to stick around two. We need two lamps in there. Ah
Get out. Well, that's you should be safe. You shouldn't be able to get over here
Get out of here. We're okay. We're in trouble something else is moving over here now. Oh my goodness
All right. No, no, go go go just get out get out get out get out
We stored one. We gotta go. We gotta go. We gotta go right now. I'm going now plenty of health
Find this tree
Oh
Shit. Oh shit. Oh shit
big problem
Somebody can swim can't they who can swim?
Who can swim one of you swims who swims? Who's the swimmer?
Who swims?
Somebody swims, right?
Nobody swims
Nobody swims. I stored the swimmer. We're dead
I stored the swimmer
Okay, well done. Was he there? I don't think so
Oh fuck off
We told you to store the lamp
Okay, you're going in there and i'm bringing out the swimmer. What's your name?
Woog wool. All right, woog wool go in there and we'll pull the swimmer out. The thing is gonna kill all of us
Okay, woog wool going in
Grutemu coming out. Where's the swimmer? One, two, three. Wait
Wrong. I don't hold on a second. Who has the swimming ability?
It's kind of it's hard to tell
Does woog wool have swimming? I wish I could see their traits right here. None have the swimming. You lost it
How did I lose it? Didn't somebody just get it? Somebody had webbed feet, right? It is woog wool. Okay
All right. So then grutemu goes in as grutemu is just
Literally just glowing and jump. Okay, put grutemu in
Yeah, we did. We had it right the first time. Yeah, I just freaked out because I didn't realize that you had the webbed feet
All right. Let's go. All right, woog wool. Where are you? You know, you know, you know what threw me off
It was the fact that um
Woog wool is glowing
Okay, I need to take a look at the map
Oh fuck
We okay everyone. Okay. All right. I need to look at the map
I think I can just swim across this
with woog wool
I think woog wool can make it
Oh
Get away
Okay, it's moving. All right. Well, you need to eat and then you swim in over there
Come on use your trait
Yes
I think it's gonna work. Don't even look back
Okay, so we're gonna go the long way
There's not there's not enough stamina
I need to upgrade my stamina to try something like that again
So I gotta go around the water. Okay, this game is cool. I like this game. It's fun
well
Who you're gonna spawn me right here?
Don't luigi me. I'm still learning do not luigi me, please. I'm not gonna hear that right now
But hold on will you get out of here?
Seriously get out of here
We just gotta move. Oh my god, just go
Where's the okay, where's the water water? I just gotta go straight wrap around I need food
just go
Pick the worst possible way to go man
No, I don't think I can do it. I don't think I can do it
I'm not I don't think i'm gonna make it. I don't think I have enough stamina to make it the whole way
Maybe I do
Uh
Yes, okay I got it we're good everything's fine already relaxed now we need to eat
They were still nowhere near the mysterious tree that we're supposed to find
But the voice and their memories encouraged them
It was wise and matters of root and rock and it could sense the soil under their feet
Changing oh no step by step
They were getting closer the thing looks dangerous
You got food reserves, don't you?
You ate it
You ate it. Why did you eat it? We weren't I didn't want you to eat that
I mean, I it was a good thing, but that's for emergencies. Don't eat that. Okay, let's keep going couple points of interest over here
But wait
Oh
No, do that again. It doesn't work. All right. I think he's he does it eventually we just have to get back and
Once he's not okay, the snow gets out for a certain reason. I don't know why
So should we give the uh attractive power up to gunu or keep the glow keep it low
I wonder how it works cool. I kind of miss the uh, the lighting it gives though. All right, so
Over here. I wonder why you would need to be
Uh attractive right? I wonder if there's something that ends up happening later or something. I don't know what it would be point of interest
Oh who's in here? I need I need somebody that can fight who's in here
Go vu you need a mushroom and you need four mushrooms and three crystals. What's up?
Go vu we got go vu. Ooh, I like go vu orange
It's a bunch of weirdos. All right, we gotta go
Uh back to that point of interest. Okay, it's like a temple
Get in get
Uh
No, so he died what who died
Who died somebody got spit on and died. Who was it?
guru
Where's guru?
Which one was guru?
Can we just no do not the one we just got?
Oh, okay. You're fine. It was guru guru is gone. I don't even remember who the fuck that was if i'm honest
so
Who was guru?
All right. I need to make a decision here was guru the purple
Max hell hold on
He doesn't even care. No, I just don't remember
Okay, I remember
the guru
shining cube is vu right? You're the cube
glow, uh, I remember the glow one is wu wu with the webbed feet
the new one
go vu is the orange one and then
Gui is the one with the big head. I don't remember the other one. Sorry that they got um
Like obliterated. I don't even know what to say
All right. We definitely need uh leadership
So this is maximum number of trebum. I definitely want it. I think that lets us have seven. I wonder what else
Probably do it twice
Water storage. This is probably this is important and stamina
I do both
food storage
food storage and stamina or water supply and stamina or
Stamina and another party member. Is this game multiplayer? I don't think so
I think it's just like a little single player campaign
Food and stamina stamina and leadership again
Um, well, I know i'm doing stamina. So where is it? It's over here somewhere, right? What about health?
I mean that one of our best friends got just annihilated in a second. That's expensive
Stamina do I even have enough to do anything? I could do stamina health. I have 7.5. So
Food capacity is probably water and food capacity is important. I think
Or I could just do another one food is important food's important
So I got food stamina
And that's it. You can yeah, I I can you can revive it probably costs money though
I don't know if i'm gonna do that yet. I'm afraid i'm gonna open this door and there's gonna be the things are gonna be here
Yep out out out
Mmm
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Are we safe?
One two, three, four five. It just hit me. I'm gonna cry. We lost we lost
Guogui it's hitting me right now. I'm actually sad. It just hit me right now. So awful
That's not his name
That is the equivalent of like if your son's name was like
David and it's like, oh no you something. No, we lost. What? Wait, wait, where's uh
Dread
Like you don't have your own fucking kid's name
Hey, honey. Do you have any idea where
Is
A new friend you want three mushrooms and three crystals. I don't have enough. There's an egg thing here though
Why are you so poor? I just spent like a million bucks upgrading everybody. There's an egg incubation thing here though
I need to find the egg. Where's the egg? I don't even there's a cave here. There's a cave here
All right. I'm gonna go to the cave
and see
We're just gonna go straight
Okay. Yeah, then right food
Uh, i'll pick up food in a second. There's a there's a cave here though. It's like right here somewhere
Where is it? Right here? Right here? Where is it? Oh, there it is. All right, let's go in
Ooh
Get that can I pick that up? Oh, i'm hungry. I don't have food. Somebody that has food everybody's any food
What the fuck are we doing?
Yeah, just wait get some food. Fuck off. No, fuck off. I can't wait to account
When can I throw like a grenade down that thing's throat? I'm serious
Okay back up
Get the agro
Good. All right head down there. I make anybody else shiny
Ooh, you know who should be shiny you you're gonna look cool shiny, right will it be orange and shiny give it to the cube
We need an attractive cube again. Yeah. Yep. Good call. All right, let's go in the hole. So what's down here friend and
five
Wugwu, I don't have five. Sorry buddy. Come back. Maybe help him, please
I don't think i'm gonna I spent too much money. We got the orange um orange guy. Unfortunately, I think that's where his
Uh final resting place is going to be i'm gonna go up here. There's also a potential egg
Somewhere hang out for a minute and see if we can find it
Making us cry. Well, there's nothing I can do about it
We chose. Um
Wugwu
This is who we picked. We picked a Wugwu
Wugwu is pretty cool
Wugwu already has jump. What about over here? Egg for an egg. Whoa, I forgot what that thing was. That was my bad
All right, I think we just got I think we just have to go does anybody have toxic, uh defense we could go down
all right, we everybody get toxic defense, uh, everybody has it right does the
Cube have it. Yes. All right. Let's go down. Are we something down there?
Right on the edge here though. I'm not gonna activate it. Am I?
Hope not. It's down here. Nothing. No, right
Gotta be something here
What what there's really nothing down here junk i'm not missing something right
No, maybe it's a place to hide maybe from one of those monsters
All right. I gotta pick the way that I want to run here. I think it's gonna be
All right. So i'm gonna come across this brush over here on the left. I'm just gonna go
Wham straight up here. It's an egg by the hole
Give it one more look if we got that. Let's see one egg by hole egg by hole
Let's see it
Where?
We need water. Yeah, i'll get water
Oh
We get out
You almost got sprayed
Oh my god, he's so fast
We gotta move. We gotta move. We gotta move. This thing is just we gotta move
I'm moving who has fins which one of you has gills you do all right as long as one of you has
gills or whatever the hell it is
That works for me. The swimmer is dead
Wait, the swimmer is the one that died. All right. Well, i'll give it to um
to
Get out of here for it. Oh, oh no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no everybody dies here
Everybody dies here
No, don't poison them all please everybody get out, please everybody get out get out get out get out get out get out
We good. Oh, thank god. I'm so happy
He's so tired. Okay
We're safe
very nice
Uh, do we need any bigger people? I don't think so. All right, i'm eating up and we're getting out of here
Oh, I thought you guys said I killed the swimmer. You have another swimmer. Oh, I thought that woodway died and woodway was the swimmer
Well, okay. All right. I gotta move. This is a horrible route. I need to go
This way and up or fuck it. Whatever. I'll make it work. I think it's okay
Come on move. Oh, we gotta go now
Don't get caught by that thing. I don't know what that thing's doing
This thing's trying to I think it's trying to suck somebody up
We're all here. Okay, gotta get to here
Go, this is a risky move very risky
Incredibly risky, but I think it's gonna work out
Shaving some time
Okay, i'm gonna calm down I gotta calm down
Come on, you're good. Everything's fine
Oh my god, it's right there
I made a mistake
Shit it moves so fast. It moves really fast
Okay, autosave is right there. We're okay. Good thing you got the crystals. I know it was stupid
But there's so many crystals in there. All right, let's go
Who's the fastest probably this game has me so invested. Yeah, kind of
It's just I don't know. It's cool. All right. I'm thinking straight ahead
From here just go get out of the way go straight
And then I gotta go right
When it drops I gotta go right left. What is that thing? Is that a bad thing?
Wait, what is that?
What what is that?
Oh, it's one of those flying things. I got you
Come on go and then it's over here
Right ahead blue smoke will refill your stamina. That's unbelievable to know. Thank you
Okay, we're safe. Very nice
Oh pretty
Does anybody still have a horn? Can you please explain this game? I am very confused. This game is called the internal cylinder
Game gives you an area to work with you find little creatures that you have join your party
there's a bunch of upgrades the internal cylinder the the eternal cylinder and
once you leave the fortnight circle the game
Crushes and destroys everything that was before and you can only move forward pretty cool
I got my little party here seem to be doing pretty seem to be doing. Okay, one of them died
Uh got obliterated by poison
What was this monstrous creature?
Was this one of the cylinder servants? He's the ones the elder had warned them of
It's very form
terrified the trevor
Even the voice on their memories seemed frightened of it. And then somehow
The trebum remembered the creature's name
Mathematician
The mathematician
Well, I say we don't go over there
We need water how we don't know
We need to eat very badly
What else has food give it to guna?
Okay, just get rid of these things
Dad get rid of those. There's no reason for you to keep carrying these
I'm gonna be pissed if I need these for some reason
You can't become double q but just food, right?
Yeah
Now we don't need these. Um, oh my god
crawling back over the cylinder
The mathematician is horrifying as quickly as he had appeared back to
To what?
What lay behind the cylinder? We need to know
I'm very i'm completely invested
All right, what's on the map?
Nothing, no points of interest anymore. I'm gonna explore over here a little
there is
No temple
That's really pretty this game's beautiful
I wonder what those things do they're kind of scaring me. So i'm not gonna go near them
Something over there now wheels
I think the guy is rolling the cylinder like a joint to smoke with germa with the people happy
so
I don't even know
I love that people happy face. I love people people is just so funny
egg
egg acquired
Somebody's dying here and I don't know who but someone's gonna die
Right. This looks very difficult. Whatever that wants me to do
I need an incubator
Get that shit out of here incubator
incubator
one of those cars
This shit down there, but I don't want anyone to get just rushed so it's safe right there
I would not don't jump down. Don't jump down. That's a very bad idea
Don't jump down. You're gonna get yourself crushed. Oh, please come back this way. Don't be silly
Um, I don't see an incubator
I don't want to go too far
Is there one over there?
This piece of shit's gonna
Drain all of our powers. I'm just taking it with us everyone. Be careful
I'm gonna be very careful
I'm kind of i'm at the edge of the map here. I gotta go okay left
I gotta go that way behind you don't say that. I think there's new shit down there. What is that? I need to see
What was this strange groove in the ground? It seemed artificial like something made to contain water
But all it contained were these large rolling machines
Who had built these things and why?
They were not servants of the cylinder that much was clear
Um, we have to do this. No, I can't sprint with the egg perfect placement. Don't tell me that wasn't perfect placement
We made it we made it slow slow down slow down if we can get out this way
Can I just get up that? Oh, come on. I have the super jump
Yes
We all here. Where's where?
Where where's where where's where oh, no everybody's here this five
Wait, i'm losing track of my children. Where no, we're all here. Okay, we're here incubator over there and there is a
Um, I think it's a baby in one of those should get two here. Aha, and then there's somebody in there
Wave warm. All right wave warm. Welcome to the family and
Vopo
Wants three turnips and three crystals. Okay. Well we get I already gave the crystals
So we need the turnips. They're all over here. Here you go. Who ate one. There were two here
Who ate the other one? Why did you eat it?
Why did you eat the turnip one of you ate one? Wait, did you eat it or you have it in your inventory?
Who who has it they ate it? I need another I need another turnip. There's gotta be one more here somewhere, right?
Bro, you had to eat the one other turnip that we needed
You couldn't have eaten anything else a flower a mushroom. You had to eat the turnip. Where is it?
How can I tell how this is where this is working?
Will it hang or beep or is it on a map?
Try it on. Yeah, i'll try it on like this plant and see what it does. It's a regular one
Yeah, like this. Those are like everywhere. Okay, so
That's what it does. This is not you tell me there's not one even in remotely in this vicinity
God damn it. Yes
Well, I need to remember the way this is in the maps right here your children inherited your lack of self-control
We needed i'm not going anywhere. That was three full crystals. I'm not wasting that
I'm not leaving till we find another turnip. There better be another one on this world
There's no turnips in this whole land anymore. Not anywhere. Shit. Well, let's get water
Dude, your kids have the hiccups. They're suffering. They're okay
One turnip better not be the death of this
Thing here hasn't even picked up anything
Just reload the save. I don't know how far back out how far back would that be?
19 seconds ago or 14 minutes ago. I don't know 15 minutes
That seems kind of far
I don't know what that means, but it's I don't like it
I need one turnip
Just one just need one
They respawn. I think they'd be coming up on the radar if they did right?
I think
There are no turnips. I looked everywhere
No
Check back. Yeah, let's go back to where it was that was
Over here. I do need to eat though. Hold on honey. Whatever. These things are coral reef doesn't help me
I thought you were a plant. Okay, let's make our way back
That's an interesting thing going on over there in the distance. I don't know if that is all right. It's over here
There ain't any there's no fucking turnips. They they wait. Wait a minute. These are the trees. These are the trees
I need to eat these these are the flying trees. I'm very excited right now
Finally the weeping oh shit the elder had told them to find were within the trebum's grasp
But though the trebum were happy they realized that they faced a new challenge
The ripe fruit were floating out of reach and the others were enclosed in a hard shell
They would have to find a way to crack them open. Uh like that, right? This is
Somebody we need to experiment on somebody
You the one that looks like a goldfish you do it good luck godspeed his power is stupid
Okay, so they can float should everybody have this I wonder because this is probably body, right?
What does this count as something else?
I wonder will they all just fly i'm gonna yeah, i'll take a few because I want to make sure I have a few
just for later
Test it on the cube. That's a good call. All right, what happens if you eat this?
Why did that not break? Okay, so it is it does count as
Body who doesn't have one body thing disco ball. I think it's okay as long as one of them has it, right?
I think that that's fine. It's yeah. It's a it's an attractive balloon now. Yeah, we're good. Okay, can't roll anymore. Yeah again
Uh, all right turnips turnips very important. I need one
Maybe water the turnip plant. I'll try it
I want to investigate this to whatever this is. I wonder if I can get up up. That's nothing up there
Are they in danger? I'm get out of the way. You know, why don't you take a horn?
Yeah, um give it to you. We won't maybe that it can scare him away. Okay, let's try this
Let's work get out of here. Get out of here. Keep going further
Don't don't eat somebody everybody. Follow me up here. Follow me up here. Is everybody all right? What's in there is some magical shit up here
What is that? There's magical shit up here. Um, we should eat this you
Get it. Can I eat it? Can I give it to the disco ball? Give it to gweg. Whom?
I don't know how that is. Should I give it to whewom? Give it to wugwol. Uh, wugwol is not up here
Where okay? Where is everybody? I got what I needed from here. What the second player here anything here, holy shit
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Wait, wugwol no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
All right, I'm freaking out for no reason. We're safe. We're all here, right? Thank God
I actually
That was as if one of my children was actually in danger. Uh, i'm gonna give it to
As wet wet wet wombs not even here
I'm gonna give it a wee wham. I think wee wham should have it. Okay, who's got it on them?
Wee wham. Yeah. All right. We won't try it meteor feet
I can do a ground pound those legs should have given it to gunu. I didn't know what it was though
I wonder if I can stomp on this thing now. This is a really bad testing of hypothesis here
But I mean thought I had the horn, but I don't have who is the horn. We're good. Okay. Is there any turnips over here?
What do you need?
God damn it. No fucking turnips or anything either
Oh, I can change that's what was going on. Okay. Well got some new abilities found the tree
Now let's go back to the turn turnip is down here and then i'm imagining I probably have to float over
Let me just see if the turnips respond is that a chest
Where is that?
What do you mean?
the chest
Maybe just an inactive roller
That's cool. All right. There's the ball with the turnip. Don't think I can get it
Uh try anything on the pillar. Yeah, that's what is that? That's the what power is this?
Don't stomp your friends, please
That's the third idea good to have
I'm just storing it. Maybe somebody else just have it
Uh, i'm gonna give it to the stop
Look i'm turnips. We got a raid. Oh, we did have a raid
Automated what's up auto? Thanks for the raid auto be having a good night
Out of water. Yeah, i'm heading over there now
Turnip there were three turnips here one two
Three and you ate one of them you did you ate one and now we cannot save our
Friend and we have to abandon the friend now. We wasted three crystals
I'm glad you ate it
I'm glad it was delicious
But you wasted three crystals. That's a huge amount of currency. This one looks a little more green to you
Can I take I can't take the crystal back?
Water for more than half a second
I mean, we're all just sitting here watering it
No, it's not gonna work
That's sad. Um unfortunate
unfortunate
I got my
thing that finds
Ernie it's uh, I think that's it
I think we lost three crystals
All right
shit
That's so sad
Okay
Well, we're leaving
Save him. I can't
Unless I reload a save from like 40 minutes ago. It's all right. I'll get the crystals back
So the play here
Is that to float over this to get to here?
Where's the cylinder?
Uh cylinder is all the way back there
I should be in a fine spot float over
Let's see. So if I go I wonder oh, no, no, there's a closer one. Here it is
I'll take a few more of these i'm just gonna keep them. I'll store them on somebody
Who knows in the hell i'm gonna get access to this again
Save yeah, I think it just saved right now. It is saving. Okay
Uh, where's my float friend? There you are
Okay, here we go
What's that even with the ability to float?
Overcoming the cylinder would have to be done very carefully what they needed was a geyser that was well positioned
Close to the cylinder when it lays still
Or their plan would never work
They would have to keep looking
And meanwhile they would try not to think about what sort of monster could kill one of the flying serpents
Oh, okay
Okay in order to float above the eternal cylinder you must find a geyser that is close to the cylinder when it lies dormant
The eternal cylinder will never allow the trepum to jump over it while it is advancing
I mean, I guess I gotta I gotta just kind of I gotta go
Everyone's making it. We're good. Okay. Here comes the border border here. All right float. Holy shit
uh
Really bad timing really bad timing go
We're good, bro
Why?
No
Um
No, um
No, the whole family made it barely
Old you just you just ate the why'd you do that? That was mean you got you're on kind of a mean streak right now
Okay, is there a geyser here? I would imagine not probably later. What the fuck is that? That's terrifying. It's sniffing. Okay
Okay, it's out of here
Please come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Just I don't know what to I don't know where to go
I don't know where to go
um
We need coats we need coats
Look at the chat. Wait, wait, wait, wait. What the geyser geyser geyser it was where I was being I see it right there
I was getting chased by this weird bird elephant thing our home
Our world. Oh, that's ominous
Drop down. What if I just run across?
Cover their eyes
I don't know if this is a good idea the other side
this thing
That's new
Is it new? No, it's
not oh
my
God
We'll get back up when we go back up, please
We just we're just gonna get out of here. We're just gonna get out of here here
What just happened?
We all here holy shit in the dream inside the strange giant's mind
The voice that spoke to the trebum seemed different
It was less like a memory more like something
alive
But there were so many other voices too. The gang goes up against the god. This is very bright
What the fuck that just made me sick
I remember the faces. Wait, where do I go?
Oh, no
We lost a couple people
I don't I think I think they're fine though. There was something hidden in this place
And the voice wanted the trebum to find it
dmt breakthrough
I took dmt. I remember a city built. I was a little fucking weird frog person
When I was fucked up, I was eating things that gave me different powers
Running for this giant cylinder. This really does feel like an acid trip somebody explaining to you their acid trip
beauty each voice
Was a memory a song from a forgotten time slowly fading
Hold on. I don't want to make any
Memories of things that trebum had once been capable of perhaps the voice suggested
These could be reclaimed
I remember our towers stretched out to the sky
Yearning for the stars
They were symbols of our best. I am tripping right now. I'm
It's kind of late
As we fought for change
For a world that was
different
Then it came
And the towers fell
Somebody said cool math games
Where our voices now songs
I only hear one and it is
eternal
So, what are we are we?
I'm very curious
I guess we're just walking has the memories returned to the trebum old abilities
Stolen by the cylinder were finally restored
But there was so much more
The voice had answers
but
It was
Frightening as it was the trebum would have to come back sacrifice gunu
I'm getting contact high from this game
Loud okay, wait, he's rolling this place of death and nothingness
There were no answers to be found here
The voice and their memories urge them to return to the lands of the living
He's the one rolling it. It's not just like a sentient thing. It's he's
Is he's wrote wait, there's like stuff here
Yeah
Crunchies
What this thing was a we saw this before this weird skeleton
That's not a time to celebrate by the way, just saying that's interesting. So I
This is freaky. Okay
This is the movie trailer for the gritty reboot of cuber
well, I guess we're going back but
Like that
Yeah this time this time he's uncensored
I don't look so good
Thank you
What is that thing?
Um
Oh, no, how do I save him?
No, govu
Govu's dead
Was dead. He's the one that can float
Excuse me
Come on. Come on. We gotta go. We gotta go
Wait float, please
A profound feeling of futility overcame the trebuch
Govu's dead
What the fuck is all this shit? I'm sorry, but this was not over here
to make matters worse
Ahead of them lay the cold and snowy lands
The tundra
What a very nice place for trebum who are not meant to get out of the way get out of the way we need the okay
Okay, narrator. This is not a please. Stop talking to me that they could find help
We need to get warm right now
I can't believe
Okay, eat eat eat eat eat eat
Uh, we're good. If the trebum were going to deal with this terrible cold
They needed to find a mutation that would keep them warm
God damn their memories
That the answer lay in the odd little purple furball
That grew where the beautiful snow corals rose from the ground. That thing is coming back and I don't know how to deal with it
It's just taken
It's taken my govu's and whatever these things are
Where do I need to go from here? There is no map
um
Okay, i'm just going this way
Scare it with a horn come here fuck out of here get out of here
That's for govu
Do water? Yeah, take it. I this I have the stomp ability too with this
Oh, what is this? Uh, I don't want to lose the stomp. I don't want to who should I give this to?
This game is 13 hours long
That's pretty that's cool. I'm gonna give it to you
Because I feel like you got the webbed feet, but what else you got?
The yellow guy
Actually yellow guy doesn't have anything
very true
Ignites a small flame at the tip. I got a fire blow blower. Okay, do you don't get burnt to death, please?
What is that thing? I don't this thing's interesting. I don't know what it does, but I have it now
big like burning rock
Okay, i'm gonna throw this at somebody
What's that? Is it the same thing?
It's like a jewel
Ah
All right
Kind of like a lantern maybe oh my fucking god. I need to eat. You're right. I completely forgot it existed
Did I cook the food what happens if I cook the food do anything different I don't think so
Get the heat source back. Yeah, I will
Want to eat a bunch of food?
You need to avenge govu
I don't know if I can do that
Okay, we're good
Uh, i'm gonna get that heat source back
I'm just taking it with us
We'll light the bird on fire
This game is 69 hours long
Go roast that motherfucker. No, it's okay
I am gonna check down here though
Please do anything
No, are you afraid of the bird? I mean maybe a little
He instantly killed my one of my friends. Of course i'm gonna be a little apprehensive
All right. I don't want to leave yet. There's nothing really down here
All right, I got a question for you. We can do a poll. Do you want to see me complete this game?
Yes, or no if the answer is yes, this is what we will play
That's a lot of yeses. All right, we don't even do a poll. It's not necessary. I wonder what this thing is for though
All right, uh gunu you need to get food a lot of it gunu should be the one doing this
Give all the food to gunu
92% damn, okay
One of those motherfuckers over there. All right, that's plenty
Never gonna play sorcery ever again
Yes, I will I promise look at this little guy
Um, that's all right. What's this?
Who should eat who's gonna eat this?
uh
Wugwool you think so?
All right. Wugwool you eat this thing
Probably a spiky head
What are you doing? They're just rubbing their butts. What were they doing? Okay
All right kind of mutate
Analytical eyes can tag creatures and add them to your compendium there. You can find important information about their behavior
With this new pair of eyes
Well
To be perfectly honest, they felt rather silly
but despite that
The voice and their minds told them with these eyes they could learn much about the creatures they encountered
Okay, the voice was glad about this
It was knowledgeable in the manner of animals
And now it could contribute its wisdom to their memories so I can tag monsters
Try to avoid them or something probably
What's the big shadow?
What's the big shadow? What's that?
This game is so scary
Okay
um
I still can't see but
I know it's up there
Plenty of food. I got the cold resist
I pat I wonder what I give it
What happened to that egg that I had?
That is completely scared of it. How are you just activated has a quest
It does
Look at that. It makes me hungry
I could I should probably eat too
I'm probably not gonna stream that much longer
um
You probably imagine some of these later night. Just hang out streams will be
not like
Eight hours long
Okay, hold on. I'll finish it though. I will
pink and green
Cool. I'll do this tower. Uh, this whatever this little um zone thing under here. Wait, where's my horn blower?
Where's my horn blower? Hey, fuck you
You see anything yell really doesn't like the horn at all. Oh
I think I think they're okay. They just got smashed in the face
Look, they hurt a little but it's okay
oh
Get that thing out here. I don't want that thing swooping down. Everybody. All right. Where's guna? What is right here? What's that?
Oh shit. Oh, it's just water. I think this is an upgrade place, but I don't have that much
Should I even go in here because it's gonna when I get out it's gonna um walk it behind me
Commit to it. Yeah, you should save it. I don't I feel like I kind of have to just get out of here
Yeah, it should give me a couple. I don't know if it's enough though activate save up for the guy you just saw
Yeah
I gotta go into more caves underground more feel like i'm lacking
Well, I did upgrade a lot last time or I wonder if it'd be about five. Maybe i'll get from this
What am I lacking? I feel like the water is not a problem
Um maximum water at six. I don't think I have enough to do anything. I don't think I can do anything
I could do health health is for stamina health is okay
I could do health or save it to be able to get somebody save it save it save it save it
There is a new party member outside. Yeah, i'll save it. We want friends. We don't need upgrades. No health. No health
I think we've got plenty of health. Although I say that when we've seen a couple of
Tragedies that happened very quickly so I can understand that maybe we don't have enough health, but i'll save it
Who govu got his neck snapped it was really sad. I felt so bad about it. All right, so here's the plan
Um before it gets too too late. We'll call it here. I'm gonna
Upgrade well not upgrade. I'm gonna where was that person?
No
How do I get out get out?
shit
No, no, it doesn't it didn't happen. It didn't happen. It didn't happen. Uh, I didn't happen the save is yeah
It never happened. Sorry. I'm not letting that happen that never happened. That's it. See you later stream over didn't happen
It did not happen. We're good save scum. That's fine, bro. You need to put both earbuds in we heard it
Oh, man. All right
Uh next time I see you guys we'll probably come back to this on
Um, I don't know friday. We'll probably do friday saturday friday sunday
We'll we'll try to finish this on if it's like a 12 hour game like 11 to 12
We'll go for a little bit longer on friday and then saturday
Uh, there's a couple things I want to do on saturday, but we'll finish it. We'll finish it up on friday
And then uh the weekend we'll do some um, some fun stuff too. So we'll start
Um, I I honestly I really like this nighttime slot kind of brings it back to like 20
16 2017 starting at like six or seven o'clock. It's a it's a nice change of pace. I really like it. You must have commercial brain
Yeah, yeah, I think the the
The later night I think just kind of lets me just kind of breathe a little bit
Relax. I very much like it a lot. We'll go back to sorcery. We'll finish this
We'll we'll do we're gonna do a lot of stuff that you can expect friday saturday this weekend
And yeah, i'm very interested in what this game even is so we're definitely gonna finish it eternal cylinder
Starting at about 6 pm pacific on friday. Do you want to come chill by all means? Please do
And then saturday. I don't know what what we might need to finish this on saturday for an hour or two
And then move on to something else on saturday. We'll probably do saturday afternoon not saturday night, but we'll see
Thanks again for watching. Thanks for chilling
Didn't really have a big kind of long game plan with these but i'm having fun
Breath of the wild will finish. I will finish breath of the wild. I I promise you
That the hold on I was like i've been holding a burp in for the last four straight minutes
Okay, I promise you we're gonna be playing a lot of just games and relaxing so don't worry breath of the wild
I'll finish it. I'll finish sorcery
I'm gonna finish this
And we'll see friday that we're
Well are on our way through this the third episode
You have 100 days to beat breath of the wild because that's when oh, right, right. That's plenty of time
I'll be all right. These are promises your ass can't check
No, they had my ass can cash the whatever it is. No, it isn't
What is it? You are you got to check cash check cash the check, right?
Don't write checks. You can't cash like your ass can't cash it or something
Whatever you that person wrote that and that's what they were trying to say and then I just like filled in the blanks
I'm getting question mark. You can cash them though your ass
Your ass
Dude, can you please do those circus tricks I mentioned
You wait from like four hour four and a half hours ago. No, why am I doing any circus tricks right now?
Get some sleep. All right. Good night. See you guys later. Thanks for sticking around. We'll see you friday friday night
Have a good one drink some water
Call your mother some broccoli. Maybe
You know what to do. See you later. See you friday. Have a good night