Oh sorry. Hi guys. It's fucking early. It's too hot. I can't, I can't drink this coffee.
All right. What time is it? It's time to go, right? I'm good. I thought it was just an Iron Man game.
Sure. Just an Iron Man game. We're here. We're here. I've got to, I've got to be quiet though.
Because everybody, everybody in the fucking house is sleeping right now. So I can't like be loud.
I've got to contain my joy. I can't be loud. Loud joke time? No. This shit is fucking,
I seriously like made this too hot. This is the Nintendo, yeah, this is the official Nintendo
direct robe. I have to look this cool. It's like a fucking baked potato. What the fuck?
Do I care about Nintendo? Yeah, I do. I have a Switch. It's literally in my bedroom. I play it
all the time. Welcome to day three. Do I really? Yeah, I was playing Slay the Spire on it like
16 hours ago, whatever it was, like two nights ago. Two nights ago. Look at this hair back here.
It's disgusting. What time is it in Vegas? It's 9 a.m. Well, almost 9 a.m. Do I play Smash? No,
I don't. I'm not, I'm not good enough. I got my ass kicked way too many times. Actually,
it was like three times online and I decided I'm not doing this ever again. It shut me off
with the game for the rest of my life. I do think it's a great game though. I got juggled around.
It's actually Italics and I played co-op together and we went in. We were like,
we practiced for a little bit. We're like, yeah, let's go. I'm ready to fucking go for it.
We're going to go online. We're going to try to like really win games. We got just so stomped so
badly. Like three or four games in a row. We just were getting juggled around,
thrown. It was just like embarrassing. And we just looked at each other. We were just like,
I think I was the first person to say something. I think it was just like,
hey, I don't like, you good? You look good? He's like, yeah. I'm like, yeah, I'm good.
We just never played it ever again. And he got controllers for it too. He was like completely
prepared for it. He was like, I'm going to get the game cube controllers. And we just,
it just wasn't, it was not good. It was bad. I'm, yeah, I am being too loud, but whatever.
Switch to the Nintendo stream. Is it coming up right now? Just watch it. I mean, it's about,
it's going to transition over right now. Yeah, we're good. I also heard through some,
I don't know how reliable sources. I don't think I'm allowed to stream things that are not on the
official Twitch broadcast. So I think the AMD stream may have been illegal. So don't tell anybody.
All right, here we go. Here comes the Nintendo direct. I'm excited. You're excited. I'm excited
as I can be waking up 15 minutes ago, 20 minutes ago. I thought that was my browser for a second.
I was like, what the hell's happening? Those coordinates, the switch LA three, 10, 20, 20.
Okay. Is that somebody's IP? Is that my IP? No, that's a lot.
Hey, well, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Show me Doug Bowser and Batista. Oh, god damn it. Oh, thank god. I was going to say I had to,
I was about to have to, my brothers. That was me. And who is it? The hero draws near. So does this,
does this confirm this confirms all the leaks he's the only one left wait so it's all of them
it's the whole party that's it does he snooze like snooze it's like it's not like pokemon trainer
is it no that's the final smash dragon quest echoes of an elusive age s definitive edition
so i just i gotta say i know i don't want any obviously spoilers or anything or any leaks in
the chat or anything like that but that i think that confirms all the characters on that list
please do not put them in here monsters to ride monsters monsters good commentary oh wait i'm just
reading the text it's so early my brain can't even do anything well i mean that i'm gonna play it
because hello everyone i'm yoshiaki koizumi from nintendo in this nintendo direct for e3 2019
we'll showcase a variety of games many of them coming soon but before we dig into the next game
there is someone i'd like to introduce first what what are you doing here
oh is that the dog bowser wait wait wait wait there's been a bit of a mix-up
you're not the right bowser sorry but i'm the right bowser for this presentation
they should have just had him talk through bowser that would have been great
if like he's just like that's just what he does not this way this way bye bye
maybe next time are you related no but we get that a lot well let's get back to it please take it
away poor bowser hi everyone i'm doug bowser from nintendo of america and i'm thrilled to join you
for today's nintendo direct this is our chance to show the world we have games for every type
of player on nintendo switch whether you love action rpg's or you're just looking for something
new i'm a pac-man got you covered okay you got something for me doug one of those games
of luigi's mansion three luigi's mansion three oh shit he's invited to a gorgeous hotel
with mario peach and the others oh lucky him he's mansion three this hotel is much more than meets
the eye for not long after luigi arrives things take a dark turn we begin our tour by taking in
some sights and sounds you may never leave you want to leave what was the other they don't plan
to move on they're ghosts after all and they're rather aggressive simply scare them with the
strobe bulb then suck them up luigi's new poltergust g00 has the powerful suction capabilities
required and other new features as well first the slam while trapping a ghost slam it on the ground
to inflict some damage it helps to get other ghosts in on the action next the suction shot
find the plunger to attach it to something then pull the string and you can destroy furniture
and more it's effective against wwe stuff and the chokeslam fruit may feel inclined to hang up in
such situations of burst should do the powerful air pressure release will blow away ghosts and
it's perfect for when you need a little air ah we simply can't overlook the latest invention
from professor egad namely guiji change between luigi and guiji to use both their skills
guiji can do everything from slipping through metal fences to walking on spikes indeed there
are obstacles too great for luigi to handle on his own and if you pass how do you make
guiji to a friend he makes what's he made out of co-op partner don't answer that caution guiji
and water definitely don't mix now please direct your attention to the scare scraper
spooky sure yet it also houses a few eight players for local or online co-op game
what defeat all ghosts before time runs out see can find our deal in this place too
of course they gotta have the codes challenges the tower throws at you
oh that's gonna be annoying oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah it's gonna fill your ears
15 people
missing mario and friends and his dear brother luigi dark souls that's all i got
so that was luigi's mansion i know the latest game in a series that i personally love
i didn't even look forward to seeing some of the new gameplay elements that await in this strange
hotel as we dive deeper into this title on nintendo treehouse live at e3 2019 we'll be
streaming content some you've never seen before right from the show floor including live gameplay
of super mario maker 2 and on day three our treehouse staff will get their hands on some
promising indie games that are new to nintendo switch while you watch today's nintendo direct
keep an eye out for this icon to learn what other games will appear on nintendo treehouse
no that's me i gotta move me oh i miss it or this have a look i like them oh i like them
oh this is this is the this is the dark crystal right
are they doing a dark crystal game
but from this dark light brighter than the three sons they spoke to life heroes of thrall
strong and brave strength and bravery alone will not save thrall yeah the dark crystals coming back
it's on netflix it's like a tv show soon this is a little tie-in game i'm definitely not going to
play it but i'll probably watch the show watch the shore a strange land a castaway will seek the
truth animal crossing only first he must awaken and link escape coho land island
this is link treasure tracker they're finally giving link a toad game this looks cute nice
i'd love to see a star tropics uh revival here you can make your own dungeon
that's really cool you can just make your own dungeons zelda maker
that's cool
the giant egg what's the egg
is the egg no but what is the egg action rpg trials of manna is getting a global release on
nintendo switch i never know what to say what for these games because i have no i have no idea
what i would even say every time i think of something to say i'm always just like
i know never mind i don't know they're probably fun games but i always just find myself going like
the meta games were fun though later today they're just rolling them out huh
wait the witcher is the witcher actually coming to switch uh you know what i'm excited for that
for i'll for one reason only i've never played the witcher three because i don't want to sit
at my desk for 400 hours i'll lie in bed for 400 hours i already have let's all agree to
meet back at the monastery exactly five years from today like a class reunion you will come
won't you years ago we fought here as classmates as big class reunions go this one's got to be the
worst in history what should we do teach kill every last one of them somebody said something
funny i'll wait till after the movie you have no choice but to eliminate those who
cling to unreasonable ideas of justice someone must put a stop to the cycle of the strong
travel of the week
let's do that from the beginning
both sides of time are revealed to you what shall you do how lovely it would be for this moment
to last forever click that but i don't think you can i don't think it's clickable on my stream
nintendo switch is the only gaming console you can play not only on your tv at home but anywhere
you go best part that's why it's so good with a system like this it might be fun to play resident
evil at a location like this what play resident evil just play just in the doctor's office
now that would have been funny he like screams at the waiting room oh somebody said that why
do i only look the same for my e3 presentations but i never look that way ever again because i
get possessed by the fucking et demon the e3 demon okay let's do this resident why would you
walk into a scary place to play a horror game this is like next level meta get i want to get
scared people still like oh i'm gonna go walk around at night in a scary abandoned mansion
but i'm gonna bring my switch this time and instead of exploring the scary mansion we're
gonna like play the switch in the scary mansion why don't you why don't you explore the scary
mansion is this like the zoomer is this like the new zoomer how to get scared
well one of those is a really good game playing a resident evil game in a place like that might
not be my way to play but i bet you could find your way to play don't you think that on the
bathroom on the toilet every time take a look i've only played the switch lying in bed and while i'm
in the bathroom that's my only way i played was today the fourth of july if not is the empire
striking back or what looks like things are gonna get weird today oh man oh come on have it be real
have this be real and powerful and trying to take over the world not some shitty top-down game
have this be real please what there are no heroes in this world oh but there totally are
my name is travis touchdown i'm the last hero around here to save the world i'm also just a
passing assassin number here's number here's three start the game oh that's the i'm so far i can't
wait they didn't show shit and there's nothing here but like in a couple of years or whatever
these games were bat shit they were insane i'm excited for that that actually is hopefully
gonna be good because they came up with that like travis touchdown virtual reality top down
that thing was what the hell was that he led an elite team contrast during war
hb is actually a cyborg i love him so much this is miss harakiri and her alien gut bucket
they survived by merging together during the alien wars the gentleman the sweetest bug you'll ever
meet
there it is there's more of it the world sucks all the time you know what i'm saying
imagine just like living in a fucking hut somewhere like in these worlds it's like the world sucks
oh i wish i was living in the harry potter universe oh you know how many
fucked up shitty worlds there are that have been made people say oh i want to get reincarnated as
a butterfly you're gonna be if you're gonna you're gonna be an ant there's like 900 billion of them
you're gonna get one of those worlds not harry potter reincarnated into harry potter
no i'm just making like that's even rarer that's like a hundred percent more rare
i was making the point that there's so many like fucked up shitty universes
that like people want to live in the harry potter world well you're gonna get reincarnated into like
fucking gundam suit mobile game two am i are you hearing that am i insane are you guys hearing
this too there's like two streams playing this is panzer jacuz holy shit yeah i'm i don't i think
it's the feed that i'm pulling because i don't have anything else going on i'll play that i'm
shinya takahashi from nintendo earlier this month he held a pokemon direct for the latest games in
the series pokemon sword and pokemon shield the developers from game freak showcase the new
gallery region the location of your new adventure and some new pokemon you'll encounter there
it will be a while until these games launch so please stay tuned
play pokemon you loser by the way in these games you can use certain functions of the
pokeball plus accessory allowing you to take a pokemon from one of these games out for a
stroll through the real world with you is that a new amiibo it's the amiibo pokeball use the device
as a game controller but if you spend some quality time with a favorite pokemon of yours
then something good might happen in the nintendo booth at this year's e3 fans can play pokemon
sword and pokemon shield for the first time anywhere in the world people are gonna lose
their fucking minds over this game you can challenge one of the gyms in the gallery region
the one and only water gym where the water type gym leader nessa will be there waiting for you
if you're attending this year's show i encourage you to experience a battle
between dynamax pokemon which is an advanced strategy from this region
so this is gonna be the biggest thing ever immediately after this nintendo direct
stay tuned for live gameplay of pokemon sword and pokemon shield on nintendo treehouse live
and now i'd like to shift gears please have a look at this please have a look at this
waiting for you
there is dementia facing down the end of the world there's a research
with a kemeric weapon please sinking captured kimeras with human operators we established
control what the hell here's here's your 9 a.m fucking commentary from german 985 what the hell
i'll give you some parting advice what the hell
legioness and a legion are perfectly well i can't stream it i think like they're two parts
and when half of that body is about to die the legion's survival instincts kick in to save it
no way there's no way this looks crazy it's a long shot but it's the only shot we have
it's all up to you my friend a blessing from the legion maybe i should say a curse we can't turn
back now yes why don't you just let them win uh is there ever a scenario where it's just like
yeah just let just let the aliens win what we got like we can't beat them just let them win and then
have something else happen destroy all humans yeah oh wishy it's like the original um like
gangsters game i remember that game i think it was called actually i think it was called gangsters
death by our hands is not an honor they have earned they deserve something much worse
even with this stone at my command this may not be a battle we can win
magneto that's still we can beat it keep fighting
oh this is ultimate alliance three isn't it i actually haven't excited to play this
i got some i might have some unpopular opinions here i do no maybe i don't but they probably are
turn down your particle effects they don't have it just gets in the way it's like overwatch syndrome
you know what i mean i don't just turn them down is it really doesn't really care that much
that's what slows all these fucking games down to a crawl is they have like 5 000 particle effects
i want to just turn them off well give me an option to turn them off it just looks messy we
want you to be feel powerful and have explosions yeah but like i already am powerful i'm tony
goddamn stark i already know how powerful i am they don't have to blow up my screen
this is pretty cool oh man this is so cool zelda crypt of the necro dancer
mario and sonic at the olympic games 2020 i'm gonna be playing the shit out of this
this is a boomer game why because the olympics eggman really has such an odd body he looks like
an ant like a spider what do you think so far now for some follow-up information on a game
i think looks pretty good waiting for please take a look follow up info from
your attention please you guys get me for like five seconds
getaway package charter flight will soon be arriving at the deserted island animal crossing
animal crossing hybrid it runs off of electrical power lim tx no ow oh snow as i've gotten older
i've learned to appreciate these games way more oh like oh here's my reaction to this
hooray right that's it that's all you have to say there's no conflict just dead we announced
this title as a 2019 release however just conflict on its own right to march 20th constant the worst
kind of conflict to ensure that the worst most terrible conflict we must ask you to wait a
little longer than we thought we hope you look forward to the latest installment of animal crossing
on nintendo treehouse live the game's producer mr nogami and the director
miss kyogoku will come on for a live demonstration of some early moments in the game
please stick around until it starts by the way there are many different types of games coming
to nintendo switch from nintendo and our partners so we prepared a highlight reel to show you what's
in store for 2019 and beyond highlight they got more let's have a look they've got more
shit to show they got some more stuff oh god it's probably gonna be re-releases
spyro i'm gonna play that you can you can make fun of me all you want i'm gonna play that a lot
what is this mine you didn't see the minecraft this game will be fun too
there's some good shit the stuff that i'm not supposed to be excited for is the stuff that i'm
excited for at this e3 and it feels strange maybe it's because like not very much was really shown
here all the triple a studios have made the same constant conflict game and if we get there's all
the stuff that like seems pretty cool there it is what is that three something three the game
three the game all right i don't know why i thought that was conquer i was gonna say why would
they not have something more substantial for this mario maker 2 very cool no actual gameplay of what
oh donkey kong country 4 donkey kong country 4 do it or like a like a tropical freeze
are they roommates no oh you gotta be fucking kidding me
oh
it's gonna it's gonna happen oh you guys again it's fucking unbelievable oh yeah
wow i didn't think this was gonna happen i really didn't
i can't fucking believe it i thought this was bullshit wow they actually did it
i can't fucking believe it i i smash brothers and banjo kazooie wow that obviously wasn't duck
hunt silhouette was it it's tell us tuned for more information about dlc in the future
as for nintendo switch we have more games in development beyond what we've shown you today
i'm looking forward to the day we can introduce them to you not today speaking of
before we end this direct i actually have one more thing to show you
thank you very much for watching until next time come on what do we got it better be metroid
thank you very much thank you i still can't believe banjo kazooie is in smash bros
i didn't play breath of the wild did i just spoil everything oh this
i thought this was like dlc the sequel it's not dlc it's a sequel full-blown sequel oh damn all
right that's it extra cool shit like floating island dude is that it that's what the first one
was missing would have been a 10 out of 10 that's awesome very cool that's so far away though you
can just feel it oh yeah yeah is it do the joke no i can't look i can't recycle the same like i'm
pretending to be on the podcast joke i've done it like three times in three days for each day
there's been an e3 i've pretended to be on somebody else's show i i'll tell you i did
banjo b and it's smash means that like anything's possible now they can put anybody in there now i
mean you got microsoft had to have had something to do with that so i who knows who knows who the
hell you'll see there in a couple years sans i don't know about that i don't know about that
dude the joke no uh i just i just closed out the browser it's not here anymore
all right let me so hold on it has been let me give you my total my complete assessment here
because this is now an assessment stream here we go okay so this is this is my e this is what i
think about e3 amd but they're lightning fast processors and they're extremely affordable
graphics processing units i'll tell you one thing that i am disappointed on and i'm disappointed
with this every single year that is a nintendo direct for e3 or anytime nintendo does anything
where they announce anything no wario where no like actual real new wario where every year i'm
just like are they gonna are they gonna do it and they just don't so they did that game in wario
game for the wii u and it was stupid it was like 16 games although it was just whatever it wasn't
really that it was pretty bad then but it's been like 10 years since it's been like a real wario
where and i those are my favorite fucking games that nintendo's probably ever made they did they
did what the one on ds wario where is dead wario where gold no but i mean like a but like console
wario where is shit oh he is the shit i want like a full-on wario where switch you know how much
fun shit they could do with those two little controllers they could have like you could have
so many different things with the two just like they did with the wii and the screen you could
they got a touch screen and they have motion controllers rhythm heaven that would be no yeah
anything like that it would be good nobody buys them i buy them isn't that enough that should be
enough one guy that's get one sale from me every time nintendo that's a guarantee dude if there was
a collector's edition for wario where switch and it was like i don't know like a wario mask
and like caffeine pills or something like i get it he's drinking pac-man's brains he killed but
yeah like i fucking murdered pac-man and i turned him into a drink no this is this is a novelty
device that came for fun um no no more heroes three uh looks i don't know how it looks because
we don't get to see it uh no more heroes three uh was a big fan of the first two i played the
shit out of him in college i'm sure it'll be all right i'm sure it'll be good uh what else is there
watch dogs three lots of threes lots of threes that i think would be fun watch dogs three is
in this weird space where i think it'll be fun for like 12 hours and then i'll never play it ever
again which i don't know the minecraft yeah diablo minecraft i will play that animal crossing i'll
play that dragon builders i'll probably play that for like 40 minutes and then realize it is way
too complicated for me and then i've got to go like file some like reports or something like taxes
and i won't do it chivalry 2 i'm not i'm like i'm not that i'm not excited for chivalry 2
i just it's not like i think it's not good i just don't it's not doing it for me i feel like i
played mordhau and chivalry 2 would have to be way better than mordhau for me to care about it
terraria yeah i have i gotta play that i've got to play like i'm just i there's so many things to do
delton ring yeah it's hard to get excited about a game that is in okay remember when securo got
teased and it was just like a close-up of his prosthetic it was just like that's it it's hard
to be like oh i can't wait to play that we didn't even know what it was it was like i can't wait to
play with that guy's bones i thought it was a guy's bones so it's hard to know what's he going to
even be like yeah it was a close-up of his prosthetic and it was like crunching i thought
i didn't even know it was prosthetic did i download roller champions i did not banjo all right
here's the thing about banjo kazooie that means this is gonna there's gonna be and okay i really
hope this doesn't happen but it's very possible i mean they might be like a nintendo and microsoft
collaboration where they make banjo kazooie 3 that's a great scenario what a fucking awesome
scenario potentially more likely is microsoft rides this hype train from smash brothers
and makes nuts and bolts 2 i'm it's jet that's probably a real scenario i just it's possible
there's an equal and opposite potential way to go here or we'll get like a banjo kazooie mobile
card game or yeah or remastered banjo kazooie 1 and 2 the the ultimate scenario is the microsoft
decides to ride this train all the way up and makes banjo kazooie 3 but i don't even
people get so excited about banjo kazooie 3 it's not even saying people anymore right it's like
that studio has been i mean even if it was banjo kazooie 3 it's like oh i wish there was a new
game in the chrono series chrono trigger chrono cross i can't wait for the next chrono none of
the people are even still there it would be different it wouldn't be the same and we essentially
all locked ourselves in this like nostalgia box for like two decades just like let me out let me
out i can't wait to see i can't no and then finally you get to see it it's like some of
these people don't even work here anymore because it's been it's been like too long that's the one
problem all these sequels and all these things that we like can't wait to see it's been a very
long time so it's like somebody writing a series of books and then halfway through somebody else
comes in and finishes that person's story it's like all right i it's it's i guess it's the same
characters but it can be tough though and a lot of people have trouble with it game of thrones
didn't want to say anything that happened to hitchhiker's guide it's actually happened
quite a few times throughout history why do i look like a character from greece
because this is my e3 persona what time is it that's my phone's dead uh what are you what
am i using my hair uh i use shampoo uh and then i rinse it out this is my hair look at let me tell
you something my hair looks like this for like maybe two or three hours and then it just goes
crazy i use conditioner not every single day but i do i mean i think that the banjo part of the
name is pretty much enough right just always thought of different kind of banjo one what do
women i want to go in by too fast am i graying no i probably will not have gray hair ever i turn
33 this year i mean 35 what's a lie turn 34 i turned 34 this year and i'm i got no gray
none i'll be bald before it turns gray i'll be yeah i'll be bald before it turns completely gray
there's plenty of time there is a lot of time left uh but anyway so we got nintendo i mean
whatever they decide to do hopefully somebody cares about it and we get something fun
obviously this is the one thing that all right so so sakurai is has his hands on banjo and he's
making banjo and banjo looks like really really great and really cool but like he might make it
too good and then like uh microsoft gets it and they like don't make it right it's like
so it'll be sonic boom when microsoft makes it that's what you should be concerned with
because of those saying yeah sakurai is seriously like he's so talented at making characters and
making them the way that they like really should be right every time a new character is introduced
in smash you're like oh my holy shit i can't wait to see this because it's going to be so true and
so awesome to what the source material was there'll be little like easter eggs with the
moves they do a great job they do it better than than like the people that made the game did
does sakurai should just make every game we haven't figured out cloning yet just clone him
a hundred times and just have him make every single video game and it'll probably be good
he works he works himself to the bone yeah he does and i mean he really does they have to and
do understand flavor when it comes to characters the actual people who own the ip forget yeah
typically i mean well think about it if you have a character that's from franchises from 15 years
ago and nobody on your development staff has ever even worked with it before and you start
and you make something else with that character it's just like oh i guess we do still have this
character to work with and then you give it to sakurai and he makes he like makes it look easy
but no that's really that's really cool to see that this actual collaboration between
because this shit you this shit that gets so tiring everyone like in constant conflict with
each other console wars get out here this is my exclusive motherfucker i'm supposed to be quiet
this is we got to see a for the first time in a long time we got to see
conflict resolved we got mic Microsoft and Nintendo no conflict that's all i wanted
i didn't realize that sony was streaming like right now what is this click the link
vermin ty two is getting a versus mode rats the rats wear the rats what is that actually
part of the article that's fucking funny the rats the rats wear the rats i mean that
it could mean anything that's that's versus mode though that's pretty funny that's pretty cool but
um do i have any more info up here in here in my brain that i would like to get out let it yeah
uh square enix i just i'll be honest i just i just don't get it i just don't get i and i'm not i'm
not saying that i don't think those games are good i just don't get it i just don't get them
like i told you last night i was kind of sitting there not knowing what to do or say
just because i made the the comment about it's like oh it's like turning on a movie 45 minutes
in and just being like who the fuck are all these people that's like okay that's like
going like lord of the rings right these are some of these games and some of these
series are in like the 10th or 11th iteration now this is dragon quest 11 and i know they're
they're different from story story but still i mean it's like some of these games are two or
three iterations and they have like books and novels and animes behind them it's like walking
in to a convention for one of these games where people already are all really big fans and they
already know everything that's going on and and you're in like like a super mario t-shirt
and you're like i thought this was this is not super mario and they're like what are you talking
about oh but they would probably be happy to be like oh i love super mario but then you'd be like
i don't know who your character is and i would feel i'd be like i don't i don't understand it's
hard it's hard to distinguish these just because i don't really follow any of them i look like a
mob boss no i look like i look like the mob boss's fucking sleazy accountant i'm a guy that's like
yeah man what do you need i can make that work for you but that's not to say any of those
franchises of games aren't any good it's just i don't get them i don't understand
watching a three it's like watching a three-part trilogy movie in the last movie and not knowing
any of the characters names but some of the things they did show were interesting
uh but i don't really have much to say about it anyways uh what else we got we had ubisoft
i don't remember anything from ubisoft i don't not one thing i remember okay hey guys i remember
the color of tod's jacket that's it oh watch dogs watch dogs free right okay all right watch
dogs free no that was bethesda so no i'm like putting bethesda into a different stage because
i got that was bethesda with the problem there okay so not ubisoft bethesda i just know the
color of tod's jacket that's why i was putting him putting him in with ubisoft what color was
the jacket it was like a it was like a taupe it was like a green beige did i get that wrong
is it not that color it was tan it wasn't like a it wasn't like a green like olive it wasn't an
olive somebody give me a screenshot is it did i get that wrong was that conference that bad
that i don't even know the color of tod's jacket is the most important thing what even was in
bethesda fallout 77 uh fallout 76 is still a video game please god come play it was one doom oh yeah
doom there was doom doom eternal all right that's cool what else oh yeah there was a couple there
was that that death loop game yeah let me see is this did i get it wrong i got it wrong i'm not
paying attention to what matters here why did i think it was like an olive color like a dark olive
green like taupe but you know having no saudi just it feels weird it feels like oh i wish i could see
some of that stuff but we don't all right this is here's another potentially unpopular opinion
follow these tonight today it's it's it's nine o'clock ten o'clock in the morning not tonight
my brain is just fried um do we really need an e3 every single year do we really need that
not really right why don't we have like a mini e3 like e2 e3 could be like the big one whenever
it has stuff to show and e2 could be so the electronic entertainment expo how about just
like the the electronic expo does it have to be e3 the intent yeah look at some of these companies
nintendo already does this sony decided this year that they weren't going to do this
nintendo decided years ago that they weren't going to really do that anymore that's not
entertaining no they should just call it the the eae the electronic ads expo because i'll tell you
i really did feel like it i really did feel like we just watched a bunch of youtube pre-rolls on
some of these conferences eae it's called growing up wait what we need more gameplay demos
i just i don't know i think maybe i am getting old it's always been but i feel like there's been
more to talk about but what i like i like is how like some of these indie games and indie companies
are really starting to kind of flow up here and start to outshine some of these triple a games
and companies doesn't everybody say that devolver's devolver didn't even have a conference
like three or four years ago they that that's new that's not it's not like sony microsoft nintendo
devolver digital so it's interesting to see that there are some companies that are starting to
actually come up here amd yeah they didn't have a car no but i mean like like a present a presentation
like they had a presentation but maybe but maybe we just don't need an e3 every single year like
maybe like stuff like the nintendo directs are the future but i mean next year this will this won't
be an e2 next year it'll be an e3 they'll be i would assume we'll get an announcement from sony
there'll be consoles next year that they're showing it will get a full-on completely just
the microsoft xbox uh what is it called what's the what's the name of the thing the stelares the
xbox stelares the microsoft stelares what is it called the scarlet the microsoft scarlet
there'll be that'll be on a desk in the middle of the stage it's gonna be a little circle it's
gonna be as big as like an amazon echo it'll be this big a donut will be bigger than this thing
i'm just making a prediction here a donut's gonna be bigger than the the scarlet how is that gonna
run anything it might be i'm just telling you it could be it's gonna be it's gonna be a little
thing in the middle it's gonna and they're gonna sell it like it's cortana whatever the thing is
called the halo halo what's the halo person bed audit i'll buy it if you're right good by the way
i love i love this i love like the they just they didn't nintendo just those with oh that transition
just like and now you know how many times they probably recorded that snap to get that perfect
there was an audio engineer sitting in a room for potentially two to three straight weeks hiring
different people to come like snap and like mixing it to get it perfect months even yeah
that was the original snap of john nintendo oh my god yeah they he snapped at a at a at a
investor meeting one time and they picked it up through the phone 1948 1962 yeah that's not even
actually a a snap yeah if it's a foley artist yeah like somebody said they they probably like
squished a bag of carrots and like mixed it together with like somebody dropping a book on
the ground to get that and they pulled one out like oh like get that little part right here when
like the carrots squished right there just like it's a foley artist a foley artist that's what
they do i don't think that's a human snap it probably isn't audio editing is a ton of fun
it really is audio editing is like some of the most fun you'll ever have uh um what time is it
we're not we don't have to go just yet but i have to dry i because kim knew that i was getting up
this early she's like oh can you drive me here and i'm like yeah i can drive you here so i'm
gonna drive kim somewhere because she knew i was gonna be awake yeah i'm not usually awake at
nine o'clock in the morning fall asleep in the chair can you imagine if i just fucking
passed out no i drank coffee imagine if i just like fell asleep here like this and she like
eventually comes in just like are you fucking gonna drive me i'm just like yeah nine a.m for
germany is five a.m for the rest of us please uh you're trying to tell me that most of you
fucking guys wake up at five a.m no some of you do no i don't believe that at all yeah well most
of us get up at five well most of you get up at like 11 10 you know why some of you especially
during the summertime you know i've got i've got demographics on my twitch analytics page i know
i know exactly how old most of you guys are i know how old you are and that's it so i mean
college age is what a lot of you guys are well you guys are in college when i was in college
i didn't get up till fucking like six p.m so oh yeah we get up at five every day
sorry the data says otherwise how do we know how old you are i have morning classes not right now
what time are you in are you in high school or college right now you're out you're out
you're out of school you got up at like fucking eight o'clock this afternoon you said as afternoon
oh you got up this afternoon at eight o'clock that's how you can tell i fucking stay up really late
eight p.m is like in the middle of the afternoon i stayed up all night i was thinking about doing
that because i didn't want to miss this because i really did not want to tell everybody that i
was going to be here at nine o'clock in the morning and just not show up so i was like fuck
i really don't want to like sleep through an alarm or something should i just stay up the whole time
and then like come and sit down here i thought about it no i i slept i did i would have been
delirious i didn't well why didn't you should have gone to bed you don't want to see that
oh you should do that i've done that before and it's i just okay do you remember the first
15 to 20 minutes of this stream go watch it this it was only that was an hour and 20 minutes ago
but do you remember go watch that i was sitting here just turning the stream on just barely had
woken up and i'm just like i was weird i was a weirdo i couldn't really make any references
my brain was just like starting to turn on okay here's here's my operating set you know let me
give you a good example here i have a really really really good computer up here it works
i mean maybe uh i might be kind of full my hard drive might be failing a little but it's still
really good it still works just fine and the graphics card works everything works but i have
like a seven to ten minute boot up sequence like if you turned your computer on it took like 15
minutes to turn on but once it's on it's it goes so i can't get an ssd i have a hard drive up here
i have a i can't what am i going to take my brain out now some of you guys some of you guys were
born with an ssd in your head and that's good that's great you can get up in the morning and
bang you're ready to go some of you guys can it also takes me like 20 minutes to like boot the
computer down it takes i have so many viruses you know when somebody has like a shit load of viruses
then it takes like 20 minutes for the computer to turn off and turn on i'm like your grandfather's
computer i have a bunch of viruses in my like operating system that i like i can't get rid of
too much bloatware but i got too many toolbars i've got too many tabs open too that's another
thing i have like a hundred firefox tabs open with an operating system from fucking windows vista
still using internet explorer but it takes me a long time to boot up a very long i still not
boot completely boot up so that's why when you watch the stream for the first 20 minutes
i am fucking useless absolutely useless i i better not ever in my whole life ever have a job where
i got to get up in the morning and like like be like ready to pull the lever you know what i mean
like i'll miss it by like a nanosecond you know what i mean i i don't i can't have that all right
here's your job or your job is to get in here at exactly 6 a.m you sit right here and you wake up
at 5 30 in the morning you got to get here and you sit and you get all your job your job is just to
pull the lever at 5 10 exactly i'll miss it that's the whole that's all i have to do i don't have to
do anything i'm the person that turns on the factory you know what i mean i just have to like
turn it on and catch it when it's going to its next uh like the transmission like it's going to
like a ninja drive i have to like catch it that's how you turn on every factory i just got to pull
that lever that's it i wouldn't be able to do it i would i would like fucking pass out at like 5 8
and at 5 10 when it's supposed to be pulled i would like snap out of it and pull it at like 5
11 like the factory turn off and like i would it would be 600 million dollars in damages to that
place what scp are you talking about what scp am i do i have to contain i gotta catch it at
the right second i'm the guy i'm the guy in that factory that is like catching the scp i have to
do everything in very in tandem i'm the guy that lets him out you play all those games holy shit i
can't believe scp 666 got out of his containment facility it's because germa 985 woke up too late
and like got in there and fell asleep at his desk i'm that person that has that happened
but anyways what else was there microsoft uh scp isn't a game no i know i'm just saying like the
the game that you've played based on your favorite uh certain service certain protocol monster i
don't know whatever the hell what is it called what does scp stand for secure contain protect
what did i say secure secure socket what ssl secure secure uh socket encryption go to a beard
i can't it's not possible it just looks like shit it already does this is where it's where it starts
and then it looks horrible in like 12 hours service certain protocol that's close uh but
anyways microsoft games as a service is going to be a reality sooner than you think that's pretty
much what you need to know from that is that games as a service is happening sooner than you probably
think senior citizen pea pants i'm so glad that pea pants is going to be a thing on this channel
it's been a thing between friends me and my friends especially burger boy for like a decade
more than that almost no no when did smite come out 2012 2013
since smite like released and was able to go into like private rooms it's been a thing that we call
each other journal cries when did i cry i love this mug you get it on amazon just type in type
this in and then put mug after it you'll find it pretty good you find a couple of them why am i
drinking this like i'm drinking a goblet like why am i holding it like this you're breathtaking
you're breathtaking that's it right can i tell you that i feel bad about that because that is
the meme of the 2019 e3 conferences that's the that's the meme that's the thing that like everyone
is so glad that they got to see and i covered it up i actually was like covering that when it was
happening so if you watched my version of e3 you didn't get to see the like your breathtaking
like the the live meme i like i've ruined it i covered it i like literally covered him up
and twitch highlighted it yeah twitch tweeted it yeah if people whatever maybe we'll get some
new friends link it it's if you just go to official twitch tv twitter scroll down will
you find it the guy who said that is getting a free copy of cyberpunk collector's edition what
do you mean the guy who said what the guy who's but what the guy oh the oh the breathtaking guy
oh well i we got when we talk about guy there's a lot of one guys on this channel when i see like
oh the guy i'm thinking of what one guy where it is a real life one guy scenario the guy which one
guy there's one guy is getting cyberpunk that's that's fun that's fun i'm glad people can have
a good time keanu reeves it's key they're giving it to keanu reeves they loved that segment so much
that keanu reeves is getting a collector's edition uh but i gotta i gotta skedaddle here in a few
minutes so who won okay that yeah i got that up there who won e3 all of us because we get to
experience uh probably nintendo um micro okay microsoft won in like a buy the stock sense because
of the new console right so microsoft won okay if there's two if there's like people that like
video games and then like businessmen in suits that trade stocks back and forth microsoft won
to these guys and probably i i mean nintendo just had stuff that i didn't have the most stuff that
i was like oh oh that didn't happen that many other times so just judging by my oh and ah meter
i would have to say it was probably nintendo watch dogs three looks really really fun
but i the the oh and ah meter was uh higher i think for stuff that nintendo showed and it was
not that long either who had the most disappointing conference i like the whole thing was just kind of
disappointing is not really the right word but nothing really like nothing really was like grabbing
but yeah but that bethesda bethesda spent like the first 30 or 40 minutes talking about how
how much they like like love the community and like fallout 76 and look at the hey hey we're
like don't you like us we like you fallout 76 we like you you know have you heard about this game
fallout 76 we really like you so they just and fall they've had so many missteps they realized
everyone started hating them yeah let's just hope that they kind of turn it around here it looks
like it looks like they're trying it does with some of these things doom is really the thing
that's like doom has doom is like a canoe right and like like they just sit the the creator of
doom eternal is like sitting in a canoe and he has like 6 000 pounds in that canoe and he has to
fucking like row it across an ocean worst analogy what i did that how is that not true
he the dude that they got like a fucking boat full of like stuff that people don't think is cool
and then they've got doom which is people think is awesome that's a bet you know i'm gonna i veto
that that's the best analogy of 2019 uh i veto everyone in the chat sorry room eternal i think
just dance uh will probably i just realized just dance is madden this new madden damn okay um
what else was there i think that's it what am i gonna do a just dance stream i would do a just
dance stream no i wouldn't i'm not gonna say this number because it's way too high and i don't know
some somebody somebody might just like fucking find a way so i'm not gonna say it i never
underestimate people in this community i won't i don't i don't do that derma lied about just
dance derma didn't even make a statement about just dance he just said it was madden
it's new madden uh but i think that's um worsted out i just said a guy was in a boat carrying
other like he was rowing his anchor-filled boat which was bethesda that's not an analogy that's
an analysis i said a guy was in a boat and all of a sudden that's the worst analogy ever heard
an anchor-filled boat i talked about like reincarnating into harry potter today and
apparently that was that was better boats all right well uh yeah i think that's it
that's e3 the last three days have been fun to hang out with everybody hopefully you had a good
time i've got to go take kim i gotta drive kim and yeah i i'll see you guys um i'll see you guys
for this stuff the next stream that you see on this channel is gonna be we're gonna have fun
friday night we're gonna do an unlock gonna have some wine probably now i'll do the bits i still
got time for that that's what i wanted to make i just i want to make sure i had enough time to do
it so what is that well you're gonna have to just see you're gonna have to come on friday night
you're gonna have to come to the stream find out what that is five nights at freddy what's
okay somebody explain this is this five nights at freddy's vr spam thing is this like a do i have
to go look this up on on memepedia later what is this is this like pull the lever is this like a
thing i have to look up it's a i know i know it's a real game but is there like a is there something
i'm missing here it's a game all right so do you just want me to play this game well put it if you
have a recommendation for a video game put it in the recommendation channel in discord play i mean
i it's vr we have to wait for another vr night he doesn't check i checked the recommendations like
two days ago guys trying to tell me we'll get oh he's getting salty he's getting salty
here comes no i'm getting peppery salty implies that like i'm irritated peppery is like i'm just
like it's like the nasal passages i'm getting a little peppered up i'm not salty i'm fucking like
cayenne it hits what what how about triggered no dude i don't really don't care about five nights
freddy's this is not like making me angry i can't believe the same five minutes of freddy's vr i
fucking i hate it oh that's fine i'll play it when we do he's turning red no i'm turning red
because i'm sweaty i'll see you guys on friday once people talk about how like sweaty i look
that's when i have to turn the camera off go check out uh the nintendo treehouse right that's going
on right now if you want to see more of that stuff uh this stream was not going to be very long just
want to do the nintendo direct and sit for like 20-30 minutes and talk about e3 thank you as
always for watching if you got up early for this uh hopefully you saw something you liked and we'll
go through the bits here there's not very many it'll take very very quickly uh see you friday
night for unlock wine drinking stream i'm looking forward to it anywho what do you say we get to
back here a couple hours ago we had three dollars 300 bits from niall oren do you do villain hair
every year as a meme or what no i do villain hair every year because i have to be here when
the conferences go live i can't turn my stream on like 10-20 minutes later so my hair doesn't dry
so i can't be late to e3 streams so i get out of the shower and just get it get the fuck in here
i can't be late to these guys every time i'm late to the stream i'm just waiting for my hair to dry
so i look all right regardless if i turn the webcam on ever i have to like look good
villain shower but no yeah yes don't i don't use a hairdryer no i don't have time for a hairdryer
but plus it's kind of like a thing now bathrobe and showered hair is just kind of the way it is
it's what i'm gonna do every year if i go to e3 next year i'm going to have that haircut that
hairstyle it's just what i'm just gonna be in a bathrobe too is that allowed if i have clothes
on it is right maybe but yeah thank you niall oren uh tar alecran thanks to the five dollars
the only reason germany is excited for no more heroes is because he looks exactly like travis
touchdown look up the trailer right at the end when he looks into the camera it's uncanny
i do not look like travis touchdown i know i don't thank you for the five dollars though
i really appreciate it i do no i don't hey niall oren again nara niall oren thanks for the three
dolls yeah the mc from persona 5 banjo and kazooie are gonna be in the next smash things i never would
have expected a year ago no i i smacked there was a lot of rumors going around that banjo
oh banjo's in the game remember like like two years ago a year ago whatever i was like oh
bullshit and then it like got like debunked and then it got debunked again and everyone kind of
lost hope and that's really really cool it's exciting to see that but yes that is true i
never would have thought the same thing freudian weapon thanks for the 250 uh mr butt woman thanks
for the 10 bucks is a better analogy for doom is a bird uh picking up somebody no it's a though the
analogy is doom is sitting in a boat and he's rowing across a huge ocean and he has like 500
fallout 76 game discs in his boat i just made it better that's so much better okay can i like
retract that and change the joke he has like 400 he has like 200 000 fallout 76 game discs
that's better that's funny okay let's see one some one person said it was funny thank you
mr butt woman for the 10 dollars fallout 76 isn't on disc uh yes it is i remember being in best buy
and it being on the shelf and very very specifically uh there was a big display for it
and there were a ton of sealed packages and it was a perfect new jenga it had not even been touched
right next to it was red dead redemption 2 and that shit was empty there were two discs like
little disc boxes things to bring up to the front so put them in the boat they're just empty boxes
yeah but they they they they personify a disc they're in a case and they're on a display
cardboard discs with codes yeah they're gonna be any more discs anymore guys it's not gonna happen
when we're gonna we're gonna go to completely to onto a disc not no i mean like a like a solid
state drive like not like a hard disc not hard you know what i'm saying like an hdd sd guys we're
moving from disc to disc the cloud i don't think we're ready for the cloud yet computers aren't
fast enough the internet's not like good enough for cloud computing to really be worth using yet
maybe like another five to ten years maybe i don't think it's there do you remember when they when
microsoft made it a huge deal that they were gonna do cloud computing for um crackdown 3
and that never happened because they probably got halfway through development and realized
that it was not possible do you remember that crackdown 3 the buildings are all going to be
cloud computing and they go you don't even need the processing oh that didn't happen we got like
we got crackdown one reskinned they probably had ambitious plans for that with what they did
and it just wasn't there yet probably i think in another five to ten years there will be no more
consoles there will be like the microsoft login and that's it you log into microsoft
and everything's just there and you might have a little box a little small amazon echo box that
plugs into your tv it's not gonna i don't think there'll be there's gonna be total packages
it's gonna happen listen to me guys i remember i i predicted the video game olympics and people
said i was wrong i'll be wrong again in 2019 i'll be correct in 2025 nobody else predicted that it
was me somebody somebody will write up and look it's it's written in stone 20 years from now
i'll be my picture will be like on the fucking hundred dollar bill of video gaming history
they'll be having i'll be one of those like old commentators that they oh and remember we
interestingly enough back in 2012 one of our most celebrated video game commentators to ever live
germa985 gave us a little tidbit and then people thought it wasn't real back then and i'll get like
a whole celebrated piece egomaniac a humble streamer egomaniac imagine really thinking
and like hoping that somebody like fucking writes a book about something you said in like a tf2
gameplay commentary there has to be people that are like that right i mean you
okay all right let's move on clue the start but thanks for the 250 thanks for getting up so early
to stream today what was your favorite game shown this year um i don't know favorite game
my absolute favorite one it's yeah i it's really easy to say elden ring but i feel like that's such
an easy answer that there's got to be another one that i would say instead no more heroes 3
probably i i really really loved those games i thought there was so much fun no gameplay but
it's it's a thing and it's real so what did i like about elden ring it's just another from
software game and george r.r martin is helping to make the world that's enough for me to be like
that's a i love that but that's that's why i said it's such an easy answer i i don't know if a game
can essentially even win this year you know what game probably won this year's e3 doom eternal
because it's one of the only video games that showed more than one minute of gameplay if you're
just going by that so if you want that that probably is what won the whole e3 but by that
logic star wars is in the top five because it was one of the only ones to show anything i like to
keep my expectations very low just because of all the i mean we've seen the videos of hey watchdogs
let's go through like five filters after release of what the game actually is so i'm looking let's
put it i'm not excited for but i'm looking forward to no more heroes three elden ring
and i gotta get a third one come on i gotta get a third one cyberpunk is really easy to say too
no i gotta get what's the third one that i really really cared about
breath of the wild no i didn't play the first one i didn't play breath of the wild
minecraft diablo uh but i is that it might be it really might be oh fall guys that yep that's
another one that yeah that looks like it's gonna be a ton of fun or that heroes of might magic
there was a good i forgot about i watched those trailers yesterday i'm not really excited for
meat fortress i think it's cool and i'll definitely do it but that's not like a video game to be
excited about that's like a cool tech display that's going to be in another game there they go
those are probably the three or four pretty cool uh let's get the credits on screen this is probably
going to be uh it's probably going to be fairly quick here actually that's going to be really
it's going to be really slow isn't it yeah let's get watch this this is going to be this is going
to be weird watch ready the faster it is the more people have subscribed thanks for supporting the
stream less than a couple hours but still thank you guys all of you vr friday no we're doing unlock
friday read them read i can't i can't read them i'll tell you know why i can't read them
because i didn't i don't read anybody else's and like this is if i read these then that's
that's not fair if i read these then like it's not fair for people that i don't read
read one okay i'll pick out one who's it gonna be who am i gonna read grill thank you so much
phil 25 for your subscription phil 25 all right now this person's like the notifications are going
crazy that person probably thinks there's an earthquake or like a meteor is hitting earth
what's happening what's happening meteor they're not here well whatever anywho
uh let's this is the only couple more we got clueless sniper 250 thank you for the 250
thanks for getting up early to stream i think we got that already but
yeah that was a favorite game right hopefully i gave you the ones that i
i remembered there's been a lot so lucas thank you lucas for the five dollars
what do you think of the valve index did you get one no i have a vibe uh i bought a vibe
like two months before all these cool new devices were announced so i have the original vibe i'm
not going to be getting the index but the vibe works just fine so i probably won't be getting
the index either at all or immediately i maybe i'll upgrade some of the pieces i want the
controllers so i'll definitely get the controllers because i like the vibe controllers
aren't uncomfortable but sometimes i really do feel like i'm an air traffic controller with
these big cones in my hands so i will definitely get the new knuckle controllers at least but
thank you uh lucas for the five dollars and finally nile oregon thanks for the three dollars
you can't tell me this isn't you no it's not it isn't look this is not me do you see a scar
on my face it doesn't look anything like me i don't have a scar there not yet what what do
you mean not yet can jesus compare i can't compare it right now i don't look at anything
like this right now no i've got i've got like i've got like a fat i got like more fatty deposits on
my face yeah i've got like fatty cheek deposits up here he doesn't have that imagine if i turn
this on and i made it like a big makeup scar right here too bad all right guys happy e3
and by the way uh i've got a skedaddle but um today i didn't even really even think about this
today is my eight year on the internet starting on youtube anniversary i didn't even know that
this is my i'm on the internet eight years and somebody made a video it's like 40 minute long
video i wish i could watch it but i can't at the moment i've got to get out of here i've got to go
i did it it was me awesome tris thank you for that video and uh yeah that's eight years i don't
really have much to say besides it's still fun and i lose interest in things very quickly and
i have not lost interest in this so i can't believe that it's been eight years and it's been
climbing up on me almost a decade i is still just as fun as it was eight fucking years ago
so thank you for joining me thanks for all you guys do every year every day every month every week
and i will see you guys on friday we're gonna do uh the unlock webcam wine stream if it's not what
i expect and it's not that fun then we're just gonna you know we just look like we do every time
what is gonna have make our own fun see you guys on friday have a great next couple days
happy e3 enjoy the rest of it take care and goodbye