Jerma, why? Why is Pog not enabled? I want to be able to Pog. I know. I'm not supposed to be here.
It's been 50 seconds. We're gonna, no, we're gonna let the intro play for a little bit and I'll be
right back. Pog, I'll be right back. I'll never have a real intro. I mean, this is, uh, hold on.
I mean, this is a real intro, but I have to go. I have, I'm just here. Yogi Bear for Jerma Rumble.
Why? Why do you want Yogi Bear? Oh, I forgot to change after last night. I forgot to change
the, I forgot to change the threshold for hype trains. I turned off the computer before doing
it and I turned it off. Hype Train! Okay, you guys have? Oh, you know, I fucked it up.
I forgot to change it. That's my bad. But thanks everybody for another hype train. Hype. Hype. Hype.
Hype. EU friendly. Yeah, that's right. Today and tomorrow. These streams are going to be shorter,
but they're going to be earlier the next couple of days. Today and then tomorrow. Community content
day is tomorrow. And because it's been so long, because the, I had a plan, like, you know, I was
going to go into the green screen again. So I delayed the last one from December because
there's probably a shitload of content. I might break it up into two days. Not that far apart,
obviously, but tomorrow we'll maybe we'll do part one and then maybe the weekend, the weekend after
do part two is because I don't want to have a problem. Here's what I don't want to have happen.
I don't want it to become like we're stuffing everything into one stream and I'm just skipping
over content and trying to go as fast as I can because it's going to be like a seven and a half
hour stream. You know what I'm saying? I'd rather like give time to people's work rather than quickly
just, all right, that was that one. That was that one. That was that one. There's 7,000 pieces of
artwork and go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Thanks a lot. That was fun. What do you mean? What voice?
What's wrong with my voice? What? Oh, my bit rate just dropped though. Okay. Is that your voice?
My bit rate just tanked. Did it just fuck everything up? Wait, hold on. It shouldn't be.
It should be normal. It should be normal. Do I have a thing on? Hold on. Hello. No, this is,
it should be, does this sound normal? It shouldn't. I wonder why that's happening. Hold on. That's weird.
Oh, that's weird. Hold on. Testing, testing again, testing again. This, this, this is, this does
sound different than I can't tell. Scam, scam level four incoming. Scam level four. You sound
like a robot. Do I have a, what's, yeah, this is weird. Hello. Hello. Oh, my fucking God didn't
mean to do that. I think it's because I have this plugged into here. Okay. Let me know if this fixes
it. Okay. I accidentally ripped out the power cord. I ripped out the power cable. Hold on a second.
Is this any better? That didn't, I didn't change anything from yesterday. Did it get, did it,
is it actually fixed? Huh. That's weird. I wonder why that happened. That's odd. Uh, okay. Sorry
about that. I don't know why that happened, but give me one second. Oh, I lost audio somehow. Hold
on. Okay. How does it sound now? Do I, is it still like messed up and crackly? I don't know why this
happened. Sounds okay. Well, hopefully I can hear this. Okay, I can. Hey, listen to that.
Okay, I'm ready to go. Everything's fixed. Everything's good. Some of you might be familiar
with that music. By the way, thanks for the hype train, everybody. But as I finish the, uh,
the intro here, uh, yeah, tonight, today we're going to do, we're going to go for about four or five
hours tomorrow. Maybe like four, three, four, five or something like that under, under four, under five.
Be you friendly. All right. Here we go. Oh, there it is. Hold on. It's a little stretchy,
a little stretchy. Hey, it's okay. It can be a little stretchy. This game's a banger. That's
what it is. Make the volume quiet. I don't think I want to make the volume quiet on a
music game. Hey, can you like turn down the music in this music game? All right, let's go.
We got to level five. No way. No way. Scam complete.
Scam level five. We're at scam level five. How would you like to label your save file?
Uh, grandma. Yes, I can't wait. I'm looking forward to this. Welcome. We hope you'll enjoy
Rhythm Heaven Fever. The game is both fun and very simple to play. You just press the buttons to a
rhythm. The key is being able to keep that rhythm going. I, you know, you guys know me, I'm fucking
good. Space channel five. Done. Space channel bootleg edition. Done. Uh, guitar, uh, guitar hero,
guitar hero, guitar-o-man. Done. Ten subs. No, no, no, we don't have ten subs. Hey guys,
we just crossed ten subs. You are quiet. I know because I turned myself down because I want you
to hear the fucking tunes. All right, how do we do this? A. Are you ready to start the rhythm
test? Press A in time with the signal. Not bad. Not bad. I just, what did I just do? I just made a
stock market. If you have a lot of marks above the center line, it means you're pressing the
button too early. Hold on, I almost tangled up. Quick sell. Sell at the top. Try waiting a little
longer. All right, hold on. Do it again. Did I fail the tutorial? If most of your marks fail below
the center line, that means your timing is a little late. I pray. Do I go a little quicker?
Let's move on to our other rhythm test. Press A when the timer hits zero. On zero. Okay, yep.
People do this differently. When there's no, wait, when there's no sound, try counting to
yourself. Okay. Three. All right, can I get the minor prize or the major prize? Oh shit. Okay.
Six, five, three, two, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one, zero, seven, six, five, four,
three, two, one, zero, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one, zero. Done? All right. Some of them
were not great. I like this so-called human music. If all your marks are close to the center line,
that means you're good at maintaining the rhythm. I was. It was one that was wrong because I didn't
realize it was changing up on me midway. Go you. That's it for the rhythm test. Hey, ladies and
gentlemen, I want to make sure this is real clear. We just crossed a level five hike train.
If you could please all scream Pog at the same time. Show us how excited you are. I feel like
I'm running an infomercial. I'm the guy directing the infomercial with the audience. Okay guys. And
when Ron Papile comes out, I want to make sure that you guys go nuts for him. Even though none
of you have probably even heard his name before in your whole lives. Act like it's your savior.
If we get in three, two, one, make it happen. Here he comes. Ron Papile. No, thanks a lot guys.
It's a lot of fucking money. A lot. And it happens every day. So thanks. That's fucking crazy. It's
not important how well you did in the test. As long as you have fun, that's the main thing. That's
exactly how I feel. So I'm, I'm, this, me and this game are going to quit. We've got quite a few
games in store for you. We hope you'll like improving your rhythm with them all. One more
thing. In the test just now, you only had to press A. But some of the other games are a bit trickier.
Sometimes you need to press A and B at the same time. Give it a try. Just squished his head.
Yep. Just like that. Remember what that feels like. You'll need it later. All right. We won't
keep you any longer. Go have fun. I'm excited. Level one. Golf. Call in one. You know what will
really improve your golf game? Climbing your swings to music. All right. Call in one.
Can we get a WarioWare intro to everything? Hi. Call me Monkey. Welcome to the first rhythm game.
Call in one. In this game, you'll just press A to hit the ball as it flies toward you.
Easy, right? But you'll see that the timing is tricky part. Let me show you what I mean. Give
it a try. Here it comes. Wait for it. Wait. Did I just do it? Nice job. All right. I get it.
It actually looks like him. Let's try with some rhythm.
This is fun. This is going to be hard. So how was that? Much easier than before, right? Well,
hello. It's my friend, Mandrill. He's a mandrill. Can I play too?
What? He's just throwing fucking balls at me. You can't do it like that, Mandrill.
It's hard to hit the ball if you just fling it with no warning. Yes, it is.
You have to give a cue or something. All right. Yeah. Sorry about that. I forgot. It's your first
time playing. This time, I'll give you a good cue. Let's try again. There. Yeah. Let's try it
again. This time, Mandrill will make a noise as he throws the ball. Okay. Nice. Good. You're
getting the fast balls too. Can you feel it? No, don't do it. Please don't do it. No, I have to.
Don't do it. It's not worth it. It's not worth it. It's not worth it. It's not worth it.
I feel it too. God damn it. Whatever. Can you feel it? Are you riding the rhythm? Feels good,
huh? All right. Let's review. So, Mandrill and I will switch off and toss balls at you. Okay.
Best game ever. This is the best game ever. This might be the best game ever made.
Close. No, Jerma. Okay. Now, let's do the real thing. All right. I'm ready. This is the real
thing. Hold on. Oh, I wasn't ready for that. My God. It's one. Damn it. I apparently... No,
that's right. Okay. I'm waiting for... It's a fast ball. I get it. I get it. I get it. It's a fast
ball. So, I get it. Figured it out. Simeon feedback. The monkey was very impressed and
your mandrill friend says he did well. You got us. Superb. Hey, even if you get some rocks thrown
at you, you're fine. Even if you get a couple of rocks thrown at you... I mean, somebody can
throw a rock up there. What's the rock music? Somebody threw a rock at me. Championship title,
here we come. What was that? I just did... I've said that like seven times in like six different
videos and like five different screens. I just gave you kind of all of them. I say that all the
time. I was just pulling out the ones that you've probably heard before from some of your favorite
videos. If you're new to the channel, then you don't have any favorite videos.
What? You don't have a favorite video of mine? Fake, fake fans. No, there's no such thing as a
fake fan. The cafe is now open. The barista is quite friendly and is waiting to meet you.
What's this one? Screwbox factory and cafe. You're encouraging copy power. Let's go to the cafe.
Let's go to the cafe. Welcome to the cafe. Is this your first time here? Feel free to stop by
anytime you find the games too hard or you just want to take a break. If there's anything I can
do to help, well, that's what I'm here for. I'm a little busy right now since I only just opened for
the day, but we'll talk more later. I'm back soon. Read something. Rhythm test. You can do rhythm.
Hold on. Microphone's in a stupid place. Give me a second. Anybody got a pair of pliers I can borrow?
I need a pair of pliers. I talked to the barista. I've got some other customers to help. We'll talk
later. Okay. A pair of pliers so I can tighten my microphone stand. Listen to music. I only have
one song unlocked. Okay, yeah. This place looks packed. I don't need to take a break. Let's go.
Screwbot Factory. Robot assembly is a precise task. I've heard this song before.
Where's this from? Is this in anything else? Is this only in this game? I've heard this.
You'll need to tighten the final screw just the right amount.
Have I played this before? Have I played this? I think I've played this.
No, I haven't. Have I? Welcome to the factory floor. This is where the magic happens. Or maybe
it's in Smash Brothers. Okay, are there any of these songs in Smash Brothers? I feel like they
would be, right? Your job will be to screw the robot's heads on. Hold A and B until the head is
screwed on. I have to do it too. Please assemble these smaller robots too. Okay, that's kind of
off beat though. Wait, did I say let's go because he said let's go? Probably. My brain, I'm so easily
manipulatable. I'm the most easily manipulatable person you've ever met in your life. That's why
the one guy exists. You can inception ideas in me and I don't even have to be asleep.
In fact, it would be harder if I was asleep. Of course it would because I would be asleep.
Movies aren't real. Okay, here we go. Two. Great. Movies are real. Yes. It's perfect if I've ever
seen one in my whole life. You finished the great robots well in the white robots cast inspection.
You got a superb. Is that a perfect? Wow, that's a perfect. Did I get? No, I didn't.
Let's go. I thought that said let's go. Perfect world. It's like, yeah, I got a perfect. I got
scammed. Well, that means I didn't. No, there it is, right? No, it's a gold medal. You unlocked
rhythm toys. Collect medals to play with more toys. Rhythm toys. Toy car? Police call. All right,
what's toy car? Oh shit, my battery, my Wiimote 12. All right, more batteries.
But don't worry because Wiimotes and the Wii is old technology and sometimes old technology
is better than new technology because I don't have to plug this in to an outlet with like a
mini USB cable. It's two AA batteries. Sometimes old technology is better than new technology.
Pull back. Let's go. Let go. What could be simpler? The A to start the right time to let go.
Too far. I don't get it. Right. Is that not correct? Oh shit. I missed it.
So wait, it's. Yep. Wait, this mini game sucks. A little farther. Dizzy bird.
Oh, it's dizzy bird. It's just car bird. Boom. Oh, okay. Come on. Oh, it's perfect. That was exact.
That's as no one has ever gotten that before, but except for me. What can I just do it?
Is it twice in a row? No one's ever done it twice in a row. How do I get out of here?
Oh shit, it gets faster. Oh, okay. Hold on. I'm just going to make noises this whole street.
There it is. Really? I think that's late. Does this do it? Does this do anything for me?
It's a toy. Okay. How do I leave? That was fun. Need seven medals for police car.
Is he enough? Let's go. We go. This one is called Seesaw. Yeah, this like.
It's definitely like Smash Brothers Brawl or something. Seesaw inspectors are here
doing important work to ensure the safety of our children. Serious business, you know,
no shenanigans. He played this game in an old YouTube video. No, I didn't though.
This is all new to me. Welcome to playground safety. We're going to inspect this Seesaw.
At the moment you land, press A. Which one am I? I'm just kidding.
Looking good. Okay. Is it that simple? We'll be checking the inner part too.
You won't go as high here, so it goes a little faster. All right. Great. No problems with the
inner part. Now we'll keep checking though. You can never be too safe. There you go. I'm going
to like this song. This is going to be my favorite song. I'm a little late. The guy going
too high, too high. Oh, they're doing the air guitar. That's odd. They're both dead. Okay.
That's kind of sad. Kind of morbid. They both die at the end. Oh, those are some happy landings.
And your high jumps were impressive. You got a medal. That's a good Seesaw. A good Seesaw.
And new toys. You unlocked endless games. See how far you can get. Oh, I don't think that's a
good idea to do that right now. That's a bad idea to click this. You know what I mean? Mr. Upbeat.
Okay. Mr. Upbeat. Personal record. What do I do? Hop over the needle. Was that a needle? Oh,
okay. Wait. So wait, hold on. For a second I thought, oh, that was it. No, this goes on forever.
This goes on for actually forever. Does it speed up? Infinite content. This is going to go faster
and faster. Can I get to 100? Let's see. Hey! Ah! I fucked it up. Whatever. I don't care. Double
date. It's your first date with the girl of your dreams. Also, some weasels are on a date. Don't
let the double date be ruined by flying balls. Sucker, you talk. Double date. Hey, you. Yeah.
You, the human. Oh, listen. I have a date coming up soon. And I have a huge favor to ask you.
If a stray ball comes your way, can you kick it? A kick. That wasn't so bad. Perfect.
Just like that. Uh oh. I see a basketball coming. I hear a car coming. I get it. Yep.
That was a little early. You guys thought I was lying to you when I said that I used to. I'm
serious. If there's a drum set somewhere and I'm there and you're there and it's open drum night,
I want you to hold me to this. I want you to say, Jeremy, go fucking prove it. That you used to,
you know how to play the drums. And I'll be like, is that okay? And I want like a written
permission from the establishment that I can do it. I know how to play the drums. I know half beats.
I know side beats. I know quarter beats. I know tenth beats, tenths of a beats. You know what I
mean? I know them all. I know every beat. Yikes! A football! Oh, I thought it was me. Wait, wait,
what's the time in here? Okay. And then I see it's done. Yeah, it's on the third. I could do it. I
just don't feel like it right now. I didn't say that. I said, thanks. I love you. Thanks. I love
you. Well, I love you too, Mr. Beaver. All right. See you later. Yes. Trying to ruin this date.
Yeah, somebody's intentionally doing this. Give me a purpose. Oops. Oops. Oops. I got it. I just
died to that. That was, I put my foot. What? Okay. Slow down. I just wanted to show you that I could
kick. Oh, it's okay. It's all right. It's okay. Don't worry about it. It's all right. Superb.
It's like you were born to kick. Footballs are clearly no problem for you. Also, did you really,
you did really well at the hard parts. Hey, thanks. Video games that I'm friendly. I've been
waiting to want to tell you. Tell me what? That was just Monka S, right? That was an actual Monka S.
This game automatically saved, by the way. Remix. Wait, I didn't unlock this one. How did I not
unlock this? I didn't get it. Usually you unlock the one next to it. All right. Remix one. Battery
is low. I know. I'm going to, I'm going to have to take a minute. I'm not having this dude turn
off in the middle of the game. Let's mix things up. This one's got a tropical vibe, like a musical
vacation. There's no practice on this one. Sorry, buddy. That's what I thought it said. Sorry, buddy.
You know, if I had, if I could set up this GoXLR to do like the remix, I would do it. I don't know
how, and I'm probably never going to learn. Hello. This is where we mix up everything you've done
so far. It's easier if you just relax into the rhythm. Have fun. Oh, that was faster.
Oh man. Okay. Okay. Okay. Second date ain't going so well. Okay. She's, she's seeing through the
veil of bullshit that I hit last time. Oh, she just, she just heard about my political views.
It's all right. Kick the basketball back. I can do it. Yeah. Good enough. Let me do that one again.
I know that that one just let me do that one again. Come on. That's the first time I've had
an issue with the game so far. Your performance was like a tasty slice of cake. I can do, I can
get gold medal on that one. Do it again. Holy shit. Okay. Remix one, do it again. I know I'll do,
I'll deal the battery later. Save the date this time. I'm going to try and then I'm going to
replace the batteries in my Wiimote controller. We're going to keep going. You already heard.
All right. Let's go. That's my sub sound from like 2016.
There it is. Okay. That's a superb.
Your performance was like a fine Thanksgiving dinner cake. This one's called Forklifter. I know
the battery's low. I'm too addicted to it. I can't stop. Battery. I know battery. After this one.
Do not let me scream until I can do it. I want you guys after this to spam the word battery.
Just say batteries, batteries, batteries, batteries, or riot and just riot until I,
because it's going to happen. I'm going to, it's going to die in the middle of the game
and I'm going to go. I should have done something about that. I should have done something about
that. Why did I do nothing about this? Forklift. Dinner time. Pity the food is so far away.
Press A to grab the food as it zooms by. Let's try it first with some cues. You don't do one,
two, go. One, two, three, go. One, two, go. That's not universal. Now let's try it without the cues.
Very good. Let's try changing up the timing. Pretty good cat puke sound. I like it. Bon
appétit. Let's try. I can't get sweaty. I can't talk at all. This takes literal 100% of my brain.
I can't speak. I can't talk. I, all I can do is just stare at the screen blankly and press the
button. What are you guys saying? What are you guys saying? So full, so satisfied. Battery. I
don't understand. I don't get it. Battery. That was one of the batteries. All right. I told you
that. All right. Let's go. Give me a second. You unlock two player mode. Oh, what? I don't have two
remotes. All right. All right. Battery. Battery. Battery. Battery. Battery. Battery. Battery.
Okay. Give me a second. All right. This is going to take a minute. Hold on. I need to go get
batteries. All right. Just take, it's been like an hour. Take a break. Go pee. I'll be right back.
It's been like two minutes. Right back. He's close. I can feel it. He's close. Sorry. Take care of
Otto. Just a good dog. The monkey watch level is going to break him. Is it though? Yo, Otto. He's
not in a, he's not doing well. He's slow and he just had a procedure and I don't want to show his
cuts, you know, his wound on his. Come here. Kim, uh, me and Kim have been switching off,
uh, taking care of him. He's fine. I mean, it's been like three or four days,
but he needs to be, you know, in the same room with you. Supervise him. Make sure he's,
you know, doing okay. What did he have? He had some growths that they removed from his legs.
He had a couple of under the skin, uh, growths. So they wanted just to just take him out and
just check them just to make sure everything's fine. You know, just want to make sure my dog's
good to go. But let's go. I didn't even put the batteries in. I didn't even put in the
fucking batteries. It's like what? Hold on. Okay. I'm back for real this time. Like actually for
real this time. I promise. Let me just get this going and connect. Monkey watch level is going to
break him. Will it though? Come on. Come on. Wait, hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait. There we go. There we go. Come on. Wait, batteries are in the wrong way. No,
I fucked it up. All right, let's go. Uh, actually, uh, Kim just got back and she just got auto and
now he's being taken care of. So he's good to go. All right, let's do it. Remember if you're in a
room with, uh, remember if you're in a room with like three or four people, don't spin around like
a fucking helicopter and hit them on the table. Thanks, Nintendo. I'll make sure I won't do that.
Oh, you guys didn't see the warning. All right. There we go. Back in business. Full battery.
I'm ready to get this going. This is called tambourine. Ready to play a little simian says
on the tambourine. Mouse cursor. Uh, is this monkey watch? Look, look, let's play tambourine
together. Okay. See what I do. Then coffee. I have to do this voice for everything.
Okay. I'll signal it when you raise your turn. How do I go?
What? Oh, what's wrong with them? Okay. You got to count. Oh, you got it. As you were,
I now switch to English. You weren't speaking English, right? Tapping the tambourine with your
other hand now like this. Give it a try. Press A and B together. You got it. Now try copying me
in time to the rhythm. Hey, thanks to the five community subs. Oh, it's A and B, A and B, A and
B. Sorry. Okay. Start the music. That's A and then A and B. Yeah. I don't remember. Do something.
Oh, you handled the basics well and oh, I like your clapping. I got a superb.
It's the memory. It's remembering the, it's the Simon says, I'm never gonna forget it. I got a
superb. It's because the notes that I did hit were so good that it made up for the ones that I missed.
Board meeting. You finally made it to the big office. If you want to impress the chairman,
follow your assistance advice. Let's get this meeting underway. First, we'll rehearse our
presentation of plan A. Your chair will spin. Press A to stop on your turn. I get it. Wish
that were me. Which one? What are you talking about? God, I, what, what, what, what in, what
are you talking about? Why did I read that? Because I'm confused. I actually am confused.
What are you even talking about? Oh, right. So I feel like it's gonna be hard. What is
this meeting? That's a great question. If you present to the board this well, you'll do great.
Yeah. Worst episode of shark tank I've ever seen. Uh, guys, yeah, I have, uh,
a new tablecloth. That was fast. Your presentation of plan A was a hit and the
board really liked plan B. Congratulations, Mr. Chairman. Why is everything on fire?
That's really, that was kind of odd. Everything's on fire. Fire. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. This is the thing
people were warning me about. Monkey watch. This new watch works differently from most. You might
want to read the manual to learn how to use it. Monka Omega Low from the monkey watch manual.
The monkeys high five to show the time. Press A when the second hand passes a friend.
It's not so bad. The monkey watch manual. Some monkeys are on the off beats, right? One, two,
one, two, three, four. I got, I get it. Hey, it's then I get it.
Going on. It kept time really well. I thought it was going to be in the dark.
Superb. That wasn't so bad. This is without a doubt, the cutest watch I've ever owned.
But everyone was like, dude, monkey watch is, he's, it's going to fuck him up. He's going to
freak out. That wasn't so bad. You were supposed to fail. Did they increase in difficulty? I'm
sure they do. All right, here we go. Mix it up. They do. All right. Well, whatever. Let's go.
Let's, that's fine. I'm into it. No practice. That's how you're going to get this stream.
I don't remember. Okay. That was, that was a little rough. It's all right. I,
let me get superb on this one. That could have been better. I'll do it again.
That was a fail. It was, you played like a first level unhatched egg. That is such,
that's such a, yeah. That, what, what an insult. A level one unhatched egg. If you get a perfect
on seesaw right now, you'll receive a gift called partners right now. It is a limited time only
limited time. I get it. Welcome to playground safety. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I already know I've
skipped practice. I don't do this. Let's go. Perfect. Get the fuck out of here. Nice commentary. If I
had said a single word, I would have fucked up partners. You've earned a gift. Read it at the
cafe. There are still 49 gifts left to get. Keep going at the cafe. Let's go look at it.
This is such a cute little game. It really is. This is so, this is so fun. How have I never played
this before? What's wrong with me? Do I not even know what a good game actually is? Oh, it's down
here. Okay. Okay. Talk later. Uh, read something. Partners C. Hey saw what's up C. How many
years have we been working together? See, uh, it was two years before I got married. Uh, that's
10 years. That's long already. Time really does fly. Just think 10 years of eat on bap boom.
Oh, I'm amazed that I'm still not sick of it. Seems like I've been falling on my rump more and
more lately. Sorry about that C. Hey, I've been the one falling onto my head for those handstand
jumps. I'm the one who should be apologizing. So no, no, no, no. I fall off my bum way more.
I'm sorry, but my head smashes away. Creepy. I'm so sorry. Hey, uh, how is your neck anyway?
Ah, it's okay. Uh, how about you? So your bum's not sore or anything.
Nah, thanks though. Let's say the kids will be showing up to play at the park pretty soon.
We better get to work then. Keeping them off this unsafe seesaw. What's the point of that?
What's the point of that? Let's just lower. Okay. Oh, that was cool. All right, let's go.
Remix two.
Do I really got to do this?
That was not, no, I saw somebody said it was thank you for buying the game.
I own all this shit. All right. Now I'm okay. You know, you got me all twisted pressing me out.
I, I'm sorry. I didn't just have to, I'm sorry. But I'm having trouble.
I fucking lost the time and already it's din, din, din. Is there a retry button?
He didn't take his medicine today. Chop up. Okay. Chop up my head. It's okay. I got it.
That's good. That's good enough. That's good enough. That's good enough for them.
League notes. That was great. Really great. Good job. Superb. You got a medal. He played like a
12th level golden rooster. That's not a very good Hearthstone rank. I'm not that satisfied
with that one. Working dough. Time to get to work. Follow your coworkers lead and move those
thingies. Look at those thingies.
Working dough. Somebody just gave a fucking, hold on.
Zyxia or Zyx, Zyx, Zyx, Zyxa. Just gave 50 community subs. 50, 50, 50. That's huge.
That's a lot of money. That's a ridiculous amount of subs to give.
Oh my god. My fucking lord. Thank you so much, Zyxia. Am I saying your name wrong?
Tell me if I am. Pog, dude. Zyckia? It's probably Zycia. Zyckia. Zyckia? Is it? Well, anyways,
that's a fucking ton of money. Thank you for the 50 community subs. Keep with us over 10k.
We're still over 10k. Unfucking believable. Thank you.
He doesn't know Pepe left. What do I not know? Press A to jump and help me transport the thingies.
Just watch and copy what I do. I love that clap. Top 40. Yeah, this community has exploded in the
last year and a half. So I hope that I can keep up. You know what I mean? I'm just going to keep
doing what I've been doing for years and that I'm not going to change much. You know, I don't want
to be like, wait a minute. Hold on. This is a fucking lot more people here. This is a ton of
money. I got to do something. I got to change. I got to do something different. I'm just going
to keep doing it. You know what I'm saying? Good. Just keep sucking at games. I just got perfect on
first try on the fucking, on the seesaw. So the person that said that, I want you to mod that
person for a week so they think, holy shit, I'm modded. And then after a week, IP ban them.
You know what I'm saying? All right. Time for the heavy ones. A and B.
This reminds me of an old flash game. That's it. You're a natural. All right. Work hard and keep
your chin up. I don't like the red light. Kind of hurts my head. Commentary Jeremy. Oh, I can't
launch it back up. It's hard to press A like that. Oh, here comes the boss. There it is. Oh God,
it's Reddit. What do you mean? Oh God, it's Reddit. Oh, Reddit. Okay. I see. It was the Reddit face.
The Reddit mascot. What's the Reddit mascot's name?
Quirky. Don't tell me. I'll get it. I'm not going to look at chat. It's like quirky or something
or like quirk, quirk, quirko. It's something like that. It's like quirky. It's new. Is it really?
Oh, I thought snoo was, people have tried to get me to say the word snoo in messages and I just
skip over it because I think it's something like that or something. Like, it doesn't,
but he actually said it. No, no, that's not right. Wait, what? Hold on. This is called built to scale.
We got them. Well, you got them. Oh, this one looks cool. Welcome to your new factory job.
First, we move the widget parts into position. Move the widget using A. I like when it becomes
my turn. You know what I mean? What else is there? It's probably moved forward, backwards. Next,
we assemble the widget. I'm it with the other parts and press A and B. What do you mean?
Press A to move and A and B to assemble. That feels nice. Great. Just like that. Please build
a lot of widgets. Okay. Cool. Yeah. I like to watch German on a spot. He's got a good screen.
His screen goes slow and down. Fuck me up. I'm going to get real fast. I could do better than
that. The entire commentary, this whole screen has just been when you lose in a fighting game
and when you're at the screen where you lost and the opponent says three words,
that's his whole screen. Piece of cake. You've got nothing on me. God, try harder. That's all
you've heard. That wasn't so bad. Nothing like a job well done. That was four words. I love you.
I don't think I've ever played a fighting game where after you lose, the person goes,
I love you. Air rally. Keep the rally going in this badminton game. Try not to let the birdie
go out of bounds though. I love when it makes like the sound. You know, there's one thing that people
impress, you know, I impress a lot of people by going, they go, how the fuck did you do that?
I go, learn. You know what I like when I'm flying badminton? Let me show you. Hit that birdie back
to be with A. Illegal. That's a penalty for you. Good. That's it. I'm going to change up the rhythm
now. Of course you will. Listen for my signal. It's going to be hard. Next, let's see how you
do when I'm farther out. The beat stays the same. Nice. Now for the real thing. That's the same
timing. It just looks different. We got a little higher. One, two, one, two, three, four.
Oh, you fuck. Stop counting. Stop counting. I just want to listen to the beat. Doing that.
When he counts. Start the whole thing over. I don't want, I don't want it to be counting.
That's okay. So if I'm playing, if I'm doing a beat, if I'm like one, two, three, four, one,
two, three, four, one, two, three, four, one, two, three, four. Stop doing that. I'm trying to hold
beat, man. Here we go. Two, three, four, two, three, four. It's like an old music instructor
from the ninth grade. No, skip practice. I already know this. Fucking counting. Stop counting.
I can't do the counting. When I hear two, three, four, I freeze and I go, what's happening? Two,
three, four? No. Is there a way to restart? Three, four. Undertale. Same scenario.
What the fuck? What the fuck? How many times have I done? What the fuck? I go, I go down to
my lowest form when I need to dedicate my entire brain power to something. If I was fixing a clock,
if I had a watch and I had all the tools and I was really concentrating with the little gears,
that's the same way. If somebody came to talk to me, if they were like,
hey, Jeremy, what the fuck? That's all I would do. And then I would look back down and go back to
work. I wouldn't be able to talk to that person. If you change any variables at all, what I'm
concentrating, you get like a one word statement. And then I have to go back to what I was doing.
Play Undertale again. I did play Undertale. Why did I say Undertale? Because the music,
it went like, it did that Undertale thing. Um, what do you mean? Listen, it goes,
watch, I'm getting question marks. I'll be quiet. Ready? Three, four, and
crazy. All right. Figure fighter is the latest in toy boxer technology.
Try him out in the ring for a few rounds. You'll be the tiny inflatable champ in no time.
LOL, LUL, omega, LUL, omega low, super mega low. Hiya, I'm what you call a muscle doll.
You'll notice right now I'm not so muscley. Check out what happens when you press A.
It's like I get pumped and macho just for the second the button is pressed.
That's, that's cool. So I'm going to punch a bag and I need to be macho at the right times.
Who comes up with this shit? This is so funny. Jab, jab, jab, jab. Let's try the old one too.
I've got rhythm, rhythm. That's from the Muppets. Ozzy and, uh, uh, rope, what's it,
Rolf the dog. They're, he's on the piano. Yes, it is. Did you say that's from Phineas and Ferb?
Fozzy Bear does that like 30 years ago. Did they take that from the Muppets? That's how dare they.
Go, go, go. Go, go, go. Go, go, go. Ozzy and Rolf the dog. No, it, I'm telling you,
keep pressing the buttons like that. We'll look it up. We'll look it up in a minute. Let's do this.
Please clap it. Hey, don't reset. Why not? I want to get it right. I have to, I have to do it right.
That was going to be a fail. Wait. Okay. Okay. I thought I couldn't skip this.
You would have gotten a great. I didn't deserve a great. You're supposed to fail.
One, two, one, two, and jab. I'll reset. One, two, one, two, and jab. Jab, jab. Wicked, bad nerd neck.
Jab. One, two. Come on. I'm going to have horrible nerd neck. Is this even worth doing? I got okay.
Fuck. Is this what you wanted? The fighters got potential. That's the first non-metal. I have to
get it right. I'll get it this time. I got an itchy nose too. I think that's quality.
Get a haircut. Why didn't you turn the face cam on? I wonder. Let's go. I'm ready. You're going to
see how I move when I, when I'm doing tutorials. Go. What? How was that wrong? Did I do it? I had
a water here, but I left it on the sidewalk and people were like ashing cigarettes in it all day.
I think water is still water though, isn't it? Oh, god damn it. I got a perfect on
screw bot factory right now. All right. I'll get it. Turn the light on in your room. No,
then it'll be too bright for me and I'll get my headache. All right. Perfect. Perfect only. Stop
waving your hair like a fucking weirdo. I know I'm on camera. That's why I'm doing it.
Keep going like this because I know people don't like my hair. Stop.
Still count? Can I still do it? Can I still do this or is it over? Okay. All right. Here we go.
Relax. Relax. Extreme bits. Somebody gave 5,000 bits. $50 from His Man. His Man? What's his name?
His Man, yeah. His Manny, yeah. That's 5,000 bits. Hello, Mr. 985. Consider this my yearly
German subscription payment. I can't watch the screen so I end up watching. I'm still using
Streamlabs OBS and they didn't update today and I fucking get stuck. And they made it so I can't
read this. No, it cuts it off. It's a mini feed. I never uninstalled Streamlabs OBS. Why would they
get rid of this? I used to be able to look over here in my Streamlabs OBS and it would just be
the message. Why did they get rid of it? Where is it? Use mustard. All right. What does it say?
Consider this my yearly German subscription payment. I usually can't watch the live streams
so I end up watching the vlog channel. Big up the stream archive. All right. Cool. While I eat and
cry over my university assignments, but thank you for every stream. These streams make everything
a bit more bearable. I look forward to watching this in a few days. Lots of love. Thank you.
Thank you. No one's ever expected to catch every stream. I know how, I know how it could be.
You know, some of these streams get long. They go up to six, seven, eight, 10 plus hours sometimes.
That's why I never, I can never expect anybody to do that. 13, especially playing the Lord of the
Rings. I have to get this. I don't care about the perfect eventually. He was doing better before he
went on cam because I can like smell you guys like looking at me. I need my, where's my lip balm?
I don't think it's even in here anymore. What do you smell like? Brand new plastic.
I can't do this one. I don't know. Why can't I? It's, it's like this light
fucks with my head. It's like when it goes and close my eyes and close my eyes and close my eyes.
Is that cheating? He's closing your eyes. Cheating. He's playing. Did I win? Nice combos.
You nailed the last part. Superb. Finally got a medal. I was, I was just feeling the music.
I was listening to you. All right. If you would have mute this zoom in on my webcam and put on
like Beethoven's symphony or something, it would probably match up a tiny new world champion.
That's me. Look at me. Remix three. Let's mix things up. This one's got lyrics because we
realized we hadn't tried that one yet. Why does Dermot look like a school bully? Go, go, go.
I feel like I'm fighting a sneeze during a theater production. You don't want to be the guy that
sneezes. Like when, when Romeo and Juliet drink the poison, you don't want to be the guy in the
middle of the death scene to be like. Yeah. Spoilers for Romeo and Juliet. That's a four,
500 year old piece of meat. Fuck dude. I haven't seen Romeo and Juliet yet. They've just made it
into a movie five times. It's been on Broadway for 700 years. Oh, and by the way, I read it in high
school three times, but dude, it spoiled it for me. You did well enough to make your stage debut,
but not good enough. Here we go. Spoiled Romeo and Juliet. All right, let's go.
My remote disconnected. That's, I know it's so easy for you to say that.
One, two.
It's so hard to press A over and over again when your fingers become covered in oil. Disgusting.
I'm covered in just water. Good enough? No. Oh, fucking come on. No, this is bad.
And the, okay, in the original Wiimote, the A button is in, is this like slick plastic.
It's a slick coating. It should be, it should be gripped. No, it's, it's, it's this really,
really shiny slick plastic button. That's gotta be good enough. I don't know. I look like the guy
that's at a party or that's at the wedding or that's at the club really, really, really wants
to start dancing, but he's not going to, may have had like two or three drinks already.
May be slightly inebriated. Really feel the music, but no, I'm not there yet. I did it.
You did well enough to headline a stadium concert. Well, look at that. Somebody redeemed a wink.
When? Wink redeemed? Did we get a wink? We did. Who did it? What do you want me to open? Yeah,
I know. I make fucking strange faces. I know. I see it. Who redeemed a wink? All right. All
right. All right. All right. It has to be full cam. You can see my cord. Did nobody redeem that?
I think I might have just got scammed. Hey, look, it's everybody's favorite. It's everybody's
favorite one. Live from ringside, we hear the champ's innermost thoughts and feelings after
the match. Here comes everybody's favorite one. The one that goes, whoa, you got big guy. I've
heard this one. This one, this is the best song in the whole game. Thanks for agreeing to do a
ringside interview. Let's rehearse a bit. No, it's like, whoa, you got big guy. It's, it's hard to
do. It's like, whoa, you got big guy. The voice is just, I think it's compression. Let's rehearse
a bit before we go on camera. When I ask a question, press A to answer.
Wow. Your answers were so eloquent. Let's move on. If I say something like you go big guy,
in quotes, that's a good time to show off. Press A twice quickly to show us what you got.
A twice. Here it comes. There it is. A twice. Oh, I get it. I get it. Whoa. One last thing.
When the photographers are ready, they'll want you to strike a pose. Really flex those muscles.
Press A and B together. Post for the fans. Yep. Pretty good. Thanks for your time.
Let's go. See you after the match. Live from the Rhythm Arena. Oh, look at how sweaty he is.
Yes. Sure. Yes. What a great song. I don't think it was perfect though.
Wrestler exudes confidence in wit and wrestler poses impressively. Oh no, that one's over.
Oh, no question or opponent is too tough for this guy. There's a lot of songs. How many songs are
there? If you get perfect on remix two right now, you'll get a gift. That's right. What were the
songs? This is the clock one. No, I don't know if we'll be able to do this. It's the clock. Well,
shit. I haven't done it in a while. I haven't done it. It's not happening. No, one more try.
I haven't done it in a while. Is that true? Whoa, you got big guy. I'm close. Whoa, you got. I'm
close. I'm actually close. Packing pests. Apologize for that. Do I have to apologize for doing every
single voice that's an animated character, an anime character? This is not even an anime
character. This is a video game character. Why does everybody get so upset about this?
Welcome to quality control. Product goes in the box. Anything else? Just knock it away. Let's
get to work. You have to say sorry. Apologize. Apologize. Apologize. Apologize. Welcome to
your training, new employee. Your main job here will be to sort product by clapping your hands.
Press A and B to catch. Let's move on. Do it again. All right. Get rid of the bugs.
Catch the candies. How could you not like it? Let's move on to the next technique. You'll
find the work easier if you get into rhythm. Pay attention to listen to the cues. One, two, three,
four. It's gonna be bad for me. It's gonna be bad for me. It's gonna be bad for me. I can
already tell. I'm gonna have to close my eyes on this one again. Just don't. It's the things on
the visual, the audios. It's just like it's scratching my head and rubbing my nose or whatever.
You know, I'm like, okay, it's B and then A and then B. Okay. Why did it do that? I don't see
a second nose. The visuals. Stop. Okay. I'm resetting. I know. I know. I know. Don't reset.
Stop resetting. Angry red face. It's the nose. Yeah. The nose is okay. I'm ready. I got it done.
See the nose already. What was that? That wasn't so bad. Don't look at chat. I'm not. I didn't look
at chat once. You're a master spider sputterer. Completely spider free. Well done. Well done.
Jeremy, you look nice today. I hope everybody reading this has a nice weekend. What a fucking
wonderfully nice thing to say about everybody in the chat. Nice work. Toys. Go check out the toys.
Oh shit. There are. There are toys. You're right. Police car. This toy is actually an
investigation tool. When you discover anything suspicious, communicate with your information.
Lieutenant, are you feeling better after that cold yet? You should look after yourself better.
Well, I guess we should start our investigation. I'm not confident in life. People hate that.
What was I going to do? All right. I don't get it. That's Shito. A? Maybe you got the code word
wrong. Try to think. It must be something you've seen. Music? Note? What do you mean something
I've seen? A nose? I mean, I've seen a nose. Does that matter? I've seen a nose. Try to think.
There must be something you've seen. Do I not have this info yet? Think. Cold? Cough? You knew
that was wrong. I know I was going to do do. I've seen a nose, you know, and everyone's going to go.
What the fuck? What are you doing? It's stupid. Fucking idiot. I'm going to go.
All right. What is the what? I don't get it. Radish. No, it's not. I'm getting out of here.
I can't leave it. I think I quit this. I have. Have you played a high hat before? I have. If you
have, this will be a cinch. If not, enjoy this opportunity to learn and grow as a person. Stop
acting. I don't get it. Four beat. Eight beat. Sixteen beat. Dermot, react harder. I can't hear
him. Can anybody hear him? Can anybody hear him? Can anybody hear him? Do something. React more.
He's a boring YouTuber. I haven't uploaded a video for like four years. I'm not even a
YouTuber anymore. I'm a Twitch TV partner. I don't like this new Dermot. All right. Let's go.
Did it wrong the whole time? Remember how cool this was? All right. Let's go. This one's called
Micro Row. Through the microscope, there's a whole other world. Yes, there is. Micro Row.
There's been selling out. I see you spotted us. Since you're here, you want to see our little march?
Press A in time with the voice to march in one step. Start to lose your voice there. Go! Okay.
Next, we'll try it without the collar. I mean, there's somebody still making noise.
Sounds like Elmo when you miss. I don't I didn't I don't recall. Next, we'll try going three steps
at once. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. We'll keep going like this.
That's it. Okay. It's captured wrong. Streams wrong. Recorded. What are you talking about?
I'm turning into. Oh, fuck. Hold on. I'm turning into like a copyright free image
of like an old person that doesn't know how to use a computer. Like, oh, capture crime. Capture
crime. Don't know. All right. That was good. I'm so confused. So am I. I'm actually not sure what
happened. No metal. An army of evil spirits has invaded a peaceful village. Only a lone samurai
can stop them. What dastardly deeds are they up to? The game glitched out. Yes. Press A to slice.
Oh, this one's fun. I already like this one. Yeah. Yeah. Right. Yeah. Okay. Impressive.
Samurai technique to lots of slicing. Hold A and B a moment to hold A and B a moment from a whirlwind
slice. It's okay. Oh, I sense a group of monsters lurking. Defeat them all at once with your
whirlwind earlier. Okay. Why am I getting hit by the last one? Is it? I'm not. Oh, I'm not. Okay.
Here we go. One, two, three. This song is fucking awesome.
Our story. What? Yay. My pinwheel. I'm getting it. The pinwheel. Fuck. Actually lost to pinwheel.
Actually lost to pinwheel. You sliced a lot of monsters and your sword moved so fast. Oh,
but still okay. Give me a break. I got almost all of them. I hear he's an okay samurai. I thought
I did it. All right. We're going to clean this up. Clean this up. That's embarrassing. Embarrassing.
Samurai slice. I can do it. He got hit by every whirlwind. But is that happening though?
I thought you guys said that wasn't happening. No, that's not happening.
You know, like the where are they now stuff. Where is that guy now? I wonder what that person is
doing. That's one of the most iconic screams used in every single video game, anything.
Got it. To be continued. Pinwheel boys. Gratitude. You sliced a lot of monsters through your sword.
So you got the pinwheel back. You got back the pinwheel. I got pinwheel back.
Thanks mister. You're the best. Thanks. That's weird. No practice. It's like there's something
in there trying to get out and talk. Like I just swallowed something or somebody and they're talking.
Like shut up. It's been a while since I've seen this. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I have to move. If I
don't move I can't do it. Like I have to snap. Snap. Snap. Snap. I have to be in the music.
Right now the ninja continues his secret mission. There's a whole nother row. All right. Let me do
that again. You get a perfect on tambourine right now. You know it's not going to happen.
Impossible for you to do that. No it's not. I can do it. Manka omega. Manka. Okay is it
Manka or is it Manka? Like Manka or is it Manka? I know how to do it. It's A in the Navy.
Get it right. Let's okay. Mix things up. Let's go. How many? Let's get relaxed. There are mountains
and a samurai must climb. My elbow. Okay that was pretty good. That was really great. Superb.
I have to move. I swear to god it helps. It helps. Right now the ninja has completed his mission.
What's with this Manka S? Manka S. Manka S. Manka S. I mean is it scary? Yes.
You can't even see it. Let's go. I mean people are gonna think it's fucking weird
out but like I have to actually do that. That helps. Catch of the day. If you come into the
stream for the first time and you see there's all the me doing this shit. I know but it actually
does help. This one sucks. Catch of the day. Let's go fishing. When the fish bites press A to set the
hook. The first fish you'll try to catch is the quick nibble. It's a B. Wait hold on. Oh okay.
Well done. Next the pause gill. Take a one breath break before setting the hook. It's kind of
tricky so I'll give you a Q. Without the Q. Oh let's try without the Q. Yeah let's go.
Just like that. Last the three fish. First we'll do it with the Q. Okay.
Oh this is disturbing. What's disturbing? Here we go. All right I messed it up.
Come do. Oh this one sucks. Okay.
I can't get any. I can't get any. I'm not even gonna pass. That's the I'm getting into the beat.
The visuals just fucking my head up. Try that again. Never rely on the visuals. Yeah but I mean
I'm looking over here. Okay try again. You missed that one. Try another. I will. The streamer said
the thing. I gotta bring out some of the references. Okay here we go. You. Not you. Don't do that.
Don't shut up. God. I'm gonna get it perfect every single time. Ready watch this. I'm not
gonna look at the screen. It's like the fish biting thing. I know it's cheating but don't
mind. What am I doing wrong? Okay fuck that one. Bitrate went down. All right.
Attention expedition team fall in. Are you ready to roll team? First press A. Attention company.
Nice. Look at how good they're doing. Let's try faster. Press A three times quickly. Okay.
Attention company. Now we'll try a flipper roll. A and B together. Okay.
Attention company. Oh I just heard somebody. What? This is the best one. This one seems really fun.
Are we ready? Let's see how you do with consecutive flipper rolls.
Just a little more. You can do it. I hope so. Attention company. Four flipper rolls.
Four. Three. Four. All right. Time to go. I'm kind of tangled up. This one has animation.
Attention. I'm turning into a fucking ping pong. What happened to his voice?
Oh he's counting. It's like somebody was just doing that like ice pick inside my ear into my
brain. Okay let's try it again. You're a terrible seal. Give me two more. All right I can do that
one. Oh baseball. It's just like the going back and forth like this. This. This. This. This. This.
At some point it's just like okay here we go. Fuck. One together. He's just counting. Hey I got it.
Superb. Let's roll. Give me the cheers. It's baseball time. I'm looking forward to this one.
Exhibition match. Okay Mr. Big Batting Hero. Time to show off your skills in an exhibition match.
Don't let anything get past you. All right this is gonna be fun. I love the support.
Let's take a look. Baseball. Let's practice before our big exhibition match.
All you have to do is hit the ball when I pitch it. You might want to count to yourself to get
the timing right. Wait. What? What kind of baseball? I thought it was gonna be fast.
I gotta hold on. I'm gonna count myself. It goes. Ow my face. All right get to the real match.
Oh by the way there are no cues in the real thing. Of course they're not.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I do it. Monkey umpire's call. You had a nice solid swing there and you get even with audio cues.
Monkey was behind it the whole time. You won't see that one again. Almost. Yeah I missed one.
That was cool. Block step. Coming up. It's amazing to see so many birds migrating together.
Of course to avoid stepping on each other's toes they'll need good rhythm.
All right. Yes. Yes. Yes. Block step. Is this a pretty popular one it seems from the audience?
I don't think I've ever heard this song. No I've seen this song with the birds. Okay let's march
together. Have I heard this song? Press A to the B. Why am I desynced? I shouldn't be desynced should
I? Let's get tricky. You need to press A and B. Hold A and B to get ready then release to jump.
That's it. Okay let's go. The flock is waiting. Where am I? Oh fucking smash.
Wait which one am I? I can't. I can't take. I don't know who you're calling. I don't know who you are.
You're the golden one. This bit rate is dying because of this. I failed it for sure. I failed
it for sure. Yeah whatever. I don't care. I'll do it again. That one's fun. Good enough apparently.
Let's do it again. Do it again. That one was fun. I'll get it this time. Perfect. Long road ahead.
I got left behind. You get a perfect on fighter figure fighter right now. Oh yeah I can do that.
Absolutely easy. Easiest thing I've done all night. All day. It's like a football in the afternoon.
What do you guys think of these early streams? You like them? Oh this is not the one I thought it was.
I thought this was um I thought this was the the flex one. I'm not gonna be able to do this
but I'll try. Once I fuck the first one up. Omega long loser. Okay here we go. That's gotta be good.
You stuck it to the end. Stuck it out to the end. Oh okay I messed up like once.
I screwed it up only one time. How did I do that wrong? Really? That's sad. I messed up way more
than once. No I didn't. I bounced back and forth like twice. Maybe. You were ahead of beat the whole
time. Was I? No I wasn't. Hopping and I'm not paying attention. It's down. Foot. Foot. Foot. Foot. Foot.
Foot. You have to hold A. You have to go A. A. A. A. A. Okay I get it. I'll get it this time.
Let's mix things up. No practice. Oh remix five. Is he okay? Oh it's got fish in it. The fish.
I can't do it. I can't do the fish. I can't do it. The fish just fucked up everything for me.
It's that like half. You were eaten by a t-rex. All right. I didn't mess up the baseball. Yeah
because I mean I know how to do that one. I might need to practice the fish. No I don't. It's three
seconds. One. Two. Three. Go. I just did it. I fucking did it. But you're nunchuck away. Right. Okay.
Yeah I guess that makes. Yeah that makes sense.
Just get it. I have to get it.
One. Two. Three. Go. Two. Three. Go. Three. Go. Three. Go. All right. Come on. That's got to be enough.
All you guys say no. If you were a dinosaur you'd be a high flying
Pteranodon. Check the new toys. This game's a lot of fun. I'm really happy I played this.
Rhythm fighter. Use rhythm in a new way to knock out an opponent. This game requires two
Wii remotes. Launch party. Countdown to launch. Or rather countdown to launches. Quite a few of them
in fact. Okay. I can't believe I was holding that fucking nunchuck the whole time. Welcome aboard
our space station. The job here will be to help us launch the rockets. Just hit A when the countdown
reaches zero. Good job. Here's a different model of rocket to try. Does he have a safety strap on?
Nope. This one doesn't require moving. There's a new one. I gotta memorize these. They're gonna
throw them. It's gonna be all messed up. They're gonna mess it all up on me. Let's do exactly that
for the real mission. Good luck. Congrats on your successful launches and you stayed focused amid
distraction. Made contact. Yes we have. You look like the person in the orchestra that makes the
gestures. The yellow webcam is a little fucked up isn't it? It's all you get. Perfect on working
dough right now. You'll get it. I'll try it. Has he gotten it perfect on anything? Yeah. A couple
times no. All right let's go. A and then A B for the big ones. This one's hard to explain. Just focus
on switching between the two rhythms. You'll get the hang of it. Comes dunk dunk. Hey guys let's
get ready to do that thing we do. Let's warm up before we go. No injuries please. Press A in the
time to the signal. This is hard to explain. Just do it. That's the way. Haven't lost the magic yet.
How about this one? Let's try mixing up both rhythms. The rhythm changes after you hear
dunk. Let's go do that thing we do. So it's dunk then we.
I'm so glad he's having so much fun. He clearly felt the driving rhythm video. The
celebrated rhythm was spot on. Also you kept up with the changes.
Nothing can stop us now. That was pretty fun. That was a good one. How many more games are there?
Let's see, we got five, right? Five in a row.
Five, ten, fifteen, twenty, twenty, thirty, thirty-five, so far, coming up here.
Bumper, it's the grease. That's what I just did.
That's when Bilbo grabs the ring.
Primitive people played a lot more primitive volleyball than most people realized.
Also, their music was pretty sophisticated.
Oh god, this one. Let's go around this one.
Why hello there. Shall we practice our bumping skills together?
Press A to bump away things that fly at you.
That was great, you really nailed it.
Why don't we switch? You can try out my side.
Ready?
Let's try switching midstream.
Great hands.
You did great. Let's go try the real thing.
Let's go.
Foam!
I just went right in the head.
I didn't say that.
They did.
Tips from the Valley Girl.
Volley Girl.
Nice bumping technique and switching was no problem for you.
Superb.
Perfect couple.
Pro Bumper.
Love rap.
Love, it's the most powerful feeling in the world.
And there's no better way to express it than through the ancient art of hip-hop.
Let's rap.
Follow me.
Is that how I talk?
Oh, okay.
Hopefully we can do it at the same time.
Keep it going.
I like this one. This one's fun.
I like your flow.
Let's go.
Something else.
Let's rap again.
Okay.
So he's choking!
Can somebody save this guy?
I hit it right at the end of the song, okay.
Why was it so high?
How about this?
I did it wrong.
I got it.
Okay, I got it.
Just delete the right wrapper.
There's another thing to try.
Why is my desk so hot?
I'm gonna f**k myself up.
You all about you all about you all about you all about you all about you all about you
All right, this is gonna be weird. It's gonna take so long for the real thing. Yeah, it is
I'm gonna mess this up probably ten times in a row. Here we go. It's different timings for each one
Crazy into you crazy into you crazy into you crazy into you
All about you
She changed the beat into you into you
Only turned it off. I don't think I liked it. We're all about you're all about you. Ah
Ah, that's too bad it comes a sneeze. How do I get out? I get it? I can stop how do we I?
Got I think I focus on my face
Boogers all of me. I think I'm all right. This is why I don't do thank you. We good
I'm so paranoid. This is like this is not somewhere on my face like in my hair. I
Need a mirror. I can't turn it back on at least unless I know
It could be like that could be like a stray booger in my hair
I don't do that one again
Not bad
All right, we're in remix six, let's mix things up this one's carnival themed I'll take you back to your youth unless you're still there
Remix six. Ah
No practice. Ah, it starts off with this
I
Got timing
Okay, that was tricky that was a train wreck well, I mean
You gotta see once or twice before you know, one of the things that happens
Your skill was a business trip you'd miss a meeting down the hall
They left hairline. What about it? I think it looks pretty good
I'll be 30 goddamn five in
2020 this is looking pretty good for three five
Now, excuse me. I've got some donk donks to take care
Crazy
You get a purpose on remix for right now yellow no, I like it. Yes, brother. I'm trying to do remix six
You are the mule
Booger face Billy
Fuck
Nailed it I didn't get okay
I think that I think a lot of people are misunderstanding when I do the remixes
It's you can't it's hard to have rhythm when you have to play seven different songs that intercut into each other
That's like if you have a guitarist that's on stage and he's playing song one and then in the middle of the song
the lead singer goes
song
Four song on the album and that's why we and he's just like fuck is happening. Why are you doing this?
Okay, they're gonna go song four on the album
You don't think it's mid song
How are you supposed to do that?
Sorry, you've had it remixes Jeremy. I just got a gold star on that one called medley
Fucking water you're aware games. This is not like me having a guitar in my hand
Yeah, you know, I just don't think he has very much medley
Playing the Mario where micro games that go one two, three. What does it go?
All right, here we go. This is called tap group
The taps on his shoes and boxes on their heads this quartet of dream is stardom. We understand the task of the head boxes
Time to tap. Let's start with basic stepping in sync with one another
Was me all right
Okay, so that's pretty simple. I'm we're gonna add the net. Let's try mixing up the rhythm slightly
Listen closely to the rhythm
Patterns on ready
Three taps, okay, let's try that again, but a bit shorter this time
Even shorter
Let's that's it I think we're ready are we all right show time everybody break a leg I wasn't ready I wasn't ready
I wasn't ready. I wasn't ready. I wasn't ready. I wasn't ready. I wasn't ready
It was I was thinking about how I have to go to the bathroom. I have to go to the bathroom
I gotta go to the bathroom
Long
Back. Oh, no about a step. He didn't put his leg back. He didn't put his leg back
He didn't like put his leg back. Oh, they're huge friendly feedback. Yeah, good enough. I gotta pee
We're back
We did it didn't we? Let me get this off
Okay, I
Can do that I can do that one better. I can do that one better
Tap tap tap tap tap tap tap
You know what pretty game like this online multiplayer
And everybody's on the screen
Amazing nice fail nerd. I respect your opinion and I respect you being mean to me
But I'm not gonna take it
Get him out of here. All right, ah still okay what I only messed up once I messed up one time
That was that bad
Shrimp shuffle
Shrimp make surprisingly good dancers and will jump at the chance to show off their skills try not to bump into anyone
Shrimp. Oh, no
Seizure warning here. Is there where the shrimp?
Camper is a low tide dance troop
Take a deep breath wait
Is it actually like a seizure warning here? We specialize in synchronized dancing like a chorus line
You know what? Let's just show you
That's tricky. All right. Next we really show off our cool dance moves
You'll hear ABC on C press A and B
This is truly the worst one let's mix it up and shift the rhythm a little bit game sucks
You've lost your damn mind. What are you on? What the hell are you on? When we give the signal pause for a moment?
I
Alright, no, no, no, I need it to like pause and then start over because it's like it's fucking blending together my brain
This one's tricky actually is he's so into it. Yeah, I have to you have to get really into it
If you if I don't lock in and just right I can't be like so
What are you guys saying lately? Three two one eight B and C. I
What time no, I can't I have to focus. I
Can't speak
Cheer readers come it up, you know who doesn't get enough support people studying at the library
Let's cheer these dedicated students on
To a silent stream is kind of what this one is for the school library pep squad
We help people study with inspiring Cheers
time for practice
Follow our lead and press a to flip your book
Lower right next pattern. Let's go. This is like a different version of Cheers to you
All right, not bad, but we've got a little more practice to do
Rissoum baboom
rissoum baboom
Our most difficult stunt we all do this one at once. So get ready
A and B and then release
Carol you're off the team great work team. Now, let's get out of here and cheer
Where am I?
Let's go read a bunch of books, let's go read a bunch of books
Okay, it's on
All right, it's it's on i'm gonna lose it, but I had to say it will do it
You just embarrassed the team
You fell to pieces near the end. What was the whole thing? Let's go read a bunch of books
You keep it down the osc is really good the game is really good, too
All right, here we go you're never gonna get to regionals here we go focus
That's gotta be good enough for uh, at least it's uh, superb
I let I screwed up. I once was twice maybe he kept in sync where it counted got it
So you have a mullet
No mullet is my hair is longer in the back than it is in the front
No, I don't have a mullet behind my head
Mullet, but it's just going back behind the ears
emo peter parker
You get perfect on forklifter. I could probably do it
I was all right with this
You have seen kid hair
Just that hair that goes back behind my ears
Here we go
Whoa, I almost missed the last one. All right, good. Perfect. Perfect forklift. You've run a gift listed in the cafe
There are 48 gifts left. Let's go check it out. Read something partners. I want my wiimote back. I want my wiimote back
Give me my wiimote back
Okay, what's it called? It's music listen to music. Oh, okay
Forklift there it is
Uh
Karate man
This is karate training at its most intense
Punch the flying objects and go crazy when a whole mess of them come at you
This one's like this one's a gamer level
I'm just trying first. Let's get warmed up
A to punch the objects flying your way
Pow time for some combos a and b together to do a combo
Let me combo hold a and b then release
Okay, so the punch is the uppercut is the last one
And smash some stuff
Attach your combo to the rhythm and hit everything
Are your knuckles ready for a challenge for this song the hedgehog song?
I get it
That one's fucking awesome, okay, i'll redo it omega lull omega lull omega lull we got a lot
We got a mega lows everywhere
Every nice guy has a dark side
All right, let's go
Plus two to the discord users
All right, let's do it. No more fucking around on beat
Stop messing up. It's hard. It's all come on
Where are my keys? They're there. Okay, let's go. Come on. Go go go go go go. All right. No resetting. I don't care
No resetting
Holding and then releasing it is like, ah, I keep the whole thing going on the go. Hey, god damn it. It's hard
Did it? Okay, I had to just lock in completely
Oh, I know and I missed too many of them
Getting
Uh, sorry, we'll go back to it. Where's my head?
It's the flying shit. Whoops. My belt came undone
Remix seven
Let's mix things up. It's gonna take you straight to outer space
Number seven
It's wait on oh, I thought it was I don't know we were starting
I
Have to completely I have to focus I have to like go I kept it for your vacation for careful rain
Turns into job with a hut
Come on, I can do it. All right, I got it
I do better when I do this ruin the joke. I'm just trying to all right. I get it right now. This is the one
Oh my god, what the fuck happened? Okay. I'm doing a trick going to here we go. I'm actually
Hey
For your vacation aim for rhythm heaven that's the quietest he's ever been I just yeah kind of I did it
Hey, congratulations on clearing remix seven
Well done. Not everybody gets this far
There are still a lot more games you can play
But why not take a break basking the glow of your achievement?
Maybe you'd like us to introduce the folks who made the game
Game
Just imagine each of them giving you a high five
We'll also introduce the characters from different games
You can reminisce about the good times you had with them
Can I do anything?
Is there a rhythm in this I beat it?
All the characters I missed to the correct end
Now
100 percent rhythm heaven fever cast. Let's see. We have the reddit guy monkey golfer mandrill
the robots
See and saw
A boy is crushed the re the weasel couple
Old the fork who could forget the force performance the executives in the assistant small monkeys
Oh, because the watch right?
The dough dudes, that was my favorite. I love the dough dudes dough dudes are probably number two
But who do you guys think is my number one favorite character in the game?
It ain't either one of these two
Two great characters not them
Not they don't it's not the wrestling
No, not samurai
Not suspicious close close the hubris of happiness of my favorite characters
uh these guys
Pasa and nova and then love pussies featuring mc dour
call tamper
the shrimp scampers
These are all great little league team names
Okay
arati joe
And then i don't I blow we didn't talk once
Marshall and miss ribbon for playing that was a lot of fun
I know that it's not over
I know
That was fun
Game doesn't end here. See I knew it
You unlock some extra games. These are sure to satisfy diehard fans
And you unlock the credits game nice box
Okay
extra game
End is another list
No, let's check out the extra games
I don't even know all perfect i'm gonna get all perfect samurai slice two
Farther than ever they've been before pursuing the evil spirits. I just I feel like this is gonna be fucking hard
I need medals
You don't get practice
What's happening? Hey
What?
All right. Was that good enough?
Was that good? Was that good enough?
Funny man's gratitude sliced a lot and you got bunny back a medal
It was good enough
Thank you. That was a very important bunny
Nice
Working dose two
Now hold on every bunny is important to go back to the cafe for a second. Hold on
Can I talk to the priest now?
Oh nice to see you
Oh, hey, hey, wait, what'd it say? How do you perfect? I'm gonna say i'm impressed
Keep it up. I'll be thinking about you between customers, of course
I didn't mean to hit. Hey, I got the itchiest nose on earth
I really think I might if I was tested I'd go
All right, you mostly gotten used to this job with your co-worker that guy's in shame try to keep up no practice itchiest nose on twitch
The bad meme you requested. Hold on. Hold that thought
You're not gonna distract me with this bullshit. Now. That is perfect. Is it more didn't miss one elegant work. You're an artist
If you keep it up, even when it got by it
Why can't I do it when?
Tea tastes better on the moon
Remember you have scary eyes
Sorry
Sorry, that's scary eyes
Let me go back to
What does it take?
A 35
Okay built to scale two pick up the pace what about your high quality of widgets has gone viral
Skipping and then replacing words. I don't understand built to scale two. Is there built is it free?
Let's go
Don't do this to me. It's so slow
Uh, oh fuck. I don't think it was enough. It may have been close, but I don't I don't think it was enough. Oh
No, it was
Got through today's award quickly and assemblers was off deep for them. Well, also the high speed widgets were solid
Finished early. I want to get to at least 35. No
Double date two
A romantic date to a farm getting close to nature. What's so wrong?
Fuck is this dermis symphony? Wait, hold on. Hold on to that song is too slow songs too slow
Start it over too slow stupid balls
I just want to like tear my rib cage open. All right, we're good
Got it. No emotion for the rat. I mean, yeah, this this is a no talking stream. All right, let me what's this video?
Let me see what it is
I got the medal good together forever. Isn't that cute?
Is it like a super remix now?
Yeah, it's remixed eight. Okay. Hold on
All right, so um, let's play this this is called dermis symphony
This is fucking stupid
Yeah
Back to it back to it
He hates his fans
What do you mean? He hates his fans
Remix eight has the what do you mean? He hates his fans. What is there another one? How many of these you guys make?
This is called germa when nobody's looking
You could put anything here
Oh
What the fuck that's katamari
Apologize i'm not apologizing for that. I'm i'm not sorry about that. I didn't do it
Okay, let's go back to this
Back to remix eight
This is currently the hardest remix in the entire game. This one's set to a song about
Unrequited love trying to play through the tears
Is
They clap for me I demand it clap for me I demand it clap for me I demand it here we go
I love you my one and only
Is
Okay, that's fucking hard
Gonna need another try that one. Yes
You were as good as a broken guitar string
Sweat
You should listen in stereo
I think I did pretty good though. Okay, good enough. You have my neck crack
You're as good as a competent rocker
It's okay
But I need to get gold medals on every single gosh darn it game. This is a lot more
How much more is in the game
How much how much more?
love rap 2
Love as always we must turn to the only true method of expressing its hip-hop. No practice
It goes up to 10
It goes to 10. All right, let's go
Light the candles
Starting
Show
Crazy into you
Fun show
All about you
What
About you
Weird
Into you into you all about you all about you
It hurts something weird something weird, what are you all about
Somebody wrote that
Hey, thank you
Thank you. Um
lord of destruction
41 I appreciate that you did pretty well if you try and thanks that that means a lot. Thanks for stuff
Appreciate it, dude
Oh, I got a perfect I don't think I can do it I focus on this shit
He thinks he's dreaming that your second earbuds causing problems on this one
All right, stop looking over here into you into you
Fun show
Into you
Crazy into you crazy into you crazy into you
Crazy into you
Fun show
Into you
Crazy into you
All about you
God damn it
Into you
Crazy into you
All about you
Okay, it's the faux show the faux show is is a little like a hair quicker. I think I got it
Did I get it? No, I didn't
Wow
Wow, wow, wow, wow, I got it. This is very good. All right lame guys are pretty lame. All right. Hold on
Lean back. All right lean back time. It's it's turtle time
Turtle time works. It really does
Crazy into you crazy into you
Into you into you
Fun show fun show
Faux show
Into you
I hate these ones
Ah go go go go go go go
Fun show into you
Into into you
Into you
All about you.
No, oh sure crazy into you all about you
This shit slaps
This is such an old embarrassing reference, oh this is some fucking embarrassing reference, okay
This is embarrassing. Hold on Irma in his car
I
Need to pay attention to the road. Oh my fucking god
The lost art. All right, yeah, that's
What a thing to bring out right now. All right, if you don't know I it was okay TLDR. I was I
had a CD in my car and I was driving some people and
What do you got for music?
Classical music and it was it I had I didn't I had a video game OST in the fucking CD player and it's a TLDR
Just huge TLDR. Um, I put this song was just playing and nobody thought it was cool
They were just silent and I'm just sitting there going
Oh, this is the music that I really think is cool. It's a video game OST inside the CD player
That was like, oh what's on the radio?
And it was this song I mean this let's be really honest here this song is fucking fantastic
This is one of the best battle musics ever. It's too bad. That game was like a 7 out of 10
It was like a 7.2 out of 10 and I wish they made another one because it would have been cool
But it was a good was pretty good game, but the song is like a 10 out of 10
It's the battle music The Lost Odyssey
Here it again
No more no more of these
I already know what it is
Okay, okay turn it off
Turn it off
Turn it off, turn it off
What is this on discord? What are you doing?
What are you doing?
You're scaring me
This is so fucking stupid
Imagine listening to that shit
Back to the fucking game
No, the other one. What do you mean the other one?
Okay, why do I
Why do I look
No, no, no, no, no, no
Don't play that again
Why do I look
Like every YouTuber
You've ever seen
Every YouTuber
Turn it off
Turn it off, turn it off, turn it off
No, I have to stop playing
Alright, you know what I mean?
I don't know why my face
The way that my face is shaped
The eyes, the mouth
I don't know, it's a combination of everything
I'm like every YouTuber I've ever seen
I feel like this is YouTube thumbnails
That's like a
This one's better
How do you still have these?
I already showed that one
Do the other one
I just showed it
I just showed that one
I just put that on screen
This is not already another one, right?
Are you really going to put that in here after all this?
That's where you're going after this?
That's where you're going
That's what you're doing
Alright, you've killed it
You've slayed it
You killed it, now let's go
You've actually killed it
You killed it
Oh, super golf
Okay, what the fuck
The monkey was very impressive
Super
Perfect score
First try
That's a golden medal
We've only got
And then we've got one more
Row
We have done it
God, so
Again, by the way, Community Content Day
That's right, it's Community Content Day
Community Content Day
Is going to be tomorrow afternoon
Tomorrow morning, probably around 11-ish
11.30, 12
12-ish
No, no, no, no
It's going to be
1?
1pm?
Hold on, let me think about this
1pm tomorrow is going to be
Community Content Day
And
It's going to be split into two
Because there's going to be a lot
Because I delayed it because
There's a million reasons why
I was going to do the Green Screen DLC free
That didn't work out
So we're going to split it into two days
One next week for a short amount of time
And then one next week for a short amount of time
There you go
That's the plan
Robot Factory 2
How long are you going to do EU-friendly streams?
Oh, it was only these two days
Shit, breaking it next
We're good
Could have been better
That's alright
Here's where we store the robot's sense of duty
Remix
We're going to get a perfect on samurai slice right now
You can't mess up two times
If you mess up once, it's just fucking over
Remix, here we go
I didn't, I know
It's head-surfing
Holy fuck
Ban, then mod
Then ban, then mod, then mod him twice
Then VIP him, then delete his account
And then send him a hundred
I can't say that
Hello
Hello, a hundred, hello
Times that by ten
I was going to say
Disconnected from the last statement
The word I was going to say was money
Okay
Read a lot of books
What the fuck am I doing?
I just looked over at the preview and I don't like that
Level nine
Pepe lap, try again
Pepe lap
It's on
A feet
I fucking don't like that
Segment
Good enough, I got it
Because you suck
I don't want to say that because then you'll use it
And you'll make me look like I said I think German
Alright, here we go
We're almost there
Take your fighter two
The last five games
Then
I'm out of here
Night walk for the final remix
Do I?
I can do better than that
Let me rephrase this
Keep your guard up
Hold on, let me rephrase this one
Let me rephrase this
Here we go again
Okay, let me rephrase this one
I don't even know the timing in this
Whatever, we don't take your fighter two
Oh, he's so close to remix ten
I am, I'm getting there
Am I supposed to punch there?
I don't think that's going to do it
It is
What?
You don't do like a hailstorm of punching if it's not correct
Why is there a bite mark on my arm?
Micro wall two
Unbelievable, the microbes are back
Can you believe it?
I already know the practice, I know how it works
I don't know how to fly
Is that enough to pass it?
He's so high
Good enough, okay
Whatever
I'm literally wearing jogging pants
There's no flight
What are you talking about?
For some research, this could be big
Oh no, packing pests too
We doped up on contrast
Okay, here we go
You still remember your training, right?
Sort of
I thought that wasn't a lot of practice
That's your punishment for not doing the Japanese audio
You want me to do Japanese audio?
Japanese audio?
That actually was an issue
It is, it is
Not bad
Alright, time to really see what you're made of
See what you can do with this new rhythm
Nicely done
Japanese audio is better for the love rap
I could see that
That would make sense
What happens when we give you an offbeat rhythm?
You watch out for the signal, you'll do fine
What was the one with the wubba lubba dub, is that true?
That's the wrestler one, we did it already
I wonder if there's a second part of it
I wonder, good luck with your overtime shift
On the ring side
Here we go
That's Gerba, they put Gerba in the game, it was Gerba
That's Gerba, that's Gerba 95, you ever heard of that guy?
Johnny Joe's intense training regimen continues
Can you help him reach the height of mastery?
No practice
This is going to be
Pretty hard
I would take a guess
Bring it on
And me got a problem at this point
Just like, that's bullshit
Be back here
It's just fucking
The console will never take off by the way
This console is going to be dead in the park, dead in the track
There's no way this console will take off
There's no way this console sells like
100 billion units
Nice throw, I didn't throw
I just didn't expect it
That was probably pretty good
You tried, and you still got it
Okay, whatever
It's just the end, I fucked it up
Let's focus my power and re-tie my belt
Okay, how many medals do I have?
I need one more medal with me
Remix 10
Let's mix things up
This one will test you on everything you've learned
It's pretty tough
Finally what?
Let me get this first guy
I'm going in
I will tell all about you
All about you
I think I made it
Friendship means meeting new people or snails
I can do that
Fucking, this needs simple, simple, simple
Simple, simple, simple
It's just
I can do that
It's just 3, 4
Boom
Bring it on
That was not a POG, that was a
Go
i guess i didn't do it i gotta i gotta fucking steal the music on this i'm gonna get i gotta get
so into this just turn it up i'm turning it up i'm turning it up i'm turning it up i'm just
warning you i turned it up fucking go turn it down turn it down turn it down it's too loud it's too
loud it's too loud turn it on it's way too fucking loud start again
i don't do well with loud music i don't i swear to god
okay that's fine a little bit louder this is the one i'm gonna smash something
i all right i don't i haven't even got this i haven't even got to see that one to be completely
honest with you but i got i haven't i got a broken that's why i can't explode it's too loud it's too
loud it's too loud it's too loud it's too loud it's too loud it's too loud it's turned on
that's just like my head just boom like those old movies with our like that blood got to their
head explode that's i wish that not a sweat would be a color you know what i mean because it would
just be like green paint stupidest fucking game in this whole game
close no i'm saying it just saying it just saying it it's not it it was over it was over at the very
beginning it was over the very i should just click right now it was over at the very beginning
i've if you hit like if you miss it like fucking if you miss i've missed all the fishes
all the fishes which by the way worst minigame of the whole game i don't know i don't like it
i don't like it i don't like it i don't like it all right here we go if i don't beat this one i will
figure it out
so
this is the one this is the one this is the one this is the one this is the one this is the one no
omega choke this that's someone has to that's got to be the one that's got to be it that's got to be
it i have to be come on i had it i i did better i'm doing better i'm getting better i'm getting
better am i crying no i've just got i've got watery eyes i've played like four concerts already
oh angry jeff you see that you see that button right there how it's made out of the most slippery
fucking plastic note man you see that button you see that shiny plastic ass fucking a button
it's like especially when it's like the one two three four like one two three four five six seven
like i can slide off the fucking god
pressing the wrong buttons here pressing the wrong buttons here albertson all right time no
fucking around i'm done let's go this is it i'm doing right now this is the hardest
level in the whole game and i how can i not
okay
that shit makes no sense doesn't make any fucking sense
i'm so tilted right now that that walking along the path doesn't make any fucking sense
that walking like that what i have to hold ab i never did didn't do that in the credits
i didn't have to hold ab in the credits oh this one this is so hard so wait hold ab when there's
two right next to each other i didn't what do you mean it didn't play the credits what do you mean
the auto credits the auto credits what are you talking about i 100 percent of that what
delete it i'm tilting i'm on full tilt
it's it's taking over oh it's like 40 fucking minigames in this game this is the only one
that's this much of a problem all right all right all right all right i want to play the shitty one
i want to play the shittiest thing i've done the worst thing i've ever done in 10 years
i shit my pants at school like within the last 10 years and this is worse than that
i don't even want to see the score this shit is so hard that what do you mean this what what is
this i wait wait wait wait wait wait wait what is this save it what do you mean he's what do
you mean oh my god he's gonna see
that was saved for some reason okay
wait wasn't this already in didn't we already see this we've seen this
now i get it this makes way more sense now
you're doing so much better than i am
remember does mvm i don't know what this is but no all right that was a pretty good all right
that's a pretty good break let's go it's time to do this i'll get the fish part let's get
fucking pay attention but it is hard to pay you know i'm saying i gotta get back to do this i can't
let rhythm heaven fever i can't have back-to-back fucking meltdown screen they need like three
months in between all right here we go
he's crying i'm not crying i'm just emotional that has to be it i fucked the whole section up
it has to be it please be it i don't can i miss it anything but do you have to get 100 on this
level it's the seals the seals are different it's like when he's like like you're counting faster
this sucked i got two out of three all right i'm trying this one more time i'm gonna practice
seals
oh my god where's that seal level good gold medal on this stupid ass seal level where is it
fuck is it i don't know where it is i have no idea where is this level that's tambourine
somebody help me please oh i can't i can't fucking believe i haven't done this yet i can't believe
this is this hard god damn it so what am i doing wrong i think it's the dink dink dink because i
can't really hear it i can't hear it over the music is it going like it's like one two three
right because it goes like i don't think i'm getting the dink dink dink
okay that's the problem that's the problem figure the problem out it's that like bink bink bink
all right that's good do i dare try to do fish levels no
okay it's like it's like a half step i just it's it's i i can't even practice it because it's just
that tap tap tap tap you know what i mean oh it's the way the transitions from the last game
slow down yeah yeah i'm sorry my fucking scream is broken my scream is broken oh my
hey it's getting out of my ear the moon landing this the world's famous clappy trio never misses
a beat you're the third in line to just keep an eye on what the other here do
where the clappy trio nobody claps like us you do the third clap okay sweating just like that
speed it up show time they're all like looking over at me like how long has it gone for your
synchronization sounded great superb all right let's um seven hours hey i came under the limit
though everyone said i was gonna hey the time to beat this member was like oh dude this is a
10-hour game look at it okay no they said eight yeah it's an hour and a half i beat the game an
hour and a half ago all right what do i not have i can't do it on that no i don't want to do it
again what am i what are we going to have roti van give me the gold i can get gold on this
one more floor step on core baby credits i want to see the other minigame then i'm done
so
the hype train well that's impossible what
why is there a hype train right now it's only been six and a half hours this is impossible
welcome back to the hype train welcome back to the scam train
guys i don't even got a gold medal on it oh here it is okay it's it's still going down
i got endless games before you quit what time is it six o'clock uh okay i got a little time
the perfect evening for a night time stroll pretty simple but let's practice it first day
we're almost at level three level two here's the basic hop yeah press a
okay this dude is scaring he's scamming his audience this is a total fucking scam he's scamming
everybody release to do a big jump level three hype train hype train completed what the fuck
no way all right but no no no it's gonna be like oh ladies gentlemen we are got four minutes and
34 seconds until the hype train is done get on that train and get there you can make it happen
get on that train my train here it comes that's people doing right i do that too get the echo in
there yeah i can't no i'm not fucking around with this thing well that's too bad
yes
oh five thousand bits in the hype train let the train leave the station
oh dude are you getting on the
fucking stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop this is out of time this shit's out of it
let's go boys yeah no no no
yo let's go boys level four levels for a hype train let's go let's fucking go how close are we
level five something pretty fucking cool i guess yo 14 you guys are fucking killing it nice work
somebody gave 50 but somebody just gave fucking by lacquerie by lacquerie wow while i make fun
of the hype train you're not supposed to make the hype train leave the station but the hot
train just left the station everybody hype train dance jeremy dance all right man hype train
all right i that's a you gave like 100 subs by lacquerie gave five thousand bits and then they
gave 69 sub well we did it again we you fell in a hole how do they how do you game over it
we did it again oh we we we did it we i didn't do anything you know what i mean like oh we
we did it guys you and me we hype trained i didn't do anything all right here we go
here comes the scam train all right skip i'm gonna beat this thanks for the hype train guys
okay i got a increasing difficulty as of tomorrow and here we go thanks for a huge amount of fucking
money for lacquerie seriously even more stuff
all right nothing on tv today
sing now
you know when you sing along with the song and you have headphones in and you're the song is louder
than you are that's how you can tell if somebody can really sing it out because when they sing along
they're singing like they can't really realize that there are people you can't i can't hear
anything you know what i mean so when you sing along with a song that first of all like i'm
speech jamming myself with the song so when you sing along with a song if somebody has
the earphones in and the earphones are loud and they're singing along they typically sound like
you can tell if somebody can really sing enough because they they all right i know what i can't
explain this i could have but i can't all right when somebody has loud music playing and is
singing along to it somebody has loud music playing and is singing to it if they're singing very
poorly they don't know that they're singing poorly so you can hear all their voice practice
shit and they don't know that you can hear that for some reason i think i got it i feel like i was
just doing that kim call the call the hospital grandma do you smell toast
yeah actually hey it's been a long day what are you talking about somebody i
seven hours of staring at a screen dancing i've been conducting an orchestra for seven hours
i'm getting this one everybody we're gonna end it with
walks down and we'll try endless i gotta go that was cool did you see that
i train little five i'm done i can't do this anymore i'm gonna have
not done until we say you're done why am i all right i'll see you i'll see you tomorrow
did i get the gold medal wait no no no no no there's one more minigame to play
then i want to play it feels so good to belong 36 right no i don't want to put the extra games
38 to the fish level no i refuse but what's an endless oh shit i didn't even see these
wake up caller i didn't see these i'm gonna see them wake me up with an alarm okay
wake me up at 8 a.m. it's a when the clock exactly is it eight o'clock
three two one go one two three
wake up
well done but can you do it when you can't see the clock
three two one go one two three
get up
try a different rhythm eight thirty oh shit we can do eight thirty three two one two three four five
six seven eight
can't count omega lull it's easy when you know the secret i'm counting on you for a perfect night's
sleep maybe about eight
what time is it eight o'clock exactly
flower this takes a while that night like with a ten i can do ten three two one two three
i don't know why i'm doing this to you for some reason but i am like it's i'm doing it to you
if i get five in a row then i get the all the flowers right
banana cream pie why the fuck did you say that what a dick what a dick because now is all i care
about okay three two one go two i eat thirty i eat thirty i eat thirty
first big greasy pepperoni pizza on a delicious boston pizza six a.m. three two three i feel like
i'm entertaining children you know what i mean i that was not early other people that just said
dad i want you to delete your comment you aren't you are you are you are
12 p.m. 12 p.m. wait a minute what time is it right now it's 12 a.m. right now
so i gotta wait i gotta go 12 exactly i win
win okay steve you're a sicko
11 a.m. this actually is not as hard as i thought it was gonna be three two one two three
and you're watching the disney channel
so
b what was the b for what's b
10 30 three two one what's the spelling
boobs boobies well maybe you're right about the entertaining children part three two one
take that back
boomer 8 40 a.m. holy shit this is impossible three two all right what is munchy monk
i don't know what it's spelled it's time to continue your training we'll begin with the
simplest task first a to feed the egg to your companion is that right next you must master
many food items am i spitting them in his mouth that's sufficient okay do not forget what you
have learned so eggs is a now use these lessons to feed tickets i don't have manco tickets
all right i think cupid let's go let's go let's go let's go lady cupid and i'm done
aim for the center on his health let's go
i guess it could be palutena there was a synthetic human that doesn't eat
no i do and i will be the last game and then i gotta get out of here it's been fun though this
has been wild one two three four i go parapet two uh i played rapid two i beat rapid two it was a
great stream a lot of fun one two three four that's what a sith would say
one two three four manka s this probably keeps going i'd be more precise than that
one two three four he's coming he's gonna assimilate us sorting algorithm come on make
it harder make it harder than this what's wrong with your head when you're shooting it's called
gamers yeah it's called gaming neck he's got his gamer stance can this i can i gotta get this
harder can this get harder i have so many arrows i lost a little bit of a mojo there but sorry
i want to be insane one two three we're good we're good we're good we're good we're good
it's hard now but i want it i had so many arrows yeah i forget the 50 000 i don't care
about 49 50 almost coming up i can't be distracted right now this is the last game
i can't be distracted that's great i can't be distracted right now i know i've already
looked at it you can't you know i've already seen it one two three four huge moment right there
i'm not choking i've got 100 arrows oh dude he's choking he's got 70 more shots i'm fine one two
i'm never gonna lose this i have to quit i'm never gonna lose i will actually never lose
never fucking lose it's just not possible i'll go for 100k all right when i get 100k i'm done
he's gonna choke why would i choke it's too easy it's not
do with your eyes closed no i don't know why would i do that one two three four okay 100k and i'm
turning the stream off the understanding only needs to hit the middle two three more and i i'm
leaving keep speeding up until you shoot what was that okay just admit that you're having fun
i can't stop but i have to leave i have i have to leave i feel like actually turn the stream up in
the next 25 minutes that's pretty good that's pretty good i lost there so good you see what
is it you told me that the highest ever score was i was close getting close so that's why i was like
i can't freak out all right i'll see you tomorrow tomorrow we're gonna do a short stream in the
morning again well no we're not that's why it's gonna be 1 pm we're gonna do a short community
content stream tomorrow afternoon at about 1 pm pacific i'll see you guys there we're gonna split
up the community night into two different days this game is fucking fantastic what a fun time
what a screen you know what i mean that's why i looked around like right right guys seriously
oh that's a lot of fun and that's gonna be the end hi you guys are fucking freaking me out here
all right i'll see you guys tomorrow tomorrow 1 pm pacific
take a run for the bits we're gonna do them very quickly here we go there's the music
there that was the we i know i got i've got the image right here i got the image yes it's
it's as scary as there was all of them have been all right let's go back to earlier
this afternoon i think this is all wrong so i'm going to go pull it from the other site
but i'll see you guys tomorrow if you're leaving if you're staying i'm going to go over this plasma
player thanks for the 250 plasma player i can't believe my favorite stream is playing one of my
favorite franchises 17 days into 2020 and you've already made my year thanks for playing rhythm
heaven fever it was great except the fish level fish level fish levels sucked i think the fish
level sucks i really believe that i really do thank you up last player appreciate it hey germa
sucks thanks for the 250 enable pog you dork that's another website i'll have to figure it out
hill sent thanks for the five community subs appreciate it this is during the hype
frame there's two of them which is just ridiculous ff12 penelo thanks for the 250
thanks for the early stream because i'm at work eating popcorn lol happy friday
be friday to you as well hope you had a good one and we'll see you tomorrow tomorrow stream will
probably be around three hours between like two and four just want to chill i got a lot of stuff
going on this weekend i'm trying to fit some streams in but yeah lm man thank you lm man for
the 1500 bits 15 bucks you are a king of clowns i appreciate that thank you uh heple able thank
you heple able for the 500 bits no message just 500 bits and then we had a shitload of community
subs come in we had your tooty your booty gave five kaj kaj tech gave five red lemonade 10
community subs ab joe five red lemonade again 10 more subs on top of the ones already it's time
for slime 500 bits early stream hype scam train hype there were two scam trains tonight wait there's
a wink you're gonna make me turn my fucking camera on what no was that was there actually a wink
otherwise yeah i've already shown this image on the stream i showed it on stream i showed it on
stream and we don't have to spare the same link what did it look like thanks though
uh yeah thank you it's time for slime though x giga thanks to the five community subs sumia
five community subs anonymous gifter five community subs guys i showed these all right i'm not i've
shown the the germ taleks one already stop it stop it stop it there's so many of these
you know what what do your parents think if they find the i melded two streamers together image
if your parents walked in right now and they saw that you were you were in the middle of fusing
two people's faces together what are they are they going to be like honey what the fuck are you doing
oh sorry bob i'm fusing two streamers together isn't that cool and then they're going to be like
so son or daughter um i don't i don't fucking think i like why was my mother swearing
shut up jeremy it makes me laugh all right let's go but thank you to red lemonade for the 10
and the five from x giga and sumia anonymous gifter gave five ruff gave five germa sucks
10 community subs thank you guys and we have some dreams here it's news and copper thanks for the
250 you appeared in my dream last night germa it happened to me too you were in a pre-stream chat
and you were very excitedly talking about a new big stream you had planned about something you
bought that simulates probability it almost looked like roulette in a can with root with tiny rice
balls so you could pull it out and decide how many balls should be in it and then you went to a black
board to teach all of us about the math of probability so we had to get our notes out
and write stuff down i feel like i've done something like that already but that means close enough
thank you but a weird dream though it's thank you dark soul for the 250 did you ever have my
domino's pizza suggestion um the one with the garlic sauce i did not i did not i haven't really
been to domino's well if i ever go i will do it also i have to apologize now for giving you shit
for streaming vr for four hours i got an index and was sweating after like two beat saber songs
and i go to the gym every day for one to two hours but we see more when the doctors fix your
glass bones and paper skin pepe hands yeah i know me too me too i'm in the same boat who do i follow
me you're following me follow me follow me me right now click the follow button just do it
question asked oh my god taeyeon thanks for the 500 bits i was supposed to build a pc today
it was gonna be my first build ever all the parts came in i cleaned the area i have your pc doctor
video loaded up and i have my spice rack ready you just had to scream this great game but i'm
loving every minute of it uh good luck with your pc build hopefully you don't put egg wash in your
motherboard because that would make it not work oops uh thank you two pock alive for the 300 bits
they say hi thank you uh hi hi how are you uh sweaty man thanks for the five community subs
as well as we had uh zyxia or zig zig zig zigzika zigzika a 50 community sub thank you for the huge
amount of subs thank you also to autumn dragons for the 250 hey germa first time sending big bits
just want to let you know how much you mean to me and my friends these streams are always the
greatest also i think it's time we bring this back what does bring this back oh the remix 10
yeah with the germa yeah that was uh that's quite interesting now i get it now i know what it is
you should do pat upon all right fine put it on the list i'll do it potion dweller thanks for the
250 i was super excited when i heard you say you got mega man legends one and two yesterday
i feel i should let you know that two is actually three in the game story wise
there's a side game called misadventures of tron bone and it's 100 worth getting also mega man
legends was before they figured out lock on control so maybe a little clunky still great you can get
misadventures on the ps3 store for like five bucks yeah i i played mega man legends when it first
came out i don't remember that much of it but i remember enough for me to want to play it again
but yeah thanks i'll probably get it i'm yeah i'm streaming those yeah
all the mega man legends i'll do them probably not in a row but i'm gonna do them i'm not sure
why should i follow you do you make something popular did i make something popular uh no not
really i don't think anything no nothing you'd know i don't think anything you know nah probably
not um the music back on oh wait no you you might know me from one of my most viewed videos on
youtube uh halloween level waves 666 it's got like 10 million views or something yeah for some
reason you might know me from that yeah that's probably how you even know that keeps popping up
on my feed i don't know why that happens why that video i don't know but thank you appreciate it
thank you sell juniors for the ten dollars you go big guy pose for the fans i did plenty of poses
tonight i think that's germa i know him from the servers hey kohi lin thanks for the 250
good day germa if you're still looking for a replacement mouse it seems like razor made a
death adder version 2 and the rubber sides aren't scuffed anymore also which anime are you going to
watch this year for your once a year viewing rule uh a ya ya forever my good dude um i'm gonna get
an amazon basic mouse for the next mouse what am i gonna i don't know i kind of just i just
fall into something use code ace on checkout uh i haven't decided yet because it is 2020 you're
right behemoth thanks for the 250 behemoth what's up gamers germa 956 here and today we'll be hitting
up some dragon one and then they say yeah yeah yeah i know what it actually says but i'm not
going to say it because people will make me apologize peaceful hailey thanks for the 250 when
we exchange our wink points can we request you do something with it like a wink with a peace sign
so it's not just a wink no it's just it's just a wink it's only a wink otherwise if you start
to have a special request it's gonna have to be 100 000 points for a special request
75 000 points for a wink 100 000 points for a wink with a special request
otherwise i'm sorry for saying a yeah earlier i i i'm sorry i do apologize for that
the great lord walden thanks for the 500 bits oh yeah they just say oh yeah thank you zake thanks
for the 250 yo merry christmas got a serious question for you what's the biggest difference
between streamer germa and real life jeremy tears from a land far far away huh not very much to be
honest i think the only difference really probably is and i'm going to be honest with you but real
life real life jeremy doesn't play video games like he used to if i play a game it's on stream
here with you guys i don't really do it upstream i sometimes maybe a little bit but i mean i the
streams are on for you know six to eight hours seven plus hours three or four times a week that's the
time that i'm gaming that's the time that i'm playing anything that i'm doing anything that
i normally would do when i'm not streaming i do very kind of boring stuff but i'll do i don't do
a whole lot it's almost like when when a stream is over and like for instance for today right let's
just give today as an example so i just played rhythm heaven for seven hours i typically would
play rhythm heaven for seven hours off stream on tuesday or something but i did it here instead
so the only difference is really just at least for gaming wise is the stream is on you know what i'm
saying so it's they happen at the same time like like it's sakiro came out right i wanted to play
sakiro i really wanted to play it i was super excited for it but i just played it on stream
and after you know it's been seven hours my goal right now is not oh i just played rhythm heaven
for seven hours i'm going to stop turn the stream off but i'm going to go turn on rhythm heaven
for like four more hours and that's just i wouldn't game that long anyways normally speaking are the
games that i prefer to play alone yeah i do there's this plenty of stuff that i've done
off stream that i didn't feel like doing on stream but it's very that's rare it doesn't happen that
much yeah that's there's your answer probably the main difference uh comes up thanks to the 250 this
is one of my favorite games ever and you're my favorite streamer ever glad you had fun with it
i did it was great wembley ttv thanks for the 250 wow you go compact guy
thanks for the 250 sticks renegade 250 i can guarantee that changing your own oil is easier
than this level it probably is probably accurate uh jay hans jay hansil thanks for the 300 bits
remember you look like a dry shriveled up prune playing this game thank you for your content
you're my favorite boomer i don't it's hard to be 35 okay it's hard being 35 thank you knick knack
for the five community subs earlier bug bear and frog 500 bits congrats on beating remix 10 sour
please thanks some of that thanks for the 250 i helped and riant deliriation or riant deliration
thanks for the 500 bits and there's just a couple of hamburgers here thanks for the burgers hey kip
thanks for the 300 bits scam train this is where the other scam train happened thank you for the
300 bits during the scam train phylactery gave the 50 5 000 bits and a 69 community subs during
the scam train appreciate it that's fucking ridiculous as always bad nutrition 500 bits
during level four of the scam train hugels thanks for 750 they say germa i dot dot dot oh god
hyper band 250 no message fluid mezzic 10 community subs thank you fluid and community
subs is a lot of subs it's a lot of money you guys drop this shit just all the time
it's a lot of money thank you hey mr goido mr go i is it go i do or go we do
go go redo mr go ido thanks for the 250 get on the scam train let the bits rain mr to redo
like from family guy oh what point what it's yeah scam train attack of the hank thanks for the four
dollars and 13 cents that's where you guys are gonna run so when can we expect the midlife
crisis stream where you scream at us about how more mortality is fleeting and you'll just wait
till you see your mortality crumble before your eyes didn't that happen 45 minutes ago when i was
playing remix 10 i feel like it did but they're the equivalent of that thanks tacky the hank they
say hey germa big fan of yours i know this is kind of a specific request but i'm a nerd for
a webcomic called homestuck and i'd love you to take a if you took a personality quiz associated
with it i'm not taking a personality test right now i know i'm kind of putting you on the spot it
might take as long as 15 minutes to complete it i won't be offended if you decide to not take it
either way i love the stream uh well i'll i'm not going to take it right now i'm seeing a lot of
people freak out i will pay you to not why is everybody losing their mind about this
holy shit people freaking off ban that person what what's going on you just swang a bat at a
hornet's nest i did all right thank you i appreciate the personality test but i'm
uh running out of time today i did personality test before i added to the list i'll do it on
like a tier list or maybe i will i i don't know maybe it's possible i really appreciate it though
it's divisive i don't okay i don't even know what this is what just happened i don't know i said
the word homestuck and then i looked over chat and people like dropped their food on the ground
and they all their plates shattered and they were screaming i don't know what happened
but thank you attack of the hank maybe i'll do it at some other time uh suck on me miss thanks for
the 250 hey germ i bet you can't win a game of civilization or i'll give you a thousand bits
vanilla no never i will never play civilization on stream not gonna happen thousand bits that's
10 10 dollars is really enticing but i will never play that game on stream flinzenberg thanks for
the 500 bits hey germ i just got back from seeing 1917 in theaters and it's a great film i highly
recommend it anyways i love the stream man keep up the great work i did hear it was really good
that's the one where they made it so it looked like it was one take i'm gonna check that out
that's really interesting to me all right let's get the credits on here i'm gonna roll out and
i'll see you guys tomorrow around 1 pm pacific time for a few hours gonna be a short stream but
we'll hang out it'll be fun let's toss the credits up here they didn't actually they didn't do that
they seriously get rid of the live events on the stream labs over here what have you done
well i'm gonna log into the website hey thanks everybody for stopping all of you
holy shit that's even though that's a wrong spot but it's still going very fast that's a lot stop
using stream labs i know but it's with anything i've set up so many things on it and so many
scenes in my stream deck and buttons and shit that going back is a huge process and i'm just
like ah i'll don't worry i'll do it i'll i will do it but thanks for the subs guys thanks for
sticking around stream is still over 10 000 subs which is surprising i still can't believe that
two three weeks after new years that's fucking crazy but we're gonna finish the stream up here
we have a few more bits to do fiti gave 250 they say here you go
log in with twitch and just enable it just like with bttv people that have bttv can see
franker phase z emotes don't worry now enable pug jesus fuck also the site might take a while
to load it's a little slow i just clicked it and it's not loading i'm sitting here right now it's
i'm on a i'm on a white screen there's no data transferring it's just sitting here
this shit this happened last time i'll make my own version of this i'm gonna make my own version of
this yeah i'm gonna make my own version please enable it god please now i'm gonna make my own
it's gonna be called germa hog and i'm gonna make sure so i get zoomed in and it'll be my mouth
you'll get it we don't want to you know we won't use it yeah you will it's gonna be disgusting
it's gonna be like a wicked zoomed in you'll see you'll use it we want pog all right i'll give you
not tonight though thanks to the 250 uh produces a sand produces a sand thanks to the 500 bits
i had the lord of the rings book as a kid never read them the movies came out didn't watch them
the hobbit films that came out my friends gushed about the series didn't watch them uh vini vinesauce
talks about and references the films constantly still wasn't interested but you doing terribly at
those ps2 games finally did it and i watched them so thanks germa also you pronounce my name
produce saw son thanks for making me laugh thank you produce sauce on before you leave can you give
us an ad sure uh sprite is better than coke buy sprite it's the best soda it's the best better
than coke here's your ad uh gtx 1080 quad sli thanks for the 250 hey germy i was just wondering
do you have any hobbies also have you considered doing a collaboration with rt game you two seem
like you get along super well and have a great stream well maybe i'll ask him maybe i'll ask him
when i see him in person this weekend because that pretty good timing on that pretty good
timing that's a spoiler wait how is that a spoiler that person has inside information they might
anyways moisture the oyster thanks for the 300 bits first time i've donated but would you ever
play the nightmare before christmas game i will just play kingdom hearts 2 and then get to that
part and then stop playing also do i have any hobbies from gtx 1080 um you have playing games
i like uh you know you know what my hobbies is you can think i'm crazy it's real taking baths
i love a good bath with bubbles it's one of my hobbies i take taking baths very seriously i love
it taking baths is actually a hobby i like it i do it all the time it's a hobby with epsom salt
oh yep absolutely soak in there for a little bit bath this that's not a hobby why not one day i
want to get a koozie or something and just have the ultimate bath and finally we had uh
kairo xiro or cryo burb thank you i keep seeing everybody's names just wrong thank you for that
500 bits we make it to the end here we're gonna go to the end cryo burb thanks for 500 bits hey
gerba either one of either one or a few of your mods were going up the chat and manually timing
people up or trying to help you read the 5k bits message before here's money towards funding
programming to better teach them emotion they do their best yeah remember there's a lot of people
here at this stream this stream has a shitload of people on it but it's still it's still moderated
enough or we try to moderate it enough to not have you know spam or anything crazy or anything
fucking bad or people saying bad shit it's tough sometimes i mean there was seven thousand people
here today that's it's they're doing their best to manage it with the guidelines that are here
and i've talked about this before you you go wow no mods or mods or a really really really tightly
moderated stream but sub only always and a ton ton of rules that you have to follow or you're out
of here a lot of people do it like that or just open the floodgates and who gives a fuck i'm i
don't like that either so i try to keep it somewhere in the middle i try to it can be hard
it can be hard it's very difficult to have the level of freedom that i want
without it getting too over moderated or too under moderated it can be tricky sub only sucks
that's why i don't do with them i don't do sub only mode really ever only when i have to or
when something crazy is going on or if i want to avoid a spoiler for a game or something i don't
i don't use it but they they're they try we've had we have meetings where the mod teams once every
every three or four months will get together and just talk about hey this is like kind of what i
want to have happen hey what's happened here why did this happen something wrong here this
is where when somebody got banned like we talk about shit all the time we really do mod meetings
technically that's what you call them is there a problem officer all right i'll see you guys
tomorrow we had one more bit come in from uh opster narwhal lover thanks with 300 bits
i said hey germa i made the original germa auto emote and you may have seen it it's gone
i replaced it with this one if you want to add it oh shit yeah let's get it all right let's add it
this this all right let's go here we go ready add germa auto to the channel
here we go it'll be available in about two minutes
is it there here it comes i might have to refresh yeah all right i'll see you guys tomorrow at one
o'clock o'clock tomorrow's stream is going to be fairly short have a great rest of your night
see you soon we'll do a little bit of community content stuff tomorrow good night