I am on time. I am on time. I'm here. Clock. By what time it was. It was ready to go.
And I freaked out and I was like, I have to press the button right now.
And landed on its side? What does that mean? Hello though, how are you?
Why do I feel like I'm so- I'm really tall right now. I need to- there we go.
My chair booster thing was up high.
The air thing that makes you go higher or lower. Anyways. Hello?
Today we're going to play Power Wash Simulator. The game that I've been talking about for a long
time. And look it, we're finally going to do it. In a booster seat is confirmed funny. All right,
let me just tweet this out. I'll be right back. Give me a second. There we go. I might- you know,
I might have to take- I might- I'm going to take a Tylenol. I woke up with a headache today. I need
like a- like ibuprofen or something. You know when you have that wicked bad headache brain?
Anybody else get this? Or your- like your head hurts. So therefore like words coming out is- comes
out slower. Like I'm talking right now, but there's- it's going through like a headache filter. You
know what I'm talking about? I hate that. Give me one more second. I'm going to take Tylenol.
I'll be right back. Also, I feel like I'm way too close, yet way too far away from the screen at
the same time. This is not right right here. Hold on. You know, I let Bugleberry borrow some of my
audio equipment and some of my monitors. He didn't- he returned them wrong. Move this back.
That's better. Stalling. All right. Everything's too close to me. Get away from me. All my things
are too close. I need to be sitting far away from my screen. He didn't change the category?
What? I'm still in hot tubs? What? No, I'm not. I hope not. My go live notification is Bugleberry's
cauldron? No, no, no, no. Fix that. Change that. That's not what I want.
He just does it again. Oh, dear. Okay. All right. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good.
We're good. We're good. We're good. Career of ruining error. Oh, God. Oh, hey. Hey, Regan.
Thank you, Regan, for the end community subs. Appreciate it. And Farz. Thank you, Farz. One,
one, two, two, three. The community subs as well. Not- this is not a hot- I mean, there's no camera,
right? No. Where's the- there it is. We're doing Power Wash Simulator. I can't wait. I'm really
excited about this game. I thought this game was a joke. I willed this game into reality in my brain.
Now I know that that seems incredibly egotistic and an insane narcissistic thing to say,
because this game's probably been in development for like a year or two. But if you remember,
six months ago, I was like, man, if there was only a game that you could just wash it and clean
stuff. And I could put my fingers on my head and I squeezed. In my brain, I willed this game into
reality. That's not accurate, but here it is. Okay, yes. Do I even have audio? I do. Oh, there's a-
this is- I don't- I've never played. We're gonna do career mode. We can't hear you. Yes, you can
hear- I can see the indicator. Uh, clean the van, this first one. Great news. Finally found a van
for you at one of the auctions under your budget. Don't freak out when you see it. It looks like
it's just been dredged from the bottom of a lake. Oh, I can't wait. But that's a good thing. It meant
no one else bid on it. They missed out. Underneath that hideous layer of gunk is your perfect
workhorse. Engine's a dream. No rust. There's even equipment in the back. Just needs a good
hosing down and you're in business. You'll certainly earn your pressure washing stripes
getting this thing clean because of- oh, there's a five-star rating and you earn money. This- okay,
I'm gonna- let's just be really, really clear. This- when did this game come out? This year?
Was it 2020 or 2021? When did it actually- well, is it- is it out or is it in early access?
I'm too quiet. Really? It shouldn't be. Hold on, let me see. Does the mic change? You know,
you let Bugleberry borrow shit and all of a sudden look what happens. How about now? Is that better?
Is that better? We good? I think this is where it was before. It got changed. I think we're good.
This might be the best game of the year for me. We'll find out. You guys ready?
Sound like Bugleberry. That was very loud. I'm really glad you didn't have to hear it.
All right, select nozzle. Raise lower tablet as escape. Okay, selecting nozzle. Select extension.
Select soap. There's different soap categories. Inventory. Rotate nozzle. Refill cleaning fluid.
Show dirt. Walk, crouch, jump. Oh my god, there's way more going on in this game. Let me turn the
volume down. It's probably really loud. Actually not that bad. Show dirt. I am. Is it an IDFOV?
Is it an IDFOV? No, here we go again. Is this an IDFOV? What do I do that? Control sensitivity.
Controls. I think it is. All right, let's do it. So, uh, this sensitivity is way too high.
Way too high. Controller sensitivity. Oh, this is gonna be on console. All right, that's fine.
So what do we do? Spray? All right, just like strip the paint. That was way too much.
Oh my god, that's loud. Hold on. If you did that to a car, you would rip the paint off. All right,
the ambience is fine. The power washer needs to come down. Water reverb. Turn the reverb down.
All right, there we go. That's fine. I think that should be good. That's better. Oh my god,
I love it. How do I change nozzle? Oh, I only have the stubby gun. 15 degree, 25 degree, 40 degree.
All right, this actually might be like the best game ever. This is what you, this is the one I
watch. I watch so many videos of people doing this shit. You have no idea. Guys, I will open
up a power washing video or like a wood cutting video and just let shit autoplay for hours. I
actually have a quick story for you. We're talking about autoplaying and maybe think about it. Um,
so like a week ago, like a week ago, I was watching TV and we're gonna go into a story here.
What's wrong with my voice? Hold on. We're gonna go into a story. Uh, so I was autoplaying videos
lying on the couch and I don't turn autoplay off. I know I just turned it up, but I always forget
to. And for some reason I'm never logged into YouTube, never logged in. I'm never logged into
any service. So even if I change it, I'm not going to be logged in the next day. So it doesn't matter.
So I'm on the couch lying down. I just had a big meal fucking Burger King. Just kidding. It was
McDonald's. I don't eat Burger King. And I fell asleep on the couch to autoplaying videos and I
believe it was cooking stuff. So I woke up maybe 20 minutes later and I was in that mode in my
brain where I just, I could not move. You know, you just, you just don't feel like it. Nothing will
make you get up besides like a fire alarm, right? Just like, I don't care what's happening. I don't
care what sounds are playing. I'm just going to keep sleeping. So I heard counting. It was like,
oh, like 2,448. 2,500. Who the fuck is counting? And I just went back to bed. I was like, I don't
care. I don't care to turn it off. I don't even know what it is. So I got up with like a second
or third time and I looked up and I was like, what is it? Why is Binging with Babish on the TV?
And I hear 30,345. I thought I was Binging with Babish doing like a counting video. So I was like,
I don't, I don't care. And I went back to sleep. And then later on, like the next day, I was like,
I'm curious, like what the fuck was that? And I watched on autoplay asleep, the entire Vsauce
Michael prime number video. It's like a four hour video. He says every single prime number up to
like 40,000. And it woke me up like three times. And each time I'm just like, shut the fucking
counting. Stop counting, please. But I was too lazy to actually get up. So I had, I feel like that
like gave me like a headache or something. It may have changed me forever. And I don't know why we
do that shit. Why do we do that shit to ourselves? And I, did you hear Otto? Let me get Otto.
Otto! It has to be a scientific reason for it. But the act of waking up like 20% the halfway,
whatever it is. It's like your alarm on your phone when it goes off. It's like, oh yeah,
I sleep through my alarms. You just don't care about anything but sleeping. Hearing four hours
of prime numbers was not enough for me to just, just to roll over and pick up the changer or the
phone and turn off the TV. That was too much work. But I just suffered, and I would say suffered
wrong, but it was so bizarre. My brain was trying to piece it together. It was like, why is Babish
doing this? Like what, what is this? I thought I was dreaming. Oh, Otto. He, I can't, he's over
there. Oh, this is going to be a good one right here. I love this. Oh, I hope there's wicked,
dirty houses too. I get to switch nozzles and stuff. I got to do the first coat first though.
You're jerking off to power washing porn. No, I love these videos. They really are. If you really
have trouble sleeping, like that's very loud. I got to turn that down. Um, you know, oh, I have
like the beach sound effects. I have the, oh, it just plays the ocean. It just plays the outside.
No, no, no. I want log cutting videos because every, every like hour at one of them, one eye
will open and I'll just open one eye and just see like, oh yeah. Then I'll go back to bed.
All right. These windows are dirty. What's going on? I love this game by the way. This is so much
fun. So the body is still dirty. I got to switch nozzles. What does this one mean? That's force.
This is so much better than I thought it was going to be. This is such a fun game
because that's more pressure. Okay. There's even more grime on this thing. Hold on.
Just go outside. What do you mean just go outside? This is, you're using that wrong.
That term you're using that wrong. I don't have a car to power wash. This is not like I'm not
playing like soccer or football or anything. Dude, just go outside. This is an elaborate
power washing device. I don't have one of these. I'm making, I'm getting it a hundred percent.
There's a removals van outside my nightmare neighbor's place. They're finally going. Whoever
moves in there is going to need a quality pressure washer. I'm your guy. That's my
favorite part right there. None I got to do with. That's my favorite part of any car wash
because the water just like spins all in there and gets all in there,
flies around out in your face and stuff. I love it. You're a raid. Who raided?
Oh, RT game prop. What's going on RT? Thanks for the raid. What's going on RT gamers playing
power washer simulator. RT is a swell, swell lad. If you do not follow RT, what's wrong with you?
Oh, thanks a lot, dude. Welcome everybody. Raid song. I don't do raid songs anymore.
At this point, the raid song is becoming like a fucking reunion show.
You understand? Like how many times you want me to do the raid song before we go through like 10
seasons of raid songs and now it's just so I don't even want to hear the raid song anymore.
Press R to rotate. Oh my God. Thank you for saving this whole stream. I love it. Let's rotate.
Thinner. This is just one of my, I'm living one of my favorite videos.
I can just see like the dirt kicking out underneath that flap. I love it. This is so good.
This might be boring to watch. Oh, whatever. This is the rest of my life is right now.
Flip it. There we go. You can crouch too. There's a crouch. Oh my God. I love it. I, okay. I gotta
stop being like the person at the restaurant that tries everybody's plate and goes, oh my God. I
love it. Oh my God. So good. Wow. What did you get? I just keep saying that. Look at how much
distilled extra dirt. And the worst part is when you get somebody that does that and you can tell
that they like your food way more than their food. So they start like, yeah, yeah, but try mine,
try mine. I'm going to give you a bunch of my spaghetti. Like, oh, I don't want all your
spaghetti. Try my spaghetti. And then you realize that they gave you a huge portion of their food.
So now you are obligated to be like, oh, well, you know, here I get half, you might, you gave
me a lot of your caps of mine. Oh yeah. Sure. I'll try it. And they scoop off like half of your
fucking plate. Like you didn't get the fucking, you didn't like, sorry, you got the filet mignon.
I got them. Come on. What restaurant are we in by the way? I hate that I ordered. That's not
relatable anymore. That's no longer relatable. What? Cause I said filet mignon. No, let's change it
to McDonald's. I love that place. And that happens to me all the time. Billionaire Billy. No, that's
not what I mean. I was just saying a random food. Ever seen water pressure videos? I missed what
you said, but yeah, I love water videos. I got to get the roof. Wait, this is still dirty.
How is this still dirty? Oh shit. I bet you eat caviar. I think caviar is fucking disgusting.
I'm sorry. I don't, I think that's gross. I'll tell you why I think caviar is disgusting. It has
nothing to do with how the thing tastes. The reason why I think caviar is disgusting is the
same reason why I wouldn't open up 12 eggs and scoop them out into a fucking cup and drink them
like a bodybuilder. Now I don't want to, I don't want to eat raw eggs. I don't want to just like
drink eggs. Why am I getting question marks? Do you guys know what caviar is? Drink the eggs.
Have you actually tried caviar? Who? Who? Who's that? Are you who-ing caviar? Why are you who-ing
caviar? It's not like a streamer. All right, change that nozzle. High pressure. Let's go.
You got to get the corners of the windows and then the middle. Dermot, stop. You're not using
any soap. What? I don't, you don't, what do you mean soap? I don't need soap. It's a power washer.
It's just the pressure of the nozzle takes out all the dirt, all the grime, all the filth,
and you don't need soap. Isn't that what they say in the commercials? All done with the power of
steam and liquid. Yeah, you don't need soap. Stop. What? Get down here. I mean, that was a really
just half-assed impression, but I'm busy enjoying this. You're going to need to, you're going to need
to go with that business name. What do you need me to think something up? I'm phenomenal. I thought
of routing Thomas for that Tyler and she's never looked back. What? No, they really are hitting a
completely untapped market here. You're ignoring the story. All right, so what do I, I see a red
canister. Oh, I would never shoot a pressure washer at like a propane tank. None of this stuff can
even move, so don't worry. I clean the ground too. All right, what do I need? The body is still,
ah, okay, cool. That's cool. Cool. All right, the mirrors. Don't forget about your mirrors.
Turn it off. How is the body still this dirty? This is going to be such a huge moment for me.
I love it. Here we go. Stop saying I love it. Stop taking people's spaghetti. It wasn't a perfect
line, but it was good enough. Let's go wider. Just like the video. Yeah, you got to do it just like
the video. It's got to be like swoops. They do these huge sweeps. Yep, you got it. You're right.
Exactly right. Use the jet pack. All right, I got it, got it, got it, got it, got it. How much more
is there left to do? This car is clean. There we go. All right, body is cleaned. Oh, back here.
Door is clean. Everything is clean here. Window, door, glass. What's that? What else? Oh, right here.
This is gross. This will be it for this one. What's dirty on the window? Where is it? Got it, okay.
99% cleaned. Tire? What else? Grill? No, that's clean, man. It is the grill, but where? Up underneath
the lights? What? 99%. All right, where's the rest of it? Mirrors? Other mirror? Press tab. Oh,
shit. I feel like that's kind of cheating, don't you think? Come on. Where is this? It's just
cheating vision. It is. I haven't pressed the tab. I don't see anything. Oh, it's the tire.
Oh, my God. How am I ever supposed to get all that? Another tire? Yep, I did it. Job complete.
Open the tablet. Wait, is that showing everything I did? That's awesome. It shows the video of what
you did. That's the greatest thing I've ever seen. How efficient was that? I would do the top first,
probably. Okay, cool. So now I got 150 bucks. Continue. Clean the back garden. It's 400 bucks.
What about the store? Power washers. A range of washers from small home units to industrial ones.
Cleaning liquids. Glass cleaner. Metal cleaner. Plastic cleaner. Universal cleaner.
But just get the universal one. Just put it on everything. From all surface materials.
Yeah, why would I get the... What do you mean no? Buy all the cleaners. It's more expensive. Yeah,
buy five bucks. Buy the stone. Buy the stone. Stone cleaner. I thought this said grass. Okay.
Equipment. Prime Vista 1500 turbo nozzle. Oh, shit. That sounds pretty good. It improves the
range while still being able to be used quite close to surfaces. Soap nozzle. I want... Okay,
I need the turbo nozzle. And I need this short extension. I want to save my money. Hold on. I
don't want to just buy a bunch of shit. Power washers. This is one I have right now. Surface,
encrusted, embedded. This is awesome. This is awesome. Everybody at the dinner table,
give me all of your plates. I'm eating all of your food. All of it. You know what? I'm eating
everything. I want to try all your food till there's nothing left on the plate,
and I'll give each of you 50 bucks. That fair? Medium. Heavy duty. Professional duty. How much
are these? 2,000. All right, we're good. Let's go. Why don't just order food? Okay, I think I know
what you mean. Like, why would I just give everybody $50? Why wouldn't I just order
everybody's entrees? Because the entrees were like 30 bucks. 20 bucks. Why wouldn't I just order
three or four of the things that they had? I see what you mean. Yeah, okay. All right, let's keep
going. Career. Garden time. Let's do it. This one's gonna be fun. I'm gonna clean the grass,
too. Don't tell them we're gonna get 50 bucks. Uh, doc, I'll help you like a challenge because
I'm pretty sure I've got the dirtiest backyard you've ever seen. That's not me bragging, by the way.
I had nothing to do with it. I just moved back to town for a bit to help my folks. We're both down
to their last knee and rented what I thought was a great little place. Anyway, my girls are itching
to get out there. I don't want them still itching when they get back. All right, I'll clean the
grass. Do I have the new nozzle? Oh, this back here is not, this is nothing. This is, this would
take 10 minutes. I need, how do I, do I, how do I equip the nozzle? Is it already on? Oh, here we go.
All right, prime vista turbo nozzle. That's what's on. Why is it doing that? This, it just makes figure
eights? Well, shit, how am I supposed to put on the extension nozzle? This is all over the place.
All right, well, let's go for it. No, I hate that. Take it off now. Get it off. What the fuck happened
in here? Don't stop saying Aaron. All right, we're going to start with the, uh, we start with the
walls, the fence, even more pressure. This is wood. How do I put the soap on? Here we go. Universal
cleaner equipped. Is it on? I think it's on, right? Is it something neighbor to come on and be like,
what the hell? Why is there a bunch of drawings? I'm just going to draw like fuck you on the side
of their house. You need a soap nozzle at the tops. Don't hold on. You didn't buy the soap nozzle.
Oh, well, whatever. Oh, this is stuff. I can't, I have to say it, but I, uh, I don't want it.
Okay. I'm not going to say it. Are you guys going to be ordering dessert? No, no, I'm stuffed.
How come we just can't say no? Just say, no, I don't want dessert. No, fuck, just go waiter. I
flew all I would. I just like so much food. Look at all this stuff. Just say I don't fucking want
dessert. Why does it make us look bad? I always make up like an elaborate story as to why I
don't want to order dessert. I don't want the waiter to think I'm like a weirdo or something.
Quit saying we, when it's only you. No, I know a lot of people do this shit, not just me.
What was that? You're crazy. I'm, I don't know. I always have this thing in my brain
where if you, if a good waiter or waitress comes over and they're like, oh,
would you like to see our dessert menu? And it's like, no, just like, oh, well, you don't even want
to look at it. Why? I, I don't want it. I know that's never going to happen, but it's this weird
thing in my brain that is going to happen. So instead of having to say no and be like, well,
you don't want to even look at it. I just go, I make up like an elaborate tale of why I can't
eat dessert today. Just say no, thank you. I know that's simple, but I, I had, there has to be like
a reason why I can't eat it. Like I lean back and I put my hands on my belly and I like rub it and
I go, oh, I would, but whoa, that's, that's weirder. Did you get to the horror part yet?
Oh, ban that guy. Is that real? I'm just kidding. Don't ban him. I know it's not real.
If you say, whoa, at a waiter, you should tip them $50. Uh, my base line of tipping
is at least 20%. That's the base. It only goes up from there. 21%. No, I hate, okay. What I'm
saying right now is the equivalent of, so if we go to a restaurant or something, if you go somewhere,
you sit down with some friends and that's like actually telling the waiter, oh, by the way,
I just want to let you know I'm a good tipper. Isn't that always seen to be the case that that
person tips like 12% or like 8% or something. That's a lot of community subs. Uh, void 880.
Thanks for the, hold on a minute. Hey void. Hold on. Hey void. Hey void 880. Thanks for the
community subs. I was spelling the name. It's hard. I can't, it's hard to spell with a power
washer. But no, I, I know that saying that I tip well means I don't tip well. I just think I do
for some reason. It's like, well, hell, yo, you think, you think like 7% is a good tip?
Of course I think it's a good tip. What do you mean? It's a, it's a tip. It's a very generous tip.
They forgot to fill my water, by the way. They didn't fill my water up twice. I mean,
you see how many people are in this place right now? I thought the waiter was, was pretty good.
No, and you know, I heard a sneeze. I heard a sneeze. So I, I don't, I don't, I'm not,
I don't like this place. Okay. Nice run. This one needs the more powerful one. Definitely. Oh yeah.
This one needs the, yeah. That's how you get in there. You're fucking up the flower beds?
Oh, I guess I kind of am, aren't I? You gotta stand back. Yeah, that's better. My dentist uses
this one. I actually love this thing at the dentist. I know we have talked about this,
but there's a lot of new people on this channel and we have to go over this again.
Everybody here hates getting their teeth scaled, right? They fucking hate it. Everybody here.
Is that, am I, right? No, no, no, I actually like, see, this is what I don't understand.
There are a bunch of people that like this, getting their teeth scaled. That, it sucks. It's
horrible. It's one of the worst things I've ever, it's one of the worst fucking things.
Scaling, if you don't know what scaling is, it's that little knife hook that they scrape
your teeth gum line with. It's the worst thing on earth. Yeah. I, I hate it. Who wants that?
There's a bunch of people that like it. It's at least like 20, 30% of people that actually like
it. I know a handful of people that I've come across, friends, family. I know people that like
it. They're like, oh yeah, it feels good. Well, the reason why I bring it up is because they have
one, it's like a water scaler. It goes like this and they do that like all over your gums and stuff.
And I much prefer it over the scraping. All right. I don't go to the dentist. Well, then you missed
out on the goodie bag. Don't tell them, don't tell them about the goodie bag. If you've been
to the dentist before, you missed out. If people that have no idea what I'm talking about, they're
like, what do you mean the goodie bag? Oh, it's one of these people talking about
no goodie bag. Okay. I still get the goodie bag. All right. Tell me if I'm crazy because I need to
know. Did you guys, when you were a kid, go to the dentist and after you were done, you got to go
to like the toy center and they had these little like small cheap toys. It was like a big treasure
chest that you can go like get toys from. That was awesome. That was the best part. When I still go
to the dentist, when they're done, I go, oh, there's cotton in my mouth. Can I get a toy? Can
I go to the toy box? And it's not even weird. They don't even care. Okay. Don't do that. I'm sorry.
I'm trying to, here's the thing about those toys that you got from the dentist. I have this like
memory. I can't remember any of them. They were all so strange. It was like a device where you
pressed a button and it made little water come up like colored blue colored water or something.
Like I, they don't even real toys. Well, one of them had like a, I'm making this up, but a string
attached to like a little bicycle thing and you turn the wheel and the string would fly around.
I don't remember any of them. They were only in the dentist's office. I've never seen them ever
again. Sticky hand. Oh yeah. They did have sticky hands. You're right. Bouncy balls. I don't remember
bouncy balls. I remember the weird like the rings. Yeah. It was the thing with the, I remember that
in the water. All right. This is still dirty, but I'm going to come back to it.
It's still a shitload of dirt on here. Where is it though? Oh, I've done that before. I've done that
before. How many of you guys have done yard work or helped it around the house? I've done that a
bunch of times or you don't, you just don't do the insides. You just do this and you don't do the
insides or the back. You just want to be done. Okay. I'll do the other side after. All right.
Should I do the patio furniture first? You should do that while painting. Well, I mean with paint,
you have to paint the fence. You can't just, what? So the only, yeah, it's when we, I don't know what
something, when I was like a teenager for some reason, but just being able to view it from this
angle and it looking clean was enough for me to think that my parents weren't going to care.
Just this picture, this snapshot was like, I did it. It's done. Oh yeah, it is done. And then like,
that's all it took for them to look. That only worked for about two minutes before they came
outside. And the weird teenager brain was like, yeah, that's enough to like fool them for me to
be able to ride my bike down the street now. I already told you guys how I mowed the lawn.
Everybody thought I was crazy. How I used to mow the lawn was I thought it was a genius idea
was I just did a giant circle and just every time I kept going, I went a little bit more
further on the line and I just kept going in a circle, circle, circle, circle, circle, circle,
circle, circle, circle, until it was down in the middle. That's how you do it. I did that too.
Yeah. But the correct way is you go is like, you're not supposed to be like, just do a big spiral,
right? That's a great way to do it. All right. If you hired somebody to do this and you looked
outside and they were going like this, but they still did the job well, what's the scenario?
Like, let's say they did that. Is the scenario you don't call them back? You just go, thanks,
appreciate it. Thanks for the power wash. And you just don't call them back to do it again.
Or do you say, Hey, stop doing that. Clean the car. I hold on. I'm getting clean,
overwhelming here. Oh, there's so much dirty shit. Is this doing it? Yep. It's like rust.
Can I get it with this? Are we going to go harder? That feels so awesome. What a simple concept.
It's perfect. All right. How many of you guys used to stand out here like this
and pretend you had a flame thrower sprayed up and down? I remember, I remember like,
if you stood like far enough away. So let's say for instance, if like, if somebody was like there,
like where the, uh, the bird houses, I remember my brother used to stand really far back and just
go like this and it would, I, there would just be this mist that would overtake the whole area.
I ever tell you guys about how I used to put on hockey equipment and my brother used to like
throw baseballs at me. I did, right? Let me give context. Let me give context. Context, context
matters. Listen, listen, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. The context matters. Just wait. So I have an
older brother and he was a pitcher. So he was like, when he was younger, he was like, you know, in
middle school and high school, he was a pitcher. He played on baseball teams and stuff. And I played
baseball too, but I wasn't nearly as good, right? So he always wanted to practice pitching, but
at the house, it was just like, Oh, who do you practice with? Uh, I got, do you want to like
practice? I want to like try some new pitches. And I was not very good. And I was like, I was,
I was so scared of, of getting like drill with the baseball. So we put me in a bunch of hockey
equipment, like a hockey mask, hockey pads. I looked ridiculous. I had that bunch of like a
football pads on helmet, everything. And I would just sit out there with a glove and he would just
like, just gun them at me, like just whip them at me. And like, it would be like chest sometimes
because I couldn't catch very well, but I wanted to like help. I wanted to like, let him practice
half the time. The ball would just hit me like somewhere in the chest or like the knees or like
the face, but I had a ton of, I was covered. I think I even had pillows all over me too.
Yeah. I w we would, we like taped pillows to my arms and stuff. So like, it didn't matter.
And on the one or two times that I caught it, it just, it would hurt. It hurt. And I kind of
didn't want to catch it because it'd be like, he'd be like, all right, okay, here comes another one.
I'm going to, I'm going to try fastball and to be like, Oh, that sucks. This sucks.
So eventually I just like started pretending like I was terrible and just let them hit me in the
chest and like the face and stuff because it didn't hurt. You're explaining the story from
the mighty ducks. This happened though. I, this actually happened. And it got to a point where
he would, he, he would be like, you know, it'd be like after school or something. He'd be like,
Hey, Hey, Jeremy, you want to put the hockey pads on? And I'm like, yeah, I want to put the
hockey pads on. And that translated to a bunch of different activities that I could just, I was
going to never get hurt. I would never get hurt. It was like a little brother suit of armor that
I would put on. This is clean, right? This one little piece that's not, where is it? Would he
beat you up in the gear too? I mean, like maybe sometimes it would just like, like scoop slam me
or something. But it was, it was, we were like doing something. It was like, Oh, we're going to
play like fighters or something. Oh, I'm going to get the hockey pads. Like we're going to do any
outdoor activity. And it required us to like do anything really active. I would probably just
put the hockey pads on because I just, what do you mean sometimes beating you up? No, no. This was
like, we were having like fun as brothers. And it was like, you know what? I'm just going to,
I'll put, I'll put the pillows on my arms just in case I don't get hurt. Repressed memory. I
just told you that it was like, it was fun to put the hockey pads on and like play baseball and
like run outside and do weird shit and like play fighters and stuff. As they made a product called
sock and boppers. Okay. Oh, what, what are you talking about? You, your brother used to like,
you used to put pillows on and your brother, you would like throw, you hold on and wait, wait.
There was a fucking product where you put these air gloves on and beat the shit out of each other.
This was not abnormal. Sock and boppers, sock and boppers. It's more fun than a pillow fight.
You put on these kids boxing gloves and just beat each other up. Memory unlocked. I,
and now that I think about it, it's like, so there was a company that they really wanted to, oh,
like a pillow fight. Like people, like, uh, like brothers and sisters or party or something. You're
like just hitting each other with pillows. You know, you've got to be careful. Let's make kids
boxing gloves. It's like, wait, what? I did. I missed a spot. I just got it. All right. There
it is. Don't crouch. It's bad for your back. It was no ad. Your brother made a fake ad so he could
beat you up with those. Well, when my brother was fucking like 12 or 13 or something, he sure was
like a really great like engineer of plastic material. I don't know where he did that. And
well, that's very interesting. He had his own like factory, I guess. Oh, that's really dirty. Get
rid of that. Still on there somewhere. Where, where is it? Oh, that's very interesting. Oh,
that's right. Dirt vision, right? Sorry. I said, take a quick shower. Stop juggling.
What's the age difference between you and your brother? Uh, 30 years. It's one star. I'm not,
I'm not going to just leave the job. I'm in the middle of doing this. It takes a while.
Oh, somebody in a pre-stream was just, I caught it. I caught it. I, look, I saw it. They said,
what the fuck is that from? Please tell me. I need to know. And like, I, I could tell you
an old sound effect. They used to put in lots of stuff back in like the early 90s, mid 2000s,
early 2000s. The one where it's the most prevalent is the first boss of the Simpsons arcade game.
He goes, and it's been stuck in my head for years and I can never get rid of it. And I just do it
sometimes, but it was, it was used a lot. I love cleaning rocks. I just got here. Has it been funny
yet? Oh my God. You have no idea. You missed so many funny stories. You missed so many funny
things. You missed like, I couldn't put the nozzle on right for like 20 minutes. Everyone was like,
pretending Pog. He's pretending Andy. It was awesome. This one's done. I don't even know.
Sometimes you clean it twice. This is good. Where is it? It's somewhere in here.
Fence post. Come on, get it. Fence panel, fence post. This is all good. All right.
I don't see anything. Here we go. I don't need that nozzle. Let's, yeah, there we go.
Wouldn't this fuck up the lawnmower? I have to imagine that spraying water inside of an engine
is probably not a good idea. Very dirty though. Oh, if you want to know what we're doing next week,
there's a couple of things that are going on next week. I'll tell you. So first of all,
um, E3 is this coming weekend. So that's perfect timing. Perfect timing. I'm going to stream on
Saturday and do the Microsoft conference. And then whatever's after that, I'm not going to do,
I don't really care about the Ubisoft conference. It really don't. I don't think it's, I really
don't think it's worth me streaming that conference, but we'll do Microsoft and we'll do Square Enix.
And then, uh, that same stream, I don't even, I'm, I might even just say like, oh, thanks.
It's my 10 year anniversary being on like line on YouTube and Twitch.
That's happening. I think on that, that's like Thursday of this week coming up. It's the actual
10 year anniversary. So I don't, I don't really have anything planned or anything.
I was kind of just going to bring it up. So I guess I just already did.
That's the best bird shit nozzle. Probably this one. You're so old. I know I am so old
and I'm just getting older. I can go wider. Can I, I need to buy that soap nozzle. Let's
probably go so much quicker. Yeah. If I don't address it for some reason on next weekend's
stream, then yeah, I, I started doing YouTube when I was like 25 and here I am at 35. Yes,
that's how old I am. People think I'm like, I don't know why people think I'm like 23 or something.
I might act like a fucking 25 year old, but I'm 35 and I pay taxes. No, they don't.
But yeah, I don't know. I, I have no idea what my future looks like. I don't know.
10 years ago, if you told me that I was going to be continuing to do this 10 years later,
I would have been like, I don't think so. I have no idea. So it's surprising that this many people
are even here anyways. So this is still dirty. Oh, it's this. All right, let's get it a little
deeper. Come on. Yeah. You, I've been watching you for 10 years. Ew. What do you mean? Ew.
I say, ew. How am I going to get on the roof? Is there a ladder? How do I get clean that?
I just have to jump. Holy shit. Okay. I guess I could, I'm going to take advantage of this.
I am, you need the propeller. I would just open up the back slider at this point, like the back
door or whatever, and just be like, ah, there's a ladder in the garage, dude. Do you need it?
You don't have to do that. I need, uh, this is very dirty. Look at how dirty this is.
Don't fall off. I'm almost there. How's it look? Okay. We've been watching you since 2013.
Yeah. And I'll make the same reference here. That's very surprising to me
because after seven years of a TV show, we keep using that magic number of seven,
after the seventh or eighth season of a TV show, usually people start to get a little tired of it.
So I, I'm surprised that 10 years later, the TV show still exists, but you're a person.
Yeah, but still, I mean, usually there's a pretty finite amount of time that is super quote,
quote, quote, media is seen as worth watching, right? Remember you're the Simpsons of the
internet. Don't say that. Don't say that. I think there's like, I think there's like 30 people that
still watch the Simpsons. I wouldn't say that. It could be a great show. I have no idea. There's a
really small amount of people that really enjoy that show still, and it might be the best television
out there. I have no idea. I haven't watched it in probably 10 years. I've not seen a single episode
of the Simpsons since probably like 2008. They definitely have your 18, 18.8 K Andy. Well,
I didn't say my, I did not say my show is better than the Simpsons. I didn't say I have more viewers
than the Simpsons. I said that maybe three people watch the Simpsons in every city, in every town,
in every state, in every country, in every province. I did not clarify what I meant by
that statement. So in actuality, it's probably like 800,000, 600,000 people. Where's this dirt?
Simpsons for every home. I'll tell this story because it's kind of interesting.
So I was at the, I was at the pet store. This is literally yesterday. I was at the pet store.
I needed to get something for auto and I did not know where the object was. I didn't know where the
item was. So I walked up to what I thought was one of the employees and I was like, excuse me,
we're going to get like the dog beds that have the things so my dog can walk up the stairs.
Because auto has like, you know, I don't want him to be jumping or anything. So I wanted to be able
to go on one of those ramps and sometimes they sell them at the pet stores. So I'm like, oh,
do you guys sell those? And the guy goes, I don't, I don't work here. I was like, what?
And then the person that they were with was like, are you Jerma? I was like, wait, what?
Wait, I, I thought you were an employee. And I actually went like, oh, uh, what's, what,
what do you, Jerma, who's that? And they were like, Jerma Twitch. I was like, what's Twitch?
And they were just like, I, it's this, you're not Jerma. And I was like, oh, look at me.
And I did the look at me thing. I don't know. I was like, oh, maybe I'll like be funny about it.
And they were like, you are fucking Jerma, you liar. And I was like, yeah, it's me.
So I, I just like, was like, I'm sorry. I'm really sorry. I thought you were like, I thought you've
worked here. Cause they had like a similar shirt on as like what the, what one of the employees
had on. And they were like, no. And I'm like, I'm sorry. I didn't mean to. Uh, this is real.
I swear to God. And no, they were really nice. They're really cool. It's that rarely ever happens
by the way. I wanted to talk about it though. The roof is done. All right. I got to get off the
roof. Stop doing the roof. But yeah, it was, uh, it was, it was really, they were really nice.
They're really sweet about it. I took a picture and I was like, oh, that was cool.
I just felt like an asshole. I felt like an idiot. It's a cringe streamer moment.
What's the weirdest place you've been recognized? Um, probably in one of the casinos here happened
to like a couple of years ago. It was just like, Hey, I know you. It was like, oh, all right.
That was it. That was literally it. They just like knew that it was me. No, like we didn't talk
about really anything. It was just kind of like, yeah, I know who you are. And then they just like,
they just went on with their rest of the, Oh no, no, somebody screamed at me. Somebody screamed at
me. Yeah. Somebody screamed at me from a car. Oh, I fucking forgot about this. I was at a mall
and somebody like was in the parking lot of the mall and they like drove by and they were like,
and I was like, what the fuck? Who's who is that? This is, this is like three or four years ago. I
think. Yeah. They screamed my name and they were in a car and it scared the shit out of me because
I was like, wait, who, huh? And I think I just waved. I was like, hi, that was it. That was it.
It was not like, Oh, hey, like, let's stop it. Like, Hey, are you? No, nope. They just screamed
my name. That was actually me. Oh, whoever you were. I mean, like you screamed at me. And that
was it. And I like, if anyone's like wondering, if you're like curious, I don't care. I don't care.
If, like, if you see me out in public or something, if you happen to think it's me or something,
you're like, Hey, I don't want to, like, I don't want to bother. He's probably so busy. Oh my God,
he's probably so he's probably, Oh, he's like the streamer. No, I'm probably literally like going
and buying like socks. Like I'm not doing anything important. If you would have like,
waved me down and be like, Hey, are you? I'd be like, yeah, I'll probably talk to you for a
little bit. Wouldn't be like it. That doesn't bother me though. So if you're, if you ever do
see, you ever see me out in public, you know, I don't care. As long as you're not like fucking
weird. Like if you're not weird about it, I don't care. Don't be weird about it. You know what I
mean? Yeah. Yeah. Let me be the weird one. Let me be the weird one. I like the, I like this,
this nozzle better. Oh, come on. Don't be weird. But I would use that as a blanket statement for
everything though. Just don't be weird. You know what I mean? I'm really happy to like
talk to people and hang out with people just for like a little while. But like,
I just don't be weird about it. Like I, I, I, I, I don't want to, I don't want to be weird to you.
Right. But I did say, I did do like look at me in the middle of a pet store, but like whatever,
like whatever, let me be the weird one. If other people there must've been like,
what the fuck is going on? Who is this guy? If I see you in real life, can I give you
bits or subs? No, I literally will not. I will not accept that. Real bits. No.
Where's the dirt? Edges? Yep. Uh-huh. What about a gift card? If you give me a gift card,
I'm going to do what everybody does with gift cards. And I'm going to put it into my wallet
and forget it's there for a year or two. And then by the time I want to use it, the store
that you gave me the gift card to, I probably not even, I probably don't even have one near me
anymore. I don't know. Like I may have like moved across like the state lines at that point. And
that store doesn't even, I don't have one of those near me. Okay. What's next? I got all that.
That's good. 32% clean. What else is left? Oh shit. All this stuff. What the fuck? I just
cleaned this. What? Go. Let's go thinner. Yeah. No. Yeah. Oh, sunflowers. I have those. Congrats.
Yeah. That was my, that was my way for you to be like sunflowers. What do you mean sunflowers?
Dermot sunflowers. And then I get to tell you about all my gardening. I'm annoying. I'm really
annoying. Look, I'll just tell you about it. And then you can just look at your phone and say every
last word of every sentence that I say. Okay. Would you, should you not do this to upholstery?
I feel like you don't do this to upholstery. So I have some flowers and I've got four in a big pot
and they are just barely going into adulthood. And I'm really into it. I think it's a really cool
thing. They're very big. They're going to be probably six feet tall. Yep. Yep. Yep. You're
paying attention. I know you are. Otherwise, how would you know the last word that I just said?
Uh, I don't know. I forget the exact name. I think they're, uh, I'm going to get, I don't
want to say the wrong name, but they're going to be really tall. I go out there every day.
You're like on your phone. Someone's telling you a story. You just type it away.
And so it was really cool when they came over and, uh, uh,
why is it? It's like, what the fuck, dude? Give me the big one. Oh, this is fucking filthy.
Do I have any other flowers? Oh, I have a, I have a money tree. That does not stay outside though.
Money tree is, uh, inside. Money tree. They're really cute. It's a, it's a little one. It's one
of those, uh, small, uh, braided ones. I have a few succulents that sit in a little container.
And then I have, I don't know what it's like a little, it's a little like polka dot plant.
I forget what it's called, but it's this little, it says like it's, it's small. It's maybe about
as big as a baseball. It has green, pink polka dot leaves. It's almost like the channel colors.
It's really cool. And I take good care of them and I love them very much.
Oh, gross. Did poison ivy? No, it's like a, it's like a little desert plant. Jesus. He's
still playing video games. What did you expect me not to be playing games anymore? I still play
games like occasionally, right? I play games like this because this is sick. Turns out they're
literally called what? I missed it. I need to get up there. Let's do the car. Play backgammon next.
I don't even, I don't know how to play backgammon. Backgammon was always a game that somebody had
in their house as a display. I never took it out of the box. Ooh, that looks nice actually. Play
blackjack in Fallout New Vegas. Yeah, that one. It's the car from the carnival. It kind of does
look like that. Uh, give me the red one. This one's better. Gambling stream when? Isn't gambling,
isn't like gambling on Twitch now? Yes, lots, lots. You know, I really didn't, I thought,
I never thought that slots were going to be a thing. I always knew that like, yeah, you could
do it, but I never thought it would be, honestly, I'll take, I'll take the loss on that one. I thought
it was going to be Battleship. Honestly, I thought it would, I would have been Twister before it would
have been slots. We just went right to slots, huh? Twister is, oh, by the way, I forgot to say this.
I watched the entire movie of Son of the Mask last night. I don't know why. Do you know why?
This is, this is weird to say. I don't, I, I, the movie sucks, okay? But listen, I wanted to watch
all like the really shitty scenes in a row, but I didn't want to open up like 10 YouTube tabs
to watch just the scenes of the movie that I wanted to watch. So I just rented it and I just
got, I just did the thing I was going to do anyways. The best part of that whole movie is
the part where he goes, you're just too good to be true. Can't take my eyes off of you. You're
just too good to be true. You're just too good. Oh, it's, it's so bad. I hate it, but I watch it all
the time. You're just too good to be true. Can't take my eyes off of you. You're too good to be
true. I know I love you so much. Yes, I watched Son of the Mask before Megamind. By the way,
there's something I didn't realize about Son of the Mask. I've never seen that whole movie start
to finish even, even 10, 20 years ago, whatever, when it came out. The, the, the actor would,
would Jamie Kennedy, right? He only puts the mask on like twice in the whole fucking movie.
That whole movie is the, is a cartoon baby versus the dog. He puts the mask on twice in the whole
movie. He puts it on the very beginning and then at the very end, he doesn't ever put the mask on.
What the hell? The dog has the mask on in the movie more than he does. What do you mean spoilers?
Nobody cares. Stop spoiling Son of the Mask. I didn't tell you the plot of the movie. I just
told you that the, the, all right. So Jim Carrey was the mask, right? And oh my God, it's one of
the best movies ever made, right? And we all can agree on that. That's, that's a simple fact, right?
I still just have to, I don't know why they made another one without having Jim Carrey be the mask.
Like, well, why would you even do it? It doesn't make any sense. Get it. This is almost done.
Movie is a really awful adaptation of the comic. Yeah, I've heard of that. That's the original.
The original comic is like kind of like dark and awful, right? All right. Looking good.
It's just, I, do I have, I have to get a hundred percent. I can't not get it.
This is going to give me a ton of money too. Oh, that's, it's better just to see this.
The comic have Jim Carrey in it. Um, wait, what? What are you talking about? No, no, it was for
money. I guess, but the only reason why it made any money is because Jim Carrey was the mask.
How am I going to get in this crevice? God damn it. I need a hundred percent. There's stuff in the
crevice. What about Sonic the Hedgehog? I thought he was good in Sonic the Hedgehog. I saw it.
This is another thing. Like look, Jim Carrey, Jim Carrey is, Jim Carrey is old now. He's like older.
I wouldn't say he's like an old man, but he's, he's like 60 or something.
Now the stuff that he was doing in his late twenties, early thirties, like Ace Ventura and
stuff. I mean, he's, he can, he's still got it. I think he's still got it. Nineties, Jim Carrey is
peak. I'll tell you, and I mean this very, very much so. If there's no Jim Carrey, there's no
Jerma. I'm serious. I don't do any of this stuff unless I thought he was really funny.
Telling you. Give me the big, the big, yeah, that one. Bro, sorry. We're going to clean up the grease.
You're a Walmart Jim Carrey. Oh, that's fine. I will never, I will never be Jim Carrey. That's
fine. Yeah. I don't care. In fact, don't even, don't even use my name in the same sentence as
Jim Carrey. Like, oh, you're a this Jim, no, no, no, don't even say that. Remove me from Jim Carrey.
That's not enough for grease. Shit. I can only get it off with this one. It feels so good. I love
this game. I know. I don't care if I keep saying it. Jim Carrey would be proud of you as their son.
All right. Now we're getting weird. This, now this is getting weird. It is now it's getting weird.
What? What did I say before that made it weird? You're just too good to be true. Can't take my
eyes off of you. I know I love you so much. I can't. I'm going to watch it again tonight.
FAD. Watch that scene on stream. I can't. DMCA exists, guys. I can't do that. What do you say?
Am I going to what? What did that person say? Am I going to what? Are you going to go on schooled?
Um, what do you mean schooled? Joe Biden is the son of the mask. Ms. Kiff's show. Oh, oh, okay.
Did I admit? Does he want me to do it? Are you guys just saying this? Is this, hold on, is this
one of those things where like you get the streamer to say the other streamer's name,
so then the other streamer then has to say and like react to me because I said the streamer's
name? Is that what we're doing? Or did he actually say this? Ego Andy. I didn't say. What are you
talking about? What about a banana? He said he hates you. No, he didn't. I know that for a fact.
I just watched that scene from Son of the Mask and it sucks. I know. So why don't you watch the
whole movie to just here's the thing. I don't even hate watch stuff. That would be classified
as hate watching, right? I don't even hate watch it. I'm like happy that I'm there experiencing it.
I don't know. It's weird. It's not hate watching because I don't hate it. I'm just so intrigued by
it. Does that make sense? That looks good, right? Oh, no. Whoa, what the fuck? You can prone like
Cod. Well, I'll say the same thing I say every time about like collabing with other people.
As you all know, I do collabs when I think they make sense or if there's a thing I think would be
fun. I do things with other people sometimes. I, the most part is just me. I don't know. I'm
not against doing anything with anybody. It just, I usually do things alone. We've talked about other
streamers before. If it sounds like something fun, sounds like something I'd want to do, I'll do it.
That's it. There's no other motive or anything. Mr. Incredible One. What if it happened to the
card game? Are you talking about Grotto Beasts? The card? The real card packs that yield the real
cards you'll be able to open very soon? Is that what you're referring to? You're talking about
the Grotto Beasts cards that you'll be able to buy and have in real life soon? Is that what you're
referring to? Yeah, I mean, that's not, it's not ready yet, but it will be very soon. It'll be soon.
He always says soon. Yeah, soon could mean whenever. It can, it's soon is soon. Soon is when you get it.
Soon. Okay, listen. Soon means real. That's all you need to know. Soon means it's real.
All right, that's good. That one's done. Wait, this backyard's done. It looked like a pretty good
backyard. What if there's a bird in here? You're causing from Boston. God damn it. I don't want
to hurt the bird in here. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Okay. Everybody get ready. It's
time. Shoot the target in front of you and ready go. Fuck. Now I lost. God damn it.
That kid next to me did it perfectly fine. But I'm just, don't just let go. Why even do it anymore?
I'm not going to, I'm not going to get to the end. Why even, why even continue if you didn't get it
the first time? Probably should have been mine. Term is bad in Amusement Park games. No, that
happens every time. If you are doing that game and there's 10 of you there and you're ready,
you're lining it up and it's like, and start. It's over. You lost. You've lost. It's over.
You've lost. If you end up, like we all do, there's one person that gets it right and they win.
Gosh. What the fuck? What the fuck? Are you kidding me? Who wrote this? Who wrote that? What the
heck are you doing? Oh my God. That's so funny. Wait, I don't want to do that last. Is this done?
What? How am I supposed to get in there? Really? Underneath. Oh shit. I'm hurting the bird.
Ms. Kiff, I'll do it. I don't even know what I just agreed to. Why don't you be like, oh yeah,
yeah, what's going to happen is, oh no. What do you mean oh no? No, I'm not invited. Did you guys
just gaslight me? Oh no, now I look like a fucking idiot. Like accepting an invitation I was
never invited to. Oh man. All right. How do I fix this? I got to fix this. What do I do?
You just self-invited? Did I? Was everybody just saying that? Just go offline, bro. Oh, I got to
go. I'm out. I'm out of here. Wait, I want to do the furniture first. Just agreeing to something
that A, I was probably never invited to and B, I don't even really know what it is. Oh, I like the
umbrella. Little bro, apologize. Your ego is showing. Is it? I didn't do anything. What did I do?
Did I do something? Is being like a 20k Andy like fucking up my brain? I don't know. Is it?
What do I do? White noise. Ms. Kip just said yes. Next week. Next week? What do I have to do?
I have to travel or something? What do we do? What? All right. Stop. All right. I stopped lying.
Stop lying. Are they lying? I just got pity invited. No, don't say that. All right. I'm
going to stop addressing it. And if it's real, then I'll figure it out. If it's not real, then
it was fun. And I'm sure it's a fucking awesome show. I really think it's probably really fun.
You're old enough to be their grandpa. Am I? How old am I? They're saying you have
to come in as the sus guy. They want the sus guy? No, they don't. That would be hilarious
if they actually did though. He said hello. Well, I say hello back. Why is this like,
okay. Oh, can you tell, can you tell them that I said hi and I think they're cool?
You just go tell them. I don't want to be your messenger. No, you do it. Right? I'm saying it.
Hey, what's up, Mizkif? How you doing? Hope things are going well. He's not even live.
Oh, I'm being gassed. Yeah, I'm being gassed. All right. This is whatever. Let's move on from
this. We're going to move on. I'm looking forward to. I don't even. All right. Cool.
This might be fun. I don't know. I don't even know what it is. Sure. Let's do it. What is it?
I don't know. That sounds good. You're a sussy baka. It's like. Hold on. Let me read this. It's
like. It seems pretty hype that you said, yes, he's pogging. Oh, all right. That's yeah. Cool.
What are you doing? I'm power washing. Don't waste a weekly stream. No, I would be on top
of what I was doing. It wouldn't be. I wouldn't replace anything. The quiz show on school questions.
Oh, he said it would take you 10 minutes. Are you smarter than a Twitch streamer? LOL.
Okay. Is it actually like that? Because what if I get every single question wrong? Am I going to
look bad? Oh, shit. I got to like study or something. When is this happening? I'm going to
make sure I can even do this. I might have to do it the next time they do it. If it's real.
It's today. It's not today. It's every Monday. All right. Let's hold on. I'll figure this out.
You're late. Hurry. Oh, shit. I got to get over there. What's my first question? What genus
is the canine family from? Arachnophobia. Kick him off the fucking stream. I'm gone. How's that
look? Awful. Did I hear about the new house flipper DLC? Yeah. We play every house flipper
DLC. It doesn't matter how long or short it is. You'll see it on this channel. Don't cheat. Why
would I? I'm not going to. What do you mean cheat? No, I got nothing to hide. Like really. Like if
everyone thinks I'm stupid, whatever. If I can't answer like a fourth grade, fourth grade, whatever.
If I can't answer that question, then I can't. And that's what that's the way it is.
Oh, no. I'm regressing into a fourth grader. I'm method acting. I'm getting ready. This thing. I
need an upgrade. Bad. 100 percent. He'll have you on. All right. Well, we'll figure it out. Maybe
if it's not this time, then I don't want to just fucking just jump in and be like, oh, you said yes.
OK, I'll see you tomorrow. Like, no, if they got plans, they got plans. I'll do it one of
the other times or something. I don't know. We'll figure it out. I make I have no plans, guys,
when I do anything with anybody. You come over and have lunch with me sometime.
No, I will not. I'm sorry, but I don't do that. I can help you pick out what you'll
eat for lunch today about about a turkey club. That sounds kind of good, doesn't it?
Somebody said, is this a minigame? What's the actual game? Yeah, this is a minigame.
This is a this is like a new shooter that came out.
There's like a side game where you can like actually just go power wash stuff.
It's like a backyard like like water, like battle game. You get the different nozzles.
This is like a shotgun. And it's just like you spray like each other with water,
like Super Soakers. But it is a second game that lets you kind of use all the available
stuff they use in the actual game. You can come and just power wash. It's really cool.
I'm really into it. The game is called Soaker Sloshers. But this is like a power wash thing
that they have in it, which is kind of cool. It's called Splatoon and it's real. No,
the game is called Soaker Sloshers. And I'm playing the minigame playing the minigame
of Soaker Sloshers. No, the trim here. I'm almost done. Look at this. All I have is just
this really dirty muddy thing and a little bit more of the patio. New job available.
This is like when your parents see you playing GTA and you pretend it's a different game.
What do you mean? Like you're in you're playing the golf or something
in GTA and you just say you're playing a golf game. You're gonna do more DOS?
Probably eventually. It's not now. There's always there's always time for DOS.
Those games are never going away. This umbrella is filthy. You just pretend GTA is a race game,
racing game. Yeah, but then you have to play really well. Oh, no. Yeah. What are you playing
in here? Oh, it's just a racing game. Oh, and then you don't realize like you're watching
and you just ran over like three people and like crashed. Oh, really? That's interesting.
You can there's people you can you hit someone. Oh, oops. How do you explain that one away?
You can't. I don't want to just go here and just smell this water.
I want. OK, so I want to be standing here. I want to be standing right here.
I want someone to go like this, bounce it. So this vapor goes right into my face
and I can just sit there and just so dirty under here. Savory. No, it's a it's just water vapor
that I just like to be near. Oh, I don't vape. I find it disgusting. Don't do that shit. OK,
like this is a public service announcement. Don't cut that out. Cut that out. Cut it out.
Shut up, Dad. No, cut it out. Cut that shit out. Cut it out. If you're thinking about quitting,
you're thinking about make this be the time you do it. Make this be the make this be it.
That's it. That's just it. That's it. What a shitty PSA. Hey, German 985 here.
Just want to say if you vape, just cut cut it out. Cut that shit out. Stop doing that.
All right. Done. Don't do that anymore. I need a wider nozzle. Is this a let's see.
Yeah, this is getting it. Damn it. I screwed it up. What if I power washed a real patio?
Would you guys watch it? Would you like if I if I just like tried to find somebody that had like
a really like kind of dirty backyard and dirty house? I just did it for free. I was like, hey,
can I like just power wash your whole entire yard and do and take into clean up your whole house?
Yeah, you just have to let me film in your house or on your like property.
I don't need anything else. I don't care about anything else. You think people would do that?
And I would sign a death waiver, too. You know what I mean? So don't worry about that. It'd be
like, oh, what about that? I would sign like a death waiver. I guess like a fucking piano
fell on me or something. Don't worry. Almost done. This is a little bit more of that. And then just
this really muddy, dirty area here. I think I would be pretty good at that. I really think
I would do a pretty good job. Eat the BTS meal. What's what's the BTS meal? What it puts in it?
McNuggets, the 10 piece nugget with sauce. That sounds fucking great. I love the nuggets.
I'm a huge McNugget guy, so that meal that I would eat that. I do have a question, though. So
a lot of people have meals at McDonald's, right? It's like, oh, this meal, this like
these musicians or this these actors or is it going to get we're going to get to a point where
just the regular McDonald's meal is just like celebrities. Instead of ordering like a Big Mac,
you order like the kind of like, you know, like the Larry David sandwich. Like, oh,
you're just on the board. It's like it's Larry David. It's not like a like a whitefish sandwich.
It's the Larry David. I do love nuggets, though. What's the sauce? What's what's the difference?
What's the what do you get for ordering that? It's like some Cajun sauce. Wait, is that did they
have it? Really? It's a cage like a chili sauce. Cajun sauce. Holy shit. That sounds really good.
And a new sauce. All right. I kind of want that. It's a new sauce. Oh, shit. OK.
Eat it live on stream. I'm just going to enjoy it. My own time. I don't want to eat on stream.
I don't want to eat on stream. No, I want to enjoy my food on my own time.
Go ahead. Call me a coward. That's why I don't want to eat on camera.
Do it as Catboy. I'm going to have to ask Catboy. It's probably going to be no. I just don't like
people looking at me eating or anybody else for that matter. I don't I don't want you to look at
me chewing and hearing like that. I'm going to make me laugh and I'm going to go. I don't want
that to happen. Like someone's going to make me laugh really hard. I'm going to have french fries
in my mouth and I'm going to go. I fucking don't want that. No.
I got to get in the crevices. What's that from? I already talked about it.
I got to get inside all these crevices like this. 15 million off the dead if you eat nuggets as
Catboy. That's not worth it. That's not going to make a dent. 200 million. No, no.
Guys, I don't even know where Catboy is. I don't even know. I have no idea. Half the characters
that are made just fuck off and they just disappear into the woods and shit. I don't even know where
they go. Some of them we see. Where did what? Who made Bugleberry? I don't know. I met Bugleberry.
I found him on like Craigslist. I don't know who made Bugleberry. I hired him. Come on and read
some scary stories. That's what it said he did and he was really, really kind of an interesting
guy. So I was like, Oh, I kind of, maybe you'll come back or something. Do some more stuff.
He did like kids birthday parties and everything. There was, he had a whole thing.
I don't know where he's from. I am almost done. You're right. What about chrome face? He's got
these fucking urns, dude. I don't know. I don't know what any of that stuff is. He create, he
doesn't just make characters for me. He makes them for himself and he does like summoning courses
and stuff and I don't know. I don't know what his daily life is like. I just know that sometimes
I bring him on to make characters. This really weird guy, but he's does, he's good at what he
does. All right. I'm almost ready to do the really dirty one. Why are all of his characters a version
of me? Well, cause I don't know. Sometimes I don't feel like fucking streaming and I don't know.
He's been making different like characters and different stuff.
He has like whatever he has. He makes it however he does it. I don't know. I don't know.
You think I've watched bugleberry streams? Are you out of your fucking mind? Those streams are
horrible. I always leave when he comes on. Why do you think I've watched a bugleberry stream?
It's bizarre that you have. Yeah. If I know he's going to be on, I'll just like
go to the bathroom or something or make some food or just come back and see when he's gone.
He's a smart guy. He's a, he's an interesting guy, but I just don't want to watch him stream.
Oh, this is going to be horrible. Look at, look at all these crevices. I think I can do the big
one for this one, right? Nope. God damn it. Green one? Yeah. Why does he stream? Because like I've
told him a long time ago that he could do stuff on camera if he wanted to. And part of me hiring
him required that he was going to be able to participate in some of the streams that I do.
Where some of the broadcasting hours, right? What was the charity that bugleberry donated to?
Uh, that's actually a work in progress. I'll let you guys know exactly the exact amount and what
charity it is. But no, I'm not, you'll hear about that soon. You're going to pocket it? I'm not
going to pocket it. No, I'm not going to do that. I'll, I'll give you the very specifics on all that
stuff. I'm not just going to be like, yay. Donated it to charity. Yep. That, yeah, I did. No, I'm not
going to do that. I'll give you guys exact specifics of what it is. What just happened?
Why did it clean it for me? I had like a whole section left. What did it do that for?
Wait, what? Free cleaning. Yeah. That doesn't mean cool. What's on this roof that's so,
where is it? Doghouse roof. Where? Come on. Ah, thank God. Did I get the rest of the doghouse?
I think I did, yeah. Use eagle vision. I keep forgetting I have that. No, don't spray that.
Stop. Somebody said I hate this game. Why? This is awesome. This is super relaxing. We hate games
now? Well, you're probably going to hate them even more when the Ubisoft conference happens.
That was uncalled for, uncalled for. Why did it do that? That was uncalled for. That was uncalled
for. I don't, why did I say that? I think it's because I hated Watch Dogs Legion so much
that I just had to say that. He hates Ubisoft? Yes, I do. Do you want me to, should I just pretend
like I don't? I do. But that's like, that's a very strong way to word it. I don't hate Ubisoft.
I just hate all their games. No, let me try that again. I don't, I just don't really like their
games. Okay. I've had fun with some of their games. Some of them. But for the most part,
when an Ubisoft title comes out, I just go, no, I don't care. I just, I don't, it doesn't do it
for me. Hate is too strong of a word though, because I really don't. All right, I want to get
right to the middle. Feels good. All right. Wait, I forgot these. This will take 10 minutes? Yeah,
but I'm, I'm being thorough. I'm being very thorough. I don't just wanna, I just yawned.
I tried to hide it. I think that's from the headache though. That's not because I'm tired,
or I'm bored. That's from the headache. You know when you get like a really yawny headache?
That's what it is. I swear to God, I'm not bored. I love this so much. I just have a little migraine.
It's starting to evolve into a big migraine, which is annoying, but I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
I'll be good. Too much CBD? I have not taken any CBD today. Or yesterday, or the day before,
or the day before, or the day before. Oh Jesus. Bong water? I don't smoke out of a bong. I don't
smoke weed. I don't smoke weed. I don't. I got four stars already. Damn, this is dirty. It's
one dollar for the car seat? Are you kidding me? So many cracks. Get the majority and it'll auto
complete? Oh, still dirty. No, spin it. It does do that, doesn't it? It does, doesn't it? Okay,
cool. Final thing is, oh, the shed. Drink lots of water? Yeah, I got water right here. Somebody
said, have I ever unironically, not joking, smoked crack? I have not unironically smoked crack. How
do you, how do you ironically smoke crack? What are you talking about? Have you ever unironically
smoked crack? All right, shed door, shed roof. How did I not get that? If you ever smoked crack,
I would unsub. I not, don't worry about, I'm not going to smoke crack. Dude, what are you talking
about? Don't worry about that. Why would I ever tell you I smoked crack? That's not something that
I would just start with one day. Hey, what's up, guys? Yeah, starting to stream. We're going to
be playing Fable 3 today. I smoked crack today. Unironically, like I did it today. Unsub. Smoke
crack or I will unsub. I can't, I can't believe it. Okay, I'm going to move on. I'm done with that.
Do you have any fuel? I got one right here. Oh, shit. Very, very nice. I'll get the caked on sugar,
the burnt sugar. Very good. Very good. I think this is done. It is. That's it. We just have this spot
over here. I'm going to go thin nozzle. The swing, I'll get it in a minute. I fucked it up. It's
all right. I got it. Yes. I thought this is not a fire pit. This is a pool. This is a dirty fucking
pool. I'm going to stop swearing for an hour. It looks like chocolate. What's the max price for
this one? 400, 500. Oh, right to the very end. Oh, yes. Look at how much better this looks.
Am I, what am I missing? 99. The grill. Oh shit. They're at the back of the grill. This thing too.
How do I get up there? Oh, all right. 375. What? Okay. Bird house. What's left? Four. I don't see
anything. Checklist is in the menu. Okay. Status. Okay. There's one fence post. Is it? Fence post.
Which one? Oh, I got it. $485. Oh, let's see. Pretty cool. Do it again. Nice. Clean the dirt bike.
Should I buy something? This one would probably be quick. All right. This is going to be quick.
I love these quick jobs. There's so much fun. It just feels so right. You know what I mean?
We do one pass with the wide. We come down to the green. Pass with the green. Let me change the
yellow. This will be quick and efficient. All right. Nice. Other side. What's wrong with the
nozzle? The nozzle's like broken. All right. Now we do detail and that's it. The tires. Get in there.
Does distance matter? I think it does. Is that tire? Oh, underneath here. Yes. Yes. Four. Four.
Four. Squeaky clean. Come on. 96%. What's left? Oh, over here. Why am I shooting over there? Okay.
I think it's just the front of the bike. The engine. All right. 99%. Just a little bit in the guts.
No. Where the hell is it? Find out. The exhaust, the fairings, and the brake discs. Okay. Oh, what?
Brake discs? What's back here? Are they not clean? How are they not clean? What is a brake disc?
Yeah, it is. Yeah, I got it. It's those. That was quick and easy. Seventy-five dollars.
Ooh. Clean the playground. Clean the bungalow. Playground. Wait. 1250 bucks. Long extension.
Ooh. Soap. Urban X U2 turbo. Primus to 3000 turbo nozzle. Improves the range.
Shit. I bought the wrong soap one. All right. Go back. Back. Back. All right.
Cleaning liquid. I already have the multi-surface. All right. Let's go.
Need to reload the soap. All right. Let's see what I got. What do I got? I have the
this nozzle. Let me check this one. Oh, no. Where is it? Zero degree nozzle. Did I not get the...
Where is it? Where is it? Bottom left. Well, that's the soap. Didn't I buy a new nozzle?
Oh, jeez. Look at this. Whoa. Holy shit. Okay. Hold on. I don't want to fuck this up.
What's the dirtiest thing here? Soap the absolute hell out of this. Is this doing anything?
Again? Oh, it is. Okay. Rinse it with water. That works pretty good. Use the wood soap.
Oh, stone cleaner. Is this stone? What do you mean dirty? Oh, this is all-purpose. It's fine.
I gotta get up here. Is the soap actually doing anything worthwhile? I ran out of soap. No,
I didn't. I took it off. Soap is expensive. I mean, the universal soap will work on anything.
Is that working? It is. All right. I'll put that back on. Just spray the hell out of this whole
thing and then we'll rinse it. Wait, is this $15 every time it goes to zero? Is it? Let me
double check. Oh, fuck that. Yeah. I'm not using this anymore. Go down the slide. Yay. All right.
Now bring out the wash. Yeah. And let's wash. What? 8%? What? It should be higher than that.
Because all I did was use soap. Stop pretending. What are you talking about? What? What are you
talking about? What am I pretending? Not bad. Play some music. Uh, yeah. What should we put on?
What do you guys want to hear? How about the one that goes? Uh, let's see. What can I put on?
Put on. No, not doom. Something relaxing. Something we can just chill with.
Supermarket sweep. Yeah, that sounds good. Ow, my fucking head. That hurts so bad. My volume is
maxed. For you guys, that was 40% softer than what I heard. Supermarket sweep. Sounds like every
first Sonic level after 2005. Something's auto playing. I don't know what it is.
Here we go. It's the supermarket sweep main theme. Didn't we already do this like fucking
two or three years ago? Yeah. I remember this. We already did this. It's a clean in here if I can.
Same joke, Andy. No, it's been three years. That means we can do it again.
Mario Kart. It is. It is Mario Kart. It's so grimy. Super Mario Kart shop. Super Mario
shopping shop. I can't even fucking say your joke. It was funny when you said it, not me.
Fuck. Go faster. Oh, I'm trying. I can't go faster. Go faster. I said you do a shitty rush job.
I don't want to do a shitty rush job. That was a bad voice crack. That was supposed to be ding,
not ding. Look at all this crap. I wonder what are we going to get? What era of
supermarket sweep theme song are we going to get? Wheel of Fortune, actually. JRPG music. Yeah,
it is. Is this shit copyright? It probably is. These songs are probably copyright. Yeah,
this shit's copyright. I got to get rid of this. That was efficient what I was just doing. Very
efficient. All right, what's next? I'm going to skip like five times. I don't know what this is.
This is fucking awesome, whatever this is. What is this? This is called the savers?
Is this super? No, this is not a supermarket thing. This is great. What's next? Skip, skip, skip, skip,
skip, skip, skip, skip. All right, let's go to something else. That was cool.
Penis music. I'll do penis music for 10 seconds, okay? Okay, turn it off before I fucking puke.
What's next? Speedrun? What's good speedrunning music? Son of the Mask. I just want, I don't care.
I just want to play the... I have to do it. I have to. Nobody, just plug your ears for a second.
I just have to hear that one second. I don't care. You're just too good to be true. Can't take my
eyes off of you. It's the only part I want to hear, is it? That's it. That's all I wanted to see.
Okay, now what? 30 Valley? Vsauce Prime numbers. Vsauce Prime numbers. I can't believe I watched
that entire four-hour video in my sleep. No, I am not doing that. I'm not opening up that can of
worms. I'm not just gonna have counting happen. It's a great video. Katamari? I feel like we always
go back to Katamari. Always. All right, you want to go outside, Otto? I think Otto wants to go out.
I will take the first break. I'll be right back. In like two minutes while we figure out what to
play on stream. I'll be right back. You're just too good to be true. Can't take my eyes off of you.
You're just too good to be true. You know I love you, babe. American Bible Challenge theme song?
I, I can't like, it's hard to find that. You know, just watch like the first, come on. There it is.
I'm Jeff Foxworthy and this is the American Bible Challenge. Everybody just stand up. I can't wait.
Everybody just stand up. Everybody put your hands up. And this is American Bible Challenge.
A computer wrote that song. You know what I mean? That's like algorithmically they just made that
song. And I think that's Jeff Foxworthy singing it. I, you guys said no. I think it is. That's
definitely Jeff Foxworthy singing. And this is American Bible Challenge. The American Bible
Challenge. Everybody put your hands up. It's the, it's the same person that he, it's Jeff Foxworthy
singing it. American Bible Challenge. That's, that's him doing that. It has to be. Why would it be
anybody else? There's nobody else that could be. I love that song so much. Everybody put your hands
up. Everybody just stand up. Everybody put your hands up. Come on and stand up. Oh shit, forgot to
put music on. Clown car music? No. Kirby's Epic Yarn. Sure. I'll try. Kirby's Epic Yarn.
True. Okay. All right. Oh. Oh shit. All right. I'm getting a lot of everybody put your hands up.
Everybody just stand up vibes from this. Oh, it doesn't go, it doesn't go. All right. That
can stay on. That's fine. Drop it a little bit. It's a little loud. I'm going to drop the sounds in
this game too. I don't want to overpower the music. Yeah. I want to hear the stuff. Yeah.
There we go. Turn up the water. All right. How about the water splash sounds? Let's see.
Ah, that's still, it's way louder. That's, I think that's good. And we'll turn Kirby up.
That's a good audio level. Jerma doesn't know audio. Jerma's so bad at audio. Jerma's audio,
fucking sucks. Jerma's audio is fucking terrible. I don't like everything. If I go to Jerma's
straight, it sounds like shit. I'm working. I'm working on it. I'm trying. I wasn't an audio guy.
I was the, I was the visual guy. I can't do everything. I can't do audio and visual. I
can do visual and make the visual look all right. Is this replaying? All right. That's good. Let's
go. Everybody just stand up. Everybody put your hands up. All right. Let's clean the dinosaur.
I want to soak the fuck out of this. What the hell was that? Oh, I didn't like that. Did I do that?
What happened? What the fuck was that? Someone just dropped something on the piano. Is that in
the song? That's better. I didn't play this game. I didn't play any of the yarn games. They made
like three of them. Gotta go more than that. Let's just go yellow. Make sure we get it all.
Play them all? No, I don't think so. I think they mean they're cool and everything, but no,
I don't think so. You know why I don't want to play those games? Because if in the event that
I don't like them or I'm just like, eh, I don't want to sour how I feel about the way they look.
Is it the games or is it just like, eh, if I'm not into the game,
I don't want there to be a scenario where I talk a bunch of shit about it and I talk about how the
game sucks. I'd rather just enjoy it from afar. Nice and clean. All right. Looking good. Somebody
mentioned speed running. I can't wait to see people speed run this game. Right? I feel like
if you want a challenge, this is, this is, this would be very hard to speed run. Cool. Resident
sleeper. All right. Come on. My stairs look good. Doing it in one pass feels great. All right.
What's next on Kirby's epic yarn? Oh, I'm done with this one. I'm skipping ahead. All right.
Okay. This is same OST. What did I do? What just happened? What happened? Where am I? What? I feel
like this one's going to be quick. All right. Let's see how fast I can do this one. Start timing.
10 minutes from right now and I'm done. Oh, this is pretty thick dirt.
I think I need upgrades for this one. I might be able to get it. Shit. I gotta keep it in the
right spot. I gotta be like a 3d printing machine. Come on. I clean the rest of that shit up later.
It's all right. Oh, come on. It's still so dirty. How did I miss that much? I need a better washer.
Yes, I do. I'll get it after this though. Kirby's epic yarn. Yeah, that's was requested. We do
soundtrack nights like right now and you'll get what you want eventually. Got it. All right. Oh,
boy. It's a lot. All right. I need to get on the roof up and down or left and right up and down.
This is some kid shit. This is some kid shit. I hope this is relaxing. This is supposed to be a
relaxing stream. While you're on the couch, just open one eye and then you'll see, oh, where is he
now? Oh, he's doing the garage door and then just go back to bed. I'm being pretty meticulous. I'm
already at 13%. This is good. What did I say? 10 minutes. How long has it been? Three and four.
Okay, I'm getting there. Hey, get on here. Hey, hey, please play Super Paper Mario. Oh, you know
what? You know what? That person's right because I'm never going to play Super Paper Mario on the
stream. I'll put the Super Paper Mario OST on the stream. That's fair, right? I think that's fair.
That one's good. Over here. Yep. That's just ready. See, I like this one. This one's simple.
It's a big cube. Oh, that's much better. I got to get closer though. How much is left?
That's way too much. Play the Among Us theme song with them and it goes
Yes, that one. I just did it. I don't need to put it on. People still play Among Us.
Or is it over yet? Is it a dead game? I don't, it's probably, I don't think it's a dead game.
It's really popular still. Play Persona 5. I don't want to, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I got to
get on the roof. Can I turn this clown music? Oh, this is Mario Party. I don't know. What game is it?
I'm not going to play Persona. That's like a 60 hour game. You're never going to see a game
on this stream that's more than 20 hours. Top. I stream once a week, twice a week sometimes.
It's not going to happen. I have to be honest. I have to be real. 21, almost there. Oh, what's this
song? The green one, I don't have, there's no use for the green one. It's either the white or the
yellow. The green one sucks. I want to use the soap. Oh, that's so good here. Holy shit. That's
so good here. Wow. All right. That's good. Soap the hell out of the whole house and then I'll rinse
it. Time's up. It's been 10 minutes. Oh shit. Oh well. Got to go green. Stone cleaner. Oh shit.
All right. They're good. I can't tell this is, this is good, right? That's pretty, kind of good.
Let me just say play Lisa. Play Lisa. I swear to God, some of you guys have bots and come into
this channel and just write that. It's probably at least two or three accounts at once every month.
Just paste it. Let's just set up as an algorithm. Is this stone? Turn the webcam on. No,
I'm not a webcam streamer. I'm a web, no, I'm a webcam streamer with an asterisk.
Only when it makes sense. It doesn't have to be on all the time. Nice. Makes sense right now. No,
it doesn't. Please. I would love a webcam. No, I like this song. Let's see how it goes.
How can he be so mean when playing his dream game? I just don't want to put a webcam on.
Stop fucking asking for it. Whoa, whoa, whoa. Yeah, I know. 50% of this whole place is a roof.
Oh Jesus. Are you kidding me? It's a ladder. Hey, Rick and Morty season four coming up.
Saw the trailer. Everybody else excited? So if I, this is what I understand. If all of you hate
this show, who's watching the show? You know what I'm saying? Redditors? But aren't redditors,
what? I don't know. Wait, so what are you guys? What are you guys? Are you twitchers?
Twitch viewers? What? Neck beards. So if you guys aren't redditors, do you guys
only hang around on Twitch? I don't buy that. I don't buy that. Who's your favorite Twitch?
I can't even talk. Who's your favorite Twitch streamer then? You like Twitch so much. Who's
your favorite streamer? Okay. Okay. There's too much going on on this one. Yep. That's better.
You're a fan of Twitch. Name every Twitch streamer. That's what I'm saying. All right.
44%. Let's go with this guy. Let's do a quick coding. Let me get the power. Door is going to
be done. Door is going to be done. Okay. Cool. Yes. Yes. Yes. Please play the Pikachu soundtrack.
Pikachu has his own soundtrack. Yes. Yes. Yes. I think it's just a roof down here a little.
All right. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. He's still dirty,
but on Nier Automata. Nier Automata. Oh, shit. All right. This is good. This is Nier. This
sounds good. Oh, wait, wait. Hold on. Sorry. Nier Automata. Nier Automata full OST.
Nier gets copyright strikes from YouTube. Oh, well. Something else. What's next? How about...
It's been 20 minutes. You're still not done. Yeah, but this is, this is flowing.
Play Lisa. Play Lisa the Painful. You should play Lisa the Painful. You should play Lisa the
Painful and just stream it. It should be like a exclamation point Lisa that just says I will
never play Lisa the Painful. But then I can put it in when the bots put it in. Pokemon? Yeah,
Pokemon battle music. That sounds good to me. Pokemon hype mix battle music. Get hyped with
this compilation of some of the best battle songs from the Pokemon OST. It's pretty, I, I, I get it.
Here we go. Is this in the... Okay, this is not in Pokemon. This song is not in Pokemon.
This is somebody remixed it. This is that song that goes...
This is a, uh, what is it? Chemical, the Chemical Brothers? No, who is it?
That's this song. Firestarter, right? There it is. I'm a firestarter. Mr. Firestarter.
Prodigy, yeah, all right. This is not in Pokemon. I know that for a fact. This is literally Pokemon.
I don't believe you. This is from Gen 8. I don't like this. This, this, this is not...
This is the only kind of Pokemon music I like. I don't like new things. I don't like new things,
like old things from 1995. This is not even in Pokemon. Oh, where is it? Where's the one I like?
Oh, where's the one that I like? This is not the Hedgehog. I like this though. I just hear
the blast processing sound. It's gonna be too hard to get these. All right, I can do this.
Yeah, this is awesome. I really like this one a lot. This thing sucks. I need a better nozzle.
I feel like I can beat this level. All right, this is almost... Come on, it's done. Give it to me.
Where'd it go? Oh, whatever. I'm going up. No, no, no. I want... I mean, this is... This playlist is
cool. Here we go. Yep, this is it. This is exactly what I was looking for. That's not... No, that's not
it. Not it. Is this it? No, I want the one from Brawl. What's the one from Brawl? Gen 2? Is it?
I think this is it. Fake Andy. What? Brawl soundtrack is fire. The Brawl soundtrack is
way better than all the other Smash Brothers soundtracks. It is equivocally the best one
they've ever made. I... Nothing compares. It was so much better than everything else. Say what you...
Brawl... You might think Brawl sucks, but the music in Brawl was totally better than anything
else they've ever done. If all... Oh, fuck that. Let's just put on the Brawl OST. Fuck that.
That's the one I want to hear. Do you remember this one when you were... Remember when you heard
this? This one was the... This is one of the best songs in the whole soundtrack. Calm down, man.
I don't think I timed out for one minute. This is a perfect soundtrack for what we're doing.
Just to... This is a coloring book. This is a pro tip for all you guys that have trouble coloring
books. Always fill in the edges first so then you can't color outside the lines. Go a half
inch around so then that's your new line so you'll never color outside the lines. You're going so
slow. Oh, I... What are you... I'm not going slow, right? I mean, I am right now because I'm trying... I
can't move that fast for some reason on the roof. It's another good one. Don't fall. I won't. I'm
good. All right. Now we colored inside the lines. Now we go like this. I can probably do green for
this one. You know what's funny? This would probably be the background music for this video.
If I was going to have this on YouTube and I'm like a power washing guy channel, this is probably
what it would be. Do soap on the roof. Oh shit. That's good. Another classic. Another one. Every
single song on the Brawl... Can I... Why do I... Whatever. Every single soundtrack on the... Oh my
God. Every single... The song is speech jamming me. Every single song on the Brawl soundtrack
was good. I never skipped one of them. They were all good.
All right. We're at 69%. Everybody yellow L real quick. This is like a weird SpongeBob Mario
mashup. Oh my fucking God. Stop. No swearing. Imagine all the junk that would be in there.
Get it. Oh, whatever. Why am I missing on this roof? Oh, it's so dirty. Filthy over here.
Is that Wario? I think it's Wario. Is it... Am I going fast enough for you now? That's a better speed,
don't you think? Soap? I don't need it. I'll use soap when I get the better nozzle. I'm still
using the original power washer. This thing kind of sucks. Really need 1200? How many... There's a
lot of Mario songs on the Brawl track, aren't there? I didn't realize there were this many.
S1? Yeah, this is really good too. 74%. Come on. Come on. You know what I'm... Come on. Say it.
Come on. Come on. That's when I hold the microphone out to the audience and everyone goes,
when? We kind of wanted to make a fake advertisement for like a comedy DVD or comedy CD.
And there's a huge audience and it's like the announcer guy, the infomercial guy is like it
and such antics as. It's this little routine of little stream jokes. Like an audience.
Just make a little infomercial of a fake CD that doesn't exist. Relive all those classic moments.
Like, come on, Gwyn. Oh, come on. Come on, Gwyn. And everybody's fucking is cackling in the
audience. And they also brought like the vault. We got access to the German 95 vault
after his estate got it. Yeah, like they got access to my vault. Wait, am I supposed to be dead?
Shit, yeah. Fuck, I didn't want to fall off. Clean, clean, clean. This is going to be a huge
chunk. This roof. How about, was it 80%? Somebody get this guy a harness. You're not safe from a
fall joke even in this game. No, you're not. You're always at risk to hear a fall joke. I see a fall
joke no matter what we're doing. Oh fuck, whatever. That tree has a smile. The tree is fucking laughing
at me right there. I didn't even do any of this. All right, let's do this. I'll finish with the
roof. What about like dinosaur playground place? Can I go back and do that again? Hopefully it's
not reset. That would be really annoying if it was. What's this from? Mario's way cooler than Mickey
Mouse. I'm sorry. If you want to have the thing that is just the universal, everybody loves it.
Everyone. It's Super Mario. Like it's not Mickey Mouse. Fuck that guy. Donald Duck is way better
anyways. I can't think of anything. When you hear the word Super Mario, you don't think, all you
think about is, oh that's, I feel very happy right now. I feel at peace for just a moment. Even just
a moment. When you hear Mickey Mouse, you also feel some joy for a moment. Mickey Mouse. Oh,
Mickey Mouse. And then you realize it's four dollars for a water at Disney. And it's, yep,
it gets a little sour in your mouth for a second. Because it must be on sale.
How much is a bottle of water at like Disneyland? Does anybody know? Just like a Dasani bottle of
water. Is it five bucks? Is it four bucks? Probably five bucks. Yeah, it probably is.
3.75, 3.50. Let's go to a water fountain. So when does the copyright run out for Mickey Mouse?
You guys know that that's happening, right? I wonder what they're going to do about that.
Your local car dealership is going to be able to have Mickey Mouse pop up and be like,
oh yes, I love Dave's Toyota. Or whatever it is. Can you imagine when the copyright runs out,
how many fucking commercials are going to be showing up with Mickey Mouse on them?
It'll be every commercial. Every other commercial, once that copyright runs out,
will have Mickey Mouse in it. He'll be in Olive Garden commercials, he'll be in every local,
every single local commercial you've ever seen will have him in it. It's going to be so annoying.
Mickey Mouse is going to be endorsing so many products. Think of the oversaturation though.
If you watch an Olive Garden commercial and Mickey Mouse is there and then your local
Toyota is Mickey Mouse and then a toothpaste commercial has Mickey Mouse in it,
it's going to be crazy for a while. 2024. Yeah, when is it actually supposed to happen?
They're never going to let that happen. No way. I would be really surprised if it actually did
happen. 2024. No way. Think of every virus website. That is a banner ad that will just have Mickey
Mouse doing the standing sideways with his arms up, with his hands pointing towards the banner.
People are going to click it because it's Mickey Mouse. It'll just say the magic of Mickey Mouse.
Come over to, I don't know, whatever it is, whatever virus website it is, whatever scam it is.
They've already, hold on, let me pause this. They've already bought themselves more time.
Technically it's the Steamboat Willie Mickey and they've kind of gotten that back by reverting
to an older art style for some cartoons. Oh, Mickey Mouse. You think scammers care about
copyright? Literally nobody under 40 cares about Mickey Mouse. That's not true. Mickey Mouse Club
House was one of the most popular things that anybody that was young, like nieces and nephews,
they watched the hell out of it. What are you talking about? That was a huge deal for at least
a few, a couple of years. All right, let's, I want to skip to, ooh, mother. These are good. Yeah,
of course you, everybody, Mickey Mouse is a big deal when you're a little kid. I could correct
that statement and say that anybody under 40 and over 10 maybe is correct, but I think you really
underestimate how powerful of a character Mickey Mouse is to young kids, especially like three,
two, three, four, five-year-olds. Yeah, hot dog. Hot dog, hot dog, hot diggity dog.
Now we've got ears. Now we've got ears. Hot dog, hot dog, hot diggity dog. Hot dog, hot dog, hot
diggity dog. What's wrong? Is it not like that? Let me put the audio back up a little bit.
It's weird to hear no sounds. There we go, that's better. Okay, so hold on a minute. Is that the
whole Disney catalog of original characters or is that Mickey Mouse? Like when is Goofy up for
auction or whatever or whatever it is? Because they have to let, is it people gonna, somebody
could buy the copyright or no, it's just public domain. Imagine they auctioned off the characters.
Holy shit. How much do you think that would go for? How many people would be in that room?
Next up is the rights to Donald Duck. That place would be full of people. Oh, I love this one.
This is the one that goes down, down, down, down, down, down. Yeah, this is the one that goes crazy.
Yep. 10 minutes, by the way. What do you mean 10 minutes? Oh, that's how long I said it was
gonna be here for when I unplugged my thing. I still haven't replaced this. It's still broken.
All right, that's good. Gosh, Mickey. Who would go for the least amount of money? Between Goofy,
Donald and, okay, Goofy, Donald, Pluto, like Daisy. Because Minnie and Minnie are,
they're billion dollar characters, right? You think Pluto would go for the least? I don't know
about that. I think Pluto is pretty iconic. Pluto or Daisy. I guess Pluto doesn't talk.
So if you wanted to sell used Toyotas with Pluto, you couldn't do that. Unless they wanted to make
them talk. What would Pluto sound like? Goofy can talk and Pluto can't. Explain that. Because,
I don't know, the four of them stepped into Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle Ooze, and Pluto didn't. Pluto
would sound like a gangster? Like a 30s gangster? You mean like, come on, what do you say about that?
Come on now, you say? You like that? I don't know. I don't think so. No, I don't think so.
No, no way. He'd be, because he's lovable, dopey, funny. What would Pluto talk like? Let's see.
Well, think of the other talking dog that exists, right? Other talking dog. And when I say talking
dog, I don't mean Goofy. I don't mean dog. On all fours, dogs. Scooby-Doo, right? On all fours,
they're a dog. Scooby-Doo's not supposed to be like a talking character. He's a dog on all fours.
So Pluto would have to be in that same category, right? Pluto's not going to be like Brian Griffin.
Like, oh, hey, what's going on? It's me, Pluto. Yeah, I like martinis. I did that joke like a week
ago. I don't care. But seriously, what would Pluto would probably be more dog-like? Let me think.
It would be some type of range. I don't think it would be as goofball as Scooby-Doo is.
What other dog on all fours talks? I think it's just Scooby-Doo. It's Scooby-Doo. Astro. Oh,
that's right. Yeah, Astro's in that same category where he's like, oh, I love you, roach, right?
The dogs on all fours always talk like Goofy.
Oh, doggy. I love you, roach. So if we use that same exact kind of barometer for how they're
supposed to talk, then Pluto would be in the same category. What would he do? I feel like it would
be very tongue voice. Like, the tongue is always out. Like, you know what I mean? Because he's
always... I feel like that would be a gimmick. Like, right? It would be kind of a big... His tongue's
always out. And it would probably be very playful. Like, hey, hey, hey, Nicky, are you hungry?
Maybe something like that. I can perfect it. Fuck. There's a ladder. It would be a lot of tongue.
Tongue's just always hanging out. That would be the gimmick for that dog on all fours. I don't
think Pluto makes sense. Wait, did... What's the Garfield dog? Asteroid? What's the... No, the dog
from Garfield. Did he talk? Wait, he did for one episode, didn't he? Odie, right. Didn't Odie talk
for an episode? I swear to God, there was an episode where Odie drank like a magic potion
and could talk. What am I thinking of? Spike from Tom and Jerry. Hold on, Spike from Tom and Jerry
is not on all fours. Yeah, he's bipedal. Yeah, he's not on all fours. Yeah, he literally walks
on two feet. I'm talking about on all fours, you are a dog on all fours. What about Bolt? Bolt?
Bolt the dog. Bolt the dog talks?
Oh shit, he does talk.
Fuck, this ruins everything for me. This blows up the whole theory. Bolt doesn't have like a weird
thing he does, like he doesn't go like, at the end of every sentence, does he go like, or something
weird? This is a movie, though, and it's like a celebrity was this role, right? It doesn't,
it doesn't count. Beverly Hills Chihuahua? What the fuck is this?
Can I show this on stream? I don't think I can.
No, this doesn't count either. This doesn't count. I'll tell you why this doesn't count.
Hold on. The reason why this doesn't count is because this is a real dog,
ha ha funny real dog that we CGI'd a mouth on. That's what makes this different. This is not the
same. That may, this is different because this is a CG, this is not easy to find a mate with papers.
Yeah, this doesn't count. This doesn't count.
Doesn't count because it's a, it's a, the whole gimmick of the movie is, look, it's real actors
and with its real dogs, but their mouths are CG'd. No, I'm talking about a created character
that's so, it's not a real animal. Bolt is close. Bolt, I think, ruins my theory.
101 Dalmatians. What? Fat Albert's dog talked? How many talked? No, no. Lady and the Tramp.
They talked? Wait a minute. Fuck, they did talk. Yeah, they talked a lot. But they, was it, was it
weird talking though? I can't, this is so dumb. Grammarly helps make your writing clear.
Yeah, wait till Grammarly uses Mickey Mouse. Does anybody else, okay, this, I look, I like,
Grammarly, I don't know how good the product is. I have no idea. It's probably awesome. I wonder,
right, that being said, I wonder how much money they spend on marketing because half of every ad
I've ever received for the last almost five straight years has been Grammarly. They must have
a monster marketing budget. Monster. It has to be like half the whole company's net worth.
Right? How would it be possible for them to show ads for this long? Right? All right, I did not,
what the fuck is this video that I just put in here? Am I getting a second ad? All right,
so anyways, let's see. Shit, they do talk, whatever.
Hey Joe! Did the animals talk to the people? Okay, all right, I'm not, I'm not playing anymore of
this. They talk, whatever. All dogs go to heaven. Yeah. What about non-movie? TV show. Movies is a
different story. What about TV show? Where is the cowardly dog? Yeah, but he stands up. What's,
what is Martha? Martha speaks. Martha speaks.
Shit. They all talk?
God damn it, whatever. Wilfred? Dog with a blog? What is dog with a blog? What is this nonsense?
Kids? Wait a second. I have a challenge for all of you. Okay, where is it? I need to show it. Dog
with a blog, Disney Channel. Wait, what? Dog with a blog, Disney Channel. Okay. Have a surprise for
you. All right, he's making noises. He's a rescue from the shelter. Coming soon to Disney Channel.
Thank you. I've always. There's just one little thing. Give me the stinking food. I'm drooling a
pool over here. No, but this doesn't count because he's a, he's a real dog. Wait, what do you mean
let mom and dad find out? They can't hear him? This is awesome. I want to watch this show. Why is
this reverse Santa? Disney Channel's all new comedy. Don't tell mom and dad the dog can talk. No,
dog. I don't understand. This looks bad. I want to watch it. October, this is from 10 years ago.
All right. Still, but you understand my point. Three, two dogs that have ever existed that have
ever been created as characters have a funny dog voice if they're on all fours. It's been two ever.
So, I would think Pluto would be the third. Nine years ago. That's insane. That was the turn of the
Disney Channel century, right? Where every show was just friends for kids. What about underdog?
Underdog was stood up. He stood up right and they're still doing it. I don't even know.
People always say, well, wow, the Disney Channel, like all those shows are suck and they're boring
and they're dumb and they're just soulless. Well, how can they keep making them? Somebody
has to be watching them. All right. Where's this? I had 2%. All right. Even the list. Oh, nice. It's
still there. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Go back. Go back. Get out. I need details. Okay. Gutter's the porch. All right. Gutter's in the
porch. Over here. Does cat dog count? Um, a little, but cat dog has a funny voice. A dog is like this,
Ryan. And cat is like this. It's like, oh, cat dog. No, that's, that's not like a human talking.
That's dumb. You talk like that. I don't talk like that. Crypto the super currency.
Dog from Johnny test. Did he stand upright though? I feel like that he was like a person. He stood
upright, didn't he? We have to eliminate real dogs that have a CG mouth. That doesn't count.
The only one I've really seen was that Martha one that fits that category. What about Paw Patrol?
Yeah, but they like, they drive cars and shit. Pluto doesn't drive a car. Scooby-Doo doesn't
drive a car. You have to sit upright to drive a car. They fly planes and stuff. What about the
wonder pets? Um, you're moving the goalpost. I think the things I'm saying are very, they're valid
points. You log with the blog. Look at how beautiful this house looks. What about Clifford,
the big red dog? Um, hold on to Clifford. I always thought that he had a funny voice.
Shit, they all have normal voices. I just skipped the whole episode. I just want to hear Clifford
talk. Yeah, he's normal. Damn it. What about the live action Clifford? Your whole point has been
ruined. It doesn't matter. The point still stands. Pluto would not have a normal voice. Can we? Okay,
let's do a poll. At least give me, give me the benefit of the doubt here. Let's throw a poll
up. Would Pluto have a normal voice? I don't think he would. All right, let me go back to my
soundtrack. What was it? Brawl soundtrack. Animal Crossing sounds good. Uh, the porch fences.
Porch fences and gutters. None of Mickey Mouse and friends have normal voices. I think they kind of
do. Mickey, um, Daisy? Yeah, yes they do. Yeah, they do. They have, yeah, they're normal. They're
kind of normal. Like Goofy's is just like kind of a low, a very low booming voice. Like, gosh, Mickey,
how are you, Mickey? People talk like that. That is, how is that not normal? I just did it.
Oh gosh, Mickey. Oh, hey guys, it's me, Germo. I'm here, just having a swell time on my channel.
There are people that actually talk like that. What are you talking about? Donald is the one
that's not normal. No, 82%. Thank you. Oh my God, clean it already. And then the gutter is over here.
You just spent an hour proving nothing. Well, I sure did. I just spent an hour proving I don't
know very many dogs that are on all fours to talk. That's what you should took from that.
And guess what? Neither did you until probably 10 minutes ago.
We baa, we baa, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack.
Gutters, posts. Post, post, gutters. In here. All right, gotta get up.
We baa, we baa, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack.
Use the ladder. I just did. Is that it? No. The gutters, something over here. Come on,
it's one little thing. Posts and window frames. What do you mean post? Posts? What window frame?
Not this, right? Window frames. Which window frame? Under the frame? Tab? Yeah, it's not showing up.
Window frame. What? Now what? Posts. Oh my God. Come on. This game sucks. No, it doesn't. How dare
you. I'm furious with that person. Furious with them. This post is fine. This one's not.
What's the problem? Beautiful. All right, I got 710 bucks. I need 1250 for that. I could get this.
I'm just gonna save the money. Now I'm gonna go finish the other one. Back to the playground.
All right, where was I? I want new music. Oh, let's go to retro. Yep.
All right, let's do the big one. I can get it with this, right? Let's do soap. Why not?
This is multi-purpose cleaner. Waste of money. It kind of is. This is not that good.
Hey, this sucks. It's not worth it. Actually not worth it. This is terrible. Here we go.
Damn it. I keep fucking it up. Can I get it all? Why does it play one second of each one of these
songs? I'm already at 30% because the songs are one second long. They are? These look much longer
than this. Go back to Animal Crossing. No, I want lips. What's the lipstick song? They have a list
here. Let's see. There we go. What's it called? No, shit. It's not here. Yeah, from Panel De Pon.
Yeah, this is the one. This one is. This one's on fire. Play Plok? What happened to this game?
Nintendo has access to so many characters and so many things that are cool. Play 100 geths.
Get off of that one. We did that already. The best part of this song is that
it's not clean. This might be like the four hour version of the song. Good. Keep it on. Oh,
come on. Why is this not clean? It looks perfect. There we go. Finally. All right. Looks good. Oh,
it's the 30 minute version. Right. I want to hear the angel. The angel island zone from Brawl.
That one was also really good. I don't even like these games. Get it up. Get it up. Get it up. Get
it up. These corners here. You can really tell the part where the drummer really picks up right
here. He starts like fucking screaming right there. In the audience, you just see the drummer just
going nuts right there. He's owning his mouth and closing it like opening him out, closing it.
This is dirty. Look at how sparkly it is over there. I love it. Play it again. Brawl had the
best soundtrack. It really did. You know, they got real comfy. They got real comfortable after Brawl.
Remember how big of a deal this was? They have all these songs from other franchises, some of
them which are not even Nintendo. It was a huge fucking deal. And I think after the Brawl
soundtrack, it was kind of just like, yeah, we're just going to put music in.
They made a really big deal about this. Why is this park covered in shit? Ultimate has a massive
OST. Yeah, but I'll be honest, I only played Ultimate for a week because I got discouraged
because of how badly I got shit on and online that I was like, I'm never playing this game ever again.
Online sucks. And it's too bad because Smash Brothers is one of the only fighting games that
I actually understand. All right, now let's do, um, you know, it's true. He's told that story more
than a few times. Oh, yeah. Oh, okay. Sorry. Fighting game. I have to put a quotes or an
asterisk nest to it. It's not a fighting game. It's a party game. The game where you fight
each other with essentially health bars. It's a fighting game. Mario versus Luigi. They beat the
shit out of each other and one of them loses the fight. That's a fighting game. Now, it might not
be a very in-depth fighting game if you really want to call it that. It's not a fighting game.
It is. They're fighting each other. The characters are fighting on screen. It's a, you could call it
a party game too, but it's also a fighting game. You pick a character and one of us wins and one
of us loses. Cod is a fighting game. Dynasty Warriors is a fighting game. It's not a fighting
game. Well, what makes a fighting game a fighting game then? What makes a fighting game? No, it's
not. You could say Madden is a fighting game, couldn't you? 2D melee combat. Well, the Hadouken
is not melee. It has to have frame data and special moves. Chips are dinner. What are you talking
about? Why'd you say that? Chips are dinner? They could be. They can be if you eat chips for dinner.
Who said that? That's funny. Is that Joel? Ah, it's fucking, what a hilarious joke.
You can eat chips for dinner. It sucks. It's bad for you. You can also, you could eat hamburger
meat for dinner. Literally Smash is a fighting game. What am I gonna put on for music? Smash is
a kid's game. Okay, is it a kid's fighting game? A party game to me is like, oh, let's put on,
let's put on, let's put the Tekken soundtrack on. I don't know. You call it whatever you want,
but I remember playing like Tekken and playing like Virtua Fighter and shit. And those games,
I remember just playing it with friends and you'd get punched like three times and you'd go,
KO knockout. You just like fell off the fucking level. It was, it wasn't fun.
I remember getting caught in like a Tekken combo and I just didn't even get to play the game.
Like I felt like it wasn't pressing the buttons hard enough in some of those games.
Tekken also isn't 2D. That's right. Let's play, let's put on Tekken OST. I remember just getting,
walking outside of bounds accidentally in Virtua Fighter and never playing it again.
Just smash like a competitive fighting game. I mean, a lot of people would tell you that,
that Melee is. What separates Melee from any other fighting game? If you, okay, if you do
no items, no bullshit, just fighting each other, how is it different? Not this debate. Okay. Like
Brawl would, I would classify maybe not as a fighting game because you can just trip for no
reason. It's just, and that's, maybe that's not a fighting game. I don't know. Like imagine if
Street Fighter, if all of a sudden your character fell down like 1% of the time,
it would suck for a lot of these competitive players.
Sakurai himself said there's not, Smash is not a fighting game. So there's no debate.
I mean, but it's, it's not, but we're just playing semantics though. Oh, look at how dirty this
edge is. It's an action game. It's an action party game that includes fighting people on a stage to
reduce their health to zero and reduce their lives to zero. All right. Reduce 100%.
That's a fighting game. Yeah. I mean, I would say that's a fighting game,
but then like somebody said, what is, is CoD a fighting game? It's you and me versus each other
on like a battlefield. And I'm trying to reduce your health to zero while we fight each other
and shoot each other. Why do we have to have all these rules? Why can't we just whatever?
Guns make it a shooter. Well, striker is in mortal combat. He has a gun. Joker has a gun.
Isn't there a character in Tekken that's literally, it's like a kangaroo with boxing gloves on.
That's pretty much a Smash character. I don't think it matters what the weapon you're using
is. I really don't think so. It's a bear. Who's the kangaroo? Roger. Yeah. It is a raptor as well.
What game is that? Tekken 3 is a kangaroo and two bears. There's no role playing in most RPGs.
That's right. Yeah. So who cares? Like, what does it matter? Smash character is an anime
protagonist with a sword. Well, I mean, I will say that makes up a lot of them. Makes up a lot
of the characters, but here's the, here's the one thing I will say about Smash to kind of rebut.
Look, I don't like that there's anime character with sword for 10 characters either. Here's where
I rebuttal that. It's the only way I can rebuttal this. It's the only way that makes sense to me.
There's like 85 Smash characters. Isn't there like a hundred playable characters in the Switch one?
That's so many characters. I guess at some point you're going to make a few more protagonists with
sword. There's 80 in the Switch one. That's so many. How many characters are in Tekken? 12? 15?
50? What? There are not 50 characters in Tekken. No way. How many characters are in Tekken 4?
23 characters in Tekken 4. All right. Tekken 5. 32 in Tekken 5. Tekken 6. 39 in Tekken 6. Tekken 7.
36 in Tekken 7. Tekken 8. 51 characters. Wait, this is not out yet. Okay. So Tekken 8 is not
out yet. But even still, in the Tekken that's not out yet, 51 characters are planned for Tekken 8.
There are 80 in Smash Brothers. So how many characters are there in Street Fighter? Street
Fighter... I don't even know anything about Street Fighter. They release the same Street Fighter like
Skyrim style five times every year or two. Street Fighter 5 has come out like four times. How many
Street Fighters have there been? Street Fighter 6? How many characters are Street Fighter 6?
Eight? There are only eight characters in Street Fighter 6? How many characters in Street Fighter
5? 16. It's not out yet. Oh. We gotta stop numbering shit. I'm serious. Stop numbering
video games. Especially ones that are in a series like this. Like we're gonna get to eventually like
Tekken 17? Why? Call it like Tekken? The Battle for Azeroth or whatever the hell you want to call it.
After five, it's like all right. Do we really need to... How many are you gonna number? Like 10,
12, 15, 20? I made this joke on Twitter and I'm gonna make it on here now too because it's been
like six and a half years. When you get to the point where your numbered franchise has as many
numbers as the Jason movies, it's time to figure out another title. Think about this. In 20 more
years, trying to remember when Street Fighter 7 or 8 came out is gonna be like impossible.
Street Fighter 4 was... Wait. When the fuck was that? Street Fighter 2? Street Fighter 16? I don't
remember. When did that character come out? Street Fighter 70? I don't know. Or if you want to number
them, just do it like they... Yeah. Give it the year. Like Street Fighter 95. Street Fighter 2006.
So then I can at least know when the hell it was. Street Fighter 2020. Like I have... I know
when that was. Sonic 06. Yeah. I know exactly when that came out. In the barrage of Sonic the Hedgehog
video games, I know exactly what that game was. I know the precise opening cutscene. I know all the
characters in it. I know the exact game. Sonic 06 came out in 2005. Whatever. It's still that same
period. It's fine. What's the name of the princess in Sonic 06? Oh! I don't know anything! Eliza!
Ely... Elisa! One of those. I know it's one. It's close. Elise. Oh! Oh! What? I don't know?
I was very close. Eliza. I don't know. It was one of that. Why did I know that? Because Sonic 06,
I remember the whole game because it was 06 and I know the exact year. I know the exact place I
was sitting. Calm down. I'm calm! I remember... I have a very, very distinct memory of Sonic 06.
You know why? Because I thought that game was weird as shit. Isn't that the game where there's
like real people and you're in like a real like human city and shit and there's like real people?
It was really weird to me. It wasn't the typical, oh, you got the cat. You've got
you got the slug guy. You've got the bat person. You've got the Amy, right? It was... They were
humans in cutscenes interacting with Sonic. It was kind of strange. Mario Odyssey did that.
In Sonic 06, the characters were very like life-like human characters. Like CG human
characters. Very high detailed humans. They were not in Odyssey. They were like very high detailed
human characters in Odyssey. They were human characters in Odyssey, but they weren't like
super high quality, high detailed facial structures and stuff, were they? I don't remember that.
They were like cartoon, right? Sonic 06 had cartoon style of Sonic and then these highly
detailed human real people. This is almost done. Sonic 06 was not originally a Sonic game. Is that
why? What was it supposed to be? Who said that? Somebody did. It was supposed to be a Final Fantasy
game, was it? It was called Humans 06. Oh, that's great. Give that person a badge or something.
I need music. How about... How about... Cupcakes! How about... Cupcakes! Um, how about...
Mega Man? That sounds good. Mega Man... See, this is another problem. I know there's a few songs in
Mega Man that I would like. I don't know if it's Mega Man 3 or Mega Man 10. I'm gonna go with Mega
Man 3. Mega Man 06. This thing is dirty. Oh, it's definitely Mega Man 3. Let's pick the right one.
Under the chin. Stuck in here. I want to throw like a water grenade right here. What do you mean?
Like a clean grenade. It looks pretty good. Water balloon. Yeah, but a big one. Water bazooka? Yep.
I just said that to you like I was being asked by my mother if I was ready for school
when I was still sleeping. Yep. Honey, are you already ready? Yep. Yep. That was my favorite
thing. I always said, I'm just putting my socks on. That was the way to get away from it. Yeah,
I'm just putting my socks on with my eyes closed. I'm still in bed. I don't know why that worked.
I guess because putting socks on kind of is a pain in the ass sometimes maybe.
Like that takes a while for some reason in my child brain. And then if you hear your mother
start to come towards the room. You hear like the here comes mom. She's walking towards the door.
You rip out of the bed as fast as you fucking can. You feel horrible. You feel like shit.
But you immediately grab the fucking pair of socks and like you're struggling to put it on
your foot. And she comes in. Are you ready? Yeah, I'm just, I'm just socks on. Like you're
just so fucked up. And then you hear the door close. You look over and you just lie right back
down. And then you do it all over again. And then your mother thinks that there's like something
wrong with you because I was just in here 10 minutes ago and you're still having trouble
putting your socks on. What are you doing? Are you all right? You're putting the sock on the same
foot when I came in here 10 minutes ago. There was one time when I didn't want to go to school.
I was like, I don't want to go to school today. Fuck that. I'm staying home. Like, oh, I don't
feel good. Oh, my stomach hurts. Oh, okay. Yeah. Take your temperature. And I took the thermometer
and I held it up. I held it up to a light bulb when she left the room. Like a hot light bulb.
I held it up right to the light bulb. And then I, when I heard her coming back in,
she was coming back in the room and I put it under my tongue. I put it like in my mouth.
And she grabbed it. And it was like 110. Something fucking crazy. And she's like,
uh, what is going on? I don't feel good. And it was just like, go to school. Get up. No,
but I don't feel good. I think I have a temperature. Okay, because if you had 108
temperatures, you'd be dead. Um, you're still alive. So I don't know what you did here,
but get up and go to fucking school. I'd be like, oh, whatever. I would just get up and get ready.
Stole that from ET. I probably did. Probably watched it and thought it would work.
I used to do that shit. I put orange juice in my, I'm not, I'm not making this up. This is a
fucking real story. I put orange juice in my mouth one time and went to, so my grandmother was around.
My grandmother was watching us at the time. And I put orange juice in my mouth and like went on the
ground going like, Oh no, like I'm going to puke. And I went like, and I spit like three tablespoons
of orange juice onto the ground. It was like, what are you doing? I was like, I'm sexy. You were a
little shit. No, I just, no, I wasn't. It was a tile floor. So it was easy to clean. I was like 10
and it was, it was very clearly. I put orange juice in my mouth and I was like, I'm, look at me.
I'm sick. I'm puking on the ground and it never worked. I always thought somehow it was going to
work one day and it never did. It's really funny because if I, if I had just, and I used to do this
sometimes, if I was like, like, nah, I'm not really feeling that great. I'm really kind of,
I think I need to take like a day. I'm like, I don't feel great. It was like, okay, yeah, sure.
But it was the times that I was like, oh, I'm sick.
And I would always put on a voice. You guys ever do that? You ever put on the, I'm sick voice?
Here's the, I'm sick voice. Mom, I don't feel good. Yeah. I don't know if something's wrong.
I think I like, I have a headache and everything. What, what does that, what does that mean?
Doesn't mean anything. Oh, I feel good because my head is hurting. Nobody talks like that. Even
when you're sick, what are you doing? If, if I had just been honest with my mother, it wouldn't be
like, all right, go to school. It'd be like, oh, all right. You don't, that's fine. Yeah. Take a day.
It was not hard. It would just be like, I don't really feel like going to school today. I like,
don't feel like it. It's like, all right. Is everything all right? Like, yeah, I just,
I don't know. I just don't want to. I'm telling you right now, it was a fucking miracle that I
like passed any school besides college. I actually, I tried. I really did try in college. I did.
I want, I wanted to like do well and I want to do like college stuff. And I, I really did try.
But man, in high school and in middle school, I think, I honestly think I did one homework
worksheet in four years. I seriously think that I truly believe that. And I would just do well on
the tests. Like I would just get like an 80 or 85 on the tests. I just wouldn't ever do homework,
ever. 2.6 Andy. 2.8, 2.6. Same. I hated homework. Homework is such a scam. It really is.
Nobody wants to do that shit at their house. I don't think it does anything for kids. I really
don't think it helps retain information. I really don't think so. I actually don't believe that.
I think homework makes a little bit of sense. It's almost like the teachers are trying just to get
you to continue to pay attention or something. But it's like, like, no, no, no, you have to go
back into your house and do this too. Cause I want to make sure you fucking paid attention today.
Well, make your class not suck. How does that sound? And then you have the other problem is
teachers are so underpaid, at least in America, we should be, we should be paying teachers a shit
load of money. And I mean it in an absolute metric fuck ton of money. Schools should only be four
days a week and it shouldn't be six hours. It should be like fucking four. Pay teachers a shit
load of money and it'll be like classes will be better. They'll be more interesting, have interesting
classes. You know what I mean? Why is it so hard to figure out? This actually is not even that hard
of a thing to figure out. This is not even difficult. This is like common sense. I was so
unproductive when I was a kid because I waking up at six o'clock in the morning and going to school
for six hours, I just, it sucked. I just didn't want to do it. I didn't want to do it. Now imagine
if school didn't start till fucking 10 or 9 and the classes were interesting, the teachers really
gave a shit, really, really did. And there are teachers that do give a shit. They do, a lot of
them. Pay the teachers more money. I would get the 30 fucking thousand dollars a year for a teacher,
40,000. Double that overnight, immediately. Holy shit, we're talking about our kids' brains for
God's sake. So much more productivity comes in place when people like want to do it and they're
prepared to do it and it's not, they're not being forced to do it. I think that's the biggest problem.
I really do. When I was in school, I felt like I was forced to do it. And there were some classes,
there were some times where I felt like, oh, actually, you know what, like doing this math
problem, I actually kind of liked this. It wasn't every day at all. Because maybe like a few times,
maybe like a few times a week was I really like in the head space of like, you know what, I guess
I can do like a bunch of long division or something. Fine. You can jump in the game. Yeah, take a look.
And it's like, even for the kids that really excel, I'm sure some of you, I'm sure probably
really excel in school. I'm sure you do. But how much more, how much better would you be doing
if you had the more tools to do better? If the classes were even more interesting, right? If
like your teachers didn't have to fucking fight the budget board to like get pens and shit and
like pencils, you know what I mean? Like there's so much things that teachers would like to do.
We're having a money. I don't know. I don't know. I don't think so. I would probably still hate
school. Look, school is school, right? You got, you do it. You got to learn stuff. And there's
another thing. What in the name of God, and I'm going to go off on this, right? This is time to
do it during the Mega Man song, right? I don't care. I'm just going off. I'm doing it. Why do
we not teach everybody, put a huge emphasis on like finances and, and how to like file a
fucking tax return and stuff. We spend like an hour on that shit. Sometimes like maybe one week
of like your, your home ec class is about some of this stuff. Teach kids what like a credit
score is, what like a credit card does. Financial like literacy, like we need to teach this shit to
people. Like we don't even, it's just, oh, well maybe one day they'll figure it out. What the
hell is school for? If not to prepare everybody for adulthood, right? It's to prepare us for the
fucking world. I'll be honest. I don't really care about like doing math problems or what
like Genghis Khan did. We have Netflix documentaries that can cover that shit in an hour.
And I'm not saying that stuff's not important. It is. It is. We need to obviously learn about
who we are and where, what people are, where they're from, what people have done,
what the world was like, what are the things that happened, major important, of course.
But to replace, to replace like actual life skills and teaching people things that they're
going to need. I think the focus is on preparing people for adulthood because when you're not
prepared for adulthood, then you get stuck. Are you running for office? Yes. No, I'm not.
This is not even some like, oh wow, he was so brave. No, I don't think that. I just,
I honestly just think. You guys know how much, you want to get like angry for a second?
Look at, at least in the United States, go look at the breakdown of where our federal tax dollars
go. Just go do it. It takes two seconds. Go look at where education is, how much we spend federally
on education. Huh? What? They need to increase that by a huge amount. This is not, it's not
political. This is not political. This is just like, well, well, well, well, it is political,
whatever. I'm breaking my own rules. I know. No, it's not political. It's not political.
I'm just telling you to go look. We don't spend very much on education at all.
And it's incredibly important. It's not politics. It's just, this is just whatever. It's not a lot.
And like, why is it not a lot? We don't, we, education is so important. Science, medicine,
technology, right? Like these are things we need to do. Just go look at the budget one day. Just go
look at it and be like, Oh, I wonder where our money goes. And just look at it. Just stare at it
for a half a minute. This is based. No, it's not. It's not. It really isn't. This is very based. I
mean, I just think it's, I think a lot of issues could be solved in our country, in our world,
in our country. Let me, let me put like fake fucking crowd music. I think that a lot of issues
in our country can be completely solved by having a much better education system, teaching kids
what they need to learn to be an adult. Fine. I'm talking about financial literacy. I'm talking about
skills that they'll need to learn to be a functioning adult. I'm talking about being
able to teach kids, not just about like history and science and social studies. I'm talking
about life skills, things you need. It shouldn't be 2% of the budget. It should be probably 10.
If that's political, I'm sorry, then this is a political stream at the moment or this moment.
I don't think it is. More money to teachers, more money to programs. Like you take a look at,
you take a look at what are like our programs that are suffering right now.
Extracurricular shit to like, like our arts and the arts programs are all just suffering.
You know what I mean? Like what the hell's going on? Oh, I'm looking at my phone.
Hold your applause for a second. I had to look at my phone. He's getting texted. No, but seriously,
programs like, okay, when we did the archeology thing, like the science center, they do virtual
field trips and shit. Imagine how awesome that would be if that was just no, like just a part
of everybody's lives as a kid. More field trips, do more cool shit. I don't want to go to the same
place for a field trip. I don't want a field trip to just be, we go into a bus and go to Dairy Queen.
That's not a field trip. You know how many times I've seen the people, the old time people churn
the butter when I was younger? Oh, this is what it was like back in the old times. I've been to that
place like 10 times and go Red Sox. Oh, this feels good. I like this. Okay. Okay. Okay. Thank you.
But seriously, if you go look at where our money goes, I think we could really stand to put a
little more of our, we could restructure our budget a little bit, have people going to school and
shit be really important. I guess it is important and not just not shitty school, not dumb school,
not school that everybody hates going to. I don't want to dump a shitload more money into
a boring shitty education system. I'm talking about, let's redo the whole goddamn thing.
Make it good. Make it fun. Make it interesting. Make it engaging. You know what I mean? Then you'd
want to do it. You'd want to go and fuck Capcom by the way. Yeah. You say that at like the political,
at like the big speech and like my campaign rally and fuck Capcom. What's with the FOV?
They need to change that. And honestly, I don't think it even matters like where you even stand
politically. I think that everybody could probably agree that we got to, we got to make our shit a
little better. You know what I mean? We've got to like put another, a higher standard here. We've
got to make a little bit more. I don't think that's like a necessarily biased statement to
any political leaning. I really don't think it is. No, you don't know what I am. You don't
know how I lean politically. I've never talked about it. You have no idea. You have absolutely
no idea. You guess. I'm going to keep you guessing. But that's not what this stream is for. And we
talked about that before as well. But sometimes, you know, you got to talk about some things.
I had to. I had to. I've got something on my mind recently. It has. You literally told us. No,
I didn't. I thought you were centrist. No, when did I say that? I said that? When did I say that?
When did I say that? Did I get shitfaced one day and say that? Was I like drunk on wine and I was
like, I'm a centrist. When did that happen? I don't think that happened. That didn't happen.
You didn't have to say that. What are you talking about? I've never, it's a fucking secret
of what, how, what I believe. All right. And no, don't let anybody ever tell you differently.
It's obvious. What's obvious? What do you mean it's obvious? Why are you panicking? I'm not
panicking. Whatever. It's in your rant section on YouTube, is it? You support Verbin Supreme.
I mean, that guy's fucking hilarious, but I don't know what his policies are. I'm already at 60%
here. Just admit it. You watched Bionicle with Biden. It's obvious. We know. You don't know
anything. Nobody knows anything. Let me just pretend that people don't know. An anarchist?
I'm not an anarchist. What are you talking about? You're a Minecraft anarchist. I don't even know
what that is. I have no idea what I just said. The ultimate secret of German 985s political leanings.
All right. This is good. I want more soap. Soap is pretty good here. Soap is actually good here.
I gotta get in there. How do I get up there? Do I have to go across the bars? He's a biblio
gugu gaga ding dongist. What is that? Sure, I guess. Stop playing this? I'm having fun. I like this.
There we go. Get in there. That's my dirt KD. Pretty high. Show us what you look like without
your dentures in. Why would I do that? I don't like the way I look without my dentures in. Why
would I do that? Stop hot boxing the playground. This is open air in here. Geriatric Andy. I'm not
geriatric. I am getting older though. You do have that right. It's okay to get older. I don't feel a
day over 30. I definitely feel 30 though. In fact, probably a little bit older. I don't feel a day
over 32. You know what I mean? I missed it. You said something but I missed it. 62%. Let's go.
How is it like living past 30? I like it. I like it. I like being 30 plus. Slow down a little bit.
Takes me a little longer. I just like kind of chill. Oh, I know. I get that.
You get angry when young people are loud. I get angry when anybody gets loud.
I like that. Trinket. From a chill, you're not 60. Yeah, I can guarantee you that I've lost a
step or two though. I mean, look, I already have like a medical problem, right? I didn't have that
in my 20s. That started in my 30s. Already, I can tell you, I've slowed down quite a bit.
Is there a ladder here? Because this is annoying. All right, this is done. I'm 20 and I have a
bunch of medical problems. It's really a dice roll. Yeah, I know. That's true. I'm sorry to hear that
though. Get some music? All right, yeah. Do it. What the fuck? He didn't even do it.
Do it. Why won't he do it? Why was this file? The person played in the wrong file or something.
Fucking do it. Thank you. It's not the mandala effect. It's right there. I need an actual
OST though. How about Donut Country? Oh, this is nice. Sure. I have a homework assignment for you
guys. I know homework. You don't want to do homework. I know we just talked about it, but that
it's in something else and I don't know what it's in. It's been bugging me for like 25 fucking years.
It's in something else. It happens in either another game or a TV show or it's been bugging
me for like 20 years. When's the homework due? Next week. Oh, this is oh my god. This one's
horrible. I'm buying the soap. Let's go. It works so much better. I can do the rest of the cleanup
later with the save for the new gun. Okay, that's good. Now go like this. This nozzle is terrible.
The only thing that takes any dirt up anymore is the green and the yellow and barely the green.
I need that new gun right now. Was it 1200? I don't know this song. Just skipping. Like it was a CD.
Why is it doing that? 1080 nozzle. I got a 3090 now, man. Nice flex. No, see what happened was
I was forced to buy one because graphics cards didn't exist and me and Community Jake were both
desperately in all these different places trying to find a graphics card because remember eight
months ago when I wanted to build a new computer? So I didn't want a 3090, but I got a 3090 because
that was all that was available and I'll tell you this thing is hot. This thing runs way hotter
than my 1080. So now I get computer room syndrome which means it just gets so hot in here because I
have this monster 3090 in here generating furnace level of heat. What's the average temp on it?
It's really high. I'm gonna have to do something about it. It's way too high. I think it hits like
90 Celsius 95 92 all the time. I think it peaks at like 100. Underclock it. It's not overclocked.
It's just regular clock speed. Yeah, these things just run insanely hot. I looked it up.
I might have to get a cooler for this thing in particular. Underclock it. Why would I want to do
that? Memory runs warm probably referring to that. Micron posted actual specs recently. Max 105
Celsius under load. That seems so hot. That seems like it shouldn't be like that. That's more than
boiling water, isn't it? That's like 200 something degrees. Get a water cooler. Yeah, I'm gonna have
to do something. I really don't want one of those big elaborate tube systems though. I can just get
a GPU cooler and replace the stock fans on it, right? That'll probably be fine. Get an AIO. AIO, okay.
What's an AIO? This whole thing under here. PC will cool it, but your room might be just as hot.
Yeah, they make it make AC units for the back of a computer. I think they do. They're probably so
stupid expensive though. All the geek squad. Stick it in the fridge. Just get a mini fridge,
put the computer in the mini fridge, and have the power cord be coming out of like a hole I drilled.
Would that work? What would that do? That would work, right? There's a Linus Tech Tips video on
that. That's funny. I'll have to watch that later. 73%. All right, get in there. Can you power wash
your balls? Well, if you did that, I don't... I think you'd be at the hospital. That would be a
bad idea. I think that would be a major, major mistake. I would not ever ever do something like
that. Sounds very dangerous and very stupid. God. 74. This one should be way more than 400 bucks.
It should be way more. This is so much more time. This is so much more work. GPU hot tub?
And if you dropped a GPU into oil or something, right? What are those computers I see sometimes
where all the parts are just in oil? It's like an oil-cooled PC or something. It's weird. Mineral
oil. Does that work? Deep fried PC. I saw videos on it before where the entire computer is just
submerged in mineral oil, right? There's a lot of downsides to it, but it does sort of work, huh?
Well, I mean, problem number one is I really don't want to fry later sitting in my room just
ready to tip over. Oh, what do I want to eat? I just thought of like fried chicken. Somebody said
KFC. It'd be like Taco Bell or something. Re-cheesy godita crunches with the Doritos,
Locos, Tacos. Yep. I think that sounds like a great idea to me. That's the best thing there.
Oh, bean burrito? The cheesy godita crunch really might be the single most brilliant fast food
invention. It really is. I think it is like the best fast food item. Where did I put it on the
tier list? I put it up real high, didn't I? Where was it? Was it A? Was it S or was it A or B? It
was somewhere higher. It was A. Where did I put an S tier for fast food stuff? German 985 meal?
At Taco Bell, it's three cheesy godita crunches with Doritos, Tacos, and that's it. You just get
a drink. That's it. You don't get anything else. Not even the cinnamon things? No, no, I just want
I'm trying to really think the last time I ordered something else off the Taco Bell menu
that was not that. I don't think I ever have. Well, before the cheesy godita crunch came out,
I ordered tacos, the Mexican pizza they had there, chalupa, whatever. After cheesy godita crunch,
every single order was cheesy godita crunch. I've never ordered anything else off of that menu
since 1998, whenever it was. It's so good. It really is. It is so good. Oh, I'm getting it.
I want it right now. What's your opinion on the Crunch Wrap Supreme? It's not the cheesy
godita crunch, so I will never order it and I will never eat it. I've never had it and I never
will. There's no other reason. There's no reason for me to order it. All right, if Taco Bell pulls
a fast one here and they remove that off the menu, I'm not sure I would ever go there again.
I really don't think so. There's no reason for me to be there. I go to Taco Bell for the cheesy
godita crunch. If it's not there, I'm not going. Fuck you, German. The Crunch Wrap is a staple.
I'm sure it's good. It doesn't matter. I'm never going to order something that's not
the cheesy godita crunch. It's never going to happen. Because you could say, well, dude,
you get three cheesy godita crunches. Just order two and get a Crunch Wrap. No, no, no, no, no.
Excuse me. No, thank you. That's one full cheesy godita crunch I will not be able to enjoy.
I want the full satisfaction. I will take a bite of the Crunch Wrap Supreme and be sitting there
going, I wish this was a cheesy godita crunch. Why did I order it? I wish they would make
more cheesy godita crunch variants. They just have the normal one and then they have the Doritos
one. Make some different ones. You're a cheesy godita dunce. That was pretty good.
This place is so, how could dirt be in every single area? What even is 864p? Don't click it,
man. It was a part of a prank video I'm doing. We just finished the shoot and I don't want
anyone else to click on it. Just be careful. Don't click it. If you want to know, it's the,
it's a resolution that's divisible by 8, therefore it is true 16 by 9. If you don't
have a resolution that's divisible by 8, then the program has to do extra work
for pixels that don't exist. That's it. See, I'm smart, I know things. I mean, I would,
I want to up my bitrate, but I don't think I can. I think there's a cap on what you're allowed to
actually do for a bitrate. It was a huge frog burp and I hope nobody heard it. Yeah, 6k, yeah.
To have anything over 720 not look like ass at 60 FPS, that's got to be at least 8,000.
8, 9, 10,000. You can do 1080 30 and it will look probably fine. Either that or you have to have
such a monster CPU that you can drop the preset down to like slow or slowest and then you don't
need the bitrate. But I don't have a CPU that can do that. I haven't really tried though.
What OST is this? This is pretty good. I forgot what it was. What's my CPU? My CPU is, I actually
forget. It's a new computer. Oh, my CPU is a Ryzen 7 5800X 8 core. So it's a 5800X Ryzen 7
8 core. It has 30 webcams but not two PCs. Well, the 30 webcam stream, the problem was all the
the bus lanes. There's only a certain amount of lanes on a motherboard where you can plug in like
webcam but there's a solution for it. Actually, Community Jake and I have been talking about that
one and the solution for it is something we can do. Maybe it would be fun to do. I donated all the
webcams. I had like 30 webcams. Like I had like at least 20, 15. I just donated them. I couldn't
even use them. I was never gonna be able to use them. Did you sign them? No, why would I sign them?
30, 20, 15. Yeah, whatever. Buff, puke, whatever. Sidekick, puke. Oh, we have a horrible news.
Pizza the Hut ate himself in his car. He was locked in his car. What's that from Spaceballs?
Oh, that's a good movie. Pizza the Hut, he had to eat himself because he locked himself in his car.
I keep overlooking that from that movie. That guy literally ate himself and died. How do you eat
yourself? He was a pizza. If you didn't see Spaceballs, Pizza the Hut is a character who
is just a slice of pizza. He's disgusting. It's gross. There's like cheese falling off of him
and pepperonis and shit. It's really odd. He's a really fucking crazy character. The king of the
Schwartz. See you next time for Spaceballs 2. The search for more money. That's classic Mel Brooks,
man. There's not, I don't think there's very much Mel Brooks did that I didn't like.
Rick Moranis. He was so good in that movie too. What the hell am I looking at? There's a lot of
new people here, but that's my favorite gag ever. If you want to know what my all-time favorite
joke ever and any piece of media ever. Comedy, stand-up, movies, TV shows, video games. It's
that scene from Spaceballs where they have to put the Spaceballs movie into the fucking video player
to find out what they have to do next. That's, that is the best joke I've ever seen.
Nothing even comes close. Not even close. Oh, fast-forward this part. Yeah, I guess it's like
the embarrassing part where he like falls and like hits his head. He's like fast-forward this part.
In fact, never play this again. Then they go too far and they get to the point where they're
actually in the same part of the movie of them standing there looking at the screen.
It's like, what is this? And he's like, oh, it's now, sir. We're watching now.
How does this make any sense? This can't be. If you've never seen Spaceballs, that's required
reading for this stream. What's the syllabus? I could give you guys the syllabus.
That actually is funny to me. Should I make a syllabus for you guys of things you have to
watch before watching this stream? I like that. That's actually kind of funny. 85%. All right,
come on, let's go. The syllabus, by the way, has nothing to do with any of my content.
You don't have to go watch any of my videos. Just go watch Spaceballs three times. Watch
Ghostbusters one, Ghostbusters two, Gremlins two. Gremlins one is good, but Gremlins two is
better. I can make the whole syllabus for you. All the Shpee videos. Don't do that. Gremlins
two is also one of the most important movies of my entire life. So yeah, I would say that that is
huge too. Who Framed Roger Rabbit? That's another one that's incredibly important, required reading.
That's embarrassing. Who Framed Roger Rabbit is embarrassing? That's in the Library of Congress.
Cars two is in the Library of Congress. Doesn't matter. 86%. What's something that I have not
done at all? Oh, down here. What about Robocop? Robocop is good, but I wouldn't put that in my
required reading list. Gorilla's Demon Days and Plastic Beach. Also required reading.
What else is in there? And Plastic Beach. Yeah, I really like Plastic Beach a lot.
A lot. I thought it was fantastic. A lot of people might not agree with that, but
I think that's... It's really easy to say Demon Days is the best album, but I think Plastic
Beach is. I know people are going to be like, no fucking way, but I just really... Replayability,
re-listenability. I've listened to Plastic Beach's songs more than I have Demon Days.
And Demon Days is just a rock solid. Just absolute banger after banger. But for some reason,
Plastic Beach just did it more for me. I don't know why. 89. I mean, I think that arrow,
Phase 2 and Phase 3 of the Gorilla's, I think that's the best. That's when they were at their
absolute peak. That's not to say that I didn't like humans, but Plastic Beach and Demon Days
are way better. Song Machine is good too. I actually haven't really given it much listen.
I'll have to do that. I liked that single they came out with. What was it called? Humility?
I like that song.
That was really good. That's from the Now Now. I actually... People were really mixed on
Saturn bars. I really liked it. I thought it was really good. 91%. This one is the longest out of
all of them. I like Moments was good too. Moments was just all... It was just super. When you put
Moments on it, my whole body would just move. I'm so happy De La Soul continued to do stuff
with the Gorilla's. They're so good. A lot of times, the Gorilla's will have that one-off
where it's like, oh yeah, they were on that Gorilla's album that one time,
but De La Soul is just on every album. I love it. What am I missing? There's a lot of places
I'm missing. Where is it? Trash. Lou Reed collab with them too. Yeah, what was the Lou Reed song?
I forget what it was. It was in Plastic Beach, right? Yeah, it was Plastic Beach. Oh yeah,
some kind of nature. That's right. I love Stylo too though. Stylo was awesome. That was a driving
song. It really was. Bruce Willis video was rad. Yeah, it was. Now you make me want to listen to
the Gorilla's. I love to do that with my cheesy Gordita Crunch. Is this already clean? Kind of.
Different nozzle. That's the problem. There it is. It sounds like the Dr. House song.
It's a song called Teardrop, right? Can I play this for a second on stream? Are we allowed to
enjoy anything in 2021? Am I allowed to make a reference to any media I've ever watched and
thought was cool to share with anybody? No? I have to lock myself in my fucking room, turn the lights
off, close all the windows, put headphones on and not tell anybody I ever listen to it.
I would play it right now. What the fuck? Whatever. Oh, this is very dirty under here.
This is a lot of fun. This is very therapeutic. If you're looking for a game that's just
therapeutic. This is one of them. This is fun. I like this. This is early access. I wonder what
they're going to put in the full game. I'm curious. It doesn't need to be anything else, right? It
knows exactly what it is. That's what it's going to give you. That's it. Almost 1K in the bank.
Almost. Wait, this is genuinely a waste of life. Wait, what are you talking about? What?
I'm just spraying some walls, man. I'm just hanging out, man.
You can say that about anything. Why have you not played the Bugsnax LST? I don't think I can. I
think that song is copyright, isn't it? It's a waste of life. What the fuck? Let's go with the big one.
I think this is, yeah, that's fine. Okay. Well, there it goes. IRL power washing stream. When?
Nope. I'll keep it in the head. I'll keep it up here. You might see it eventually. I think that'd
be fun. Almost done. Man, this is a pain in the ass. This one doesn't want to go. I've got to get
the other side. How am I going to get that? Are we going to get into through the ages stream?
I don't know. That was kind of fun for a little while. Maybe. That was pretty fun. Maybe we should
do that. A lot more people here now than were here before. I'll give you some context. Those
that don't know what we're talking about. So through the ages stream was, there was a website
that was made that pulled every single stream I've ever done, every single video I've ever uploaded,
and it picked a random timestamp randomly across one of those places. So it randomly picked the
video and then randomly picked the timestamp. And the idea was we were supposed to see what we got.
I did it with channel points. I don't think I'll even do it with channel points this time.
It'll probably just be like five minutes. Just five minutes or 10 minutes it just switches
automatically. I'm gonna get up. Is there a ladder? What about another royalty-free movie night? Yeah,
I'd want to make sure that the movies were good and not just, because the movies we watched were
funny. Is there any more Ritz Brothers movies? That's all I care about. It can't be Bionicle.
I looked into it. That's like a copywritten movie. I can't broadcast that. Even if it's free on the
internet, I don't have the rights to broadcast it. I need something that there are no rights holders.
There are still people that own the rights to all the media around Bionicle. I can't stream it.
Do it anyways. Oh, okay. All right. Well, I'll see when the channel gets deleted.
It was a good run. Should I throw it all away for Bionicle? What do you think?
I mean, that'd be kind of a hilarious last stream ever. That would be lame as hell if that was my
final stream. I mean, it kind of would be. What if you did it with Joe Biden? What would, how would
they, what would, they wouldn't be able to do anything but about the president. I'm not going
to stream this. Just make a movie and watch it. I mean, I made a thousand YouTube videos.
We've watched a bunch of those already. When is Otto's Pogtastic Adventure? I don't know. I have
to make it. Streamer videos, resident sleeper. Everybody's entitled to their opinion. You can
have that. You can, you can think my shit sucks if you want. That's fine. I'm not going to combat you
on that. You are free to have an opinion, which you have. I can't change that. All I can do is
say thanks for watching. Thanks for coming here. Thanks for spending your day here. I was going to
scream. I was going to just scream like, get the fuck out of it. I was going to scream it.
My voice is already kind of fucked up and I thought it might've scared a bunch of people.
So I didn't do it. Some people are probably actually lying down right now and I don't want
to scream in their ear. Shit, I got to move the ladder. Wait, no, I don't. Can I just get up here?
Some people are probably asleep. Should we like fuck with their dreams? How do we do that? Like,
just talk about how they're asleep right now. You're asleep right now. You sleeping right now. I
know you're asleep. Wake up for a sec. Look around you. This is a dream. Don't worry. This is a dream.
It's me, Derma, talking to you. Sleeping. Make sure you take the trash out. Go back to bed now.
I don't have anything funny to say. I thought I might have something funny to say, but I didn't
come up with anything quick enough. So I told you to do a small chore. Go back to bed. This is a
dream. It's a dream. Don't worry. You're fine. It's a dream. 20,455. 20,460. 20,466. 20,600.
Oh, get me off. I can't take it. That's not a prime number. Whatever. I don't know. I don't
know prime numbers. Put on forest sound effects. Make them think they're in the woods. Put an ocean
sound effect. Hey, you're asleep right now and you're in the ocean. All right. Yeah. Let's
make them think they're in the ocean. Hey there. It's me, Derma985 on the beach with you.
This is a dream. Don't worry. Don't get up. Just take in the salty air.
Hear the seagulls. Ah, it's so fresh out here. Don't you think? What I want you to do is I want
you to let go. Anything negative that you're thinking of is the waves. And you and me here,
when you wake from your sleep, don't get up. Don't get up. It's okay. You're going to go
to twitch.tv slash Derma985. If you're not already, which you have to be because you're
here with me in a dream. Ah, you're going to. I was going to say sub to me and shit,
but I don't want to do that. It's still a dream. Don't it's you're still in a dream.
Look at the boat go by. Wow. Watch the seagulls. Look above you. They just flew up one shit in my
mouth. Oh, what the fuck? Oh, don't get up right now. You're still in a dream.
When you rise, I want you to just have a new clean day, clear day, clear head after this.
You're going to watch Derma's streams. He's so good. He's so funny. He's like the funniest guy
on Twitch. And continue to watch. He's like your favorite. Let's hear the waves and my voice.
I snap my fingers. You're going to wake up and you're going to act like a chicken.
The audience is going to laugh in three, two, one. You're up. You're up. I don't know, man.
I was going to do like the sub thing, but like I got caught halfway through and I just,
it felt very ugly and I didn't want to do it. Fuck, fuck. Oh, everybody's laughing. I can't
believe it. He's doing a chicken. He's doing a chicken noise. Statistically, you have at least
one celebrity fan. Who do you think it is? It's you. So I got to figure out who you are.
You are literally the celebrity in your underwear watching the stream right now.
And you asked me that question. So I wonder who you are. I'm going to say,
who would word it like that? The Grinch? The Grinch is not a person.
It's a character that an actor plays. It's not Vin Diesel. No, it's not. No, who is it then?
I don't know. Who is that? Yeah. You know what? It's probably like a senator or something. It's
probably, it's probably like a congressman or like a congresswoman or something. And it's probably
like a congressman that you would not expect. Dave State. It's Mitch McConnell. I was asleep
during German on at fives as well as a stream. And he was very, very kind to me.
And he told me to be the best I can. So what I've decided is I've decided that there will be no more
stimulus. We don't need another stimulus. I've decided to stimulate German's bank account
by providing $200 million to his bank account. All in favor of that stimulus, say aye.
That's not even how it works. Don't you have to vote? Mitch McConnell. Guys, I don't think
it's Mitch McConnell. I think Mitch McConnell still has trouble opening up web browsers.
I think Mitch McConnell still needs to call his son to ask him how, like, Microsoft Network still
works. Like, yeah, I would feel like he has like an MSN account, don't you? Mitch McConnell's the
kind of guy that has like an at AOL email. All right, what's left? Okay, the monkey bars,
tools, the bin. What bin? The trash bin? What's wrong with this? Is it the back? Oh,
shit. It's up there. This place looks pretty good. I can't wait to see the time lapse.
There's a second bin. I'll go look. And by the way, what level of celebrity are you guys talking
about? Are you talking about an A list celebrity? Are you talking about like a person of interest
or something? Like an A list. I don't know if any A list celebrities watch this stream.
You think it's Tom Holland? I don't think so. I don't know. Might be. Imagine if I imagine ever
meeting somebody like a comic con or something. Oh, yeah. Like at the autograph signing or
something. It's like, Oh, hey, Mitch McConnell. Oh, Mitch McConnell. Wow. I can't believe you're
at Comic Con. I mean, I may as well be being a rubber mask. I might be a scary monster. But
I may as well be a scary guy. So Tom Holland. I fucked up the whole thing. Going up to Tom
Holland at Comic Con or something and getting something signed. And then being like, Oh,
here you go. What's the name? The name? Jeremy. Jeremy. Jeremy. Oh, yeah. And he leans in and
just whispers into my ear, I love that Mitch McConnell voice. What would I do? I love that
Mitch McConnell voice you do. Hang out with me. Should I scream that? What's left? Oh, over there.
Okay. I'd be like, Oh, Spider-Man is my favorite character. Spider-Man is my favorite character.
I love Spider-Man. Spider-Man is my favorite character. And he'd go, All right, man. And I'd
be like, Oh, it's me, Mitch McConnell. I can't do it. Hold on. Miss Damien. I can't. You liked it,
though. I love Spider-Man. I would have to do his favorite character in front of him. I would get
it so wrong. I would be so choked up like this. I wouldn't be able to do anything. But I would
have to do another character instead. I'd be like, You like Mitch McConnell, but I'll give you another
one. Here's SpongeBob. And security just grabs me. And then somebody a week later comes in with a
username. Nice SpongeBob, LOL. Nice SpongeBob impression, LOL. And I know it's him. That's
their username. Oh, it's inside. This is a huge fan fiction. No, it's not. This is not real. This
is just make believe of nothing. Self-insert fanfic. Yeah, I know. Whatever. What's not clean?
Stools. What else? Uh, the bars. That's the only factual thing you've heard me say in this stream
so far. Is the cheesy Godita crunch is the best item at Taco Bell. And that we need to redo our
education system. Those are the only two things I've said that are real. What is left? A bench.
Which one? Underneath? This one? No, it's the other one, right? So what about when you said you never
pooed your diaper? I did probably a lot. I did probably all the time. When I was one. A lot of
you guys don't want to hear this, but you probably have filled, you yourself, you listening to this
right now, have filled probably two to three thousand diapers of shit. You don't want to
hear that though. But you did. What do you mean question marks? Oh, almost there. I have 1,160.
Oh, cool. What about you throwing up orange juice on the floor? Yes, that was real. Golf cart.
This will be quick. This will be really quick. Give me the big one. Give me the, uh, no. Should
I just spray? This should do it. Yeah, this will be quick. Okay. I got to get the other nozzle.
You said you missed the whole screen because your Wi-Fi died. Oh shit. I'm sorry.
But mud. Get it. Who covered the cart in cheese? I think what the actual question is who took the
cart off-roading? Jackass. Johnny Knoxville. Maybe it's Johnny Knoxville. You're gonna do
more VR streams? I am gonna do more VR streams. That's coming up soon. I actually think I might be
getting an index because the Vive is, I like my Vive, but I broke the controller. So I need to
get the knuckle controllers anyways. I think I kind of want to upgrade. So I'll probably just,
I'll probably donate the one I have now to another one because I had the original Vive,
not the Vive Pro or the new one. That, I think that was the original Vive.
I'll probably get an index. Isn't there another one? What's it called? There's another one that's
coming out too. Isn't there? Wait, 1250? Well, all right. I have enough. The Oculus Quest 2 is good,
but requires Facebook. And the Reverb G2 is supposedly really good too. I'll probably just
get the index. I feel like that's the one to get if you were going to get one. All right. Medium duty.
Here we go. Surface more, more, more. Oily ingrained. What's that do? All right. So now I
already got the attachments for it, right? So now I got this detached house. This place is huge.
Reverb G2 is great when WMR decides to work properly. Index is a goodbye if you're just
going to do strange stuff. Okay. All right. So where, where's my, where's my new nozzle?
Just bought it. Where is it? Isn't it one of these ones here? Medium duty, the Urban XU2.
I own the attachment. Where is it? I didn't equip it. How do I equip it? Oh, E. Okay. And we'll do
the extension. Ooh, that's better. All right. I think I should be able to do this now, right?
Looks like a gas tank. It's not optimal. I like going side to side. It's much better for my brain.
Yeah. What the fuck? This thing sucks. I just take it off. This thing sucks. Dope. Oh shit.
That's right. I should do soap. Oh, I don't have the soap nozzle. It's like 500 bucks.
Even this, maybe this is just really dirty. Shoot closer. It's the distance.
It is kind of distance, isn't it? All right. Not bad. Nice. There we go. Looks better. Change the
radio. Oh, about. All right. This, this is probably going to be the last thing we do
after this house. I'd probably call it. What's, um, what's a good one?
Ape escape. Oh, I like plants versus zombies. That's a good one. That's a good one.
All right. Let's go. We're zombies. We're coming.
And if only they made the second game, not a never ending cash grab or pop cap. Pop cap had
so many cool games. Can you imagine not making an insane aquarium? Another one. Why won't they make
another one? Why would they not have met? I would have rather taken the pay to win insane aquarium.
They just leaned so heavy into plants versus zombies. It made like five games of plants versus
zombies. It's like, I, I will give me something else. It's my favorite PS2 game. Um, what is my
favorite PS2 game? Oh, I don't know. I don't think so. Favorite PS2 game. I don't remember a lot of
PS2. I really don't because I have my favorite N64 game. It was no mercy. WWF no mercy. That was
probably my favorite game of that whole generation. This thing actually is much more powerful. I like
it. All right. That's that. Let's go back to this one. This is going a lot smoother. I'm already at
10%. It's going way smoother. Are you going to make a TikTok account? I'm not going to make a
TikTok account. So sorry. All of you anxiously anticipating a TikTok account. You're not going
to get it. Already 10, 11%. Holy shit. No, no TikTok. I'm not making any more accounts or any
more platforms. I'll tell you, I got to be honest with everybody here. This is it. I ain't moving
again. I went from YouTube to Twitch. I'm not going from Twitch to like TikTok or something.
No, this is it. This is where the story ends. I got to get the ladder for that one. Oh, that's caked
on there. Was that ink? That's really caked on there. Check this out. Oof, really caked on there.
There we go. End's dirty. I can't get up there. How old am I again? 35. Good. Good. Very good.
Very good. Very good. I like it. Give me the ding. Come on. I need the ladder. Where's the ladder on
this level? I'm asking you like you guys know. All right. There we go. Ladder. This is a pretty
good spot. How do you fast forward? You can't. I'm sorry. You have to suffer through me playing a
chores game. These are my favorite games. You know it. I know it. We all know it. Go to the swirl.
Did they actually make them that do this? That's kind of cool. This is a big house. God. Celebrity
that watches him is Chuck E. Cheese. Chuck E. Cheese is not an A-list celebrity. Chuck E. Cheese
is one of those people that they get to be on like one of the seasons of Survivor or something.
You know what I mean? It's like, oh yeah, I remember you. He's famous. He's a celebrity,
but he's not an A-list celebrity. No, no, no. I didn't say I hate Chuck E. Cheese. I just said
he's not an A-list celebrity. I'm not an A-list celebrity. And look, Chuck E. Cheese is way more
famous and popular than I am. He would get invited onto Survivor. I wouldn't. Who covered for you?
What do you mean covered for me? What do you mean he covered for me? What did he cover me for?
Fun fact, you can hear zombies on your lawn here. That's a pretty fun fact. Liar. Celebrity tier list.
But what would that even mean? Like who do I think is the coolest celebrity? Who's the most famous
celebrity? It's probably Tom Hanks. Tom Hanks is an S, I think. Brad Pitt. Yeah, S. It's Brad Pitt and
Tom Hanks. Brad Pitt is absolutely an S tier. Don't even tell me that. Of course he is. But Joe Biden.
Joe Biden is a politician. If you're a politician, you're already a known person
because you're a politician. We're talking about people that are like movie and TV show actors.
Tom Cruise. Yep. Kenneth Paltrow. I don't know. Not so much. Not so much really anymore. I don't
think. No. Jennifer Aniston. I would put probably an S tier. Yeah, Jennifer Aniston is probably S
tier. George Clooney. Who-ing Jennifer Aniston. What are you talking about? One of the most famous
people ever. Where does Kathy Mitchell go though? I would be more happy and more starstruck meeting
Kathy Mitchell than Jennifer Aniston. I'm serious. I would be nervous around Kathy Mitchell.
Kids, I have a surprise for you.
The following is a paid advertisement for the Express Ready, Set, Go! brought to you by GT
Direct, Lewisville, Colorado. We don't have time in our busy lives to wait for food,
so we fall into the fast food rut or buy carb-filled snacks. Well, millions have
discovered the secret. I love this lady. She's one of the best entertainers, one of the best hosts
ever. Even desserts. All thanks to the original Express 101. What would you say? Here comes Kathy
Mitchell. What's his name? Mama Farigno. Mama Farigno. What's his name? Joe Farigno and Kathy
Mitchell. Introduce them already. Introduce them. Oh, look at how good that looks.
You select for your family. This is possible thanks to breakthrough design advances.
All right. Well, where is she? This is just resident sleeper until we get to.
The Express Ready, Set, Go! Just like millions of you, the Express 101 is always there for me.
Joe Farigno. Joe Farago. It's not Kathy Mitchell.
Yes.
What a star. She's an S tier.
And look at these pies. Blueberry, even cherry. You couldn't do that before. You've improved
on perfection. I think we've made it even more perfect. Come on, Joe. She's S tier. I would
watch this whole thing right now. I don't know if I can. This is the Express Ready, Set, Go!
Well, Kathy, this is beautiful. And it is ready. Look what we've done. We took out that center
divider. So now you have 25% more cooking area. Can I watch this? Is this going to be right?
Exactly right. I just think Kathy Mitchell is fantastic. I really do.
Now, this is my almost instant pizza dough. And the recipe comes with it. All you have to do is
pop it in there and then put one over the other. And I like to call it a pizza cookie. Yeah,
I call it a cookie pizza. Where is it? I make a cookie, make a pizza. I call it a cookie pizza.
Come on, where is it? I call it a pizza. Where is it? It's my favorite line.
Kathy Mitchell is S tier. I would rather, I would pay a thousand dollars to like meet
and greet Kathy Mitchell versus, I don't care about any other celebrity. Why? Because I,
she's cool. And she's so good on camera too. She's so quick. She's so good on camera.
You can't teach that. She's so natural in front of the camera. Can we pay you a thousand dollars
to stop talking about the infomercial lady? It's been five minutes. I've been, what do you,
it's been, I'll tell you, Kathy Mitchell was very, very comforting. I remember being,
I don't care. I don't care. I'm talking about it. I remember a lot of these, these Kathy Mitchell
infomercials would air at one, two, three o'clock in the morning. And this is back,
I think when I was in high school and college and stuff, it was so comforting to hear Kathy
Mitchell's voice. It was, watch them. It was so nice. It was wonderful. Just having to go
fall asleep to it. Yeah, it was great. Anytime whenever I was like half asleep and I'd be like,
and now coming up next, ready, set, go. And I'd be like, hold on. She in this one?
And if it wasn't, I'd be like, nah, I changed channel. But if it's like, and you're coming up
weird, we have our resident host, Kathy Mitchell. And I'd be like, put it on, turn the volume up
higher. And now you have my attention. I'm honest. I probably really am Kathy Mitchell's number one
fan. I don't think anybody else can say that. I think just me. I'm not crazy. I'm not crazy.
No, I'm fucking fine. Everybody relax. I just think an introversial lady is cool. What's wrong
with that? What's wrong with that? Why is everybody treating me like I'm crazy? Shit.
I can't even. All right, let's go. Oh God. Whatever. I got to get this hole on the side.
This house is so dirty. Did a fucking volcano erupt on their house?
No, this is from years of not cleaning the roof.
Express 101. The Express ready, set, go. The snack master. Kathy Mitchell's dump cakes.
Kathy Mitchell's dump meals. Kathy Mitchell's copper pan. Kathy Mitchell's square pan.
Kathy Mitchell's turbo cooker. I've seen them all. All of them. Many times over.
How many did I buy? None of them. Oh, except I think my family had the snack master. I'm pretty
sure they did. Fake fan. What are you talking about? What do you mean fake fan? I had the snack master.
And I had the copper pan. Kathy Mitchell's copper pan. I had it. The only pan I had.
Your family had it. What do you mean my family had it? I had the copper pan.
I had the copper pan. I bought the copper pan. Like five years ago. Four or five years ago.
Show it. I don't have the pan anymore. I stopped using it like six years ago or something. I bought
it like five years ago. Oh wait, I got caught. Hold on. I bought this pan when I was still in
Massachusetts. I did not bring the pan to Vegas. It was the copper pan. Kathy Mitchell's face was
on it. It's not a lie. I'm not lying. I had the Kathy Mitchell copper pan. I only bought it because
her name was on it. Her face was on it. Yes. 30% that's it. Oh goodness. Buy another one right now.
No, I don't need it. Actually, I kind of do actually. I could use a new pan. Maybe I'll buy it.
Maybe I'll get the Kathy Mitchell copper pan again. The big one. There we are. Buy it if you're a real
fan. I'll probably get it. It was good. It actually worked. Buy the XL square copper pan. Yeah, that's
the one. My square copper pan is better than all the others. Let me show you. I'm putting two
tablespoons of teaspoons. I'm adding two cups of flour and a little bit of milk. My copper pan
is better than all the other pans. Look at that steak. Yeah, I bought it. And they always put a
piece of cheese in there. Why do they do that? They put one piece of cheddar cheese in the pan
and they cook the cheese. Who the fuck is cooking cheese in a pan? And as you see, I'm cooking cheese
in this pan and the cheese does not stick to the bottom. Why are you cooking a piece of cheese?
To show the quality. That's the point. A grilled cheese. No, but you don't just put a slice of
cheese in the pan. How many times has this happened to you when you're cooking slices of
cheese in your pan? To show it will not stick to the pan. To show it doesn't stick. I love when
that guy says technology too. With anti-stick technology. There's always a technology.
With vacuum-sealed technology. The word technology in infomercials was the best way to make anybody
over the age of 70 to pick the phone up and buy it. With true cooking technology. It's a convection
oven. That's it. The super cooker cooks around all sides with our patented super turbo cooking
technology. It's a convection oven. Done. Oh, technology. It's got, it's got technology in it.
I'll call that number right now. Hey PeacefulHaley, thanks for the 10 community subs. I think I missed
a bunch of other subs too. Thank you though. Apparently also works on you. Also, look at it.
It looks even better already. You won't shut up about it. You're doing E3 next week? I am.
We're doing the Microsoft conference. So next time you're going to see my face is Saturday
at the Microsoft conference. Well, I won't be there, but I will be streaming it.
I've been giving our reactions to things. I wonder what they got in store for us this time.
Yes, Saturday is a React Andy stream. It is. Is Microsoft Sunday? I thought Microsoft Saturday.
When is the Microsoft conference? Is it Saturday or Sunday? Got like 10 AM Pacific. Yeah.
Sunday. Oh, okay. Well, whenever the Microsoft one is, that's what I'm doing.
No Nintendo? No, Nintendos are usually, they're always like on like a Tuesday or something.
And they're always like 40 minutes long. And I really don't know what the hell to do afterwards.
So no, no Nintendo. And it's really early in the morning too. It's like nine, eight or nine
o'clock in the morning. He hates Nintendo and Luigi. It's not true, but I have not played a
Nintendo game all the way through since like Mario galaxy. I mean, I guess you can count
Mario sunshine, but I haven't really played very many Nintendo games all the way through.
What's the last Nintendo game I really played? Did I, I beat, did I beat Pikmin? Did I complete
Pikmin? No, I don't think I did. Right. I got the first ending. Oh, well I got like the, yeah,
the ending, like the first part of the game. I saw an ending. Oh, that game was terrible by the way.
I was, I was holding in so much, how much I hated that whole game. I wanted to scream so badly about
how much I just despised playing it. I just held it in though. It's been a lot, enough times
gone by. I can tell you. I'm kidding. Jesus. I'm kidding. Oh my God. I'm kidding. Don't worry.
Oh, there's a lot of dirt still. 40% and everyone back to Hades. That was the game. That was my
game of the year too. Yeah, actual game of the year. And I only played, I played like, I played
it for like seven and a half hours. Hey, look, I know exactly how good it is. I don't need to
know anymore. Was it in Half-Life Alyx? Oh yeah, it was. That game was awesome. Half-Life Alyx was
so good. It was truly a fantastic game. I underrated it? I did? Didn't I say it was the game of the
year? What'd I give it for a rating? 9.4? That's pretty good. Going higher than a 9.4. I mean,
that's one of the most, that's one of the best games I've ever played. Having, having to score
over a 9 means that's one of the best games I've played. What else have I given a 9 in the last
five years? Minecraft? Makes sense. Minecraft makes sense. House Flipper? That makes sense too.
What game is a 10 out of 10? I don't know. GTA 4 is probably pretty high. Resident Evil 2 was
really high, the remake. TF2 would be pretty close as well. Yeah, I don't know though. Bloodborne?
Bloodborne needs to be 60 FPS. That's the one thing holding it back. I'm not sure I've ever
played a perfect 10 out of 10. Team Fortress is close. It probably is TF2. I can't think of much
else that deserves a 10. Chrono Trigger? Yeah, Mario RPG, Chrono Trigger, those are all really good.
They're all at least 9.5. Is this side over here? And I'm probably going to call it sooner than I
think. I might not even finish this one. I'm really hungry. I keep thinking of cheesy goudita crunches
and I want one right now and I want to go eat one. Diablo or WoW Classic? Diablo 2. That's not an
easy one to answer though. I still think Diablo 2 beats it. My god. Get up there. Diablo 2 is just,
you don't get better than that. I think Diablo 2 is a 10. Well, Diablo 2 Lord of Destruction.
That game was so good. Am I going to play the Diablo 2 remake? I mean, probably. I don't know
if I'm going to stream that though. I'm not sure that, I think that's something that I want to do
in my own time if I'm going to do it. And then whenever Elden Ring decides to come out, yeah.
Elaborate? Um, I don't know. I kind of would just want to play D2 on my own.
Just sit there with my mouth open. That's my McDonald's order. That's uh, it really depends
on the day, but usually it's uh, it's right now. I'd say it's two McChickens, two McDoubles,
and a Big Mac, and a five and a six piece nugget, and two cherry pies. Window frame is so
finicky. There it is. Very good boy. You're a liar. Now it's two McChickens and two McDoubles,
and then if I'm really, really hungry, I'll get nuggets. Like a six piece. That's not obscene.
They're not even that big. A McDonald's patty is like two ounces. What's a McDonald's burger patty?
It's two and a half ounces. It's three ounces, isn't it? It's like a two or three ounce patty.
You know, there are people that make four, six, five, six, seven ounce patties. It's not a joke.
What even is a joke? I hate big patties. I think they're gross. If your patty is bigger than your
bun, you got a problem. There's a problem there. The ratio of meat to bun has to be different.
Has to be enough where you get, I would say, meat to bun ratio. Like uh, the meat should be
half as big as the bun. Maybe even a little less. In terms of volume or mass. Um, like thickness.
Your bun should never be thicker. Uh, you know, your bun should never be the same thickness as
your meat. Because then all the condiments have to go on. All your lettuce, your, you know, if you
have tomato, I mean, that's disgusting, but if you put it on there, good for you. You've got your
cheese. You've got your onion potentially. You've got your chopped onion. Not, not whole onion
circles. No, thank you. Etch up, mustard, pickles, whatever. That one felt good. You don't like
tomato? No, I don't, I don't like cold, wet tomato on my hamburger. I like tomato. I just
don't like it on a hamburger. I don't think it belongs there. All right. The house is clean.
All right. I'm probably going to call it here. Just don't look at the side of the house. I need
to go get a, I need to get some food. I'm hungry. I'm going to get to, I got to 50%. Once it's 50%,
I'll leave. But thanks for watching everybody. This has been Power Washer Simulator. It's very
good. It's very relaxing. It's very fun. I'm surprised I sat here for seven hours and 15
minutes. It was a lot of fun. Had a good time. I'll see you guys next week for E3. I'm going to do
at least the Microsoft conference. We'll see you after that. We'll see you soon. It is my 10 year
anniversary online on YouTube and Twitch and everything. That's happening I believe on Thursday.
I'm not, I'm probably not going to go live for it. We'll talk about it at E3. But in case I miss
you, it's been 10 years officially as of this week. It's been a wild ride. It's been fun.
We'll talk about it some more this next weekend. Not my birthday yet. All right. Yeah. I'm going
to call it here. I need some food. I will see you guys on whenever the Microsoft conference is.
Have a great rest of your week. It's very, very soon here. I'll have a lot more to talk about.
There's another few projects that are coming up that are going to be in September, August.
Talked about baseball. Baseball is confirmed. It's a go. It's happening.
There's a lot of things happening. I hope you think they're interesting. But I'll see you soon.
Let's transition out of here. Show the credits. Yeah, the baseball stream is confirmed to be
happening at some point in September. There's another big stream that's happening in August,
which I'll talk about more later, among a couple other small things. Don't forget about Mizkif.
Yeah, I'll hit him up. I'll see what the deal is. That might be fun too. When is your Among Us
stream? Never going to play Among Us. How late to the meme do you guys really want me to be?
You really want me to be that late to the meme? Two years too late. Yeah, I'm getting Taco Bell.
I'm into it. Let's do it. Play it the day the servers go down. We'll find that out. We'll find
the day the servers turn off, and I'll play it on that day. I don't think that's going to happen.
I really doubt that'll happen. It's still really popular. I think it's a lot more popular than
you guys are giving it credit for still. Raid Mizkif? All right, we're going to raid Mizkif.
I mean, we've been talking about him all stream. We might as well go do it. I've been talking about
him all stream. It's been like seven hours of us talking about him. Go say hello. What is he doing?
What is he up to? He's doing something. Raid yourself. Go say hi. Look, we've got to at least
make a... If I'm going to go on that game show thing, whatever it is, schooled, and here's
an introduction, I guess. I don't know. He's doing something fun. I'll see you guys soon. We'll see
you next week. Take care of yourselves. Go say hello. Network Andy. Network Andy's back.
He's back with a vengeance. Take care, guys. See you soon.