Hello, I'm here. Sorry, I had to take a very, very important phone call.
Hey, pizza in 30 minutes or less or it's free. Here I am.
I already said it in chat and I thought it was funny.
No, what's up? Yeah, 30 minutes or less. And that's when I got here.
Did you encourage the Cowardly Dog? Nah.
No, but what's up? How you doing?
Gonna be hanging out, chilling out again tonight.
Playing some more Pizza Tower.
I'm very well rested. Got a nice tea here. I had dinner already.
So I'm good to go. After this, I don't think this is going to take that much.
I mean, it probably is. What would you say? I'm probably halfway through the game.
Maybe 50, 60% of through the game. Probably like another three or four hours maybe.
We'll see. I don't know.
But after this, the idea is whether it's today or at some point next week,
because after this stream, you are not going to see me for probably about five days or so.
Four or five days at least. Big, big Grotto Beast stuff coming.
News. That's the intention.
And I am a day early.
And I'm going to tell you what's going to happen to the sus,
because the sus at this point is kind of a weird spot.
So the sus, which is when you come to the stream and you're in the chat,
you type in, hey, exclamation point, sus.
It tells you when the next stream is going to be.
It has never been accurate.
And in previous years, I have always come into the chat
and said, hey, guys, I'm going to stream.
I'm not streaming tomorrow. I'm going to stream two days from now.
There was always a window of the, it was scheduled and I would always delay it by a day.
It would happen 50% of the time. I'd say 40% of the time, at least.
This year, we have a different problem.
This year, instead of delaying the stream, I pull it forward a day.
It happens almost every time.
So I do all these reverse delays now.
That's the problem this year.
Oh, well, problems. I mean, yeah, it's not a real, it's not a problem, but you know.
So what's probably going to happen to the sus
is the sus is going to tell you when a stream is absolutely not going to happen.
So for instance, if you do the sus today, after tonight, tomorrow,
it's going to say, hey, you cast sus.
He ain't going to be here for fucking four days.
And it is when I know I won't be here for at least a few days
or when I know I will not be streaming.
So the sus is now going to be not when the stream will be
but when the stream will not be.
Isn't that interesting?
I think I like that.
You cast sus.
You sense a stream not happening for the next three days.
The anti-sus.
Yeah, we have we're going to the sus is going to go through its evil arc.
Very confusing.
The evil sus is anti-sus or maybe I just maybe sus is just a general.
Hey, yeah, I'm actually I'm planning on streaming a few times this week.
Just you'll get notified.
Maybe that's the plan.
But I definitely I'm starting to see the issue of instead of delaying every time.
Now I'm pulling it forward a day every time.
So whatever and I'll be honest, the sus has always kind of been there to keep me honest.
Because if I know that the sus is telling people there's a stream like in a day or so,
I'm I'm it was like, oh, yeah, I'm going to be here in the next day or two.
If there's no schedule, then you might I might run into a problem where it's like,
hey, there's no schedule and I'm fucking streaming tomorrow.
I'm streaming Tuesday and I'm streaming Wednesday.
You know what?
Fuck it.
Why stream again?
It's been been a way to keep myself honest in a way,
but we'll see.
I've been streaming a lot more this year.
That's not the point.
The point is not to stream more.
It's just a stream kind of whenever I feel like it.
And I feel like it right now.
So you cast sus.
You sense the next stream is whenever this weirdo feels like it.
How's that sound?
Is that good?
Oh, I didn't tweet.
Oh, but after this, after we play Pete's Tower, the plan is to play
Hilux and looking forward to that.
We did.
I'm going to.
There we go.
OK, what's a good a good tweet about my throat is so fucked up.
What's going on?
Pizza Tower part two.
That's what's happening.
OK, there we go.
It's going to hit your feed in a second.
Hey, look at that.
There it is.
You need to watch part one to understand part two.
I can give you a quick rundown.
I'm just going to run into walls and make frustrated grunts.
That's kind of what happened yesterday.
So it's pretty much going to be the same stream, just different levels.
Well, actually, you probably should understand part one.
Let me help you.
So let me give you a quick recap of part one.
No, and that's pretty much it.
Let's see if we see it part two.
Here we go.
You can play VR again.
I don't know.
I think VR might.
I'm going to have to set up like a seated VR scenario
just because of the every time I do VR,
it just kind of kills me for four or five days straight.
It's happened pretty much every single time.
As much as I would love to do it all the time,
because it's so fun and just so interesting
and there's always such funny, cool shit to do with it.
Probably I'd have to figure out to get it in a different spot or something.
All right, let me go.
I did.
If you actually do want an actual recap, I did the first three floors.
There are five floors.
And where is the?
I guess I didn't 100 percent, but I'm not going to do that though.
Did you go to the beach?
No, I think the beach.
Can I use the same elevator to go?
Oh, no, it's different elevator.
Where's the other elevators?
Did I do all?
No, I did.
I didn't complete this, did I?
I did this one.
Did I do all the levels down here?
This is one of the.
Oh, that's a seat.
No, we're getting better than that.
What level is this?
Yeah, this is the last thing I did.
I'm getting better than the seat.
Fuck this.
I should maybe I should warm up first.
Yeah, I got to get at least to be.
Oh, I got stuck.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Restart, restart, restart.
I got stuck.
I wanted to jump and I didn't.
That was just bad RNG.
I was just seeing if I could throw them.
I want to see if I could throw them, but I'm testing the game design.
I'll get game design handy, game design handy.
Let's see.
That's what's called pivoting in the middle of a decision.
I want everyone to see that.
You see my immediate problem solving.
Fuck you.
I got to shut up.
All right.
I got hit.
I'm ready for God.
This is fake.
What?
How big is that explosion?
Oh, this is huge.
All right.
I'm just trying to see what the game design is.
This one's fake.
I come on, man.
Come on, man.
I was just testing.
It was just test.
I was going to see like how the controls work.
Play tester.
I want to restart so bad, but I'm not going to.
That was bullshit.
Turn up the music.
I will after I play test for a few minutes.
I got to stop running, but the whole game trains you
to hold right trigger the whole game.
Whatever.
I'm sticking to it.
Oh my God.
Why did I look at chat?
And this is like, okay, if I restart, if I restart again,
I will stop streaming.
No restarts.
I forgot he.
Oh, I did the same thing.
Parry that.
It's hard.
Dude, this is one of those cocaine games.
All right.
That's what I'm going to say.
It's quiet.
This is what I, this is what I feel like cocaine is like
is this whole game.
Just like, got it.
All right.
That's got to be at least a B, right?
So this is what I think cocaine is like.
I've never done cocaine.
I have no fucking plans to either.
Hey, I'll take a B.
I'm way happier with that.
I'll take a B. B is fine.
I don't think I did all the other missions here.
Did I?
I did mini golf, which I got an A, excuse me.
It's a space level.
There is a space level.
There's also, oh, I didn't do it.
Almost everything here.
Okay.
You know what else I need to do?
I need to really slow down in the first part.
In part one, I still have that mindset where it's like,
I have to go as fast as I humanly can, right?
Which is inaccurate.
Okay.
Let's do this one.
What up?
Make it a little louder.
How's that?
Better.
All right.
So don't go fast.
Just chill.
It's not a big deal.
Just relax.
It's all about combos.
This song's great.
In the box or up here?
Okay, up here.
Oh, I don't know.
This might have best soundtrack 2023.
I mean, it's we're only two months into the year,
but I don't think I've heard anything since.
Even well into 2022.
Okay, this is amazing.
This is really, really great.
What about this?
Interesting.
How'd you get up there?
Bell up there.
The blue is part of the environment, or are they?
They're just there.
Actually, let's do that.
Is this hurting me?
Stop.
Who's this insane guy in the top right?
Come on.
That's Pepino.
I want to go down there.
How do I get down there?
To run faster?
Why did that hurt?
Very cool.
We got a D, so I want to get up to that.
To the right, probably.
What cartoon does this remind you of?
You know, it's funny you say that
because it's this weird non-descript cartoon.
It's a style from, it's like Rocko.
Yeah, Rocko's Modern Life.
It's got this weird like 90s,
late 90s, mid 90s kind of vibe.
Cow and Chicken.
Yep, that's another one.
Early like Cartoon Network kind of stuff.
Courage Cowardly Dog.
Yeah, for sure.
Go backwards.
There we go.
I got to go up here.
Can I make it over there?
I don't know.
Yeah, I can.
Whoa, come on, give me that pocket.
What level is this?
Um, I don't know.
Come on.
Frost Cove.
Secret.
What does he say sometimes?
He goes like, it's a goal.
Very nice.
Paranoid is what he's saying.
He goes paranoid.
Is that what it is?
Pizza.
I think I can get in there.
I had a bad day today.
Sorry to hear that.
No, what the?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I want to go back down.
Oh, I missed it.
That's all right.
No, no, no, it's moving too fast.
No, I wanted to get that stuff.
Oh, I can't grab these.
This level is cool.
Nice.
Oh, I have to do it a bunch of times.
Oh, yeah.
I got a big combo going.
No, shit.
Whatever.
Oh, my God.
Sorry.
Geez.
I think I might have a secret up there.
All right, I'm good.
Anything else in here?
No, good.
Nice.
Very cool.
That was a fun level.
That might be one of my favorites, actually.
That was probably my favorite one.
I like it when you bust a move like this.
I like how you can move with this.
Do you eventually get to do something with this?
Or is it just a fun little thing to do?
Just for fun.
That's cool.
All right, so there's one more level, which is up.
Maybe all this whole time.
I didn't even ask.
How the fuck you're doing?
Remember to not take too many breaks.
Keep playing.
Your time here is limited.
Damn.
Don't take too many breaks.
Rapino pizza 3000 is going on over here.
Change direction and jump.
Oh, well, we're going that way.
Level lap two.
The moon smoking?
Yeah, whatever.
Wait, can I move up or something?
Oh, I can do that.
Sega Genesis.
Yeah, that's another one, too.
It definitely feels like an old Genesis game.
Old Super Nintendo game.
You mean Sonic?
Yeah, it doesn't look like Sonic, though.
Some other games are like Boogerman, somebody said.
This is looks and feels like Boogerman.
Pop that.
I am not going to miss.
You know what I'm saying?
Earthworm Jim.
Yep, exactly.
It's really cool that there are people still kind of making stuff in that kind of style.
I can definitely get in there.
That sound effect is somewhere, too.
That.
Just don't know where.
There's the other side, wasn't it?
Or maybe it's up.
Might be up there.
No, it's probably the left, the other side.
Damn it.
Oh, well, I actually don't.
Can I go down?
Cannot.
Okay.
Not yet.
Well, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I can get it now.
I can get it.
That's actually a good thing that happened.
Oh, God.
No, no, no, no.
Just fly.
Everything's fine.
We're good.
Hey, welcome to Turbo 985.
Funny noises.
I already went in here, right?
You can only make 114 funny noises this stream from now on.
Whoopsie.
113.
Motherfucker.
I'll never be able to hear anything else.
I didn't even make that one.
Oh, yeah, I kind of did.
All right.
Well, I can definitely go up.
Well, whatever.
I don't have to get everything.
I'm just so, I'm just so concerned
that something's going to be underneath me.
Really?
Has to be the other side then, huh?
How do I, how do I change direction?
Oh, we have to be on the floor.
Okay.
Whoa.
Jesus.
Up and up?
No.
That sound right there.
That...
Sound that goes...
Where's this person's room?
Okay.
Oh, shit.
Whatever.
Damn it.
Okay.
I'm going so fast.
Don't...
I want to get this in one hit.
Okay, now...
Oh, my God.
I fucking ruined everything.
Got it.
Oh, wait.
But what about...
So many things to do in each level.
Shit.
There's so many cool things to do in each level.
How loud?
Do you think the person that screamed that...
I'm just curious how loud that really was in studio.
Wait.
Down here maybe somehow?
Oh, wait.
I keep it.
I think I'm done with this game.
I don't play puzzle games, and this is a puzzle part.
You know how I feel.
Like, anytime I get to a puzzle section, I just quit it because I don't do that.
I just don't play games like that.
I just don't like it.
Yeah, that's it.
I just don't play games like this.
Anytime I'm like, oh, I have to use...
I have to put this circle into that circle hole and then take that key up.
No.
I'm done.
Hurry.
I'm not going fast.
No.
I need to get in there.
I don't even know why, but I just had to.
What?
Hmm.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Get out of my way.
Oh, my God.
What?
Oh, shit.
No, stop.
I'm fucking panicking right now.
Stop panicking and just play it.
Come on, dude.
Oh, my God.
I'm panicking.
Stop.
Just go.
Just crawl.
Get the sandwich.
I want to get the sandwich.
It's worth money, man.
Shit.
What did I miss?
Not bad.
I believe that's the whole floor.
Can you put this game into food mode?
No.
See, this game is not...
I would never qualify this as a game that could be food mode.
This is too much to pay attention to.
Food mode is specifically a game
where it's pretty slow paced
and there's a ton of downtime in between each major thing to do.
You don't...
I'm not running full sprint like this.
And then it's like, oh, hey, it's time for dinner.
No, no, I would just quit the level.
I don't know if I'd be able to restart it again.
I think I did pretty damn good on this floor.
I missed two toppings.
Can't do better than that.
There's over here.
Kind of looks like Super Jail.
It does.
You've gone far enough, buddy.
You need to be this tall.
This image is so fucked up.
It's so scary.
But somehow, that's it.
That's cool.
Good show, I say.
I'm going to move these out of my way.
I just became...
Yeah, now.
You got me now without the arm rests.
That's how you know everything's going to get fucking crazy now.
Big city.
Does your fridge smell weird if you check the expiration date?
I guess I'm just going to do this one.
Oh, shit.
What?
That's the name of this place?
This actually says, oh, shit.
Sewer level.
Okay.
Oh, that's kind of gross.
Stick to the wall and then wall.
Okay.
Hold on.
You're way slower like this, too.
Shit.
I want to jump over that.
Let go.
Get in there.
How did I get in there last time?
Jump.
What the fuck?
I thought...
Okay.
I thought you had to be...
I thought you had to be rolling.
Really?
Are these supposed to be the Ninja Turtles?
No.
Different pipe, though.
Can I not go on that one?
I want to break it.
Like the cat jams.
I feel like the rat dancing.
It's so cool.
So cute.
It's just so funny.
So the orange pipes don't seem to do very much, huh?
Or am I missing something?
Of course you're the screamer that likes the dancing rat.
What team are you on?
I'm on neither one of these teams.
I just like seeing them both dance.
I don't think you can be on either one.
I think there's something back here.
There was.
Come over here.
How do I get in there?
I want to get in there.
Geez.
I thought that was Peter Griffin for a second.
Just from right here.
I was like, oh, that's Peter Griffin right there.
Why would it be Peter Griffin?
Idiot.
It's not funny.
That wasn't Peter Griffin.
Fucking idiot.
Stop talking.
Hey, Peter Griffin's in the game.
Fuck that.
Stop fucking talking, Jeremy.
No.
He's always looking for secrets.
You know what I mean?
Turn the music down.
I think that would be very upset with me if I did.
Ah, shit.
Is it more momentum?
It was more momentum.
Well, I screwed that one up.
Actually, maybe I do want to go that way for a second.
Shit.
So hold on.
All right.
I'm bouncing around all over the place.
Stop.
I can't stop moving.
All right.
We'll just go this way.
Blame.
Well, I definitely want to go that way.
Are you counting down how many sounds I'm making?
You are not.
What happens when we get zero?
What happens at zero?
Jeez.
Ah, damn it.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Dude, come on.
I just stopped streaming.
Sorry, guys.
That's all for today.
Well, it's definitely over here.
Come on.
Did I not even get the thing I was supposed to get?
How did I not touch it?
What?
I grazed the frame of one little frame above.
What are you talking about?
Come on.
Oh, well.
I'm getting rhythm.
There's no rhythm to this right now.
No.
Oh, my God.
What's happening?
No, I have a second chance.
What just happened?
Hurry up.
I'm going.
Get away from me.
Get away.
Fine.
Go this way.
Just kidding.
Jeez.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What are you doing?
Oh, go.
Oh, my goodness.
You have to hold it first.
It's like it takes like a second.
So is there anything else to get?
That's it.
It's an A.
A minus?
That's not what it says.
Can you eat a whole pizza on stream?
Very unhealthy.
That's it.
It's probably a bad idea.
Oh, new costume.
Killing a thousand enemies in a playthrough.
I don't think I could do it.
I don't know why you'd want to do it.
How about the...
The too much fat and sauce and shit.
Like, it's way too much.
All the calories, all the heaviness on your metabolism.
Blood sugar.
Like, something crazy would happen to it.
No, it's a bad idea.
Oh, no.
Snoddy's dead.
Missing.
Oh, no.
Snow level?
What's up here?
Probably 300?
Only 200.
All right.
Let's do the snow level.
You ate a whole pizza on the Sea Man stream.
Yeah, but that was a small...
That was a personal pizza.
I didn't eat the whole thing.
Did I eat the whole pizza?
I ate it over the course of a couple of hours.
Yeah, that was a personal pizza.
You ate it in five minutes?
I did not eat it in five.
You literally ate, cut it into four pieces.
Yeah.
But those...
Yeah, it was a whole pizza.
But I ate it...
Also, this is important too.
That stream was...
One what?
Almost 12, 13 hours long?
You ate...
It was like an 11 plus hour stream.
Yeah, that's the only food I ate over the course of almost a whole day.
And that's really bad to do that.
But, you know, I was streaming and I was playing Sea Man and that's what happened.
I'm going way too fast to stop.
I can't slow down.
I can't go that way with it.
What am I doing?
Shit.
I can get it.
Come on.
There we go.
I figured it was going to be a secret over there.
Guess not.
Hot pepper?
Ooh, spicy.
Oh, shit.
Okay, that's what it wants me to do.
Did you like the Sea Man stream?
I think there was a lot of stuff that happened on that stream.
Yeah.
Sometimes you have to just finish something.
Even if it's like, you know what?
I don't know about this.
You have to finish it.
If you know for a fact that I would no chance, no chance,
would I have actually finished that game on another day.
You all know that for a fact.
Can I not bring it over there?
It's probably a secret over there that I'm not getting over here.
Can I avoid all this and just jump?
I can, kind of.
Really?
I'll probably be on the way back.
Damn it.
Do you like the pizza tower stream?
Oh, that pizza tower stream.
It was insane.
It was just so wild.
It's so fucked up.
The art style was so cool in that game though.
You ever get like, nostalgia and you just don't,
you want to play it so bad again.
Like, you wish you could just go back and just do it everything again.
I kind of feel that way with the pizza tower stream.
Because I was having such a good time.
Just wish I could like, do it again.
Does that mean?
Jesus.
I think I'm going the right way?
I'm missing a lot of stuff though.
He's doing his bit voice.
You can always tell.
That's true.
Whenever I lower my tone,
and I talk really like this,
and I'm just like, that's, you got it.
You're right.
That's my bit voice.
That's my like, slightly kind of, you know,
really slowed down, mellow.
Yeah, I mean, I just wish it like, you know,
that's how you can tell.
Although, here's the problem though.
I have talked with that tone,
when talking about serious stuff too.
So it's, I don't know.
That's my, I'm serious voice,
but you can tell when it's pretend serious.
Somehow.
All the bit to you.
Okay, I'm stop locked.
No, not everything is a bit.
Just most things are.
I think, honestly, I like to operate in a world,
like in my own world here.
Where really, really important shit is not a bit, of course.
But I stream to have fun.
That's what I'm doing here.
So that's why I've always said like,
90% of the things you hear on stream
are just me having fun,
because that's what I want to do here.
That's what I'm doing here.
I don't really have another purpose here,
besides to try to have like fun,
make a fun environment.
That's it.
So yeah.
So let's talk about that time that I,
Clint's Breath of the Wild Season 2.
No, go back.
There's so much more shit over here.
That was the serious voice.
But yeah, but it wasn't a bit though.
You see what I'm saying?
You understand the difference?
That was not a bit.
That was me being for real.
Are we a joke to you?
I couldn't, I couldn't hold it.
I couldn't hold it in Santa.
Holy shit.
He's, he's cracking.
Hey, by the way, nobody counted that down.
I'm, I see you all moved on from that one real quick.
Why do you keep ignoring the Breath of the Wild question?
I'm not, I, I'm going to play it.
I just don't know.
They're going in or I don't know what I'm going to do.
I've got obviously things that I would like to play.
Breath of the Wild is one of them.
Oh, I meant to say finish it.
No, I don't know why I haven't played it again.
Honestly, it hasn't, it doesn't have anything to do with.
I can't really speak to a reason why.
Oh my God.
Okay, hold on.
Let me hold this for a second.
Nice.
Holy shit, that was cool.
Oh, I wish I could just run fast through this.
Like everybody else that plays this game did.
I wish I just could run through them.
Like everybody else did.
Everybody else did it that way, but I didn't.
This level is really, really cool.
Oh, hot sauce on pizza is actually like 10 out of 10.
You should get banned for like five minutes someday.
I think it'd be pretty thrilling.
It would also probably like potentially ruin my life.
So I don't think I want to.
But what do you mean banned for five?
Yeah, you don't get banned for five minutes on Twitch.
Banned for five minutes?
That's a bathroom break.
Should I, when I go pee, should I just say I'm getting banned?
Um, what am I doing here?
Is there a tutorial I should have?
Oh, I hold.
What?
Holy shit.
Holy crap.
Banned for five minutes.
Yeah, guys, Twitch bans do not operate the same way
as when you get timed out in this channel
for saying something strange.
Although, I mean, some people have been banned here for a pretty long time.
Some people get banned permanently.
I got banned for three years at one point.
And did you say you were sorry?
Oh, shit.
I wasn't prepared for that, but now I have to go.
Oh, never.
This is the best song in the game.
I got two minutes.
Free milk.
Oh, shit.
What?
Okay.
Well, I got a 51 hit combo.
A good baseline can change anything.
that changes everything i think the i think the bass player the bass does not get the
credit that i think a lot of do they deserve the base of a song is what holds the whole
it's the glue of the whole song 10 bucks i can go up another floor no no no uh did i do this one
what's this music the pig city the person didn't even do anything wrong what long shrimp oh is
anybody else feel this way if okay i'm not a big shrimp person when shrimp is i want to say more i
don't like big shrimp they're too meaty and they're too weird i'm i don't like it when shrimp goes
above a certain size i no longer like it okay get in what um okay smoking okay well i gotta try to
get off me pineapple on pizza couldn't fucking be there but jerma what about the sweet and savory
sweet and soft stop come on i can break it going this way i know i can oh my god bro didn't even
think about the sweet and savory yeah you did uh i'm gonna be completely real with you let's talk
pineapple on pizza it's not the fact that there's pineapple on the pizza because pineapple
has those who have been here for years that's probably my favorite fruit pineapple is my
favorite fruit pineapple maybe in banana and lemon um but it's a textural thing pineapple is very
fibrous and it's it's very fibrous and stringy sometimes when you put and it doesn't match with
the pizza for me i love pineapple it's just the fibrous pineapple does not match with like a crust
in the sauce this doesn't do it for me you like it and good for you i'm glad you do get it away
from me and never talk about it in my presence good for you though like i'm happy i'm glad i'm
happy for you wonder if i should have gone the other way first wait hold on banana on pizza um
i can't believe it happened again i can't believe it happened again no we're good
i don't like warm pineapple yeah you i think you just actually figured it out for me seriously
if i'm really honest oh thanks i gotta forget um to me fruit should be cold i like when fruit
is cold not when it's hot i think that's you just unlock the reason why i don't like um apple pie
i'm not like a big warm apples like warm fruits it just doesn't do it i think that's what it is
apple cider is not the same because it's a drink that's a it's a drink i drink hot
coffee hot i drink ice coffee too i don't prefer it either way so i do like hot coffee blueberry
pie no i my top eyes are banana cream and then uh chocolate cream i like the cream based pies like
banana cream banana cream pie is it's so high up on s tier that it's an insult if anybody thinks
anyone thinks that it's even close to anything else it's it's when you talk about pies banana
cream pie is s plus plus plus plus every other fucking pie is like could be s or lower not even
close and mods i'm getting real sick of people fucking talking like this just start timing people
let that disappear with me i don't know what's wrong with me tonight i'm sorry i'm a weirdo
i'm in a good mood today i don't know today tonight hey all right let me ask you about what's that do
you want to talk semantics it is is it today or is it tonight and does today still work because
it technically is still the same day it's still that no it's today it's still the same day
love that laugh who did some of the voice work nice fucking job seriously you get it it's not
just stock sounds i mean it's a vague question i still think today works because it's when you
say a day you know sunday right monday tuesday it's not tuesday night you know at seven o'clock
on tuesday it does not become tuesday night checkmate yeah you would say it is thursday night
it's still thursday thursday night it's not thursday night this that was crazy are they
drinking a milkshake that's funny oh that's funny thermal watch this back flip what the holy shit
oh my god dude whoa what the fuck that was that was awesome you can just do that
from your chair i've never seen something to do that before like from your from a seated position
holy shit man just like call somebody it's not like the fucking news or something
you might have somebody seated it how seated in a chair and just lunging themselves up and back to
the point where they could backflip out of the chair okay it's probably some you know performers
or something they can probably do something similar i feel like that's incredibly dangerous
and should never be attempted i think my buddy eric could do it oh that should absolutely never
be attempted buddy eric should never attempt that do not attempt that that's a piece of pizza
with a piece of fish on it will you do lap two from my understanding lap two can only happen
if you beat the level already so i don't have to go back and do it again eric is different
you made eric up that's the difference but yes eric is different you made them up
i think that was the best song in the game i want to see tons of people dancing i want to see
sons of of cat dancing rat dancing doing that i'm not doing this well at all what's happening
look up
fucking crazy does somebody have to be driving to have that reaction only be fixed up somebody
else to kill ah well i think i spent too much time in the taxis let's do it if you got two taxis
no secrets either yeah there's kind of junk you did the boss i'll try the boss
i got one more level here and the boss
oh what is this you know versus pino what i don't get it okay um what is he oh do i just
fight i he doesn't blink okay i just fight him whoa they're not what the fuck oh oh my god
i get the head damn it this is crazy he sucks no you're trying to bait a paragraph out of me
from me to like yell at you shit i forgot they turn whoa i always go to the middle by the way
that was dumb tracking i thought he was hitable again all right now what what the fuck which
one's who do i attack jesus whoa what the fuck i'm gonna die oh man this is really hard very hard
this one's crazy st around this one good luck no hit run on this no way see if i could carry it
i mean i'd rather jump over it i'm more i i any game where i can dodge something i'm way better
at doing that than actually parrying it shit i thought i was ready where am i wrong one i'll
take a b on there help when you get trapped you just you just fucked i'll take a c on this one
okay this one's really really hard don't do this to me like that i can't even get the health off i
can't even touch the health cocaine game oh what's wait wait wait why did this happen what
this didn't happen last time my god crack game stop oh my goodness stop getting attached to every
wall i think i'm i'm fine did i do it whoa was i just completely just blanked right there do not
enter not do not enter inside do not go inside believe crack game i can do better than that
that face i'm just realizing that face blow it already that backwards jump never seen that
before backwards backwards jump what the heck excuse me excuse me why did i not parried that
when he ran by me i don't care i'm leaving did i yeah i did them all didn't i nope i have that
one more but let's see staff only get out the elusive p rank you can get it by doing everything
there is to do in a level problem is that you need to keep a combo for the entirety of the level
it's a tough challenge so don't feel bad if you don't want to do it it's not just not get hit
it's you have to keep a combo going the whole entire time holy
shit how come you don't have uh tts um it's it's very i'm an incredibly distractible person
and i feel like tts tts would just distract me every five seconds and i would never be able
to pay attention to anything ever i've never done it before and i probably will never do it
ever although i can't honestly i can't appreciate um obviously you watch some streamers that have
tts on and sometimes it can be really really funny t honestly tts for a lot of other streamers kind
of in a way is sort of a one guy moment because like there's been tons of moments where i've like
seen a stream where like uh tts was just like hilarious and it's just like wow okay well that's
funny but also i tts can get spammed pretty hard um and there's a difference to think between
like tts spam and somebody saying something funny i guess um but it's like i don't know it's a
community engagement it's a way to get like your audience to feel the like hang out participate
make jokes make references do whatever they want um but it's just not here i understand why people
do it though just mute it yeah take a stance that's a centrist idea i mean i just i just told you i
don't do it and i don't want to do it but i can understand why somebody would do it is that
centrist i did i took i did take a stance that is my stance that no i don't like it and i don't
want to do it so okay the centrist stance with that would be tts interesting idea and well on
one hand i can see why i would do it i might i'm thinking about it but i haven't i haven't decided
yet i think that what i would like to do with tts is maybe look into it a little bit more and
see what this uh why it would be on but the other case it being off is like i being on i could see
that no i i took a stance oh he's getting stun locked all right uh i want to go to the other
level that's pretty much what you said no i made my stance on how i feel about it then i told you
how i can i can still understand because it's like a one guy moment for some people and here's another
thing how about this centrist take you ready a lot of streamers that have huge huge audiences and i'm
talking into the tens of thousands right how do you get a one guy moment you can't even read
sometimes you can't even see what anybody is saying right like so i can understand that
this channel is still at a point where i can look over here and i can see at least for a second
sometimes what somebody is saying what's your review of the game so far uh well on one hand
i can see how somebody would like this game um it's got really cool artwork it's got really
interesting scenarios um i can see how some people would want to play it and get some
something out of that but on the other hand it's a cocaine game and i know i just i can see how
some people would be not that's really really hard to play um it's super intense so i can
understand that and that's my take all right where's this last level that i didn't go to
pizza scare uh castlevania yeah can you please be more in the middle please be more in the middle
i am danos i am danos i am danos what does that do what's this doing kill the ghost
do i just kill them all like do i have to kill them all is that like part of this
it said literally yeah i know i know it said kill the ghost but do i have to
do i have to kill them all to like progress or something does it matter or does it just
it gives me the ability to a lot of things in this level can just stop you in your tracks and hurt
you everything can hurt you in this level what's happening right now what's going on this thing's
just okay get out of here this level's too stressful i don't like it it doesn't let me
slow down and explore pekino's world how do you break the bowling pins to this one whoa voting
to kick me uh it's not gonna happen how do i get that i gotta turn him into a thingy how do i turn
him into a thingy here we go wait what i gotta go faster than that huh there's a lot of little
hops in this level like tiny little ones just keep here again here again all these little
fucking hops uh avoided elite gameplay you have any idea how hard this game is you know how hard
this game is right you have any idea it's simply not just left and right and jump you get attached
to surfaces like the roadrunner game for the yes nas you have any idea you have any idea how hard
i'm working right now you have any idea how hard i'm working right here this level's got so many
bumps too many hidden enemies too many bumps i rate this level a five out of ten skeleton looks like
you too many too many look at this too many bumps too many like wasted all right too many bumps
can you do your best auto impression yeah sure what um i'm gonna slow down a little bit like oh
my god oh i thought this thing was active what what too many fucking bumps i gotta wait i have
to wait i have to wait i have to wait i can't i have to wait the whole thing's fucked up the
whole thing's fucked up i gotta go back that's so many goddamn bumps in this fucking level i
swear to god why did i take the ladder funny no dude i have to oh my god no go down go down
i hate this level so much go where am i what's happening just get me out of here i'm never
playing this level ever again i got all the toppings i'm never going in here again did it
get darker i feel like it didn't look like this i feel it was brighter all right well that's that
you know you could really could lose some weight hey what about what's up there
do you have anything to say no you missed a level on the last floor
oh you're right i did whatever this one was it's just so so bizarre looking okay
i can't destroy that no no no no no throw it oh that's right the bombs right let me go back down
there was a bomb spawner down here wasn't there where was that rat who is the rat up a little
bit higher god damn it i was up here i got stuck that's okay also another thing i'm still having
trouble getting used to is holding right trigger forever when you want to stay running just like
can't do it i guess we're there hmm you'll hold y forever but not right trigger yeah because
over a hundred years of video games holding y holding well it's x on the xbox has been like
run super mario made that very clear over the last hundred years when the pilgrims were playing
mario they were holding y that is eons of gaming sorry let uh lap two oh i gotta jump it's
incredible precision to get this correct incredible precision really
when you get it it's so much fun when you get in one of those modes where you're just sprinting
the whole time oh i was just so confused but i don't what was going on right there did i
do something wrong what did i just do i was i literally was reading chat did i do it i thought
i had like i started hearing screams i was reading where you get what happened i looked over and
things were just dead usually with those secret rooms you have is that you don't just complete
themselves that's weird the same door stuck oh i did i thought that was a wall no no i want this
i want the toppings okay sick yeah i don't want to go too too fast i'll ruin stuff then lap and
spin oh god this thing will be fun i'm a pizza box any weird ways to go keep the combo going
this is the only place i'm gonna get a from here keep going keep going it's the only way i'm gonna
get a oh oh don't do me like that oh i don't like mushrooms on my pizza either way sound like it
you sound like a fucking smart dude you sound fucking smart shit come on it's all right i could
have gone i could go back and get it but i don't want to do it again no time hey where's it going
hi i'm new here you are not seeing your name many times that was a fun one
extra money too that's good thanks for telling me to go do that you guys are you guys are all right
okay so this is the last floor right final floor are you guys ready are we gonna see the end
of whatever we got two more levels i'm very excited i'm getting excited did that one
i know they're scared happy birthday it's like scary don't make a sound
this place is weird oh my god binaf is that thing counting down i gotta get up there
really what's up there lap two thank god binaf pizza brother i
whack the rat what the fuck it takes stop what was that it takes your points
what i got oh i i okay i did with binaf alarm it was open okay okay well i definitely don't want
that to happen so let's clean that up i'll be really honest i don't know how you get lower than
a c in this game or like a d like how do you get low is it even possible c i can understand
million times try to get a d is just don't kill any enemies just try to get to the end of them
just go to the end of level and just avoid everything just skip everything just avoid
items avoid everything oh oh my god oh my god he's coming he's coming he's coming oh my god
binaf is coming i'm gonna go that way in a sec i just want to clear this area because you know
i will it'll be stupid
oh no what do i do
whoa god damn it i got stuck in the jelly what the hell this is goodness oh come on not again
dude how did you not break through this what oh it's blocked door
i go that way i'm gonna get a d dude hold on you gotta yeah you gotta go i want the secret
you gotta go fucking fast hold on a minute there you go all right let's get started come on
oh dork see oh viney vine sauce viney here comes a viney raid here comes a viney raid
thanks a lot for me welcome everybody currently um playing i think viney you're playing the same
game right did viney beat it no thanks to everybody what's going on welcome everybody
no spoilers no spoilers or i will tell viney and then he will be very upset with you
thanks a lot everyone's having a good day good night whatever wherever it is where you are
oh he hasn't beaten it yet okay he said hey fuck face what's going on how are you doing
i want to sneak in that way it's not about speed it's about getting it done it's only
about speed when you have to run with the timer i feel like they would wait there's gotta be
something here Jesus all right let's go this game makes my head hurt or something
let's clean uh this level is really fun i like this one i get this level a a all right well
what what oh my goodness oh okay this is where it starts i need to get up there quick no my b rank
downstairs oh shit whoa good thing i'm bad at the game it just saved me oh he already broke it i
can just run all three of them here oh i don't know i feel like i thought i had to go i don't
know i thought i had to go down okay i thought that was a secret janitor's i know janitor it's
over gun shoot or shoot down but how do i get up there oh i okay oh pineapple on pizza
jesus i feel so much safer with this okay hold on where are they where are they
oh what do i do how do i fix this how do i fix it no come back to life oh my god you shot all of
them 22 that's not 170 only one more level in pizza tower well i want to hold on can i go up here
i can can't i what's up there are they hiding from me are they hiding from me over there
super jump will i go will i make it no dude i gotta start over
uh-huh oh that's okay that's what i'm supposed to do 210 is the last level
war oh this is gonna be a stressful last level isn't it i'm just gonna run all right i gotta
oh you idiot three seconds no okay i oh man okay this one's hard this one's
crazy this one's fun though all right i gotta i gotta stop shooting i'm sorry when in a game
when you give me a gun with unlimited ammo i'm just gonna be i don't know
monk i get a rubber down our duty okay stop doing that uh whatever shit
i wanted it so bad stop throwing for the bell i need it though it's extra points
what am i doing wrong i keep killing this thing oops
timer stops timer does not stop timer does not stop timer doesn't stop timer doesn't stop what
no no i thought it stopped after the timer stopped
all right i'm not gonna shoot at anything and i don't care about the bells i'm just going
i don't care this level is way too intense for me to give a shit about bells
except for that one oops i blew it i got i got three bells sorry no more bells
but just stop spamming me ah shoot the gun downwards fuck
no i have to do it i knew it i knew i was gonna have to
it's like a problem who are these people oh no it's not worth it just go
up hurry up hurry up i made it i need a few points to get a i need like two points i need
10 000 come on no ah whatever i needed like one or two more people to whatever okay
i got all the toppings 220 come to mr stick to rent a boss stage i think this is it
is this that's creepy that thing's gonna move isn't it it's gonna chase me
it's gonna be a pizza the last boss is a giant pizza so this is the pizza tower is it not okay
for a second i thought it reset my whole game i mean i i just want to know i want to know if
there's something at the bottom you know there's tons of secrets in this game who knows if there
was something to the left right on the ledge to the left or something i don't know i was
i thought it reset the whole game for a second i was like no it did not the fun part is remembering
where all the elevators are any new clothes i'll go for red one at least we get to look through
the areas one more time there's a spot to go over there 90 what is this for something else
okay well i won't i just want to see what's down there it's a pizza face okay yep i it's
just like bowser from sns the last boss and it's gonna be the same shit i played that probably five
to six thousand times so i probably won't even hit once shit damn it press it too many times
all right now i'm just like i'm just rushing i don't know why you know when you get that
mode where you're just like no go go fast i don't care just do it all right you gotta clear it you
gotta you gotta start clearing phase two let's go what done he took the tv oh no i get hit by
oh my god oh that's just carnage damn it oh that stinks it was i could have had it too but
it was just at some point you get it out of that focus state and it's just everything is just
colors they're blending together and things are screaming at you i can stay in that state
for a solid minute two minutes after that though it's like everything kind of starts my brain can't
i hate my brain hey my brain i have a brain can't because i hate you know my brain can't
i restart i gotta this is gonna be way cleaner oh fuck off my nose is itching my whole face is
itching all right and i have a health right there let's go is it they don't despawn right
so he does not hurt you i'm realizing that now i thought he was all right all right i got it
let's go is it s is that s that's gonna s oh no what the hell no oh goodness gracious me
oh goodness i am my i am okay i need to breathe for a second because like i'm like not ready for
this thank god you don't have to do the whole fight okay i'm way way less scared now oh we
have friends wait what this is a different fight what grab him what do you what's going on here
i'm in so much trouble
oh come on here's my health no perfect placement that was just so unlucky
so i just double unlucky that was just fucked okay this is incredibly difficult that just
fucked me so bad when there was no gun in that second fight it was just like what is happening
triple unlucky yeah i was looking for the gun i was like when's the gun spawn where's the gun
and it's like no throw your friend at him i didn't want to pick that up that's disaster
oh double unlucky i didn't i tried to hit up oh quick brutal unlucky in a row
fuck this is hard ah fuck uh it's hard all right i got it let's go
what the hell what oh my goodness you what all right just grab someone and don't throw them
ah god damn it it's a fucking mess
spawn enemies there seems like a standstill oh my god that little cog blends in with everything
fuck you hey believers let's hear it orphan of cost yes i didn't want to pick it up sorry
all right
oops god damn it sorry i don't need it
get out of here oh oh get out of here whoa
oh
how many times you have to do this that's it is that it nice oh no you've seen the crumbling tower
of pizza oh it's destroying okay go five minutes i gotta go through every level let's go oh there's
my um what's your friend can't really tell that's the wrong way you're gonna get out of here
i love how you're just in a line it's funny whoa santa santa gonna come with us
nice piece of shit he's not coming with us this santa is what just happened hurry wait
this other person coming with us i thought this person was an enemy that uh the other pizza
pepino guy i mean you got this shit up here i'm gonna go look right what was that the redemption
art oh okay jesus oh my god dude this reminds me of a cartoon don't mind it's too me don't
mind it's too me i'm the streamer primo burg what i have no way i failed it oh no it's okay i got
a hot dog hot dogs are just as fine go chicken friend hurry up go pineapple pineapple those
fucking weirdos that like that come on come on i have to get the pineapple oh fucking who cares
jerma said i was weird now to get down oh the apple jesus everybody dance quick
i don't think you're weird if you get pineapple on pizza it was a joke kidding around
don't worry no we don't care about that cool that was very very enjoyable game
cool customers is very goofy very good very hard a lot of challenge in it
well hard you could beat this game without even caring about getting high scores games like this
are really cool because depending no matter what your skill level is you're going to finish it
you just are you don't you can't die it's just a score attack so good or bad everybody gets to
enjoy it it's kind of cool how that works out that way you're not gonna get p on everything
i'm not gonna get p on one level centrist take because i don't want to get what about isaac
i'm probably gonna stop here there's a lot of stuff that has to happen this weekend
it's gonna be very busy but i pulled the stream back to today because i want i knew there was
only like three four hours in this game left so i might as well just go just get done play it have
fun and then get to work on some stuff what about frog detective frog detective will be
before the end of february that's still happening didn't make that up any post credits enjoyers
here let's see yeah hylix is as well let's see let me look at a good timetable here
well here i got an here's the thing how long is frog detective three
that they're all of them have been two or three hours long right like three hours four hours
they're only a couple hours each aren't they depends on how fast you go about two hours yeah
so okay here here is the plan i sauce is gonna say that there's no stream until early this coming
week and then probably on monday or tuesday we're gonna play frog detective three and then after
that we're gonna move to hylix in the same stream and then after that we'll see in the same time
i'm gonna be talking a lot about grotto beasts i know a lot of people are waiting for it a lot
of people excited for it it's uh it has been a journey but everybody on the team is incredibly
excited for it everyone's super happy cannot wait to show you some things in the next five or six
days is there gonna be a lot of announcements yeah you set the sauce for our early next week
i mean it's gonna has to be monday or tuesday because otherwise i i'm in breach of contract
with chat or playing frog detective for the end of february so it has to be them what are you
announcing i'm announcing grotto beasts you'll see you'll see it's gonna be a multi it's gonna
be multi-layered so there's gonna be essentially two or three different times that you need to be
aware of we're doing our best to try to make sure as many people can get it and what we're
gonna probably do a presale to make sure because i know a lot of people saying but wait what if
it just goes on sale and i and i want it and then like somebody buys a thousand of them or
something right that's we're gonna make sure that that's not gonna happen we're doing a presale is
it a pyramid scheme it's not a fucking pyramid scheme oh my my grand pyramid scheme no what the
fuck most no oh because i said i'm an idiot i said multi-level no i said multi-layer
shit i did just say i put multi in the front of that i said multi-level but i didn't oh god damn
it okay but i get multi-layered announcements is what i meant multi-layered rollout multi-layered
rollout not multi-level marketing that let's correct it immediately before everybody thinks
what the fuck is he talking about he's so stupid i would never oh my god
all right post credits anything or is it just on this for now there's going to be a big faq
that's going to answer a ton of questions as well uh it's being worked on we want to make sure that
everything's accurate there what's the game rate this game oh he looks so stressed oh no
capino's pizza animated film when capino's pizza animated series when no i'm just kidding
that was phenomenal excellent excellent excellent excellent you know final judgment no i got a d
that's the one officer wow oh hey d plus is uh is passing grade one percent off too bad yeah
too bad psycho b is failing b is not failing that was awesome yeah i'll uh i'll see you guys
next week early next week with a bunch of stuff to talk about again we're really trying to shoot
for that 28th february i really kind of start talking about a lot of stuff uh it's come together
i told you very briefly before but this project started off as kind of a little oh like a fun
little thing to do and then it grew into a decade of references and it's essentially just
i know a lot of people ask about merch and hey how come you don't do merch why don't you have
this merch how come you don't do that merch and figured this is kind of an interesting thing to do
and having hundreds of these cards that you could just get if you wanted to you know nobody's
no one's ever obligated to buy a single goddamn thing but i just thought it was a fun it's a fun
idea for sort of this multi-year long 10 plus years of merch that kind of combined into this
one cool concept so multi said multi again all right let's uh let's say goodbye to time rate
the game that was a who cares what i have to say about rating the game that was a nine point nine
point oh that was a nine point oh i would say that was great i was thinking is it an eight point
is it an eight point nine is it an eight point no that's a nine point oh that's it that was an
excellent experience that's very fun music was great level design was great except that one
level i didn't like but that's just because i'm not very good bad gamer but yeah see you guys
later have a great rest of your evening i'll see you guys early next week we have a lot to talk
about hope everybody enjoys it bad gamer see you soon can you do the pepino scream impression
no it's like 10 o'clock here and i kind of want to just chill out i'm good raid um
raid raid great stir you're saying what's they're doing what was it wasn't um i think stirs just
chilling out right now i don't know ultimately everything that i'm like going about is just like
if i actually i think he's just hanging out he's just chilling who else is live
rate him yeah if i okay if i raid stir stirs just trying to relax let him relax you know what i'm
saying he's playing overwatch just hanging out be chill if i rate stir well why don't we ask him
work and shit all right sir it's like stirred do you want me to raid you or do i'm just
nah are you like not you just don't want to fucking deal with that right now
let's hear he said also this game this game i wonder i'm curious i he's probably he's the
type he's probably gonna be like nah fuck that no no he doesn't
let me just talk in his chat let's see what a mess i will end stream of germa raids i am holding
my stream hostage to a germa raid oh hold on you want a germa raid like i i wish i was doing
something more interesting okay i'm not tired that's what i'm saying no it's all good it's all
good he's validated no it's all good that's what i'm saying that's what i'm talking about
how can yermol eat this super like like imagine imagine you're a devout catholic
this is what i'm saying you're just super religious and then you hear the voice of god
finally after years of prayer finally i've heard god and you're out you're on the fucking toilet
reading a newspaper like seriously god now this is not a good time i i do not look good right now
all right
carts really far back we are used to all right well if you want to raids if you go to i'm not
going to raid it he's just hanging out he's just chilling it you know where he is if you want to
go watch i'll see you guys later see like suddenly this feels like a real ass fucking
game with people calming what did you say germa is a false idol yeah unofficial raid if you want
to go over there all right see you guys later tonight bye take care of yourselves
oh your mother you know what's going on i'm trying to read my chat
all right i'm gonna oh now i'm doing it did you hear that did you hear that now i'm doing it
now i'm doing it yeah oh yeah let's go
oh now he's fucked now he's fucked well guys here for what you wish welcome to the late night
star stream the last time i streamed this late at night was i don't even remember it's been a
very long time beat let him chill though for real he's just he's literally just hanging out
oh be good here's some heal some boys all right see you later we've got some gamer
words being thrown out holy shit