All right. So, what? Uh, HillScent, thanks for the five community subs. Hill. Uh, what's- what do you- uh, what do you-
Eh, what do you guys want to do? I don't know if I want to do Jump King. I think I'm- might be too
wound up for that. Put in the two towers. Two towers! Let's go! Two towers! Let's go! Let's go! Two towers!
Oh shit!
Damn it. I like just fucked up my Xbox controller. Everything's full. What? Oh, it's all right.
It's good. It's okay. Okay. So, uh, did you hear that oh shit, by the way?
That was so weak. I was like, oh shit! Real voice. Two towers. You guys ready?
You said it and now we're going. I've- this is- this one is fucking awesome.
I guarantee you, he's gonna like the first part of this game. Are we finally gonna watch Lord of
the Rings naked? Uh, no. We're not gonna watch Lord of the Rings naked. All right, let's get this on.
How does it look? Here we go! I gotta change the, uh, I gotta change this. This game is actually very-
God damn it. This game's actually very, very good. It's actually fantastic. Do not let the last game
sour you on this one because this one is actually fucking incredible. All right. All right. I gotta
get it. I gotta get there. The world has changed. Feel it in the water. Feel it in the earth. No,
this game is actually fucking one of the best games to come out on PlayStation 2.
It just- it's- it's got like the red banner at the top. It says classic PlayStation 2 game.
Yeah, I don't know. It actually is true. It began with the forging of the great rings.
Okay, this is just the beginning. Am I allowed to watch this?
I'm gonna get in trouble. This is the beginning of the movie.
Get your popcorn, guys. We're watching the movie. Who above all else desire power.
For within these rings was bound the strength and will to govern each race.
But they were all of them deceived. For another ring was made. Yeah. In the land of Mordor,
in the fires of Mount Doom, the Dark Lord Sauron forged in secret a master ring to control all
others. And into this ring, he poured his cruelty, his malice, and his will to dominate all life.
What is this nerd bullshit? What are you talking about? This is the greatest PlayStation 2 game.
Red banner. The free lands of Middle-earth fell to the power of the ring. But there were some
who resisted. A last alliance of men and elves marched against the armies of Mordor.
And on the slopes of Mount Doom, they fought. Nerd bullshit. All right. All right. We I really
probably shouldn't do something. Literally just the movie. There's gonna be an algorithm
is going to find this screen and I'm going to get fucking my screen. Let's go.
This fuck is Harry.
I hate that shit, by the way. Anytime a video game pulls you out,
there's a huge, it's epic battle. You square to block. Like, no, don't just. Oh, wait. What do I
do? I wasn't looking. I wasn't looking. Shield attack. Look at this epic battle.
This combos in this game and shit. You want to listen RPG. There's RPG elements in this game. I
can't wait. I'm excited. Is there a dodge roll in this game? If that completes the four buttons,
if there is. Let's go. R2 when they're on the ground. Yep. Oh, that was pretty sick. Good,
good, good, good, good. Did somebody just say your movie sucks? I didn't make this movie. Hey, dude,
I just like came to stream model. You know, your movie sucks. Oh, we go. This is the best part.
It was in this moment. We get the movie again when all hope had faded.
Wait, wait, that was just that was just the piece PS2 one. I wish it was the PS2 render.
That would have been so much better. The enemy of the free peoples of middle earth was defeated.
The ring passed to Isildur who had this one chance to destroy evil forever. He didn't do it.
But the hearts of men are easily corrupted.
Oh, this is great. This is when actors get into the room in the audio booth
and they have glasses down on their nose at eight o'clock in the morning
and read every line like this. I am Isildur's era to me. Let's go. Next page.
It is read. All right, let's go. Good. Mission experience 711. Save the game. Game one, game
10, game two, one, game one. This game is crusty. It's very good, though. It's very, very, very good.
Harry in order to block enemy attacks with black arrows. It's a classic game.
Visengard is empty. It is an army bred for one purpose, to destroy the world of men.
Ring. Oh, oh. Boss fight. They seek the ring bearer. Stay close.
Wait, where's Broto? Can I lock on? How do I put fire on here? All right, I got it. I got it. How
do I swing with the other hand? Light it up. Fire. How do I swing the other hand? All right,
it's on. It's on fire now. There is definitely a lock on. It has to be. I know there is. Is there
not all right i gotta stand next to the fire come on here we go oh god i'm gonna die fucking
please do something the ps2 fucking sucks laughing my ass off it does not with one hp
whatever keep away from them proto god damn it i tried to block my dad there's no i remember
they've been a lock on somebody came and said how are you still playing this it's a different
game this is not the same game i probably shouldn't have done this because everyone's
been there that left is gonna come back and be like fuck this game dude what are you nuts
what happened i think it crashed come on give me one second it's all right it's because i
tried to skip it really quickly i fucked it up somehow i have blue ass screen laundry machine
that was kind of a laundry machine you're right yeah yeah yeah 2002 this came out one year after
the last one yeah games uh-huh this game i this game really is so good i just have to be good at
it it's hard 20 years ago almost yeah watch the movie again no thankfully i did save it all right
let's not get killed by the cutscene that would be nice return of the king is even better and they
did they did to get better as we went along all right here we go bison guard is empty
wait one army bred for one purpose to destroy the world of men hold on no no no i was gonna
say no it didn't go to the very beginning did it okay we're good all right let's do it
game's fucking hard i got a parry and then light they seek the ring bearer stay close
pass the ring take them out quickly good good light it up again every time you hear the ding
that means i did it by the way look at that all took us one try to fucking remember how to play
and now we're good i'm not getting swarmed on keep away from them attack of the bathroom yeah
watch it come on give me a perfect give me a perfect give me a perfect out of here
i wasn't looking at the fucking screen
oh i have a special move i don't think a special move doesn't matter
i can't even hurt them with this only fire oh yeah if you fill that meter you get the super moves
now i remember ow somebody said harry potter what do you mean harry potter this is the lord
of the ring all right we're good tutorial done somebody from twitch is gonna skip through this
and see this and they're gonna go what the fuck was he doing in the sanctuary is he stupid
trying to get suspended the fellowship was forged i will take the ring to mordor
you own the disc of the game right i do not yeah it's in my ps2 right now
the thumbnail is the move no is it really the thumbnail of the screen right now is just the
screen half of the movie
that's and i don't have a face cam or anything so it just looks real bad
all right so uh i got upgrade points aragon is now level two cool what can you do with
upgrade points you might ask somebody that thinks this is cool all right rising attack
what do i got 57 charge forward and drive unshielded enemies to the ground x circle
how does dna work i'll get this one let me see okay here's the next part that's really bad about
this the title of the stream is i guarantee you will like the first part of two towers
so whatever save the game yeah i'm just streaming the first part that's okay right twitch
the category too the game category is just the title of the movie not gonna lie for a moment
i thought you would just straight up watching the movie for whatever reason that's so fucking
funny okay we have here we go aragon unplayed legolas gimli we play as any of them who do
you want to play as gimli gimli every time ranged weapon virus attack speed attack knockback
repair a killing move ranged weapon is l1 okay god damn it if you refresh if you go to the tower
if that fails you're gonna refresh if you go to like just twitch.tv live channels and you scroll
down a little bit and you find this stream every time you refresh i hope to god it's not another
thumbnail from the fucking movie we shall wait here until the path beyond appears safe when in
trouble sending a dwarf it is again no way dude that shit was just on screen
for one second shut up well i know it's the thumbnail right now i'm talking about
in the future all right let's go let's move oh yeah i forgot this game had analog controls
yuck let's go the best part was when you do x x all right move out of the way x x triangle x
x triangle oh oops the buttons are pressure sensitive are they really what is this
checkpoint yeah dude it's ps2 quickly this way gimli's best character did you know
that the actor john was on his knees every single scene pretty interesting
new thumbnail good all right throw that at him maybe i can't we could pass through the
mimes of moria my cousin palin he was a thumbnail i've already seen it watch i saw it i know
watch out for the block bro bro jesus bro please throw it throw aragon block
aragon block aragon block for me oh my god how many times are the dead all right we're good
are there bosses in this game i think there are get the chest did i miss a chest is it a chest
oh that is a chest all right cool yeah i remember playing as gandalf coming up there's a gandalf
section that i have to get to that's the best part of the game when you do the uh what's the
what's the big battle helms deep gandalf helms deep hey gandalf helms deep give me half hp and
i'll fucking destroy it throw it five bits says you can't do that i'll take those from you
that's not this game that's a different game oh shit lord of the rings is just golden axe
oh block oh fuck this is bad can i please get up the superpower please almost there
block block do the axe move you're not doing the axe move what are you talking about axe move
what do you mean axe move what's that mean do the axe move bro i don't even know what the axe move
is let's get in the middle there we go there we go come on come on come on build it up
eric oh you don't do shit by the way you stand around he's so bad all right relax
so where's boss it's because you have to hold it and let it go okay
um what's going on i'm trying to throw i can go in the water why am i why am i staying away from
the water well it's got the it's look it's got the things on it get out of here nice
shit blocked off three of them come on up dude this guy was just vibing it's all right
here it comes last one right one more i'm reading chat i didn't that's not me saying that
minus two for zoomer humor minus two you friends are yours in the chat man well struck gimli this
is the door of duty lord of warrior at least it's not an in-game and at least it is an in-game
cutscene and not a fucking movie god damn this streamer doesn't care about t.o.s
all right bye what does gimli have moves no perfect how do you get perfect
uh all balen swift terror a very effective combo if we're taking out there we go xx triangle that's
what i was talking about xx triangle it's very good there's also this one too wound knock down
then finish off powerful enemies so it's x o r 2 cool dwarven fury press and hold triangle
button to use this yeah i'm gonna get this one xx triangle and that's good for now
xx triangle and i also have this thing hold triangle to use this is the axe move you guys
are talking about level one has moves they're all purchased i'm gonna stay with gimli i don't want
to spread the levels out too hard until we get to gandalf it was here that we would find far more
than the tomb of we have barred the gates drums movie time not movie time not right now
oh xx triangle xx triangle all right what about the move that i just got hold triangle
oh yeah that takes a while to load though get that shield out of here
shit that was fucking awesome holy shit that was fucking awesome
holy shit that was fucking awesome i remember how this works you have to build up that meter
to even get perfect or awesome points right i remember now i remember he's mashing i'm not
mashing he's dead you gotta group them up and then do that move like that
kill i just got full health
are we just going in a circle saying each other's names to make sure we're all in the same room
all right how long is this gonna go on for don't kill you
that's not what he said all right can get off can you blow a hole in the wall or something
oh god okay that hurts a lot oh my god that hurts a lot run run run run run run
i'm throwing shit at him i'm gonna die i don't want give me help help help help
oh okay it's only heavy attacks work give me press x ah can i block him
i wonder if i can parry nope we get gimly's cutscene oh god what if i do oh i have to
hide hide hide can i block that no oh fuck don't die here oh shit right in the eye
i i'm okay look at his eye he has so many axes in his left eye
nice job how many i got i got at least a handful on excellent i know that for a fact
there we go how many perfect none on perfect whatever sorry 14 000 points what is might
of permanently increase your health yeah i already have these xxx triangle triangle r2
circle yeah yeah yeah yeah i got them all already all right let's do uh
permanently increase health does this one permanently increase your health again i can
do this more than once i'm gonna get the rush attack too sounds good to me i love this game
somebody said this game sucks too that's just that's just not me that's just not true
a little the ring sucks overall
whatever all right here we go we can go down photographs of characters and scenery
what do you mean is this this is not a level is it just production stuff what is this it's just
pictures it's just photos of the set well there they are as we just did that
this would be pretty great screensaver pictures are there that's it that's it okay change image
if i can go down no you're gonna get oh thumbnail will the thumbnail change help i don't know how
to view photos all right here we go dude we're almost at literally the end of the game back to
gambling let's go helms d the lord of the rings 1080 extended blue ray dts hd fellowship
the quest stands upon the edge of a knife straight but a little and it will fail but it
would become darker still for a fellowship was failing i would have gone with you to the end
and into the very fires for who carries the fate of us all we protect proto let me try to get some
perfect you gotta keep the combo down yeah i saw the thumbnail of the face or that kind of too
small these guys are like three times bigger than me like i'm like out of range this movie is weird
what 59 have to kill 59 people is that what that is where the other 59 i think it's just waves
let me get like a perfect here settle down like a list let us get let us have you know what i mean
let me get what's the line that still only conscious one there it is we must defeat these
wrong movie is it though did that happen in return of the game what did happen
come on keep the meter up block block block block block
reminds me of the chronicles of narnia game why do i know what you're talking about one hit
where are the other two why am i doing this by myself am i doing something wrong
am i where are they they by myself all right go back go back go back back back go back
go back that didn't fuck did that not hit anybody fuck away from me quick get it while you can german
nude get fucked germa oh you got me he was actually scared
i picked that up okay why are they still back here i'm missing something back what are you guys
doing where do they go uh hello i don't know why they're not here that's odd it's just a solo
level oh all right all right gamely get down there all right 33 wait um frodo's dying
frodo's dying my god hold down l1 hold down square hold down up let go of x
urs go go go go go go go go go go where are you frodo he's not gonna die is he
don't die i gotta do this quick you can shoot the crossbow what are you doing
what a dick keep going come on hurry up i don't have time for the scope come on i need to kill
16 people fro's fucking gonna die all right stop axe move bro axe move bro no i don't have to do
axe move now where where where where where where where where where are you come on nine nine nine
nine nine nine nine nine nine nine nine oh hey guys i made it um what happens if i break the
cutscene um three no no no oh that sucks he crushed his head i didn't even realize
i thought that we were fighting together and they ran ahead of me oh fuck me had been a dark
fuck me give me a break what did i just do i wanted to we must defend it i'm sitting there
looking and walking around in circles looking for these two and they ran all the way to the bridge
i don't even know how that happened that seems almost impossible to happen can i fucking hit i'm
getting angry it's the same shit's happening again i'm too small to hit these guys when they're in
this spot exactly all right now now what now we oh yeah yeah wait you stand around
this is the same shit that happened last time and then they disappeared and i was looking for them
and they appeared at the fucking bridge just go just fuck you don't have the range we must
defeat these uruk-hai for proto to escape yeah sure just go ahead of me and run in front of the
bridge you two assholes we must defeat these no we're not here sorry gimli do it alone i used
to watch my cousin play this it's pretty good all right go just go down to the bridge that's
gonna be the easiest place to farm this shit god go oh no i'm standing in the fire
although i'm gonna kill me right okay made it to the bridge i actually have my two other heroes
now thanks for waiting i actually play the game now with you too i can't wait for germa to die
never mind yeah now i can this is how i'm supposed to be playing this part
actually figured the cutscene on the bridge yeah come on come on come all right geez now i'll get
it why am i not playing legolas come on important come on spawn spawn spawn oh my goodness really
how did you idiots let somebody through more perfect let's go one more who's left sick those
guys only mash yeah it is annoying um why does he have a health bar now
uh-oh one-on-one this might be you shall enjoy this you got nothing of course you're gonna have
a guy come from over here get two people get in there i mean he blocks everything
okay that didn't even hurt him now i have to shoot him with arrows i know i can't hurt him
i have to do full charge i'm gonna have to start this fucking shit over it's the tree boss again
now finally now we fight let's go me and you one-on-one let's do it of course you have to
have another guy you have to be another dude cctv angle don't make me laugh cctv angle
this happened outside of a fucking like 7-eleven oh my god please have it be right there
oh
god thank god thank god god god god god i shall enjoy this
times am i going to say that oh god oh god i keep saying it i have no vocabulary right now it's
gone how i heard him i was challenged outside of the logo 7-eleven i just show this is so stupid
why are you right about this ha ha ha ha ha ha three drunk men take bar brawl to the streets
yeah that's kind of what happened the lego game version of this scene is better
level up all right do i did i get a little above four now i have three i got look at this four
goblin bane now hold on what about two should i get this that's kind of good hold on what's
what do we got instantly kill an attacking goblin link to charge attack didn't
i'm not already here rush attack that just gets upgraded attack as you regain your feet taking
enemies by surprise yes and that's i need that so bad wound knock down and strike your enemy with
this combination i like this one x triangle xx germa's average dong just gave 10 community subs
thank you average dong appreciate it that's 10 subs on top of the shit load that everyone's given
so far thank you the sound is a half second before the video is that for real you should be here in
a right when the light you see the light bang bang bang bang you should be seeing that hey guys
i'll fix it right now one two one two one two one two um i forgot to delay my mic by about
three or four hundred milliseconds the whole screen it's been like that the whole time
just redo the whole stream what a noob now it's unwatchable nobody even noticed
despite horomir's heroism the servants of saruman captured members of our company
we would not abandon our companions to torment and death for days we followed their trail
finally it led us to fangorn forest this forest is old no shit very old it's full of memory
and anger good transition there yeah some of you guys that might remember they came this way
that was but the trail ends here that was so cool split up to find them quickly 20 years ago it
really was let's split up what i get i got a new combo right that looked pretty good
out of the way all right they got these guys got shields break those shields i'm just gonna
farm parry's bounced around fuck i had it he's getting hit by every attack there's five people
around me sorry i didn't practice my playstation 2 action game skills before the stream started
wait what do you what do you drop this is another tree boss is this a tree boss i think it might be
oh great this shit troll he's dead i wouldn't have that actually that's pretty easy
what am i i'm not gandalf you don't in this game oh that's only in the turn of the game
behind behind behind behind they can't kick me in the hole can i give me that meter meter got it
perfect perfect perfect come on anybody else somebody somebody please
oh give me the meter i mean you're back there what the hell are you doing back there are they
alive uh it was slow is this the bb bb bb stream what's that i don't know what that means
come here just do that move like three times in a row he's drowning while fighting
vvvvv is a good game um that's the where you the gravity one right that's pretty cool
it just got released open source i always imagine that's probably so what does that
so people can now just essentially have the entire game's code to be able to make their own
levels or what's the benefit of doing that what do you make you can only make like a sequel or
something make your own levels make your own game essentially in the game it's on github that's
crazy i wonder what the legality of that stuff really is i guess if you self-publish right what's
going on why can't i move i was i was just like stuck that's weird okay that's just that's my
that's my mirror i thought that was an enemy really starting to overuse this and i know you're
gonna scare me come on i need it god come on how have i not done it yet this is the same one where
you defend a door i actually have no idea click click boom click click boom come on most of
perfect give it to me oh well gimme has terrible range yeah i've already i'm already playing as
him though if i played it does not if i took another character i don't think it would go over
so well with chat you know they want me to play with a little guy well all right you know am i
gonna pull him jesus how am i gonna do this what the fuck uh die come on jesus that hurts
oh man get out of the way this health right behind him is that was that grass was that
grass that i saw what was that grass wasn't god damn it don't kill me what happened i tried to
swing at him i tried to swing at him and he did a half swing and let go give me a fucking break
fake gamer no it's called god what the fuck don't even tell me i have to do this thing i'm so happy
thank the thing that i've said a thousand times today this is ridiculous thank auto
my controls keep changing when the camera changes glorious die i win good all right let's see this
link what do you got we need him to see this what is it you guys have you guys are so quick i love
it this is gonna be great i already know this is gonna be called a quality quality video okay let's
hear it did you reach sense sense fortress yet no not yet hopefully soon okay why can i hear
anything okay there we go it's cctv there's people lying on the ground what happened outside
what could have possibly happened is that it like look over here ready there's somebody
somebody's already dead back there some already you know somebody's already been beat up
three people he's uh he throws the axe too i love this so much
that's quality man seriously that is absolute quality that's just me playing well yeah i know
how we met up there is something out there what do you see legolas the white wizard
saruman saruman do you fight saruman in this in that great forest many parts converged
there is a union now between the two towers or sank and that'll do it really is kind of
the tldr the whole thing huh but needed elsewhere more points go five do it i remember when i was
younger i was able to get so many points everything was almost all excellent i don't know how the hell
i did that how the hell did i do this what this one i'll do this one maybe i'll just save
now this one looks cool x circle triangle you had a non-void gamer license that's true
motor skills deteriorate with with age i'm not even sure that's what it is i think it's just
games changed i didn't change games changed not me it's it's the children it's the children
that are wrong not me yeah this one kind of sucks this is self a vertical video really vertical
picture what you don't know is i don't know the actor's name christopher lee is it christopher
lee what's the actor's name it is right yeah i think i might myself burnt out right now i was
gonna say what you don't know is it right before this scene started to be shot christopher lee said
a funny joke to paul stevenson right before they started shooting that's not a snarl that's a smile
but they left it in the movie i was gonna do something like that why am i so burnt out right
now what's going on he's getting old a little blood sugar uh maybe i don't know the tree took
seven years off of your life plains of rohan it must have consumed my entire life force
it probably did i also gave a shitload of it away too yeah what what did i do that what was i doing
that for i remember this part i actually do remember this part yep this exact scene
yeah it's gandalf didn't move there was a string when i was younger where i could have perfect
100 percent oh come on gandalf you're so bright you're getting in my way he got past the tree
eventually i did i am needed elsewhere no you can't introduce gandalf and then delete him that's not
fair um what happened what's going on uh the cutscene just didn't trigger okay that's great
watch out get out of the way i have to save the family i blame the cutscene not happening i stood
around play of eight seconds and then the cutscene just didn't work i was like am i in the right spot
save the family i'll get him you didn't have to run into the fire well i thought i was supposed
to go up the stairs which i was but it wouldn't let me until the guy fell down he's gonna watch
gandalf he's after yeah but come on in here let's fight with me let's go what is it bang bang bang
my nose is so itchy right now just burn him open it germa broken to my house three i'm naked
ranting about how he needs the keys to my car to flee to mexico after he streamed lord of the
rings and got banned open it wait does he does he need to walk okay what is going on he needs to
walk in the room first all right get up there why do you have so many fucking tables in your house
you don't need this many tables families were huge back then where is this family
the camera switches dude are you gonna block every attack i do man the old man is getting
fucking destroyed get out of my way i'm coming he's blocking everything this old guy
i'm coming what are you safe all right go where's the rest of the family they're all
they're over there how do i get over there how do i get over here how do i get over there
what about the roof okay it was on fire i don't even i don't even know what happened
he likes the first part i guarantee you'll like the first part of two towers
first part of two towers fellowship with a ring fuck that's actually correct
the last level of this game is hard as fuck i don't remember i don't remember the run around and
save i don't remember any of this zero somebody's still dead open the door you must press on i wish
i could save the game right here okay get clean let's clean this up seriously best ps2 game ever
also me i don't remember this no i don't remember a game i played 20 years ago
like what i was like fucking 15 i didn't play this last weekend how am i almost dead
get the fuck over here oh go go go go go go go break it what give me a break man
who's left who's left is already left i can't help that person
oh god everything on fire they do it who's even oh this gandalf good thank you gandalf help us
okay i'm losing my mind what's he doing how they're gonna burn they're gonna burn they're
gonna burn what do i have to do what i have to hit i don't even know where they were i don't even
know where that person even was i tried to throw an axe in the barrel and it didn't even do it
get the fuck in here we must save everyone that we can or this image should fall just kill them
i'm starting to tell it's happening who's this person and why they're not staying to help
it's already at fucking 50 man well i can't even do anything about this is it 50 already what are
you talking about they're already dead they're already fucking dead what this is unfair this is
not fair these motherfuckers are dead already i can't even this is impossible
get out of the fucking way out of the way out of the way out where are they where's it
i'm gonna die give me health please health health go save the save it save the village right over
they're getting killed there's nothing i can do about it
okay that guy comes out and just starts slashing motherfuckers and there's five people around me
i can't even throw anything up there it takes gimli five seconds to throw a fucking axe
you want to see how long it takes gimli to throw ready let's see how long it takes one
two three it takes almost full three seconds to throw a fucking axe this character sucks this
character sucks why did i pick it for the meme and now i'm disappointed to save everyone damn it
i can't even man i can't even where's this thing you want me to do before i get in the building
so i don't lose 80 percent of the village people's health where is it my god give me a
fucking break give me a break motherfuckers i swear to god get out of the fucking way
get out of the way i can do it i can hey you should have guaranteed i wasn't gonna beat the
two towers because this game's way harder go barrels hurry up come on get the collectible
i don't give a shit about a collectible i'm trying to beat this stupid part of this mission
well now i'm surrounded and the guy comes out just slashing people all right get up there
how do i get up there that guy up there even fucking gandalf can't even hit this motherfucker
we can't hit him even the ai can't do it i'm cracked my voice is cracking all right settle down
i don't don't understand what's happening right now don't i go up there i i'm not soft-locked
we care about the townspeople not about these people though please get rid of that meter
i don't want to do this anymore get in that building get in that building get away from me
get away from me which building are they in this one is it this building um what what building are
they in what building are they in get out of my way please i don't want to do this whole thing
again get out get out get out get out get off this kid is asking no stop what are you doing out here
get away from this get away from this why are you here please get away from the battle
do they leave oh my god gandalf okay go what's left down the homestead you still have work to do
oh my god i'm so i am that was ridiculous all right let me please gandalf no gandalf
i didn't level up either i must have done pretty bad then huh oh well
i'm gonna save my points i do the first playbook i gotta eat a fucking steak after this
i don't know what's going on today all right we're almost done four or five more levels the west
fold i don't need production photos all right i'm gonna try i'm gonna try a different character
let's try legolas king's god i have seen it before but never like this
grab it yeah i've got gamer snacks our only hope is to stand together all right if i fail
next time i fail the mission i'm going to get a gamer snack through this town help us destroy
i got crave beef jerky now let's check out these must destroy these explosive devices
is
i'm going to i'm going to get a fucking gamer snack i'll be right back
okay i got my i got some uh grade a beef here show it just crave i don't have any clothes on i
can't turn on i have seen it before but never like this this is what i needed this is absolutely
what i needed hope is to stand together now that's the power of peanuts you ready help us
destroy them what's this we must destroy these explosive devices oh already got a character
i'm doing gimli so wrong here he's great i'm getting my ass kicked oh he's level one that's
right oh my god you're right holy shit i'm gonna die by two auto attacks i thought you were on my
team what do you mean you're doing easy mode this is this is how the character plays
it's legolas that guy's bomb on his back watch out watch out guys bum
oh sorry guy back it up holy shit there's a lot of people coming what are you aiming at look at this
what are you aiming at there's nothing over there good don't move oh god all right we're
good we're good we're good we're good i got all right jerky moment oh why am i doing this so slow
that was the slowest i've ever put food in my mouth i dropped it like three times
all right just that one that was sandy for some reason what is what are you aiming at
this guy's fucking dead that guy is buddy that guy dropped his last life potion hold on wait wait
wait wait wait don't kill me oh my fucking god all right i don't think i can do this at level one
i can't do this at level one somebody said are you screaming at the beach
because they hear the cars drive by no it's because of the sand oh it's not because of the
sounds of like the waves of the cars going by that too yeah our only hope is to stand together
saruman's forces move strange explosive devices through this town help us destroy them we must
destroy these explosive devices try this one more time i'm turning it on now i'm gonna actually
do try as hard as i can i'm glad to keep the levels though i'm taking way too much damage
ahead i can't do this with legolas i'm gonna get comboed by somebody in insta duck and i'm
gonna be so mad about it you all know what's gonna happen you know what i mean no way streaming 5g
somebody dropped something thank you does level increase your health i can buy it
this is gonna be rough though jesus we gotta get out of the fucking way just body blocking me
what are you guys doing i gotta okay oh oh jesus fucking christ this is ridiculous
i can't i can't even i can't even man dev and chat there's no dev and chat absolutely not
yes there is who is what are you talking about there's no dev here so just go back and just
gain levels hello i developed this game well these games are good these are classic ps2 games
they're fantastic dude the entire cast of lord of the rings is in the chat right now
oat horse five community subs thank you oat horse thanks a lot seriously
i was too close but i got it that's the dev oat horse is the dev oh shit really
what's going on is this for real wow what are you up to now what are you doing now
i hit that from all the way back here hey germa sean b no no stop stop anybody can pretend
i don't know if this is pretending why is this not blowing up yes give them a taste of fire
okay let's go he worked at storm front studios damn really that's so cool well
welcome to the stream this is one of my favorite games for ps2
and the sequel return of the king is even better it's not it's hard i just murdered that guy okay
it's very hard it's you can co-op all right i have to be careful here i don't want to die again here
back it up there's so many people here damn it block oh i leveled up i thought the guy still is
he okay no he's he's dead he's georgia r martin in the chat all right i gotta pay attention
if i stop paying attention for one second i'm dead in this game dead all right watch these
these dudes that run with the bombs up here there is any more there's like one more that comes over
here right he's fucking with us wait who's oh my god oh that's actually cute what let me see
up the whole baggage i picked it up upside down i picked up the bag of fucking jerky upside down
it just dumped everywhere 5g brain today guys i'm still eating it i mean it i don't care fuck it i
don't care i taste hair all right what we got i bought five subs tonight i was a programmer
on okay this is i hold on a minute i sound like i just got out of the dentist so just give me one
second while i do this hold on still here still here i just forgot that putting a handful of
jerky in your mouth is gonna take five minutes to eat oat horse thank you oat horse seriously
i bought five subs tonight i was a programmer on two towers back in the day and love seeing you play
the game my daughter and i are huge germa fans and i was thrilled to see my game on the channel
that's so sweet thank you a lot harder than i remembered but still it still holds up 20 years
later it'll work okay right when i come back i think i just breathed in jerky i just breathed
in beef jerky is that bad if i gotta like is that gonna hurt me i just i breathe it's in my lungs
did i just breathe it in is that bad for you how bad for you is that how bad for you is breathing
in beef jerky get this guy away from me i can't look at it don't hit him don't hit him i couldn't
run i can't fucking believe it i couldn't walk backwards anymore um okay i just like
breathed in and beef jerky went into my lungs you aspirated food i mean i'm all right it probably
didn't why did i pick beef jerky i should just have a tahini sludge for a stream snack why beef
jerk it's like takes it's so hard to eat i just fucking aspirated food because oh i should just
make a smoothie pick like the hardest thing to eat on earth i may as well have just chewed bubble gum
and swallowed it what am i doing aspirating food is that actually even possible can you like inhale
food and it like yes but you just did wouldn't well wouldn't i see other symptoms it's called
your it's called choking choking doesn't mean food is in your lungs jet that's not how that works
what's this i find this worth carrying i swear to god if i have to go to the doctor tomorrow
and they're like yeah you what happened looks like you aspirated beef jerky how well you
see doctor i was playing a 20 year old game called lord of the rings you ever heard of lord
of the rings yeah of course i have here we go again with another doctor bit and you see a dev
came into the chat the dev of the game and it was like a big surprise and then i unpaused the game
and three explosions happened around me and i inhaled beef jerky oh shit i thought you were
gonna say something fucking crazy like you're on a roller coaster or something that's pretty normal
and he nudges me with his elbow hey imagine eating beef jerky on a roller coaster
those guys just keep running in somebody's gave 10 subs he just gave it office source
thanks for the 10 community subs office source imagine aspirating beef jerky on stream
people ask jerma why don't you eat on stream that's not a big deal eat on stream
because i am such a fucking weirdo and i so strange shit happens to me all the time that i'll be the
guy that aspirates the food on stream true stop saying aspirate why look at how many enemies are
here this is i i i mean i do this god just keep being my shield what a lucky drop thank god this
guy's just taking huge hits over here dead dead lightning bolt lightning bolt lightning bolt dead
dead dead we got a raid coming in we got a raid raid coming in this village burns like
raid coming in box box raid coming in oh my god pay attention no don't let this ruin everything
oh my no no no no no no no no no no no give me together keep it together i can do it
thank god hey what's up box box thanks for the raid welcome everybody this is three they they
the deaf knows i'm playing he just did this he got into my game and okay please kill one of them
uh frilly five subs box box hope you had a good stream welcome everybody we're playing lord of the
rings the playstation 2 the two towers about 70 of the way through the game 60 of the way through
the game um i don't know what to do about this i just uh i just asphyxiated on uh some beef jerky
i just inhaled beef jerky well i mean there's that you just you just missed that one by a little bit
it's followers only turn off followers only we got a raid pull that up thank god lord of the
rings of two towers is considered to be uh harder than sakiro that's not me that said that that's
every reviewer and that's quite a few uh pieces of literature have come out in defense of that so
this is gotta be the end of the level blow up every one of these you know can i just say that
this guy's the mvp right here this dude the guy that's been with me this whole time can you just
blow up already what do you leave me alone blow up the dude that's been just inhaling hits
it's just the tank and then you need a tank too you always need a tank are you seriously this is
knock them down good keep on they're waiting for me over here yep oh man that's one of these
assholes and i can't look at how slow i am you've got to be fucking kidding me you've got to be
kidding me you've got you've got to be kidding you've got to be kidding you've you've got to
be kidding me oh man it's all the way i have i think i'm gonna have to level up i have to go
and do one of the levels again
you gotta go with the water oh man
god damn it man i think this game was balanced around two people playing it
not me and this random dickhead i already have second controller that's not fair to this guy
he did so much work dude in front of the dev in front of the dev no i'm not i'm just saying
it's very hard yes give them a taste of fire yes yes
yes
yes what are you guys doing yes
i gave him pittling to swallow us all i think you got this there's too many enemies on the
screen i feel like level 10 for this shit uh dude just don't get hit for it just don't get hit
which one he said who said it what am i doing i didn't know is i thought it was far away
this is not a game for jerky breathers
get out of with this you hit a guy from behind no honor i'm taking it slow i'm not fucking this up
anymore okay i need health add where why would it why would i even throw it over
what do you think i'm aiming at i'm so upset right now i'm just beyond angry this village burns like
dry tinder don't wait did i get it it's the same place where i got where's the health this time
that was a huge chain oh my goodness killed everybody i want to hit that thing not the one
behind it come on come on what do you got anybody else so we got somebody here omega lol i see lots
of omega lows beef jerky inhaled brave chili lime beef jerky inhaled it's so good though
all right i'm gonna stay back for this that's noto that's noto photoshop
lag lag lag didn't hit him all right what's the plan here should i just go just run across
i'm just gonna run across don't fight anybody just go across no i i can't i can't man i can't i'm
stuck here uh dude i can't even run backwards what the fuck where's the health i can't go back
anymore come on let's go let's go better aragorn all right let's see i can't hit it that's not a
bridge i can't cross it i just tried fuck away from me get up there don't hit the thing behind
i did it all right those few of us able to fight march for helms deep there the future of rohan
helms deep that's the final mission of the whole game close only three more missions after this one
i'm gonna stay with the original i'm gonna stay with gameplay i need 10 000 didn't get it i hate
this i don't like this image 9 000 uh i need this i'm gonna wait is that oh hold on wait a minute
that's not even you made those bigger didn't you even in the real image i don't think it's
those are that big no that's an accurate image gap of rohan look at this we're almost there
helms deep helms deep helms deep coming up the breached wall we're so close the game's pretty
short yeah i could i could finish it unless i get stuck and dump a bottle of beef jerky on me
but these creatures reach the refugees
seamless all right now at least i have friends don't pick up that health not yet um again great
make them fear the wolves of eisengard
it wasn't that bad come here one it didn't hurt okay get up well get roll dodge do anything
and literally do anything jump dodge x he gave up kill that one the boss i understand
can't where is he come here does that mean get in uh i print this guy kill that one
i have to hit him i i did he blocked it all right watch out watch out i'm dead
uh at least it's right here that's one thing that makes me happy you have failed all right again
we'll do it again we'll do it again quick so i have to dodge around until he goes up in the
air and then hit him in the belly this boss has kind of a gimmick you have to get his health to
zero before he'll die okay i'm not gonna pick up any health either well i might have to all right
come here wait till he moves around to a point where i can hit him in the stomach i'll try that
go up in the air there it is charge oops kill that one that didn't hit go in the air so i can hit
you yeah no you don't go in first you wait please don't stun lock me forever the health
just despawned it did kill that one kill that one thanks for the health go in the air go in
the air you're pissing me off try the lord of the rings conquest is that the rts no it's not okay
come at me all right i'm gonna hit you one more time it's like battlefront why do i know what
you're talking about i feel like i've played it or heard of it before it's battlefront 2 on lord
of the rings that sounds awesome you gotta be kidding me look at that hp please have health
thank you i win you lost my arm play the mmo is that the whole level so it is that by various
paths we have all come to the four domes deep make a final stand okay well that was the quickest
level so far i can upgrade him please help we're at helms deep x we need more health
fax health increase let's see what else can i do not a level six yet i need bane pool health health
health better axe
so
root of protection charge attack maybe i'm gonna hold on to it i think yeah
let's get it that's an instant kill
remember you are a strong burnt out dwarf i love it the ring is stealing your soul
i'm all right now this is before i it was the tree bosses wouldn't stop me deeping wall
helms deep this is why i got this game but this string of two or three levels in particular
this is why i got it where is the horse and the rider where is the horn that was blown
they have passed like rain on the mountains like wind the days have gone down in west the hills
to shut up we must keep sarons gaze fixed upon us keep him blind to all else that is moving
you know what i wish there was how come we have street addresses right why don't we have
fantasy names and video game names and movie names for our street address
how come there's not like 22 gondor lane or like 621 super mario boulevard that's kind of cool
wouldn't it be cool skyrim street you're a fucking door i'm sorry but if i lived on
legolas lane you don't think that that would be cool wait and that's still only conscious one
what do i have to do oh well that was just our water for the week sorry don't have to kick the
things down left side left side left side left side left side left side left side hold on have
we already been overrun i can't see this rain is blocking my view i just lost kick the ladders i
tried to hit the ladders i actually like to kick them not swing at them when we kick them i swung
at them with my axe this is a bad way for the movie to end my girlfriend started playing skyrim
she would be so happy if you streamed it no i'd made too many monsters i can't play it
okay right i i was i tried to swing at them
move i'm the latter guy by the way why can't you guys do this why does it have to be me
stop saying that because i'm gonna say it a bunch of times now dude uh
oh is that okay okay okay stop doing that
okay there's so many fucking ladders this is all i can do is be the guy that knocks the ladders down
they'll sing songs about me please put them down move out of my fucking way
um don't even fight don't there's no reason to fight don't fight only hit ladders that's it
don't do anything else when does this end how long is the helm's deep battles
you guys are in the way it lasted for two movies well i mean just the battle sequence at the gates
two movies all right after these two i'm gonna fight all right let me help let me help out the
fight good i killed one guy it was worth it i thought you said this was the good part of the
game uh yeah i it is um this is the part it is a part okay unbelievable thought you said this is
the fun part i'm trying this is it's over did i seriously kill i did not just lose
get move the fucking guy move get out of my way you motherfuckers you fucking idiot i'm just being
body blocked oh my god you can't even remotely be serious did i forget this part i lost if i don't
run in the circle and hit every ladder i i lose but if i don't kill anything i lose what just win
oh knock down every single ladder or lose but kill them though please kill them hurry
you know i wish i could delete all the people standing up here
how many times have these fucking golden motherfuckers just been in the way
and i just walk into them like i would rather just run around and do this you need these guys
well can they can they just stand in a different spot get out of the way good
i gotta kill him i should play fucking betty alivia is like what a great what a great place
for a fucking torch right in the way kill kill him get out of the fucking way why even have
collision with these motherfuckers i swear to god
move move move move move move move move move move move move move
i chose the joke character i this is not the joke character this is gimly of wherever he's from
i don't know there's fucking so many people over here no no no no no no no no no no no dude no no
oh no man no
do you have to swing an extra fucking time get out of the way oh my god this is fucking million
people oh is this even possible with one person oh my god man i bought the game because of this
one mission they gave me run around and shove ladders down for 12 minutes
and they just get overrun because you don't have a second player
all right this is the one third time's the charm let's go no more fucking around i'm doing this
this is the last one i'm doing it kill move this is like the game algorithm aio i can't even read
that and they all have shields so i have to use this triangle i don't have any combos with triangle
all these motherfuckers come up here with shields
it's hard to even tell what the fuck is going on right now i don't even know who's on the screen
i don't know where my character i want to throw this fucking guy off the edge i want to push that
guy off the edge i want to throw him off the edge by his grab him by the jeans in his shirt and
fucking throw him off every single fucking one of you has to have a goddamn shield on
look at this mess over here i can't just bring a combo together because these motherfuckers got
a shield
to fucking block me bro
i have to have to die they have to die or it's over
just start killing people kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill oh don't worry don't
mind me everybody got a shield i'm gonna lose my mind
that's it it has to be it that's it that has to be the end
how makes you feel like you're part of the movie really makes this is just what real
war is like
every ladder is back guys every ladder is back i can't even move kill everybody please
hit us all stand in front of stand in front of everybody hit us all please
oh my god i can't even do a fucking combo just broke something
oh my god
you don't understand i have to do triangle because it's the only thing that breaks the
shield if you don't do triangle you can't hit the enemies oh my god this is so fucking ridiculous
god
just stay in the middle i ignore middle ladders they're too much work i think we're gonna get
overrun we're just one person far middle don't ever go right it's already overrun leaf center
ladders up funnel enemies through choke points you gotta fucking look at that mess
oh
it's in plus so hey why are you not doing combos it's like kind of even hard to see
well how i'm swinging the axe move i can't believe you got fucking through check the game boomer
tip good knockdown i don't hate you anymore why do you have to do it twice like i didn't even
press it i didn't press the button fuck the metal right now like i blended in the background
that didn't hit the fuck out of the way teleporting run this guy's still alive
kick the ladders first they come this is like the ultimate backseatable experience
because on your screen it's just kick the ladders down dude kill the guys you kick the ladders down
scratch your head pluck your eyebrows use your blinker just fucking go that didn't kill him
you gotta be fucking kidding me dude gimli it takes you forever to swing it takes gimli
a hundred fucking years to swing exactly it's over it's over it's over there they're flooding
the middle i didn't get i didn't get how many people up there this is fucking insane
oh did any 12 year old us do this how did we do this when we were like 16
there's no way i would have done this when i was like fucking 13 i need to farm xp now where's
error all right we're going where's a good farm level what's a farm level i'm not playing this
game anymore what did i unlock here but that's actually john race really i have to level the
other characters he's too stout and small what's a good one to do i'm not watching the gimli
interview until i beat the fucking game i am so burning up right now all right what game boomers
dot com lord of the rings here it is what the fuck is this this is a i thought i just got my
computer hacked to click on that this is unreadable i can't even read this this is what i feel like
it looks like if you put an entire book on my screen at the same time a whole book it's just
every inch of my screen all right let's see let's look at all right let's see let's put it on the
screen uh text let's do uh i think i broke it you can see this font size i think i crashed my obs
just put it in text to speech i don't think i can even there's too much here to put in text to
speech what's that website that i can do too i don't it's too big type helms deep all right
find helms deep helm this is not in the right guide yeah this is an incorrect guide helms deep
is not even on here oh no yeah it is now helms deep okay i don't think this is the right guide
no this is incorrect plus i did all these text to speech sites cut off after like 150 characters
it's the second to wait the lord this this is this actually correct
no it's not let me just bomb for a little bit this is for the game boy version i've played like
four hours on gimli and i don't even know the fuck i'm doing now
i don't i don't know man i'm i might just delete game i'm thinking about i'm thinking about just
opening up playstation 2 and turn the stream on like we're always at like 60
levels of uh of take disc out of fray it's like 65 i think
grinding or aragon's broken just abuse his stuff i you know what i hate about this you can't tell if
they're dead on the ground or just lying on the ground you know what i mean there's like no i don't
even know if those guys aren't gonna get up enough it says good yeah but when you're surrounded by
people who knows if it's the guy behind you the guy in front of you that died doesn't really help
you're gonna stop me in the middle lat how dare you i'm so over it i'm so over it i'm so over it
why am i reloading the game well because uh the last helms deep level heads is deemed to be
impossible with my current character uh i don't know this is the way i'm playing with yeah no
we know what let's play get back on gimli and get them back in fucking helms deep no not
give me a minute i mean completed what do you mean completed i can't do it wait i cannot do this with
gimli i didn't even want to do that fucking r2 by the jeans by the jeans off the cliff
i love 12 fps as well what a great experience
that's
i didn't fucking getting up still like that fucking night getting up still
i need to fucking act his head up and wait
yeah stop oh the controls make me want to puke in my mouth he's already dead
okay you can't be serious man
fuck the middle for now i gotta throw axes it takes like three seconds to throw an axe guys
it's not gonna work oh it's over i think this is the level where i gave up as a child nobody
beat this by himself i don't think it's possible nobody did where where are the steam trophies for
this one it's gonna be gray across every single united states of a i'm only gonna kick ladders down
there are enough for us both gimli
why can't you motherfuckers do this too i came up here because i knew that was gonna happen this
damn it i didn't get it before they fucking came up with this shit in every goddamn fucking angle
i get why is my character turning around what the fuck is going on right now get out of my god
this is this is this is close i have to go up here you better be dead finish the job oh you
finish the job and don't germa sounds like a super villain i am right now give me you
fucking tiny little motherfucker i swear to god you can't even swing at anybody within five feet
of you hold the axe by the bottom of the handle gimli not the top unbelievable are you seeing that
shit are you seeing this shit are you seeing this shit i can't go to the ladders these people this
is this is unfucking believable this is not possible i can't do it i can't do it this is
fucking the hardest thing i've ever done all the guides have to level around 10
this motherfucker's level five he's level five and i can't do any other levels with him
am i gonna do it again i i don't even know if i can physically do this
set up a t a t a s bot i don't think they would be able to do that can i not play the other levels
why can't i replay these these now these are photos i have to beat the game with somebody
what what do they say what are the guides say lord of i don't remember this being this ridiculous
the next level is worse than this is it i'm going legolas jesus christ i don't remember being like
this start to grind i don't want to grind i want to beat it it's gonna just get worse
what's a level that i can reliably oh push the ladders baby ignore combat 100 completely don't
hit anyone do not hit anyone just only do ladders but i i'm gonna get overrun you're swinging at
air i but it's hard it's the game the game's controls are hard kick the ladders only in the
middle that's not gonna work i'll try it kick ladders only in the middle stay in the middle
okay are you okay i'm gonna i'm only gonna kick the ladders in the middle
that is the worst idea ever kick all ladders i don't want to hear this
i don't want to hear that anymore i'm sick of hearing it
okay i'm only gonna knock down the middle ladders and i have time though that's this
this is not a good idea stick to the plan stick to the plan stick to the plan what was the plan
what was the plan only ladders in the middle after what was the plan only throw axes no ladders
for x what do you mean where am i throwing the axes at am i doing it right the plan sick of the plan
take the plan axe move what no no the axe move takes like five seconds to charge up it's not
gonna work you take 10 seconds to kill a guy and mail it i think you severely underestimate how
hard it is to play this game i think you under like i said you can sit there and go wow he's
fucking stupid what a dumb motherfucker i hope he shits his pants swinging this axe is hard
i'm not ignoring the left i have time to do one okay now i'm gonna ignore it
finish the fucking job mate now we're going come on you're supposed to be the best player
get over there get over they made it in they made it in they made it in this guy who didn't
finish the fucking job made finish the fucking finish the job aragon he finished the job thank
god what a legend sorry i flew off the handle there you did you finished the job it's these
elf it's the elves that just stand around and look at stuff and swing and fucking miss over
and over again what do you mean ignore entire left side it actually seems like it's working out
imagine ignoring the entire left side and that's what you had to do imagine there's there's so many
ladders why don't we uh here's an idea guys why don't you dump gasoline where they're putting
the ladders down and drop a match um why not you just start dropping the anvils over the edge
go wire up a few pianos and drop them over the edge okay here we go here we go
just sit there and drop anvil just have a guy being a huh huh guys
um
i got hit by a boulder then i got hit right the fucking head by a boulder
stick to the plan that's i can't even stick to the plan there's too many there's too many
curvy um so they shoot boulders bar goes immediately to red game over there is the
horse and the rider i got two there are enough for the top youtube search i just watched this
what does this say so the top youtube search i just watched for this mission is from 2015
doing basically the same thing you're doing by focusing the ladders they don't get swarmed
nearly as much as you so i i have as you have so i hate to say that i think you're just getting
unlucky no i'm not getting unlucky all right only ladders okay every time i swing the axe i give
10 community subs he's faking his own hype train move out of the fucking way that was a good start
too but it was ruined by the standing people they were trying to get in my way it's like they're
trying to get in my way it's yeah we're playing football now get out of my way get out of my way
i didn't swing no swinging i did this game when i was nine lies lies lies surrounded by lies
surrounded by them i wonder if jerma still likes the lord of the rings after this
that's pretty good series uh all right come on two on the right
don't i hosted that's what i was waiting for this shit i don't care i don't care i don't care i have
to kill this guy good i had to kill that guy i really did that's not a swing that's a push
that was a push not a swing that was a push don't twist it oh no no no no no no
no no the yellow bar no no
fucking ice these motherfuckers come on ice them ice of aragon this body's in the way aragon
ice these motherfuckers please ice these motherfuckers wasn't there a part three that's
supposed to happen here like right now wasn't there supposed to be a part three that happens
right now why is this taking so long okay here we go only ladders just knock down the ladders
here we go it's gonna instantly turn red i'm trying to push the ladder you fucking dick
just push it down man i got stun locked i got stun locked i am about to oh my god i got
stun locked by this fucking motherfucker right next to me oh my god it's this is the worst
look at how many people are up here there's no way i'm gonna be doing this there's no way i can't
even do that is anybody gonna kill somebody up here so it came back and i got stun locked by the
way is is there in the most celebrated franchise in human history is there a reason why catapults
launch and then the bar fills to red in eight seconds how did actual gimli do this this is
based on history god i wonder how did how did they do this back thousand years ago
guys i don't know i'm supposed to stick to the plan but let's be completely honest i'm not sure
that plans i'm not sure it's a sound plan anymore that's the furthest we've made it we make it to
there every time and then everybody just there's a thousand people on the screen try the left instead
where is the horse should have just built up aerodrome i shouldn't have to do that
i'm just here for the free sub well what is it at 30 this area okay this area needed
this area needs is is over tweaked it needs to be under tweaked there is this is this is over tweaked
it needs to be under tweaked how is the right left side been doing that poorly i have enough
time to get left at least the first one that's in one why it's like every time there's a cut
scene the game continues to load the enemies that's what's happening whenever we whenever we see a
cut scene it's still loading ladders and people in here but the ladders don't matter it's the
amount of orcs on the wall yeah but if there's ladders up i can't kill them uh you get a
completely overrun what's supposed to happen is player a runs around and hits ladders and stays
on the left side and player b runs around on the right side and hits ladders and kills enemies on
the right side my player b is standing over here swinging at the same two orcs i don't even have
another controller to plug in i fucked it up i fucked it up no sorry salvageable that spawn
right next to me on the right salvaged everything right at the middle left side right side here it
comes ready one two one two one two one two come on oh my god it's just a game it's just a football
game it really is they just they just it's three or four of them on the screen at the same time
and they take up almost all of the real estate on screen the left side if you have time i'm not
sure i ever will first time i've fallen because that guy backed up look see he's doing a great
job walking around maybe collapsed on he's toxic to teammates well tell them to push a ladder down
even if they did it once if one of these ai pushed one ladder to the ground one
i'd probably be why is this this there's so many people up here right now but i'm not i don't
understand why only two ladders are up fuck that's that doesn't count that was a recovery
god damn it i just got so screwed the less the left side i can't as the left side of all
is left side done as the left the left side might be fucking toast push the ladder oh my god
block that's block that was a block you guys i think seriously seriously there's so many
people on the screen that you can't even walk to the ladder these are blocks these are blocks
i'm gonna watch is there a speedrun of this anyone played this fucking game
to a to a point where they want to speed run this painful shit two towers helms deep speed run
how the fuck does anyone reliably do this um let's see i want to see this skip to helms deep
what the hell do they even do it's okay if it's too hard jermal i just want to see i guarantee you
who wants to make some bets here i'll make a bet with you this is a speed run of this game
in 47 minutes i guarantee you i will gift another 10 subs if during this this guy doesn't go
stupid fucking part of the game you ready no i this is all wrong oh that's why it's doing that
okay all right makes sense okay
there are enough for us both ghibli
right look at it right now he's going the fuck out of the way he's there's no mic
he goes left too guys he goes left he doesn't he goes left he has not swung the sword once
so far he just i feel like i'm doing this faster than this doing it in order
wait in order of what do you mean in order is he fasting is is he faster running animation don't
even tell me that's what it is no it's not wait ghibli has a slower running it's ghibli is actually
a slower character no no way i don't believe that for a second 100 you ignore the left two
ladders i feel like i'm doing i'm doing it the same way i'm doing it the same way no he's not
ignoring the other ladder this is like the world record holder he's taking out the two left but
that's legolas no it's not legolas doesn't have a two-handed sword he's doing it in a pre-determined
order so should i just be doing it as they pop up all right so let's see the right just popped
up right there does he run all the way across to the right side he does he's doing them in the order
that they're popping up is it yeah he he's skipped that other one that all right no see what he did
see what just happened there he's doing it in the order they pop up not in the order that they're
in the way he's doing it no he's not he's just doing the closest one he's not the middle was
up for ages he's just knocking them down as they pop up i swear to god if it's because ghibli is
like seven percent slower i'm gonna be real angry he upgraded the character ghibli's upgraded too
about that there's no speed upgrade there are two ladders near each other he goes there instead
of wasting time going all the way down the middle so he's genuinely doing them as they pop up
all right i'm gonna i'm going aragon i'm gonna try it let's go i think i got it
i think i got it i'm going aragon boys and girls you ready let's go let's say check the
description on the video there's no fucking way this person's watching the stream where is the
horse and the rider where is the horn that is blowing i got two there are enough for us both
ghibli he's way faster he's way faster than ghibli it's not even a fucking contest you gotta be
kidding me did i seriously waste all that fucking time because i was playing as the character that
was a little bit slower than everybody else no way i is this just is this like a placebo effect
i feel like it's like five times as many people on the screen am i getting placebo
um this this just feels just different like this just feels different to me i don't know what drugs
i'm on but this is different you know what i'm saying let's ignore the left side i think he is
he is right i'm not going crazy right thanks for getting in my way everybody um come on i need some
spawns that was incredibly inefficient it's okay i'm at zero bar i swear to god get the fuck out
of my way you punk one guy spinning around in goddamn circles you might you're not really
gonna let this fucking happen are you get out of the way how did that not hit how did that not hit
and i'm blocking i'm not swinging i'm blocking i don't want to i'm level two is aragon guys i
can't take like two hits fucking god there's only three ladders up how the fuck did this many people
out right now oh god i'm gonna fucking puke i really am so many people over here i'm gonna
get hit and die blocking is not running when you parry it doesn't do anything it's you don't even
get a second of like hip recovery you just don't take damage it doesn't do anything else
i'm fucked i had to do it i'm getting a fucking run the same shit keeps fucking happening to me
right side right side right right right right right right right come on aragon go
here we go all right all right now don't fuck this up damn it there's so many people i'm telling you
during the fucking cutscenes it continues i'm stuck in the corner jesus christ give me the help
please don't you even fucking dare i'm being you're all body blocking right now and it's driving me
mad what just what the fuck just happened what just happened i insta died i instantly fucking
died what the fuck just happened i was trying to dodge and not get and and excuse that's the
first time that's ever happened that's the first time that's ever fucking happened i got instantly
killed by what was it what did i die it shot a fireball at you i should have five but wasn't
i standing behind them i got catapulted i it was because i was alongside the wall i did better
that time with aragon do i really have to go back and play all these fucking levels again with this
dude i don't why is this nine straight minutes i honestly don't believe you can try change this
i guarantee you won't beat helms deep part one he bought the game for this no i didn't
one of the best ps2 games yeah i why don't you attack because it's an inefficient use of time
for some reason and i don't know why attacking any any orc on this cliff is an inefficient use
of any of even one second of your time we just watched the world record speed run but the dude
just runs around in circles 10 more minutes till the next height the speed runner attacked and i
also i we're going left we're going right side i got i just got hit directly in the head with one
of those and it didn't kill me it was because i got hit with a giant catapult in the fucking head
i think i may have unlocked the ultimate strategy no i didn't never mind it's too sloppy to be able
to do that no that's not gonna work this tube there's too much body collision to even attempt
to attack a person up here i was gonna okay one of this one spawned over here so i was like you
know what fucking i'm going this way that's stuck stuck stuck awesome it didn't even it got the one
time that the motherfucker doesn't swing for three straight seconds that always just spinning in a
circle randomly flailing around trying to hit anything and that one time am i gonna get hit
by more of this shit am i gonna it's been eight hours how am i screaming i've been serving eight
hours holy shit i thought it was like four i'm gonna die i can't like i'm fucking dead i'm dead
wish i could see the right side of the screen right now you know what a fucking miracle god
saw me god did that for me god don't care there's only one way this is possible we have to get
fire has to rain down here right now you can't physically even fucking walk
no speed run done over miracle is there gonna be a miracle nope why is it this complicated
why does it why did it have to be this ridiculous
fuck man i don't even like i can't even comprehend it helms deep is hard game gotta be hard i don't
even so all right this last time i'm doing it i'm gonna go shovel pizza in my fucking nose
you have to grind i can't even play the other levels with another character
i was gonna go back and play care i was gonna go back and play the other levels with gimli i
can't even do him him is forever at level five is it all just spawn at the same time too did i try
yeah it's grayed out you can't click it hair going i'm already kind of lose
is
the old germa wouldn't give up i didn't give up yet i'm gonna beat it right now i'm beating this right
now no questions asked get the fuck out what are you doing what are you thinking why do they do
just stand still thanks for the help you two nice work not not what is this fucking fourth grade
jeremy get out of the fucking way not no no no no no no no this way it's just brainless
fucking brainless brainless there's just brainless weights that stand in the way
i'm telling you i'm doing it right now come here come here get here middle middle middle spawn
middle middle middle nothing good spawn good good placement good spawn that guy should have
fell off like no jokes that guy shouldn't have been out here he's a little tweaking i think
spawn right on top of me right on top of spawn spawn spawn spawn right here that's okay sorry
it's okay get them all in a row come on like a lesson right in the middle help me help me
somebody help me out here what happened there don't fucking blow it much help for the they're
dropping they're gonna drop the rain on me they're gonna drop the rain on me i need health
yeah get down get out this health right here oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god i need help
what are we at 50 who cares right side right side right side right side right side right side
all right fucking here we go come on don't get hit by this all the way skip i can't skip there's no
skipping run this health right over here no man no there's no fucking way it's impossible it's
physically not completable it's physically not completable this is an in this is an
uncompletable encounter are you kidding me look what happened it was everything was fine
what stage three happens and then
is this even beatable do i have a broken copy of the game hey what's up joel hey what's up everybody
hey welcome to the stream i'm currently uh beating i have a bootleg broken copy of uh
lord of the rings the two towers i'm at the uncompletable mission um cool watch the phase
three on speedrun i don't want i don't want to do that again i don't i do i don't want to do what
we just did again i would rather rip all my eyebrow hairs out and eat them than do what we just did
one more time i'd rather eat i'd rather eat corn on the cob with the husk still on than do this
level again i can't what do you mean watch the phase three thing this is just so bogus i can't
even what the fuck i'm what okay let's watch the world record speedrun on how to how to complete
helms deep level one i feel bad for all the fucking 13 year olds that played this back in the day
that didn't have a youtube speedrun of the best player in the whole entire world but watch do this
so they could complete their game what does he do phase three phase three come on is the game
drops of meteors okay here's phase three what the fuck dude come on there he goes kicks him down
he's doing the same damn thing he hit that one guy why is he not taking damage all right he's
not taking damage he just got hit by a meteor and like eight swings even when i was on gimli i was
taking more damage here what's he doing can he hear me it's not that far after that either
but anyways thanks joel for the ray welcome everybody i'm currently in a in a little bit
of a pickle i'm trying so hard to do this i'm straight for eight hours trying to do the oh man
man man man man man man just don't get hit by the meteors just don't get hit oh what time is it
it's late it's gone the gray bar underneath his health bar is a second health bar he's looking at
another youtube video no i just like aragon i got but is it really is gimli slower is okay can we
please figure that out without us either no doubt at all is gimli actually slower he is god damn it
why did i pick him like yes he is according to the wiki and it feels slower i have to
oh this level is very quick and it's just a boss and it's like 10 15 000 experience oh by the way
joel if you're watching i'm not sure we're gonna be doing a screen tomorrow wrong screen i got it
because this is going on like eight nine ten hours uh i'm not sure i'll be streaming tomorrow
you can see you can see just give me my experience and do the health upgrades and then just run
fear the lies and god only germa stopped after the first game to defuse bombs
all right and there's also a certain threshold where i'm completely out of gas too
i may have already hit that yeah i think it may have i think i hit there already
he's level two i can't do this at level two insult to injury he comes and shoots the
fucking arrow at my dead body he's actually angry not really i'm just disappointed i don't
think anger is correct i think i'm i think i'm just genuinely genuinely disappointed
i'm genuinely make them he's sad i really thought i was gonna do it on that last one
i'm just so disappointed about it did somebody think this game actually isn't even two player
why did that not kill you the third hit didn't even land i can't even hurt these fucking guys
yeah aim at that guy that's what i wanted you to do punished for choosing joke character gimme
he's not even bad in the game he's just slow don't even give me my 10 000 experience why does it have
to keep hitting me i'm trying to run around i can't even what am i even gonna tell you know
look at that i'm not even hurting him stream for your bathtub again yeah kill that one
just never ending stun log
fuck you guy fuck off get out of here i'm i i i i i i'll see you guys later
see you later first tried the final boss of normal heroes but can't kill these dudes
this game's 20 years old and might not be tuned to the best way that 2020 games could be tuned
kill that one i'm dead
another child's game jeremy can't beat you don't understand i know that you're fucking with me and
that's fine but this game is rough this game is rough i know i know you're trying to get the guy
to be like fuck you idiot fucking stupid you chat member i don't even like you you're an asshole
no i know you i know this game's rough he used to like lord of the rings well the rings i'm
never reading the book i'm never reading the book yeah i'm not ever gonna read the lord of the rings
book not that i planned on it dude so i love you jeremy i'm so sorry this had to happen
i i like i didn't like i'm gonna be fine i didn't like break my leg
i don't blow it here i need these points dude i'm so sorry that you like fell out your window and
like broke both your legs that's the equivalent of how i feel apparently right now playing lord
of the rings with two towers so please drop a health pack drop it don't yeah yeah yeah yeah
derma so sorry your gamer license has been revoked you can't take that from me you can't
take that away from me no no you can't take that from me you can't take that from me
i'm sorry jeremy but we have to no you can't take that from me
is it the start of the movie where i become the bad guy or something where i gotta lose everything
i'm sorry it's on the list and we have to take it no no no no you don't need to understand what
i've done i built this up from nothing okay don't fuck around because i'm gonna die by the magnet
enemies no health you can't be fucking serious come here come here come here come here come here
come here come here come here come here nice dance you baited me oh my fuck i can't lose this
if i lose this i have to turn the stream off i have to i have to look at that like this how do
you dodge this you just don't you just don't you just don't it's impossible you can't block
any rams india you can start biting the controller i'm gonna bite into the controller try the wall
with the dwarf no they they made him 15 slower to keep to keep the moviegoers happy instead of
have a consistent three character game you should return to this yeah we'll return to the king
not to the two towers i i would rather i'd rather go to the barbershop after a long day of customers
take a broom and fucking sweep up all the hair on the ground and bake it into a large vanilla cake
and eat it let's see if i can block it you can't block it prove it fine dude i'll prove it that's
literally a filthy frank video is it really
what does that actually happen literally when he goes he gets a bunch of hair from the barber
does that actually happen watch he's running me over what wait there's no damage i'm gonna
fucking start bolting spits everywhere it's everywhere kill that one fuck off jeremy are
you winning it depends what you mean by that sentence literally no fundamentally no
theoretically no metaphysically no kill that one hypothetically yes are you winning son
chemically no drugs drug-free we got a lot of rates today i don't want to say thank you everybody
you have to attack him you can't attack him trust me i beat this like four and a half hours ago
they got you can't attack him until his dog goes in there this game is chilly times this game is
like chilly time level of difficult i you know i think i'm i think i'm holding it together pretty
well considering how hard i think this is i think i'm holding together pretty well i think i'm doing
all right i think metaphysically it could be better theoretically could be doing better but
hypothetically i'm doing just fine i mean my pants are just just wet i must have pissed my pants like
probably an hour and a half ago i don't know i don't remember doing that i must have i mean
i'm my pants are theoretically wet hypothetically wet pants just go in the air so i can get my 10,000
points what do i upgrade though health kill that one why have none of you dropped health
that's what i want to know upgrade your brain a mod a founder and a subscript of subscriber
you're the number one person i can rely on for complete support really
you're supposed to help me a trader i think we got a traitor amongst us so close so close
derma are you doing the dodge button now kill that one okay hold on no more looking at chat
the people that are that are that are not that are not my supporters
just want to see me fail i i look over here in this chat and when i i look over and i have
i i don't see go for it you're the man you can do this you're doing so good oh this game looks
really hard no you know what i mean no no no they're traders all the people were defended
okay let's get some points here 12 000 all right aragorn can we please what just happened he
hasn't gotten a single perfect all game that's not true how do you get a perfect there you just
don't you can't there's no perfect there you got to stand around in a circle surrounded by enemies
at every front behind me in front of me to the left me right of me enemies everywhere
derma you should read the controls
all right i got the health upgrade there's one there's one more health upgrade
i am going to actually do this one i'm gonna try to get some perfect i'm gonna try to really get
some quality shit on what's the one with you have to kill 100 people forest no it's this one right
here all right let's go i can't believe you've been doing this all night you've out streamed
even you out streamed me sometimes you got to lock in and hate play something it's his
favorite ps2 game well that comment came at a really bad time who carries the fate of us all
we must defend it this actually is so good for ps2 it's just it's just a little on the extreme
side all right let's go let me get some good combos what's the new move i have what's the new
move derma you should look at the controls didn't i did wasn't it no i didn't get a new
move i didn't get a new move right because i did the health nice perfect
i get a perfect by having combos aragon doesn't have any combos i did the health upgrade first
it's so hard you have no idea when you when you parry you don't gain anything from parrying
it just stops one attack and then it says okay i'm attacking you again it doesn't do anything you
know it doesn't it's not like a no it's just it's my new ringtone i gotta make it to the bridge
let's go oh my god it was the horn of god was it you know you go to the arcade and you feel like
the games there are are tuned to a way to take all the fucking quarters out of your pocket i feel
like i this game wants me to put like 200 dollars in quarters into it was this in the arcades first
i walked in the fuck hold on let me let me reach into my pocket and grab my my tokens continue
come on part told her germa's gonna give up an hour ago we must defend well it's too late now
it's too late now to give up you know i'm turning into dust waiting for
to wake up tomorrow with an email from fucking like warner brothers we regret to inform me that
we have dmca'd your twitch stream please deposit 1600 dollars in quarters into the machine
at once just cheat why would i cheat at this point there are no cheats what do you mean just
cheat yeah you know what this is bullshit because the three other slots at the arcade game with
three other players are supposed to be are empty and i decided to do it alone
i'm playing the x-men game with an empty booth you all know how that goes there's no co-op in
this one don't say that don't steal my thunder don't steal my thunder come on um how many times
do i have to shoot you with an arrow name it i got a great video name for this video nightmare on
helms deep what would be nightmare on helms deep street because i did make that reference
i did make that reference about it being yeah that's a pretty good one you don't also be a
pretty good one if i could beat this fucking goddamn game thanks for the help guy i need that
experience giving me freddo's almost dead i have to run over there we have to go now to the bridge
they must not surround let go lord of the rings i'm never gonna kill all these guys over here die
let this motherfucker die anyways why do we even have to save this guy he's already
dies we could have just watched two lord of the rings movies by now
in his honor you shall pay you're gonna play this longer than the actual lord of the rings movie
trilogy don't say that what is the actual lord of the rings trilogy how what's the what's the
mac what's the full length 10 and a half hours 12 to 12 hours 10 and a half hours don't say that
i don't think that's gonna happen there's the cctv footage again okay i seriously he's pushing me
around the screen so fast i fucking can't see anything i need help this feels rotten this feels
rotten i'll tell you i need help he's so fast oh my god what a sloppy mess
i feel like i'm watching two bugs fight this is what it looks like when two beetles attack each
other i'm like national geographic don't hit me don't fucking hit me don't hit me
hey having a cranky wanky oh i said i wasn't gonna do that ever again
he's the honor you shall pay he's having a little cranky wanky right now
oh
when they sped the movie up by 300 percent
i love that part i'm gonna run out of sticks i'm gonna run out of stones i'm gonna run out of
stones is there any more stones what happens when you don't have any more stones do combos
they don't hurt him on his honor you shall pay he only he takes damage and then is invincible
for like a whole second that's a fact you want to get another guy over here i spot another guy
there he is yeah why i don't know just because i don't know why not hey boss does that ever happen
again no this is this game's actually making me not care about this scene this is like a really
like bad like sad scene i don't give a shit anymore we've seen it like five times
son of god okay here we go it's time nice perfect by the way i know i know that that person i i i
thought i was like hey shut up dude perfect whatever it's hard that person waited until
i didn't get a perfect and then on a regular level to write you know like fucking nice perfect
and they were and i and it was a good one it was actually it was really good it was a fucking got
you it really was but i hope that person is banned from the channel how dare you okay
what is the play here i need a combo i need a single goddamn combo press and hold triangle
swift terror i need a combo and then i think i might wait till i need level four i don't use
this shit powerful enemies will this will this work on shielded people rising attack i feel
like i don't want rising attack i feel like i actually i abuse it you missed that one try
another ladder you're seriously just leveling up air going to kick ladders you really don't need
combos that's a really good point that's flawless that's true that's absolutely what a statement
yeah i don't just level enough and run around and kick stuff i'm gonna save it oh you missed that
one oh you missed that one try a ladder oh you missed that one try a ladder
you missed that one try a ladder one more level with aragon and that should be it take a crack at
the ladder no i need that i need the second health upgrade not i'm not doing the burning building
one again which one should i do the dog again no wasn't easy i'll just do this like easy ass
mission this will be it just cheat don't grind i have to do it legit at this point it's been
almost nine hours guys i can't can't not do this it was here that we would find far more than the
two imagine playing this game for nine hours and like pissing your pants and shitting your pants on
stream and then you get then you cheat no that's not how it works this is so loud i don't know why
that is here's how you get perfect if i can land it the shields this is batman give me a break
if this one guy with a shield and a group of enemies you he fucks the whole thing up
because you just bounce off of it randomly let's go hey bro did you get a perfect yet
hey bro hey yo bro did you get a perfect all right don't lose fuck the perfect just stay alive i have
no health drops this whole time okay let's do it here comes fucking fraud don't fuck this up
jesus god damn it man i did he blended him with the whole background did he just say i'm not even
kidding easy don't you honest to fucking god man do you really have to fucking fly in here like a
hero too and then hide hide here comes another fucking hero come on running out of fucking things
to hide behind here oh my fucking god no what happens if you run out of arrows oh god i have
30 all right give me the fucking purpose i'd like 50 perfects this round come on that's like three
upgrades let's go 25 000 points come on four increases your health permanently done fired
like a dune dane bow the barbed arrows do serious damage so this is level six increases the damage
of your speed attack increases more devastating attack fork vein is op
oh i know i'm double six maybe i should do the bow all right okay i think it's time to attempt
what do you say ready to knock this out of the fucking park let's go
both give me cool bow you fucking idiots put the ladder back in the host already getting
overrun speaking of being overrun nice shot guys uh we could use some of like the 10 of you that
are over there over on the right side you know not all of you just stuff in the same one pixel
like can three of you go to the other side i'm going no i'm going all right the middle
left and right side middle gonna spawn right now check it oh my brain is just so big
it's so huge it's like it hurts i feel it pulsating and it like it hurts i mean it's
full of baked beans but it's big where it's zero keep it up keep it up i don't want to do this shit
no more left and right side check it check it here it comes right side one two three that was a hang
up no no one two three get this guy with me get this guy with me behind me one two three good blocks
good blocks and now i'll get out of my way before i kill you how can they be naked nobody left
like a list there's a body in the way you can't be fucking serious you cheap motherfucker it's
all an opportunity you had to take it there's like a pixel here that you get stuck on it's such it's
such dog shit there's one little pixel that you can get stuck on god smooth it out with the
fucking paint tool god damn it man oh come on i have to do this i have to change the route
what is with this magnet jump like fuck i need help is it helping that oh fuck here we go here
we go all right i have to be careful don't get hit by a fucking magnum where's the help in the
box i got the help already didn't i didn't i get it it's up there help let's go start it from one
but this guy's glued to me like a fucking glue he's glued to me like
watch out don't get hit by that gandalf save me gandalf come on gandalf get in here
gandalf gandalf gandalf gandalf gandalf show yourself gandalf gandalf do something
gandalf please do something gandalf gandalf oh my god that was horrible that was terrible
that was horrible i wanted i wanted fucking him you didn't do shit legless you didn't do
shit i did it on my own i did that by myself i just beat all of the the knights uh the knights
of the republic whatever i don't know knights of ren i don't know what they what are they called
the mist the mischiefs of gondor the orcs of of sar what is it called what are they actually called
the uruk-hai but what are they what's the army called the bad guys who cares all right i think
i'm gonna save my points oh by the way that's i that's also not the hardest mission in the
game apparently uh the neck the next one is good luck uh joel if you're watching right now we're
gonna have to reschedule because i i'm taking a break tomorrow i'll be back in a couple days
after this one we have two levels left breached wall anybody have one of those poland springs
things in their house do you love them or is it pain in the ass germa lied about playing with joel
no i didn't i lied about playing with joel this weekend but next weekend no but we know what to
do for next weekend what are you up to hold on hey we about hey me and joel there weren't any
communication about this we were like yeah everyone will do it next weekend and then we know but we
didn't talk to each other we didn't i didn't reach out to him he didn't reach out to me he reached out
like in the middle of stream we're like all right well he's he's like we'll do it another time
whatever all right what if i go just defend i think it is defend oh no arrows left oh oh
uh oh where are the arrows uh oh uh oh oh it's gonna be toasty in here in a few minutes
you have arrows give them to me are they walking past me got my hand okay what's next walk out i see
health over there what's the health for is there another spot i need to go to that's the door
i got perfect coming up perfect coming up too perfect nice i'm just standing right here
this is just defend germa you idiot they've gotten to the gate don't call me an idiot
hey go what was it go you're gonna wash your mouth out with soap it's really fucked up by the way
that's like dangerous and shit people do that oh this is where we get overwhelmed
explode does that affect the gate it does all right get up there get away from the
fucking door perfect come on i have a perfect meter what is even hitting me you fuckers just
this is i can't even see them coming down the screen i gotta get up closer god look at how many
bombs there are coming jesus man jesus i might as well just let him blow up next to the door
it's gonna be less damage probably than if they you know i'm saying it's probably less damage
just blow them up at the door that's probably the strat oh fuck just blow up blow up bro come on
bro are you fucking me are you fucking me here really you can't even fight this many people
you actually can't i think you kind of can't i need arrows arrows arrows arrows oh oh my god
do i win oh oh what is that holy shit guys oh that's a pog moment right there i just
poked my pants i seriously did that was piss easy come on give me something i didn't know you were
here i'm gonna get fucking am i actually gonna get stun locked right now you piece of fucking dog
shit oh my god what a joke what a fucking joke it's health right in front of me and where are
those coming from i don't know what i'm looking at here there's a troll there's a troll there's a
troll coming to the door ever going technique y'all know it this is not it oh what the fuck am i doing
now you gotta be shitting me there's got to be somebody here that's coming up to fight this too
there's like 60 people on the screen it has to be a cut scene kill him he's dead what do i have to do
i have to go kill the fucking machine the machine get over on the side i gotta hit the other side
in the front one more oh he parked his shirt off
oh
i took every ounce of my energy why is the flow i actually thought the flow was wet and it was just
that's i'm not even gonna tell you
piss my chest no it's it's the cold ground of the thing that i have to protect the carpet
i have a thing to roll on to protect the carpet and um i just put my feet on it
all right 26 000 what should i do here this is the final level guys strength i okay i need how
much how close am i what do i need i definitely master swordsman absolutely um i don't care about
this all right i need 10 20 so i need 20 000 and then 30 000 36 000 all right so i need like
36 000 points i don't think i really want any of these this just takes too long hope you're ready
for the nearly impossible level not yet i'm gonna get a drink of water i'll go back and farm
something because i'm almost level six and i need like 20 yeah i need at least 20 000
i could get one of these though or maybe i shouldn't no i can it's too slow goblin bane
so i'll hold it yeah i'll hold it okay i'm gonna grab some water have it back and we're going for
the last level soon he beat yeah i beat the ladder level it deleted 16 million of my brain cells
but i did it what have i not done with aragorn okay i haven't done this one okay it's a mora
all right i'm gonna grab water i'll be right back see you for the remainder of the first
10 hour stream of 2020 see in a minute all righty howdy all right let's do this one
try to get aragorn to level six give it a try this is a relaxing mission i don't have to do
very much i just have to just sit here we shall wait here until the path beyond appears safe
we have had no word from moria ah it's a break we get our break oh yeah it feels pretty great
actually this is this is fucking nothing this is like fucking easy man oh it feels pretty sweet
oh all right i gotta like at least i gotta i have to get at least some good points here
because i need them i need to level up what was those six perfect come on somebody somebody
somebody somebody quick quick oh hurry up i need these perfects excuse me bounce behind him
what am i even shooting at right now all right dude i don't want to beat around the bush here
but what are you gonna up everyone wants to know what are you gonna do another grandpa video
hello everybody welcome to grandpa plays lord of the rings the two fucking towers
and this game came out in 2001 which is pretty much when i was i was like 40
don't play it here with the arrogant and his little buddy i think his name is i don't know
so as you can see i'm using the scar l pretty good oh we've gone full tuber back to the tuber roots
hurry up you're not dead i'll take a perfect from you and that's level six we get our new
oh perfect again let's go train it together chain it together train it together okay you can always
tell when somebody that's a streamer or youtuber doesn't know what to say next when they just go
okay i can't let like 15 seconds go by without saying something okay all right so
come on hurry up spawn on me you're gonna go go go go come on i'd like to get out of the sludge
please better combo system than skyrim i almost had perfect there shit i had it this idiot behind
me it wasn't dead gimli didn't even hit him once don't worry let me just put on this giant backpack
full of fucking anvils oh wait i'm sorry what's that is that gimli behind me i'm trying to just
cue up a big move here there it is is it i don't even know what's going on okay what was he the
guy that's off screen great all right fucking tone down tone down the sass here jeremy let's
relax tone down the everything that happens is not my fault i don't make any mistakes nothing is
my fault it's the game's fault everything like can we tone that down i'm crossing that path
like i just crossed it but i really though like this is not my fault what you just saw right
there was had nothing to do with me everyone does that i know everybody does it's like it's
like such a bad trait of gamers we all do it everybody does it doesn't matter who you are
oh no that's like fucking stupid that's stupid what just happened no that like what
what what okay sure what that wouldn't happen to me that doesn't happen to me okay sure
i mean i pressed x and it didn't do anything like that's not me something something's wrong
with the game i have i have a bootleg copy of the broken game my game copy must be bootlegged
dude why the fuck would they put it in here like this all right speaking friend
somebody to recharge me i just drank two full cups of water all right i got 34 000 points level
six let's get those upgrades you did that 15 minutes ago yeah that's that's what i was going
for all right increase the damage of my speed attack yes and increases your health permanently
yes instantly kill an attacking orc that sounds pretty good actually but what about i'm level
seven level eight i need ten thousand for the health and then six thousand for the bow
i'm gonna i'm gonna hold on to it i mean that's pretty that's pretty good there's only one more
level i can even do right how many how much how close am i to level eight hold on let me
save this here because i need to get to level eight with aragon before we do the final and
impossible level do you i dose i don't know what is this i mean i know i dose like dose
i doser is an application for the playback of proprietary audio content
did you just make this word up uh i'll do i'll do the forest we support you even if you i dose
you guys are up late 11 30 2 30 a.m eastern still a lot of people here there are a shit
lot of people still here thanks for staying up guys but the trail ends here we should be done
shortly split up to find them quickly okay you little shit i've been supporting you this whole
time where am i come on i had it it's always an asshole with a shield that fucks the whole thing
up and now i get perfect i'm sad i'm not even mad i'm just disappointed all right okay well that
doesn't make any sense like the only enemy in the game that i can't hit with a what in the name of
fucking god is going on right now the guy's bodying me yes he is and it's embarrassing
you got the late night debuff no you know what really does happen to me is i don't get the
late night debuff i get i get the late night power i increase in power the the more i go like
off like the handle he's a vampire who what's the pokemon that like when he gets when he rages he
gets more powerful like the more upset this pokemon gets the better he is and the more you
you want to put him in your party is there like a superhero that does that is it like a character
superhero pokemon that get when he gets upset and over the edge that's when he actually is worthy
using the hulk yeah the hulk that's what i'm thinking of that's like actually who i'm saying
is i'm actually thinking of the hulk that's so stupid who's that guy that when he gets really mad
he does he gets like stronger he's big and he's green you guys know who i'm talking about perfect
time oscar the grouch shaggy shaggy doesn't get angry when was the last time you saw shaggy and
scooby-doo getting mad like that's really out of character for him shaggy definitely be level
eight excellent excellent excellent you don't remember that one scene where shaggy snapped
screamed at somebody troll this is the double troll level isn't it remember how mad i got at
this remember i was sitting here going dude how are you supposed to beat this how is this even
possible man you do it with the airborne technique his chest in here oh it's experience
friendship friendship again this jumpscare too bad you do dumb to pull it off
double ko mortal combat style this game is hard you're doing good it is pretty hard the game is
pretty hard everyone told me that it's not that hard you're you're playing a game that i beat
when i was eight but they're misremembering they played it on easy not today not tomorrow
not next week not even probably next year but eventually they're going to open up their
playstation 2 and i'm going to go to their old memory card and they're going to see their save
file for lord of the rings the two towers and they're going to go oh right here it is remember
this old fucking dopey game and they're going to open it and it's going to be a completed game
with a continue on easy and i'm going to get like 600 letters in the mail apologizing to me
come mailed it to him right now here we go make it look easy come on jeremy make it look easy
make it look easy jerma let's go there's something i don't know what do you
somebody just says true you know what i'm doing you know what it sounds like
can i get to level nine cad what oh well what cad why are you astroturfing the stream right now
this is real hey man i'm being supportive yeah but you uh i looked over you said like some nice
things and you told me it was just a fuck off or something all right let's get increased permanent
health level eight super bow or should i do the instantly kill and attacking uruk-hai square x
square xr2 square x i can instantly kill any urk-hai instantly kill any orc that's definitely what i
should do i can instantly kill any enemy in the game they can do it orcs what does linked move
mean i have to block so it's block xr2 i have to test that out i need 40 goddamn points so it's a
counter um we don't even need it let's go what is the combined length of all the lord of the rings
the three films in total are 11 hours and 23 minutes the stream is about 10 hours long let's
try it this is hornberg courtyard this is the one that's a lot of boring shit oh those games
the those movies those movies are legendary i don't agree with you i don't agree with you
all right here we go and we what is with this camera another cctv
oh wait holy shit jerry and what started as a small confrontation has turned into
an absolute bloodbath brawl outside of the 7-eleven we have no idea where we have started i think
somebody called the small one there short and spit in his face it looks like they're upset that
mcdonald's
we're not even into roger i'm not even entirely sure what they got these weapons
that's not the mcdonald's
like a left arm hurts okay we're good look at these perfects i'm gonna get where am i
shoot roger what started it was a simple altercation
people have started to actually pick sides in this fight the battle the battle for the battle
for home depot roger people are people on social media are calling this the battle of home depot
this reporter cannot understand just how ridiculous this is seeing this from above above
you don't see the other 300 people that are back behind the doors
holy shit legolas is dead this is a mess this is a fucking mess this is just seriously
where even is legolas where is he where is legolas where is legolas where is legolas
is he up top what do you mean the stairs guys i don't got the best angle right now
up the stairs he's fucking dead can we fly a little bit closer tom helicopter sound effects
no somebody will put it on somebody will do it somebody will edit it together
somebody will do it somebody i can't pump it through no you do the joke lazy no i'm saying i
i can't pump it through this because i'm going through my xlr thing hold on i'll take care of
this okay i'll even help you out here okay so all right so yeah roger i'm up here in the channel
five news chapter and we're getting word that there seems to be some type of altercation going
on outside of the mcdonald's not entirely sure exactly why this is starting but i'm getting
sources in my ear right now that apparently somebody threw mcchicken out the window
and hit some lady in the face and apparently started this massive altercation out here
they've started picking sides and actually i like if you can see there's there's two people down
there who have who have swords and i'm not i don't know where they got these swords
in fact i'm not entirely sure where where all these where all these these green men came from
this might be the strangest thing i've ever seen in my damn life roger roger i don't even
apparently there appears to be orcs down here where's the music coming from
roger roger roger i'm sorry about what just happened there i thought it might be a little
comical to play some old old helm steep music from lord of the ring i mean this is not comical
at all this this is people fighting and killing each other around here but again apparently
mcchicken out the window i believe it hit it may have hit it may have hit the the man in the
center of your screen there may have hit his girlfriend in the face we're getting a new
feed here now oh he's good this is oh right into the camera that was that well did you get that
labyrinth did you get a close-up of that i'm just unbelievable roger i i know there's a schedule
i know you want to see yes we will return to shut up and dance
just after this but this is that we this is breaking news here ladies and gentlemen
put live in the corner i have to beat this fucking game save legolas hold on i have to
reconnect elvis put on scrolling text no i i before my gamer liquid is gone
they call me at the battle of home depot they all seem to have weapons a brawl has started out here
it's still black and white by the way this helicopter is really fucking low where do they
even get the costumes why would you be in a costume why would you be in a fucking costume
well you see the opportunity to larp oh shit this is my chance there's a huge fight going on
outside the mcdonald's this is my opportunity i've been saving this for so long where's legolas
come on i saved him the mick war i have to turn this back to normal i have to turn this back to
normal this is abnormal i need to be back to normal i can't even i gotta take the filter off
shields put it back on put it back on put it back on put it back on put it back on
put it back on put it back on for a second put it back on for a second
turning back in here roger it appears that some of these patrons have taken the car doors off of
their cars and i guess they're using them as shields i can't get a closer look here i mean
there are there are 13 there are 14 or 15 cars over here that are missing doors
i hate to i really hate to interrupt again but it looks like he looks like what
looks like he may have looks like he may have coded his weapon in something he's coded his
weapon in something it looks it looks magical roger this is fucked up roger roger this is the most
thing i've ever seen people are dressing up they're coming down here in all kinds of clothes i have
no idea i excuse my language get this off before i lose my mind live beeping i can't i need to win
breaking news
legolas is gonna die again i have to go save legolas before i have to do this a
third time follow this guy follow this guy follow this guy follow that guy follow him follow this
guy follow this guy that seems to be the leader by the way roger why is it 2020 and we still use
black and white cameras no he's dead i'm winning i'm winning it's where i'm we cross 10 hours it's
time to go i'm done i'm done let's go let's go i gotta beat it right now move move move let's go
let's go win win win win the battle for all of middle earth right now come on i got perfect
right here give me a break somebody said i feel like i'm watching a gif i feel like i'm watching
a gif oh it's a mutant oh god
this seems to be an aggressive clicking noise coming from this new the streamer's new dog shit
mic setup yeah well this just in um hold on just getting word here roger it seems that uh streamer
has been streaming for and making videos for almost 10 years and still can't figure out
how to set up a fucking proper compressor on his microphone so every half second you hear
wow is it it's surprising roger you think that somebody that went to
literal film school and has almost 10 years of experience wouldn't get so upset about somebody
throwing a mcchicken at him out a window legolas come on fight through i hate this
fucking 2d 3d i hate this 2 3d 3d 2d 3d get out of my way that guy dropped instantly all
right perfect here we go the legolas is gonna be saved now oh roger it looks like he's dealing
with a potential uh 2d 3d problem who's in trouble gimli derma are you drunk not at all
not even slightly not even not even close can't get through move out of my way
i need those perfects i need those perfects i need those perfects perfect perfect perfect
i need those perfects if you're not drunk then turn the webcam on let's see what you have in
front of your drink i don't have to do that um why did i go right in the middle of the mosh pit
you don't ever do that i'm gonna die where is going on they i can't even swing they all have a
shield and then you can't even swing a normal swing this seriously is fucking crazy there's
nothing to even look at uh what is going archers on the wall but what about the fucking hundred
people down here smashing into the wall what you gotta be kidding me legolas do anything do
do anything do anything anything anything anything do anything
do anything the gates the gate the gate sorrow the gate sorrow that's hard stuff what am i doing
is that it i'm stuck
perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect
nice good job you've got great artificial intelligence i'm glad we've come to fucking
quantum computing this mission reminds me of when you go into gary's mod and you just spawned like
20 scientists versus like 40 fucking ant lines and you just look and just watch from
100 feet above all right here we go roger seems that they've made it into the store
i'm not sure i'm not sure what they're after all right it's it's block xr2 right are these guys
urakais they i don't have the urakai one though i'm just gonna snipe people why do any other move
i mean i don't have combos but it's it's kind of hard to even see what where what what direction
my weapon is even swinging i could block square you know our xr2 i got the battle of home depot
in front of me get rid of all the shields that didn't kill you all right here we go legolas
coming gates in good shape i thought he had zero health for a second i was about to say
did i get bugged out of all my ex and my bum and my ex and my bum and my bum
just standing in the way you fuck face he's still playing this
yep he ain't ever gonna stop perfect come on i gotta bring this together right now i need this
pretty good pretty good spring i gotta start shooting the boat when i get perfect
watch out for the walls can i get a camera change you bugged ass piece of shit
i just dropped the meteor okay i fucking comment this i think that's it that's it that's it that's
it back down back down back downstairs back to this fucking mess who's even attacking
get in there and fucking hit somebody like this is
do it oh there's my technique quickly what
uh roger it seems that uh the guy playing gmod spawned two antlions
well we can't really see anywhere where i just i have no view of anything actually roger
yeah there's a whole lot of noise uh looks like they're gonna get through the game again
let him do it roger don't let him roger don't change the channel
oh no i think i have to uh i think i have to
whatever they got it we tried sauron wins how do we even know how do we even know sauron's gonna be
that bad right he what if he's what if he's he's a murderer didn't sauron say like let me tell you
something sauron what's the what's the crisply line that he says end up sauron and you sauron is
one of the most disgusting horrible men in the world join me and together we will destroy the
sauron this is s word sit together we will destroy the sith he's in another movie what a
fucking phenomenal actor by the way lock this shit don't work do or do not do there is no try
i have no idea what's going on i don't think 5500 people who know what's going on
hey you ready for the nearly impossible level i guess so but i guess so i'll be honest though
like imagine watching the lord of the rings and aragon drops on his ass this many times you'd be
like this movie sucks look how many times i'm just getting knocked on the ground this is what it looks
like when you fail every qte get it get it get it get it get it i have a perfect you should be dead
i'm coming i'm coming i'm coming i'm coming i'm coming i'm okay but to get back to the uh
thing i just got hit by a bomb archers behind i don't think that happens yet i think i have to
go back down here first can we skip this game please um you're uh you're 10 and a half hours
late so i'm sorry but you're 10 and a half hours late archers we're in two helms deep right now
you're right this shit's going down this used to be a fellowship stream and then it turned into a
beat the entire second game screen how can there be this many people where are the archers thank you
yes you fucking ruined everything
oh just somebody deal with this guy hot hot back to the gate smooth it out in
fucking pain god damn it can even break where's the goddamn blend tool in photoshop you need it
i can't even get these motherfuckers off this gate they're they're like just insects
they're just bugs everywhere you can't get rid of them clear the gate okay pick up the trolls
if these are trolls or do we lose trolls go i have to go triangle triangle triangle triangle
triangle triangle they're gonna break through i don't even know where the fuck i am like how
what in the fucking name of god what this this is unbelievable holy shit i did better than i was
12 get the fuck out of here don't they're just trying to get under your skin i need to do it
on level like this is this is just this is fucking this is ridiculous it's absolutely
fucking ridiculous there's there's no way i'm doing this with another at least two levels
but absolute zero i'm not gonna stop the fucking breach of home depot it's never gonna fucking
happen what level have i not done there going these two the west fold which one of these
these suck you lost the battle home depot all right so imagine me playing i can't really imagine
what is what it's like watching i imagine you have like to put on glasses and lean in and squint
and go oh there yeah there he is somewhere in there like the beef jerky kicked in i have seen
it before but never like this it's okay to lose uh i mean i have many many times tonight many many
times hope is to stand together saruman's forces move strange explosive devices through this town
help us destroy them watch out oh shit this i should be able to do this pretty cleanly with
everyone the camera and quantum computing that should slow them
three shots three you have to you have to beat the game to unlock the cheat menu i don't think
i'll be doing that how is this streamer so bad you can't pull that one that's too easy
that was six hours ago easy it was six hours ago easy come on you gotta give me some 10 and a half
hour material here i gotta unlock the other weapon thing oh that guy has an explosive
am i shooting over people am i about to get real mad this stream is real late yeah you get a double
feature today you got lord of the rings fellowship of the ring for about three hours and then you've
gotten this uh suffering for the last like nine hold them at the gate he did all it costed was one
of your friends all it costed was a friendship with somebody what do you mean we're friends
fucking shield enemies like you just bounced off these motherfuckers man it's always there's
always at least three guys with a shield and you're going to bounce off them it's just it hurts me
on the inside it hurts him or joel joel's fine joel hit me up and said yo
hey we can do this another time how about tomorrow and i was like yeah let's do it tomorrow
hi everybody my name is german985 i thought this stream was going to be four and a half hours long
just hanging out me you know crossing almost 11 hours i thought this was going to be a short one
today we're just going to check out the lord of the rings on playstation 2 yeah what do you know
about that whatever somebody said you're never gonna get past the first part of this
really yes i will germany it's monday morning this ain't even my longest stream everybody don't
worry relax you must like the game i i do all right leveled up level now level nine
i'm just gonna get over i'm not gonna die from an explosion i'm just gonna get over here
let's blow up thank you i had the invincibility frames from being on the ground worked out
perfectly you said simpsons hit and run was a great game too yeah and what's your point
you return of the king i'm going to do return of the king just not immediately those few of
us able to fight march for helms deep there the future of rohan shall live or die the point is
you're a masochist i don't i don't know about that am i it only cost 200 bits for him to spend
10 hours on a game this does all stem from just one person saying that they
all right what do we got here gone to a bow is this is the best bow i can possibly buy
and then i want one of these super moves use against a powerful fall to smash his shield knock
him to the ground and strike him triangle triangle oink triangle this is the one
one and i can't i can't reliably do this shit very effective for dispatching shielded enemies
is wait hold on over this one this is triangle xx triangle sildor and gondor
yeah the bow oh that's bow in the game we're done i can't get this bane to work
i'm too bad i can't do it we're gonna i get the best bow in the game we need it's triangle
triangle we're just gonna smash the fuck out of everybody triangle triangle circle triangle
this is just power power power power power power i do have an oh shit moment where i can get to
level 10 if i need to there's one more level i didn't do it's the one where everyone's burning
in the building the battle for home depot hold on i let me get let me just get this let me get
this done while i'm locked in i'm locked in here i thought that just said unemployed aragon unemployed
legolas unemployed gimli unemployed all right that's rough okay didn't you start the stream
this morning um like two o'clock pacific i've taken i've taken a couple breaks so don't worry
i've taken like two three breaks had a bunch of water i've even i've had my nice big meaty beef
jerky snack let's go i can't it's still hard to tell where i am i think i'm doing it
i'm the guy that wrote the book okay good hokey and sit hokey and chat let's go
playing lord of the rings i see hog wolf hog legolas you're worthless
worthless worthless worthless worthless worthless worthless archer show up immediately
after saving legolas they're not they're not there right now
there's nobody target back there there's nobody back there he yells archers on the wall
anybody get any of that anybody getting any of this can you repeat that
there's no rhyme or reason to anything on the screen i might as well just fucking put the
controller down and just like walk away archers on the walls he didn't even say it
did he say it he's been up there dude this gate is doing so much worse than it was before
keep it up germa you can do it i'll probably do it but it's it's just throwing dice in the air
this entire last level is just whipped 400 dice in the air did you get a 92 do it again
oh try again this fucking archers up on that wall
okay camera man please change the camera let's probably get in there there are we the gates
jeremy the gates i can't even walk forward oh yi yi yi yi yi fuck this fuck this shit man i'm dead
i think i have to just get to level oh my god just get in the middle and do the tornado
that's kind of what i did it didn't really help work your way from the sides i'm gonna get like
rug burn on my arms from my chair well it's hard to not be in the middle when you start in the
middle i thought that was a death sound when it's perfect you just got sniped what is this cluster
fuck somebody said i should come to the stream right now what the fuck is they what are they
doing man i imagine just opening the game imagine opening this and the first thing you see is like
don't you think you immediately click the x or you'd be like holy shit it's like it's like
gdq wrapping up i'm on i'm in perfect is he out of his zone to be able to die
that's supposed to be one hit kill bro use the arrows imperfect yeah i know i know i should be
doing that done all right same deal let's go where i don't where am i standing there's a health over
here i can't see anything give me that full help perfect let's just shoot arrows at me i think
they're showing like this in the face
oh look at us doing a great job keep it up thumbs up wink this game has an average playtime of six
hours for the main story fuck that yeah right liars bullshit you've seen you look at what's
happening on screen right now and you think somebody's gonna beat this in less than five
or six hours that's horseshit what happened was this what happened to that guy all right are
they dead i can't even fucking look five hours fuck off five hours fuck off with that not a
chance in hell he's a gimli main that's why it's like all super powered fucking orcs at the gate
right now do you understand like it's all these super powered motherfuckers five hours by the way
this is like playing dark souls against 60 people at the same fucking time no way you took five
hours to beat this i refuse to understand or believe you i have to get to level 10 or it's
actually impossible how a level 10 fix it i don't know it gets me away from having to see the same
smudged smeared across screen of 100 people swinging and falling down it lets me break it
up a little somebody said back when games were hard back when games were hard just do combos
i'm doing the two or three combos that i have here are my combos here's the other one you've
seen me do that move 500 times the walkthrough for this level starts with oh my sweet loving god
this mission is so hard it makes the previous two missions look easy why is he not let's go blow
you're wasting time gandalf how did you beat this as a kid guys i may have just gotten to like the
second level and gone well this is fun i like lord of rings sorry about your tables all right
will you fucking i've leveled up everything and i can't even kill a standard uruk-hai
with a couple of slashes you just don't have oh man get out of my move move move move move
oh sorry we have to get in the way slaughter this motherfucker i think i'm stuck in the wall
i'm stuck in the wall there we go i found a way out that's what i wanted so i can kill you in one
hit is this hit and run too it might as well be this might be harder than hitting run
where i'm almost of the whole trilogy almost why is there a family photo in the top right
corner because i have to save the people in the building we've peaked too early in the year what
do you mean we peaked too early all right i have to i don't know they're gonna die if i don't do
this right now oh damn it they swing they swing so much faster than i do and the family's dead
where are these family members where are you are you just standing around waiting to die
where even are you did you just let these guys kill you blocking doesn't do anything trust me
trust me when you block it you just it's easy you can block against one guy but when you're
surrounded by 12 people you're gonna get smoked i just dropped my mouse who cares not even level
10 by the way do i get my upgrade screen all right what the hell am i buying but look at how
long this move takes to kill one person one two three four it's almost five full seconds
it's an instant kill but it takes i'm doing i got it there you go i got it how am i going
to pull this off in the sea of fucking humans don't you guys remember the hobbit sneaking game
what happened to that so i can instant kill in uruk-hai and instant kill any orc in the whole
game i have to block press x and then r2 it should kill instantly kill every single work in the whole
game that's i'll try i probably should have picked another level to practice it we didn't
yell fake rumbo's name fake rumbo okay so block and then x r2 okay you just you see how long this
is gonna take to do this to every single one of these guys one by one glad i picked it
no it's a waste of time i'm gonna do what i was doing before
he's hitting with the backswing now that's just annoying i'm damaging the gate with my moves
what no i'm not no way just run why are you still alive move move dermal is going to defend
helmsley for five full days you know it would be nice uh the kingdom of men dwarves and elves
if you sent more than three people that'd be great oh we're being attacked we're being overrun by orcs
it's okay we have three people oh what how many how many how many were there
sorry sorry kandalf we were there 600 million fucking orcs oh yeah don't worry we'll just have
three people to do this hey they did it in 300 i'd like 300 somewhere and while i try to block
no one attacks did you see that did you see that one i'm sitting there like spamming the
block button and everybody stands still arches on the wall you got it gimli coming right up i'll
take care of that just let me follow this real quick over here jesus christ doing better than
last time though by the way i'm breaking the disc in half when i'm done
oh by the way the second i get to the the last minute of the cutscene i'm gonna break the disc
in half with my teeth every single motherfucker has a fucking shield oh slow down jeremy i can't
even do a combo in here this is did anyone beat this did anyone beat this and i mean literally
one person one person on earth you can't block that you can't do anything they try i do i have
to stand oh my god hey just watch the speed run to figure out how to play the game normally
we cannot hold sounds about right you thought jump king was hard
all these fucking like dragged out 12 minute sequences and same thing over and over again
i don't feel like aragon right now i feel like i'm in the dryer
crazy bill fuck that move again it's like a lantern in the way
instant kill pauses ai but it doesn't pause people hitting the shelf with their swords
i'll come and get you i'm coming with my little sword this cost is 300
dollars at galaxy's edge and you can't even play with it because it's made out of glass
stab stab stabbing head stabbing head okay go use the insta kill use the insta kill it'll save you
no i'm going here we go it's these urakais you gotta get over here before they get in
all right just figured out where i was i have no idea i'm truly gone at this point
i'm like getting perfect somehow let's go god are you fucker you motherfucker he's still chasing
me no that's just useless legolas he's still chasing me it's scratch that you know i'd like
if they send more three characters i'd like it if they send more than one me that's it is there
anymore i think that's it that's it that's it that's it let's go it's the same guy with
shields still following me no one will kill him same fucking thing happens super powered
fucking mutants look at the there's like 10 of these guys they're like unstoppable it's the
hardest enemy in the game and they're like just lining up they're super mutants if only i had an
instant kill it's so oh just do the instant kill i can't even tell what's happening on the screen
it's this one fucking guy the guys that you can't kill you can't swing at these guys
where am i what the fuck is happening this is out fucking for ages this is out this is worse than
gary's mod gary's mod what the shit can't even happen there's like ai ceilings there's literally
ai ceilings in gary's book too many processes going on the same time
imagine playing this on anything other than normal holy fuck holy here come the trolls to
break it down instantly stick to the plan there is no plan you can't have a plan when there's
a hundred people spamming moves spamming at you on the screen there's no plan there is no plan
where are the trolls where are the trolls where are the trolls did i can you imagine putting it
on this that there's there what on earth would you have it on there for you want to just do it
for once just try it let's try it let's see what happens when the game's on expert do they swing
twice as fast do they have twice as much health does the wall have 50 left health left left health
the only thing i notice is the frame rate is worse you can't the shield doesn't break in one hit
what kind of mistake is that you know i'm saying it's a shield what kind of mistake
why have i not taken a single point of damage and now i have aragon he's stuck as my favorite
scene in one of the rings where aragon fell down every half second and when he spammed square in
the middle of people like this
he's already are you gonna kill him of aragon get over there this movie i love this movie
i don't know what he said whisperoto i don't know probably dead no one's checked on him in a while
who knows where he is he's retired archers this movie this seems longer than i remember i don't
remember there being a 45 minute helms deep scene in the movie i can't even get over here this is
like pushing your fucking face into quicksand is what this feels like i am smushing my face into
quicksand actually quicksand would probably feel better than this it's simulating how helms deep
was why are these now all of a sudden take two hits okay it's not fucking expert is that it that's
it all right come on clean it up here comes the trolls oh here comes the super mute
swing at me swing at me all right if i if i seriously hear like the here comes the
sit song again i'm gonna fucking throw up here comes the trolls here comes the trolls you're
about to hear is some encouragement to let you know that was the options fucking money
um
did any do did they did they did anybody test this level were they under a like a large
like get it out an 11 year old tested it
just swing the sword i feel like the trolls was like just a little too much or like why can't i
okay if i'm in that board meeting with wb whoever the fucking this was hey um maybe this shouldn't
be a nine and a half minute segment maybe make it six and bring the troll make one troll up
the trolls are the easiest part of the level i mean when they i can't see i can't get near
dude kids are fucking crazy kids can beat this shit i want to see the like lightning iq that it
would take to truly do this in a timely manner not even lightning iq you you're superhuman
go take a blood test and i guarantee you vitamin d levels are at 100 they have to be i bet you
you have vitamin d vitamin e vitamin b12 vitamin b6 vitamin b3 omega 3 and omega 6 you're probably
at 100 of all those god you fucking superhuman you're a vitamin d deficient asshole shut up
shut up i'm flashing out i'm flashing out now it's been almost 12 hours i'm flashing out
how dare you how dare you say that vitamin b
i'm going i'm going i wish somebody would protect the gate while i was gone
that guy is a statue he's made out of fucking stone i had to just look at it get him on the
stairs get him on the stairs terrible rng this is just just just just all right
they're on the front page of twitch i'm on the front page of twitch right now
am i seriously oh no what a bad time to be on the front page hey i can't even hide it i'm so
fucked hey guys this is uh playing lord of the rings uh fellowship of the fucking home depot
battle we are just this is a tricky part of the game where it simulates smashing your head into
a wall as hard as you can spinning around a circle 10 times and then picking up a playstation 2
controller and trying to play that's in the dev diary okay that guy was already dead hit the guys
attacking the door yeah but what happens when there's a guy attacking the door and a guy
attacking behind me a guy attacking on my left right forward the whole clock is taking up right
now you see how many things that was the entire clock it's not like oh watch like six o'clock
no watch all clocks watch every clock at the same time the ai actually fucking stops why
did he do that second part they're still they're still the archers didn't stop the archers keep
going same oh you legolas just fucking do anything for me oh my fucking god why would
why is this what is this segment what is this segment that i'm playing what is this
segment i'm playing what is this segment i just got five feet away from you it does the second
i didn't even press that button it's doing it a second time didn't you say this is one of the
best games ever made oh that was a lie that was a mistake he said it was the best ps2 game no
god of war 2 is okay i can't even fucking move i can't even move mate i can't even move this is
camera this camera kill him kill kill him he's almost dead oh put it on i can't put it on easy
mode all right if we get to 12 hours and i still haven't done it i'll put it on easy mode
i could not up here anymore i don't give a shit about this anymore oh no i can't beat for the
rings two towers in playstation 2 are normal i've forever soiled fucking let him attack the god
dear wall unattended doing good get off the air gun
move controllers that guy ran by real fast why are you almost dead let's don't die on the air man
him
this game has broken him oh i i'm in half i'm in half but both halves are still alive and there's
still one that one half is holding one side of the controller the other half's holding the other
side and they're working together there's somebody is somebody hacking in my game this is like a speed
hacker in here jesus man children their brains would have exploded if they had touched this
keep your kids away from this game don't let them play they'll end up they'll end up with
like a deficiency and fucking vitamin something but why am i on the vitamin thing why am i on
the vitamin thing this is just no hope for this level eat your flinstone gummies don't don't eat
those those are radioactive oh sorry that's bananas right guys it's not even hitting anything no
archers where are the archers did i already get them is there am i what am i waiting for here
just they take take so much damage i feel like i'm doing a like a mmo dungeon that's a five
player dungeon by myself okay that didn't like oh shit like the timer really shouldn't be down
this far but there's supposed to be 10 people here square x r2 square x r2 i don't know who i'm
aiming at this is where the camera just decides that it just don't give a fuck no more here we go
like we're gonna shake the screen and who gives a shit people floating around who gives a fuck
right like oh god it's already like dead there's no help there's so many i have to spam square
or i die there's no way it stands there's no way it stands it's over focus on the gate it's real
hard to do that when the screen is shaking and the screen is filled with bodies like i can't even
it's just it's like 10 out of 10 out fucking rage just cheese it stand on the stairs okay
do i actually have to break the game's code to play the game normally i have to break the game
play the fucking video game normally holy shit in my pants fill my stay on the stairs
what happens on the stairs uh this ain't working shoot towards the gate i mean it's the gates
already almost at like five percent health uh well i've turned off my friendly ai so that helps
get rising attack i don't think that's gonna help me though all right let's try the stairs again
stay on the stairs i i have to get ammo for my bow what these are wrong stairs
guys try the orc insta kill more it's just so hard to do when you're being spammed by
people in a circle it's it's oh block somebody and then press x and r2 but what you don't even
know who you're doing it to you don't even know who the fuck you're doing it to i thought the
stream ended hours ago no i'm still at uh what did what did the guide say the nearly impossible
level still here stay on the second floor all right try to get him down here all right legolas
get down here come on did they just continue to spawn up here they might because he's not going
anywhere he's not coming down this he's thought he's literally not going to come down these stairs
they just spawn just stay up here until the archers is that fucking going to happen
oh what gimli you're going to scream my name or what great camera it's fantastic it's the
best i've ever seen in a video game like top two top one top one ever
welcome to watch watching and watch wojo.com and today we're going to show you the top
one cameras in fucking playstation 2 history here it is why don't you stay up here
the point of going down there just kill everything up here until the until that this shit spawns
there's no health up here though break this motherfucking shield i need health man no don't
swing don't swing only swing when i don't want you to i need health though i need health i need
health it's a meteor okay where's i need health where's the troll i need health i need health so
bad i have to go down for the health i just help down here somewhere come on like let's down here
is it health down here
who's left who the fuck is what is going on over here really getting in your hours this week huh
i never thought i would be do i'll be doing this right now but like just out of principle i want
to beat this game right out of principle stay up here stay up here and fucking let the screen
shake by the way can i just say that screen shake is the shittiest thing that anyone has ever put
in their games why do you don't put don't get why do you put it even why is it in any game
at what point do you say hey like this game's kind of fun maybe we should shake the person's
screen like nobody everyone turns it off if it's available to turn off has anyone figured that out
yet in the gaming industry i turned off uh katana zero screen shake is it zero percent same with
motion blur i just don't get it is it to like hide the fact that like your game sucks
is that like why people do like a shit load of motion blur and stuff
yes because you don't want to see the trees popping in when they turn around too quickly
the arch is here yet i need health oh my fucking god need health all right i got some
this music's making me go insane imagine being the guy driving the car imagine i'm gonna drive for
this road trip you guys have been able to eat like eat snacks i've got my hands on the wheel
and my eyes blurry you've at least guys been able to eat some snacks can we not kill this guy
i'm not going down archers are coming up and they don't swing
why is this game so hard because up until 2004 people were just putting random code into the
engine and going oh shit i guess that works oh my god don't die don't die don't die at legolas
you have to fucking kill everybody here baston legolas pill that's not even a fucking device
that's not even a box i can open the fucking jesus christ somebody help me okay go back up the
stairs i thought i could open that box let's go all the way to the left oh my fucking god get this
motherfucker out of my way npc just standing in front of me
i don't even know what where i am i'm just holding down square i'm just
all the fucking archers dead in my favorite segment i have to go down here and get health
there's no health oh oh no this is bad it's over there's no health down here it's fucking
over there holy shit why don't you look you can't look i can't move the camera it's a resident evil
camera it goes wherever the fuck it wants it's a resident evil 4 tank camera let's three two one
you gotta call it this shit is fucking unbearable i can't even nobody can play this
the people play this wasn't there a dev here earlier did he beat this i wonder i wonder
that's 80 percent odds that the dev was fake oh i gotta put on my own music i'm done with the lord
of the rings music i'm putting on my own music my own damn music so i don't have to hear the same
oh
you have to beat it already then put on my fucking music
believable oh shit that's 10 and a half hours ago what am i gonna put on for music i don't know
what do we put on no no it's gotta be something relaxing it's gotta be chill music like something
like the wii menu music or something anything
this doesn't really fit with the theme of what's happening
i can't i can't i'm out of steam i'm out of gas there's no more gas in the tank
there's no more gas in the tank it's empty i'm fucking pushing it in neutral
oh there's no hills left i can push this down gate's doing okay i guess
go back to the first game it's too late it's too late now i'm coming legolas i'll be there soon
ah that's all right it's all right
what's that it's all right
just hanging out after you help legolas go back down to the gate i don't i i don't know the gate
gets hammered if you go down there it gets you get it gets crushed i have to stay up here until
the arches and then well no no no no yes you don't you don't you talk about it yeah i know
what you mean no not like the archer that i'm playing with the arches that are on the walls
i i know what you mean like i like hands are getting stuck
like i was underneath my desk
worst part is if you miss that uh instant kill you just put your sword in the ground where are you
going archers not yet no we're no not yet i'm caught in here it's just garret you're just dead
if you're fighting more than three people you're just dead the the systems in place you know what
i'm saying i need health how many fucking people have to die here until this ship can i need a
health pack there's nothing down here
i need to get health it's gonna be a disaster is it health over here not over here okay got it
archers not yet archers hurry up and get here so i can fucking beat this shit
didn't even break the shield fuck the shield enemies like fuck these guys there's two
fierce swings it couldn't break the damn thing fuck you save these for the archers why are they
no archers it didn't take this long the last time up here they are okay let's go wait they're not
here just there yeah oh my god it's so painful i got okay i did it i did it i did it now
i need health too though this okay so there's two berserkers down there they have to die
the two there's two berserkers down here they have to die right now
of course they're both attacking me at the same fucking goddamn time
i don't even know what's hitting me what did he do what the fuck what did he grab me
what the fuck is happening all right where's the trolls where the trolls bring them in bring in
trolls now i got full health wait this is another berserker here I can't even stoo
come here They just killed the trolls easy easy let's go easy
I did it i did it i did it i did it i did it i did it i did it i did it i did it i did
I did it I did it I did it!
I did it I did it I did it
I did it I did it
Did I do it?
Is there another part to this?
I don't know
YES!
I don't have to do it anymore
Oh man its over
It's over. It's over. It's over.
Sauron and Saruman are titans.
Sauron and Saruman are dead.
But for all that we have won over, the ring remains hidden.
Let's take a look and see what I look like.
That we should seek to destroy it.
How do I look?
So the weapon of the hands of a hobbit each day brings it closer to the fires of Mandu.
Sauron fears you.
Is this the Shmeagol music?
You look hungry.
I am hungry.
The fucking Gollum music had to play the second I turned the camera on.
Give me a break.
I don't know what I even...
Nice mic noises. I know, I'm sorry.
Okay, so...
Wait, is that not the end of the game?
How is that not the end of the game?
I don't think I want anything else.
I guess I'll get this.
I told you I was going to do it.
I told you I was going to get past the first part of Fellowship of the Ring.
That's right. Fake Grumbo.
I told you I was going to do it.
I want my two dollars from you, fake Grumbo.
Although I made that part up.
You don't have to give me any money.
The process of the video game construction and the building of it...
is not made for fighting things.
Vigo, you didn't get to fucking Helm's Deep. Give me a break.
I'm surprised. I mean, it looks much more realistic.
It seems it goes to another level.
If you got to Helm's Deep, you'd probably be like, I refuse the interview.
I think Aragorn's aim video game is better than my outfit.
You sound so tired.
I'm glad I did it.
What I've seen of the video game seems to reflect the fact that the second movie, as opposed to the first one, is on a bigger scale.
And I'm looking forward to seeing them just as I am to seeing the rest of this game.
I've only seen a sample today.
I'm glad to see, for example, that sometimes Aragorn gets knocked over or falls down or rolls around.
And that his fighting style alters to fit the situation.
It's not always neat and tidy.
He falls down.
I love it when he falls down.
That's true. That's true. I like it when he falls down.
Somebody said he hates it.
Did you know Vigo Mortensen hates the game?
Wait, was that sarcastic?
Well, you know, I really love when he falls down and has to change and gets shit kicked out of him.
I didn't like being a lot slower.
I can't believe it was slower.
I can't believe he was slower.
I did that level like 20 times in a row.
And I didn't know that he was like 15% slower.
It took me actually like two or three solid tries.
You don't have to do so much darn hard work as you do when you're originally creating the character.
Shooting a film is necessarily very slow.
Wait, wait, wait. Go back. How do we go back? How do we go back? How do we pause?
How do we pause?
That was a grip.
Look at that grip.
He put his right hand over, I think, to grab the...
You fear to go into those mines.
That was a sick claw gamer grip.
You know what they're worth.
I enjoyed making the game because you don't have to do so much darn hard work as you do when you're originally creating the character.
Shooting a film is necessarily very slow.
The wonderful thing about the computer game is, of course, I don't have to get in the makeup.
When you do the game, you stand in the studio.
And you say, well, I think you ought to say this and this and this.
He's awesome, by the way.
All these wonderful lines.
Ambush! Ambush!
And then they take all that, and they incorporate it into the games, and you get some of the credit.
Those explosive devices must be destroyed.
This model of me is Gimli.
I'm such a vigorous, virile, attractive character.
He's really the only person you want to play.
I mean, the rest.
The Aragorns, the Legolas.
Handsome, good-looking guys and all that.
But for real quality warfare, you have to go for a Gimli.
We spent 14 months in the most beautiful locations in the world in New Zealand to get the right look for the film.
The game is a wartime combat situation.
Because you betrayed him.
And it's wonderfully and brilliantly-
I didn't betray him!
I can't leave him there!
They made it impossible to beat the ladder level with him.
That's not my fault.
It's a new addiction that I have discovered.
So, Gamesters, well done.
Congratulations on getting into this little niche that gives you the interview.
I wish I could tell you how to play the game better, but in fact, I could never get to this level.
Good luck with it.
Gamesters.
Oh, he's so wonderful.
I could just listen- I could listen to him talk all day.
He's just- he's phenomenal.
Do we have any more?
Oh, no.
Oh, I need level 10 with Aragorn and we get the super secret video?
What's down here?
What level- how close am I now?
I can't.
I can't replay anything.
I didn't get to level 10.
Wait, whoa, whoa, since when can I do that?
Since when can I do that?
Oh, because I beat the game.
Now I can do it.
I beat the game.
I see.
I don't want to- I don't want to see that ever again.
Alright, for all the shit that I was talking about the game, you do have to give some credit here.
This shit was 20 years ago.
This is pretty damn cool for 20 years to go, except for these three levels.
Delete them.
And this one.
2001.
If I remember correctly, Return of the King is a much more polished, better video game.
I didn't like this one.
This one was- this one was good.
I didn't- okay, let's go- let me- let me reassess here.
Cool.
That was cool.
Fighting the ringwraiths, yeah.
We had to get- no, this is when they were breaking through the ice and stuff.
That was cool.
This is the big- the big troll with the- yeah, that was cool.
Um, eh.
I didn't like this one.
This one was good.
I like to walk around forests and you sneak around.
This one was cool.
No, don't like it.
This is not even a level.
This was just a door and then a boss.
So, I mean, it was okay.
Delete.
Good.
Alright, for how, like, horrendous this was.
It was still hysterical.
Like, do you remember our first four or five attempts in this level?
Just how much fun we were having.
We were having so much fun in the first five or six attempts.
Then an hour and a half went by.
Then I lost all the feeling in my tongue.
It's back now.
Twelve and a half hours.
Okay.
I want that ten- I want that level ten video.
Remember when he aspirated jerky?
Damn, it really has been a whole day.
How close was I to ten?
Okay.
Have I actually gone crazy?
YouTube.com.
Aragorn level ten video.
It doesn't exist on YouTube.
I want that- I want that fucking video.
I want to see Viggo Mortens talk about how much he loves the game again.
Look, this is going to be simple.
I'm, like, max level and shit.
Oh, look at how- I'm right there.
Oh, yeah, I'm right there.
Let's go.
What's the longest stream I've ever done?
What is actually the longest stream I've ever done?
Does anybody know?
It's now this one.
Is it actually this one now?
Level ten.
There it is.
We get the secret video.
Lifeline was pretty long.
I think it was, like, eleven and a half, though.
Come on.
Did I- wait, can I actually hit him?
Um, no.
Don't kill me.
He's going to be mad.
What do you mean mad?
Well, actually, I am a little bit mad.
Nothing to do with the video game, really.
It has to do with- I've been- I've been streaming on Twitch for, what, four- just five years?
Six years?
Like, just almost a full five years, right?
And the longest stream I've ever done is going to be for a long time.
Lord of the Rings The Two Towers on PlayStation 2.
I think that's more upsetting.
And the first Hobbit game.
Yeah, but that's not why this was so long.
Longest and worst stream.
I don't agree with that at all.
No, no, no, not even close.
I had a fucking lot of fun on this stream.
I thought this was a lot of fun.
Yesterday's stream was the worst stream.
Oh, I see what you're doing.
Yeah, because this was streamed yesterday.
Oh.
This was- I had a lot of fun on this stream.
Alright.
Level 10.
Secret video.
Let's go.
The CCTV joke was worth ten hours of setup.
What's the final thing I'm going to buy, though?
Probably this thing.
And... this one.
Here we go.
Alright.
Vigo.
Tell me your secret-
Tell me your secrets, Vigo.
Aragorn.
Unplayed.
Let's play the video then.
It's about to be played.
What?
Floor 1 out of 20.
I'm not doing that.
We're not doing that.
I'm sorry.
I'm not doing- no.
No fucking way.
It's not- alright.
I want to watch this trending now on CNN.
This was probably somebody's first experience with Lord of the Rings.
Yeah, we talked about that earlier.
This was somebody's first stream.
Yeah, it was probably a lot of people's first streams.
Probably.
Where's the music?
I don't want any sounds right now.
I don't want any stimulation.
I just want to sit here.
No stimulation at all.
Except for this.
No stimulation.
Just quiet.
This is the only thing I want in my life right now.
The battle for- the battle for Home Depot.
Roger, people on social media are calling this the Battle of Home Depot.
This reporter cannot understand just how ridiculous this is, seeing this from above.
You don't see the other 300 people that are back behind the doors.
Holy shit, like, listen.
This is a mess.
Hello?
Wait, why is this not working?
There we go.
Is this- hello?
Hello?
Yeah, guys.
So this is what happens.
This is what happens when you- yeah, it's been a long night.
So we're just gonna chill for a little bit.
You know, just hang out.
I might sound a little different, but that's because, you know, I've been yelling a lot tonight.
So I've been making a lot of noise.
I inhaled a piece of jerky, and that's kind of why I feel like I'm-
So for the bits of what- turn this off.
Someone was like, fuck, this is weird.
Todd Howard?
And next, coming up, we have our first mobile game experience.
I can't.
I have to go to bed.
If you thought for one second that we were not gonna go completely crazy here with Elder Scrolls Blades, that's the one.
Welcome to Fallout Con.
You can do some really weird shit with this thing, man.
I'll tell you.
Okay.
Like, for instance, what if I do this?
Ready?
Like, what if I go like this?
And then go like this, okay?
So right now- how does this sound now?
This probably sounds really weird.
Like, very strange.
Oh.
This is- this is, uh, this is one- this is one hour after two towers.
This is two hours after two towers.
Four hours after two towers.
This is six hours after two towers.
This is ten hours after two towers.
This is how I feel right now.
Hey.
Why- I sound weird now.
Why do I sound so strange to myself?
I sound weird to myself.
Anybody else sound weird to yourself?
Okay.
Um, I am gonna have to forego the bits tonight, guys.
I'm really sorry.
I feel like somebody just punched me in the face with a car.
Uh, we have like 12 hours- 13 hours of bits.
It's gonna take me like two or three hours to go through it.
Um, this is the second time we've moved bits to another day.
I'm really sorry about that, but, um, it's like I got- I got run over by a car.
It was a shitload of money and a shitload of people supported the channel.
You guys are fucking incredible.
I can at least run the credits.
Do them next time.
Yeah, by the way, this is not- I'm not streaming tomorrow.
This was- this was like a mega stream.
So what's gonna happen is you'll probably see- you'll see me again on Wednesday.
I'm gonna take a day or two here.
You'll see me on the 15th.
Wednesday the 15th.
This is an omega lol stream.
You ready for me to fix that once and for all?
Uh, it's because the- the- the heater turns on behind me.
I just figured it out.
Yep.
That's the heater.
And the gate is not high enough to mask the heater.
Figured it out.
Let me fix that right now.
There it is.
Got it.
That fixed it, right?
Okay.
Good.
Oh, wow.
I'm so sorry that that's been happening.
I'm so sorry about that.
I'm so s- I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Okay.
That sounds weird.
There's one more thing I want to do before I go.
Uh, let me look at this.
There's some weird shit here.
Hello?
Hold on.
This is actually bad for Mike.
This is...
Okay.
There's a lot of random shit here.
It's me.
Hello?
This one's called- this one's called Big Ferb.
Big Ferb?
Uh...
Oh, Big Reverb!
Big Reverb!
Some of these are ridiculous.
I can be in a chapel.
I can be in a club.
This is in a music club.
This is a hockey arena.
Weird.
That's pretty ridiculous.
And you can do a lot of weird shit with this, too.
Okay.
I had my fun.
I will see you guys in a couple days.
Thank you again.
Here come the credits.
Go eat something?
Okay.
I had my fun.
I will see you guys in a couple days.
Thank you again.
Here come the credits.
Go eat something?
I...
I'm good.
I'll eat something.
Tell Joel, uh, sorry I did a 13-hour stream.
We'll- we'll schedule it for a few days or something.
Anybody even, like, streaming right now?
Do people stream on Twitch at, like, 4 o'clock in the morning?
I guess they do.
They ha- like, yeah, they do.
Who's streaming right now?
Uh...
You.
Oh, right.
Other countries exist, Jeremy.
Yeah, they do.
I'm still on the front page.
Okay.
Everybody on the front page has a...
Everybody on the front page has, like, a...
Hey, this is the person.
This is the streamer.
This is the person that you...
Hey, check them out.
This is what they do.
They do this, this, this, and this.
Mine just says, video and streamer guy.
I don't know how to do anything.
I don't know how to run a business.
I need to run a business.
This is my business.
Who else has, like...
Germanite5 Incorporated.
No, I don't know.
Who gives a shit?
I don't care.
All right.
That has been fun.
I'll see you guys later.
Here come the credits.
Actually, we're gonna sit here and let them roll through.
Close to 13 hours?
Yeah.
Look at this.
You massacred my business.
What the fuck?
Grandma's stocks are dropping.
Um, that's okay.
It's not all about how high.
What the fuck is...
What's happening?
Somebody talking in my head.
Oh, no.
These are the front page streams.
Okay.
Gotta get off the front page.
What is the title of this stream?
Oh, I guarantee you will like the first part of Two Towers.
We did.
That last part, though.
That last part and maybe not so much.
But I still did.
I'm glad I streamed.
I'm glad I streamed Lord of the Rings Two Towers and beat it.
I hate that game.
Why?
Oh.
Well, this is a wild one.
Didn't plan on it.
This was gonna be just a...
I played Lord of the Rings Fellowship for two hours.
But what can I say?
Sometimes it happens.
Sometimes...
Sometimes this shit just happens.
I didn't plan hit and run either.
How does it feel to be a gamester?
Feels pretty good.
I'm so glad I got rid of that background bullshit.
Hold on.
Let's put the compressor back on and see what it sounds like.
Hey.
The compressor's back on.
Oh, now I know what you guys are talking about when you say this sounds fucking terrible.
I really thought everyone was just gaslighting me telling me that I was crazy.
This fucking sounds terrible.
This sounds awful.
See, now it sounds a lot better.
That sounds way better.
That sounds a thousand times better.
Holy shit.
I didn't believe you.
I really didn't.
I didn't believe a single word anybody was saying.
Because this is what it sounded like before.
Maybe I need to be closer to the mic.
It's just my room is so noisy.
That's the problem.
Oh, hey guys.
It's the podcast voice.
Good afternoon.
Hope everybody's having a great day today.
The following has encouragement.
That's what it is.
It's a bunch of compressed.
The following has encouragement and love.
We want to thank you for being here.
You're the one that gets things done around here.
Well, tell him.
A great job.
You're the one that gets things done around.
That's what he did.
Holy shit.
I love that guy.
Okay.
Let's go back to normal.
Hold on.
What if I do this?
Well, I think I fixed it.
Did I fix it even more?
I think I just fixed it even more.
Did I?
Hey.
How you guys doing?
Is it fixed?
Fixed even more?
Are we fixed even more?
How are we?
No, it's worse now.
How about now?
How about this?
Is it a little bit better from here?
Sounds exactly the same.
Now it sounds horrible.
What if I do this?
Okay.
I just did this.
All right.
Maybe now...
How's that?
Is that a little bit better?
Does this change anything?
Does it make it sound better?
Or no?
Still just as bad?
Go back?
Okay.
I'm still trying to get it to sound okay, you know?
Go back to podcast voice.
I really don't think you want me to go back to podcast voice.
Hold on.
What about this?
Okay.
Listen to how weird this sounds.
So this is 100 compressor and 100 de-esser.
This is like...
It just sounds so strange.
Don't I sound so weird?
I sound like a different person.
All right.
Anyways, guys, I'll see you in a couple days.
See you in...
On Wednesday.
See you soon.
I'm going to wait until it's 13 hours though.
Because...
Come on.
I got to take my victories where I can.
We want to thank you.
I just normally sound like that guy, I think.
I think I just actually sound like that, dude.
Somebody with a raid?
I mean, nobody I follow is even streaming right now.
It's so late.
Who cares?
It's got to be somebody that you follow.
Let's see.
Do you want to just pick somebody?
We could.
We should just see.
All right.
Who the fuck is streaming?
Um, um, um, um.
Raid somebody with zero viewers?
No, I don't.
That's a lot of pressure.
Some people really don't want that, I don't think.
I mean, you know what I mean?
We could, but that's a lot of people to dump on somebody.
I don't like putting that kind of pressure on somebody.
Um.
Raid my friend.
Dude, can you raid my friend?
He's live right now.
Go raid him.
I'm just scrolling down looking.
Find someone streaming a Lord of the Rings game?
Impossible.
I don't think that's possible.
Hold on.
All right.
Let's pick a game.
We'll pick a game first.
From there.
Raid the guy's friend.
You please raid.
Hold on.
What's your friend's channel?
Let me look at this person.
Either that or we're just.
Is that right?
My friend's channel.
Everyone keeps saying cry.
Cry, cry, cry.
Cry.
What do you mean?
I'm cry?
Oh, cryotic.
Oh, okay.
Where's, um, playing Noito?
He just went offline.
Swivel.
Thanks Swivel for the 10 subs.
Did he just go offline?
Just finished.
Oh, okay.
Thank you for the 10 fucking subs.
Let's just go to bed.
Oh, you know who we, you know, all right.
You know who we could raid?
We could raid Immortal HD.
I've hung out with Immortal a few times in real life actually.
At random events and stuff.
Let's do that.
Let's go raid Immortal HD.
You know, I've like hung out with them at events and stuff, you know.
No big deal.
I know him.
I know this guy.
Don't worry about it.
All right.
I'll see you guys on Wednesday.
Have a great rest of your night.
Thanks for sticking around for 13 hours, 3 minutes and 33 seconds.
Take care guys.
Thanks for sticking around.
We'll do the bits on Wednesday.
I promise.
Good night guys.