Oh, you know, you could be this guy with the book too. This like, Monopoly man. You're the fucking Monopoly man.
Nope, it wasn't me.
What?
I'm pretty good at these things, I think.
Well, you know, I'm going to know what they are.
Yeah, I know.
That's fine.
I'm picking my spy.
Alright, I'm ready.
Are you?
Because you're going to pick the Monopoly guy now. I'm going to see the Monopoly guy.
Why would I be that stupid?
Oh yeah, let me pick the guy that you would just... Yeah, that's a great idea.
I'm looking, I'm looking.
It's so scary. It's so scary because I can see the laser.
Is it on your head?
No, I can just see it. I can see the laser.
I know. Well, if you see the laser on your head, the Monopoly guy.
I can see the laser pointing into the room. That's all I'm telling you right now.
I'm so scared.
No, don't shoot me. Don't shoot me.
Playing the psychology role.
Oh yeah. Well, I'm going to get you. I think I've already got this figured out.
You should be scared right now.
Oh yeah?
You should be whimpering.
Fuck!
If that's the indicate. These guys are all suspected double agents, okay?
So that means you're over here somewhere. You're in this crowd somewhere.
Of course I'm in. This whole room is a crowd.
No, no, no. You're in this crowd like over on the right.
Because these guys were suspected. They were suspected criminals.
And you're over here. You're one of these four people.
How could I possibly be one of these four people?
Because I think you're the guy in the mustard jacket.
I think you're the guy in the mustard jacket.
Who wears mustard?
I got my eye on you.
I got my eye on the mustard jacket.
Okay, now you said I'm out of here.
Which means you have to be one of these people.
Because how would you have known he even walked away?
Oh, that's right. I just figured it out.
You're one of the guys in the mustard colored jacket.
Okay.
I don't know which one of them you are, but I know.
Or you're the lady.
All right, great. Everybody else out.
I know which one of these guys you are.
Yeah, you're that guy. You're definitely that guy.
Say your prayers.
No!
You're not good at this.
You were the lady. I knew you were one of those guys or you were the lady.
Oh, no.
You're going to be the freaking monopoly guy again.
You're just going to play with the monopoly guy every single time.
This is a poker game. I'm not going to give you any tells.
Are there even 16 different party goers?
I don't know. It looks like there are.
I'm taking the shot.
I was the monopoly guy.
I should have shot the monopoly guy.
Yeah, you really should have because it would have been like the monopoly guy.
Like it is every single time.
Seriously, better not pick him again. It's not going to work.
Hmm. This is tricky.
I don't want to get it wrong.
I have my suspicions.
Screw your suspicions.
My suspicions are squabbling.
You don't have very much time.
You haven't completed your missions. There's no way you have.
Okay. Okay.
Screw you, monopoly guy. I don't think it's you, but screw you.
Are you kidding?
Oh, you made him the double agent.
This is a weird stage. I'm in the middle. I can't move.
Really?
Someone's already in...
That can't be you.
Because that's the double agent as well.
You can think whatever you want, bro.
You want to know what I think?
What do you think? Let's see it.
I think there's a lot of statues here.
There are a lot of statues here, I guess.
You know what, Terma?
Safety is off.
What do you mean the safety is off?
Oh, you're going to shoot that guy?
Do it. Shoot that guy right now.
Shoot him.
Shoot him. Shoot him right now.
Shoot that guy right now.
Shoot him in the head.
No.
I'm taking my time.
Blow that guy's fucking head clean off his shoulders.
Who's this lady?
Pay attention to the other guy.
Pay attention to that guy.
No, that lady didn't do anything.
That lady's going the other way.
See? I'm telling you this lady's going this way.
Man.
That guy's just like, I'm just staring at you.
Why don't you shoot me?
What is about to happen?
Everything.
Everything is about to happen.
You ready?
I'm ready.
You have to hit accept. Hit accept.
I was stretching.
He was looking at me right from the start.
He was staring right at me.
I was like, no.
I'm not having this guy show up to no more parties.
No, dude.
Are you sure it's not him?
Look, I'm not...
Okay.
You're picking him this time though.
I know you can't resist.
Can we please play around?
Yes.
Where you do not instantly kill the Monopoly Man.
You could just watch my laser.
That's fine.
That's perfectly fine.
Fucking Monopoly Man every time.
What's he doing?
Just standing over there.
He's not doing anything.
Too suspicious.
All right.
I'm not shooting the Monopoly Guy.
I'm not going to shoot the fucking Monopoly Guy.
Instantly.
What?
You missed.
You're so bad.
You took like a turn too quickly.
You had one knob.
Was to kill the Monopoly.