Yeah, there's at least two creepers out there. Yep. And they're like on top of the roof.
This was a horrible place to build the house. Whose idea was this? Mine. And mine. I'm gonna
build out, see where my name is, guys? Whoa, they're lagging too. That's the worst part.
Yeah. Be careful. I'm coming to rescue you. Oh no, they're coming for me. I'm digging
straight up, guys. I'm trying to take care of this skeleton over here. Get in here. I
might be able to just lure them away. All right, they're coming after me. Both the creepers
are after me. This is our time to act. Oh my god. I have, I don't know where to go.
Oh jeez. Head towards me. Where are you? I'm digging out. Are you in the original home?
Yes, right here. Get in, get in, get in. Oh, the creepers are coming lefter. I got in,
I got in the house. All right, are you in? Me too. I'm in the house. We're both in the
house. Nice. Oh my god. I'm gonna get away. Oh my god, they're pounding. See how scary
that is? Hey. It's terrifying. I need food. I'm dying. Because there are creepers out
there too. Hey guys. You guys can't do nothing. We got food. We have food. I'm gonna defend
myself, yo. Get these creepers and, oh gosh. What happens if I open the door? Don't open
the door. All right, viewers at home, while you were away, we started a lovely weed farm
and as a result, wow, thank, why? This is not working at all. Give me food. Chests do
not automatically pick that stuff up. Just an FYI. I want those. Where are those? This
is real. All right, you get one bread for you. Actually, two bread for you. Om nom nom
nom nom nom nom. How's your hunger doing, Jerma? It's all right. Oh, I was gonna open
the door. I was just tempted to. And I need to eat. I need food. Yeah, I do. Actually,
I got bread. I just gave you one, so. Oh yeah. All right. It's a total bread party. Oh no,
no. I didn't mean to do that. I'll take the hit. Oh my god. I have to piss them off. Oh
wow. Why did that just happen? Why? Oh my god. They are so good now. What is this? Okay,
I'm rebuilding the wall. I'm distracting, but they're everywhere. All right. I didn't
know if you right click, you open doors. Oh my god, they're so good right now. Yes. I
right click to like throw a snowball at the door and I open the door. All right. I have
to make another door. I've got the wall back up, but man, we need a safer way to do this
now. They are way too smart. All right. I need to pick up all of our items. Oh my god.
Open up. Oh god. Oh, I'm coming for me. Don't worry. I'm here to the rescue. Oh, he's.
How did he get inside? He went through my. He went through. Oh my. What is going on here?
Hold on. This is this is a secondary entrance now. Lepter dug up. Remember to distract them
and then a creeper like dropped out. He went through his hole in order to come down here
and attack me. Oh my god. Luckily for me, he only needed one fist punch to die or else
they would have exploded our chest. All right. So masterful, you know, movement around the map.
All right. So if I if I right click, I don't throw snowballs. Don't do it.
Here you go. Hang on. We're going to fix this. Good lesson. Good lesson to learn. Do not right
click near a door. I got it. I should make another door for us up top here, though.
Here's what I'm going to do. We're going to make like a secondary, secondary door for the
to protect the first door. You know what I'm saying? Yeah, we need one door to protect the
second door. Exactly. Exactly. All right. So I have a door up here now as well.
Like one exit on this side and one exit on this side. You know what I'm saying?
Like two exits. Yeah, because if they're on one side banging on the door,
then we just go to the other side. Hey, what if they're smarter than that? What do you do then?
What a great way. That's a great way to deal with like a Jehovah's Witness.
Just make two doors so you can escape to the second door when they knock on the first door.
Let's go. There we go. All right. Oh, wait, no, no, don't fill that in. That's where the door is
going to be. Oh, yeah. I cut down this tree. I think totally. Yeah, I did. Actually, we could
have three doors. We could have one in the front and one on each side. And then it's literally
impossible to get back in the house. I can't believe we really are making a door to get into
the door. That's so funny. We're making three doors to get in the door. We heard you like doors,
so we gave you a door with the door next to another door. Oh, my God. Look at all that snow
video. I love how I'm not doing anything. I'm just like watching you guys like build this house.
I'm just like, what time is it? What a great voice.
Okay. It's granddaddy germs. Now we just need doors. Oh, no, this is off by one. Okay, I'm good
now. I'm okay. Oh, did we freeze? We froze. Wait, what happened? Yeah, we froze. I need one more
door. Oh, this looks really, really cool. I think we need to up the style a little bit, though. So
I'm going to just. I almost feel like I belong here. We'll sacrifice practicality for an uneven
house. What are these shenanigans? This isn't allowed. No, if you play Minecraft long enough.
Hey, hey, don't we have a lot of glass? Or am I just mistaken? So they can't like punch out
windows, can they? Let's hope not. Yeah, I'm hoping not. Do we have any more glass? Yes,
absolutely. All right. Well, I have nothing. I can't. I can't let this slide, man. Can't let
it slide. I don't know what's going on. Is that thing up there supposed to be like the chimney
or something? There's like a little like dongle up top. We have a snow. I'm going to add a
glowstone block on top of that. I do have another snow block. Where do you need it? Right in this
corner right over here. Hey, guys. Did I make you miss? No, it apparently made Jerma's mistake.
Oh, right clicking doesn't do anything. Oh, it's there. It's easy. I think it's I am helping.
And you know what we can do? How did you even get up there?