Alright, I'm back. Sorry about that.
Make a new green tea.
But I'm here now.
How you guys doin'?
Alright, so how this is gonna work...
Couple things here. Cut the music off.
Um, should I do like a OST in the background?
What do you guys think?
Because here's how this is gonna work.
I had this tier list that I found
has every single boss
across the entire franchise. All franchises.
Uh, so I need to...
Obviously it's been a while since I've played any of these games.
I remember all these fights.
But I have a bunch of videos over here
of all just the boss fights.
So I can just kind of scrub through and be like
Alright, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's that person.
Okay, sure.
So I just need a refresher sometimes.
All the Dark Souls 2 stuff, you guys did not see me play.
I did that off stream.
So, without further ado,
let's get an OST on. What do you guys think?
Any, uh, anything reaching out to you?
Anything doing it for you?
I could put on the Bloodborne OST. That seems fitting.
We'll switch it up in a minute.
Okay.
I don't want it to be too loud.
Okay, so that can just stay on.
This is the Bloodborne OST.
Without further ado, here we go.
So, take a look.
Here's what I got for you.
I've got...
Uh, let me just make sure I got it correctly.
Do.
And this correctly as well.
Which I do.
Okay.
So, here we go.
There's a lot here.
I can grow a little bit.
Maybe in the bottom?
There are a shitload of names.
This is gonna be...
This is gonna be difficult.
We are going to start with Demon's Souls.
He's growing.
Is that better?
A little bit of white on either side or no?
That's good right there.
Okay.
So, we're gonna start with Demon's Souls.
I need a refresher because I have no fucking idea.
The refresher is, by the way,
I have all the Demon's Souls fights right here.
So, let's get started.
Let me do the ones that I know for certain absolutely.
These are how I feel the best from software bosses.
The criteria.
Game mechanic-wise.
How cool they looked.
How...
Like, their animation style.
The damage they did.
How angry I got, right?
Like, what was the most universal best fight I've done in any of these games?
I can already tell you what the first one is.
Ludwig from Bloodborne is by far...
I'm not gonna say it yet,
but I think it's the best fight they've ever done.
Where's the soundtrack?
All right.
So, we're gonna go down to Bloodborne.
Here we are.
This is gonna be so hard.
This is gonna be way harder than I think.
Okay.
Where is...
There is...
Okay.
I gotta move you all the way up here.
Those of you that don't know this fight,
it's the best fight From Software's ever done.
The second phase of this fight had an amazing reveal.
I don't want...
I don't necessarily need to spoil too much.
The music is incredible.
It's...
It's a full package.
The boss fight is not too frustrating.
The first phase kind of is.
So, we know that's there.
100%.
The other one that's going up in S...
Let me see if I can remember if I can find it.
It's from Dark Souls 3.
DLC.
Slave Knight Gale.
Absolutely one of the...
Probably the second...
It's probably the second best fight they've ever done.
Right here.
I think...
Let's just get the S's done first.
I mean, I'm gonna put...
Let's get Gwyn up here immediately, right?
Like, I...
Come on, Gwyn.
Like, that was...
I don't know if that...
I think Gwyn is probably a B.
I think it's only...
It would be a C if it wasn't for the...
Come on, Gwyn.
Alright, now...
What are the S's?
Guaranteed S's.
Where's Horolue?
Horolue from Elden Ring?
I gotta say, it's probably...
Top...
It's gotta be at least A or S.
That whole fight was amazing.
I've never felt so...
Involved.
And my heart was just...
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
I was not annoyed.
I was not mad.
I was just truly...
In the zone.
It was really, really fun.
Alright, where is Horolue?
Uh...
It's gotta be pretty far down here, right?
Oh, yeah.
This part.
Let's turn it up.
Horolue.
Oh, I can also make sure I do the ones that are literally zero.
That are like the worst I've ever done.
Let's do the top ones first.
Where are you?
There's so many names.
There you go.
Alright.
Horolue slash Godfrey.
It is technically the same fight.
That's going up to S.
Who else belongs at S?
I don't know if any of the Dark Souls 2 bosses are gonna be even A.
I don't think so.
I'm trying to remember.
You know who else I need to put pretty high?
Where is it?
Bloodborne.
Why is Brainsucker a boss?
Brainsucker wasn't a boss?
Um...
I knew this was gonna be hard.
Ibritas.
Ibritas was...
I don't think it's S.
But I'm gonna say B.
Ibritas is really cool.
That was just one of those reveal fights.
Where you walk in the door.
And it's just like...
It's so scary that this thing is even down here.
The fight was...
Eh.
But I think the reveal was pretty cool.
Uh, where is...
All the Sekiro bosses.
Oh, fuck all the Sekiro bosses.
Yeah.
I think all the Sekiro bosses are gonna be C or lower.
Although, probably not.
We have to take a look.
I might need a refresher.
We should probably go one game at a time.
Alright, let's get a refresher here.
So this is Old Monk.
I forget what Old Monk was.
Old Monk.
Power Knight.
Flame Lurker?
No.
Is Old Monk even on here?
Was Old Monk even a boss fight?
Old Monk.
What do you got?
What happened here?
I forget this fight.
Old Monk is the invader.
Oh, right, right, right.
I need a refresher though.
I mean, what the fuck?
Let's go.
Hello?
Oh, there we go.
Okay.
So what happens here?
It's the guy that invades you.
Oh, with all the chairs.
I forgot about...
Yeah, this wasn't that bad.
Oh, yeah, he had the funny hat on.
Okay.
Wasn't he really, really easy?
Okay, this guy was stupid.
Yeah, this guy was pretty stupid.
Um, he did have the funny hat on though.
Comedy hat puts you in C.
Where is the spider?
Armor spider.
C.
Alright, I'll give you one refresher on the armor spider.
Here you go.
This is the one where you had to go down the hallway.
This...
Oh, I hated this.
This was stupid.
Yeah.
It starts back here.
Yeah, this boss was...
Oh, this was awful.
Yeah, this is going way lower.
Yeah.
No, fuck this boss.
Oh, shit.
Here comes Gascoigne.
Might as well put Gascoigne now because his music is playing.
But let's...
Oh, yeah.
Armor is D.
That fight was awful.
Okay.
Let's get Gascoigne up there because he was probably A.
It's going to be very blood-borne.
It's going to be blood-borne heavy at the top.
Where's Gascoigne?
Cleric beast.
I got to put...
Okay.
One of the only times you're going to see a blood-borne boss be like somewhere near F
is cleric beast.
This boss was just stupid.
There's like a...
You fight it on the bridge.
It takes up the whole bridge.
It's annoying.
This boss sucked.
Cleric beast was awful.
It just...
I don't like you fighting the things on like the tiny little bridges where they take up
the whole thing.
Although these have...
These might change, but where's Gascoigne?
Oh, the Gascoigne.
Alright.
This fight was awesome.
Let's change into...
Well, it's good.
Let's put it at A.
Put Pinwheel at S.
Pinwheel is...
Let's do that now.
F.
Hold on.
Stick with Demon's Souls for now.
The Adjuncticator.
What's the Adjuncticator?
Oh, Phalanx.
This is F, right?
Yeah.
This boss was stupid.
This thing was terrible.
Why is this lagging?
Why is it lagging?
Yeah.
That's going to go probably F or lower.
Because the fight was just...
It's a huge blob and the spears just stick out.
You're not even fighting a boss.
You're just fighting a big annoying thorn bush.
It's stupid.
That was Phalanx.
Okay.
Let me make sure this is right so far.
Yep.
Oh, Sif!
Wait.
Just stay in Demon's Souls.
I don't want to jump around.
Except for the ones that I know are going in F, which...
Where's Millenia?
Millenia is 100% F.
Wait.
Hold on.
Tibia Mariner.
We're going to get this one done right now, too.
The Tibia Mariner was like C, though, because it was funny.
Molting.
The Millenia fight was one of the worst things I've ever done in a Souls game.
And I know I said that for Isshin.
But nope.
No, Isshin is better.
Isshin is going down there, too, though.
Don't worry.
Where are you?
Godskin duel.
I like the Godskin stuff, but I feel like they showed up way too often.
I'll put Godric.
We'll do Godric.
I actually really liked that fight.
The music is great.
He laughs.
He has like a...
I like his moveset.
But I think...
Wait.
It's not gone today.
B plus for now.
For now.
Let's stay in Demon's Souls.
I'm going to all over the place.
Adjunct Cater.
What is that?
Was this the thing with Big Tongue?
It was like a big fat guy, right?
Yeah, yeah.
I remember this.
Wasn't this the fight that you had to...
Yeah, you had to stand up here and throw shit at it?
F.
Yeah.
Tiny room, huge boss is already a C or below.
This is at least a D.
All the tiny room, huge bosses are going to get at least a C or minus.
Old Hero.
Right here.
This music is too intense for me.
I think this music is too intense.
What do you think?
Another hallway boss, which I'm not a big fan of.
I think this guy actually had a pretty cool moveset though.
From what I remember.
I remember this guy being fun to fight against.
What else did he do?
Yeah, we need like Animal Crossing music or something.
This is like...
I feel like I need to be screaming at you.
Yeah.
This was solid.
I remember.
Yeah, let's put on like...
Yeah, let's put on like Stardew Valley or something.
Stardew Valley.
That's like in easy listening.
I don't know.
I feel like I need to be like...
Run.
Everybody run.
Hey, there we go.
Now we can do it.
Get back to this.
I'm going to put Old Hero in C.
Storm King.
Let's see.
What was this one?
I don't remember this at all.
And you're probably wondering, why do you not have the Demon's Souls remastered shit
up here?
Because I haven't played it yet and I'm going to probably eventually.
Oh, yeah.
It was a giant moth.
Yeah.
This is cool.
It was...
This was a gimmick fight.
How much of a gimmick was it though?
It's a manta ray.
The Stardew Valley music makes this like weird.
It was a gimmick fight.
Yeah.
Oh, didn't I hate this?
I talked a lot of shit about this.
I think I distinctly said this was awful.
Yeah.
This was...
You had to get the cyclone thing and it was freaking loud too.
Yeah, that's not that great.
All right.
Storm King.
Let's...
What about Leechmonger?
We'll do three or four of them.
Leechmonger is here.
This is the one where when you just being in the room, you got hurt.
Oh, yeah.
I hated this.
Yeah.
And there was no rhyme or reason to that move at all.
His arms just like flail around.
Yeah.
This fight was absolute dogshit.
Somebody said, Demon's Souls had some real stinkers.
Yeah.
That was terrible.
Okay.
Dirty Colossus.
Which one was this?
Honestly, I don't even remember fighting this.
I'm gonna have to put this a D because I don't remember.
I don't even remember this being in the game.
Okay.
So, cool.
So, Storm King.
That was pretty gimmicky.
I don't think it's F though.
It's pretty stupid.
Leechmonger, F. Dirty Colossus.
I'm gonna give it an F too because I don't even remember playing it.
Or almost through Demon's Souls.
Where's Flame Lurker?
I remember Flame Lurker.
You know how I remember Flame Lurker?
Because I beat this first try.
And everyone was really, really confused that I was able to do it.
This fight was really bad, but just because I beat it first try does not mean it's a good
fight.
Let me get refreshed on this again.
This is the guy that had all the explosions.
He jumped around a lot, right?
Let's get some, let's refresh.
Yeah.
This thing jumps all over the place and explodes.
It's cool, but yeah, those explosions were so horrible.
Even though I did beat it first try.
Way too dank.
What?
Can't even hear anything.
I'm gonna keep it in B.
Maiden, Astria.
I don't remember this fight either.
And if I don't remember you, that means you're probably down on the list really low.
It's two.
Maiden, Astria, and Garl, Vinland?
What the fuck was this?
What?
I don't, how could you forget this?
I just need to refresh my memory before I can tell you.
I don't remember doing this.
Wait, what?
Hold on.
You just get, you just walk down here and just kill her?
This is, all right.
I don't know about this.
I don't think this deserves to be anywhere higher than C.
But wait a minute.
It's a story boss?
Okay.
What about the penetrator?
Penetrator?
Where's the penetrator?
Dude, there's no penetrator.
Did you go by another name?
I went over it?
Old monk, man eater, bullseidle.
Oh, penetrator.
Okay.
I'm stupid.
Oh, I remember.
Yeah.
This was fun.
Give me a link to the list?
I will in a second.
I mean, kind of forgettable, but still fun.
I summoned an NPC on accident.
Okay.
Old king.
All right.
I remember the old king was a good, was a cool fight.
It was for a quest.
This is one of the last fights in the game.
Mm-hmm.
This was cool.
This was an easy last boss, but I don't think it was a bad fight.
It was a fun fight.
Yeah.
This was cool.
I need to do something else later as well.
This grab lowers your soul level, right?
Cool.
Okay.
Any more refreshers that I need before I do the rest of demon souls?
Primeval demon, I think I need to see.
I'm going to need this especially with the demon soul stuff.
It's been a long time.
Did I go over it again?
Primeval demon.
I don't think this one's on here.
It's not an official boss.
Oh, I don't remember this one.
Turn the music off?
You never saw primeval demon.
Oh, shit.
Turn it up.
It only spawns if you fuck the world up enough.
All right.
Well, then I can't place it.
I'm just going to put it down at, um, I'll add a category that says, let's call it, um,
I don't know is the category, but I didn't do it.
All right.
Only a couple more that I need to remember, but let's actually, let's, let's go back to
this and do these ones.
Okay.
Do primeval demon.
I didn't do it.
That maiden fight was, I mean, if you want to talk about in the entirety of all of from
software running down a hallway and killing five or six regular enemies to kill this lady
that's sitting on the ground.
I don't think compares with, uh, like father gas coin.
Okay.
But is that better than the phalanx?
Yeah.
Is that better than storm king?
No.
Cleric beast is better than armor spider armor.
But as a joke.
All right.
Penetrator.
Was a good narrative.
Yeah.
I'll put this at C. All the, okay.
All the guy that has a sword in his hand, I'm probably going to all be C. I like this
fight.
I'm going to put it to be, it might change vanguard demon.
This is the, um, this is the asylum demon, right?
Yeah, it is.
Yeah.
I mean, it's Ron Majula.
Oh, you actually know I'll put on dark souls too.
It's got a great OST Ron Majula.
Yeah.
I'll do that.
Uh, vanguard is probably like D stardew valley.
Like, yeah, it doesn't fit, but nothing.
What does fit right now?
Okay.
Give me a sec.
Uh, where is it?
Majula.
Majula extended.
Ooh.
Okay.
All right.
This might be the best hub world music without, yeah, that's probably the best one.
Uh, vanguard demon is, I really want to put it in F, but it's a tutorial boss, so it kind
of can't be there.
I don't know.
What are you guys think?
It's a tutorial boss.
Should any tutorial boss be allowed to be over D?
I don't think so, but that's a better fight than the maiden fight.
The maiden fight is just, is, is a better, at least you actually fight.
Hmm.
I'll keep it here for now.
Oh, there's also regular King Alant, right?
I already know where I'm putting like half of these, by the way.
I just saw this and immediately wanted to put it like down here.
Okay.
What is, what's a regular Alant?
Well, let's, let's look at the rest of these.
Blue dragon, old King Alant, King Alant.
Was this the actual last fight?
I don't remember.
Wait, is this when you kill the, the thing in one hit?
Oh yeah, this was fucking stupid.
This was fucking stupid.
Why is he talking like the TikTok filter?
Oh, I don't know what I'm seeing.
Okay.
That's not a good fight.
I mean, so, um, what about blue dragon?
Blue dragon and red dragon.
Power Knight was kind of, eh, like all the giants in Elden Ring.
Oh yeah, you could go up top.
This was actually pretty fun.
Let me get some more gameplay here.
Yeah, this was cool.
I remember it was a pain in the ass to kill the, uh, this stuff up top.
How come it's so long?
I think this is the guy that took a long time to kill it.
Yeah, no, this is cool.
I remember this.
It was, it was intense.
It was exhilarating.
Uh, so the dragon, the dragons were not technically bosses.
I don't, did I fight them?
I don't remember.
At least I can do these ones at this point.
Okay.
King Alant is F, but it's a funny F. It's not like a zero, right?
Oh, you want to link, right?
Hold on.
This is the one I'm using right now.
I don't even, why did I have to turn the screen off for that?
Power Knight.
Okay.
Was Tower Knight better than Penetrator?
Yes.
Was Tower Knight better than Old Hero?
Was Tower Knight better than the Tibia Mariner?
Wait, actually, Tibia Mariner, I'm going to say no, I'll have to re, I have to think
about that again.
I just know what's going there.
So why not?
But Pinwheel, King, King Alant has to go all the way back here.
At least these are fights, but that's funny.
He makes funny sounds.
Oh, I'm going to burp.
That's the worst.
I think that actually might be the worst thing From Software has ever made.
I think so.
The Bed of Chaos, I think is truly just, they just mushed a bunch of stuff together and
just pressed it.
It's so awful.
It's just not even close.
I don't think.
The whole area was just, they just rushed through it as fast as possible.
That's probably the worst thing they've ever done.
I know that.
I'm going ahead.
I know.
The Mario slide?
Yeah.
I hated that shit.
Yeah, that's definitely where it belongs.
Okay.
Wait, let me, let's go back.
Let me, let's refresh.
Dragon God fucking blows.
Is that the one where it's just you, it's a cutscene, right?
This is a cutscene, boss.
Am I accurate on saying that?
I remember it's a cutscene.
Yeah, this is pretty awful.
It's the stealth one.
Yeah.
No, I remember that.
It was dumb.
Is it on the video?
Dragon God, right?
I think it was.
Yup.
Yeah.
He spits the fire everywhere.
Is this not even a boss?
He goes near bed of chaos.
Yes.
All right.
Yeah.
This is down here.
He's got one hit kills.
He looks cool.
I am taking coolness into consideration, but not that much.
It's definitely cooler than bed of chaos.
Okay.
So I know what that is.
Fool's idol.
Saw that down here, right?
What was this one?
Arch, right?
The floor traps.
Yeah.
This thing sucks too.
And again, another one of my big problems from software games, I don't like fighting
a boss in a corridor that is like there's one kind of straight line and a bunch of shit
in the way.
Yeah.
You can get stuck spell casting and like the midi file that is that laugh.
Okay.
What about the man eater?
We're almost done with Demon's Souls.
Oh yeah.
I remember this.
This sucked.
Oh my God.
Are no Demon's Souls bosses even remotely close?
I don't think a single Demon's Souls boss is going to make it out of B. Okay.
Don't you fight two?
Yeah.
All right.
This is F. Yeah.
This is like, it's absolutely F. You fight two of these.
It's stupid.
All right.
I think I can put these out.
Uh, man eater is F. Fool's idol is like D. Man, this looks bad.
I don't remember these two.
Maybe I'll refresh my memory later.
Am I happy with this?
No, I'm not.
Cause Godric was definitely way cooler than the flame lurker.
I got to get Demon's Souls in the right place.
Is Gwyn better than flame lurker when the Gwyn fight kind of sucks though.
It's I'm only doing it because I say, come on Gwyn, like all the time, like seven years
later.
All right.
Is Ebritas better than Gwyn?
Yes.
Is old knight Alant better than Gwyn?
They're kind of the same thing for me.
They like in the same spot.
They feel very close in my brain.
I think this is good for me.
Ebritas is cooler than flame lurker.
Was the Tibia Mariner cooler than the monk?
I don't want recency bias to ruin this list.
No, I don't think so.
Hour knight probably cooler than Tibia Mariner.
Old hero probably cooler than Tibia Mariner.
Penetrator definitely not.
Lyric beast better than Penetrator.
Armor spider is bad.
Okay.
I think I'm okay with this so far.
Godric is at least a low A. I'm thinking about it.
I don't, I think gas coin was cool than Godric.
At least for now.
Give us the list.
I put it, I already put it in chat.
It's already there.
I already put it there.
Am I too much of a big head?
Should I have like more space like here?
What do you guys think?
Right?
Like I'm just kind of like a big floating head.
Yeah, that's like better.
I'm like a person here now.
I'm not just like, okay, that's better.
All right.
Ornstein and Sma.
Um, am I happy with this?
We're, we're, for now I am.
Beta chaos, worst.
Dragon god's probably low as well, but the, he was cool looking.
Vanguard demon is better than that.
The D and F is just all demon souls fights.
I kind of feel bad, but unless something changes, I think that this is correct.
Definitely cooler than the flame lurker.
Not cooler than Ibrutas in a way.
All right.
Now we're into Dark Souls 1 stuff.
I need some refreshers.
I have them, but I do remember most of these.
Moonlight butterfly was pretty cool, but was it cooler than the Tibia Mariner?
I don't know.
They're kind of the same fight.
Let's get the Taurus demon out of the way because it's just going to be down here.
All right.
Taurus demon is probably, they're the same exact fight, so why not just put them in the
same place?
Sif was cool.
I think Sif might have to be up in A for now or maybe high B. I don't want to go too high
with Sif.
Wait, the Taurus, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
The asylum demon and vanguard demon are the same.
Not the Taurus demon is the one on the bridge, which that was okay.
Again, these two are just in the same exact category for me.
You're both on a bridge and you're both huge and you're both too big for the bridge.
This is the scorpion chaos witch, right?
The scorpion lady.
That was all right.
That didn't wow me, but it was okay.
The bell gargoyles were like, mm, they weren't great either.
Capra demon F. Even if that you beat that fight really easily, it's stupid.
It's a terrible fight.
Let's make a room as big as an apartment bathroom and you fight this fucking annoying thing
in it.
And there's two dogs here.
It's awful.
I actually liked gaping dragon.
I like when he goes all the way forward.
I don't know if it's a gaping dragon was a cool was cool.
It was a weird bus and weird.
It was a really weird fight.
He hates all these bosses.
No, I'm trying to be fair.
This is the one that just spams down the hall, right?
It's the fight is you just literally have to run down the hall with the magic.
The caster.
Yes.
This is F.
But it's F.
That's F.
F is going to need a lot of moving around because I'm going to have to kind of go one
by one.
Nito.
Actually, let me get the other because I have the Dark Souls one bosses to get those up.
I remember Nito with Nito summons a bunch of shit, right?
Where is it?
Let's look at it.
Nito was was interesting, right?
From what I remember.
I'm going to need this for a few of these does the undead guy come in here and he summons
a bunch of skeletons and you have to run around the circle and this guy actually has really
annoying moves.
Yeah.
He doesn't just chase you down.
This was horrible.
He's also in the worst area in the game.
I don't think this is F though.
I think the boss design is cool.
I mean, it's a big thing of melded together skeletons and summoned skeletons.
I think it was cool.
I don't think it belongs below C. I don't know if it goes below above B though.
Yeah.
Okay.
I remember that one.
The four kings.
This is the one where it's just pitch black, right?
This was all right.
The design of the boss carries this one.
The fight is F, but the design is like B.
So I think it's go somewhere in the middle.
Yeah.
This is stupid.
All right.
Demon.
Is this the one where it has the stupid thing that you just walk into?
I actually might put this below bed of chaos just because of how truly dumb this thing
was.
Yeah.
The Capra Demon takes three hits to kill.
There's nothing fun about this.
Art equals bad.
I mean, but objectively speaking, this area is stupid.
This boss is stupid.
Look, the person even making the video on let me show you the bosses is having trouble
with this because of how annoying this is.
And the guy in the video showing us this encounter is that he can't even do anything.
This is a way useful.
You fight this piece of shit.
He's gonna die.
Yeah.
You got to let him.
That's it.
That's what you do.
Yeah.
Okay.
My opinion is validated for myself.
The Demon Fire Sage.
This is the one that had the area was small and you'd walk backwards and fall directly
into the lava and die.
Right?
Because that was annoying.
The fights actually get the fight.
Yeah.
The fight's actually kind of fun though.
I wouldn't say it's a bad fight.
Demon Fire Sage.
Where the fuck is this?
I'm like halfway through the game, right?
Elgar Goyles.
Where is it?
The right?
Did I miss it again?
Am I still doing this?
War Kings pinwheel.
Cease.
Is it not ceaseless discharge?
No.
Read video description for timestamps.
But I mean, it's right here.
It's right here.
Like, how have I not seen it?
This shit's not even here.
I'm not gonna go look until I find it because I really don't think it's here.
Stray Demon?
It's not...
Oh, there it is.
Okay.
Ceaseless discharge is what I was thinking of.
This is just an Asylum Demon that has fire.
I'm gonna say pretty low.
It's probably better if I would put it above Asylum Demon because at least it's a different
thing.
He's on fire.
Yeah, okay.
I need Centipede Demon which is right here.
I don't remember this one.
I think a lot of the ones I don't remember I blocked out of my memory because I might
have hated them so much.
This guy almost just died instantly.
What the hell happened?
This guy's character looks like such a goofball.
Yeah, no, no, no.
It's coming back to me.
Because you have to put a ring on, right?
You need the lava ring.
Yeah.
Okay.
Cool.
I remember Seath.
Seath is, design-wise, I think is at least A.
It's such a weird, just kind of like gooey.
This fight was not fun though.
It was kind of sloppy.
I love the way this dragon looks.
This, eh, I don't think it's that bad.
It's a cool fight.
It's, well, the fight's not great, but it's not terrible.
Okay, yeah.
I'd say that goes somewhere in C.
Alright, Stray Demon.
This is the one that, after Stray Demon we'll do some placement, Stray Demons.
The one, okay, I don't think I even need to look at Stray Demon.
That's the one that you fall through the ground and it's just an Asylum Demon, right?
The surprising factor makes this kind of cool, but the actual boss is just another Asylum
Demon with a couple extra attacks, yeah.
Okay, I can do some placement.
I think I got it.
I got some placement here.
Uh, Nito's going up to C. Four kings are D. I-D though, for now.
Centipede team, uh, D. Do I even like these games?
Demon Fire Sage was, oh no, it was Seath.
Seath is like C. Stray Demon is like D. Demon's Fire Sage was
just, it's just another Demon.
How come the Storm King is so low?
I'm just trying to get things out.
This is a very hard thing to do.
Barely anything is above average right now.
I fucking hate From Software games, apparently.
I remember the DLC fights where, okay, this, the night.
I remember the night being really, really fun.
The night was really cool, actually.
This is one of those fights that I remember was cool.
Like I actually really enjoyed it.
Night, Artorias.
Let me just, let me refresh my memory.
This is the guy that uses one, the one hand to swing, right?
The one handed knight.
Yeah, this was awesome.
This is going at least today.
And you want to know why Gale is at S?
Because this fight, Gale was just kind of a cooler version of this fight.
I mean, let me refresh my memory.
All the cool swings with the one arm.
Yeah, this fight was awesome.
I mean, he's going to kill it in like fucking five seconds, but you know, with a thousand
damaged sorceries.
This was really fun though, I remember.
This was a dance.
This is one of those From Software fights where they got it really right because it
really does feel like a fencing match between the two characters.
That's why I like Horror Lou so much.
That felt like I was fighting that boss.
It was a back and forth dance.
That's why Horror Lou might actually be number one.
Okay, I know where that's going.
That's going up pretty high.
Sanctuary of Guardian, I think I hated, right?
It was just like this thing.
Yeah, don't you fight two of them too at some point as well and it's just annoying.
He's killing him so fast.
I just need refreshers.
That one was alright.
I remember being angry at the way you have to fight two, so that's kind of souring how
I feel about fighting the one.
Which I hope that doesn't happen with the Elden Ring bosses, because needing to fight
two of those godskin apostles was just, come on.
Fighting two of this thing was always just annoying, and it might sour.
Alright, I'm just checking the rest of the DLC.
We have Crossbreed Priscilla, I don't remember this.
Oh, I do remember this.
This is the invisible fight.
And it was awful.
Yeah, you fight the invisible character.
Yeah, come on.
Where is it?
Wait, what?
They just beat it in one hit?
Alright, we need the Dragon Calamite, and then Manus, and Iron Golem was alright.
Alright, what about the Dragon Calamite?
Yeah, this was cool.
You know what's going to be really, really sad though, for when this was a fun fight?
Oh my goodness, does it even hold a candle to even one of the dragon fights in Elden
Ring?
How do you put this even close to Placidix?
I don't know.
That's going to be hard.
Then let's round it out, Iron Golem, just so I can make sure I know.
It was pretty early, right?
It's so much better.
Better than the Overworld Dragons.
Yeah, that's true.
But that first encounter with Agil was ridiculous.
It's just kind of a tower knight, but maybe not as cool.
Yeah, it's another one of those things where I fight me on a tiny area.
Yeah, this is a D. Or like a high D.
Alright, it's time to place.
I got enough info.
Welcome back.
Uh, this is...
I mean, the fight is just, she's invisible.
Invisible.
How do you give that a high score?
I don't think it's worse than the Four Kings.
Sanctuary Guardian was cool, I'll get these right.
Dragon, I'm going to put in B for now, but just keep in mind that Ibritas is in B as
well.
B does not mean bad.
Oh, the Ceaseless Discharge, that thing, yeah.
This thing was like a C. That's where you fall, yeah, fuck that thing.
I didn't see Manus, did I?
No, did I see Manus?
Oh yeah, this thing was crazy.
Yeah, this thing was actually really cool.
It's just what all the Asylum Demons like wished they were as a fight.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, this is at least a B. Alright, Dark Souls 1 is a- I- we're gonna take a minute
here because I need to make sure these are in the right spot.
I'm gonna put this in B for now.
Dark Souls 2 is gonna be as hard as Demon's Souls because it's been a very long time since
I've played Dark Souls 2.
I'm actually probably gonna do that last.
So, let's begin.
Ornstein and Smog.
Was our Artorias cooler than Sif?
Was he more fun, more interesting?
I don't know.
Everybody, look, I know that From Software has put a like wolf or like an animal with
like a sword in his mouth.
I know they've done like the look it's a wolf enemy again like a thousand times.
But in Dark Souls 1, that first seeing that for the first time was really cool.
I'm gonna keep it there for now.
Is Ibritas better than Artorias?
God, I fucking love Bloodborne.
I just do.
I'm so biased.
It's awful.
Because the music, Ibritas' music is so cool.
That like, it's just such a, it's amazing.
Music in Bloodborne makes these bosses better.
That like, it felt like I was on a cosmic journey.
It's going up here.
This might change.
Gaping Dragon is probably not close to this.
You should play it.
Yeah!
Yeah, that's a good idea.
I don't know why I keep pressing that button.
I'm an idiot.
Here it comes.
Turn it up.
I'm gonna put both headphones in this because Ibritas might go higher.
Bloodborne's music is by far the best out of any of these games, without a doubt.
Wait for it.
Godric's music is good too.
And you know what makes a good song for me?
It's, I've figured it out.
Any of the bosses that have like the...
Ludwig has it.
Godric has it.
Ibritas has it.
They all have it.
Not the chorus.
Godric's music does this thing where it goes, is it a violin?
What's that instrument?
If it has a violin, I like it.
Okay.
Let's keep going.
I think these are in the right spot.
Gwyn is probably...
Flame Lurker and Gwyn are like this.
Like these are all like the same fight.
Doesn't really matter.
This is cooler.
This is cooler than Flame Lurker.
Ornstein and Smog was probably...
Yeah.
Slave Knight Gael's music was amazing.
Oh yeah, it was.
Ludwig's music is the best, without a doubt.
Nothing compares.
What about Medir?
Alright, let's get this right.
That looks good.
Gaping Dragon is in a good spot.
I think Gaping...
Gwyn's probably...
Gaping Dragon, I don't know.
It's so hard to tell.
I just...
I think Ibritas is cooler than Sif.
I do.
Alright.
Go down here.
Four Kings is better than this.
I'm going to put this pretty low.
I so badly want to put the Armor Spider lower, but I don't think I can.
This sucked.
I almost feel like somebody needs to level up here.
I don't know which one's going to level up.
These are all the same.
Xenopy Demon, what's the worst out of all of these?
Probably these, right?
Yeah, Junk Decatur's so bad.
It's going down here too.
I just got a baby formula add?
I don't know how you fucking got that.
Was the Penetrator that bad of a fight?
Or was it just kind of like...
I feel like it doesn't belong down there.
It was a regular enemy.
I think it should be.
I mean, it was still...
It's cooler than the Four Kings.
The Four Kings is just a pitch black room and they teleport next to you.
I'm alright with this for now.
Now for Bloodborne, I am not going to need to do any...
I don't need to refresh at all for Bloodborne.
I know all of these by heart.
Maybe some of them I might want to just take a quick look at.
So we're going to skip Dark Souls 2 for now.
Because Dark Souls 2, that's going to take us the longest time, I think.
Yeah, I'll remember you.
Yeah, it's better that way.
It's more fun.
So let's open up...
Let's get Bloodborne up here.
Because Dark Souls 1 is complete.
Nobody from Dark Souls 1 got to S.
Bloodborne, Dark Souls 3, and Elden Ring all have a representative up here at S.
Dark Souls 1 does not.
Is that fair?
I think so.
Okay.
Bloodborne time.
So if you remember from Bloodborne, Leric Beast is already up there at S.
Eh, I think that's fine where it is.
So we've got the one Reborn, which I believe this fight was...
I wasn't a big fan of it, but let's refresh our memory.
There's the big blob enemy, right?
Yeah, this is just a huge blob.
This thing was annoying.
This is probably going to be one of the lower ones.
Okay, let's put it up here.
I don't know where Rom's going to go.
Rom's area and Rom's scariness was there, but nothing else for me.
Yeah, this fight was...
I didn't like this.
I actually didn't really like this area that much either.
The thing to swing...
All of its extremities were just always attacking, and it was no opportunity to do anything.
Just spit a bunch of...
Yeah, this thing was...
Yeah, this is one of the worst bosses in the game.
F?
Yeah, I agree.
I agree.
Oh no, F for frames.
Oh, come on.
Really?
I was just going so good for a while.
Why does Twitch hate my connection?
Why, Twitch, why do you hate my connection?
What did I do?
Write it out for a sec.
Are we alright?
I think we're okay.
I wish I had a solution.
If I open...
If I do a speed test right now, it'll be perfect.
I don't get it.
What?
Why is everybody Omega lowing?
Why is everybody...
Why was there so many Omega lows?
There was a lot.
Is it the bitrate?
No, it's not...
The bit...
It's just...
I'm losing packets to Twitch.
The only service it's happening to.
And I think it's okay.
I don't know.
Alright, yeah, but I do agree with you though.
I think the one Reborn should be F, if not very close.
I'll put it at low D for now.
The music's gotta change as well here.
That was cool for a little bit, but let's get that off.
Something else.
Anything else you guys want to put up?
Any songs?
Why is everybody saying Omega low?
Firelink Shrine?
Yeah.
We'll do some Melodin Ring as well.
Okay, let's put that down.
Let's do some more refreshing, please.
I'd like if we could do some more refreshing.
Alright, that's the one Reborn.
Awful.
Let's do...
You already know these ones.
Blood Star Beast was not a flashy fight, but it was interesting at least.
It was hard.
You could make this fight really trivial if you have an item, and then the fight is essentially
a free boss kill.
You're making shit up?
What?
I'm not making shit up.
You throw one of those skulls into the wall and the Blood Star Beast just goes and attacks
it and you just get like a thousand damage for free.
Five thousand.
Alright, what about some other ones I need?
I liked Vicar Emilia's fight.
This was really cool.
Nobody tell him.
What?
What happened?
Why are you guys doing this to me?
What's going on?
I don't know.
Are they just trolling?
Yeah, this fight was really, really intense.
It was scary too.
Witches of Hemwick.
This is F. It's one of those just there's four or five of them just standing in corners
just kill them.
Yeah, this fight was awful.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Let me wait.
What else do we need a refresher on?
Shadows of Yharnam.
This fight was another just three enemies in the same room.
I did it with the snakes though, right?
This was actually pretty cool.
I don't know if this is going higher than like a B or a C, but I think it belongs somewhere.
It was easy.
I don't remember this being that easy.
I thought this was kind of a pain in the ass.
They turn into a snake.
That was really cool.
Did they show that part?
Yeah.
Right there.
Ah, this fight's cool.
I like it.
Who else do we need?
Rom was all right.
Rom was cool because of the area.
The fight was stupid.
Okay.
Rom did this really annoying thing where if Rom rolled, it did this kind of roll, roll
move where he would spin around and it killed you in one hit.
It was stupid.
Okay.
This fight was kind of disappointing.
The Amigdala fight, this was a disappointment for me.
I remember these are the things, like you're so scared of these things the entire game
and it's just kind of a boring fight.
It just shoots lasers.
This fight wasn't as scary as the enemy was hanging around.
Does it have the laser move?
Maybe that'll help.
Hmm.
Eh.
It's all right.
You know that one, this is the electricity monster, which I'll give you a refresher.
By the way, if you haven't played any of these games, you probably shouldn't be watching
this stream because you're just getting spoiled on every single enemy.
This was okay too.
I wouldn't put it very high, but cool.
Okay.
Artir Lugarius.
Oh, this is the old guy.
Right.
This, I actually liked this fight.
Yep.
I actually liked this one a lot.
He was cool.
You cried here?
I didn't stream Bloodborne.
I played it on my own.
This is before I was a streamer.
It was a camera fight.
Yeah, he was rough, but I still feel like he was fun to play against.
Okay.
I'm going to turn off the fucking...
I feel like I am idling right now in Dark Souls.
I'm just sitting at the bonfire at the Firelink Shrine and it's driving me fucking crazy.
I feel like I want to alt tab and close the game.
We don't need a soundtrack for right now.
We're good.
We can change it when we need to.
Okay.
Let's keep going.
All right.
Well, we have our audio right here.
Celestial Emissary?
This is bad.
Fuck, man.
Is there a lot of Bloodborne bosses that are like D?
I might surprise myself a lot because this is absolutely like D or lower.
If you guys see me put the deacons higher than this, if they're not on the same line,
this whole list is wrong.
Yeah.
Okay.
That...
It's Ibritas, by the way.
You're wondering why I like it so much.
The thing is just so crazy looking and so cool.
Look at this thing.
It's so crazy.
Crazy!
And it goes like...
Okay.
Yeah.
Wait.
Hold on.
Here comes the music.
I want to hear the music one more time.
Here it comes.
Come on.
Don't kill the boss before we hear it.
I...
This game ran like shit.
Yeah, it did.
It's not even going to play the music.
Fuck it.
Whatever.
Micolash, this fight was an F, but his funny voice lines make it like a C. You chase him
around this mist area, and he goes like, oh, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
Yeah, this was...
I hated this.
Those of you who were asking if this changes, no, this is the whole fight.
You just follow this guy around a maze, and he laughs at you and says, yeah, this fight
is like a D. You can't put this higher than C because this is the fight.
You're watching the whole thing.
You just run behind this guy like a fucking recess.
You're like tag.
And sometimes shit just gets in the way.
No.
Look at how long this one is.
The longest one.
Ooh, Mergo's Wet Nurse was cool because the music was creepy.
I liked it.
That fight is F. Stop the blood-borne bias.
That's true.
This thing was creepy.
I liked it.
Okay, yeah, I know where that goes.
Undead Giant?
What is this fight?
I didn't do this one.
Merciless Chieftain?
Who is Merciless Chieftain?
Ah, these are from the Chalice Dungeons, okay.
I didn't do any of these.
Watchdog of the Old Lords, another Chalice Dungeon.
Eh.
Eh, I didn't play it.
Yeah, I didn't do it.
Eh.
No.
No?
I skipped over the Chalice Dungeons stuff.
It's kind of funny, they turned the Chalice Dungeons into the dungeons in Blood Elden Ring.
Very similar.
Almost the exact same setup.
Oh, that's pretty cool.
Wow, I skipped almost all of this.
Alright, okay.
It's time for you to see the re- It's time for you to see.
This is the best boss that From Software has ever made.
Without a single doubt, by far.
Bloodborne also has the best DLC in many of the games as well.
Actual fake fan?
I did some of them, I just don't remember them.
So, if I remember, this boss is fucking dumb.
Boy, it's just like, you've given this, uh, in Dark Souls 1 bosses like this, in Demon
Souls bosses like this, you gave this like a B, like a C or a D.
I'm sorry.
You're gonna have to, you're gonna have to wait a second.
You're gonna have to wait a second.
Okay, now we'll watch.
Turn it up.
Wow, you're fighting this like beast and he's scary and he's fucked up.
Pretty cool.
What's happening?
What's going on here?
Shh.
Quiet, we're watching.
What's happening?
There he is.
Now the real fight begins.
Why, why, why, Bat Chest, what?
You guys are all haters and that's fine.
That's fine, you can be a hater, that's the best, this is the best encounter that From
Software has ever made and I'm gonna tell you, Horror Lou is close.
It's gonna be, I'm gonna need some Jeopardy music because, I don't know, that's the coolest
fight in the fucking entire game.
Not only in the whole game, in the whole franchises that they've ever had.
Bat Chest.
And I'll tell you, immediately following this boss is one of the worst bosses that
they put in the DLC.
Sorry, I just, hopefully I didn't hurt your ears.
Uh, Lawrence is just Cleric Beast on fire, we've seen them use this technique before.
And this fight was dumb.
Just Cleric Beast that is on fire.
We've seen them do this a few times.
There's a Ludwig Funko pop.
And I, you know, that sound, it's kind of overdone.
Living Failures, this is bad too.
This is the same fight from, yeah, this is really bad too.
I heckin' love Lud, yeah, I heckin' love Ludwig.
That's fine.
This is so bad.
It's so unfortunate because this area is one of the coolest DLC areas of any From Software
game.
But the boss at the end of it is dogshit.
Now we're getting into the Riddiel shit here.
Hard equals bad?
No, just putting like, just small enemies that just spawn over and over again, you know,
I don't know.
Just place around just enemies and kill them, like deacons.
I don't like the deacon fight either, I thought it was horrible.
This fight was crazy as well.
Not only that, this was a, I believe a three-phase fight.
Lady Maria was, I'm gonna say it, probably the, mmm, did you just say, did you say bootleg
millennia?
No, I'm sorry, this is actually a good encounter.
This is actually a really cool encounter and a really fun encounter.
This is high up there.
The only reason why I don't know if I want to put this at S is because the, it's, it's
just a long fight and the second, the second phase and third phase, whatever, um, it just
takes a long time to get there.
It's millennia with a gun.
Oh, it is not?
It's not bootleg millennia!
Maria came first!
Don't you understand?
Check this out.
Oh, no, no, no, now you fucked up.
Now you got to phase three.
What makes millennia bad other than that she's hard?
The waterfall dance is the stupidest move in any game they've ever made.
Just dodge it?
I don't care.
I don't like it.
Yeah.
This is now, this is a fight if I've ever seen one.
All right.
We all know where that is.
Orphan.
Oh yeah.
Orphan's design is, I don't know.
He kind of looks like one of the nobles in Elden Ring with like a big sack.
This fight was so hard, but he just screams.
Yeah, he just loves cartoons like Tom and Jerry screams.
I'm gonna put it at B. I don't think it's S.
Yeah.
That sounds like you.
No, it doesn't.
I'm not going to do this great.
All right.
We know what this is.
These are huge like spoilers, guys.
Like if you haven't played these games, what are you doing here?
Garamond's fight is awesome.
In fact, Garamond might actually be S. Garamond I think actually is S.
This fight felt, I remember, I remember when doing this and being like, yo, this is really,
this is really happening right now.
It was just like, holy shit.
I am playing Bloodborne right now.
This is happening.
Yeah.
This was so cool.
And then when he goes, I mean, my bitrate is probably awful right now, but the scythe
is, he's got a gun, play the cut scene.
I don't want to spoil the whole game.
There's tons of people that didn't play this.
It's only on PS4.
What a shame.
Okay.
So this is the actual major spoiler coming up.
I mean, like absolute true major spoiler.
This is like literally the final end of the whole game, like just to let you know.
The moon presence, which I thought was all right.
I didn't love it.
I can't say I particularly enjoyed this that much.
Cooler than Ludwig?
No, I don't think so.
It's ultra mid mega C. Yeah.
It's a lot.
That's a lot of this.
It's a big dash that moon presence does.
That's really annoying.
It's not Garamond.
All right.
I think I'm ready.
I believe I'm ready to do to place all the Bloodborne characters.
Some of these are going to shock you.
Blood Starved Beast is a C. Blood Starved Beast is better than Tibia Mariner.
I don't think it's better than the old hero or Nito.
Nito is the kind of C plus for me.
Micolash, Host of the Nightmare.
This is D. I mean, it's F. So let's go ahead and put it there the way that we're, we've
got to do this for real.
Characters cool.
The fight is just annoying.
It's voice lines are cool, but I'll look.
Is it better than the one reborn?
I don't think it is.
Is it better than Pinwheel?
Pinwheel actually probably should be here.
It's better than Pinwheel.
Is it though?
Because at least with Pinwheel you get Pinwheel over with very quickly.
Micolash takes a long time.
You just chase him around.
You get it over with.
Um, I cannot place Mergo's Wet Nurse yet.
I can place Amigdala.
This is a C. Martyr Lugarius is, I don't think it's A. I think it's B somewhere, but I'll
get it right.
Airman is A. I don't know if it...
Let me get it in the right spot before anybody freaks out.
Moon Presence, Super Ultra Omega C.
Living Failures, F. Are they better than, uh, no.
The Witches of Hemwick, this is a D. Although it maybe should, I don't know, how many Bloodborne
bosses are bad?
Alright, Lady Maria.
Lady Maria is coming up to A. Um, Lawrence, high D. Where's Cleric Beast?
They both, I mean they're both the same exact thing.
They're fine.
Orphan?
I don't know, I'm gonna be honest with you, the final boss of Bloodborne, being just kind
of like a naked guy screaming, it was like, I get it, I understand the lore, I understand,
I get it.
But I don't think it was, I don't think so.
I have to consciously put this higher than the Flame Lurk, than Gwyn.
I mean, was it, probably what, Gwyn maybe shouldn't be this high.
It's not, it's not better than Lugarius, I had more fun with Lugarius.
I'm gonna keep it there for now.
Something that's high, from C. Alright, Vicar Emilia, I'm gonna say B.
Celestial Emissary, somewhere down in F, or D, whatever, it's just, no.
Virgo's Wet Nurse, I'm gonna go low B for now.
Arl, C. Shadows of Yharnam, high C. I did not do these ones, so we're gonna put them here.
I know, dude, your favorite game, your favorite game is Bloodborne, and you have not done
any of these.
I didn't, none of them.
Okay, that's my favorite game ever made, and I didn't do any of these.
They were hidden deep in all these Chalice Dungeons, I just, I didn't really like the
Chalice Dungeons.
Okay, we are getting there, we're getting there.
Let's go ahead and get these out of the way, because all the Elden Ring ones are in memory.
So let's get the Bloodborne stuff in the right place, and then we'll do Elden Ring.
Alright, Father Gascoigne, A+, Rodrik, yep, Maria, I think that's fine where it is, although
I think they're better than these.
I gotta knock down Sif a little bit here.
Orphan, Legarius was cooler than all these.
What a great game.
Ah, alright, so Legarius, better than Ornstein and Smog, Koss was, I mean, Old King, I mean,
I don't know, Caping Dragon, better than that, Flamelurker.
Did you play the game?
That's one of my favorite games of all time!
Well, I didn't do the extra side dungeons, that doesn't matter.
Oh, guess what, I think Super Mario 64 is one of my favorite games.
I didn't ever get 120 stars, I got like 80!
Do I need to get everything?
You missed half the bosses, I didn't miss half the bosses!
Alright, I think this is fine where it is.
I actually don't think this is better than this.
I think Gascoigne was better than Garamond because, I don't know, I thought, Gascoigne
is like one of my favorite characters in that game, you're a fraud.
I didn't do any of this, the challenge dungeons were confusing, I just played the game.
I beat this game, okay.
I beat Bloodborne, god, like probably ten times, and I never did any of the Chalice
dungeons.
They were annoying, it was like, they were all the same, they were all the same, dungeon
just randomized, I didn't like it, I didn't want to do it.
But it's fine.
Okay.
Moon, okay.
Shadows of Yharnam, Wetners, I think this is fine up here.
Blood Starve Beast, definitely not cooler than the Tibia Mariner, or definitely better
than the Valgar Goyles, because like, those things are stupid.
Horus Demon as well.
A lot of Cs all in a row here.
I think Omigdala is better than, I don't think it's cooler than Seath.
At least Seath looked kind of weird.
Moon Presence was probably better than this.
Yeah, these all have to come up.
Like, Penetrator is just a guy with a sword, it's not like a huge deal.
Hmm, these are F.
Micolash is probably the worst of the four, just because I just, chasing him around was
annoying.
Why the fuck is the Tibia Mariner above the Moon Presence?
I'm working on this, okay?
This is, I'm working on it.
I need to make sure.
There's a lot of creatures here.
The Tibia Mariner is cooler.
I think so.
I think the Tibia Mariner is cooler than the Moonlight Butterfly.
The Moon Presence is just, yeah, the Moon Presence is cooler than the, yeah, that's
true.
Yeah.
I don't think, I think this is the wall.
This is the wall.
To graduate to C+, you have to be cooler than the Tibia Mariner, which seems like apparently
a pretty big feat.
This is the wall.
You have to be cooler than the Tibia Mariner.
Or, excuse me, you're not getting any exclusive C++.
Is the Moon Presence cooler than the Tibia Mariner?
Fight-wise, mechanics-wise, looks-wise?
No.
Are any of these motherfuckers cooler than the Tibia Mariner?
Shit, somebody might be, hold on.
I gotta make sure I get this right.
Rom might be cooler than the Tibia Mariner.
Do you know what I mean?
I think we, I think Rom graduates.
Quelaag might be cooler than the Tibia Mariner.
Absolutely no way the Taurus Demon, Bell Gargoyle, Butterfly, Seath is definitely cooler than
all these though.
Alright, very important.
Is Seath the Scaleless cooler than the Tibia Mariner?
Yes.
Alright, I think we're good.
One Reborn at least is a fight.
This is going up here, Pat, I mean, this is just, there's stuff that I don't want to put
in F because I don't want to have F be crowded, because I want to at least pretend like I
like these games.
So I can't just put all these things in F. I don't think this belongs down here.
This is definitely cooler than this.
Capra Deep, what's the worst thing?
Dirty Colossus is not the worst thing.
Dead of Chaos is probably the worst.
And I gotta be honest, so is the Celestial Emissary is not even a boss fight.
You fight like three dozen of those little like bug alien people and then it ends.
This actually could be the worst.
Dirty Colossus is just, it's not bad, it's just boring.
Living Failures belongs down here too.
I didn't like these at all, they were terrible.
I'm trying to get it right.
Capra Demon is probably the coolest out of all of these.
I think this is accurate.
I think I got it.
Dirty Colossus should be in, no, not F, right?
If I'm going to put Dirty Colossus in F, then all the Asylum Demons have to be in F.
Same thing with the Maneater.
Dirty Colossus is going up and so is Maneater.
And we're going to bring all these Asylum Demons down.
This is looking a lot better.
Way better than it was before.
Centipede Demon is definitely cooler than this.
Just put the two bugs next to each other, who cares?
Iron Golem is going down here too.
Who cares?
You're at least a fight, this goes here.
You're at least a fight, you go there.
This is hard.
I think I'm good for Bloodborne.
I don't know if I want to put any of these at S.
I have to reliably say that was one of the coolest, that was awesome.
That was unbelievable.
I'm going to leave it for now.
I think I like Godric more than Maria.
I like Godric more than Gascoigne.
Oh shit, no I don't.
That's recency bias.
Alright, let's do Elden Ring, because I can do these quick.
Elden Ring, I can do it really quick.
Here we go.
Uh, Mog.
We just did it, I don't need any refreshers.
Mog is going to be up at C, or B, for now.
Probably here.
Wait, is Mog cooler than the Tibia Mariner?
Yes, absolutely.
Mimic Tear, it's a comedy boss, so it's just going in D.
I don't think it's F, it means it's close.
Also, Rikard, okay, Rikard was a gimmick fight, but was a really cool design boss, it's going
to go B.
Do we need some music or something?
Uh, yeah, we can put something on.
D, I'm just getting him in the general area.
This is not, we're not done completely, hold on.
It's got to be in the general area.
I can hear myself breathing.
I'm working on it.
How about, um, it's a good OST.
Bugsnax?
No, it doesn't fit.
Mario 64, yeah sure.
No, that doesn't fit either.
That's going to annoy me, I know it will.
Halo?
Hmm, Hollow Knight.
Yeah, that sounds fun.
Okay, because we're not watching any Elden Ring stuff.
There you go, now we can not freak out.
So, uh, Godskin Noble, that's the fat one, right, or is that the skinny one?
Fat?
I actually like that a lot.
That was a cool fight.
But, I don't know, I kind of, they used it too much.
Don't you feel like it was kind of used a little too much?
I'm going to put it down to C just because I feel like they used this too much.
This character appears in the game like four times.
Three times?
Yeah, but I mean, it's like, I don't know, I feel like there wasn't too many places.
I'm going to keep it here for now.
Um, actually, I could probably do some of the Sekiro ones too, get off of memory.
Alright, we got Elder Dragon Grail.
This is the one that you just put a bleed weapon on and kill it, right?
It doesn't really attack back?
I mean, is this really a boss?
Or is this just kind of like a set piece that dies?
Eh, eh.
Yeah.
It's F.
F, but no, I don't think it deserves to be an F.
Or Dan?
F?
Uh, Regal Ancestor Spirit, I like that a lot.
That was a lot of fun.
It's going to be for now.
Uh, we've got the gargoyles, which I feel like I would have been kind of, I'm going
to make a statement here.
All the, it's two enemies in the same room boss.
Those are all at least a C or lower.
They just are.
Like, we just put two in the room.
Eh.
Uh, Dragonkin Soldier of Noxtela, did I do this?
Oh, and these are the dragon soldiers.
They kind of overused these two, but they were interesting.
C.
B is champions.
These were bad.
Alright, this is, this is the Godfrey Shade, which is probably somewhere in the high sea.
Maybe not.
I got to, that's going to take a lot of looking.
Okay, Astel, Natural Born of the Void, this, I liked this one a lot.
Astel's going up to at least high B.
We'll, we'll sort it.
We'll sort it.
Some of these have to get, you have to graduate these to A, you don't just put it in A, unless
you're certain.
Margit.
Margit and Morgoth are going to be next to each other, because they're the same person.
If one fights, it's a lot harder.
Margit.
It wasn't that, it was alright, it was okay.
I think it's like a B.
And Morgoth, it's kind of unfortunate.
I'm going to have to put this down here.
Morgoth goes down and I don't know, because I didn't kill him.
I summoned the Mimic Tear before the nerf and it killed him in less than 15 seconds.
I don't even know what that guy does.
I have no idea what Morgoth's moves are.
Mimic Tear killed him in 10 seconds.
And it was at that moment that I said, I'm not going to use the Mimic Tear again, unless
I need to.
I got one attempt in, but I didn't really even fight this boss.
Commander Nihil.
Commander Nihil was the one with the summons, with the electronic lightning prosthetic,
right?
I don't know.
Bulled and Margit?
Maybe.
But the Ancestral Spirit I thought was a really cool fight.
It'll be here for now.
Why is Rodan so low?
I hated that fight.
It was stupid.
I don't like it.
I don't like it at all.
It was one of the worst.
This one was cool too, but then they started using this as a regular enemy and it kind
of took the magic away from me.
But I would say at least like a B-.
Borey.
Okay, these are dragons.
We'll leave the dragons for now.
Fire Giant.
I would have loved to have been able to see the Fire Giant, but it actually was a pretty
cool fight.
Especially the cutscene and then the second phase.
It's going to stay here for now.
Hard equals bad.
Wait, when did they say that?
What are you talking about?
All right, which one of these down here is hard?
Let me tell you.
This fight you can kill in one hit if you really want to.
This is not hard.
This is a gimmick.
These are tutorial fights.
And this is a gimmick.
How are these hard?
Oh, you're talking specifically to Rodan.
Rodan is staying at F. Rodan, that's not a hard fight.
It's a dumb fight.
And that was pre-nerf, which was even worse.
And let's make everybody angry just because they'll get out of the way.
Mog, Lord of Blood.
Wait, didn't I already put Mog?
Where's Mog?
Didn't I put Mog?
Mog?
Mog the Omen.
Mog.
All right, well, whatever.
It's the same thing.
We never fought the other one.
Oh, whatever.
It's just in the same place then.
Gold skin duo.
I mean, all right.
C-.
Dragon Lord, Placidusix.
Dragon Lord, Placidusix is very high.
I think we've got our first A, at least, besides Godric.
Yeah.
Dragon Lord and Godric are pretty close.
I think Dragon Lord is cooler, though.
Dragon Lord is cooler than Gaspine.
I have to be fair.
Nope.
Rinala.
Rinala was like C, C-plus, maybe.
Better than that.
It was just kind of the magic spam fight, right?
All right.
Malekith.
Malekith was not, I don't know.
I feel like, did I have a lot of complaints about Malekith?
I think I did.
I love that clergyman.
I love that beast clergyman.
Really cool design.
We're going to use that part.
Design-wise, really cool.
I think it's a good spot for it for now.
Oh, Gideon.
I'll be all knowing, of course.
D.
Maybe D-plus.
That's better than the Four Kings.
Leone, Misbegotten.
These are the kind of lion, wolf, people with the sword.
They weren't bad.
They were, I mean, they were used a lot.
Kind of like, I would put it in the same categories.
I'm going to put high C, low B.
The bosses that they just kind of made regular enemies like five times.
I think that is fair.
These might come down.
Gideon deserves better.
We'll see.
Hold on.
It's above comparing to the other games.
Loretta?
This is going to surprise a lot of you guys.
I may have just gotten like 10 unsubscriptions in a row.
I really liked that fight.
I thought it was really cool.
That fight didn't feel annoying.
It was kind of challenging.
The dodging the magic and the spear with the horse.
You can't get on the horse.
I liked it a lot.
What music is playing?
Don't tell me what this is.
I forgot what the OST is.
Don't tell me.
Hollow Knight.
Um, we got Ancient Hero of Zamor.
Oh, some of these are the jail.
Deathbird.
Oh yeah, I remember that.
I hated that.
Soldier of Godric?
Just a regular enemy?
Why is it Soldier of Godric?
Deathbird.
Put the death magic on the ground.
This is a D.
Melania.
Blade of Micola.
Worse than Soldier of Godric.
Radagon and Eldenbeast together.
This is a mid-C.
Gave you my reasoning.
Oh, Scream is dying again.
Interesting.
Very interesting.
I don't get it.
That makes sense.
Like, um, I don't get it.
My internet's fine.
Why?
So as I was saying.
I just like almost swallowed it and choked.
Melania is F.
This reminds me of the Cox days.
Here's the thing though.
If I run a speed test right now, it'll be 1,000, 1,000.
I could go watch like a 4K movie while the stream is dying.
It's not my internet.
It's not, it's not the internet.
It's some, the connection that this internet.
But I have two Twitch's servers.
Sometimes it just gets fucked.
Just gets fucked up.
While that was happening, I, I did a test.
While that was happening.
Not a single solitary problem.
When it was happening during the Fortnite tournament thing.
I was in the call.
And they were, I had green bars on Discord.
Everything was normal.
I don't get it.
Doesn't make any sense.
Speed test does not equal stability.
Well, then I should have dropped out of the Discord call.
I looked over here and I went, I went to zero a couple of times during that Fortnite tournament.
And it was green bar.
Perfect connection on Discord and to Fortnite.
I didn't get kicked out of Fortnite.
I was in it the whole time.
You know what I mean?
The routing issue between the ISP and Twitch.
It has to be.
There's nothing, there's like nothing I can really do.
The only thing I can do is I can contact Twitch.
And just be like.
Yo.
Um.
What's happening?
Like what?
Can you look at my connection and see like what's going on?
Because on my end, nothing is wrong.
But before, when I used to have internet problems all the time.
That was a me problem.
That was like.
I was dropping packets.
My internet browser wouldn't even open.
The speed test would be like 0.5 up and like 0.2 down.
So it's not this time.
It's not the internet this time.
It's something to do with the routing to Twitch.
Who knows?
Anyways.
That was a.
I don't think Millenia.
Obviously let's be, I'll be fair.
Millenia I think was somewhere up here.
Hard equals bad.
Yes, hard equals bad.
Some of these were just kind of the little mini bosses, which I don't know if they should be on here.
Magma worm was kind of cool.
I actually liked that fight.
I'll stick with this for now.
For now.
Ancestor Spirit and Regal Ancestor Spirit.
I'm going to put the same spot.
Kind of the same fight.
But the Regal one was upgraded a little bit.
Where is it?
Right here.
A Ulcerated Tree Spirit.
They used this a lot.
It was cool the first few times.
It's not going to be F.
It's going to be like C.
Somewhere around with the dragonkin there.
Regal had the big heal.
That was fine.
You should put Radan higher.
I probably will.
Alright.
The Tree Sentinel was...
I know they did it a few times, right?
But.
That fight was really cool.
Because the first time you see the Tree Sentinel.
It's almost like, holy shit.
There's a boss right there.
And that's the first time you have to do any horseback fighting if you wanted to.
And it was really intense.
I like it there for now.
We'll see in a minute.
Hatches.
Eh.
I wouldn't really call this a boss fight as much as an NPC encounter.
But whatever.
I'm going to make a new category here.
For mini bosses.
I don't think it should be on here.
I'm going to make a category for mini bosses.
And that's it's own category.
Yeah.
That's a good idea.
Mini boss.
That's better.
Okay.
So.
Mini bosses.
Because these are going to just...
It's going to get all gummed up.
It is.
This just doesn't belong here.
Right?
This is going to get all gummed up.
And I don't want it to.
Tree Spirit.
That was a mini boss.
Technically.
It's going to get all gummed up.
Who else is a mini boss?
Tibia Mariner belongs down there.
Tibia Mariner I don't think deserves to be down there.
Hmm.
I mean very clearly we know what a mini boss is.
Right?
Like the Crystillion.
That's a mini boss.
I'm just going to get them up here and they'll do it.
Dragonkin Soldier is kind of a mini boss.
Wouldn't it?
The Ancient Hero of Zamor.
That's a mini boss.
There are like five Tibia Mariners.
That's true.
Future...
Oh yeah.
All the tree avatars.
Okay.
Do you really think that Sanguine Noble is something that should be up on the boss list?
I don't think so.
Runebear is not a boss.
I know.
I know that they show up everywhere.
Royal Knight Loretta.
This is the same fight.
Just a little bit different.
I actually liked the first one more.
I'm going to put it up.
Beasts of Farum Azula.
About here.
Mini boss.
All the dragons are mini bosses.
Mini bosses.
They're going up in the same place.
Percival Knight.
Mini boss.
The second one is way better.
I liked the first one better.
I don't know why.
Our Urchary Avatar is times five.
Times three.
Times two.
Times...
Yeah.
Times two.
Percival Knight.
Yeah.
Wraith Worm.
This is technically a mini boss, right?
Technically.
Miranda the Blighted Bloom.
I don't even know what this was.
Percival Knight Duo.
I don't even know what that is.
Kindred of Wrought Duo.
Did I do those?
I think so.
Elber of the Briar.
I don't know what that is.
Fortisax is really cool.
That's going to pie on the mini boss list.
Wait.
Was Fortisax a mini boss?
Kind of, right?
No, it hadn't...
No, no, no, it wasn't.
But I just was so overleveled it felt like one.
It was a really, really cool fight though.
I just killed it in like not even a minute.
Oh, I remember Necromancer Garrus.
The Red Wolf of the Champions.
Yep.
That's a mini boss.
Spirit Caller Snail.
Did I fight that?
Mad Pumpkin Head.
Nox Duo.
I didn't do that.
Hezgar...
Well, that's not the right game.
Lienrot Knight Duo.
I don't think I did that either.
The Demi-Human Queen.
Three of them.
I think I did one of these.
Eve of Fire.
Did I do that?
I don't remember.
There's so many bosses I don't remember.
I remember the Crystalline Duo.
I remember Wyrmface.
Wyrmface was kind of a...
Was a real boss though.
Not really.
Did you even play Elden Ring?
Dude, I streamed all...
Yes.
Flying Dragon?
Commander O'Neil.
Didn't I already do this?
Was it a different person?
Featured avatars.
Yep.
Put them up there as well.
It's going to be way too hard to put these anywhere remotely up with all the regular
bosses, in quotes, right?
It just is.
Battle Mage Hughes?
Rafted Sion?
I don't know.
Did I fight this?
You're not doing a Tireless.
You're doing a shitty From Software wiki.
You have to put them up here.
I gotta put them up here first.
What do you mean?
There are like 300 squares in this.
This is not a wiki page.
This is a list of my favorite bosses throughout the whole series.
We haven't...
I have to get them up here.
There are 10 Knight's Calvaries?
Holy shit.
I didn't fight that.
I did fight the Falling Starbeast.
But not these ones.
Did I?
Where is it?
Yes.
Super Falling Starbeast, right?
That's when I fought.
Is that a miniboss?
These are minibosses?
Sentinel Tree Bob?
Brave Warden Flying Dragon?
You know what?
All the minibosses are on the same fucking level.
Okay.
There's too many.
And I didn't even do like a third of these.
So, minibosses are just...
Whatever.
We just delete it.
Yeah, just delete it.
Yeah.
I just delete it.
No.
All the minibosses, we're not even gonna put them.
Who cares?
No.
All the minibosses, they were cool, they were fun.
But I don't need to place like three Stone Digger Trolls.
So, who is a real boss that's still down here?
None of them.
They're all up there.
All the dragons, I'd say, are up there.
Wait.
Godskin?
There are too many.
Brave...
I don't know.
These are all minibosses.
Agent Dragon...
Oh, this one.
Right?
This is a boss.
This is a real boss.
This is the worst tier list.
Dude, just give me a minute.
I'm going to get...
I'm gonna put this shit where it goes.
Tibia Mariner.
Remove it.
But that's our wall to determine if somebody's cool or not.
All right.
There are four Tibia Mariners.
I get it.
But that's like the wall for...
It's something cool.
Fine.
I need to have a new wall then.
It's gone.
Okay.
We're good.
All right.
Put the Taurus Demon up there as a wall.
No.
The Taurus Demon sucks ass.
That's not the wall of if you're cool.
The Taurus Demon is stupid.
All right.
The wall for if you are cooler than a sea.
Shit.
These have got to go.
I got to get rid of the miniboss.
These are miniboss versions.
You're working backwards.
It's a...
I got it.
The first Elden Lord, a lemonade version of him, is...
I would say...
What happened to my eye?
Is a sea.
Straight up sea.
Sea.
So...
We have to do some work here.
Death bird.
Get out.
Is Ranala cooler than the Godfrey?
Yeah.
Is Tower Knight cooler than Godfrey?
Radagon is definitely better.
I just thought...
I thought...
The Radagon right into the final boss.
Elden Beast.
Just...
I don't know.
I don't like that.
I'm okay with it being at a bit...
Radagon's fight was really cool and then they just like, all right, here, if I end the game
now.
The Elden Beast was all right.
I don't think it's bad.
I don't think it was great either though.
We got to start from the bottom.
No F's in Elden Ring?
Oh yeah, there is.
It's like two of the major characters.
Oh my god.
I will move Radan because Radan is better than the Asylum Demon, I guess.
Not...
I like Gideon more than Radan.
He can stay there.
We might see some S's from Sekiro.
We're almost done.
We've got Dark Souls 3 Sekiro and then Sprinkle in Dark Souls 2.
This is almost done.
Okay, let me get Elden Ring done.
Horolue, Slave Knight Gale.
Was Horolue cooler than Slave Knight Gale?
It's too recent, but I don't think so.
It's tricky.
I don't think so.
I think that makes sense to me.
I think this makes sense to me as well.
Now, that's recency bias.
Put it back.
These are the same boss, but I'm going to keep this one because it's Loretta, right?
This is kind of like the two versions of this boss.
Okay.
That's not fair.
I like that.
Ligarius is better than Malakith.
I feel like Malakith's fight is so quick.
It's just a DPS burn fight.
It's really cool, but I don't know.
I think some of these have to come back.
Malakith needs more HP.
How many humans do you sacrifice to look so young?
Zero.
I have a skincare routine.
I talked about it earlier during the Fortnite thing.
Moisturize your face.
When you're out of the shower, get a nice light moisturizer and just get it on there
and rub it in.
It takes 10 seconds.
Please.
I'm telling you.
Do it.
All right.
Raikard was...
Raikard is...
Okay.
Raikard and Gaping Dragon are similar.
Fire Giant comes down.
Is Malakith cooler than Astel, probably?
But no.
But the fight doesn't last long enough.
Kalamith's probably not as cool, though.
Ligarius is cooler than all of them.
No smoking and no drinking.
I mean, I drink.
I drink maybe once a month, maybe five or six times a year, maybe.
Maybe like 10 times a year, maybe.
I don't smoke.
I don't really drink that often.
I mean, I dabble in THC a little with CBD, but not, you know, crazy.
I don't drink that much alcohol, though.
All right.
Let's keep going.
I actually don't think I have to move any of this.
Maybe this.
I'm trying...
I wish I bought this at the right level.
It would probably be way higher.
What's cooler than the Tree Sentinel?
Like, let's be honest.
Yeah.
I like this.
I think this is good.
Shadow's Yarnham cooler than Ranala.
Yep.
Noble needs to come down.
How does the old hero...
The old hero and old punk.
Okay, nobody move.
Is Gideon cooler than Godfrey?
What do you think?
He might...
It might be.
Hmm.
Maybe.
Okay.
Yeah.
You know, you're right.
You're right.
Right.
Fia's Champion belongs down here.
I'm gonna put Melania behind the Mimic tier.
I laughed out loud.
No, I'm not.
Fuck that fight.
I was just doing that to make you happy.
And this is my list.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I think Elden Ring is good.
Three A's from Elden Ring so far.
Do they belong up there?
And one S.
No representation at all from Dark Souls 1.
You missed like 60 bosses.
I think I'm okay with that.
I think because there's a lot of B's and A's.
Margit was...
Yeah, the Ancestor Spirit I like more than some of these.
Right there.
Right here.
Gwynn, come back.
You were stupid.
You were cool but stupid.
And you too.
Okay.
I like what they are.
All right.
Looks good so far.
Now it's time...
Remember we're not doing mini bosses.
So all these.
These like...
The Shinobi Hunter.
The Headless.
We're not doing any of the mini bosses because that would be way too hard.
We should go to bed.
This is not going to take that much longer.
No, let's do Dark Souls 3.
I don't...
Let's do Dark Souls 3.
Yeah, Dark Souls 3 is a good idea.
Okay.
Pontiff Sullivan.
Pontiff Sullivan is going to be up here.
Cooler than Lagarius but I don't think cooler than Loretta.
Maybe.
I think so.
The ones that I remember...
I remember this fight.
I don't like it.
This is like a D.
This is the caster with the big tail.
Yeah.
Didn't like that one very much.
It was kind of like eh.
Put that next to Gideon I think.
The fight was kind of ass.
All right.
Gundyr.
I'm going to just put one Gundyr.
And I actually really like the Gundyr fight.
Except the phase two is kind of annoying.
But I like the fight.
Let's put...
Where's champion Gundyr?
We'll leave index down here because it's literally the same thing.
Oh, the Lothric Prince fight.
That was awesome.
Yep.
That's going up to A.
I liked that fight.
Somebody's riding on the other ones back.
Can we get a refresher?
Yeah, we can do some refreshers.
Turn the music off.
Why can I not?
Okay.
We'll do some refreshers on some of these.
We don't need too much though.
Okay.
This is index Gundyr.
Vort.
I don't think we need it.
All these...
Oh, no, no, no.
How do I get this one in F?
Yeah, that's what I'm doing.
In a single video.
That's right.
Curse Rod of Greatwood is just the Erd Tree avatars, but way bigger and more annoying.
You had to like pop the bubbles, right?
Yeah, that one was okay.
Crystal Sage was kind of rage inducing.
I know everyone thought that was one of the easiest bosses.
It took me a long time.
I remember...
I remember dying like 20 times to this on stream.
How's that annoying teleport and then bring every...
You just clone yourself 10 times.
The Abyss Watchers were cool.
Probably B, I would say.
That fight was pretty fun.
They fight each other.
And then it gets all smoky and fiery.
Yeah, this was cool.
I feel like a lot of the Dark Souls 3 bosses are going to be very high.
That was kind of...
That was kind of like the shine...
I can't even speak.
That was kind of the shining part of the game for Dark Souls 3 for me.
It was...
The bosses I thought were great.
Deacons are going to be F.
Comedy F though.
So it's not like I hate it.
It's just...
The fight is not that great.
Wolnir...
Oh, yeah.
This is the big guy with the handgun.
This is the big guy with the hands.
You have to hit the bracelet, right?
This guy was cool.
Fuck, man.
This is a good game.
Old Demon King.
I remember this one.
What was this one?
Oh, yeah.
Am I...
Do I have rose-tinted glasses on or is this game amazing?
Pontiff.
Yeah, we already know Pontiff.
Aldrich.
Yhorm is probably a D.
It's a gimmick fight.
Yhorm is just Rikard but boring.
This is the same exact fight.
No difference at all.
Okay.
Dancer, the boy real.
Dancer was cool.
I beat Dancer first try.
Although a little spammy though.
I'm not sure this is higher than a B- or a C.
There's a little spammy.
Dragonslayer?
Armor?
D.
This guy sucks.
This is the guy that leaves the area and shoots you with fucking shit from across the game.
I hated this fight.
This guy was annoying.
And all that crap comes in just spamming at you.
Yeah, this fight.
This guy's a D+.
This guy leaves and then...
Yeah, he does.
Watch.
He leaves.
He doesn't leave?
Who's the boss that leaves the area and then spams shit at you?
This guy does not do that.
Butterfly?
Okay, well.
I love this.
I love this fight.
There's an old little ocelot.
I will protect you.
Is it A?
He's holding what he thinks is like a baby or something?
Yeah, this is a cool fight.
This is a wild boss.
This is at least A+.
This is terrifying.
There's Champion Gundyr, so I think this should be pretty high too.
Damn.
Am I being shown that I actually like Dark Souls 3 more than all of them?
I think that's what's happening.
This is the Lothric fight where he rides on his back.
Yep.
Okay.
I like that fight a lot.
Ancient Wyvern.
Oh, this was kind of a gimmick, right?
Don't you just like jump on his head?
Eh.
Like D.
Well, let's just see it, right?
Might as well.
Yeah, you have to just run through this.
I remember.
It was such a pain in the ass.
Just to jump on him and kill him.
Yeah.
Nah.
This is pretty low.
We don't need to see it.
Nameless King.
Yeah, this is a great one.
Riding the Dragon.
This was insane.
He gets off the dragon and you're like, oh my god, I gotta fight this guy.
Might as well just refresh, right?
See if we can remember.
Yeah, this is awesome.
This is probably S.
This might be the S from Dark Souls 3.
The music too was so crazy.
Soul of Cinder.
Oh, this is the last one.
Yeah, this guy was not...
It was alright.
I would say Nameless King.
You should have just given Soul of Cinder Nameless King's moveset and encounter.
I remember having fun fighting this, but I don't know if it's S.
Okay.
This is the DLC.
This is the wolf and the grave guy, right?
The gravetender.
This looks like such shit.
720p.
I think I got really mad at this one.
Yeah, because the wolf could just sprint at you randomly and just...
He ran across the map like three times.
This fight was...
I don't like this.
It was bad.
It wasn't necessarily bad.
It was just...
I don't know.
It was just frustrating.
This is the guy stuck in the chair.
I remember laughing at this, so that's at least a B.
Yeah, this is the guy that was stuck in the chair.
Yeah, then he gets angry and you fight him both at the same time.
I don't think I beat this on stream without help.
Do I remember that correctly?
I think I got to a point where I was like, no, I don't care.
Just come help me.
It was a cool encounter, though.
Let's just see the chair because it's funny.
Really cool, though.
All right.
Demon Prince and two demons.
Phase three is S tier.
Did I do this?
Demon in pain.
Demon from below.
Did I do this?
You did.
Took me a lot of...
Oh, I did do this.
Yeah, I remember the area.
Spear of the Church.
It's a boss.
Oh, this is the invasion one.
The PVP one.
Yeah, it was all right.
But whatever.
Afflite?
Yeah, the whole Spear of the Church thing was kind of...
It was okay.
It was an interesting encounter.
This is the one where it was actually like people could have invaded you and tried to kill you, right?
Which is really funny.
And then Medir, which...
We tried to Mario Party this boss and I don't think we beat it.
All these bosses are absolutely amazing, though.
And then who could forget this?
He's already an S.
Slave Knight Gale already an S might be the best.
This is another one of those fights that just felt like a dance.
It was tough.
It was really hard.
It was fair.
There was a lot of interesting things going on.
Dark Souls 3 is too easy.
Um, I don't think so.
I thought Dark Souls 3 was actually really hard.
This was so fun.
I remember I didn't get mad.
You know how you can tell when a boss is really, really good?
When I don't get mad at it at all.
It's just like, wow, this is amazing.
I can't wait to fight that again.
All the things that are in S tier were that for me.
You mean when it's easy?
Garmin is not easy.
Horoloo is not easy.
Ludwig is not easy either.
You know how many times I died to the first phase of Ludwig?
Horoloo is easy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is a great fight.
This fight is not even easy.
What are you talking about?
Okay, it's time.
What time is it?
Oh, God, it's getting late.
How long have I been doing this for?
All right, let's do it.
This is where they belong.
Old Demon King.
We'll see you up at the B tier.
B minus.
You're on the giant.
Dancer, B.
Maybe high C, low B.
Here it is.
Okay, this is the Ocelot.
This is A.
I'm going to have to move that around.
Champion Gundyr, high B.
The reason why I want to do this so bad is because I want to see what game I actually liked the least.
And here's the crazy thing.
Dark Souls 1 looks like the game I fucking liked the absolute least.
I came to watch the Fortnite VOD, but he's still streaming this stupid tier list.
I hate to break it to you, but there was probably like six minutes of Fortnite gameplay in three hours.
We were looking at a spectator screen.
If that's what you're here for, I'm sorry.
That's not what you're going to get.
You came here for Fortnite.
I should just delete that VOD, because it's literally five minutes of content in like three hours.
We got to play for like ten minutes.
You have Demon Souls?
Very low.
Yeah, but I need to do the remake.
Everyone's going to bother me about Fortnite.
Oh no, it was fun.
I actually had a great time.
It was fun yucking it up with the boys.
But if you're talking about Fortnite gameplay, what you're looking for, that's not what happened.
That is absolutely not what happened.
The remake is exactly the same.
Yeah, but I'm remembering PlayStation 3.
Right?
Okay, let's keep going.
Oh, the daunting task is almost complete.
Because I'm going to be able to burn through a lot of Sekiro really quickly.
Index Gundyr, I don't need to go up there.
Dragon Slayer armor, that's the one we just watched when I thought it was a different encounter.
We're going to put it up here.
They're all Fs.
No, a lot, some of the Sekiro fights were really cool.
I don't, some of them were probably going to be high.
I really didn't like this fight at all.
I didn't.
Medir, I didn't really beat it.
Half-Light, yeah, this is a gimmick fight.
It was cool, but let's see.
Vort was fun.
I think Vort's at least a B.
First Rod of Gwe...
C.
Nameless King?
Yeah.
S.
The Deacons are F.
Welnir is somewhere in the Cs.
Once this is here, I'm going to make sure it's very accurate, so don't worry.
Demon Princes, I didn't even remember the fight, so I must not have liked it.
Crystal Sage, not F, but no, it's low C.
Abyss Watchers, high B, low A.
Put it here for now.
Demon Prince is good.
Welnir is like a low D.
Fried, is that Fried and Soup Guy?
The one stuck in the chair?
That's up there.
It was crazy.
I can't say it was an S, though.
All right.
Gunder's staying down here.
Wyvern, F.
Is that fair?
We'll find out.
Soul of Cinder, C, high C.
No, that was a B, let's be fair.
Okay.
Dark Souls 3 is up there.
We just have Sekiro and Dark Souls 2.
Make sure this is correct.
Put some music on.
Oh, we had the Hollow Knight one on.
That's fine.
Yeah, it's getting late.
Oh my god, I've been doing this for like four hours.
Holy shit.
Wow.
What?
No, I haven't been doing this for four hours.
Why am I so into this?
I've been doing this for four hours?
I actually can't believe that.
All right, I gotta hurry up.
Jesus.
All right, let's get this correct.
Wow.
Cool.
That was a good, that was a good tuba reaction.
Yeah.
Was it?
No, not this, not the second stream that I turned on.
I don't think this was Fortnite.
I think that first stream died and I did the second one, right?
All right.
Old Demon King.
I can stay there.
Dancer should be up here.
This is going to get so hard eventually here.
Is Dancer cooler than the spirit from Elden Ring?
I think so.
Probably.
And I think Dancer is better than Soul of Cinder as well.
I think the real test is going to be this one.
I don't know.
The real test is going over the dragons from Elden Ring.
That's the real test.
Is Pontiff Sullivan?
Yes, yes he is.
Yes.
No.
The dragons were snooze?
Were they?
I think that they're okay.
Bistwatcher is definitely, I think so.
Raid was also cooler than this.
Damn.
One, two, three, four, five.
Five bosses from Dark Souls 3 or A or above.
I still have to put some more up there.
Fire Giant was probably, yeah.
Radagon and Elden Beast are better than these at the very least.
I think so.
That was a cool fight.
I think it goes right against the wall here.
You have a McDonald's?
Nice.
What's your order?
I actually think this is a good barrier here.
That's cooler than Gideon.
Crystal Sage, Cooler.
Wulner is higher.
I like, Old Demon King should be in C.
You know what?
Wulner was awesome because when you went to Wulner's room,
it was just pitch black.
And then you keep going and all of a sudden he's like,
it's like, holy shit.
What the fuck is that?
I like that a lot.
This stays down here.
This can go up above Nito and above Ranallo.
Yeah, this goes down here.
That's a gimmick fight, but it was cool.
All right.
How we look?
I actually think I'm OK with this.
I think this is perfect.
The only thing I would change up here,
surprisingly low for Medir.
I just, it took too long.
Medir had way too much health.
It was just annoying.
You just suck.
I think design-wise Medir was awesome.
I just realized it's just way too much health.
I remember summoning like four people
and we gave Medir like five, four times more health
and we couldn't even hurt him.
I think collectively the four of us did like 30% damage to him.
I'll put Millennia up at D.
F is for truly.
Well, no.
F is for dog shit.
Millennia's fight sucks, but is it like the witches of Hemwick?
I mean, no, it's not.
It's OK.
All right.
I'm happy with it.
Time for Sekiro.
Sekiro only really has a handful
and we could probably get a couple of refreshers here.
Imagine liking the Millennia fight.
I mean, it's not bad.
It's just awful.
All right.
Sekiro.
We need to do a little bit of research here
because we're looking for...
Who was an actual boss in Sekiro?
I'm actually going to turn this off.
Because there was so many mini bosses in Sekiro.
All right.
So we're looking for the names that are orange.
So it's not very money.
Owl.
I didn't do Owl.
I don't think I fought that.
That's going to have to go immediately down there.
I don't know.
I don't think I did that.
Demon of Hatred.
I don't know if I did.
Did I do that?
Chained Ogre is not...
All right.
This is the first fight here.
This is the one that you die.
It's the tutorial one.
Do I really count it?
This is the beginning of the game.
Demon was awful for you.
I feel like every one of these bosses, I was furious.
So I don't know how to even rate these.
I hated these.
The Owl was a story boss.
Did I hate everything in Sekiro?
No, I like...
No, no, no.
That's when everything was burning down.
Okay.
Let me see if I know where it is.
That's where the whole...
Everything's burning down.
I remember the ape was Owl.
Owl.
Isn't it where everything's burning?
Or is that a different fight?
Oh, no.
I did do this one.
Did I?
Yeah, there's two.
It was fun.
You had to do this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That one was fun.
Okay, what else do we need to see?
We need to see pretty much all the major fights, which are...
I don't think that's a major one.
Lady Butterfly.
Let me remember this.
Oh, I remember Lady Butterfly.
You know how I know Lady Butterfly?
Here's how I know.
Every time I've tried to replay Sekiro, I've only beaten Sekiro one time.
I always get to this point, lose like a dozen times in a row, and go,
fuck this game and uninstall it.
And I've tried at least probably three or four times.
All right, so this...
How do I even rate these?
I hate...
Did I hate this game?
There's the bull.
I remember the bull.
This was crazy, but it was kind of a cool fight.
I remember that.
These are all mini bosses.
Okay, I remember that one.
Right?
This is the...
Inichiro, right?
This is the first time you fight it.
Hard equals bad?
I didn't say that.
He turns into lightning moves, doesn't he?
Yeah.
This fight was actually pretty cool.
Watch yourself play this game.
I don't know, man.
I remember this.
This is F.
This is the monkey one.
We had to run around.
This is F.
This actually might be below Bed of Chaos.
Yeah, this is lower than Bed of Chaos.
I don't even know if I would count...
Yeah, this is when you run around and they're all invisible.
It's just like not even a boss fight.
It's just stupid.
Is the Great Serpent even a fight?
Don't you kind of just run away from it?
It's not a fight.
Really cool, though.
Probably the coolest part of the game.
One of the coolest parts.
Yeah.
The ape.
The Guardian Ape, aka the Twitch streamer reaction compilation fight.
Where, no!
What?
He's getting up!
No!
What the fuck?
Dude!
It's actually cool, though.
I think this should be somewhere at least in A.
It's a really cool fight.
Yeah, because there's just the face cams in the corner.
What the fuck?
No, dude!
What?
Yeah.
I liked it, though.
This is the gimmick shit, right?
They throw the two at you at the same time.
I hate the fake YouTuber voice.
Yeah, I remember that.
This is not a real fight.
They put two at you at the same time, which is annoying.
Emma?
Why do I not remember this?
Oh, no.
Wait.
Did I fight this?
Wasn't there an ending you could get in Sekiro that was not even halfway through the game?
This is part of that, right?
Yeah.
I did not do any of these.
This is the one where everything's on fire?
No.
Am I just making up that I did that fight, or did I watch somebody else do it instead
that I did it?
I do remember the owl fight, though.
This fight.
I liked this one, actually.
This fight was cool.
This might be one of the best fights in the game.
Yeah, I loved this one.
This is when he jumps up in the tree.
Yeah, no.
It's cool.
This is another bull.
It's a mini boss.
Oh, yeah.
The big fish.
I wouldn't classify this as a boss, either.
I wonder how unfair I am to Sekiro.
That's not a boss, though.
Old Dragons of the Tree.
Oh, everybody made fun of me for this one.
They said this is the easiest boss in the game, and I couldn't do it.
I remember this.
I remember people were like, oh, Megalol, like, he can't do it.
This is the easiest fight in the whole game.
Why don't you go up on, like, pillars and shit, and they throw lightning at you?
No, this is different.
This is just a Deacon fight.
Which always goes to D, at least.
This is the one, the Divine Dragon.
Everyone made fun of me for this.
Yeah, this is cool.
Even if the fight's easy, this is really, really cool.
I remember being awe-inspired by this one.
It's beautiful.
Yep.
Oh, these are mini-bosses.
Is he even of hatred?
Yeah, I...
Yeah, I remember.
I'm getting flashbacks.
This fight did suck, though.
This fight was bad.
Did we get a raid?
Did we?
We did get a raid.
Atriarch!
What's up?
We're doing a very long, painstaking thing.
Welcome, everybody.
I hope you had a good stream, Atriarch.
We are trying to rate every single boss across every single From Software game.
I've been here for about four hours.
Is it tough?
I have not done Dark Souls 2 yet.
We're in the middle of doing Sekiro.
Dark Souls 2 is going to be the hardest, and in fact, I might just like...
I don't know.
It's...
There's so many bosses in Dark Souls 2.
I feel like every boss in Dark Souls 2, for me, is the same boss.
I don't know why.
I remember the Pursuer, and you shoot him with the bow and arrow thing.
I'll do it.
It's not going to take that long.
But yeah, we're going over, getting refreshers on what the bosses were, so I can remember
if I hated them.
Hated this one.
And then...
This...
This fight.
Yeah.
I cried during this fight, didn't I?
I'm pretty sure I cried.
I think I actually cried on camera.
Yeah, I think so.
I think this took me like 60 to 70 attempts.
I cried on camera.
Alright, I got a good idea.
I've got an understanding for Sekiro.
Sad, really.
It's going to be sad, really.
Because I don't think...
Scary music.
I don't think there's anything in S or A in Sekiro.
I don't think so.
We'll find out.
Here we go.
So, okay, can I put this into like, I cried...
The fight is awesome.
It's such an amazing fight.
It's so beautiful.
And it's so...
The moves are so cool.
It's such a dance, but my god, I cried on camera.
Like, I fucking cried.
There were a stream of tears.
And I was like, I QUIT STREAMING, I QUIT STREAMING, I QUIT STREAMING!
And then I was like, calm down.
And I was like, I FUCKING QUIT STREAMING, and I turned the stream off, and I didn't
come back for like a week.
I never thought I'd quit.
No, I can't put it up...
I fucking cried.
I'm gonna keep it there.
Um, Guardian Ape is gonna be A. I think.
I don't know if we're gonna get any S from Sekiro.
It was just too fucking hard.
Lady Butterfly, F. Because even Hatred is D. Owl is not...
Lady Butterfly is F. Because you keep preventing me from doing another playthrough.
The only reason.
I keep...
I've tried to play Sekiro, and I get to Lady Butterfly, and I go, why am I doing this?
I don't want to do it.
So that's...
You have to be there.
Like, you keep preventing me from playing the game.
This was actually awesome, though.
So this, let's be fair.
Lightning moves...
That's probably better than...
That's bet...
I'm sorry, it is.
Better than Pontiff Sullivan.
That was a crazy fight.
It was so intense.
Why is Butterfly lower than Pinwheel?
I never said it was gonna be perfect.
Okay.
I didn't...
I couldn't do this one.
True Corrupted Monk.
Oh!
That's the good one.
Yep.
B.
Monkeys.
F.
Which one of these is the real one?
Corrupted Monk?
Over...
That's the one I'm thinking of, right?
The right one?
I like that.
These weren't really bosses, and if we're not doing mini-bosses, then I have to...
I can't put them in.
Corrupted...
No.
That's a different game.
This is...
The...
Tutorial.
Genichiro.
Which...
I don't know if I can even place this.
C?
No, you're just supposed to die.
I'm not gonna place it.
Genichiro's already up there.
Who is...
Gyobu?
Gyobu.
Who's Gyobu?
Gyobu?
That's the final Genichiro.
Oh!
It's the guy on the horse!
Okay.
Now that was cool.
I actually liked that one.
A lot.
That one's B.
I liked that one.
It was cool.
I don't think it's A, but it's definitely B.
Low...
Mid-B.
This doesn't need to be an I don't know section, then.
Genichiro Way of Tomo is the final version when he transforms mid-fight.
Ah...
Okay.
That's the one I like.
This is the tutorial one, right?
I don't want to fuck up Dark Souls 2.
We're almost done.
Headless Ape.
We're in a Corrupted Monk there.
These are mini-bosses, right?
Oh, these are the ones where you...
Okay, I think we're done.
Oh, Divine Dragon.
Right, Divine Dragon.
Beautiful.
Beautiful fight.
Not an A, though.
All right.
No S's in Sekiro.
Sorry.
No Dark Souls 1S and no Sekiro S.
Those are my least favorite games, then.
They have to be.
And let's build Dark Souls 2.
It might be like...
I know a lot of people really like Dark Souls 2.
Dark Souls 2 for me.
These are kind of like the left side of the Monopoly map.
These are not really worth that much to me.
You know what I mean?
It's like these are all Baltic Avenues.
I don't...
These are like, you know, Park Place, Boardwalk.
Up here.
But I don't know.
To me, these are all just Baltic Avenue.
Let's see, though.
I'm not going to talk shit until I do it, because that's the finale.
And then when I do that, I'm going to make sure it looks right.
And then I'm going to see what my favorite game for real is.
No bullshit.
Because you...
Let me...
Without looking.
Let me just tell you.
Not T-Rex, but like, this is where the games sit.
Epic.
Bloodborne, number one.
Elden Ring, number two.
Wait.
Let me start backwards.
Dark Souls 2, bottom.
Sekiro, just over that.
Dark Souls 1, just over that.
Dark Souls 3, over that.
Wait.
I need to write it out.
This is my, like, you know, like, stupid fucking list.
Demon's Souls.
Dark Souls 1.
Zero.
Okay.
This is what my list looks like at the moment right now.
This is really scary.
Whatever it is.
Is Elden Ring better than Bloodborne?
They're the same to me.
In my head right now, I can't decide.
Done.
So that's what I think.
We're going to find out if it's real.
Sekiro is done.
Let me just check.
This is such a huge wall to cross, though.
High B. It's not Lagarius.
It's not.
God damn it.
I don't know.
I think this has to be there.
I think that's actually accurate.
Because it's better than Lagarius.
It's better than Abyss Watchers.
Cry-Card is...
No, is he?
Dark Souls 2 is the only thing left.
Why is there an open can of food on your shelf?
There's no open can of food with a fork sticking out of it.
We're almost there.
Dark Souls 2.
You guys ready?
Find out how much we like this game.
Here we go.
Giant.
I remember the giant.
Actually not that bad.
It's a pretty good intro.
Pursuer.
You can kill the Pursuer in, like, two seconds if you shoot the crossbow at him.
I like the Pursuer because he chases you around.
He shows up a bunch of times.
It's alright.
Dragon Rider.
Oh, this is the joke.
Laugh out loud.
You make him fall off.
That's a C.
Old Dragon Slayer.
I don't even remember fighting this guy.
I don't...
There's so many bosses in Dark Souls 2, I don't even remember fighting them.
It looks alright.
Oh, this thing was cool.
It was the sentry.
It has the two bodies.
This fight was good.
Okay, Ruin Sentinel.
This is an F. I remember this was stupid.
I hated this.
The F, for sure.
The Ruin Sentinels are absolutely F.
Belfry Gargoyles?
F.
Is it literally just Dark Souls 1?
Is it F?
Okay.
The Lost Sinner.
I didn't even fight this guy.
He looks...
What about the Skeleton Lords?
This looks like shit.
I don't know...
I think this one sucks too.
What about the...
What about Slimer from Ghostbusters?
I actually remember this fight.
This fight was fun.
Yup.
I liked Slimer.
This is probably a C.
Why do these all look like they're in the same exact area?
This one actually was pretty good.
That boss is bozo shit.
This one's pretty good.
Yeah, I remember the scream and dodging.
Yup.
That was fun.
I'm not seeing any A's that I remember as being like, holy shit, that's an A.
Smelter Demon.
This is bozo shit right here.
Oh, I thought he died.
This is actually cool.
Yup, I remember this.
This is probably a B.
Smelter Demon and Old Iron King.
This is the fight I'm talking about where you can fall in.
Yeah, this one sucks.
D.
Executioner's Chariot.
Oh yeah, the Chariot fight.
Dude, playing Dark Souls 2, it feels like it was a dream.
I don't remember any of these things.
And I didn't even play it that long ago.
Art equals bad.
Looks like shit.
Bozo shit.
Didn't fight him.
DLC?
What?
You should replay it.
I don't know if I want to.
I feel like I'll hate it.
I think it's D.
I do have a pretty strong memory of this one.
I think this fight was cool.
It was probably like a B.
It was pretty fun.
Scorpion was kind of like the queen from the first game.
Yup.
Royal Rat Authority.
What?
That's a dog.
That's not a rat?
I thought Royal Rat Authority was a bunch of rats in the room.
Did I play Dark Souls 2?
That's the other one.
Oh, okay.
Well, that's a fun dog.
Fowling Magus.
This looks kind of like some Bozo shit right here.
The Duke's Deer Freya.
Is this the one with the...
It's the spider.
Yeah, this one was really scary.
I like the design of this boss.
This boss needs to be higher than the armor spider.
Otherwise, I pretended to play this game.
Which I didn't.
I beat it like three times.
Ah, here it is.
Royal Rat Vanguard.
I like the room.
I remember fighting these and the room is cool.
I'm not going to give it an S because of rats.
I'll give it probably like a C.
Rotten.
Whoa.
Oh, yeah.
This fight.
I mean, it's kind of Bozo, but it's...
I would say it's probably high.
Not that high.
I'm trying to find the one that I'm like, yeah, yep.
That one is definitely like A.
Two Dragon Riders.
That's not it.
I don't think that's it.
I know for a fact a few of these I thought were really good.
Maybe this is one of them.
Looking Glass Knight.
I have a distinct memory of this guy's shield and me being like, that was fun.
Okay.
I'm looking for one that wows me.
It's this one.
This is the one with the fucking skull in the mouth of the big frog.
Yep.
We finally found at least our B.
Most people give this an F.
I give this a B because the design is really, really just carries it completely.
Actually, so far, design wise, the only like interesting looking boss in the whole game
so far.
Everyone else is kind of just like a...
Besides the spider.
I don't know.
Dark Souls 2 is huge though.
This is so much content.
This is the Bell Stat?
Royal Ages.
I just don't have any memory of fighting this.
Dark Souls 2 is just like a billion guys in armor.
Dark Souls 2 is one of the biggest games they have though.
So there's a lot of content.
The areas in Dark Souls 2.
Some of them are really cool.
All right.
He's all right.
Oh, the dragon in the cage.
This thing.
Okay.
This is high.
This is high because you get to see this from a distance for a while and you go, holy shit.
Do I actually have to go in there?
Yeah.
This is probably at least a B.
Ancient dragon.
Oh yeah.
That's right.
You can just come up.
Oh, you can't kill this.
This takes way too long.
Don't you have to cheese this fight?
Isn't this impossible?
I don't.
I don't want to just hate on Dark Souls 2.
I really don't.
I don't want to be like that.
But doesn't Dark Souls 2 look like it came before Dark Souls 1?
Is he alive?
I enjoyed myself a lot in the game.
I don't want to pretend like I didn't.
Right?
Giant Lord?
It's so simple to sit here and be like, you know, Dark Souls 2 is the worst one.
But I mean, do you want more from software content?
Would you rather this game didn't exist?
Be honest.
No, I'll keep it.
The alternative is this does not exist.
I remember these giants there.
They were kind of annoying.
King Vendrick.
This one's not bad.
This is how I got into Dark Souls?
Yeah.
So should that be the Dark Souls 2 section of our kind of map where they're all in C
and they're all in a row?
None of these are apps.
You know something?
Guys, Dark Souls 2 has no S's and has no A's.
But it also has no F's.
Interesting.
I don't remember any of these me being like, this game sucks.
That's a barometer you need to use.
Did you fight this enemy and say this game sucks?
Fix it.
I'm trying to remember.
Is this just forgettable?
I don't remember saying that this game sucks.
Fix the game.
The ruined sentinels.
Yeah, that's right.
They get one F.
Don't you feel like you're watching what we're watching in a dream right now?
Like this is a Dark Souls game that you made up in your head asleep.
Like the way the animations are and the way that it's being played.
I feel like I'm dreaming this.
This is what my brain would put together to say, hey, this is like a Souls game.
I don't know why.
Something about it.
It feels like uncanny but real at the same time.
Oh, this is the first time that I'm going to tell you I remember this a lot and it was really crazy.
Yep, this is one of the end game bosses.
This one's actually really cool.
Is it?
Do I just want to give Dark Souls 2 like a spot somewhere in A?
This is literally the final boss before a scholar.
Oh, is this the guy that looked like Lord Zed and he comes out of the ground?
It is, right?
Yep.
Okay, that's not really good.
This is an F boss?
I don't think any of these are F.
I don't.
I think maybe one of them is.
Alessandra is an F. That's adorable.
Compare any of these to Dark Souls 3.
Yeah, but there was a lot of time in between.
That's kind of cool.
Grave robbers.
Why did Dark Souls 2 have so many just put three people in a room fights?
I don't remember this.
I would have hated this.
This is mega F.
Is this fights mega F?
Is it worse than Bed of Chaos?
Is this mega F?
What about the...
Where's the third person?
Where's the third player?
Where's Sarah the old explorer?
Where's this other person?
This does seem kind of omega F.
Okay, where's the third person?
Alright, what about the slumbering dragon?
This is cool.
I played so much Dark Souls 2 and looking back it may have had some of the worst fights.
Is it that?
Yeah, this is weird.
This feels kind of weird.
I don't remember Dark Souls 2 looking this terrible.
It wasn't.
It was fun.
Like, I liked it.
It wasn't this bad.
No.
No, we're being unfair.
I think we're being unfair.
This is without seeing the areas.
Some of Dark Souls 2's areas are really, really cool and really majestic and awesome looking.
I don't think this is Copium.
I think it was actually a really fun game.
It was.
Dark Souls 2 never drops off in quality.
Let me read this.
Dark Souls 2 never drops off in quality is the second half of Dark Souls 1, you bozos.
That's actually a good point.
Like I said, there are not many Fs or Ds.
It's a bunch of Cs and Bs.
No Ss, no As, no Fs.
It's very consistent.
Even Elden Ring.
The last arc of Elden Ring was alright.
I mean, that was the whole thing.
The whole package was an unbelievable masterpiece.
It's consistently bad.
I don't think so.
What about the smelter demon?
You've already said three Fs.
Is it the Hollow Knight music in the background that's making this seem dumb?
I don't know.
What's going on?
It might be the music.
Oh, the Fume Knight.
I remember the Fume Knight.
Fume Knight was crazy.
What's going on with the health in Dark Souls 2?
What was that?
What's going on with this health?
Slow heal.
I remember this fight was actually pretty crazy.
I do remember this one.
Sir Alone.
This was fun too.
The timings on these were fun.
You know what it is about Dark Souls 2?
I figured it out.
There's no bodies in any of these suits.
It's all just metal.
Nobody's alive.
You're just metal suits attacking each other and clinking into each other.
Yeah, this fight was fun.
What about the king's pet?
Yeah, but if I was craving some Dark Souls, I'd play it.
It's not a bad game.
Yeah, this sucked.
I remember the cat jumping down and then I remember wanting to uninstall the game.
Why though?
It's because it's invisible.
Okay.
Blood, the king's pet.
Wait, you need to do it again?
It's not a bad game.
Yeah, this sucked.
I wanted to uninstall it.
Yeah, but I said...
Okay.
How many times did you hear me while I was playing Elden Rings?
They're saying I wanted to return the game.
What about the burnt ivory king?
What's going on?
Who's the king?
Where's the boss?
This is just open PVP.
Bro, somebody said, bro, this is so ugly.
Everybody's made out of clay and rocks.
That's what is wrong.
Where's the ivory king?
Bloodborne is uglier?
Oh my god, ban that person for life.
I mean it.
Ban that person for life.
Bro, that looked like battle chess.
Battle chess?
Oh my god, you just ruined Dark Souls 2 for me forever.
You just ruined Dark Souls 2.
I can't even play this again.
What the fuck?
Okay, you made me want to put this high though because that's really fun and funny.
It's a fun game.
Leave it alone.
Leave Dark Souls 2 alone, okay?
It's got...
Listen.
It's got some of the most content of any of the From Software games.
It might look like a mobile game ad, but I haven't looked back at Dark Souls 2 in a
long time.
You know, if I was a Dark Souls 2 defender right now, you're probably sitting in the
chat going like, fuck, I am a Dark Souls 2 defender.
Fume Knight is...
Okay, let's do this.
And then I've got to make sure it's correct.
This is like 5 hours.
I'm a Dark Souls 2 defender and I'm malding.
Come on, that was Battle Chess.
And everyone's made out of pots and pans.
I like Dark Souls 2.
I do.
I really do.
It might be...
Fuck, it's literally at the bottom of my list, but they're all good.
Alright, let's do it.
Fume Knight.
Let's put the ones we know that are high, high.
Is Fume Knight cooler than the Taurus Demon?
Where is our...
Where's the Barometer?
It's Godfrey, right?
Is Fume Knight better than Godfrey?
You know, I think so.
I actually think so.
I do.
I even think Fume Knight is better than the Bloodstarve Beast, but that's where it ends.
We gotta give it to him, guys.
We gotta give him at least one encounter that's over the C-minus threshold.
I'm not done.
What...
Any of these...
Where's the...
Where's that fight right here?
War into Ivory King is fucking high.
Okay?
It's really high, because that was hilarious.
And comedy sometimes trumps gameplay a lot of the time.
Comedy can make gameplay look stupid.
I'm telling you right now, that Battle Chess comment makes this funner than the Elden Beast.
I would have more fun walking around hitting those guys and watching them play Battle Chess
than doing the Radagon-Elden Beast combo again.
I think that's okay being there.
Watch the intro to the Burned Ivory King.
Why?
Okay.
This stays there.
I love this.
This is...
It reminds me of the boys.
It does.
Some of them are standing still.
Do you see?
That guy just drank a potion and he didn't get hit.
Yup.
I'm...
Comedy trumps all sometimes.
Sometimes comedy trumps all.
And that's where it belongs.
It's not...
I'm not giving it an S.
In fact, it's going here.
It's staying...
Okay.
Alright.
It's staying right here.
I don't...
Okay.
The Chariot is D.
That sucked.
Skeleton Lords was D.
The Slimer Demon is D.
C.
The Medusa Fight was actually pretty cool.
High C.
I don't think that's cooler than Godfrey though.
Old Iron King.
I forgot what it was already.
Smelter Demon.
I forgot what it was.
Rotten.
This one was...
This one was kind of fun.
This is like another Slimer.
Demon of Song.
Oh.
The music turned off.
That was weird.
Oh.
The music turned off.
Video paused.
Are you still watching?
Continue watching.
Thanks for confirming.
Did I just get Netflixed?
I gotta go.
I've been sitting here for like so long.
Okay.
I want the Demon of Song.
It's definitely not cooler than any of the Sekiro fights.
Is there a Sekiro fight that's...
Yeah.
Okay.
You can stay down here.
The Scorpion was pretty cool.
C.
Royal Rat Authority.
I mean, everyone was laughing at that.
It was like a Scooby Doo dog with a tongue hanging out.
I didn't even fight this.
I was gonna put it down here.
Rattling Magus and Congregation.
I don't remember fighting this.
The Last Giant.
That's the first boss in the game.
I'm gonna give it a good low C.
Duke's Deer Freya.
That one was not that bad.
Probably like a high low C.
Twin Dragon Riders is a low C.
Looking Glass Knight.
That's a high C.
Not better than Fume Knight.
Not better than Godfrey.
The Royal Aegis.
This one was pretty cool.
Low B.
No.
High C before Godfrey.
Fendrik.
This was a D.
No.
This is a low C.
Ancient Dragon F.
Guardian Dragon is like a C.
Giant Lord is like a C.
Dark Lurker.
I don't think I fought this.
Pursuer.
Pursuer was pretty fun.
It was pretty challenging.
I'll give it a C.
Throne Watcher and Throne Defender.
Machandra.
I'll give it a C.
Fowler of the First Sin.
That's the funny guy that's in the ground.
I'll give it a C.
Grave Robbers.
Everyone said give that an F.
I don't even remember fighting it.
Dragon Rider has comedy points because you can make them fall off the edge.
And that's pretty cool.
I like that.
B.
The Queen was pretty cool.
I'll give it a C.
Flumbering Dragon was pretty cool.
I'll give it a high C.
Smelter Demon.
I'll give it a C.
Sir Alone.
This one was pretty cool.
I'll give it a C.
King's Pet F.
I actually like this boss that's going high.
The design of this boss alone is cool.
It is cooler than Godfrey.
Where's Godfrey?
It's cooler than Godfrey, for sure.
Where the fuck is Godfrey?
Where's Godfrey?
Oh wow, you're way higher than Godfrey.
You're cooler than the Godskin Noble.
They overdid this.
I'm putting it down.
Dragon Slayer.
I'm going to give it a C.
Gargoyles D.
Ruin Sentinels F.
Lost Sinner.
I'm going to give it a C.
Royal Rat Vanguard.
I'm going to give it a D.
Well no, I'll give it a C.
Okay.
I've got to get this right.
Top row is done.
Now it is.
I need silence for this because this is really important.
This is the thing people are going to point to to say that I'm like a piece of shit for
the rest of my life.
I have to make sure this is correct.
This is one of the most important things I've ever done on stream because some of you after
this are going to hate me for the rest of your life.
I've got to see what happens here.
Is Gas Coin better than...
No.
This was a cooler fight.
Sullivan cooler than Gas Coin.
Yeah.
Ibritos cooler than Gas Coin.
No.
Any of these cooler than Ibritos.
Yes.
Bloodborne is losing a lot of ground here.
It's Dark Souls 3.
No.
Sekiro sucks.
I refuse to give it a S.
I'm kidding.
It's fine.
Dark Souls 2.
I don't think I can move any of these.
B is just as important as A though because some of these might have to level up.
No.
Yes.
And fuck Raikar too.
Dancer is cooler than Mog.
You know what?
So is Isshin and so is...
Shaping Dragon is not cooler than any of these.
What is this doing up here?
The music in this is so good.
I think Wet Nurse goes down below Tree Sentinel.
That was just such an insane awesome moment when you open up the door and Limgrave is there
and there's the Tree Sentinel.
It's like wow the graphics.
I can...
Wow.
Shit.
Sekiro is way better than I thought it was.
Thank you for the correction you're right.
Is this good?
Is B good?
This fight didn't last long enough.
It would have been A.
It just was a massive DPS raise.
These are like the same kind of fight and this one was cooler by far.
This is cooler than this.
Cooler than that too.
No it's not.
Vort's way too high.
Vort and Wulner make sense at the same spot.
Gundyr is in the wrong spot as well.
But cooler than this.
These are way too high.
Way too high.
I think this is too low.
I think that's in a perfect spot.
Okay.
Um.
Dark Souls 2.
Oh okay.
Everything in Dark Souls.
Is every single boss in Dark Souls 2 that's not the ones I put high better than the Taurus
Demon?
I mean I don't know about that.
Put these down.
Put this up.
All the Dark Souls 3 stuff goes up now.
Except for this.
Cleric Beast goes down.
Fuck this fight.
Stupid.
It's the worst fight in the whole game.
But it's better than everything in Dark Souls 2.
Hold on.
I gotta make sure I do this right.
Dark Souls 2 is like the C.
No that can stay there.
So can that.
And so can this.
The gold skin duo is bad.
These are cooler than the Taurus Demon.
They are.
Old King is cooler than the Taurus Demon as well.
Way cooler.
I'm swapping these.
Moon Presence has to come way down.
Fuck.
This is too high.
I think that's in a good spot.
Seath the Scaleless sucks.
Um.
But it's cooler than Godfrey.
And it's cooler than the old hero.
Is it cooler than the Fume Knight?
I'll say yes.
But the really important one is what is the worst fucking thing I've done ever in a From Software game?
I think that's good.
These are all the same to me.
That's where it belongs.
To me.
And I have to be honest.
Okay.
What's the worst thing I've ever done.
Ever.
In a From Software game.
This is pretty low.
It's always bed of chaos.
I hated this so much though.
I did.
I hated it.
This is probably worse.
And so is this.
These are probably worse than that as well.
Dragon God is worse than that.
The Grave Robber shit.
I mean it's bad.
These are all bad.
Ruin Sentinels are bad.
Probably the worst.
No.
Maybe.
They might be.
It's possible.
Deacons could be the worst.
Is it done?
Millennia is better than the fucking goddamn Skeleton Lords.
Right?
Like I gotta be fair.
I'm trying to think.
Is better than.
Millennia is better than Pinwheel.
Pinwheel will come back.
Pinwheel will go to F.
I refuse to put it higher than D.
I just hated that fight so much.
Lady Butterfly is only there because it prevents me from playing the game anymore.
It's an encounter you have to do.
Done.
Stamp it.
Sign it.
Done.
It's over.
All these are mini bosses or stuff that I can't really place.
What about Morgoth?
Yeah, I made the joke about how I can't place Morgoth, but I'll place him.
It's cool.
There you are.
It's over.
There is my official From Software boss tier list.
It only took us about 5 hours.
Butterfly is optional.
You're a dumbass.
So what game do I like the most?
Okay.
We're going to count how many bosses are in S, A, or B.
Let's start with Bloodborne.
It's right here.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
There are nine bosses here from Bloodborne.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen,
those are Demon's Souls.
Twelve, thirteen, fourteen from Elden Ring.
Dark Souls 3.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve.
Twelve versus fourteen.
And there are way more bosses.
Way more bosses in Elden Ring.
Dark Souls 3 might be my favorite one.
Boss encounters wise, if we're just talking straight up boss fights, I think Dark Souls
3 has the best boss fights.
Below that, I think Bloodborne and Elden Ring both kind of are tied for me in boss encounters.
Although I think Bloodborne edges it a little bit more.
Dark Souls 3 is baby easy.
And Sekiro though, five, six, seven, there are nine.
I liked Sekiro, apparently, the boss fights as much as I liked Bloodborne.
Kind of, right?
I guess I'm surprising myself that I actually did sort of like that game.
What about the F's?
This is important too.
Holy shit, I don't give a fuck about Dark Souls 1 at all.
One, two, what about the D's and F's?
Lots of Dark Souls 1 and D. A lot.
Damn.
Huh.
If you take the aggregate, I think Dark Souls 2 has a better score than Dark Souls 1 on
this tier list.
I mean, there's way more Dark Souls 2 bosses, that's not fair.
Lot of Elden Ring and D as well though.
There was like a fucking hundred of them.
Alright, that's cool.
I still think my opinion stands.
That's Demon's Souls, oh right, not Elden Ring.
Dark Souls 1 unironically sucks.
It was just better than Demon's Souls.
I actually liked Demon's Souls better than Dark Souls 1 because you could fast travel.
Wait until like two thirds plus more than halfway through the game to travel in Dark
Souls 1.
I think that Dark Souls 1 is way higher than am I lying to you?
If you told me right now, would you rather start playing Dark Souls 1 right now or Sekiro?
I would probably say Sekiro.
Yeah, I think so.
Part of that I think has to do with the fact that I have played through Dark Souls 1 like
five to ten times.
I've only played through Sekiro once, so that's probably one of the reasons why.
Dark Souls 1 is just a solid video game that kind of, it was right after Demon's Souls
was cool and everybody was like wow that's a cool concept.
They made Dark Souls 1 this interconnected world.
It was a cool experience.
It was unlike anything else anyone ever played.
It's just old.
Older.
And it's hard to put it above stuff that came ten years later from the same company
that is effectively the same video games.
And even still, like somebody just said, it is unlike anything else still because they
got rid of the interconnected world where you run from place to place and you don't
fast travel.
They got rid of that.
Sekiro's level design was really good.
It was.
Maybe I unnecessarily hate Sekiro for no reason.
Maybe it was just hard.
I remember crying.
If Millenia didn't have the one bullshit move, where would she be?
We have to live in reality.
Waterfall is fine laughing my ass up.
When you make your tier list, you can put Millenia, Blade of Mykola, up here.
But there's no chance in hell that Millenia is cooler than Gehrman that's not happening.
Nameless King, not happening.
Inichiro, not happening.
Seed, not happening.
Pontiff Sullivan, not happening.
Better than Legarius, not happening.
Better than Abyss Watchers, I'll give you that.
Better than Ornstein and Smog, not happening.
This is really unfair.
I'm just mad at this because I just did it and I hated it.
Give me like two months, ask me again, and she'll probably be up here.
Ornstein and Smog, overrated.
A lot of people think I have this underrated.
I thought I put it in a good place.
This is a good tier list, not happening.
We're not doing this again.
That was fun though.
That was just chilling, just doing this.
What a weird stream.
I played in a Fortnite tournament and I did a five hour From Software tier list.
What a fucking weird stream this was.
I had a good time.
I don't like the fact that the internet kept having problems for no reason.
Somebody was going like this to the wire.
I don't get it.
It's annoying.
Dude, what the fuck is the Fortnite?
The one guy that came in for the Fortnite question?
I feel so bad.
That person is going to go to the VOD and just like scroll through and be like,
this is fucking stupid.
This guy had to resort to doing magic tricks because he doesn't know how to play Fortnite
and he joined a tournament.
I put money into Fortnite.
I bought a skin.
You missed the magic tricks?
You did?
That was the big nose of yours?
Sure.
I have a crooked nose.
Do you know that?
My nose is crooked.
You know, it goes that way.
Like it goes like this.
It's way more pronounced going this way, right?
Like that.
My nose is like this.
A link to the tier list.
Yep, I will.
I think it's a pretty good list.
I think it's, I mean, obviously Dark Souls 2.
I don't want to hate Dark Souls 2 and I think it's not fair.
I think it's a good big junk.
A bunch of, it's good.
I liked it.
I do like it.
I had enjoyed my time and I played through it a couple of times.
Osiris is the most forgettable thing in the game.
It shouldn't be at A.
Well, it should be at A, but it should not be higher than that.
That's what you meant to say.
Because, I mean, it's not cooler than that.
It's not.
Okay, now we're done.
Are you doing more magic tricks?
Or Dark Souls 2.
I feel bad.
It's okay.
All right, let me link to the, let me link to it.
All right, I'll see you guys later.
That's the end of the stream.
Kind of a weird one today, but you know.
The next stream, by the way, is going to be today's Tuesday.
I will see you guys on Friday?
Is that maybe Friday or Saturday?
Let's say, let's say Saturday.
We'll do Saturday, Sunday.
Is this the time where we pick to do Elden Ring invasions and PvP and stuff?
That might be a fun time to do it on Saturday, like afternoon.
And that will wrap up a lot of the Elden Ring stuff.
And then Sunday, you know, why don't we go play DOS games?
I think DOS Sunday sounds fun.
I'll get a bunch of crazy shit.
Do some DOS games.
So if you want to do Elden Ring multiplayer, Saturday is the day.
Put it on your calendar.
You're going to do a fight club?
I think I'm just going to put a password down and I'm just going to put my sign somewhere.
See what happens.
I moisturize.
I actually really do that, seriously.
Your 30 to 40 year old self will be very happy with you.
The battle chest, that might be my favorite one guy of the year so far.
That was an amazing comment.
You see the R play stuff?
I did.
I've been keeping up with it.
Although, isn't it over?
It ended, right?
Yeah, it's over.
Link the tier list.
I did.
I did, didn't I?
There you go.
What's the moisturizing routine?
Right out of the shower.
Dry your face.
Use a light moisturizing cream.
Make sure it's for your face.
Light.
None of this heavy, heavy cream shit.
They don't like the hand cream stuff.
No, no, no.
Get a light face moisturizer.
Water-based.
The ones that are gel.
They're kind of like a watery gel.
That's what you want.
When you get out of the shower, you dry your face.
Pat it dry for a little bit.
Get your light, kind of water, gel-based, base lotion.
It's the tip of your middle finger.
That's all you need.
Work it into your hands a little bit.
Maybe tap it on the cheekbones.
Rub it in.
All around your face.
Do that every day.
Skin routine.
It's really good for you.
It is.
It helps.
All right, guys.
It's late.
I'm going to get out of here.
Thanks for watching Fortnite?
Question mark.
And the from software tier list.
This is a weird one.
Sometimes they're weird.
Hanging out and doing the tier list was fun.
It's cool just to kind of look at stuff and hang out with you guys.
Doesn't have to be like crazy, right?
They don't all have to be crazy.
In fact, none of them are crazy.
I'm a normal person.
I'm a regular guy.
And I don't do crazy things.
We relax and do tier lists.
That's what we do.
If you're still here from Atrioc, thanks for the raid.
Hope you enjoyed yourselves.
And I'll see you guys on Saturday.
Have a great night.
Take care of yourselves.
Bye.