Somebody in chat owes somebody $20. I gotta be right off the bat, gotta tell you right immediately.
Somebody in chat bet somebody in chat, I think, somebody else, that I wasn't gonna be able to capture this.
And they thought this was gonna be a disaster stream where I could not cap the 3DO.
Well, I am sad to say to that person, we're ready to go. It's good, it looks great.
It is working flawlessly, actually.
But today we're gonna do a 3DO. Welcome everybody, I'm excited for this. I've been waiting to do this for a long time.
I've owned this for almost a year. I've been collecting 3DO games in anticipation for this very moment today.
Do we need proof? I mean, okay, I can give you proof. I mean, I got a 3DO, crying out loud.
This is not on an emulator, this is actually... I'm gonna give a shout out here when there's a shitload of people here
because I wanna shout this company out because this thing works, it works very well, and I wanna shout out that company.
I've used a kind of old console converting upscaling hardware before, and this one is the best that I have personally used.
Wouldn't you like to know what it is? You'll find out once there's more than a thousand people here.
So I can show that I said to more than a thousand people that most amount of people were here.
And I said it. No, it's a Retro Tink. The Retro Tink 2X Pro. The thing is amazing.
It was the easiest thing I've ever used in my life. I just plugged everything I needed to plug in in.
I downloaded some updated firmware, flashed it, and it's ready to use. And it looks way better than anything else I've ever used.
It's a Retro Tink. If you wanna use original hardware and you have an HDTV, get a Retro Tink 2X Pro.
And tell them Germa95 sent you. Who cares? No, it's actually really great. And you're gonna see what the picture looks like right now.
Hey, look at that. Take a look at that. 3DO on original hardware. Somebody resident sleepered.
Whatever. This is big to me. This is a big deal for me. You haven't even shown it yet. Well, hold on. Let's restart this.
You haven't shown it yet. Look. Ow. Germa heart. Germa heart. It looks great. I know. It looks awesome.
Show us the console. Alright, hold on. Let me show you the console. I don't... whatever.
I had a fucking tank. I had a tube top on. Alright? I had a tube top on that went like this.
When you have to delay your audio and video on OBS, what happens is, it doesn't matter if fucking hours have passed.
A whole day could pass. If you didn't close OBS, it saves the last frame that you did.
And when you're setting shit up, sometimes you just don't even think about it. I'm just happy that you didn't see my dick.
Like that's... I'm just telling you a fact. I'm just happy that that's not what happened.
Oh, yeah. That's fine. Look. I know. I'm fine. Alright. Anyways. What am I doing? I'm showing you... okay.
So watch. I'll show you for an example. An hour can go by and that's going to save there because I delayed the video.
Was he wearing pants? Yes, I was. I remember wearing pants. Don't worry.
Okay. You know that photo of me playing TF2 with just like a bare chest? That just happened.
I don't care. I don't even care. Okay. I don't even care. Even if I was naked, I wouldn't even care.
Even if I was naked, I wouldn't even care. I would just be like, whatever. I don't even care.
Okay. Let's show this thing. Here's the whole setup. So what we have here, here is the...
Here is the... Well, that's a controller. There's the controller. The Panasonic 3DO controller.
What is that guy plugged into? There it is. The 3DO.
The Panasonic FZ10 3DO. Connected to Game Retro Tank 2X Pro. Connected to my capture card.
Break it. I'm not going to break this thing. This thing's awesome. Why would I break it?
That was pre-recorded footage. Or even if that... Okay. Even if that was pre-recorded footage, who cares?
I own the console and it's plugged in. Does it really matter?
Do you think I went through all the trouble to plug in all this stuff and like set it all up just to take a video of it?
I mean, that's next level. I see where you're going. All right. Let's go.
One more stalling. Time for 3DO. Let's restart the program. I'm so excited.
Ladies and gentlemen, Rebel Assault Star Wars for the 3DO.
I am not seeing even nearly enough fucking hype right now. Hype it up, guys. Come on.
Actually, don't. I'd rather you be disappointed. Up pilots.
No, I want to get the... How do I get the... I want to get the intro. Just restart the system.
All right. Hold on. I'm going to restart the system. I'm going to restart the system.
I hope I don't break it. Don't break it. Okay. Ready?
Zach, is it going to break the hardware?
All right. Here we go. You ready? Nobody wanted to see the intro anyways.
That's the intro. It's pretty bad. It's loading. It's loading. It's loading. I can't wait. Here we go.
I'm so excited. I'm so excited for 3CVDO.
Did I even have to do that? I didn't even have to do that. I didn't... I really actually didn't even need to turn it off.
Will you... All right. Here we go. Quiet. Yes.
It is a period of civil war. Full spaceships striking from a hidden base have won their first victory against the evil Galactic Empire.
Who, under the command of Darth Vader, rule the galaxy with an iron fist.
That video is so good. 144p video file.
It's Luke. I know Luke. Many young unknown pilots have joined the Rebels in the hope they can restore freedom to the galaxy.
Either way, this whole thing was made in MS Paint. It probably was, if I'll be honest. It probably was.
3D movie maker, actually. We can talk all the shit that we want.
It actually looks pretty good, considering that it is an upscaled image of like 140 or like 240p or something.
It looks pretty damn good. It'll look a lot worse. Let's go.
All right. I'm done stalling. Let's play.
Smells pretty good.
We're a pile of crap.
Can I sneeze?
Attack com control. Request attack com control. Clearance granted. Is that you, kid?
Yeah.
Jack! Good to hear you.
So you're running your trials today. I wish I could be with you.
You shouldn't have any problems. Beggar's Canyon isn't half as tough as the rest we used to do.
So unsettling. I love it, though.
Good luck. Thanks.
All right. So in Rebels... I don't play this.
It's T-Rex. Oh, no. We're flying out of this canyon. Never mind.
I thought it was a T-Rex.
Should I steer clear that you have to fly?
All right. I'm actually flying.
Wow. This is awesome.
This definitely wasn't the trailer for the 3DO. There's no way it wasn't.
All right. It's a little tight. It's kind of hard to tell.
Working the canyon.
Let's go right.
I'm a true hotshot, man.
I am.
Why would you bring the trainee here?
This doesn't seem very safe.
Okay, trainee.
You don't know how to fly planes yet, but just do this hard shit.
I'm doing it.
That guy was trying to kill me.
This guy wants me dead.
All right. So far so good.
I...
Oh, it's too tight.
Good. Did it fly up with him?
I'm so excited. I can't wait to play.
There's 40 games. I have 40 3DO games. I'm so excited.
Shoot at the targets?
Wait, what?
I got him.
Wait, was that my friend?
Wait, did I shoot one of the good guys?
Oh, my God. Did I get to do the whole thing?
Okay.
I'm going to go left this time because I want it to be really easy.
That was friendly fire.
I'm going left.
Forget about going right. No.
No, I don't want to be a hotshot. I just want to be a regular guy.
I went left.
My ship was tilting left. It's forcing me to go right.
It's okay. I got plenty of health.
Okay. Now this time, it's like a top-down view.
All right. Don't screw this up.
Is it actually a loser of choice?
It might be.
Stay with us.
What the fuck happened?
No, dude. That's not even what?
Stay tight. Follow and stay clear of the walls.
No, I don't want to.
It's very weird. I don't understand.
When do I get the lightsaber?
Do you get a lightsaber in this game?
You get a lightsaber, right?
You have to.
It's a Star Wars game.
I have to beat this.
Left.
Yeah.
I want as much health as possible.
I have to beat this.
This is harder than the other one.
Okay. Don't mess this up.
Shoot the drones.
Okay. I tried.
All right. I'm going to fucking sit up.
Watch the pillars.
Pillars.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
All right.
What's that? Is it?
What's a bug's fight?
Fuck. I ran into it.
Shit. I just crashed into it again.
Okay. It's hard to see.
Fuck.
Okay. Just stay away from the shadows.
Oh, fuck.
All right. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good.
No way.
All right. I can't lose my mind.
I cannot lose.
I'm just dead.
They're leaving me for dead.
Oh, I got game over.
All right. I'm going.
No. It's not even worth putting my name in.
That was just a warm up.
That was a warm up.
That was a warm up. Ready? I'm ready.
All right.
Somebody just go get the password for after this level if I can't do it.
That was a warm up.
What is this?
Rookie one is dialogue and text.
Volume difficulty is normal.
It's kind of cool.
Everything's right here.
All right. Let's go.
Oh, this is so fun though.
It's just I love it.
I don't care if I lose here a thousand times.
I'm holding a 3DO controller in my hand.
That's all I care about.
The song doesn't match.
I'm crashing the bridge.
Okay. Don't mess it up.
Just avoid the pillars and don't even who cares about shooting the drones.
All right. Go.
Who gives a shit about the Google Earth image that's underneath you?
Is that a shadow?
Watch out. Watch out.
Is this a wall?
Who cares?
Just let them go.
I've got no damage done to me.
It doesn't matter.
None of this matters.
Just live.
Where are they?
I did it.
I got a password.
Part one, path taken easy.
Password, boffin.
Yes.
Let's go.
Keep going.
After two, asteroid field training.
Okay, one.
This is commit.
One standing by, commander.
Let's get something straight.
I don't like hot shots.
If you want to impress me, you won't stand a chance.
I'm not like my twin brother.
Dave, I don't like hot shots.
He likes them.
Don't try to prove anything to me.
Sick.
What happened?
Why?
You guys moving number bunchers?
What was it?
Math blasters?
Watch.
Fine.
Shit.
There's a lot of them coming.
Down?
All right.
We're good.
We're fine.
Perfect.
Thanks, man.
Omega low.
Erglick.
Yeah.
I know.
Okay.
Cool.
Good link.
I'm busy.
I was expecting her head to spin around 360 degrees.
Hard course.
Holy shit.
This is hard.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
I have to calm down.
How?
That was insane.
How did I not get any damage done?
Am I regenerating health?
This is what it's like when you're in a dream.
That's what it looks like when you're flying around in a dream.
All right.
Now where's the lightsaber training?
Password.
Leaning.
So now what?
Do I get on the ground fighting?
Okay.
It's a static shot.
Sure.
Wasn't that funny?
My bit rate is really low right now.
Okay.
Wait, is there an internet problem?
It's like, oh, no, no, no.
Right.
There's like fucking a thousand kilobytes of data on the screen right now.
I'll lower it.
It's a little up.
Vader.
Within moments, our troops will board their ship.
We'll then have the stolen plans back in our possession and Princess Leia as well.
Excellent.
I shall oversee her interrogation personally.
Uh-oh.
Fake actor.
Okay.
I'm just waiting for a guy to turn the corner that's supposed to be your dad, but he doesn't
look like your dad at all.
He has a mustache on.
Your dad doesn't have a mustache, but it's your dad and your dream.
It's fucking weird.
I'm going to regret this.
This thing is safe.
Battle station plans are not on board this ship and no transmissions were made.
An escape pod was jettisoned during the fighting.
No life forms were present.
She must have hidden the plans in the escape pod.
Send a detachment down to retrieve them.
See to it personally, Commander.
Okay.
Darth Vader is dead in that chair.
Somebody's holding his mask from behind and doing a voice.
Oh, he's just sitting there.
Okay.
Uh-oh.
Emergency.
I took the animator a full three days to do that, by the way.
You just watched.
Lift it up.
Drink it.
Put it down.
It's a full day of work.
I'm ready.
Let's go.
Uh-oh.
Emergency.
I took the animator a full three days to do that, by the way.
You just watched.
Lift it up.
Drink it.
Put it down.
It's a full day of work.
I'm ready.
Let's go.
Seems a very enthusiastic.
We have to take out the command center.
Watch out.
There's a ton on the line.
Here we go.
Wait.
Don't go that, uh, how do I?
Star Fox? Um, sorry, Star Fox is shitty Star Wars. Can you rephrase that please? Cut his
mic. No, can we be, let's be real, Star Fox is Star Wars with animals. I love Star Fox,
it's like one of my favorite games, especially the one for 64. Star Fox 64 might be one of
the best games ever made. In fact it is, why would I even say it might be? I'm actually
doing pretty good. I can't wait to get, when does it, I gotta get to the lightsaber fight
with Darth Vader. You're one hit away from death. Don't distract me like that. How many
of these fucking things exist? Don't hit the wall, don't hit the wall. Alright, let's take
out the things on top. I did my work, can I do the other thing? There's nothing left.
This is fun. I am having a great time. I love this, I'm so happy right now. I feel like
my son was just born. Is this what it feels like? Get it! No, I don't want to do another
cool Redditor soy boy. What? Because he's comparing the 3DO, playing it for the first
time with having a child be born. Alright, I'll give you that one. You can have that
one. Yeah, that's fine, you can have it. Kind of true, actually. Well, whatever. I don't
have a son, I don't know what it's like. I have to imagine something like this. Okay,
please don't die. Don't die, just kill the thing. Don't crash into the wall. How do
I have to? Torpedo's armed. Shoot it! Shoot it there! Did I get it? Oh, I got it. Having
children is like playing Donkey Kong. We got more. I got to be careful with this controller.
Is he alright? Oh, he's not. I feel like this controller feels so delicate that I feel like
if I mash buttons and hold it tightly I'm going to mess it up. You know when you have
your friend over that's a big strong person and you give them the controller and you don't
like how hard they're pressing the buttons but you can't find the strength to say anything
about it? You can hear the like, and you're like, ah, fuck, I wish I could fucking be
like, dude, yes, don't fucking do that so hard. That's my shit. Okay, I got him. I did
it. Dermas of Beta. What? Yes, time to get on the ground. How many times have I said
yes in the first 30 minutes of this stream? Holy shit, I can kill AT-STs in one hit. I'm
kind of low to the ground, don't you think? It's 18. Shit, alright, left side. Just do
a Jerma joke and crash. I can't. The game is on rails right now. I cannot crash. Give
a shitty blaster? I'm killing things in one hit. That's not shitty, that's really good.
29. What's 30? 31. Oh, 32. Who's left? Am I single-handedly destroying everything? This
ain't like Galaga, right? I don't have to kill everything. Is it? 40? That's not real.
I got 44. Did I lose? I didn't lose, right? No, good, good, good. L-W-Y-L-L. Tony Hawk?
I played Tony Hawk already. Oh, it's R2-D2. No, I played Tony Hawk 2, Tony Hawk Underground,
Tony Hawk 1. I did them all. If you think you're going to get anything good from me,
from Tony Hawk, no. You're going to have to teleport back to when I was 16. Don't do,
don't lose, don't lose. The new one. Wait, what do you mean? Didn't they just remaster the first
two? I don't even know what to drive to get away from this. God damn it. Okay. All right,
all right, all right. I'm fine, I'm fine. I have plenty of lives. How old is Jerma? 28.
And then in parentheses, plus seven. I am dodging. What are you talking about? I don't.
I'm going to get hit by the asteroid. Calm down, I'm fine. Don't hold it. Don't death grip this
thing. Shit. Kill it, kill it, kill it, kill it, kill it, kill it, kill it, kill it. Kill that guy,
kill him. Oh my God damn it. Play Doom for the 3DO. I got plenty of fucking video games. Don't
you worry. Don't just focus on dodging, nothing else. The amount of damage that the asteroids do
is pales in comparison to what? Down or left? Down or left or right? Right. How am I not dodging
that? I very much am. Down, down, down, down, down, down, down. Which way? Which way? Which way? Up,
up, up, up, up, up, up. We're fine. Did I actually get hit by it? There's no way. Damn it. Okay,
don't get mad at the first game. You can't do that. They programmed this game on a toaster,
okay? You can't get mad at this. All right, if I lose another life, I'm just going to chip
chip away at change games. It was actually a microwave. When I get to zero, I'll do that.
I love Star Wars. Just hold on. How was that not a dodge? Run that back and tell me. I'm going all
the way to the right. Just dodge everything. The fuck? How do you dodge in a game that's on rails?
It's all right. Since when did looking in another direction dodge your car? It's not like somebody's
driving straight at me and I go, oh shit. I lean my body to the left and not turn the wheel.
I'm not going to do anything. Thank God. No, no, no, no. Dude, what? What are you talking about?
I was holding the controller all the way to the right and I still got hit by that one.
Right, right, right, right, right, right, right. It's right. It's right. I remember. I've memorized
the whole damn thing. I got to get the password for this one. Fuck you. Come on. All the way,
all the way, all the way. Don't hold down. Don't. All the way, all the way, all the way,
all the way. Which one is this one? Up? I don't know. I have no idea. Up? Left? Right? I don't
know. I can't even see them coming at you. I don't know. Down? Down, I think. Fuck. I'm okay. Can
this please end so I can get the password? Please. Don't fucking drive into me, dude. What are you
doing? Give me the password for the next one. Give me the password for this one. Give me the password,
password. Give me the password right now. Give me the password, password, password, password, password,
I don't care what is give you a password for that since it's wouldn't give you a password I want play lightsaber level
That's not cheating I didn't he drove into be they guys an asshole I hear all the passwords
nice okay good perfect
Okay, so level one all right cool. I don't want a high score next game. Hold on I like this one
Let's go with a
Okay
Mazak? Mazak. No. So why don't give him that he's gonna keep playing this. I like this one
I'm sorry. It's been it's been 30 minutes. I'm gonna go. I'm breaking the rule. It was it has to be at least 30 minutes
Yeah, but don't worry. I have it. I'm like it. Okay, mazic. Let's see what it does. Just watch the cutscenes
Wait, I'll put the next one in the wrong password. I might come back and play this one though
I actually like this one. I think there's more to see
next is
twisted the game show
You're gonna see the colored the colored bars thing wanting you you're gonna see it right now. All right. This next one
All I saw with this one is the box I just turned it on to make sure it worked
I think this one's going to be insane. We go. These are collectible items. I'm not gonna
I gotta make sure I keep these in a good spot. Yeah, I'm using the retro tink 2x Pro things. Awesome. We go
EA
This is an EA game back when they used basic shapes for the fucking logo
The good green screen footage
Me
Find out which of television's tortured talent will be playing this round of twisted. Thank You Twink
Contestant number one will sell you the shirt off your back. He's the clunker king. He's wormington and he's dog
Oh, I wasn't know who these people are
An Elvis
Contestant number two
Camels are trading futures. She enjoys mind-reading channeling and vodka. She knows you're thinking
1-900 Elaine I can read your mind and you should be ashamed
Okay
We have
Is he all right? Why is he frozen?
My favorite character so far that's my favorite character
In the kingdom of humble how what is it with the 90s with the above wide-angle lens pointing down at somebody
It was everywhere. It was in every commercial every TV show
She's the star of war crimes workout Admiral of aerobics sergeant of sweat feel the burn
Wait what the fuck
Not me who is contestant number six, right friend of folks and presidents alike
He travels the world spreading love and tooth decay short in stature, but long on flavor. He is uncle Fez
These are chance. What do you say? It's not even a person
That's not even a that's just a car that's like a 3d character, right?
It was the cursor pad to select your contestant then press the A button press the C
I like that. Okay, come on. Oh, it's just tough. This is tough one
Make them stop I can't what do I would I do
Want to be picked me? Yeah
Think tank X now Johnny Powell
How smart do you think you are use the cursor pad to set your trivia difficulty level and lock it in really a difficulty?
This is child adult I'm not gonna do expert
No intelligence, no, no, no, I would this is like the difficulty of the questions
We're gonna do a felt cuz I'm an adult. I can't do expert. It's gonna be impossible stuff
Okay, will the next player please select a contestant the next one all players have made their selection. I made my selection
proceed
It has to be to people
Okay, I like this guy's movements
This guy's way more excited
I
Have to go
That's it no more characters we're done throughout the game
I will refer to you by your contestant's name the object of twisted to great even really quite simple
Roll the cyber knife complete the various challenges and get to the end first and what happens then right?
Well, Twink our lucky winner will receive a one-way trip out of this TV wasteland into whatever the hell's on the other side of the screen
I hear reality is just beautiful this time of year
Gee, I can't wait to get going. It's game even for Anna. Are you as excited as I am?
Right now let's get twisted Howard you're up first
It's perfect. Okay. So what about I don't what what is this supposed to be? I don't have to roll dice
Think fast you're on the challenge square
Johnny pal take the controller and secretly select a row from the matrix. Okay. Um, I'm gonna just go with a
Now Howard take the controller and select a column from the matrix. I
Want that top left one
Use the cursor pad to assemble three complete faces
Recomplete, but whose turn is it?
Wait, what? Wait, is this right?
Got it wrong
What?
Think very you're on the challenge square challenge square. So you just have to do these weird Mario Party games
I want to what's what's soupy now, Johnny pal take the controller and select a call
But that one all the way to the right. I need to know what that is
Answer all the questions correctly before time runs out sports and recreation
Daiquiri is made with oh no strawberry Daiquiri vodka shit. I don't know
Nickelodeon presents twist it
This is a Nickelodeon show look at this stuff, it's awesome
Johnny pal take the controller and secretly select now Howard
Look out the window cursor pad and the a button to recreate the picture
recreate the picture
Okay, departure launch recreate this photo of a cactus
Okay, this one's very easy. That was incredibly
It was just done. Yeah, Howard. You're still the puzzle was completed. I didn't even have to do anything
Think fast you're on the challenge square. What are the other squares?
What's this take the controller and secretly select a row from the matrix you can do a B
Answer all the questions correctly before time runs out. This is pop culture trivia
What are the name of Mork and Mindy's son? I don't know or key
Orky Orson who or key?
That's a TV pop culture from 25 years ago, Johnny Pat. I
Want a different square you've entered the challenge zone
That was a weird tone
Take the controller and secretly select a row from the matrix. All right B. B. A
Behold the items on the shelves two of the items were not in the group select the item that was
Okay
Wait, what am I supposed to do? I wasn't even paying attention. What wasn't on the shelf the peanut butter
Commercial break each garment is hand-sewn with 198 stitches and it's made of genuine six carrots in you gold
They're measured Smith. It's slices and dices. It cars forward. It even performs surgery in those hard-to-reach organs and now back to the game
Actually would prefer that it's time to roll. That was ten seconds. Don't make this hard on yourself beat that challenge
Johnny pal take the controller and BB from the matrix BB. I want to see what the bomb is
Killed him give it your best. Look at how long this staircase is
Beat that challenge. This is a huge staircase real tragedy
BA now Johnny pal take the control
No, no, no, no, no a B is what I wanted whatever a button to recreate the picture
All right, it's gonna be one of three things. They already finished the puzzle for you. I'll laugh my ass off. It's done
Wait, oh no, wait, what I get I did I get it wrong. I actually got it wrong
I got it wrong. I did the wrong picture. Yeah challenge challenge challenge
That oh no is from something to that. No take the controller and okay
CB
Behold the items on the shelves two of the items were not in the group select the item that was
Three
How do you have to have a free? Okay, what's not here?
There's a bunch of fruits and shit. Ah, the mock wasn't there
what I
Press see
It's the opposite oh
Okay, we're gonna go we're gonna go a B
To match what is there
Excuse me, but what do you what do you want me to do? Oh, it's fuck. Okay. I didn't understand so very slow down
I got a timer your turn
You give a zero you've won absolutely nothing a lifetime supply of nothing Johnny pal good luck. Okay, that's
sure
Bonus square roll again bonus square roll again boss
Good job, Johnny pal. You go again, right that background was just the side of a sneaker
from 1985
In cap kids, it's challenge time
Take the controller and secretly select a row from the matrix. All right, I want to do a see
Use the cursor pad and the a button to unscramble the movie before time
Had an a to unscramble the movie like I fit like a TV tuner
Jesus
Johnny pal, it's TOS still up
You're going to the wheel of torture. What?
Okay a on three of a kind
Very impressive you still control the cyber die. Oh cool. All right
Good roll. You're going bonus square. The name is pal Johnny pal
Good job, Johnny pal. You go again
Feeling brainy you got the challenge. All right, let's go early
10% of the way through the game and secretly select a row from the matrix. I would'll be see
Now Johnny trivia answer all the questions correctly before time runs out
Terms summa cum laude means with the highest honor
That's the same thing. You said it a different way
You've hit the challenge square
2.5 GPA. Yeah, it don't matter. Take the controller and secretly select a row from the matrix. What are we not seeing CB?
Just see how I'd take the controller and so like
Use the cursor pad and the a button to zap the commercials and stop the fuse zap the commercials
No this one
I did it manual ad blocker. Yeah
This board is so huge it's challenge time shouldn't be this big of a board, right?
Take the controller and secretly select a row from the matrix. I'm gonna do this one again
Pad and the a button to match the sounds we go ready
I
Penis music. Yeah, sure
You go again think think think the challenge square. This is what they actually sounded like
BA
Use the cursor pad and the a button to match identical pictures
Oh
What identical pictures? What's the hair? I don't know. What's identical here? Oh, no, what is it?
I did match identical pictures. Oh wait, that's not what I have to do. It's but what's behind the picture
Try plucking sniffing burning, but those nasal hairs kept coming back introducing zap
We'll take your hair and leave your nose bare
I used to be a loser
Now back to more to the original tick-tock there's your original vine guys, it's right there right here
I'm gonna get that one BC
Five thank you fell six of the five community subs appreciate it. Thank you. Yeah
This game's scaring me like harvester did
Johnny pal you're in for the you're in for it then because that's almost all the 3d. Oh games. They're all terrifying
So much more to go
I
Don't even know what to say
It's very strange
I wonder what the absolute lowest difficulty is
To assemble three complete faces, I don't mess this up
It's this one that one's not right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
What the hell is going on? I had it I did I do I don't what it's confusing
You're bad at that one. Yeah. Oh, yeah
I wonder what how much more should I do? I think I've seen everything
Wait, a a so we're supposed to do that in secret. You have to finish this
I'm not halfway
Think fast you're on the challenge square get a single trivia question, right? Take the controller fine
I'll get this one right. This is the one
Answer all the questions correctly before time runs out world history who sits on the
Chrysanthemum throne. I have no idea. I have absolutely no idea
It's a 33% chance. I get this right
Yeah, well done keep going six the challenge that's a big one
Johnny Powell take the controller and secretly select a row from the matrix. Let's do more trivia. Trivia is good. Trivia is easy
No, no, no, no, I
Didn't mean to do that from the matrix. Let's do the fart noises again
Use the cursor pad and the a button to match identical sounds chat told him. It's okay
Oh
Honey sounds people happy
Again we're going again going again going again
You can't stop on an occupied space roll again
Why not Howard you're still up. I can't stand on occupied space. Why not?
Powers on a roll here
Good job Hummel Howard you go again. This would be so much fun
Magic being one of these actors beat that challenge. This probably was a whole day of the funnest time ever Johnny Powell
Take the controller and secretly select sports trivia
Answer all the questions correctly before time runs out, which martial art was invented by Bruce Lee
Choking
Johnny Powell so far behind isn't he relations the square let's shake rattle and roll
Very impressive. You still control the cyber die
Beat that challenge
trivia
What about the mystery thing from the matrix
We're gonna do the Firefox logo wherever this is or your logo. What's the internet logo? This is
Switched places challenge challenge challenge Johnny Powell take the controller AC
Leisure and travel answer all the questions correctly before time runs out
Where is Fort Knox? Oh, no, I think it's in Kentucky. I think it's Kentucky
Where would you be most likely to eat kimchi? That would be in Korea?
Yes more vines
Bad taste to found love through our dating service. Why don't you and now?
I
Want that so bad, I want that too. I want to be able to see that whenever I want that was incredible
We picked the wrong character we picked the wrong character
Take the controller
Behold the items on the shelves two of the items were not in the group select the item that was what was here
See you got salad cake pie cake pie cake cake. No banana. Oh
my god
Johnny pal it's to you on your thinking cat kids
It's challenge time
Take the controller and secret baby
Now Johnny trivia answer all the questions correctly before time runs out. Oh world history
Who was the first person to fly solo around the world that would be?
That person's distracting me over there Sam mr. Mr. Boeing Sam Boeing
although Redenbacher
Square
You can't stop on an occupied space who's gonna win that's what I don't know it's both me
You've landed on the wheel of torture again
Hey, how are the new day?
We'll be back wait that I'm still waiting and keeping clean
Satan let's get you off that wheel. What do you say?
Okay, hold on what happens if you don't get off
I'm just still on it
Feeling brainy you've got the challenge
Johnny pal take the controller and secretly select a row from the a science
Answer all the questions correctly before time runs out at zero gravity body fluids move towards
ones what
zero gravity body fluids move towards
Eat this bit to feed right? Oh wait, it floats that would be sinking
Nothing I can say to I there's nothing I can say to stop wait absolutely get off the wheel
This guy's dead
You've hit the challenge square
Johnny pal take the controller and sports trivia
Answer all the questions correctly before time all the fluids are going into his brain
See how he does your brain Leonard has been boxing's world champion and how many different weight categories
Who was the Sultan of spot that would be Mickey Mantle a brutal fuck
beat the wheel
Give it your best. Come on Howard. I'm now playing a single-player game. Well, one guy gets tortured
You are no, holy roller. I'm slugger. Let's get you off that wheel
Sit this one out, we'll be back Howard's almost there
Help him. I'm trying to beat the game beat the wheel. All right, fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. I'll get him off
Oh
Very impressive. You still control the cyber die
It's challenge time
Take the controller and secretly select a row from the matrix. This game is really funny and really interesting
But now Johnny, it's like five mini games answer all the questions correctly
I think the budget went all to the green screen and actors in LA in 1989 72 days exceeded the EPA's carbon monoxide standards
How many did in 1990?
72 days exceeded the EPA's carbon monoxide standards. It's probably gonna be a hundred and thirty four. Oh, I thought it was gonna be higher
We're down time to roll
Think think think the challenge square
Johnny pal take the controller and secretly select a row from the matrix
See be Howard take trivia answer all the questions correctly before
Time runs out the fuck literally so bad at children's trivia. All right, ban that person for a week
My what name is dr. Benjamin Franklin Pierce better known as
dr. Benjamin Franklin
Pierce
this Hawkeye
That's not Hawkeye's name Hawkeye is not dr. Benjamin Franklin. Who is this person?
It's not Hawkeye
that's
Hawkeye's name is dr. Benjamin Franklin
I thought I did not know that at all. What was the wanker one take the controller and
Trivia answer all the questions correctly, but not the same Hawkeye runs out not Marvel. Oh
We're not talking about a different series
18th century what name has been taken by the Kings of Thailand? I
Don't know
Shitload of you guys got it wrong. Don't make fun of me
a
challenge square
Johnny pal take the controller and secretly select a row now Howard take
Trivia answer all the questions correctly before time right Thailand fan. What?
Where does the Mary Tyler Moore show take place? I don't I I think it's Baltimore. I don't know. Why would I know that?
Johnny pal omega loss. Stop saying that you don't you didn't know that
I don't know what Mary Tyler Moore is good job Johnny pal
The only thing I remember about Maryland Mary Tyler Moore is throwing the hat in the air. It was like
Roll her hat in here. It's the only thing I know
Planes or statues stat planes
Correctly before time runs out how many seas are named or colors?
the Red Sea
Their green sea blue sea the orange sea black sea red sea black sea
the
Two I think it's just two
Green sea no, there's only two
Four what's this? It's four
There's a blue sea. There's a yellow sea. There's a blue sea
Twisted will be right back
The creatures of the inner air are too powerful for flimsy cotton swabs what you need are teeny tiny chopsticks
When I wear magnet perfume, no man can stay away. The passion could be fatal and now back to the game
How it's really okay. Where was that?
El Squero s. Occupado keep rolling. Good job. I'm gonna get in there almost the top go again
Challenge square
Take the roller and see be a
Answer all the questions correctly before time runs out which film was made first
Frankenstein Dracula King Kong. I think it's Dracula
The Frank's not dry Dracula probably. I think it's Dracula Dracula
For Frankenstein Dracula who spends her first year of the facts of life on roller skates. I have no idea
tutti
Okay, what band went on the worldwide Texas tour in 1976, it's probably see I'd see you talk
Get it without your help
You're still up
Think fast you're on the challenge square
Take the controller and secretly select a row from them
Have to try to get this at least once the cursor pad to assemble three complete. I can't get it
It's just too confusing. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's right, right? That's it
That's it. I got that's right, isn't it?
Shit, it's not right. Fuck
No
It looks right
I thought it was like a chef. Oh
God damn it. Give it your best challenge choke. Whatever. It's fine
Secretly select one of the matrix secretly select your favorite
Have to get this one right I can't just I have to complete them all behold the items on the shelves
Two of the items were not in the group select the
That's an awesome high of a hog calling competition. All right, what's here? What is here? I didn't even look
I think the beans is the turkey breasts or the grapes. I don't know
I'm gonna get this right
Didn't get it I didn't mean to I think Johnny Powell might take this away with a victory here very possible
Beat that challenge
God damn it, man. I have to get this. Come on
That win
Before time runs out, so this guy likes to pretend no stop actress Natasha Richardson is the daughter of what actress?
Who's on the wheel of torture, oh you are still
Johnny Fowler your winner did it I win
Yes, but he's gonna Super Mario into it, okay
There's one more thing that I need to see I need to select expert and none
I just want to see what they do. Did you guys know the 3DO has an L and an R button?
Surprise that exists and then we move on to the next one, which that's a mystery because it's a shitload over there
I'm just gonna pick one up. I can't I can I not skip this
game show cast I
Didn't say okay name is twink. Yeah, they said yeah
I'm gonna take a piss and I'm gonna grab some water
I'll be right back by the time the credits or over we can play it
See you guys in a minute. I don't trade futures. You're gonna literally fucking you're gonna blow up your whole account. Don't do it
cursing
stocks omega low
I want to see something here. I
Want to see what happens when you do the cursor pad to select your contestant then absolutely need to see this guy's
after everyone has made a selection
Okay
Let's do none now wormington. How smart do you think I was gonna say don't put the dog underwater, dude?
Will the next player please select like the pez guys see when all players have made their selection sounds good
expert now uncle Fez how smart do you think you are use the
Set your trivia difficulty level and lock it in with you. Okay, you've that didn't he doesn't he doesn't put his head over the water
Will the throughout the game I will refer to you by your contestants name the object of twisted is really cool
I know how it works. I was a contestant before great now. Let's get
twisted
Uncle Fez you're up first
Thank you. You're on the challenge square
expert, right
Wormington take the controller and secretly select a row from the matrix
All right, let's do this one down here
Pad and the a button to match identical sounds now Howard. He's not the same character
Sounds gonna be harder
Expert huh stop playing this masterpiece. What do you mean? Why would stop playing the masterpiece? Don't you want to keep playing the master piece still up?
on the challenge square
Wormington, okay, hold on secretly select a row from the mate. This is still on expert
There's take the controller and select it archer loud
Use the cursor pad and the a button to the difficulty only for trivia. It's trivia only. Oh
Shit, okay
Are you sure?
Car crash
What is that?
No
Don't say it
Good job. Uncle Fez you guys trivia that it's only the trivia feeling brainy. You've got the challenge
Wormington take the controller and secretly select. Let's do the hard trivia
Trivia answer all the questions correctly before time runs out
What was the first state to be readmitted to the Union after the Civil War?
I know this I know I know I know I know I know I know I know it
Georgia what the hell is up? Why would it be Georgia?
Wormington your turn
Think fast you're on the challenge square fake American
Take the controller and secretly select I'm not even from I'm not in front of this world
Now wormington take the controller
supermarket high-rise
Behold the items on the shelves two of the items were not in the group select the item that one
I have to get this right before I change games
Okay, this is all the stuff. Okay. What is there? Oh
Cheese there was cheese there. Thank you. He got it
Good job, wormington. You go again. All right. Oh, I want to get every one of the other guys turn
All right, dude
What the fuck was that? You can't stop on an occupied space roll again
Very impressive. You still control the cyber. Um
Okay, so no the dog is all the bozo square lose a turn
Uncle Fez good luck
Take a spin. All right on the wheel of torture. I put up one. I'm gonna put in one of the Japanese
I don't I don't know Japanese, but we're gonna see if we can get through it
Contested on bozo space doesn't move on this turn. I'm gonna see I need to get one
That's scary beat the wheel
I just want to do trivia. I'm not gonna beat it again. Good nurse uncle Fez. You're still up
bonus square roll again
Uncle Fez, okay, why is he a pez dispenser? I don't get it. I don't get it
Reference here. I don't understand what the reference is. I don't get it wormington. Take the controller and secretly. So I want trivia
Answer all the questions correctly before because he has a pez on yeah, but okay. Okay, if I was like
Wait, I got this one. There's five
The first president throw out the game ball in a baseball game
Was the only manager to win the World Series in both the American and National Leagues that would be
Sparky Anderson, except I pressed the wrong button. I press see an action. I press see action
All right, let's move on this way more to see twisted. We'll be right back
He's your last two vines. I used to be a wimp a loser that no woman wanted till I discovered hunk juice
It's unbelievable come on down we're giving away everything
And now back to the game
wormington give it your best
It's challenge time what happened
Take the controller and secretly select a roll from the matrix
Oh
Okay
Now wormington's wait a minute controller and selected. I don't want to look. Okay, we'll put it in another game
I'm gonna next is I think wacky racers. It's a Japanese game. I have no idea
We're about to find out
Interactive CD-ROM wacky races
It's Japanese but the thing about the 3do from what I was told is the 3do is not region locked
So I believe I can play whatever I want in here, I'm pretty sure Japanese games work in here
Yeah, this is a TV show. Let's see what it does. I don't know if it's actually region lock you go. All right
Okay, there's 7,000 people here. One of you has to speak Japanese. So you'll be able to help us get through this
Do you who does somebody has to write?
The scariest thing I've seen probably all week future pirates incorporated present. Oh boy. I thought it was Japanese
You know, but wait a minute what?
This whole this is all it's Japanese
Oh, it is Japanese
It's just the cartoon but Japanese what do I do do I press start
This is the same technology that you guys do to get me to talk
All right, something's going on here there's a race and they're gonna they're gonna mess it up
Okay, all right stop here we go is you don't do you race a car in this oh shit
Whoa, this is my car
Accept that car
Now pick a style
Remember once you pick something it's there forever. So make sure you're okay with it
This one has larger reach
You can smash your enemies from in front
You should
Can't even learn a new language to me is I
Cheers to you guys that can do that. Oh shit. Wait
racist TV help
Is there like a it's in English though. All right, hold on help
I don't understand
How is this help this guy's monologuing at me
Oh
Okay, we're gonna do we're gonna do racist TV
See what happens. This is like the the Pokemon game. We watch TV with Pikachu
Was this a show? I'm talking about this exact iteration here. I'll be watching this show
I know it was a cartoon, but
This cannot be skipped by the way, I can't get out of this we're stuck here forever
Which cars do I do lumberjack car
I'm all these these all look very sexual to me
All these cars. It's just like okay. What's what that? Why do you look like this?
Or maybe just I bet on them two machines one click a machine. All right, I'm betting on it like a machine
We're gonna bet yeah, okay bad stop doing that you're gonna hurt us
Okay
Get a special driving. Okay. Now I'm gonna bet on the two cavemen
All right, so we're betting on either
Here we go. This is it
All right, let's go. Come on penis car. Wait, they're in first and second
We didn't the race already start what race is this
We've already saw that oh in first place did I miss a queue
Very inefficient, holy shit
What what bullshit
I lost
The worst thing I've ever seen
um
All right, we're gonna bet who won
All right, let's bet on
I'm just okay. We're gonna bet on I don't even know what this is
We're gonna bet on Shaggy and school
Okay with that we're gonna the next thing I'm gonna do is umbrella car
I did
Umbrella car
Oh
All right, that's us right there come on
Right in the front are we gonna win
Stupid I have to win one of these and I bet on the mustache guy on
What about the actual race man drive a car I'm gonna go the other one I'm gonna see if I can drive a car
There's two modes. There's racist TV and then this trip
What the hell is trip?
Okay, open the door I'm gonna get in the car stealing the car from the laboratory
Wheel why is this a baby toy?
Oh
Insert disk what
What other desk there's no other disk. There's no other disk. I don't know. There's no there's no the desk in here
There's no space for another desk. This is the original box. Wait a minute. Is it behind here?
No, there ain't no second desk in here. What I don't understand. I can't do it. This is like paid DLC or something
Insert
Yeah, we're gonna go to the big night. You know driving the car. No, I'm sorry
Bullshit
Wacky races is not I repeat not a racing game shocked. Yes, me too
Wacky races is split into two parts one part is betting the second part is map and object-finding
Yes, there'll be a little country part of it. Yeah, you don't have a driver's. Okay. Stop talking
What was the second disk I don't have a
Why is it taking so long to say this? Okay. I want to do racist TV. I have to win one
This is my last try. I know exactly who I'm picking by the way
You need to win the gambling to get a card. Are you serious?
That would make sense
I love this one. It's super odd
I
Look it over there and I see a bunch of gems
Take a lot longer than I thought it was gonna be like
37 more games
Okay, let's go
Guy the helicopter
And a special driving card, holy shit you're right
To do that I the actual like seizure warning for real
It was Waluigi this is the universe that Waluigi
I
Want the driving part the real strategy here guys is to pick the same car every time and do it
You can't do it hard
Is that both of my guys? That was the two cars that I picked get the fuck out of here
God give me a fucking break
I
Touch it. Why did you touch it cavemen winning again? Yeah the dragon power. I
Yeah, yeah, I
Don't have to apologize for that. Tell him to
Am I ever gonna win? I don't think I'm ever gonna win. All right, I'm going with
Okay other plane
And then the lumberjack
Okay, how about the two planes both planes both flying machines the helicopter in the plane?
Who wins the TV show all the time?
the data on this
Dick never wins
Shortcut all right. He's not gonna get the planes planes can fly
Why would you you have you bought would you go in there? You can fly you both went in there
Still get a guy in the race. There he is. Oh shit
And go I think that's a win. Come on
Pass him pass him
No
Watch it
Cut his head off
You shitting me and fucking Penelope piston goes in front of us unbelievable
Unbelievable. I did so much work there, too. I
Have to win we get it hasn't even 30 minutes. I'm fine. I'm okay. We're gonna same deal
We're gonna pick the same two people again ryo bait. Thanks for the 10 subs. Thank you ryo bait
And community subs. That's a lot of fucking subs. That's 10
Thank you, seriously
Always pick the same two fucking people. Why are you watching this?
I have to win
One of these times it's gonna happen. I'm gonna I don't care how long the stakes
Chris
Start flying already. He just bombed us. Is that all of us? Was that all my guys wait
Let's look at somebody in right now skip skip it
Okay
Statistically speaking we should pick the caveman. It's a rerun episode
No, but now that you can't pick the caveman because now it's never gonna happen again
That's how illogical the world is I could happen ten times in a row and then when you pick it
It it never happens ever again. I'm doing it
Cavemen and cavemen and the and like the fosters home for imaginary friends crew
Come on
We have cavemen as a backup will wait it will want the fosters home for imaginary friends crew to win
I see a plane in first place and it's pissing me off already
No, all right, it's okay. It's all right. We still have another guy
These cars are made out of shit
What does the steering wheel come off so easily? Where's the airbag?
Who's that thing the plane no somebody pass them somebody pass them
I have to win. I can't just not win one. This game was like 30 bucks. I'm not I have to win
How much was it actually never mind. It was nothing. It was all right. It was 15 bucks
And then we're gonna go Penelope piston
Oh
Come on how many one two three four five six seven eight nine was a ten
Chance to win every single time. We've lost every single time right or a little bit more
Yeah, good not this time I think we're still good I don't think we're in there
Our two characters are not in there
You're you're playing the Foster's home for imaginary friends music. That was me. That was me. That was me
What they've won they don't win ever they don't there's never been an episode where they win
They've never won in a single fucking episode. This is ridiculous
No, they don't win
They're a plot device to teach you lessons
Like brush your teeth and to always like be kind to your neighbor and shit. I'm doing it again
All right, we're going we'll go with a wild card here penis car
We have not seen a single penis car win
We've seen almost every other person win it's been to that heaven we're gonna go with the odds of it's time
No, this is different this is different
Come on Buzz Lightyear take your giant dick and go forward
Oh
That's fine, that's not us that's not us
Wait Penelope Piston passes everybody. Oh, wait, where's mine? No
Don't do it you can't let Penelope
Oh, do the brakes you hit the brakes you fucking idiot
The first place I just do that you could have won we just definitely gas
And I'll be pissed in is a sure bet. I just keep not picking her
Because he's a gentleman
All right, and I'll be pissed in and
We'll be in tweedle dumb up there. I have one twice each. I think it's time to go with the trend. I'm going okay
Why am I so engrossed in this
Game it
Yeah, yeah, that means let's go or something, right
Um, I
Excuse me. Did you that doesn't make any what the fuck just happened. There's anybody else on the course. Oh, it's a dream. Okay
All right
We got a guy in second place right here
Do it
Cross that finish line
Do it. Why are you hitting the brakes again? It's a photo finish you want
That's a photo finish rollback
There it is. Get over there
If only his penis was a little longer
Okay, it's perfectly fine just the way it is but if it was a tiny bit longer
What's a wild card here who hasn't won you if the tank
This they haven't won model t has not won
Kills people I understand like oh put a little bit of oil in the road. You're you're trying to kill all these people
Wow get parried
Now lumberjack doesn't win
He's our guy
Nobody told me to pick the tank somebody actually said it in the chat and I didn't listen
Nobody said it and I didn't listen. I was gonna do it too
Why is that just me?
That character is me
That guy get crushed by a rock
Really speaks to me on a spiritual level
Elmo
Elmo and Penelope the lumberjack. I got it. I got lumberjack and Penelope
I
Let chat vote. I
Would do that. The only problem is I don't want to keep it on this screen for too long because it I just hit cancel
Fuck, it's this is incredibly abrasive and horrible
All right, we'll do it from here we'll do with click map but fuck that stupid thing
Hold on. Ah, it's just so awful. I don't I'm gonna hurt somebody
Link please
Please notice me. Hold on
It's pretty good. All right, we got Penelope and we got lumberjack
Wait, this is the dream who wins the dream one. I forget
Penelope did we actually win? I think this is a win Penelope wins this one. We're good. We're good
Yeah, cuz we get forward and then he backs off right yep, this is it we win
All right, I'm gonna do we'll do click maps, but please be aware that there's gonna be flashing horrible images on screen it sucks
All right, where's my extensions? I'm gonna keep it on this screen for a second. Hold on
Did they change the extension page?
All right, I'm gonna do this because I really don't want to fucking have anybody puke
We're gonna temporarily go like this. You know, who is down here
Lower left is Buzz Lightyear lower right is lumberjack
You know where they are
I'm gonna turn on the click maps in just a second. Let me make sure I can do that. I
Have to win. Okay, you ready?
Go ahead and start clicking, you know where they are take a screenshot. Oh, yeah
I but here's the thing. I can't take a screenshot. This is a console
I'd have to take a screenshot of my monitor capturing the game. You got one
You guys are fucking on top of this like crazy. Holy shit. All right
All right redo redo. Whoa
All right redo you ready? Hey, thanks. Jerma sucks with the five community subs. Appreciate it and
Go
Not oh, that was kind of laggy. All right. It looks like cavemen
They've been a number one so far
All right, cavemen is first click. Wait. No, that's exit. All right. No, forget that cavemen first
Who's second? No exit. We have to win one. I can't I'm not leaving till we win one
Penelope Piston
got about 1200 clicks
All right cavemen and Penelope. I would say those are pretty good choices. Those are safe choices
All right, we got Penelope and caveman. It's better win
You guys win first try I'm gonna be mad I wish Penelope I'm not gonna read that that's fine
I hope you're right. You picked the two statistically biggest winners of the entire
Oh shit, I missed a raid from RT game crowd
Why did that not show up that didn't show up over here
Wait, wait, do I do we win do we win an hour ago? That was a long time ago
You still here everybody. Hi
Welcome to stream
They all left omega low that's what happens in a raid you go to the other channel you spam 10 emotes and then you leave
Oh
You were right
You guys were right. No, you weren't
Oh
Second place does not mean you won. Unfortunately try again. I can't take this and neither can I we have to win
We have to win one. I can't just not win
Even again, are you sure? I don't know if that's a good idea
Please next Jerma games sucks. I actually I don't agree. Actually, I kind of like this
This is so basic and simple, but I don't know. It's kind of doing it for me. All right cavemen
Well
You can't do cavemen twice I can't double down on this bet
Okay
Seeing it looks like it's gonna be tank
Okay, we're gonna I'll go take a choice
Penis card dumbasses. I hope that person's not right because I was gonna say penis car
Cavemen and
If you're the first screen you lose
It's us right tank did we cross first
Can you even win a click, let's see
All right, there's two more
One more after this if you don't get it. Yes can't click right now. Hey, you got it. Hey man. Wait
Okay, I think a tie means it's cavemen and buzz later. I don't think I even need to do it again. No, hold on
All right, I was light year
The second are now
You
Don't win you have to give a hundred subs, that's not fair considering I have no control over any of this
Hey, Ben
cavemen
Alright, let's go
You have to give a hundred subs if you lose. No, that's I'm not gonna pay
I'm looking for $500 on the line. I've lost every single time. You want to put 500 bucks up. No
Oh
Electric fence bit again we've already seen this episode
Who wins this one I
Wasn't any of our cars
Dude, I think we're good
Hey Ben, holy shit. I should have bet on this. I should have been I should have been a hundred subs on this
One time no, it doesn't matter we lose the dragon power again
I kind of want to do like a hundred stuff. Okay, what happens if I win?
You want okay, how about this we each pick a car, okay, I pick a car then you pick a car
My car wins I
Don't know if your car wins. Oh
Give you a hundred community subs fine. What if my car wins?
Yourself scamming yourself. I get nothing. I just get like cool. Well, you did it. All right. Yeah
Okay, wait, I get to pick my car first. I get I get this total selection
I get tie goes to the streamer, right? I get to pick first
This is really really fucking important cheater. What do you mean cheater? I got 100 subs are on the line
Fine you pick first fine
You pick first. Who do you think is going to win? There are 100 subs on the line. Whatever whatever character you pick wins
I'm going to gift a hundred subs if I if my character wins
And I get at least one stream next week
When you guys have to just the whole ever every chat message has to be how awesome I am and how cool I am
Know like oh my god, is he pretending like cool. He she discussed the best. I love him every fucking comment
Every single one doesn't matter how bad I'm playing doesn't matter how poorly I'm doing
You've got to like boost my ego like crazy are the stream of my choosing the deal
Okay, fine cavemen. It is good pick
Okay, imagine not picking Penelope piston in this kind of situation
Oh, you guys are fucked and just for transparency sake
I'm gonna make sure you watch me pick see you have cavemen up there
Here's Penelope piston. Oh you guys are gonna lose. I can't wait for that ego stream. It's gonna be awesome
My pick Penelope piston. Let's go good luck
Come on Penelope get up there. No sign of the cavemen
Where's Penelope? Is Penelope still there? Where are the fucking cavemen? They're not gonna go
Penelope do it no
The cavemen didn't even get any screen time. Okay guys you guys were written out of that episode
Do it again, let's do one more time. Oh you pickin double or nothing. Um
Guys, you're starting to get into the point where now you make it you want me to have to I have to dump a thousand
Dollars into subs. I don't know if I know we're not double or nothing. This is not double or nothing
Neither one of us won
Nobody won
Haven good pick. I'm sticking with my guns here and I'm going for an LP again
Let's go rematch
Just to make sure, you know, I'm out of wire
No
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
This is gonna be the one
Get those cavemen out first screen means you're out
Come on
Come on do the like and then get hit by a rock guys
Fuck those cavemen get them out here
Let's just got Viagra that's a win. That's a win. I get it. I win
stream of my choosing
You guys have to boost my ego the whole stream. It has to be only thing you write
Yes
Yes, I win. I had a feeling I had a feeling that it was gonna be that I picked Penelope so many times
cavemen won too many times
Buzz Lightyear didn't win once. I don't know. Don't do it. Not not don't do it right now. This is urban double or nothing
No, I don't know. That's bad idea
No, you just have to win and leave
You guys are doing the gifted subs are going key 20 community subs
I Elliot I a Elliot 10 community subs, but you guys already we has won. That's it. It's over
20 from zap X
You guys win to 20 from zombie eater. Whoa
Okay, all right settle down settle down. That's a hundred
Three lich all right settle down settle down
So no, I you I can't win twice, okay?
That's a hundred community subs from phylac three lich five from labster five from royal rogue
Holy shit. You guys are doing you guys are going over. What was it owed five more from Klosky?
20 oh my god five from Jamie to 803
Five from Van Kia. I think they gotta go out. That's it. We're going out on top next game wait
No, I have to do the thing. I got a card right 50 community
Oh my god, dude 50 community subs from zap X you guys are going nuts
Jesus it's so many. That's too many
How many subs is this it's like 300 talking about double or nothing just tripled or nothing
Sombra I so my thanks for five subs 50 from zap a hundred from phylac three 20 20 20 20 20 20 Jesus
I from Doc's rocket five from destroy dude. Oh my god turn off the smart maps
All right, I got one look
Urban let's go
Oh, yeah, do you want to go yeah
Put it in let's go destroy do thanks with five subs wait. Oh, we this is a first-person mode
Special map items
Go yeah go
I
From fungal or I from yeet god fire from both air you guys are going absolutely crazy. Oh
So what do you do on this is this a hidden object game?
We said eight possible racers two choices two out of eight or one fourth chance of winning or point two five or point
seven five chance to fail
For example after 15 tries we can calculate the chance of losing every time by raising it to the end of tries
two point seven five
Up up arrow 15 equals point 14
In other words, there is a ninety eight point six percent chance of winning at least once after this many tries or germa sucks
Stop where are we?
What is this this is stupid
What planet are we on live laugh love lucifer 5 Zurich 5 blue comet 5
Tona Kaiga 5
guys
Blackout 5. Why are you guys giving so many subs right now?
Labster 5 gun. What was that? Welcome to urban land
I
From Aikido special
AGB clown 10 community subs. This is some this is like 500 subs. This is fucking outrageous
We're supposed to do
That motherfucker on a cereal box. What's the cereal that guy on?
Max honey, like honeycomb. What is what is it the bear?
I
Are free 64 5 sub
Poison type 5 sub. It's just like 5 subs a second
I said this before I don't say it again that you this is like you guys you guys are trying to put me in
Another tax bracket
Is it weird that I we haven't been able to understand a single thing anyone said but I get it all I get it
What are you doing in this car?
What are you doing
This is my guy
Okay, all right, we're gonna move on to the next game I think we've we've
Exacerbated all things. What does that say?
Observatory top of the city five docents good for one person. Here's what you have
This is the strangest game ever
Okay, it's an adventure game now, yeah, this is weird like I don't have the line for this right now
All right, we're gonna move on
Coming up next is who knows I don't want to flash those
Colored bars in your face. I'm gonna go like this. I think that was a good one
I would give that a solid B plus I play Gex
We go right to Gex, what do you think like X let us pick this too many there's like this
So many games back there. You can't I mean Gex is the Mario of the 3d. Oh
Somebody's give 31 subs zap X another 31 community subs. What on earth is going on right now? This is fucking insane
You know, I'm gonna I'm gonna piss I'm gonna get some water. I'll bring it back. I gotta I'm gonna this is insane
You're back, I'm gonna not mute my microphone. All right, we're doing it manually. Sorry about that. I couldn't find Gex
It was underneath a huge pile of games. Here we go. Here comes Gex one of the
Exclusive a lot of these are exclusive 3d. Oh, here's some history for you
Gex was supposed to be the crash bandicoot Mario or Sonic of the Panasonic 3d. Oh, and then
Unfortunately, a couple of years went by and he turned out he was selling car insurance to people instead what he does now
Some lore for you. Yep
Yeah, yeah, all right that sure that was a dad joke, but I'll I can do I can do some dad jokes sometimes
It's fine. Don't tell me I'm not allowed to make a dad joke once a year
Crystal dynamics Gex and the Gex character are gone crystal dynamics. I think they still make shit don't they?
It all started so simply. I had just finished my usual morning routine of nude funkercise
Fired up the barka lounger grabbed a quick bite to eat and prepared to watch some serious, too
Little did I know
My snack was sent
by reds get poisoned
Okay, yes, you got sucked into the TV
reviews
We got
This doesn't belong on the disc it really doesn't
You have soiled the timelessness of this game by putting trailers for other games on the main menu. You just kind of have
By the way, I own this
No, you'll be seeing this
The trailer for like an hour from now
Great. That's it
It's just a trailer for a basketball game. That's it. There's nothing else there. What's the name of that game?
What does that game come out what's the point of that I have no idea, okay
Was up this year damn sound voice
Hail whip jump run
He's the same people that made Marvel's Avengers still dynamics
dynamics made
Marvel's Avengers holy shit
Yeah
Let's get it all that's unbelievable video deck level one video deck
Save file company got worse
Enter a level stand in front of a working TV and press the a button
That's the only working TV is down here
It's not the same people at the same
It's like Mario world
Frankie and Haley
Whip jump run. Oh
Shit, this is actually pretty fun
Fine level remote controls to turn on new level TVs and hit him. Oh, it's just shitty gas
What are you talking about? Yeah, what power balls for one health pointer eat them for special powers?
Castlevania, this is pretty fun
Get a springboard tail, what do you how many of these you need to collect is like coins games gex is so cool
power up to
do shit
Bubsy and gex are dating gex and bubsy our boyfriends. It's always I don't know why I'm just I don't know why I decided to
Read that one. I hit this. Oh
Shit, can I go down and get it?
3 2 1
You always read that one. Yeah, cuz it's the one thing that's just sticking out every time
As I'm surprised you don't like gex he's one letter of removed from Jax can I crawl? Oh, I did it
level one one completed
I'm trying
What does it remind me of
What game am I playing right now? It's not gex. What is it?
Con country, yes, there it is. Thank you got the exact same vibe is don't come country
No, not a clogged toilet. I get in there. I get in there
Run and slide or something. Oh
Shit, dude this verticality in this game getting me
rabbit
Why can't I make that jump G for announcer?
G for announcer voice. Is it the same person or are you just saying that?
Does that mean I
Just skipped the whole level
He for his back by the way. Yeah, I saw
That was easy. You got it. Come on. No you game. What appeal does G for having 20 20?
I've very long time
Well here like I'll tell you exactly what you mean by that aren't they doing like a please come host shows on our network thing
I
Saw that right
You do it
What would I do?
Wait, you can grab the edge. This is awesome. Yeah host
I'm not a host. I can't do host work. I'm not well just okay. Look, I'm not good at being me in front of a camera
I'm good at being other people in front of a camera. I'm very bad at being Jeremy in front of the camera
You get I mean you give me a fucking ski mask and I'll be something. I'll be a weirdo. You know, I mean
I'm dead you you give me like a character that I get to be and I I'll do great
I've lost. Oh
Shit, come on. Really? Oh checkpoints. Nothing. I'm gonna speedrun it. Come on
Bugleberry to post
Fuck I just got hit in the head by the knife bugleberry on the g4
Their ratings are gonna die. I
Like this feature. This is really cool
Honest, right?
When you get a hundred of these you get an extra life
Is that our word?
Wait something up there. How do I get that? Is there a double jump or anything? Oh
You have to actually damage boost up here. What does this do?
It's another life oh I just broke another life is what you're saying
Hold down while jumping to yeah, I know I know
Try damage boost this
Mom this is the greatest game of all time
Pretty good. It's the first time I've ever played it
Wacky racers was better
Well, okay, wacky. Wait wacky wacky. I can't say wacky racers was not a better video game, but
It was more it was more interesting to me
Does that make sense? Right? It's by far not a better game
Wacky racers is not a better game at all then get
Stand in front of the exit. Okay. Yeah, there it is
Let it be level two and three
this is the kind of game that you would just keep your mouth open and just sit on the couch and play it and
Did you just puke kill your TV man?
Try to make like a Bart Simpson kind of character Bart Simpson and
Character and what was it for the lights in your house off?
Which TV should return on the one on the bottom one of the top the d-pad to choose remote
Hey, that's not the one I turned on illusion of choice
Brave danger
Well that hurt
Can't lift people to death. This is a ripoff of super bra. Oh
Super bra
L
TV man, it's Bart Simpson trying to be worse. That's Bart Simpson
All right. I just killed a guy that guy's huge. Who was that? What was that?
You get it
Casket wait work like link it does this must be power-ups
Well, I got the flower. That's good
Why do you why do I get attacked by Duke Nukem? No, that's the slaughterhouse guy
Splatter house not slaughter house splatter house
They make that game too reference
References is all gecks is
TV shows on amy made this
Crystal dynamics did oh my goodness. I
Get it. I
Did I got it?
sick
Don't fall down if I fall that I'm dead
Sorry, mr. Presley. I
Was pretty sick. All right, what's this thing? Do gas register?
Open the can of what the photo wait save pictures of you
Give me that picture the checkpoint. Oh, okay. That's cute. That's a cute way to do that
Money this looks like a shield right the lag in the game if bosses and gets
Yes, there are I think I'm so confused. What's not is the health up top, right?
There are 100 bosses and gags
Very good
Good job
That's a good job
platform is pretty fun the platform
No, I said was I'm just lying when they do that
It is though
Mr. Remote I did. Oh fuck. I missed a remote was I supposed to all right. Let me get the remote
Where was it? What did I miss?
I'm fucking so mad, but I can't show it to you. I can't show it to you. I'm so upset
I have to be very very careful. I don't wanna be screaming. It was right there, too. Sorry the checkpoints right there right here
Make it again. Yeah, good spread it spread it everywhere. I
Want you to show my grandkids that I was this remote
No, I'm just saying I don't does it does it I don't care it doesn't bother me
It's bothering him. No, it's not
Take it was bothering you. No, I wouldn't I would say don't do that
Show my grant. Well, okay
There's nothing wrong with that photo
Guys replace the background with me sitting at the beach or with a pool behind me
What's wrong with that?
Where's the remote? Where is it? Oh, I thought this is the top of this thing. Did I destroy it or did I get it?
Where'd it go? I get it. I got it, right? This place is weirder than 4th of July at Rick James place. It is bubsy
They saw bubsy and they were like wow that game sucks absolute asshole
We can make a bubsy character that does the same thing that bubsy does but not have the game making one to throw up and
Punch yourself in the face a hundred times
Like the slime boys nice job
He thinks he's funny lol
What a find a videotape and your game will be saved when you beat the level he thinks he's funny
Me and one for me for me and one for me
Saying that you're freaking me out
Immediately lost it that always sucks in Mario the worst sound to hear in Mario is
Hey
Nice the interlaced TV I
Love this power-up. I don't eat anything but this that was sad. He said that in a crying voice
We should be laughing at that. Oh
Shit, what have I done? Checkpoint right there an old windows cursor
It really is
Console sucks. No, it does not are you kidding me?
What did you what did you just do? What did you just say? I?
There's no way that I can't believe what you said
No way
It's called so sick. What are you talking about? It's called. So doesn't suck. What do you want about it? Who sent you?
It's a spike
On them
That camera
How do I get that?
Radio fucking sucks. It doesn't know it does not how dare you say something like that
Can you imagine unironically?
Dot dot dot dot dot dot dot text text text text text text. You know, I mean
It still hit me up
Don't fall in that water
I'm gonna give us another ten minutes. I like it, but I
Like it, but you know, it's one of those scenarios. I like it, but
Speed run on this game
We got that info. What are you minutes? I'm gonna say 30 minutes. It's only so fast. You can go through these levels
I want that full health careful. I don't want to mash on the controller. This thing's expensive
It's a 30-minute nap music's not good
Yeah, yeah, this could be better radio cost like $800 we have lunch no idea
It's pretty expensive now
799 holy shit, that's insane
It was 699
What was their intention with 3do?
It wanted like a big home entertainment system, but
What eventually didn't they want to have like into the fully interactive movies on here and shit?
It was a goal with this radio they never achieved. What was it?
Come on fuck it's ten, right?
Well, I got a remote. Holy shit. I got a remote
Oh
Let's end this level so I can get away. I'll get out of here. Okay. Okay. That was weird. Don't fall in
dangerous very very dangerous
It's pretty good cat puke noises. I would say there's a remote right there, right? No, what is this tape?
That is wild
That's my favorite one. Oh, that's why that's wild stuff. That's Johnny Carson
Nice touch. I have a remote. I didn't get a remote. I thought I got one from the bonus round
We told you yeah, but I thought I
Know I don't have to do this. Oh, come on. No
I'm gonna go very fast again. Get it. I care about any power-ups go
No, no, no, no, not next. Not next. Not yet. Not yet. Wait, wait
This is the flagship game of the entire console. Just let me get to the first possible. We just watch
On ps1
Fuck that. No, what are you talking about? So ps1?
Wait, this is it's not the flagship 3d. Oh game. I thought this was an exclusive 3d. Okay, this is fun PlayStation
It even runs better on the ps1
Come already back to where I was army men was the flagship
All right, that's not bad speed I don't want anyone to tell me that wasn't pretty good speech
We get back here immediately and get the remote. I got it. Let me get the first one. All right, where is the remote?
Need for speeds radio is awesome. I have that it's over there
Only five minutes remain
Where is this?
I'm gonna walk by it where oh shit. Okay, I got it. Yeah
That was gex
It's just I'm getting out of here. I
Thought I could have momentum and jump and you can't have you can't have momentum and jump did I get the
Finish it. I can't I don't want all right. I will
I'll do all right. I'm gonna finish it. I finished it. I will go go go go go go go go. Oh god. Damn it
Fun game. It's great. What is a platformer and like whatever
Gex is awesome. It's a flagship game flagship game for this radio. Go get it one day. It's good. I like it
I'd like it, but 30 minutes is up next
More fun. It wasn't are you guys have a choice?
You can I need ones in the chat for original John Madden football
Need for speed it's too. Oh, I gotta save this one for last. It's gonna be so fun
I
Hit streamers choice next and it's gonna be fucking awesome
Here comes the original need for speed X is cool. This is 3do
Classic console
Yeah, X enter the gecko was released in 1998 on the Gameboy color. Yeah, if you want to play the fucking fake version
That's okay guys in in 40 years. My gex copy will be worth like five grand. That's alright. No, it won't
I feel like I'm gonna think I love this game or I'm going to hate it. I think I'm gonna love it or hate it
Okay, I gotta tell you a MIDI track does not work on this footage
Doesn't sound very badass. Is this real footage though? I'm confused. It's a real footage game
You actually drive a car
It is real footage. Oh, yes
road and
Track presents the need for speed. Well, this is it whatever red blooded land love and land speed record want to be ever wanted
Free ticket in the rock of your dreams again one way to camera pointing down ride. You won't die looking up
Fasten your seatbelts
EA Canada
Still exist. How do I play?
Start I press start. Oh, it's waiting. Oh, look at how cool this guy is
All right. What do I do?
What do these mean?
This is I this is scrapbook. I don't know what to do with this. Okay, I'm gonna click on him
Alright, this is how it works
You can stroll this puppy out and go up against the best times or you can stick your ego on the chopping block and make
This an old-fashioned gunfight. What does that mean? Is that a race? Is that a fight? Is that like a test?
I'm taking is that what is that? What is that? What's he referring to?
Did I just order something from a diner? I don't know what that was
I'm gonna click the road
city
11.8 miles from the tranquility of suburbia to the pandemonium of the urban jungle
This route opens up with gentle freeway and winds its way to the bowels of the city's underground
Oh deep poopoo. He said bowels snaking everywhere. That's quick
It overpasses concrete barriers long winding tunnels. It's all here for you, but watch out for traffic
It comes up real quick when you're at speeds these cars want to travel
187 miles. Why would you ever drive that fast on a regular street?
Let's go, it's like my car at Lamborghini Diablo VT next
All wheel drive helps with the VT's 492 brake horsepower to the ground up to 15% of the power is put through to the
Front wheels don't care about any of it. I don't care about any of these things low speed turns
But the rear drive care I don't care about the coordinates. I don't give a shit about how fast you go
I don't need the things to spread $252,000. All right, whatever. I don't you see your math problems. I get it
It's fast. You just could look me in the guy look me and go car goes very fast
Dangerous first is in trouble. This one is hydroplaning cool
Zero zero to sixty. Yeah, I love the zero to sixty shit who cares
Zero to sixty in ten seconds. Oh, were you in a school zone? You're under arrest
When does zero to sixty mean anything helps put the VT's 492 brake horsepower to the ground up to 15
No, I don't want to watch the video again. Get me out of here when you are racing. You know, what are you gonna wear?
You're racing this
You're commuting to work with this thing. Good thing this thing goes zero to sixty
So I can be at the red light and step on the gas and then get a three hundred dollar speeding ticket
Yeah, that's pretty biased as people used to drive by my house at like 80 miles per hour
Yeah, I'm a little biased. How do I get away from this video?
Wait, what is this? These are other cars. Okay, I press B. Does B leave
The wrong side of the road he's gonna hurt somebody
He was swerving into the other lane. I'm gonna play the game. How do I play the game?
Is it not a game the small size of the Yarek? Okay, how do I go back?
select
Okay, we're good. Okay. This has a wheel on it. I'm assuming that means drive the car skill level. Sure
Audio this is the options menu
Okay, this is the options menu
Just drive the car. Do I get to pick my car? How do you drive? We get a three two one
What's the three two one go? He has the parking brake on how do you turn the parking brake off? I'm in neutral
Oh, there we go. Got it
No, that's reverse
More than you bargained for too real for you. How are you? I'd keep this little episode quiet
Why are we in the woods? Did we just murder somebody together? We just bury a body. I don't understand
I don't know. I'm gonna put my name in
Real height
There's no context to any of this am I lying on the ground in agony, okay, so let's get it into board
Do you have the manual? I don't think it matters. Okay. Here we go. Is it in drive put it into fucking drive
I don't know how I get up with it. I was a manual first gear. All right second gear
Let's go third gear fourth gear fifth gear. Are these people not part of the race?
But it's odd. Is it auto shifting? There is there's that motherfucker right there in that red car. I think she's gonna get away
Nope
Get the police on me. Why is he still such a little blob? All right, here we go
I'm going like how fast we go like 500 miles per hour
Come on. Hurry up judging from the dashboard. This is like my grandfather's car. What are we even driving? Don't shift so soon
It's on auto. I'm not doing that shit. I got a ride in the breakdown lane
I got 160 miles per hour. This car doesn't go faster than a hundred and like 70 miles per hour
What is it the pass them? I passed them
Yet, how do you win the race he didn't say there was a beginning a middle or an end
He just made fun of me and looked down at me three times. How do I win this? He's long gone
I blew by him a long time ago. Where's the end this level? There is no end how yes
There is that has to be you think that guy just gave up and was like, all right. Well, whatever. I'm done
You beat me. Why am I still going? Oh, that was I did it. I beat him
167 miles per hour top speed
Steal becoming one. Yeah, he waxed my ass. Congratulations waxed his ass. He was in the lead for like 15 straight minutes
Are you sure he didn't win?
replay highlight reel
Let's take a look at the highlight reel. It's just real time
Okay, it's
We can skip that part
Okay, just get out. What is it is the audio is too early. What do you mean like the in-game audios too early one guy?
Okay, I'm doing it again. I'm racing the same guy. I'm gonna do the same thing
different track
I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. You've waited for me
Wax his ass. I'm gum. What do you think I'm trying to do?
Change the camera, but now it looks like an ugly video game this ticking sound
I don't get it. You go all the way up the police show up do anything last time. Yeah, I just hit the cop
That's exist cop car. I just hit him. Wow, you suck pull over should I where is
Speeding I look dumbfounded. Here's the goal
Can I catch up after getting a speeding ticket crash into him?
I must killed that guy the cars in neutral right now. No this am I gonna get two speeding tickets. All right, come on officer
I'm right here
The cars so I got out of one somebody pulled up another one and I'm still about to pass this guy
Shit, it's gonna be a photo finish. Please. Shit. Your horn is the biggest wuss horn. I've ever heard in my life
That's not intimidating at all, dude, that's does not say fuck you
Oh shit a cop's gonna get me game just didn't let me crash into okay, but I'll pull over what about him
Look at how fast he's going. Yeah, pull that guy over my pulling him over. I can't drive. I'm holding down the button
What's going on? Well, I do believe I got me my first UFO capture
You better start turning green real fast gizmo or the National Enquirer ain't gonna buy my story. What I got to I get two cars left
Assume the position fast boy. Now you're in the fast lane to the county jail. Did you walk up to the car with a shotgun?
Let's go
Okay, you want to talk about like 20 20 video cuts you put handcuffs on me, which takes about one second
They were probably probably 12 cuts and that three seconds to put on a pair of fucking handcuffs
How many times I have to beat this guy before we can is over you didn't win. All right, I'm gonna win
I need first-person driving. It helps. I want to see what happens if I beat him
Don't have to beat him. It's gonna be the fastest. You've ever seen somebody do this course stop pretending
It's no such thing as pretending while you're going 160 miles per hour. It's no nuance at 160
Don't pretend to go 160. I I cannot do that right now
The old strategy was just blow by the cup. I'm going too fast. I'm gonna catch up to me. Why doesn't he spin up?
Where's his?
Total cascading over on the side five out of ten link don't even bother
I got one guy said not to do it no more mess it around
I really don't want to do this again. I need to beat him three times. Sir. So don't even understand how that
He's gonna be right here. It's okay. Forget about the cop. I'm gonna blow right by him again and clear here
He is absolutely gonna buy him ride the breakdown lane. That's the best strategy so far this thing up to 160 easy easy
I'm coming up quick. See you later. All right, good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good on to the next chapter
I passed him on the inside. You know, it looked at chat. I looked at chat. All right, let's beat him again
I'll tell it look if it's if it's a five out of ten is average
Let's take a look you got the nerve to push the envelope man got some skill
That's that's what it takes. I'm hanging out with this guy in the woods every time. I mean that is a what do you want me to do?
round two
continue
Next game I got to beat this guy three times we change
So much faster than me off the gun. It's like it's the type type of car that he has
I'm so bad at you. I need to be driving in first person. I can't drive like this
I need the wheel to guide me you guys want to stay on the driving theme should I put in road rash?
We want something completely different and John bad. No, I think we're gonna hold on to John bad
There is no music. That's weird. Where's the music idiot move the radio on? I don't have a radio. Well by the cop
No, go go go go go quick quick quick quick. Go go go. He's right behind it go
120 oh you keeping up with me, dude. It's going 120 miles per hour right now. Where's this?
What why did I reach out? I gotta stop looking at that. Don't look at that every gun
Oh my god, you gotta be kidding me. Don't look at chat again red guy coming up on this side
I got a Mario car. No, no don't let him go in front of me. No, he passed me. I'm gonna get in trouble
Oh, it's okay speeding ticket. Here's your reddit gold, sir. I'm gonna crash again if I'm not careful
I don't want to lose this it's so if the cop passes you that's how you get inside
Oh over the checkpoint very close very close. You pulled it off
The next thing you know, you're gonna be getting a sponsorship a race with the big boys all mama, but yeah, I hate this guy
Here we go. We got a new cutscene
first
speed
champion on the road and in your face what a drive what a
Driver all the scale all the thrill hard driving man. You blow me away
Yeah, the thrill the finish line is just the start man. You are bound for glory with your foot to the floor, baby
Wow, you need to drop the exposure on your webcam and put up the lighting in your room
That's why it looks like that guy
Okay, so do I just race him now what oh shit, okay, is that the whole game I
Just beat the game
Link link. All right. I'm clicking now. I got it. That's not even the right one
That's another one. That's a cop handing you something through the window. Not the right one. Is this the right win?
This is the right one. That is not worth it
It's not worth it also wrong. Okay, how about what give me the right one then? All right, whatever city
Alpine coastal. All right, we're going coastal
Definitely going coastal
This is the last race I'm gonna do and then I'm just gonna turn it off and then we'll put it in I
Think we change I'm gonna change the theme up a little bit here
Yeah, it's time for a theme change. They pick a different car
What happens if I kill him? Oh, what a race?
All right, I'm done. This was fun. I'm done moving on what we got next. I mean, this was not fun
Madden all right. I'm gonna put in madden. I'm putting it in we're gonna get it off with I'll give you a choice
your choices are
John Madden the original video game on a sports direction here. You can either do John Madden or
Wicked 18 which is a golf game one for John Madden two for wicked golf. Yeah, this is tough
neither one of them
Do an actual poll. All right, we'll do an actual poll because this is very difficult for me
There's drop all John Madden or wicked golf by the way
I want to make sure that I gotta get this has got to be very clear
Just because it's called wicked golf does not mean it's interesting. It's golf. So could be pretty pog
I don't know. We'll see John bad. No, it's original FMV John Madden
There's at least probably five to ten minutes of John Madden talking into the camera. I think it's gonna be wicked golf
Let's go to BRB for a second. I don't blow your eyes out third option. There is none
There's so many games back there
We got a look we have to get through the wicked 18s of the world before we get to the Jurassic Park interactive
That's gonna be holy shit. No, we don't
Yeah, we do
About 40 of these I didn't buy like the ten good ones. I bought all 40
TV so why'd you do that? Because in 20 years is gonna be worth five grand
Wait, is this the thing that the arcades of the ball and you spin the ball as hard as you can golf?
There's the green why are we playing golf in
Egypt does not look at golf course because it's a wicked golf. Oh, sorry wicked 18 same damn thing. Who cares? Oh
whole number one par five champion teams
540 yards members teams 520 yards
The starting hole of devil's course is a part five that requires considerable skill water
Flanks both sides and rocks flow perilous. Why is this an eSports intro a good drive on a normal course may only find the rocks here
Fortunately, the approach is pretty easy after running this gauntlet. So a birdie is usual for this hole
Okay, use the driver every time I got it. It's the American Ninja Warrior intro
Okay member data. I mean was gonna what the hell game devil's open player one. That's an alien
Okay, sure. You weren't good at driving last game. What makes you think you'd be good at golf?
I'm gonna get a hole in one the first hit
First par two or par three that's available. I'm gonna get a hole in one
Just cardboard cutouts. Those are not real people
All right, first day player one versus Alan. Okay start this 17 holes here
How do you play him Alan the fucking volcano on the right he up. Oh, okay. Is he saying
Direction, okay direction
Where is the hole?
Pretty wood one wood. All right. I want the one wood. I'm just gonna hurt as hard as I can. Give me the one wood
Okay, you sure about that? Yeah, I'm sure
stance
Slice the fucking ball. Oh
Shit, that's just every single person at the driving range even go hit golf balls the driver
There's always somebody that just fucking skims it every single time. All right, let me try this again
Give me the one wood. No, I want the one wood. I'm going full power
I'm happy Gilmore in this shit over the mountain again
Embarrassing golfer I've ever seen
Music is so okay. Let's try it again. This guy's shit-faced
Well player one really probably shouldn't have come to the course after four Red Bull and vodkas
He's one of the top seeds. It's unfortunate to see him like this
then
People
Holy shit that bounce. Are you kidding me? There was some pinball level shit right there
All right, what do we think right through the middle? I'm gonna go right through the middle
What do you want to do to wood get it into the volcano? No, I'm going right through the middle bingo
How many strokes is this? Don't you just pick it up after seven? It's on acid
Okay, what point is the caddy just go? You know what? I'm gonna take over here, dude
Oh
Fuck so like every single golf game ever you do the power and then you press a again when it gets into the little middle
Thing right that's what I'm doing watch ready. I'm not doing it on purpose watch okay here
We go ready that bottom part is where I want to hit it here. We go power
Hey, hold it hold a all day and let go of a I try holding it and then let go of it
I'll try I am holding it
We good we live yeah, my internet didn't turn off my internet was fine
I don't that wasn't on my end my internet was perfectly fine. It's weird the twitch servers get nuked or something
That was weird. All right. We're back. I haven't even moved. Did you use that time to go look up how to play?
No, all right. Let's go which has been doing that lately. Oh, oh, oh well sorry about
Whatever 270 yards. Let's go. All right. Let's go. Yeah, that wasn't that was not on my end. Oh fucking twitch servers. What the fuck
Fucking I'm gonna miss that was such a bad miss that was a practice swing
So do I have to do it before I'm trying to do it while it lands in the thing in the middle
Here we go ready
Up up right. I'm pressing a I can't I don't get it. I do it. I'm doing it too early
Are you pressing a on the orange part? I'm trying to all right. I get it. I get it. I understand what's going on
I'm going way too far up cut the viewer count in half. Well, it's whatever. It's all good
You did this. All right, dude. Give me a fucking break
Really? Really?
Gonna just gonna bounce that shit off the rock mine my turn. What do you think it's far enough away? Hey, thanks for the placement
Alright, can I can I hit it with it? Can I get it with the driver? I'm gonna go really small. Fuck the putter
I don't use putters only driver only one would
The crowd there is no crowd to hit those are paper cutouts. There we go on the green
That's like plus two meter. All right, it's a little bit slightly elevated. Can't even change clubs it in there
Okay, it's nine feet straight in. All right. What's that our player one plus twelve? What do you get? This is for birdie?
Wait, you got it. Damn it. I was gonna say that would have been way worse than me
Well number two coming up am I even on the board? All right now I get how the game works
We're going 300 yards straight ahead how much THC zero, all right
We got to try to get it right on the mountain. You could we sports music was that going?
Alright, I mean for an amateur. That's fine. I'm going right for the top of the mountain 318 yards
That's it's been son of a bitch. I flew too close to the Sun. It's alright
I'm gonna make it up right now. I'm gonna pay attention to chat. What how do you what what I have the same caddy
Wait, how am I supposed to do this? This is possible. There's a gigantic rock in the way
I got a ping-pong this 125 yards. I'm gonna go with 140 get it up the ramp. Holy shit. It worked
No, it didn't what? Oh, how did you do that? I can't hit mine over that. You're the pigeon wedge over it
I'm not far behind him 35 yards to the hole pitching wedge again. All right
I'm gonna take a little bit off the top halfway shit. You're not gonna get it. Oh
Can I get over this mountain? It's gonna be too hard. It's way too hard. No, it wasn't the shit
That shadow is really deceiving. Where'd it go? Where did it go? I went across the other side. All right, fuck it
Whatever. Give me the give it to me. I did skim it up the mountain. That's good. Get on the green
We're on the green. Good. No, we're not. Do I just keep bouncing it back and forth? Fucking give me a break
Alright, can I take two strokes and put the ball wherever I want? It's not possible. It's not gonna do anything. I do it
Let's be fair though. If you saw this on TV for golf you now watch golf when no fucking way you would before that
I made it up to the second cliff. All right, we're on second cliff. What the did I make it? I made it
I made it I made it I made it I made it I made it I made it I made it I made it
What should I use pitching wedge? No, no, no, no putt this shit. Just hit really hard too hard. Yeah, that was a little too hard
I'm just gonna try to putt up this I'm gonna putt up this thing. I'm gonna hit it up the mountain
It's gonna it's gonna slide up. See that's all it took. That's all it took
I had to putt it up the goddamn mountain. Yes. Fuck. Okay. I'm fine par. What am I at?
Did I get slaughter ruled rowing? I'm plus 14
wasting
Everybody's time at this tournament. What an asshole like to just end it like just do it you wasting so much
Everyone has shit to do, you know turn around and have a tan tantrum and hit the fucking ball drive it into the ocean
Just put it in dude. Fuck you
Okay, like
Security remove this guy get security and just put him in handcuffs and get him out of here
How light does it have to be?
Shit, I almost got it. Yeah, finally finally Jesus Christ. We've been sitting here for so long, dude. Hurry up and I turn around
I'm like, thank you. Thank you. I do like a bunch of files. I tip my hat. Is it possible?
Okay, I'm good plus 19 already dread. Holy shit. You just gave 50 community subs my god hole number three par four
Champion tease. Holy shit. That's a ton of subs. Thank you, Freddie
Freddie dread ladies and gentlemen
We also had 50 bucks from zombie eater and 50 bucks from sir canine back-to-back
Which is an insane amount of money. They said a bit of big fan as zombie eater says a bit big fan of yours
You always succumb to clicking links in chat though
I'm offering you a simple challenge
I don't think you can go through an entire week of streaming without clicking a single link from chat
Address this challenge if in reply if interested or ignore this
Now it's impossible. That's a physical impossibility. No way and then sir canine says German
This is the 27th time I've reached out about my dork cube
My friends are considering leaving because I lost my mind waiting for it. Please reach out to me. My friends keep telling me
It's a scam
That's a scam. You got scammed. Sorry, dude. Let me beat this guy once. I'm gonna try actually pretty hard
I'm in front of him. Even if I'm in the trees damn it. All right
I'm gonna get I gotta get in front of him you hit it now hole it out
All right, come on winds coming in two miles per hour bitch and wedge this shit 72 yards. Let's go
This is snow level music. Holy shit. That's so accurate. Ah
That's unbelievable. All right. I want to go all the way
further than him shit
35 yards away
Third stroke. Let me get a par. Please eat shit. I'm right there. I'm right there. I'm gonna fuck this guy up right now
sweet approach
talks
Ain't got nothing dickhead get out of the way get out of the way. I'm gonna beat him. This is it
I gotta be very careful. All right, this is slightly elevated
I got a bump this to the right a little bit. No
Yeah, I'll put to the right a little like right there. It's straight. Should I straight how much power though?
All right, I'm gonna say quarter powder a quarter pounder. Oh, no, is it I was right? Yeah, I was right
I should have listened to my gut
Okay
Stroke four stroke five
Dammit. All right, this thing's coming up. I'm not doing 18 holes if I don't get a hole
Okay, if I get a hole in one right now
Here's the opportunity
There's only 160 yards I'm gonna get a hole in one right here it is very possible. Yeah par 3 I can do this
Let me at least get par. So you got just a bowling alley
I
Didn't close dude, you're fucked
160 yards full power with a 6-iron. We're gonna go for iron. It's a win only one it in there
That's everybody naked. Why is everybody dressed like they're at the beach? It's a golf tournament
I can get it right here 11 mile per hour win right there. What's it look like?
Come on, I can get it. Give me the putter. Let's go. Why is there sand trap on the green? That's a great question
Yeah, I have no idea. Oh
Oh
Procedurally generated it would be funny. Oh fuck off. Sure. Okay get out of here, buddy
This is a par I think I have to hit this and then the disc can come out of the tray and I can go
Piss this is straight on straight on not too hard. Not too soft. Just I don't know like this. I went nice par
Thanks. All right. I'm gonna pick a mystery one next hole number five right back par five
Champion tees three hundred and replace the members to get a water 350 yards
This bar five is a lot
So coming up next
We're gonna play balls
Balls the directors cut pretty cool. We actually made by Panasonic
They're the ones that developed a game one of PE magic did PF magic
The name of the game is actually called balls directors cut with a Z
We go fighting game it kind of looks like one I think I bought this from my friend once
Oh, did you and a sonic software? Yeah, so they had something to do with it. Whatever it was
You make your own balls
Or is it three rendered balls? Welcome to my world. Let's see who's got balls
Sure balls the directors cut
one player, okay, wrong
special moves nutcrush
Loogie fencing lunge bone sweep turbo covering CBC BBC head pound
rusher
horns like it's a rhino
divine
bump and grind and knee to nuts
Nutcracker so does like a balls thing
tsunami
variety chop belly chart jump sidekick
boomer clown
self-destruct
Okay
bruiser
Yoko
stun fart
Zombie
Alright, I think I'm gonna have to go with I have to go with boomer first speed is normal. That's fine. Alright, let's go
It's a kind of clay fighter
self-destruct
They're hurting them
Am I doing I just kicked his ass don't make a habit of losing they come back to life
Okay
You can change the plane. All right cool
Tekken I was not racing to tell what you mean by that
Smashing I am mashing. What do you want to do play the game normally?
I'll decide you beat anybody that's of your completely parallel skill level
To beat this guy. Oh replay. I'm gonna up next. It's crunk. Do the combo
All I remember was self-destruct
Oh
Holy shit, that was pretty cool
Pull the lever crunk pull the lever crunk. Yeah
Pretty good. I was pretty cool
Throws
The head throw the head
Well, well, well, well, well
And lose what's he doing? He's playing pool with my body. Ah
This game is incredible. I don't know if I'd go that far
Slightly humors kind of humors
Your final boss, I wonder what the Shang Tsung of the balls universe is. Oh
Shit, I'm so sorry. I just went to go drink my water and I put me
smell the mat
This is a smell the mat
He's talking about. Oh
Okay, I get it. I get it
Do not let him come back, please
On my body
Hey, this is three in a row here quick eat pant
Kind of just I'm just pressing buttons at this point. I don't even know what's going on
What makes this the director's cut is what I want to know
off
Fuck off. You can unlock Santa. I kind of have to go till I lose, right?
Whatever that was
Let me get Santa
Yeah, that isn't that is the wrong game
That's play fighter, right?
I gotta let an auto up. He wants to leave the room. Come on. Let's go
Duggler and ostrich. Oh shit. Sorry. I just like ran away without the BRB screen. I'm sorry
Okay, that's this is
Bending over and turning in. All right, whatever
This is unfair your neck is so long. All right, I'm regaining health. What the fuck? I'm trying to self-destruct
I can't do it. Well, I did. All right, this is like a boss
All right, I'm just get away from having an aneurysm watching this my feet on my hands
Okay
That's been bald
That's balls. The director's cut of hope you liked it
Okay, Chuck E. Cheese just came to the chat and said hey German
Just figured I'd throw a message in here to mess up your chat for the rest of the day omega low
Why is Chuck E. Cheese such a fucking troll?
What he's still here? He's been here. He's been in the chase been hanging out. Don't say swears
Hey Chuck E. Cheese, it's like 60 Chuck E. Cheese can come in here and I can swear at him
Well, no, let me rephrase that I could we can swear. He's like 50. All right, that was balls. That was pretty fun
All right coming up next it's gonna be probably the final one of the day
And I would back here tomorrow with even more end of the stream voice incoming after the next one make it a decent one
Huh? All right. Do we end it with John Madden football or do we end it with another Japanese one that we can't understand or Road Rash?
That's right. Just end it with Madden. All right
I'm gonna end it with Madden so then we don't have to start with Madden tomorrow. That makes sense
Plus another reason why I want to give this a link kind of a break
It feels very it's very hot
I don't think they ever expected people to sit here for five hours straight to play this game on this console
It's it's pretty warm and it's it's very hot. We shall see here comes Madden tomorrow
I'm also gonna get more details on FTK
Those who they're interested in that there's gonna be a lot of details tomorrow because that is happening this weekend on Sunday
All right, let's get mad in here
25 years old
All right original John Madden football
This is the man would he makes a horrifying demon noise, I don't think that's in any of them
I'm excited for this one
radio experience from Electronic Arts
exclusive
Hey folks, it's me John man today. We're gonna wait you actually not play football
Do you just watch games having a realization? Maybe I do not even play football. No, it's really weird
Don Madden has never played football. Yes. He did. Hi everyone. Welcome to John Madden football
Look so young
That's it. That's all the FMV we get
New England versus center, oh bring the bay regular season one player home
Yeah, the Jets. Yeah, fuck the Jets. Let's go
Well, the game's finally here the teams are taking the field and they're about ready to kick it off
Okay, why is he yelling that like he's in the bathroom yelling out to you like put the groceries away or something
I don't know. That was weird. Let's take a look at both teams. Here's how they match up
Okay, mine is to try harder. I'm that guy up for an hour
Why do they need an FMV for that
We won
We are going to receive the ball
Using team picks the home goal. Okay, let's go. Okay. Here's the opening kickoff. Everyone should be ready
It's the opening kickoff. Everybody shit. I can't see it. It's Trump
I can't even unsee it that you've ruined everything you've ruined John Madden for me. Why did you do that to me?
Five-yard game. All right
We're gonna go here Hail Mary pass
I get John Madden's advice like you could do in the other games. I'm gonna go big shotgun
Quick slant. I don't even know how to play audible. No, I want to
I was trying to throw the ball
We do I don't know how to play
Pats suck, huh? No, they don't
Alright, how do you pass?
Start a fine
I'm trying to pass the ball. It's I think it's see you snap with C and then you pass this thing
Okay, here we go. You not catch that one. Why did he not catch it? Why did you do that? Just catch it
You were right there. Oh
Damn, we're all the way back here tack center. This game's really old as illegal to be offside. So find out
Yeah, it is. They can't go any further. So who cares? I'm going right for the quarterback right down the middle
The guy kicked me in the face. I'm Brady
What I'm not even trying to block the field
Oh
Let's go for some run plays. Where's John Madden did an intro and an outro and that's it
And he got paid like six million dollars for this. All right, let's try. I'm gonna try to get a touchdown right here
Let's do a good drive normal. I'm gonna do
Near let's just do right here. HB toss. Hold that right side like that ball deflated ball
Very very very funny. Nice block
You knock that guy in the ground and he got up and got me
Just think you guys don't understand like you could say deflated ball. I don't care. I'm not on the Patriots
I don't wait. Would you just say about hate? I want that fucking team. I've run that team
Don't you say that about my team? I'm on it. I don't know
I'm not I don't have any connection to the Patriots and the cuts cool. They have New England in front of it
All right, catch it. That was such a perfect pass to press again. Is there a catch button? I think it's a
Ref get the hell out of the way
Tackle the ref. I'm not sure you can do that. It is the floss. Oh shit. You're right. That's amazing
Okay, I wonder if a is the catch button or it's C C is you jump in the air like a block
Long as the quarter last in this game. Hopefully not that long. Come on
This is my drive right here. I don't win right here
But I'll get a touchdown right here. I'm turning it off. Okay, we can talk a lot of shit if we want
This actually is pretty good for an old 3DO game. I guess wide open. There's no way they don't catch this
You mean by I'm still on this plays pretty well for a game that's 20 fucking years old more than that
The open is weak
No, I'm not turning it off yet. Not yet. Is it second and ten? Okay run. Where's my blocking?
We're the block if that's where I was supposed to go to the left
Okay, I'm in trouble
Hail Mary it just in the end. Wait, I was supposed to go right shit
Okay, John do you need any toilet paper
Give me a baseball game and I'll wipe the floor with everything. I don't play football. I don't know anything about football
I don't care about football. I
Don't know. I thought I thought this is gonna be a game
We're like John Madden grabbed his stomach and like shook it up up and down a bunch of times. It was like
Welcome to the game punk. I don't know
Fmv game. I think it was gonna be like an actual football game
The amount of question marks right there. I'm gonna be in the bath later. I'm gonna be laughing my ass off
That's a turnover. I need to get at least a one touchdown
And get it where's it I gotta stop screaming dude, let's you turn it over and you punty immediately
This time for real we're gonna punt it I mean we're pretty far away
We don't have very we're down by a lot of points
Fire that guy. Okay, good. Awesome
We're getting close first and ten. I think we should probably punt it here
Isn't a punt here if it goes through you get points the one guy ever in history that did that
Second time why would you guys has his back turned to me?
Watch down there. It is we in New England easy. Yeah, I'm simple. I faked this
I wanted to do I just wanted to give one point. It's a fake
What do you got? I?
This is me kissing somebody no more kissing images. I don't know. I'm not looking at it
It's me kissing Tom Brady. He saved it. Yeah, okay
All right two-minute warning that of what quarter
Second quarter, I want one more possession with the ball. I'm gonna tie the game that I'm gonna turn it off
We're gonna Chuck a Chuck E. Cheese juke. That's a word
I don't know how that's a sentence no one has you ever with that's a fucking up my brain
Chuck E. Cheese got a juke. What that's not even that statement is not making sense
They're punting it. All right, they're actually gonna punt it. What if they fake it though, you're gonna fake it
It's a fake pun. They watched me do it like ten times in a row. It worked. Oh
Can you do it?
Yeah, I almost had it. All right. This is my last possession. I'm going for it
Let's see if I can get 14 points tie the game and then everybody runs off the field
The New England Patriots have tied it up at 14
We all run into the clubhouse even with the timer still going Chuck E. Cheese is spamming links ban him
That link Chuck E. Cheese
We do. Oh shit. Yeah, you actually did get it. I thought people were just messing around
I saw like the path one the fake link or does that actually happen? It's got a delay of game. Oh god
Damn it. All right. No, all right. Stop. I'm done deep outs. Let's go. Why would I fake that?
This what?
Isn't this what um, Eli Manning's team did to the Patriots that one year
But Eli Manning just threw like five Hail Marys in a row and they like accidentally got the Super Bowl
It happened right
Eli Manning Manning just turned his back and threw the football backwards as far as he could has had on
That's all we get
points first downs
completion percentage 35 percent
None of these stats matter who won the game. None of those matters. Am I actually kicking it off? Oh, that's not good. I lose
You hear Otto
Yeah, he was just like, let me in I wanted to just get out but let me back in right now
All right, come on in no, I don't want to go in he rolls on his back and he's like, I just leave you alone
And he runs just played itself
Six already and Jermis having so much fun that the stream hasn't ended. Yes. I get to see more 3d. Oh
We tell him we tell him this is this is the last
Like five minutes string here of game until tomorrow. I love this console. I've been having a blast
All Sam's all right. Everything else I loved and we haven't even gotten to the real
Balls that I don't care almost me all time before the stream ends. Is that a game?
Go with this one Chuck E Cheese Panasonic sellout. We're gonna open tomorrow with Jurassic Park the experience
There's so many really good games left. I just didn't want to go into him hard
Today, this is the opener
We got some real shit tomorrow. We have Jurassic Park tomorrow
Possibly psychic detective that one's gonna be a real hit and already tell
Can't wait to play it
Jurassic Park
Road rash. That's right. Yeah, tomorrow's gonna be and some shitty ones, too
I don't know. What was that pass attempt failed you drop the ball. They never even did anything
You're gonna do wacky races again. I don't think we even need to
The perfect package. Why did you dive that way?
I lose I'll see you tomorrow wicked 18 was pretty fun, too. I'll tell you
Wayne couldn't even wink I'm gonna play plumbers. Don't wear ties
I don't have that but I'm not against getting it if there's no sex in it, by the way
Also, I'm not going to play sex on the 3d
There's a video game of the 3d. Oh called
sex
Thinking that was probably not streamable. I think it really is just porn. It's just porn on the 3d. Oh, which
Gotta say pretty. Oh, you really messed up here
Imagine having interactive porn
This thing would have sold to like hotcakes. It would have been on every single shelf
Instead they wanted to have John Madden football and not FMV 3d. Okay
Suck not 25 years ago. All right, that's it. I'll see you
Star Wars is fun. Everybody didn't want to give that chance. I might actually play that tomorrow
We might go to like level five. I might just skip all the plane levels
Well, yeah, I want to give this thing a rest. It's been spinning for five and a half hours
It's scaring me. You lost to the New York Jets. No, I didn't I abandoned the New York Jets game
It's a little different. We've ran away. We didn't lose. We ran now
You could say one's probably worse than the other but still didn't lose. All right. Good night everybody. See you tomorrow
We'll start with Jurassic Park. It's an exclusive by the way. Here come the credits
It was an absolute shitload of community subs today. I had a ton of fun 3d
It was a lot of fun
It's just as good as I thought it was gonna be and there's so much more that we haven't even seen
See you tomorrow. Take care guys. Here come the credits. There were a lot of subs
FTK news we'll talk about it tomorrow. I will go over all the FTK details start times
Pre white listing of people we're gonna go over that tomorrow. It's really not gonna be that complicated
It's gonna be very very streamlined
I've seen a demo of it twice by now and I need to tell you it's gonna be great
It is way more than I thought it was going to be initially. I really do. I really did what that'll be the end
Good night. Good luck to the rest of your things. You're doing today. If I say I'll give you auto
What's the auto? Hey Otto you want to say hello after the 7,000 people that were subscribed today go by
Otto here comes an auto reveal
Want something to he's looking at me like all right, let's go. I'm ready to go outside. Let's go come here
Oh, he's right at the door. He ran to the door. Come here
Yeah, screen is muted
One
Why are you doing this? I want to go
Radio radio controller was like on my lap, but I was just about to fall. All right guys. I will see you tomorrow
Good night
Goodbye