Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight
I'm gonna be playing as the Soldier and a couple other things. It's just random clips of TF2 in the
background. Playing TF2 again. Yep, it's been a couple months, and then before that it was a
couple months, and then before that it was a couple months, but I got back into the game recently
because of this most recent update, the Gunmetal update, and that's what we're going to talk about
in this video. We're also going to talk about some other stuff too in the end, so this might be a
little bit longer of a commentary than I typically do, but let's talk about Gunmetal. It just came
out, brand new update yesterday. I think it's really awesome. There's a lot of great things
about it. I do have like one or two little reserves. Well, not reserves, but there are
just some things I wish they did differently. First of all, four new maps. That is something
we are not used to, especially one map that Valve made that's not in a beta. Why is this map not in
beta? And why are the other two maps still in beta? You know what I mean? Like the Cactus Canyon
still in beta. Who made this? Something's going on there. I don't know. I'm not going to pretend
to know the inside and outside of it, but it's a finished done Valve made map. It's called Power
House, and it's three control points. The first time they've ever really done that, so that's pretty
cool, and also there's a new map for each popular game mode, right? You've got a new King of the
Hill map, a new payload map, and a new control point map. Snowplow? They came up with Snowplow
too, out of left field. They just decided to release this? That's so odd. Like I thought they
didn't want to put Snowplow in this game. There's a lot of questions. There's a lot of questions
to ask about this update and why they did certain things, because if Snowplow is now an official
supported Valve map, why didn't they just make end of the line the Smithsmas update? Why didn't they
make those two coincide? If they were just going to put it in the game anyways, they probably could
have saved a lot of face by doing that, and I don't know what the reasoning behind putting it in the
game now is. It just seems like, oh, by the way, I guess it's not so complicated after all. You can
play it. Okay. Thanks. Whatever, though. It's in the game now, and it's fun. Snowplow is fun.
It might be different. It might be totally weird, but it's fun. It's a gigantic map. It's a huge open
playing field. Whatever. You might hate it. You might love it. It's in the game now, and it's
official. So there we go. We can move on from the maps. We can talk about the items. Well, not the
items per se, the item skins and how I feel about the contracts. I really like the contracts. The
contracts are probably the coolest part of this entire update. Really. I love the contracts. One
problem, though, after you do your two contracts, there's not a whole lot left to do for the update
because we only get two contracts a week, and each one of these contracts takes like 25 minutes
to do each one. So you end up doing all your contracts. Oh, I can't wait. Gonna play Spy.
Contract. Let's let it take. I just did it. It's over. I got my item. Okay. See you in seven days.
Now you contrast that to when Man vs. Machine came out. Imagine if Valve only let us do one tour a
week. I would have lost my fucking mind because when Man vs. Machine first came out, that's like
all I wanted to do. I just wanted to do tour after tour after tour. Good. Valve, take my fucking money.
Take my one dollar ticket. I don't give a shit. I want to play. I want to do the update. I want
to get involved and I want to do it. You can't really do that in this update. You spend six bucks
and it's just dragged out over the next three months, which that's cool. But in my personal
opinion, if you're going to have two contracts a week, those contracts should probably take a
little bit more time to complete. And even if they don't want you to keep getting items, maybe they
want to limit the amount of items people can get, then at least let us still be able to do contracts
and level up that coin after we get our first two items. I don't know. We'll see. This is very early.
It's a pretty interesting concept. I just really want to see more of it. That's I was starving to
do more, not less. And we're going to move on. They did a bunch of balance changes in this update,
a ton of them, and they're getting ready for competitive. It's pretty obvious based around
some of the changes they have. And there are a bunch, there are a million changes. So I really
don't want to go over them all because that would take another like 15 straight minutes for me to
talk about it. But I will bring up two things in particular. One, the big earner change. There are
now spy scouts that are going to be all over the place. I don't even want to know what some of you
comp level guys that play spy are going to do with that item now. And the other thing is what they
did to heavy. They made the Natasha and the brass beast have a 20% damage mitigation while you have
the gun spun down. So you can no longer insta kill headshot a heavy that's overhealed anymore. You
can't, you're gonna have to shoot the dude twice. That's a huge deal that change that I used to
hate playing heavy, because you turn the corner and be a fucking sandbag and insta die. Now,
as long as you have the overheal, you can at least react when you get that crit in the face,
you can try to move or get into cover or something. You're not just going to be
target practice for every sniper on the other team. But besides those two things,
I mean, everything else is really awesome and cool. I just it's so overwhelming when they do
valve likes to do this thing, right? Where instead of giving one or two balance changes every couple
weeks or something like that, or every week, they do like a tweak, they give us this giant
dump list of fucking like 500 changes. And it's like, all right, here you go. Here's every change
we've wanted to make to Team Fortress two over the last like three years. Okay, guys, take it and go
tell us what you think. It's a little overwhelming sometimes. So I'm doing it. I'm taking it as much
as everybody else is. And I'm trying to get as much information as I can to myself. So when
competitive rolls around, maybe I'll start playing competitive matchmaking. Of course I will. I've
been looking for reasons to get back into this game. And with competitive looming, and the recent
contract stuff, I have reasons to play. That's been the big deal for me in Team Fortress two.
I haven't had reasons to want to play. I don't know how they're going to flesh out. We'll just
have to wait and see. But that's going to wrap up the update portion of the video and my thoughts
and all that jazz. Now we're going to talk about a life update. So the next like two or three minutes
is going to be me talking about a life update. How exciting. So what's this big life update?
What's happening here? What do you mean? Oh, there's a life update. Would you stub your toe again?
No, I bought a place and I'm moving. In the last couple of months, at least the last like two or
three months has been extremely hectic. Trying to juggle everything that's going on, getting
financing for this place, finding it in the first place, and moving everything in because it's empty.
And it's been taking a wreck on my brain. It hasn't been all that smooth of an experience,
but it really never is, is it? Anytime you move out of a place, you buy something new. It's just
all the shit you have in your old house, all the stuff you have to bring to the new one. Are you
going to get new furniture? Are you going to buy a new fridge? Are you tearing up a couple floors?
Are you painting walls? Is the place on fire right now? Is the place on fire right now? I don't know.
I'm not there. There is no discernible way for me to say or not say the place is or is not on fire
right now. These are the things that go through my head when I'm sitting here, not at the place
because I obviously haven't moved in yet, but you just stress out over random shit that you don't
need to stress out over. You just got to take it slow. Everybody I've talked to said anytime
you buy a place, do one thing at a time. You don't got to go bring a cot in and live there
immediately. You just get things situated, get ready, and then live, baby. Live. And we transition
talking about how I'm moving into the fact that now I want to stream pretty much every single day.
Once I actually get all moved in somewhere in the middle of August, I want to stream at least four
or five times a week. This is something that I've wanted to do for a long time, but I've never been
able to get my ducks in a row in my brain and my body in the right position to be able to do this
thing. I love the idea of streaming. I love just hanging out and playing games with whoever shows
up, whatever game I happen to be playing. It's something that I really want to do, and I'm going
to try it at my fullest ability the second that I moved into this place and everything's ready to go.
So this is like update video and hey I'm moving and stream announcement video all in one. So
that's going to wrap it up. Take care everybody. See you all soon. Enjoy the new Team Fortress 2
update. It's going to be so much fun. I can't wait. Now here this is this is the part of the video
where it goes BOO!