Hello. Good afternoon, good evening. Good to see you again. Welcome to an interesting stream.
This is going to be like, I don't like anything we've ever done before. Weird voice? What?
My effects aren't on. They shouldn't be on. Real voice? This, yeah, this is my real voice.
So what do you want me to tell you? I thought I had my sound effects on. You fixed it. Oh, I did?
Okay. Anyways, today we're going to do something different. This is the culmination of the last
16 hours of time. If you were not here a couple days ago, or not even like a day and a half ago,
we were talking about how funny it would be if there was a way for us to watch old videos.
You know, you've seen those streams before, right? Not only watch old videos, but all of them have
every single stream and every single video I've ever done be available to skip through. And what
would that even look like? What does my entire almost 10 year career look like? Did we just get
subs? Hold on. How many? Was that 10? Oh, shit. I don't even have my fucking thing ready. Yeah,
I said it like that. Career. And we can find out today. Because after talking about all that,
and hey, wouldn't it be funny if we could just like get a random timestamp and go through a
random video? Lazy Luke made it. Actually made this capable and possible. We are going to do
something very interesting today. Holy shit. Hold on. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What? Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. I don't even have my
dashboard open. Hold on a second. I got like seven windows open. What just happened? Hold on. It's
loading. It's loading. It's loading. Oh, you know, Kazzy gave 10 community subs. Thank you, Kazzy,
for the 10 fucking community subs. And then thanks to Freddy Dread for the $500 in bits.
That's 50,000 bits. An absolute madman. Just a true madman. 500 bucks. Holy shit. And then great
Canadian FK Club, 10 community subs. Austin Atlantis, 10 community subs. It's just, it's the
hour of money. It's the money hour. He's going to turn into the fucking Monopoly man. I should
just start wearing a monocle. Do they even make those anymore? Can you buy a monocle? By the way,
isn't a monocle just a magnifying glass that you stick on your eye? Right? That's what it is.
The only people that use monocles are, are people that sell jewelry, like
diamonders, whatever they're called. Jeweler. That's it. Another 10 community subs from Labster.
Holy shit. All right. All right. We got, we got all, this is a lot of money. This is, this is too
much money. Uh, Freddy, Freddy, that's fucking insane. That's, that's 500 bucks right now.
Hey, hey, any, any, any diamonders in chat? Any diamonders? Am I loud today? I feel like I'm
loud today. Am I loud today? I feel like I'm wicked fucking loud. Is that better? Am I wicked? Am I
not wicked fucking loud anymore? Why am I this loud? I'm looking over at it. Hey, that, that,
that, that, that, that, that, that, that's better. That's not as insane as it was before. I'm always
quiet. Yeah. I'm always quiet, but now I'm always loud right now. All right. So, uh, thanks for these.
Yeah, that's a hundred. Oh my God. That's fucking so much money. That's a thousand dollars.
That, that's, wait, that's five. That's a thousand dollars, Freddy. Freddy. Freddy,
that's a lot of money. Freddy, you've given me like 10 grand, Freddy. Freddy, that's a shitload.
Holy shit, Freddy. A hundred more subs on top of the $500. I think Freddy Dread has given this
channel more than 10 grand. Holy shit. Wow. Freddy. And there's not even a message on this, on
the $500 donation. Not even a message. He's just like, boom, take this money. I will. Holy fuck.
It's your birthday. Well, it's not, but I can pretend it is. Anyway, I want to show you something
really, really, really fucking cool. So while we can, we can take a minute before we start this,
but take a look at this. This is my entire life, about 90% of my entire life. There's
3217 hours of videos and streams that is linked into here. This is every live stream I've ever
done and every video I've ever made. If you want to know what that looks like, take a look at this.
This page loads a random moment out of all German videos and streams. Although there are a lot of
main channel videos, they are unlikely to be played because they have such a compact duration.
And they do. Here's some statistics. Almost 1500 total videos, 778 archive streams and 712
main channel videos. So if you take a look at this, the, the amount of hours, most of the hours I've
ever spent on the internet have been from a stream. So when I press this button up here,
something very magical is going to happen. The first thing that's going to happen is it's going
to load a random fucking video and a random timestamp in that video across 3200 plus hours.
What also is going to happen is a timer is going to pop up in the top left corner of your screen.
That timer is going to count down from two minutes. It's going to start at two minutes.
When that timer reaches zero, it goes on to another random timestamp. So that's kind of
interesting in itself. But you know what else is interesting? If we started, maybe decided to play
a little bit of bingo too. This is over 10 years of my life on a bingo card. Now, after two minutes
goes by and we go to zero, we're going to go to a new random part of my entire life. How you come
into play on this stream. German, what are you going to do about channel points? Well, I'll tell
you. Today, if you would like to add 30 seconds to the timer that is in the top left corner of the
screen, you are going to give 10,000 channel points as a highlighted message. We had to do it
as a highlighted message. That's why highlighted messages are not here right now. We had to do it
as highlighted message because that's the only way that the website can pull the data that we need.
So 10,000 channel points will add automatically 30 seconds onto the timer. But 10k is too little
for that. I know, I know. It might be way too little, but here's the thing. I'd rather adjust
up than adjust down because if it's, if I started like 30,000 channel points,
and then like in 20 minutes we bring it down, I would have scammed a shitload of people.
We're going to find out. So we're going to play bingo and we're going to, it's not active yet
because I know people are just going to be like, oh, give 10,000 channel points right now. So it's
not active until I, I'm going to press this fucking button. We're going to get started and then I'm
going to turn it on. Remember the goal is, the goal is if you want to extend the current video
that is playing, this is not like, oh, we're, I mean, you technically are extending the stream,
but it's for the current video. Every video starts at 120 seconds. If you give 10,000 channel points
during that period, it's going to go up 30 seconds. When it reaches zero, we go to a new video.
I, let's, let's just go, but get a good screenshot of this because I'm going to need you guys help
for this one. Yeah. Get a good screenshot of that because I have to keep track of this too.
You ready? Are we ready to do this? Are we ready to start? I'm going to turn it on. Remember,
it has to be a highlighted message. Make sure your highlighted messages stay, stay. I'm looking
forward to this. I don't even know what the fuck, you could get anything. We could get fucking
anything from 10 years. Are you ready for me to press the button? It has to be a highlighted
message. I'm going to press the fucking button. Are you ready? Let's go. It begins in five, four,
three, two, wait, hold on. Okay. Hold on. I had to, I had to get the, the, okay. Ready?
In five, I have to be able to see this shit in five, four, three, two, roll the fucking dice.
Here we go. Welcome to the stream everybody. If there's anything, Nancy Drew, just let me know.
Thanks. I might just take you up on that offer. So what can I do for you? Tell me about,
tell me about Paseo Del Mar High. No, no, no, no, no. Oh my God. One of the students was
murdered in the school last week. We're all pretending to be students. No, no, stop, stop,
stop. Stop, stop, stop, stop. I'm going to make it more expensive. I'm going to make it more
expensive. All right. I'm going to turn it off. I'm going to turn it off. I'm going to make it more
expensive.
Ten thousand is too small. Ten thousand is too small.
Ten thousand is too small.
How long is this? This is just two hours. There's not even two hours in this VOD.
I can't play barnacle blast. Are you serious? That's a shame. No, no, no, no, no, no,
God damn it. Oh, you got to be shitting me. That makes a cool song. Let's find,
let's find our uncle. This is the most boring one. This is the most boring stream
of all the Nancy Drew streams. I can't refund bits. I can't fucking refund anything.
Oh my God. I should have fucking killed it so much further ago.
So what do you got for me? Well, I was hoping you could debrief me on the investigation.
Oh, sure, sure, sure. I'm just a bit. Well, my undercover assignments are usually not so
suburban. I can't believe it. I understand. I can't believe it. All right. Wait a minute.
I have a night. Oh, I fucking should have said this. The students know about any enemies.
All right. Listen to me. Listen to me. Nothing came up from searching his home computer,
cell phone or locker. I get a veto. I get three veto sneezes. I get three veto sneezes.
We suspect he was involved in something shady. Drugs, gambling or blackmail. That's where you
fit in. I can't fucking believe this is going to be two hours. See what you can find out.
We think he might have kept information about his activities in a notebook or journal. So
keep a lookout for anything like that. Anything else? Oh, 10,000 might be too much. 10,000 might
be too much. And it had to be Nancy Drew. Of course it starts with Nancy Drew. And all of
these fucking Drew motherfuckers over here have been waiting for this shit for weeks,
for actual weeks. And they got their opportunity right now. By the way, we got to pay attention
because there's a bingo card. What? What? Okay. I got to pay attention. I'm just going golf club.
Surf club is cool. That's cool. It's the locker. All right. Uh, I don't know this information yet.
All right. The gym. This is unbelievable. I'm coming.
Add something that's subtract. Oh, we don't, we don't wait. We don't have the capability for
that right now. We just started it. Sneeze and vid. Unroy. All right. What is that for?
Translate them into links instead. Like 10,000. I can't. No. Okay. For a second,
I thought that their mascot was a sock with boxing gloves. Is that, is that, wait, is that,
is that anything? Was that something on the bingo card? Check the bingo card.
All right. If, by the way, it's going up to 20,000 channel points. Grape, orange, soda, cool,
or spot cola. I would love to have a sip of cool cola. That's 20,000 channel points. It's probably
a puzzle. Spot cola, cool soda, orange soda. I am so angry right now, but it's like hilarious.
I need, I need more quarters. It's guys. It's already been like, how long has it been?
How long is this actually? Holy shit. You just kind of new girl at school. Do you realize what
destiny has brought you today? Yours truly Hector Sanchez, but you can just call me the Hulk. It's
an hour and 40 minutes. The Hulk? You are new around here. I play for the manatees,
one of the best teams in the state. I leave the others in the dirt, man. Soon it's college ball
and then the pros show time. That's not, no, surprise face. Who are the manatees?
Paseo Del Mar's mascot is a manatee. That's only in the video that we're watching. It had to be
fucking Nancy Scott. I know what to do if I come across a manatee. Why would you immediately talk
about fighting, punch one and hurt one? Here's the worst part. I can't even
I'm not going to pause. I know what to do if I come across a manatee. It's yeah. Just
it's like a zero point zero zero two percent. These are a great team at a great school.
Everyone is cool. It's like a zero point zero two percent chance to get Nancy Drew first.
I knew Jake, but I didn't hang out with him. Sorry. Can't talk now. I got to go to practice
later. At this point, I could let I could just like go take a shower and come back who died.
I could go take a shower. Yeah, this school is pretty cool. Jake Robert, Jake Robert sucks.
I hate him. Oh, OK. You know, he he's dead. Oh, yeah. Well, welcome to the school.
Is that is that an impression? No, it's not. How's it going? How could I get into Jake's locker?
I could tear the door off with my teeth, but it just might be easier to ask how to knock it.
His locker was right. This is the worst Nancy Drew stream, by the way. Oh, this is so bad.
Tell me about Daryl Gray. He seems like a cool guy. His family used to sponsor the annual
football awards dinner until last year. You know, he's the one who found Jake's body.
Wait, what? Hold on. Vito Vito lost right now. But what if what if it happens again immediately?
He knows that he's OK. I'm so scared. If I veto this, what if we get Nancy Drew again?
He talked about how much he's like he sucks. And now he's like, oh, yeah, that's where the body was.
I'll talk to you later. That's a finance. Yeah, this is a psychopath. Just one veto like checked
every box of are you make it max out at 10 minutes? All right, we're going to find where's this?
In the trash. I test. I wasn't prepared for this. I'll do it for this to happen. 10 minute max.
I'll do the eye test and see how good I do. Oh, where is it? That's that's a surprise face, Kim.
E, V, I, F, O, R, E, Z, E, E, R, H, T, E, G, I can't get over this. P, K, O, O, B, Y,
R, T, C, Z, M, N, J, K, O, O, L, K, M, O, T, E, M. I don't know. B, F, F,
A, L, E, E, U, L, K, Y. Boomer eyesight. K, A, P, I. All right, I have an idea. Should we add
like a hundred thousand channel points to skip? No, no, we can't do that. No, no, no, no, no,
we can't do that. You know, OK, when you when you go, OK, Jeremy, please cover one eye and do it
and you do it and then it's like, oh, do the other eye. And it's like, that's too many. But I can't.
It's all blurry. You can't. You can only do this once.
You actually can only do that test one time. You can't do the other eye to reduce time.
We did it. We don't have that set up for today. You got about half of that wrong. Ten minute max.
All right. What how what has it been so far? We're keeping right away. We're keeping track
of everybody. It's the that it's the light coming back into your eye. It's like all blurry.
We're keeping track of every every single highlighted point. What are you talking about?
So can a mod right now message me how many channel points, how many people highlighted
messages? What are you talking about? I'm fine. All right. I get I get three vetoes.
I forgot to say that I actually was going to say that I get three vetoes. When I cover one eye
and I cover one eye for long enough and I take my hand off that eye and I cover it, it's like
this eye that it was covered is all fucked up. Bro, don't you have a hernia? Yeah, it sucks.
You fucking liar. Then veto it. But I don't do I want to drink. All right. Do I want to use it,
though? That's the problem. This stream could be more than five to ten hours long. Do I want
to veto this right now at the beginning? You know what I'm saying? How do I get the hell out of here?
All right. Drink. But what if I want a I wish I could cool soda or should I get extra pop?
I'm going to do I have to use a video. Definitely. I think I have to use a video.
I'm going to use a video. I'm going to I this is this like this this this stream is so boring.
Like you don't want to watch this one. That is wasted quarter. All right. We're going to talk
to this walker. All right. All right. I'm sorry. I can't sit here for Nancy Trump for two hours.
I can't never exhaust. I can't do it. Regret. I'm vetoing Da Vinci. Bree Bree to one veto.
What is this murderous pursuits? Do a 10 minute stream delay.
Oh, this is like a multiplayer game. Field cart doesn't stream. I don't think anybody's stream
sniping. I don't. I remember this game. I haven't really seen that much evidence that it's happening.
Maybe it is, but there's no way I can avoid that. I'm not going to do a stream delay.
You want to turn on like a three minute stream delay.
Hey, how many seconds is 10 minutes? I can do that at this point. You only get one veto.
No, I get three. Hey, I'm still playing it though. Like I still am enjoying it.
All right. You guys seriously like you. It's called Presto Magesto. I'm not going
to use another veto. I have two more. Oh, my stomach is eating me alive.
Keep your eye on the bingo card. That's important. I don't even know if I can do that
being live. I think I have to set that before I start streaming. That's all right. Come at me.
I really don't think it's going to be that big of a deal. 30 seconds is too much.
Tell us about the Boston accent. I have two more vetoes. I have to get this right.
Thanks for the game, Jerma. And sorry about the circling. Your chat made me do it.
Wait, so somebody was in that game. Make it 10 seconds. What do you mean chat made me do it?
No, I think we're good. Yeah, I have to restart the stream for delay. Do I have anything
necessarily planned for the rest of the night? No, I mean, there are a couple of options, but
I'm having like a lot of problems right now with my stomach. This is the second time I've talked
about like medical issues in two roles. Don't take this the wrong way, but you seem very silly.
I should have put that up here. That's all right. I think I'm nice. I'm stuck here, I think.
What am I in queue? What am I waiting for here? I'm ready. Yeah, my stomach is like in a knot
right now. Make it one. I am just drinking water and we're good. But we got a lot of fun stuff
going on this weekend. So is this the end of a stream? What am I talking like? I'll eat my
stomach. What are you five grow a pear? Oh my God. What is happening right now? This is like
the middle of a stream. Jesus. Oh my God. That's inappropriate reading of chat. Tell me how you
really feel. Hunter. It's not that guy. It has to be that guy. I just blew the cool down. That is
inappropriate. Okay, where is that? Inappropriate chat reading. Where? Oh. As they like to opine on
the back streets of Limehouse. Floor below. They don't like it up, do they? All right, let's take
a look at what it looks like right now. All right, I'm going to try to actually win this one. Let's
go for it. Actually blind. No, that doesn't count for this. Take a look at what we got so far.
Now you guys have me paranoid for stream snipers. I got to go all the way around. I'll put the
webcam on so you can tell who the real one is. No, but this just looks like I'm on the same stream.
Floor below. I'm going to run right into them, I think, if I turn this corner.
I could just go like this. Hunter nearby. I really thought you would have come upstairs by now.
We got to hide. Damn. Is this like the ship? It is like a combination of it's not isn't the ship
like you talk like text to speech and shit. This is more the Assassin's Creed multiplayer
from. I need to get down the stairs. Keep doing it. Person is at one of the dinner tables.
Let's get a good look. It's the lady writer.
Where's my Hunter? Where's my Hunter? Where's my Hunter? Hunter right behind me.
Yep. Sayonara. Those who hesitate are lost. We got we need brass knuckles or we need a different
weapon. We only got 10 more. Don't say anything. There's a delay. Hunter's near. Shouldn't be. Nope,
right here. God damn it. I wasn't going to do it in time apparently. You heard those clicks.
You heard those clicks first place. Serious business. Damn it. That's not angry. I was
going like tickety tickety tickety tickety tickety. You know I was going tickety and it didn't
matter. No, that doesn't count. That's not the fucking ping. What's my ping? Well, they did
manage to get in first. 102 ping. That guy had zero. This guy's got zero ping. That's not. No,
it's not. There we go. That's not molding. Molding is way different than this. Not even close.
Yeah, I'm gonna take a gamble here. I know it. Yeah. Sometimes your intuition pays off.
Most inspirational. Why is a TF2 video on the board? Well, that's because there's a 3.4% chance.
It's like the line. There's a 3.4% chance to get a German 985 video and a 1.2% chance to get a
Team Fortress 2 video. And that disguise on, that's fine. But those of you that are confused,
let me turn it down a little bit. For those of you that are confused, this is pulling a random
timestamp from every single video and every stream I have ever done. For those of you that
are confused. So when we get to zero, or if I veto, it goes to a random timestamp of a random
thing I've ever done on the internet. And the first two we got have been very, very exciting.
It's been Nancy Drew's stream, which I had to veto. And then arguably one of the most probably
boring streams I've done in five years, which is this. Oh shit. Man, thanks for the stun.
Appreciate it. That person was a player the whole time. Hunter is near. That wasn't a
tuber voice. This guy right here. Definitely. Yep. No, that's to be distinct. Oh my God. Oh my God.
That's not a strange noise. No, that's just, is that a strange noise? No, no, it's not.
Was it a weird noise? What was this guy doing? That was me going like, ah. He's on a fucking rampage.
I gotta hide. I need a thing. I'm exposed. I'm exposed. Where are they? Lady right here?
No, that was a rumor. That was a rumor now. That was a rumor right now. Like in here. That wasn't
in the, oh shit, I gotta mute the microphone so you can't hear me. You're doing all right. I have
to get out of here. Fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Where are they? Just be in this. Oh, you were in the
circle. You were inside the circle. I ran right into the circle. Of course it was me. All right,
don't blow it. I got a commanding lead in the first place. Come back. We don't want to hear
this boring vlog. Well, why did you spend so much money to keep it here? There is a 0.04% chance for
you to get one of the Shmee videos. Don't you want to let this play out? When you see somebody
turn a corner there, I'm just going to activate it. I'm not going to veto this. Give me that weapon.
I want full exposure here. This is not, that's not. Tapping of running around. They're coming up
the stairs now. This pod is so boring. I'm going to activate my. This whole vod is just me going
like, okay. Got that guy. All right. If I attack that guy, walk around, hit this guy. Got him.
Got this guy. I'm not sure if I should have done that. Should I do that? Where's this guy?
I'm not sure. On the same floor. Pick this up. Okay. I think I'm still that person's target.
Question. Question. Question. Say question. Hey, question. Question. Did I get that guy?
Did I kill that guy? Should I go this way? What's up there?
Yeah, that was, that was, that was a Jeremy and I've learned to not be Jeremy.
I'm doing a different approach. He's laughing at his own jokes. He thinks it's so fucking funny.
Oh, this is the worst stream of 2020. This, this, this stream was like 2015. So sorry.
We can't pull a stream from 2015 and make it worse than 2020. The first person that walks
in this door is my killer. The most improved streamer award. I can't be just complacent about
this. Five minutes. All right. What is five minutes in, in, in time? Three, what is it? 320?
How many seconds is five minutes? They are right down here. 300. Shit. I gotta make something
happen right now. One minute left. 320. 350. How many seconds is five minutes? 300. Shit.
Okay. All right. We'll keep it. We'll make it 300 seconds. When it gets to 300 seconds,
then you've maxed it out. All right. Here's the thing though. Some of you guys are going
to be pretty upset by this. All right. All right. 300 seconds is the back. I gotta get one person.
When you hit 300 seconds, it triggers it. It triggers the fucking kill swing. What the fuck?
10 minutes is better. All right. If you want five minutes, press one. If you want 10 minutes,
press two. So I can't hit that guy. What the? I got it. I had it. That was mine. That was me.
Oh my god. Five minutes it is. At 300 seconds, you're going to trip it.
I can do this. I can control this. Don't worry. All right. Well now for future. I didn't know that.
Like I thought that even if they're getting arrested. Okay. So here we go. Because then I'm
technically still their quarry, right? Every single one is going to get to 300. Well,
you don't know that. I thought that even if they get arrested, like I can go up and hit them
because that it's like they got stunned. No, the stream is this, this like what we're watching
right now. What a bunch of dog shit. Wait, the guard. Yeah. Get the fucking guards out of the
game. Pointless. Mad. Oh, like what, what purpose do the guards serve? I don't see a purpose for
the guards. I don't. I'm just silent right now. That's how you can tell when I'm actually upset
about something. When I just sit there and I just sit there quiet.
For more than 20 to 30 straight seconds. Okay. So if a guard is like essentially stun somebody,
I'm technically still their quarry. So we haven't changed in five years. I don't know who it is and
I have to just hope I click first. You guys have been the same for the last decade. It's been more
than 300 seconds. If the counter is in the game, the guard seems like the most meaningless addition.
No, because people are going to count that as a veto. Wait, where's my one? What? Oh,
okay. That's not my mouse. That's, that's, that's his mouse. People are going to,
people are going to come back and count this as a veto. No one's going to count this as a veto.
You sure? Here we go. She's ready to go on a date. Let's get this right. The ego maniac stream.
Bridget has a dog named beefcakes, whom she loves more than anything else in the world.
Beefcakes is a presumptuous pet. He is fond of removing pieces of your body that he presumes
to be of no use. Well, now you've capped it out. These have included on various occasions, pieces
of arm, leg, toe, whatever happens to fall into his cavernous jaws. Bridget is thankful that beefcake
likes you so. What do you think about this? I should keep quiet. If it ever came down to a
choice between me and beefcakes, I would be the one in the dog house. I'm going to poison that
animal one day. It's just a matter of time. I'm going to ask that beefcakes be kept in another
part of the house while I am visiting. Why? These are so extreme. I'm going to poison. I'm
saying this to her. These are spoilers. But watch the stream from two years ago. It's a matter of
time. Why would I say that? Can you guys still read that? Is that still legible? Like, can you
still read this? No, be quiet. Wimp. By the time the two of you get serious, you may be missing
one of your most valuable parts. What the fuck? You wanted me to say that I was going to poison
your dog? This is like mad again. No, what? Veto the spoilers. While on a date with Bridget,
you've discovered that you've forgotten your wallet. What will you do? No, be quiet. All right,
I'm out of here. Excuse yourself. Tell the story to the restaurant owner and ask if he will give
you an IOU. Excuse yourself. Drive home or to the bank. Get money and come back. Ever think of
trying out for the Olympic Decathlon? It's only a few more events than you've had to perform tonight.
Bridget gets a bit suspicious when she notices that the car is parked in a different spot.
I'm surprised that in three streams we have no... Your chest heaving while you try to catch your
breath is very romantic. We have no look at me, which is kind of odd. Can I get something to go
right here romantically? Is that wrong? Bridget admits that every so often when the two of you
are being romantic, she makes believe that you are a famous movie star. How do you feel about this?
No, that doesn't count. I have to do it. That's fine. Does that count? That's okay. That's fine.
Can you date me? Can we go steady? Can you be my wife now? Actually, this is quite a common way
for people, both men and women, to add variety to their relationships. The ultimate in recycling
content. I'm glad you were open enough to accept it. Now what if I told you that the name of the
famous movie star is Flipper? I'm just kidding. No, I'm just kidding. That would be fucked up.
All right. Another good date. Here we go. Can this stream be on the random video player?
I don't think so. The two of you are very cozy. Bridget begins to get very romantic
and respond in kind. She explains that she would really like to make love with you but doesn't have
any birth control. What will you do? Suggest that you satisfy each other without intercourse. By the
way, if we filled out this drug store, is she going to be mad about me driving and is the car
going to be parked in a different place? Dude, I'm going to get fucking flagged for this shit.
After 35 minutes of searching, you finally find a drug store that is open late. Laughing fit? No,
no, no. Laughing fit has to be like- You purchased the condom and rushed back to Bridget's house.
She's falling asleep in the living room and does not answer the door.
Fucking god damn it. Don't you work at the drug store? Here we go. We're about to move.
We're moving. As often happens in relationships, Bridget begins to gain access to your personal life.
Want to know what she finds out? Yeah, what is it? She finds out that you still play with toy boats
when you sit in the bathtub. Now that's personal. Does she know about the real boat that's in the
bay? Toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat,
toy boat, toy boat, toy boat. Stick that into my gut, aren't you? Close. Go steady. You and Bridget
make a handsome couple, okay? We gotta live together. No, go on a date. Bridget has an annoying
habit that grates on your nerves. Here we go. I don't even like this person. I just want to
get married. Where are we going? When you go out to a restaurant, she licks her fingers at the table
and sometimes makes loud sucking noises. What do you intend to do about this? Fucking gross.
Three seconds. Here we go. A little sweep as Orson Welles, maybe a somersault slam,
whatever the hell that was. And Flanker now has an opportunity. This is an old one. Instantly
reversed. Dr. Roker is in no shape to be eliminated right now. He's still doing pretty well.
Ah, you tripped it. I said that and immediately he gets eliminated. Unbelievable. How old is this
one? The sheer strength of will. 2K17. And he's going to turn the tables. He turns the tables
immediately after getting almost a new one. And here comes the Snatacat. Snatacat's in the ring
now. Just praying nobody can see him. He's invisible right now. Nobody knows where he is.
They can't even tell he's there. And that's how you make a reversal. Oh. Ladies and gentlemen,
why isn't Flanker gets eliminated from the German Rumble? Not an entire game. Stamp on the bingo
card. As the Snatacat now makes himself visible to Orson Welles, who is in a little bit of trouble
here. Orson Welles. Oh, big backwards elbow there. Took him off guard. I thought he was.
This is the first live rumble, isn't it? Go ahead. Try to reverse Dr. Roker. You're going
to get this. It has to be. This crowd. They are so behind him right now. And the Snatacat.
Oh, shit. Here comes another serpent. It's the air serpent. Yeah. When you see an air serpent,
you know it's at least three or four years old. Guys, I think there's like three boys
surface left. Orson Welles gets a drop. No, he's still in it. Easiest content ever.
Was just making seven of these fucking guys. Snatacat drop kick. Chin buster. He was like,
holy shit, I could just have 10 fucking people be the same person. He's still in it. Kissing
the elbow. You get to see another elimination here. Could see a easy Pete elimination.
It's possible. I think who even wins this? You know, you could take that opportunity to
attack him. Fucking keep doing that. And here comes the tooth goblin.
Half these characters are sorcery related. He's like just kind of rid of rage. He's seeing red
right now for the tooth goblin. He hates this fucking spell. He's just destroying right now.
He came in the ring like a bullet. By the way, just started smashing.
Derma rumble charity edition should be within the next few weeks. Backstage.
Sincerely pissing off the air serpent. Look at the top of your screen. Now we have an
opportunity. That's it. See you later. Easy Pete. That's an elimination. Oh, too bad. Easy Pete.
Add should be on the bingo card. It is carrying slam there on to the goblin.
As he goes down, Pete is gone. It's so funny to see in the the serpent edition. I know pretty much.
Yeah. At this point. Oh, no. That's going to be gone here. Does that does that count as making
the same joke? Does that count as making the same joke within the last week? No, it doesn't, right?
That's not a joke. That's me. That's a reference, is it? No. You pick him up. How can you have that
I don't think that counts. It's a reference. He's looking into doing push ups, whether on top of
somebody next to somebody. Well, they're in his hands. The goblin, the tooth goblin has an
opportunity. No, it was an observation. There you go. Yeah, exactly. Dr. Roker's not taking that shit.
In comes the next contestant. Who wins? No, no, no. James Madison, James Madison with his appearance
came in around the same time last time. It had to be a president in every one.
Snap suplex there right under Orson Welles. I can't believe I almost sat there for two hours.
He was like a ninth president or something. For Dancy Drew. I'm so glad I used Evito.
Sidewalk slam there onto the two Roker. Air serpent is currently. No, he's all right. He
just jumped and landed on top and did a bulldog. I think that was scammed a bunch of people.
I had to do it. I had to do it. Who just who just punched the air serpent? I don't know.
Air serpents crawling now as if like he's got like no nothing. Nothing on this one guy. Sorry.
Here he is. Here's the guy. I have no idea who the fuck he is. Here he is. Here's the mystery guy.
Crash incoming. If it's going to happen, it's going to happen like right now.
You know what's ridiculous? Drew crew was going to be a slot on here and it would have been
instantly circled. Because there was like no way it was going to happen.
Video too quiet. Yeah, I'm trying to adjust it.
Gone. Mystery man eliminates. He better not fucking win.
Less than 60 seconds to go to the next one. Tooth goblin. Wow. The air serpent now seems to be
in a little bit of a problem here. That's not it. No, that's okay. He's getting his chest pushed.
He's getting his head. He's getting his stomach smelled by Dr. Roker.
And that's no, it is barely the air. Wait, doesn't it? Doesn't a serpent is he though,
win this shit? Can you stay in? Did I let that happen like four years ago? Oh man. What the
fuck was I thinking? Doesn't look like he's going to get it this time. Sorry, Dr. Roker, but
nice right hand. He's going to get it this time. Possibly again with the chest push.
He gets stomped in his tracks. Fortunately. And here comes frogman. Oh frogman. From dark souls
three. And a very good. Here we go. Let's go. The sims for murder house.
We could get a few here. Oh no, I've heard about this guy. I gotta get out of here.
We could get a few bingo cards here. Get over here. You tripped it. I'm going to find you.
There you are. I'm the local resident fucking murderer. Here we go. We could get like three
or four of these here. We really could. Why'd I stop? This is three hours and 20 minutes into
what the second stream may be. Her head is just a swivel. And I'll tell her a joke.
I smell so bad. So many nerds. At this point, was there violence involved in this one?
Well, that was a log on disabled, disabled reactions, disabled cops. Wait, this might be
the tail end. Mod info, make partners in crime. It's possible this is the tail end. Exclude the
sim from getting killed. Enable drain all blood interaction for the sim. Okay. What the hell does
that mean? Look at all these urns. I gotta get out of here. Did I say it? Did I say I gotta get out
of here? I gotta go? Did I? No, I didn't. Did I? I did? No, I didn't say it. No, did I? You said,
I gotta get out of here. Oh, God damn it. Really? Oh, he doesn't care.
Clear reputation on social media. Somebody's going to walk by and throw me a doll, right?
Come on. You know, you like this, dude. Don't start laughing. Don't start laughing.
He fucking ran away. No, he wanted nothing. That is not a laughing fit. That is a chuckle. That is
a slight chuckle. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. I think he was just a little nervous at first.
No, no, he's gone. Okay. Practice singing. Uh, what about rage? What does rage mean?
Dude, but we don't have the yesterday's stream. No, not, we don't have that today.
That's like freaking out and smashing shit.
Here he comes. Oh, fuck. He's coming over here. Wait, doesn't like death shoot somebody with a
gun. No, I somebody shoots death with a gun. What's the, what's the drink? All blood.
When does that happen? I'm going to drink all this lady's blood and see what happens. Deadly
slice of machete bash head. No, I don't think I've seen any of this yet at this point of the
stream. Non-deadly. See, I'm like, oh, non-deadly. What's this do? What's that? Where the hell is it?
Holy shit. I didn't enable it. I thought I did. Everyone else is already dead. Wait,
hold on. Everybody at this point was, it's already dead. More choices. Uh,
rain, all blood. Okay. So we're catching like the cool down. We're catching the cool off period.
You need to be, you need to be a vampire. Oh,
like asking chat. Hey, so how do I fucking be a vampire? Like I've killed everybody.
It's time to end this. I'm just gonna try to practice singing. Come on, practice singing.
It is the tail end. Yeah, you finally get it. This is where I got sick of doing this for so long.
It was like, oh, I killed everybody. Uh, I like ran people up with cars and I shot like five people.
Uh, I guess I'm like bored. I guess I'll just stab the character in the stomach now.
What am I doing? Are we going on an adventure? There's somebody left. What the fuck am I talking
about by a retail store? I thought I was going to get my head ran over. It's time for gardening.
Club gatherers can only be held at residents owned by garden gnomes members. I don't think
I'm sleeping. I'm now, you know how we feel most strange as a cube. This is how you guys feel a lot
of time. Huh? I'm sitting there going, what the fuck is he doing right now? I'm like, what's what?
What the I'm sitting here going like, what is he doing? Why is he, why is he doing this right now?
Now I understand. I get it. I am retroactively annoyed with the way that I am playing the game.
Fast forward. I'm just like, come on, dude, let's fucking hurry up. It's gonna take a long time.
He's got five people. That's something done for God's sake. No, no, I get it. What's with the
Xbox? Oh, that's the alien still bleeding out. No, he's still, see, is it, is it like a I
misinterpreted something? I can't believe it though. I'm dead. No, the no Nightwing shirt.
No, not a bad analogy. I tried to get a picture. I couldn't get it. Game over. Or is it the last
Sim in this household has died, but you can create more Sims choosing the existing household to play.
No, don't save in managed world. Exit the main menu. You got a game over in the Sims.
Okay, manage world. Hey, look at this new stuff. So we need a 10 seconds family to move in.
You ready? I'm ready. I need a household. Uh, where are we going? Cry of fear co-op highlights
it was. If I replay the video, I might, if I replay the video, I might break the algorithm
that's running this whole thing. If I, I might break it, I'm going to break the algorithm.
All right, we're good. Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with scare Saturdays.
This time on scare Saturday is going to be going through some of the co-op of cry of fear
with star. Now before anybody asks any questions, this is not going to be a full let's play of cry
of fear. As much as that would be cool, I would probably rather stream something like that than
to upload like 50 episodes of this onto my YouTube channel. But it's about a 15 minute video condensed
kind of highlight reel of some of the scares, some of the funny things that happened, some of
the happenings we came across. And that's probably what you're going to get. Like I said, I don't
want to have a huge let's play on this channel. It's like, you know, 50 episodes long. I've gone
down that path before, as a lot of you guys know, I've done some let's plays and yeah, we're on
episode six. I'm done. But with that said, here is the video guys, not going to take up any more
time. I want to get to the content, obviously. So, uh, it's been sunny out, go outside and go
get some sunbathing because I'm about to do it right now, baby. Sunbathing. Whoa. Take your
clothes off. I cannot pick up that gun. There's a guy, there's a guy, there's a guy, there's a guy
over there. There's a guy over here. He's like shifting around like a freak show. Don't shoot
him. Don't shoot him. What do you mean? Don't shoot him. This is a fricking neighborhood.
What did you do? Do I have no bullets left? That's not bad aim. I got him in two shots.
Such recoil on this gun. It's unbelievable. Help me, help me stop shooting this guy. Shoot him please.
Please. You do it. I have to change my sensitivity. I can't aim like this.
This video is almost seven years old. I'll cover you. If I die, this is all on you.
All right, I will cover you. Are you ready now for real? By the way, remember,
if you were part of the pre-stream chat, hey dude, star, do like a star appearance,
like an italics appearance. I have a gun too, but this is insanely rare. But number one,
this is a YouTube video. YouTube fucking video, which is 3.4% chance and a star inclusion,
which is like an extra like 0.2% chance. I do see it. Is it dead? I don't have any bolts
left by the way. Yeah, that's kind of happening. We should, I think in our inventory, we have a
nightstick. I don't know how to equip these into slots. Stars in 30% of your videos. Yeah,
but we have to hit a video and it has to be a star video. So it's 3.4% chance to have a video
even play. And then 30%. What's 30% of 3.4%. Something's going to jump up. Wait,
did I just get bullets? I did. Didn't I? No, I didn't. That was you reloading. I think
1.2, 1.1, 1.25. This is fucking rare. Get out of here.
What? Game over. Game over. I was so scared. Good idea. I heard somebody. Did that guy throw a
brick at you? I think it was blood, but it looks like a brick. I don't think I can take another
two minutes of this. Where is he? Oh, he's right there. Okay. I have two more videos for the rest
of the night. Get out of here. Go back to Ikea. Who thought this was scary? Go back to Jordan's
furniture, you piece of crap. That was kind of fun. The upside down flying mattress, man.
That was pretty funny. There's more of them. What do you mean there's more? Where are they?
Oh my God. They're like a flock of crows. It's actually a murder of crows. I remember that
comment in the YouTube comments. Jeremy, it's a murder of crows, you idiot. You guys haven't
changed in 10 years. He's still sitting there all mattressy. Something else, something else,
something else I heard. By the way, 10 years have almost gone by. That guy might be a pain in the
ass later. Well, we got to go in this way. I think there's a person in this house as well.
10 years. 10 fucking years. We could be brothers. Oh my God. Oh my God. Is she dead? That was my
girlfriend, Jerma. What the hell is that? What is that thing from like the island of Dr. Moreau?
No, that's from XCOM. We made a lot of references back in the day. No, that's the thing from the
island of Dr. Moreau. Moreau, not Munroe. The thing with, who's the fat actor? I'm scared. I
can't like think. What do you mean don't know who the fat actor is? You don't know who? What's this
box over here? That's not a bad analogy. That's pretty good. We're moving.
Nope, that'd be too easy. We got two of our voices been checked off.
None of these. This is tearless.
Guys, I think that's going to be it. Wait. I'm sorry we had so many problems today.
It was really bad today. What was? It wasn't even bad in the sense of,
it wasn't even dropping frames. It was just dropping everything. The whole thing would
just turn off. That sucks. Sorry about that. I think that's like four or five VODs.
Not much I can do. I knew they were doing maintenance. They were doing something. They
were upgrading. Oh god, this is going to get close, man. The node or something. This is going to get
fucking close. Right on time. Give me a break. Maybe they either fucked something up or maybe
it's one of those scenarios where they're still working on it because the internet here was
turned off for like eight hours or so. Six hours or so I think. What's wrong with this list? You
got a problem with this list? Why is GameCube in B tier? Why is the switch so high? Because
for the longest time, and I'm talking more than 15 to 20 years, I've been searching and hoping
for an entertainment device that you can use in the bathroom and take a shit when you go
to the bathroom for 40 minutes. He's so right. I used to bring my computer into the bathroom
and plug it in and like set up a desk in the bathroom and sit there. He's so right. God,
imagine being this correct about something. Why is the switch so high? Give me a break.
It was bad. I used to sit, I used to bring my computer into the bathroom, set it up on like
a stand-up pop-up table, and then plug everything in and sit on the toilet. Now, shit joke is not
on here guys. And even after I was done, I didn't, because what a pain in the ass that was to get it
all in there. So my legs, my legs would start to tingle. I would sit there for an extra like
25 minutes and I would have to like, I would be getting like tingly legs. This is true. This is
real. This is not a joke. I was sitting there for too long and that's what maybe had to get up.
This is, that's not, this is not a lie. This is what, this is actually real life for me when I was
like 14, 15, 16. I think I remember my mother at the time fighting this and eventually just being like...
VaudeGerma is funnier than liveGerma. VaudeGerma is Germa. If you're gonna do it, if you're gonna do that,
this is me talking. This is like four months ago. That's me. That's me talking to you. What do you
bring, why are you doing all that? Why are you bringing all that stuff into the bathroom? It's
like, uh, because I wanted, I just, I'm like working. I don't know, I was an idiot.
No, no, don't, I'm gonna turn off. I'm gonna turn off. Listen to me before I go, before I turn off.
I want to do the bits, but it's gonna be fucked up. Hold on. All right, long story short,
I can bring the switch into the bathroom and I can shit on it and keep, and keep my hands close
and not have to worry about my legs tingling so I can get up whenever I want and put it over. Okay,
done. This is for real. My internet's gonna turn off. So let's try to get some of these bits done
before we get shut off. Done. Let's get the, no, not BRB. I will see you guys later. The next time
you're gonna see me. Stream's not actually over. This is like we're watching something on a certain,
that's gonna be our stream. So you will see me after this weekend. I'll be back on, what's today?
What day is it? I will be back on Sunday. Oh my fucking god. So it is, right now it is Thursday.
I'll be back on Sunday. It flashed. There's a couple of things I want to try to get started.
I want to try to do a few things on. All right, what are you looking for here? Remember, remember,
this is. I want to try to set up. This is for 500 community. So I'm gonna work on that. 500. We can
get it like that. Not 100. A good announcement I can make next week to set that all up. If you don't
know what I'm talking about. Does it not count? You'll know very soon. It was accidental. I also
am obviously gonna work on the other stream too. So I will see you guys on Sunday. I'll see it. No,
this is not, this is fake. But for now, let me see, let me try to get through these bits before the
internet turns off. And if it does, I'm sorry if I miss your bits or your subs. Remember, not real.
It's kind of out of my control at this point, but I'm gonna try. It doesn't count. It's not rapid fire
these. Which usually means I'm gonna do it much slower than normal. All right, press one if it
counts too. If it doesn't count right now. I hope not. Let me actually hold on. But thank you for
joining me. It was a lot of fun. That doesn't count. Kind of a long one. I did a lot of twos.
Playing with Star was a lot of fun. I've seen a lot of twos. Star again? Mentioned. Jesus Christ.
That doesn't count. That doesn't count. That doesn't count. The majority is spoken. Raid Vinny. Yeah,
I'll raid Vinny after this. Raid Vinny after this, by the way. That sounds about right. We're gonna
raid Vinny. All right, so let's go down. 14 seconds. Let's go. Today, I want to see where this
cuts off because the stream turned on and turned off like five times. Let me make sure this is
correct. Do you remember back in October, November of last year? It was every fucking day. It was
horrendous. Here we go. Here we go. That's my vote for Cheez-It. Let's see. Best snack. Cheez-It.
Another one. Cheez-Nip. Let's see. Well, let the people decide. Wait, I'm doing a vote for
Cheez-It or Cheez-Nip. Put a filter on your voice so we can determine who's talking. I hope they
come up with like a Charlie Cheez-Nip. That would make me fucking laugh my ass off. All right, let's
go. Here comes the poll. All right, I'll put a filter on so you know who's talking. Please vote
on this poll if you'd like. Okay, okay. The lower one is me. The lower one is me. The one that's
currently live is me. And introducing first, he doesn't need an introduction. Captain Chi,
he's currently, he's wearing the best cheese flavored snack belt.
That is a real belt. He is the champion of all cheese snacks.
And don't worry. Don't worry. Ladies and gentlemen, it's not like Jerma gave Captain Cheez-It like 99
in all stats and Captain Cheez-Nip like 30. There's no reverb. He deserves it. Where's the echo?
Cheez-Nips are fucking gross. And you also be ashamed if you think Cheez-Nips are better than
Cheez-It. There's no echo. And introducing next, his opponent. His opponent coming into the ring
right now. A disgusting human being. Trying to kill the American people by the way. Turn off the
lights. Here they go. Why is there so much reverb? What the fuck is happening? I'm not,
I don't understand. What's he holding in his hand there? What is that? I know what that is.
I know what that is. That's the third ingredient in Cheez-Nips. It's poison. I knew it. I probably
shouldn't have said that. He's poisoning his body. He's getting his ingredients all ready to go.
I should never have said this. This is like bad. He's fucking poisoning himself.
Just like all the Cheez-Nips. Disgusting. This is a joke. Charlie Chee at Cheez-Nips. That's not an
ad. That's me talking about how much this thing sucks. That's not an ad. I don't want to even be
in the arena right now. Lawsuit incoming. There it is. Okay, let's get that off the screen.
Hey, by the way, this is like this slander campaign brought to you by. Is it still there?
Ring that bell. This is an extreme rules. Who has the best cheese flavored snack? Charlie Cheez-Nips.
Right off the bat with the scoop slam on. This is going to be fucking hard to remember these names.
This should not be. I'm going to call them Cheez-Nips or Cheez-Nips. This is weird. Hello?
Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello?
Ooh, a low blow there. Remember, this is an extreme rules match. Hello? Hello?
Anything goes and then you can go to the outside like Charlie Cheez-It. There we go.
It's not his name. Just say Cheez-It. Cheez-It. Now you know who's the German.
Scoops him down. The regular one. My favorite snack is Cheez-It, especially the Tabasco ones.
They're fucking unbelievably delicious. You should buy as much as you can possibly
fit in your house. You've got a spare bedroom? Fill it with Cheez-It. How's that? This should
be bad. You've got a bathroom you don't use very much? I'm a little bit lower. There you go.
So now you can tell who the real German is. You buy it in the Cheez-It box,
put it in the Cheez-It box. There you go. This is a real hoist turmoil.
No, he almost slipped there for a second. Cheez-It's going to be a little greasy.
They can be a little greasy. Cheez-Nips aren't as greasy. I will agree. Wait a minute. He gets
caught by Mr. Cheez-Nose and throws him down to the ground. Now he's going to go on the top rope.
Second rope. We all know if you go on the second rope you're a fucking wuss.
And that's what he's doing. Exactly what he's doing. You go on the second rope, you're a wuss.
Wow. Lame. Why does this sound so fucked up? That was fucking lame. It's all right though.
Totally Cheez-It is going to be able to get up. Okay. Why does this sound so fucked up?
The yellow guy just did a elbow drop onto the orange guy. Is it better? Orange guy,
get him. Orange guy got him by the back. Now drops him into the nose.
No, this is so weird. His big fucking ugly Cheez-It nose. Cheez-Nips nose.
Nice miss by the way, orange guy. What about that?
Oh, he gets reversed there. And these are extreme rules. Go get something. Thank you.
God, I'm talking all this shit and he's going underneath the ring finally for the first time.
Is that better? No. He picked up a Kendo stick. No, that's a Cheez-Stick. What am I talking about?
He picked up a giant Cheez-Stick, but he gets reversed. Remember, these are all cheese based
rules. That is a sharp cheddar cheese stick. Just turn it off. Gets reversed. Now he's going to get
thrown over it and go for the steps. Well, here we go. We get 25 seconds left before.
I'm just, I'm trying to differentiate the voices to make it so you can tell who's talking.
Get him on the table. Get him on the table. What about this? What are you doing? Is this better?
Everybody stood up. It was perfect. Holy shit. Captain Cheez-It is now on the top
ropes all the way to the outside. Here comes a no. No. Let's go. He just got a double kill.
Oblivion. Now this guy's dead. Why are you doing this to me, game? Stop it. Oh, I gotta turn. I,
I just can't. Something I never fucking finished. Didn't even try. That's a glitch. I told you. I'm
just julianning fucking french fries. That's a glitch. Okay. Let's put it on there.
Oh, what are we getting close to? That's not a terrible analogy. That's a good one.
Julianning french fries. That's fucking smart and funny and interesting and hilarious. Finally.
All right. Mouth music. No music. No terrible aim. I can't have this happen. Actually hurting
people. No fall jokes. Hope not. Stop it. Yeah, this is a glitch. This is all fucked up.
That didn't help. Yeah, no, this is, there's a, it belongs on here. You're right. Hey, stop that.
Okay, this is wicked fucked up. No, why do we have to, why is there to be at this part?
No, technical difficulties is something wrong with the stream or a, this is not ignoring the
game's story. This is me fighting. What? I'm fighting like in a fucking dungeon. At least I
dungeon. No, I can't. I'll throw up. I'm seriously going to fucking get sick if I do that.
Is that a technique? I mean, I mean, it kind of, no, it's not. That's me doing that intentional.
Chainmail greaves. It's a shitty joke. It's not technical difficulties. I wish I could compare.
I think these are better than what I have. Guard helmet. I think is a little bit better.
Chainmail greaves. No, they're not iron greaves. Guard helmets. One. I think the other one is one
as well. I forgot. That's what he looked like for 45. I do. I did a face cam fucking yesterday.
How close are we? I got to take a look at this. You can't do 720. I think 360 might be the max.
Don't make any impressions. Yeah. Don't remember. We can go down here too.
No nightwing shirt. No, I don't think we're going to see the star wars shirt.
Breaking a game is not on the list. 360 FOV. There it is. Now if you're wondering why
you're probably curious as to saying, hey, Jerma, why have you not finished Oblivion?
Why wouldn't you go back to play Oblivion? Because I did all this shit and then the game
became not interesting anymore. FOV 10. This is just magnifying glass. You ignored the story.
No, I did, but not right now. Oblivion is like a 450 hour long game. This is not a story.
This does not mean ignoring the story. This is me like doing one of the quests.
Why would I? I turned it down. It's a side quest. Nothing else in here.
Plates, sleeping quarters. I'm so glad I haven't mentioned eating or ass or pissing.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on. Why? Hey, wait a minute. Nothing up here at all.
You realize that all your life you've been coasting along as if you were in a dream,
suddenly facing the trials of last few days, you've come alive. Is that, wait, hold on,
wait, wait, wait, wait. Wait, is that strange noise or is that music? Is that music? No, it's not.
I mean, it is. It's fucking music. Athletic strength. That's a, no, that's a strange noise.
How much fatigue you have. That's not me going like. That's like. That's a weird noise. Yeah.
Don't get mad at that. Basket case. I said level up.
Well, let's get going. I'm like getting it on my phone. I've just grabbed it as I failed the tutorial.
He's going. Are they biting people? Why would you run towards the animal? All right. I get it.
I understand the gist of the game. Is there a rewind? Is there a rewind button? That's not a
laughing fit. Is this how giraffes sleep? That's fucking crazy. What? Don't you get a stiff neck?
Okay. All right. I get it. I get it. I understand how this works. That's not a laughing fit.
That was not a laughing fit. That was not a laughing fit. How do I pick you up? That was not.
How do I pick you up? That is like where I can't stop. Emergency capture. Oh shit. How do you.
Too much. Too many bits. This is disabled by the tutorial. No laughing fit is like I can't even like
talk or breathe. It's all you hear for like 10 straight seconds. So how do I get them back?
Where are they? There's a lot of potential for. Look I didn't mean to delete this. I'm trying
to delete plants because it's like. They don't like the shrubs in there. Get rid of them. They
hate it. What is it the sims? When you have a painting in the room that the sim doesn't like
they're like fun goes to zero. There's an undo at the bottom. We already have a bad bad impression
of who? Impression of who? Of what are you talking about? How do I get the animals back in?
Or I. All right I gotta pee. I'll be right back. I'll be right back. No no where are you going?
Where are you going? How do I get these animals back in here? He's just walking around. All right
how do I delete this part? Here come here. Just let them walk around. Let them roam. No I need to
do the second tutorial. Okay let's do this. Come here. This is this is temporary. I didn't want to
fuck this whole thing up but I have to. Get rid of this shit. How do I delete this road?
Call the keeper. I can't. Can I not even. I don't think I can do that.
Call vet because look I can't. I can't like emergency capture. Is vet gonna go over here?
What about this? Call the vet. They'll walk back in when I'm hungry. It's going to the bathroom.
They're all trying to leave. There's a line. There's a line out the door to leave.
He can't even escape. What the hell was that? What you got? Sniper rifle? What the fuck?
Just keep keep. Get him. Get him. I didn't want it to go to like to shit.
Oh no.
He can just step over this. He can step over this. It's like a baby game. Are you serious?
All right what'd I miss? What'd I miss? What'd I miss? What did I miss? Just because I deleted
this that was. Did I miss anything? The vet's on duty. What'd I miss? What habitat's invalid?
What's wrong with this? Wait where are you going? Laughing fit? Wait is this the part with the
gorilla? If this is the gorilla part. Did I buy something? Hold on a minute. No no. That's lying.
Okay okay. All right yeah I see I see. How about a brick wall? All right are we still good?
Watch the clip. It's funny. Well I I can't. This is an invalid. Well how did it become invalid?
I can't like watch your clip and watch. I gotta pay attention to the video. How did I fuck this
up? I don't understand what's wrong with this. You have 158 seconds. Hold on. Where is it? How
many are in here? All right what I what is wrong with this gate? Marked as not. No no where are
you going? Where are you going? How did I screw it up? That's pretty funny. Is this part here
that's a problem? Oh my god Jerma fucking just go do something. The fence was fucked up though.
How did I fuck up the tutorial? Well it's very easy because I was selecting I was selecting the
bushes over here and it was selecting this fucking building and I deleted the building when I was
selecting the bushes here. I did it like 10 times. You sure you don't want to pick up this building
and delete it? I mean look I'm moving on to the next tutorial. Moulding should have been a free
space. I know what I'm doing. Seriously. I don't know why it's over here. It should have been a
free space. I soft-locked myself somebody said. Why were they selecting the bushes? Because they don't
look. That's not bad. They don't like bushes. They fucking hate them and it was like there's something
wrong with their habitat. They don't like the bushes. No get 60 seconds. Look see well you know
they really really don't like those trees. They don't like the bushes either. Oh I think I feel
an Alex Jones coming on. Is he gonna do it? So I have to go through and get rid of these
or they're gonna hate their environment. Oh that's close. I know how to play. I'm done. We're gonna
play. That shit was real close. All these plants need to be deleted. He has to mention Joe Rogan for
it to be an Alex Jones impression. Wait what? That's so true. That is unbelievably accurate.
Well they hate everything in here. 10 seconds. Okay well in Richmond we need food in here.
Here we go. It's the middle guy. It's the middle one. With the pursuit of justice. Yeah here comes
the straw pole. Second from the left. All right here comes the straw pole. Hold on. I have no idea.
We're about to identify the fucking murderer. I'm just gonna do one two three four five.
One two three four five. Who is it? Let me give me some help here guys. Ah too bad I didn't have
does a pole. That would have been really really easy. One two three four five. Does a pole would
have been instant. It looks like three is winning. Oh wow. Almost as tall as suspect number one.
Actually guys sorry to say this but like I'm like up here. I'm like right there. You motherfuckers.
I'm taller than all these guys. So sorry. You're wrong. This is five six. These guys roll wide.
Five six to six feet right here. That's not that's not doesn't make any.
All right it's it's the middle guy. The middle guy is winning by a huge amount. Thank you for
voting. That's it's a closing poll. Middle guy. By the way why do I have to pick for her?
She's the one that witnessed the crime. I was just told about it. Why do I have to pick this?
That's the guy. I'm sure of it. Okay let me scan these people. Okay we need it. We need to go to
legal level. We got to build the case here. Do identity. Case constructor. I know case for
identity. There he is. Case for identity. Line up. Okay see. Yep there he is. Why would he just
scan that by the way? That doesn't seem like something that needs to be scanned. Oh level up.
I think you spang grew for the 10 bucks. These streams make my night no matter what don't ever
stop. Wait this is when I was still reading bits during streams. Thank you for the 10 dollars.
Also sticks renegade. Sticks welcome welcome to stream against it. With 10 dollars and 26 cents.
This one is still doing it. Jiggas up the news is out. They finally found me. The renegade who
had it made retrieved for a bounty. How old is this stream? 342. Oh thanks a lot man. Thanks
for the 10 dollars and 26 cents. So 342 three times. Thank you for making me laugh and keeping
me going while working on game sprites. Well your name makes sense now sprite 37.
You know it's a good one as well. He skipped my bits. I also thank you for sprit take again
for the five dollars. Have the rest of my tax returns.
All right let's go. Good old days. All right thank god we're getting the fuck out of here.
Probably not but you know. There has to be something I can do here but there's just
absolutely nothing to do. Okay cool. Why does this exist? Of course.
Like there's nothing here. Let's go back to the courthouse.
No wait. Well if you really think you're prepared enough go ahead.
It says four day three. No you guys are looking for a tf2 video. Let's go. Wait I have a new
I have a new message. An actual rumor issue. Click maps. From what I understand the hearing
will be conducted in Judge Hilton's office at 10 o'clock on Wednesday morning.
Yeah yes sir. A court reporter will be present at the time. That was a click. Shoo me away.
No no no no no. That's the last chance here. That was literally a map click. No no a click map.
Like the the the circles on the screen. No you can't you know. We're not playing semantics.
We're not playing semantics.
The witness tapes. Right the witness tapes.
Uh that's that's not me talking. That's not an impression. Thanks for the filler.
Thank you for the filler. I appreciate that. Let's go to the map. Where were those? What happens
after a bingo? I give 500 community subs. This is what happens. Interrogation records evidence.
Let's get in here for the trial tomorrow. Basketball, weed eaters. Why are you extending
this shit? Where's the evidence? Uh we got the car. Scan that. Okay. I gotta stop talking. Just
got to scan all this shit aren't I? Oh of course I am. And like I'm gonna have to get the fingerprints
and shit. Oh no. No time for that. Court is about to start. Good luck counselor. Oh no oh god.
Okay okay. Case for identity. We got this. Okay we got the good old days. Never end.
And case for murder. We have like killing of a human being. How do you extend
with channel points? If you highlight a message it is premeditated. 20 000 channel points to add
30 seconds to a video. Right by the way. And I'm not supposed to be talking. None of this is right.
You just you know I'm a good talker. You get the guy on that stand and I'll be able to fucking make
it happen. Here we go. All right. I might have to use. No. I'm gonna use my second needle. The
honorable Judge Lawrence Adams presided. I'm gonna use my second needle. Uh if you trip it at five
minutes. I actually just got baited. I did. That was fucking horrible. That guilty motherfucker
right there. Baiters and gentlemen. Court is now in session. People may proceed with their case.
It's been five minutes. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury. Tommy Wu was a pretty worrisome
with thoughts. All right. Where's the game glitch? Game glitch. Here's Sonic the Hedgehog.
January 24th. Walking around. You killed it. You killed it. You killed it. By the defendant
Michael Fong. You will hear in the testimony of Cinderidge Chen how the defendant came into
Hal's bar with a group of Chu Sing gang members and headed straight for Tommy Wu. You will hear
how Tommy was choked with a steel cable and dragged to the floor. The defendant is charged.
In his suit. The evidence will show he is guilty of this charge. Walking back and forth like moving
his hands around. Oh god. Damn it. I tried to use my second veto and then I... I can't wait to put
the third disc in. I only get one more after this. Did I miss that? Did I miss the entire
rat tattoo arc of the whole stream? I had to. There was probably like a whole huge story about
the rat tattoo. There's an underwater taxi. I thought he was going over the thing.
I wonder if this is going to get tripped. Of course it is.
All right. What's possible here? What's actually possible here? Who's in this car? Who the fuck is
in this car? I mean, molding is done. Screaming is still on the table. Yeah. Ambulance. Impressions
are still on the table. That's true. Use horn. That was a... That was a rumor here right now.
Not... That was a rumor here. Not in the past. What the hell is the lion pose? It's this thing.
I do... I used to do it fucking every stream. This guy's freaking me out. Bad. Big time.
Okay. Drive to the hospital. No. None of these counts because it's... No, no, no. It has to be...
No, no, no. Doesn't count. All right. Talk to Dr. Hibbert. All right. Final mission incoming.
Final? Wait. This is the last mission? Oh yeah. Jerma, you think it's the final mission?
There's six more fucking hours in this mod. What are you talking about? You think it's the final
mission? Is that... That was way too fast. Is that a bait? Here we are at our final destination.
It's just between me and you. Random object. Well, I... Did I say final or did somebody in
chat say final? That was a selfie. I know my face cam's not on. Why? There's no... Put down the rocks.
Oh, I was like, what the fuck are you guys doing? Chat said last level. Did they say that?
We're putting them down by throwing them. Fall joke is very important to not have happen.
TF2 video's fucking guaranteed to not happen.
Need a disguise? Purchase. Who's American clothes? Another 425 coins. Click maps is possible. Shit.
Got this. Is slowing me down. An impression incoming? 57 coins. I mean, that's... It's
possible. It's possible. I don't know, though. All right, we have to scrounge around now.
How long am I gonna do this for? We're gonna find boxes. We're gonna find sewing machines
and box over here. I don't know, until I'm fucking bored. Do a wager race.
We've seen how much of a disaster those were. I should sleep more.
Okay, right before he loses. No, no, no. I'll give you time. Okay. So, we'll do this for...
Uh, not a bad start. At least three or four hours. At least. So, if it's like,
well, you know, guys, I'm gonna feel like I'm a little sick today. Right before you get a bingo?
No, no, no. It has to be at least a four-hour spring. At least. Box right here. And a B.
It took a lot longer than it should have. It's not an impression. What do you get if you win?
Uh, nothing. I've already been given so much by this community. That's the fucking good answer,
right? 400, right? Or was it 425? But if I lose, then I'll give Twitch a percentage of the money
for 500 of you to be subscribed. Nothing, nothing, nothing. That's a nice PR spin. Yeah.
Yeah. I'll just pay Twitch a bunch of money to sub 500 people. What about the statues?
The killer sock. Thanks a lot for the sub. KillerSock11518. Thank you for the sub.
How about one of my cars? Is that person still subbed? How do we check?
Well, this is too bad because we got rolled a really boring shitty part of this stream.
This is, this is crazy. So remember, I beat this whole game in one stream.
This might be the one five to 10 minute portion of this stream
or I don't sound like I'm going to fucking strangle myself.
This is weird. This is like a weird downtime for this stream. All right. Do I actually? Very calm.
I'm very calm and just relaxed. This is a slippery course.
Did they block off on most of these ways to skip group?
This is so bad. I think I'm going to have to restart this. Holy shit. I suck.
Unless I can, I don't think I can do anything. No.
Maybe I could have like, let's go. The offices. Resident Evil 2 remake. Which one? Up here.
Oh, by the way, best game that came out last year. Well, what's even hidden up there?
Cause he talking about that. That's quite, that's a journey for me to go on right now. Hold on.
If I go up from here, I'm going to get myself fucking killed. We might get a scream. It's
possible. This is the, this is the one point where it could happen. Thrip it. There it is.
You might get your scream. So I'm just going to try. I'm going to go up the stairs from here
and we'll go to the star's office. You got five minutes for a scream to happen here.
Star's office. You will posing webcams. No, there's already a webcam on the stream. You
don't need me. If you get screamed, then you're looking for a look at me, a laughing fit,
or ignoring the game's whole story. Hold on a second. No, I can't go to the showers. There
are lickers all over the place here. I've got to walk through here and then through the door.
Now you do. I know there's at least one up here. I've shot this thing 10 times.
Straight and it's on the left. All right. So where was that? It was somebody's desk with
coffee on it. Let me take a look. There's a stereo player and then a phone with some
pens. Let me put the phone with some pens on it. Okay, right here. Wooden box. A slightly heavy
wooden box. All right. That's all I got. A piece of wood. Come on, I can open this. Red dot sight
for the lightning hawk. A custom part for the lightning hawk that allows for lightning fast
aiming. All right. Pretty cool. Oh, so then from that's sick. But the other one is
with the boom box. I got to get back out to the main hall. And then first floor, it was like down
here, right? East office or press room. What did I just got more film? Oh, what kind of wild goose
chase is this putting me on? This is like a treasure hunt. I get the USB to go on the computer.
I've got to go check the press room. I got to watch out for the liquor. All right. So I got
back through back into the dark room or maybe not. Yeah. So I got to go back to get to the main hall
again. It's going to keep searching the desk. What there's like hidden prompts everywhere.
Why do we get every single part of the screen is so boring? I'm not doing anything. I'm just like,
how long is this board? We get it's eight hours for me to beat this game. And I can't
fucking even shoot a guy. I'm going to do the same thing. It's going to go down from here
and we're going to develop this film. So we just have to slowly make our way away from the liquor
through the shower. Wrong way. I'm just going, I'm going just back down to the
hurry. Kiss him. USB USB. I already got the lightning. Forgot that. What do you mean?
I'm going down. What are you guys talking about? I already did it. Yeah. I know I had, I have it.
And then I'm going to put that in the secret room downstairs. No, I know. I know what's going on.
10 seconds for a scream. So then let's just go. No. Fuck it. Run out of time here. It's gone.
Mafia three. So brutal. Can we get in this car? I pushed his face into the ground from standing.
Oh no. Witness. Holy shit. Running out of time. Made it to the bar. All right. Let's go. Why? It's
like GTA. Well, how come it's not working? I thought it was going to like just instantly go
to the mission. If you don't play mafia, by the way, this is probably here.
Welcome home, son. Early. Yeah, it's an early stream. I'll be better once I get some of that
shine in me. Let's make a toast. I just drove over like four people.
He was joining the military. That's not confirmed yet. That's not confirmed yet. It's
gone out. Oatwells. Oatwheels. Thanks for two months, dude. Go out and make his mom.
And that's precisely what he did. I'm so, so proud of you. Oh, cut scene. Ain't seen one of
those in a while. Oh, that's such an ignoring cut scene. That's so my god. Oh, cut scene.
The cut scene started like three minutes ago. Wow. Holy shit, dude. That was unbelievable. The
cut scene started like two minutes ago. I really appreciate that. God damn it. Whatever.
It's hard to explain what it's like coming home. That was so bad. I didn't even know the cut scene
started. Holy shit. What's the consensus of this game? What's like the reviews on it?
Like six. You didn't know that before you started streaming it? Why? You knew it wasn't in the
schedule. You knew it was a six before you started streaming it. You were just concerned
that other people might not have liked it. It sucks. That doesn't really. That doesn't really.
Yeah, you knew that. Bad, bad, very bad, really. Story is good for the gameplays, man.
It feels pretty fun so far. Feels pretty, feels, you hear that? Do you hear that?
Feels, feels pretty fun. Why? I gotta work on that. I gotta work on that. I gotta work on that.
Feels pretty good. Is this any good? Is this any good? Is this any? I gotta work on that. Bad port.
Liar voice. I gotta work on that. I'm glad we're doing this. Bad aim could happen here.
I need like a meditation video. I need to do a meditation. Guided meditation. Hold on.
Tripped it. What do we got here? Guided meditation? I have to do this, guys. I'm sorry.
I'm like, I'm all fired up. Damn it, not a Star Wars shirt. I thought it was a Star Wars shirt.
It was possible. What the fuck even, what happens here? It's supposed to be instructions. What
happens here? Thank you for being here, dear soul. I'm Kenneth, and from my heart I will...
Is this the cheers for you, guy? This is the cheers to you, guy? I think this is the cheers to you.
...make yourself as comfortable as you can right this moment.
You think it's sweaty? No, I'm not. We gotta get an armpit shot. We gotta get a shot of the
underarm. If there's sweat under the underarm, sure. Observing the words I share with you like
a soft breeze on a summer night. Noticing that whatever it is that you notice,
your body may begin to relax more and more as you listen to my voice and go deeper within.
How would somebody be able to sleep to this? Could you imagine... All right, seriously,
wait a second. Wait. Can you imagine if you were trying to go to sleep, okay? You lay down and
you're like, man, I really wish I had something to help me go to sleep. And I'm like, I only help
you there. And I go right up to your fucking ear. And I'm like, very soon you'll be sleeping.
And just to let you know, it's so relaxing in this room. And very soon you'll be going to bed,
just like the breeze of a sunny summer Monday morning. That's not an impression. That's the way
that you'll see the world. You're gonna be like, what are you doing to me? Like, I'm trying to
sleep. I need complete silence and I need nobody talking and I don't want any lights on. That's
not an impression. All right, let's see if we can... Now I'm even more fucking on edge than I was
before. It didn't help at all. No, that's not an impression. It's not an impression of that guy.
That's me doing, me doing that video. No, it's not an impression. Not an impression. No, it's not.
Where is my meditation? I just had it. Where is it? It's on a different window. What the fuck
is this window? Why is it down here? It was an impression of that fucking guy. Of course it was.
Help me. Come on. No TF2 video and we're good. And I want no Nightwing shirt, no TF2 videos.
Color in the molding box. Yeah, okay. We might as well just fucking color this in.
This is the free space. You know, just fucking write it on there.
Turn this shit off. Stubborn. Just seriously write it down. Let me fucking relax.
Because I drank a Coke that's an ad. That guy just made me so fucking angry.
I drank a Coke on camera and it's an ad. What? I can't drink a Coke on camera? All right,
I need to actually go over this. Tristan found him like this. He must have been taken here.
Found cut marks around his wrists and ankles. Death by strangulation. TF2 video.
Fall joke is bad. A real rumor moment is bad too. Yeah, seems like a killer may have robbed him
on like previous victories. Uh, not victories. Couldn't find the kids. How's this going on?
Who knows? Might have been someone else. Oh, I forgot about this. I did this shit, right? I
recorded myself for five minutes before stream. I'm on. I'm off. Right. I forgot about that.
I did a full like five to ten minutes of recorded base cam before the stream turned on.
I'm gonna head back to the office. And it was voted one of the worst jokes of the year, right?
Two years ago? This is ruining the game for me. I'm too angry. I'm just too hard. Oh,
it's gonna get so much worse. I'll let you know if we find anything else. All right.
Yeah, that was like worst joke that took. Yeah, I remember that. That was two years ago.
Why does that guy have that move? Why does that guy die? Why does that guy die in one hit?
Jerma mocking him getting mad at a video game should have been on here.
The same people who make this game. Like Jeremy getting angry at a game is one thing,
but then he mocks how mad he was and how embarrassed he is that he got that angry in
the first place. That could have been a square. Bad aim incoming. We have 50 seconds to see it.
Hey guys, just got the masks we ordered. Pretty cool, eh?
They're all chickens. Well, how do they feel? You like them? No gameplay at all yet, guys. Zero.
Zero gameplay.
I'll get it. What's next? L.A. Noire part three. I gave up on this game by the way.
I got like three or four streams into this and then somebody told me, dude,
you got like another 30 or 40 hours. And I was like, oh, okay. That's fun. Matches.
Matches are never anything. Ever. It's never matches. That's a one guy moment? How?
What do you mean that was a one guy moment? What are you talking about? How?
I still feel these seeds in my mouth. I'm going to have to go throw up.
No. One guy moment. It happened. You said it did. It didn't happen in the video. No.
Not at this part. No. It's there in my teeth. It's bad. I can't wait until we get the 1%
chance for Otto's Great Adventure 2 and I've used my third veto over the night to get rid of it.
Somebody did the scene plus the blood stains. No way is this coincidence.
Okay. Shoo on head. I better put this on my head or chat will think it's pre-recorded.
That was good. That was good. Where's like the good fucking joke square?
Where's the good joke square? Cause that was a good one. We kept the area pristine for you boys.
That's too rare to have it be a square. Boston accent was going to be one too. In
pre-stream we were trying to talk about what should be here.
Boston accent was a square and I got rid of it last second. God damn it.
15 seconds. Five house keys strung up like bait. There is 3,200 hours of footage.
Where will we? Oh, nevermind. I said five seconds. I said five seconds remain. Like what?
I can't say that you get the timer on the screen. I'm reacting to the same timer that you have on
your screen. I'm safer. Two by three. Rise up. That was such a waste for an extension.
This is nothing happening. What are you doing? What's 253? What is 253? Why are you guys saying
250? I'm not going to veto this. What a waste. What is on the roof? Oh, is the note. All right.
That was record time. That was record roof time. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't fall
off the edge. Do not walk off this edge. Do not. Don't. It's not worth it, Jeremy. Don't do it.
Three years ago, Jeremy. Don't walk off the edge. I know you probably think it's going to be very,
very funny, but it's not going to be funny. Don't do it. Don't fall off the fucking edge. Don't do
it. It's funny. I'm laughing at that one. I don't care if it's me. It was fucking four years ago.
I don't remember saying that. That was funny. That was funny. I liked that one. If it would
any other streamer doing that, I would have laughed at it. That was a funny joke. Guy from four years
ago. What? That game's not good. Who has this much blood? You would have died two pipes ago.
Okay. Oh, look. Another wedding ring. I'm the wedding ring killer. I kill people and then take
off the wedding ring. Here comes the fall joke. Find me if you can. I'm probably going to do it,
and that's the worst part about this. Looks as though the killer was decorating with this.
He's just a sick fuck. Okay. Here it comes. Here it comes. Red bag. Don't do it. The other half.
I'm not this much of a dickhead. Each once are identified. Mrs. Antonia Maldonado,
712 North Hill Street downtown. No, I'm not this much of a dickhead. I wouldn't just walk off the
edge. Okay, well, we have an address. That's the end of the trail. Oh, we almost did. Yeah,
it kind of has to be. Too bad to all those people that wasted their points. Whoa. I was
thinking there was going to be a fall joke. Sorry, guys. God, that was an explosion. It was Mrs.
Maldonado, right? That's affirmative. Right, so then there's a husband we should be looking for.
Get him. We've closed the case. Rusty's razor, of course. I don't want to question your tried
and tested technique. I'm going to T again. I'm going to be pissing out C. But doesn't the D.A.
require sound casework before he'll close the book? No, he's got to confess. And you know,
there's ways of getting. I'm sure. Testings and a stomach and everything that could process all
this shit. Wait, why is this one black? Oh, no. It was actually to your benefit. Oh. Have a stomach.
No, no, no, not a stomach, but just the way that it separates it. You guys don't realize your body
is a gigantic coin separation machine. You know when those old machines you put in the dime,
the nickel, the quarter, and it would go, put it in the right slot. If your body didn't have one
of those down there, we'd be in a lot of trouble. That's true. No, I get it. I know what he's saying.
But the weird thing, though, is even those machines, sometimes you put like a penny in
and it would fuck up and go in the quarter slot. So why are our bodies so good at?
How come a nickel doesn't go into the dime slot sometimes? If you catch my drift.
Sometimes I read the one comment that makes me laugh. Are you this stupid on purpose?
I'm here. Which one's Kenny? Tables are turned now, haven't they, boys?
Hey, look, old man. We're sorry. Well, Kenny's not here.
Kenny's not in this scene. Blatant one guy moment. I know. That wasn't bad aim.
No, that wasn't bad aim. That was fine.
That was not bad aim. That was I shot once and the guy was running.
Blatant bad aim has to be very, very much confirmed. It's got to be like, holy shit,
that was horrendous. I want to subdued the last one. I want to scream either.
Got to reload. He's got to reload. How do I tackle him? No scream is like, oh,
it's got to be fucking a scream. It can't be like, oh, or oh, I tried to hit X,
accidentally tackle. It's going to be like, oh, we're like, oh, it's time to eat lots of bacon.
This is car 11 K shots fired at South Flower Street, Scott's garage. It's cold for here,
but just like it's down, I need an ambulance and corner. So the guy did die. 95. We've already had
too much bacon. What do we got? I'm surprised. No shirts, no night wing shirt, no star wars shirt,
no clip maps. I did that all the time. You guys eat eggs in one bite for us. One bite.
You go to a breakfast place and you order to sunny set up eggs or two or whatever.
Shit, I'm not even looking up and sorry, the whole thing. I wasn't even looking.
Watching this shit from an audience perspective, you don't get all of the other stuff like
sometimes I'm just I'm gone. When I'm talking like this, I'm gone.
I'm not even, the game is not even here. It's like,
I'm just talking and there's nothing here and I just drive into shit. I don't understand.
But yeah, that's disgusting. Where we going? Then you think like 30% of the audience here.
Let me restart it. Turma streams, chat, playing games. We got cul-de-sac smash,
Ed Eddeney's candy machine, lunchroom rumble, or spin stadium. By the way, the title says
Nickelodeon. Click map there though. Okay, we've got cul-de-sac smash. And there is a fucking
vroomer there too. Got pretty good radio, 44 million plays. Two in a row. You got to kidding
me. It looks like this is going to be the one. Uh oh. No TF2 video. See how it is? I don't even
remember this stream. Here we go. Cul-de-sac smash. Okay. Instructions. Accelerate. Let's turn
the ads already filled in. I can't do this. This music is going to make me fucking scream.
This is nightmare music. I can't even talk. I have to take my headphones off.
When each derby to advance to the next location, earn cash by competing in derbies
and make repairs and build new go-karts in the shop.
In a collision, the faster go-kart does more damage. Keep an eye on your damage meter.
Okay, peace driver. Does that just mean fast music? That's like cartoon fast?
What does that mean? That's fast cartoon music.
Okay, looks like we're going to be Ed. Here comes an impression. I'm going to go.
I'm going to do it. Is it filled in? This is already filled in. Get a dollar for first prize.
I'm going to do it. Okay, I'm ready. Zippy, pick a go-kart.
If I have an excuse to do an Ed voice, like an Eddie voice.
Oh, I'll do it. I'll do it every time. There's probably three impressions in
this part of the screen. This is so loud. Click maps. Are you stupid?
Oh shit. This is on screen. Get off the screen. How are you supposed to play this?
I don't understand what's happening. Is it just bumper cars?
Could have done a loud game. Yeah. I guess golf is out. Why is Eddie just Bernie Sanders?
Okay, so what we're going to do is we are going to just, unfortunately, the one percent
has all of the money. We've got to take it away. Kind of. Not really, though. That was fun.
All right. Okay. That was Ed, Edd, and Eddie. Thanks for playing Ed, Edd, and Eddie. I hated
that. You can tell. You can tell that I was like, holy shit, get me the fuck out of this.
Please let me do anything else. I got to pee. Can I piss? I was like rage drinking water.
I'm going to pee. I'll be right back. You got to keep like clicking on the screen. No, no, no, no,
oh, no. Oh, the only thing that this, if I do this, if I do this on camera, 500 community subs.
Oh, this is a, this could happen if you thought there was no chance that this was going to happen.
I got news for you. I used to do that once every other day. Where are we going? Oh, no, no, no,
not a face cam. This is possible. Oh, I'm going to do it. Well, I mean, you got to see once or
twice before you know when the things are happening. Your skill was a business trip. You'd miss a
meeting down the hall. They left airline. That's pretty good. God damn it. You got to be kidding
me. 30 goddamn five in 2020. This is looking pretty good for three five. Excuse me. I've got
some donk donks to take care of the shirt. No, that is not a star wars shirt. It's not a star
wars shirt or a night wind shirt. This is before I got very, very upset. I said an email. What
email did I say? What was the email? What email? Wait, what did I say? You said Pepe laugh. Oh,
shit. Where is it? Where is it? Oh, we got like three right now. Oh, shit. No, look at me is no
baited. Don't do it. I'm too distracted to do the lion pose. It's not going to happen. That's not
mouth music. Me going. That's not mouth music. Mouth music is like me humming a beat or me beat
boxing or me like singing, not going like you get a purpose on remix four right now. You look like
you can't throw that. I'm trying to do remix six. Oh, don't do it. I can feel myself looking into
the camera mule doing that post Billy. If I win by a large amount on one of these, I'm going to do
it. No screen either. It's kind of crazy.
You fucking idiot. You stupid asshole. God damn it. Just hit every shot from now on. Please.
That wasn't a scream. That was a yawn. That was a loud yawn. That was not a scream.
Now, scream has to be very, very clear. Do not do any bad aim. Nailed it. No TF2 videos.
I don't have any rhythm. Something that I think a lot of people are misunderstanding when I do the
remixes. It's you can't it's hard to have rhythm when you have to play seven different songs
that intercut into each other. That's like if you have a guitarist that's on stage and he's
please. Stop. If I fall, I just need to, you know what I mean? You panic
because you know you're going to be skidding. Here comes the scream.
And this is late game too. I was fucking. What happened there? I did a full jump. That's worked
every single time. I did a full jump. What the fuck happened? I did a full jump. That's happened.
That's worked every time. Come on, man. What? That's not a fall joke. Fall joke is
somewhere where you're not supposed to fall ever aggravating. You walked up here.
I'm waiting for a sorry. I forgot. I'm playing aggravation simulator.
Oh, just rename it. Just do it. What? What? Oh, I call this jumping like just rename this game.
I'm trying to piss you off. That's it. Just that's what it's that's what it should be.
That's what it should be called. This is not about jumping. It's about trying to make as many
and many people angry as possible. Terrible aim. I think this shit was in an episode of Dexter's
lab one time. There was like an evil guy that like didn't want to make everybody like sad or
like angry and gave them like a video game to play and it like worked. Oh no, sorry. That's the
that's jump king. Right. What the fuck is he talking about? I think that's the same thing.
If you miss a jump. No, you missed. That's the whole point of the game is to miss jumps.
That was the powerpuff girl was from. That's from Phineas and Ferb. Is that show still on there?
Are they still making new Phineas and Ferb cartoons? No, talking about Vegas either,
which is weird. I'm going to get up to the top. How far away is the bud? Thank God. About halfway.
Why? What's wrong? Why? What's wrong? I'm going to get up there and scream. What's wrong with
Phineas and Ferb? Did it end it? Did it really? Once I get to the end game here. What's wrong with it?
Phineas and Ferb was only good new age. The only good new age cartoon show.
It was years ago. I didn't say I was somebody in chat said that. I didn't say that. What are
some of the cartoons that were like worth watching? I don't remember. That's not me
talking. That's me responding to chat. Come on. That's not me saying that. That's not me saying
that. Nope. Holy shit. That's a that's an odd one. How do you get that jump? Holy fuck. How do you
supposed to get that? We're good. Didn't say shit. Wait, that's the first time I've seen this. Oh,
boy. Don't move. Don't move. I sound pretty calm. I saw them collected. What am I? Am I
defeated at this point or what? Fall all the way. Still haven't nailed that down yet.
Fall all the way down to the candles and I'll probably scream. Here comes. I'm not saved.
Wow. That set the jump to the the jump to the it's just so hard to judge it.
Even when you do a little one it doesn't seem like it's enough. Wow.
That's remarkable. It's already filled in. Don't even say it. It's been filled in.
Get out there. It's only a minute left before this is done. I'll be back in an hour. Hey,
I'm gonna go get some boots. What size are you? 16. I've got these big ass goofy feet.
No, I'm I'm still perfectly fine at this point in the butt.
It's this this one. You got one more chance up here when I get up here. Didn't make that.
Why did I not make that? Wait, how did I not make it over that? Is the same person? I don't
understand. What? I'm shocked. Why am I so calm? Because it's wasted breath to be angry at a game
who was what was it was designed to make you hate everything about your current life. What
you're doing right now. I'm not going to let it win. I'm not going to give it the saddest.
I'm sorry to say. TV Robo. Well, plan on it.
This is the last week. I don't know. Look, I got all this to do first. I got
we got Mario Sunshine to do first. That's priority number one. Did that. That was fun.
I was slowly going up the rankings now. It's pretty early in TV Robo.
Same joke as last week. I also played those old Zelda games when they first came out.
I did Ocarina of Time. I don't think I have a lion mask. Where are we going? Cry of fear
co-op highlights. It was okay. I'm going to say something. Wait, where are we talking about?
Where are we going? I'm going to say some lion pose here. No, this is a real, real opinion.
Thumbnail. What do you mean the thumbnail? What? I think I've said this before on stream.
Zelda games, although I respect everything they've done for the industry,
I respect it as a series. I understand why people love it. They don't do it for me.
Zelda games don't do it for me. That's it. That doesn't count. That does not count.
It doesn't count. That's not the video I was watching. That's a separate video.
Oh, my fucking stomach.
Oh, my stomach. That was really good. That was really good. Lion pose possible. Lion pose.
I don't want to get any spoilers. I keep fucking going to this. I don't want any spoilers.
All right. Let's take a quick pee break. Thank God. See you guys in like two minutes.
Oh, thank God. We're at pretty much the halfway point. Please, please take a piss.
More to see. Step in straight minutes. Oh, I got to get some water.
Take a step in straight piss. Oh, wow. Thank God for that fucking RNG.
Saved by the RNG God. RNG God. This is empty. I can't fucking believe it's in that thumbnail,
but it has to be in the video. It's so fucking funny. That is actually fucking funny.
That I mean, it does, but it doesn't count because it has to be in the stream or in the video that
we're currently the time that we have. It can't be for a different video, but that should give you
confidence that within the next hour that it's going to show up somewhere, because if that was
in a thumbnail, that means I do that shit all the fucking time. You have an opportunity with
the lion pose. Terrible aim. The this one's the most likely to happen before this for sure.
I'm so glad we hit this right here because this is green screen movie night. This is
I'm so this is that there's so many of these could happen in here.
Technical difficulty. Why go to the bathroom? Laughing fit could happen here too. And then
we just need a Star Wars shirt. Bad aim to the toilet. No, I see. I see what you're doing.
I get it. This is how long it takes, huh? What do you guys do when I go BRB?
What do you guys do? Go pee? Do you leave too? I'm gonna laugh my ass off if it's the whole
five minutes. That'd be great. He's back. Fuck. He's back. Oh, so far these have been fucking
fantastic. That was a turbo room. He's back. He's back. Yeah. All right. So coming up next,
this one is called we'll be back. Hyper dimension. Germania Elbertson breaker.
What? Sounds good to me. All we need is a baseball video. Already got an interesting start.
All we need is a baseball video. That's true. And you'll get a laugh. Three, two, one. Here we go.
Life is paint.
That was quick.
I gotta see this one again.
This is, I love this. This one is called images of German 985 real. Do not watch at night.
Hopefully it's not night, wherever any of you are. Oh, we're getting close. Star Wars shirt ends
this whole thing. Terrible aim ends this whole thing. The lion pose ends this whole thing.
MS DOS games. Um, replace this line with your specific CD-ROM driver line. You only need to
use this line with DOS six on a CD-ROM to book. Oh yeah. You had to punch in some shit, right?
Because the manual track instruction didn't work. Course one. Yeah. Course quiz. Before playing the
game, you'll be asked to identify a piece of track from one of the five courses. Ignore the page
reference. Use your mouse pointer with the correct piece. A 10. God damn it. G seven seven.
That's a bingo. That's a bingo. Hold on. Let me stunt driver. Hold on. Let's,
let's do this together. Course quiz. On course two, page 40. On course two, what is the piece
at location? Question mark. Course two. What is the piece at location? I five. I said three hours,
right? I said within three hours if it happens. I needed 15 more minutes. Course two. I five. I can't
is it one, two, three, four, five. Yeah, this is like, this is me meaning that I can't play the game.
Little oil can on the right. Straight line with an oil can on the right. I think it's this one. Hold on.
All right, here we go. How do you drive? Hold on. I got my hand on it. Control,
alt, p, q, r. R is, I fucked it up. It's all right.
You're going the wrong way. Scream. Turn the car around. Q. How do I gear it into,
got it. Get it out of neutral. I can't put it in first gear.
Oh, no. Watch out for the skittles. Let's go. We're in the M&M's candy world. Oh my god.
Jerma Gaming. Oh my god. I can't believe it. Oh my god. Dude, Jerma. D, S, A. 200 community
fucking subs. D. I really didn't think this was gonna happen. W. I thought I was, I didn't think
this was gonna happen. There's too many variables. R, Q, tab, shift, space, press one.
Not the candies. Oh, I just ran over everybody. Fill it up. Let's go. Fill it up. What just
happened? Oh, it's a new, new stream. What the fuck is happening? I can't turn off the crop.
Hold on. Why is this going, why is there like fart noises? Okay, so.
I think, I think, I think I just got like shut off. I tried to do it again. I just tried to
do it again and I think they just like banned me. Hold on. Wait, wait, hold on a second. Hold on.
Hold on.
PayPal fraud alert. Are you trying to do this? Oh, Gabe Newell from Half Life
Softworks. I got a PayPal fraud alert. Thank you. Thank you, everybody. Whoa. Okay, so what,
everybody needs to settle down here. Okay. Yes, I'm Gabe Newell, I am. Okay, very much. Thank you.
Yeah, okay, here we are. It was like, hey, by the way, somebody's done like,
like, more than $1,000 on your PayPal account. Wow, interesting. Wow. Is this you, dude?
Yeah, it's me. Yeah, it's me. Hold on. Oh my god, another somebody else did it.
We are sorry. Let's go. We are delaying our new game to 2013. Hold on, I got fraud alerted. Yeah,
I know. Not many of you here today, unfortunately. We're delaying our new game to 2013. There's 100
subs from Austin Plains. A few days ago. Fucking 100. A few days later. Freddie gave 100. When we
reached out to Warner Brothers, we were assured the delay would be brought under control,
at least for now. But no further information was forthcoming. Hold on, I have changed. At some
point in 2011, we also came across an official FAQ from Warner Brothers that stated. Let's do it
again. We would like to thank you for your great love and support of the Kingdom Hearts franchise.
What the fuck is happening on this stream? Somebody else gave 100. I just gave 100. Did it
go through? Holy shit, every single person is going to get subbed on this channel. Every single
fucking person will be subbed in this chat right now. Jesus Christ, who just did that?
The fact that this series takes on so many different forms, including the addition of a
new game feature. I'm losing my mind right now. I can't even take me talking. Reads the press release.
This is precisely what we'd like to introduce. I'm losing my fucking mind. Who just gave the 100
subs besides me? And that is all. Thank you. It was Abe Kashim. Fuck you. Yeah, I've wanted to say it
for a very long time. Fuck you all. I got 100 more to do and that's it. 100 more subs. This is
500 here. How could he say something like that? 35 more seconds. No, god damn it. I got a circle
in scream, by the way. There's been at least three screams. No, that's like the meme. Like my brain just
typed the thing that's the meme. What a fucking idiot. What an asshole. Where are we going?
Where are we going? I get another alert from people. No, no, no. Of all the places to go.
That guy. No, not the Karazhan stream. That is a geared up tank. This is a 0.52%. The worst stream of
all time. Just got queued up here. It's just walking around side by side. No, no, no, no.
Kill it, Danette. You tripped it. You tripped it. You tripped it. Is he DPS or heals?
Holy shit. This is the worst. This is the worst stream I've ever done. I can't fucking believe
Karazhan is here. All right, just need a healer. Just need a healer. The one time I played WoW on
stream. Yeah, sanctuaries are where the Horde and Alliance can both be. And they do not. Dude,
what did I forget? My PayPal password? I can't even get into my PayPal. I'm like locked out of
my PayPal. Shatterer, Shatrath City, whatever it's called. And we're going to Blackrock Hold.
I might get turned off for 24 hours. I think I just got turned off for 24 hours. We'll finish
in. Hey, come on, PayPal. I got the money. Over the edge. Heal us with your laugh. Oh, God. Stop,
Jeremy. Did it work? Walking around and fucking in. Yeah, Burning Crusade was the first time.
New friend. It's cool. You watched me from the toilet. Well, hi. Okay, I think we're good.
Sanctuary was the last Dalaran in Wrath. Yeah. Dermot, what's your eye level? Who the fuck is
talking? 854. Oh, that's MLC Stealth. What's yours? There you go. 500 community subs. I'm a man of
my fucking work. 856. Thank you. What the heck? Oh, this stream sucks such ass. Like I'm going to
use my third video that I'm using. I'm using my Veto. Wow. Yeah, we just need a healer and then
we can get going. It's going to be this for like another 15 straight minutes. The Bloodhouse
vendor. Where is he? That's boo. I'll heal if you can't find anyone. I can't believe that. That
means you're going to have to get in here. Dodged a sub. You sound depressed in this video. Yeah,
because I'm playing Warcraft on stream. Bit too stuffy to talk. Oh, it's hard to be excited
about this game. He's new to Felforge. If I'm completely honest with you in that case. Yeah,
boo is sick. He can't really talk, but he can heal. I'm going to give it like another wipe the
after I check out the vendor. If nobody, not even kidding. This is the worst stream I've ever done
in 10 years. This person over here. No, this is the worst stream I've ever done. I got one more
Veto. My God. 200 order resources for one. Oh, nobody cares. Look at my inventory. Holy fuck.
It's so bad. Look at how bad that looks. I never do the world quest. They give it. Why do you have
this? Why do you have that in your backpack? Resources? Why is it in your backpack? There's
15 teeth in here. Delete the teeth. It's 15 teeth. 10. Oh, my. Nobody wants to watch this shit unless
you know what you're doing. I have like a shit load. I think I have like, I have like at least
like 40 or 50. I'm like on this character, bottom tier player and I don't even know what I'm doing.
And I, I, I still, I, I still click the mouse on moves. Got a lot of money. That was a lot of
money back then. Holy shit. Go kill the world boss. We could do that while we wait eight hours of this
Now, let's just do that. Let's go. Let's go kill the world boss. Yes, this was.
25,000 gold was not a lot of money. Four years ago. Five years ago. Yes, it was. You guys,
there's always an auto cam. That was, that was a decent amount of money at the end of the stream.
That's not going to be for a long time. High mountain, right? Yeah. Guys that are here for the
dungeon. We're going to just go get the world boss real quick. Oh yeah. This is when MLC self was
like snorting up the fucking boogers all stream. I remember. Yeah. I remember this. That was another
reason why this stream was so mad. Where are you going to fly to Stonehoof for? It was like sick.
Uh, stop. Where are you? I'm watching wrestling. Okay. I'm watching what you should be watching.
You need to get like geared up for this Sunday. Hell in a cell where you're not going to know any
of the story. I love how fucking tuned out you are right now. Yeah. Wait. Yeah. What are you saying?
I'm saying where do you, where are you flying to to do the world? To iron horn enclave, which is
the high mountain. I'm also about to blow my nose. I'm going to blow my nose. No. I fucking told you.
I told you this is what happened. I told you. What time is it? It's the three PM. It's Alex.
What? Wrestling bosses and wow. My God. This is so boring. It wasn't even that loud. Oh,
it got louder progressively. This is excruciating. Who did what again? He went like, and then he went
and action cam might be cool for melee. You can message people across realm, but you have to add
the realm that they're in as well as the name. Who's here? Who is it? Who goes there? Hello stream.
Oh, hi. I just woke up. You sound like you got a raspy voice. Well, if you want to do carousel
voice has actually been getting better. That is you want to do carousel attunement where you have
to do. Why is that covering the whole screen? I did hear that there was a big,
a big deal. Thanks fucking God. We're out of here. Thank you, Lord. Get us the fuck out of here.
We're up here. 74. Let me, uh, let me just give me one second. I want to check the patch.
Now we're in the Punisher. We got a bad uncut patch. I mean, it's, we are, it's already done.
We already did this. It's already over the gore level setting. It's high or none. I already
changed it. What about a full blackout? A full blackout is just, I mean,
that's going to be very difficult to do. Go for double bingo. No, no, I can't give any more subs.
PayPal is going to seriously like call me. If I give another hundred community subs,
I'm going to get called by PayPal. They're going to be like, Hey dude, like somebody guaranteed
hack your account. Guaranteed. I'm going to be like, no, they didn't actually have this one.
PC gaming with a gore patch 3.5, but honest to God, there was a lot of money that came in.
Yeah. There was like three or four other people that gave $50 to a hundred subs.
It was fucking crazy. What happened? It was almost a thousand subs brought in during that
whole debacle. Uninstall the old one. How do you uninstall the old patch? Isn't it like a hook into
can I just remove the exe here and that'll be fine. Remove the, what am I talking about?
Yeah. If you didn't believe the technical difficulties, we're going to happen.
It happened right now. I have a backup of everything, but that's doesn't include the,
yeah, that's absolutely. Yeah, but I got to know this. This is a full on bingo profile
over here without any fucking around. I'm going to copy this profile and move it over here. I'm
going to try this patch profile paste, replace this file, do more just for fun. Yeah. We don't
need the bingo anymore. Gore patch 3.5. I'm just going to start skipping around.
Congratulations to those that got the community subs and congratulations to me for just paying
myself money and giving a bunch of it to Twitch. We are going to turn off the, you can eat a lot
of it and not really feel that guilty, but it's high in fat. Just be careful. Don't go crazy.
What, what is it? You don't want to like cause like a stomach problem or like a digestive issue
for yourself. If you're just like, I'm going to eat a jar of peanut butter every day.
No, that peanut butter is good for you. High quality proteins, especially after you fucking
work out. This is the Africa. I used to like to do a spoonful of tahini before bed. Yeah. Okay.
Next. This thing, this is not going to fit in a priority box. This will, this will not fit in
the box. It's massive. Destroy all humans. He's going to get a pub G win. That was your last
veto. What? No, the game is over. You won. You guys won the game. Can you buy the dream cast
is coming with me. This is pretty random stuff is coming with it is a junk company just coming to
take care of all the stuff that I can't take with me.
I didn't say Vegas. I can't extract these guys. I don't have that yet. I didn't talk about Vegas.
I said it's not coming with me here with me. Where didn't we calculate this on stream?
We did like how the dimensions of the thing. And it said I couldn't ship it. I had to go like,
get like this. I had to get special treatment. That's not a requirement. Ass hat. We already
looked at this on stream. I remember we were sitting there. We were looking at like pricing
for stuff. It was like, is this a shitload of money? He's going to say it's 400 pounds,
200 or 400. Doesn't matter. I'm talking about shipping my computer with the United's postal
saver. The United's postal savers. No, I need to transmog these. Leave them.
It's not worth anal prom with these guys right now. Next. Why you continue to throw rocks at my
house? I thought we were over that. I wish I could pause this, but I can't. The last Simpsons hit and
run thing that we saw was talking about people throwing rocks at my house. This is I feel so
unfulfilled. I'm so unfulfilled. What's the fastest way to lose? Drive into the ocean?
It was just this level for two hours. You gotta be kidding me. Just drive to the,
just like go to the power plant, I guess. Yeah, this is the end game here. This is the final
mission of the game. Just exit the car at the beginning of the mission.
It might be faster to just beat the missions. Same joke as last week. I was done. It was so
close. Oh, just wait the 20 seconds. I sound so done. Our number 10. I remember being at our
number 10 or 11 and we got a big raid that came in and I was not in the game. This is a,
and I was fucking furious. And I remember we got a huge raid and I had to like prop myself up and
be like, Hey everybody, welcome to the raid. Hi, thank you. I can't just like, fuck it up.
Where are we going? L.A. Why is it L.A. Noire again? Where's the crime scene?
This is part four of L.A. Noire. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait. That's right. That's right. That's
right. In the fountain, we shall shine. Nope. That'll get rising revenge. No, this is all over
the place. What are you guys doing? This changes. What is happening right now? As you click maps.
How is this even possible? 30, 36, 39, 32, 36, 31, 36, 34. What? This doesn't make me sense.
Oh, I know what's happening. Nevermind. Everyone. People are clicking on both
because 12, 15,000 people have clicked the screen. Okay. Well, I need to change that.
One click per user. That's the exact same thing. Yeah.
Finding more bugs would be nice as well. All right. Well, what's, um, how long have we been
streaming for? Like two and a half hours, something like that? Yeah, about two hours or so. Nothing.
When is there anything else you would like to do, my friend, or are you going to want to do?
It's all up to you. Do you have another game you'd like to play? Um, I mean, we could hop into
something like GTA if you wanted to, for like an hour or something.
Oh, it's been two hours. Yeah. 2000, uh, needs a break or something. Just let me know.
2017, 2016, German. Two hours stream. It's been enough for me. All right. Well, yeah, that's it
for this, this particular stream. I'm going to take a pee break. I'll be right back. Oh, if you're
turning off your stream, then I'll turn off. Oh, no, no, no, no. I mean like this like particular
game. That's what I said. I didn't make it fucking clear enough to me.
I'm going to pee. I'll be right back. Just enjoy the fucking random bullshit that you see. I'll be
right back. I'm having so much fun right now. This is perfect. I'm having a blast right now.
I really am. This is fucking fun. Oh, my like head hurts from just like laughing internally
right there. First question. God, the receptionist part of the wedding. I did better at this game
and I love high school. All right. No more fucking jokes. No more messing around. We're going to
play an action that worsens an already bad situation to set the head, add insult to injury.
You seem certain it's a, oh man, that's so fucking fun. And you're right.
Right. Laughing internally. They're going to run out of $100 questions.
They're going to run out of the $100 questions. Add insult to rights.
Okay, come on. Give me the $32,000. I got my lifelines.
It's beautiful. We see the love of your life coming down the aisle.
According to a well-known proverb, what do many hands make?
Many hands. I ain't doing it. You know, it didn't happen. Smosh did it. I'm not,
I don't care if Smosh did this. Well, I don't like, I've never watched Smosh.
So they did that Pokemon video like nine years ago. All right. What do I do with these two tabs?
Sweetheart, I know you're watching right now. I'm working on two tabs.
Can't get waxed. Not going to happen. Hey, sweetie. Not going to happen. All right. Time
to connect the arms. Wait, what's happening? Hold on. Connect the arms and the orange strings.
Thread them properly. Take the string from the shoulder strap with the R-zool on it and
tie it to the arm. Take the string from the shoulder strap with the R-symbol on it.
For this fucking guy. All right. Hold on. What'd I miss? What? Hold on. What? What? What?
Hold on. He's so handsome. What happened? What are you talking about?
Drunk, sweaty. Wait, what? Drunks. Who the fuck is out there?
Fucking weirdo. Holy shit. That was a fucking pog moment. Holy shit. That was unbelievable.
Imagine being that quick. That was it. No. The first VR we've seen all night. Thank you,
Walt Disney. I mean, it's locked. It's too quiet. I'll get it. Hold on. I need to replace this with
something, obviously. Got to have to come back later. Any other doors? This is so. I'm having
a blast. This is so fucking fun. Coin. Everybody, thank Lazy Luke for making this possible.
On a stupid whim of shit that we were talking about. Literally not even a day ago in the
pre-stream chat. I made a reference to this. Oh, not even a full day ago. And this shit is
ready to be used now. Not even a full day later. That's unfucking believable. No problems. It
worked like a fucking charm. Like it's been great. It's been absolutely fucking fantastic.
I have to like make this coin do something on the wall over there. I'm going to assume. By the way,
that is sky. If you feel like it, you can do this too. This is available for anyone just to play
with. We'll figure that out later. If you mean, obviously, you'd just be watching old streams
and videos, but it is available. Serma.org slash random. You can play with it yourself. Sky Hunter.
I'm actually going to take a second just because there's a lot of people that probably didn't see
this in the beginning. Let me just go ahead and do this real quick because there's a lot of people
that weren't here in the beginning. Oh, dad, can I at least get some tuna fish next time?
Remember that? Write that down. That's a map. Okay. So if you're curious how this all works.
So this website is it's Serma.org slash random. This is my entire life on the internet. So this
is probably like 90% of everything I've ever done. If you click this button, you're going to pull from
778 streams and 712 videos. So just for the people that weren't here before. Now I know
that some people that have just trickling in and just like, no, why the fuck would I want to
skip through 3200 hours for your fucking shitty stream? You don't have to. I'm just the website
is available for anybody to use. Let's see another shitty stream. Get out quick. Oh, I'm stuck. No,
get back in. Get in. Someone gifted me a sub. A lot of gifts. It was probably me. In the back.
It was probably me. What? You will not have the countdown. No, because this is a special
thing made for the stream. So you can watch as long as you want. And you can just skip
whenever the fuck you want. Pick another spot. 700,000 games. That's a pretty good one.
Fuck it. Super Mario maker. Pretty good job. I just wanted that longer than seven seconds.
This is the McChicken stream. Well, this is, it's a nine hour stream. So
when are we going to get Jerma's family dinner? Oh, did you just get it?
Lightning round? No. Okay. We're probably going to pull it back. This is probably going to be the
end of the stream. Um, just wanted to do something fun today. Just experiment with some stuff.
We're going to do a lightning round. I will see you guys tomorrow for community content night.
And it's happening tomorrow. So it's time for a lightning round. Every five seconds,
we're going to press the button. Here we go. Monster hunter three. I need to kill these things
anyways. So old. Not a big deal. I think Kim is, this is the first time Kim ever showed up on video.
Yeah. This is, this is a Kim appearance. The first time ever.
Whatever. Amid evil part two. You guys have to keep linking shit from my birthday.
Is it my birthday? When the fuck did I play this? Wasn't this like two months ago? Enter at the
dungeon. Picket fence credits. And I don't have a single memory. I never played this. I don't have
a memory of playing this. I didn't. I've never played this. When did I play this? Are you crying?
Was that your king? Get fucking sod. I've never played this game. When did I play this?
Uh, wasn't there a chest that I couldn't open? Is there anything else I could buy?
This is freaking me out. I don't remember ever opening this. I'll try. I'll give it a go. Why not?
It was just once. That's it? What a monster. This actually might mess me up because it's going to be
bouncing all over the place. See how much damage it does. 2006. Oh, hello. Let's go. Oh, here's a
Might and Magic 3. This is the best unit I can make. Worst stream? What? You're bringing in so
many people. I've just spent so much money. This was not the worst stream of last year. So many
people. I'm going to win. The turtle wins the race. Did you see the end of that movie?
Oh, I love this game. Condemn 2. What font is the bandicam font? Oh, wow. We landed on
not only unregistered hyper cam. Holy shit. What a thing to land on.
That's that's better. That's much better. Unregistered hyper cam is five times funnier.
Don't skip. I won't. It's going to skip in a minute. Stop the timer. I can't stop the timer.
It's going to be down a little bit. Extended. I can't. All right. Somebody extended. Somebody
extended. OK, I'm ready. All right. That's good. Should be right here. Should be right here.
There it is. We're having fun on our game. I honestly don't know what's going on. Put dot net.
Dot net.
It's got like a weird text to it and it's black. This should be put in the Library of Congress.
This is staying on for the remainder of the stream. I hope you guys are aware of this.
It looks a little like glitchy, right? Just put the picture at the top. That's true. I
could just do that. This belongs in a museum. This is for cultural significance.
You guys are fucking crazy. It's got to be perfect. All right, let's play. Turn down the stream
resolution. I don't. This joke is a bit. That's a funny joke. If it wasn't real,
because it's actually real. Somebody said imagine low quality. OK, imagine if we had just stopped
watching the Nancy Drew stream, like not even an hour ago. Oh, this would have been the worst
stream of 2020. That could cause a problem. If I didn't veto that, this would have been the worst
stream of 2020 for sure. How does this sound? Does this sound fucked up? Are we losing quality?
I thought about it. It floated around in my brain for a little while. How does that sound?
To let it play out for an hour and 40 minutes. OK, like that. Remove my pop filter too. OK,
hold on. I need a fan on the background too. All right, let's do. How about this? I don't even
know what this is going to do. Imagine if I played a video game. It's going to do. I don't know.
Half of these clips we'd stop in or just don't know what any of them mean and not even playing
a video game. I got to remember where these were. Oh, guys, no, I have a much better idea.
We're turning on the webcam audio. That's some gross hair. People talk shit about the hair I
have now. I can't pull it in. Really? 2017 hair was way grosser than this. How does it sound now?
Pretty terrible. That's some gross hair. Wait, I might be able to. I actually think I can. Let's
see. It was awful lighting. We still have awful lighting. How's this, guys? Hey, hey everybody.
Yeah, make the quality of the camera terrible too. OK. So I did this video. I'm going to show you
my new favorite game that I played. Let's make the camera look terrible. What is making the
quality awful? Didn't I one day? One day wasn't there a scenario where I had my webcam mic plugged
in and I didn't know for like two hours or something? We can do custom resolution. We're
going to change that. When was that? That was recently, right? Oh dear. Kiss him. I don't know
where it went. I'm not going to kiss him. Where did it go? It looked so awful on my screen,
but it disappeared because it was 160 by 90. Where is it? Pretend to be the mom. Where's the
camera? It's gone. There is no. Mom is upstairs and you can't hear. Hold on. Let me see if I can.
Here we go. Almost there. Let me see something real quick. So if I do this, if I go like this,
is that possible to? OK. Honey? Honey? OK, honey, it's time to come downstairs. Come downstairs
right now. There's a couple more things we can do. We're going to sharpen the fuck out of this.
Are you still playing? It's time for dinner. Add an echo? Are you? Are you still playing
that game downstairs? This looks like I'm from fucking 1930. Is he in a fucking cave?
And we're going to put a long con on here. I'm going to make it look like a fucking terrible
streamer. It's time for dinner. Fucking ghost mob. One more thing. What's there? Put up the
saturation like fucking crazy. Are you streaming? God, I'm going to tell your father about this.
That's good. That's too high. Are you? Are you? Are you? Are you? Are you streaming? Are you?
How's that? Is that a fight? Is that fine? That's too good. I know. It is pretty good.
Thanks, Jeremy. Wow. No, that's obvious. That's too obvious. And I got to be in the wrong spot.
Somebody extend it. Down here? Extend in a few minutes. Extend in a few minutes.
And I'm going to be like fucking silent. My webcam is going to be in a wicked embarrassing place.
All right, we're good. Hey, what are you doing? That's good, man. I got to get in my acting mode.
It's desynced. What are you doing? Holy shit, this looks so fucking bad. Hold on. Let me move this.
Remember, like everybody needs to fucking be in on this because I need some people are going to
trickle in randomly and I have to be like a piece of shit. You know what I mean? Okay, that's fine.
I'm just going to add one more thing. It's so funny because people were. This needs to be.
People were writing like your stream sucks and shit like that. Like, fuck you, dude.
Maybe I can. Yes, I can. Can I? Oh, fuck, dude. Oh, my God. It's about to get so much worse.
I'm apologizing in advance. This is going to look fucking terrible.
I'm going to fuck up the footage, too. A lot of people were in on it. It was awesome.
Good call. If you came to this stream that was this one, this person is view-botting,
right? If they were like at this point, this is like two or three years ago, something like that.
There was probably what? Fifteen hundred, two thousand people watching this stream.
Like you're a view-botting fuck. We need to pass it through one more time. You are a view-botter
if you have a stream like this that has like three thousand people on it, right? Like you have,
like there's no way you don't have an unregistered Hypercam 2 stream. Holy shit. This looks, look at
this. Look, you can even see it. You can see like the pixels moving. Imagine how angry you'd be if
you came to this stream and you saw that this guy had like a hundred and forty p quality and he was
just like blowing his nose and shit. I thought this was real. I'm serious. Was this one of your
first streams? That makes me so happy. By the way, this is like, this is like irreversible.
Quick, extend it. All right. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait. All right. Extend it one more time.
Extend it one more time. Room lights. Yep. Extend it. Some of you guys have a shitload of
room lights. Turn off the light. Yep. You got to be sitting in a dark room, completely empty.
I'm going to turn these off, at least low enough where it looks really fucking creepy. And like,
I don't, I don't know what I'm doing. And then we're going to play and everybody needs to,
you guys need to be in on this because somebody, somebody eventually is going to come to the stream
and be like, what the fuck is going on here? Why does this guy have any viewers? I see. I told you.
No, that has to be it. I get it. I look like a fucking serial killer. Okay. Do everyone pretend
to be bots? Right. Right. The bot messages. How's that? Oh, wow, man. Cool kill. This is such a fun,
epic stream. Smiley face. Same joke. No, I'm laughing. That was somebody in chat that said that.
I'm laughing at a chat joke from like three years ago. I don't know what I did. I have to go over
here. No, this guy here. Fuck, man. Fucking. How do I go up there? What? What are you doing?
No, I'll go to bed in like an hour. It's two a.m. Yeah. Okay. I'll be up in like 20 minutes.
No, it's not what I wanted to do.
Perhaps it's your drinking. My drinking is not an issue.
I'll go get this processed. In the meantime, Farrell wants to see you in his office for a mission.
Fucking it. Keep your cool.
People in the chat right now. Yo. Like pretending that this is happening right now.
Dude, like, oh, pog, dude. Nice shot. Like, what the fuck? Oh, you guys are going to kill me one day.
You're going to kill me one day. I'm going to die on stream one day from something like that.
Of course, I take like a sip of fucking water. What is what? What the fuck am I thinking?
Is it weird that I don't want to stop doing this? Nice shot, man.
Keep doing it. All right. I'm going to give I'm going to make a timer for like Siri.
I took a sip of water and choked on it. I got one more. I got one more bit I want to do.
No, no more bits. No more bits. Let's get the fuck out of here. Next. Next. Right now.
I can't. I can't climb this. I mean, there are no bricks.
Is this guy home? I don't even know if this guy's home.
No, veto this one, too. That's what I get for reading fucking chat during something like that.
Tell me you guys say the funniest fucking shit, I swear to God.
Glacial crystals. I can't pick up more than one of these.
Skip terraria. Fine. That's some of my favorite means of travel. I'm glad you're bringing it up.
Red Dead Online with Vinny. But before we before we do that, I want to also say there's a game
called Rust that just implemented hot air balloons. Oh, God. Are you serious? Yes.
So many technical problems with this one. Let me give me one second. I have to say hello to
somebody. Somebody's knocked on my door. I got to say hello to them. Hold on. What? Hey, it's you
guys. It's my stream. My stream chat. I'm half expecting this to be. It's not. I just want to
say hello playing Red Dead Online Pog. That's up. The simple things make me fucking laugh.
How you doing? Oh, it's me, Elvis. Vinny Vinesauce.
My hair is fucking really good. That was really I just that was really good. I had to come back
and say that I'm half expecting this to be a skit. And you threw me all off. I had a fucking
clown here. Hit that sniper. Dude, that sniper is like going like this. What the hell is your
medic doing back here? Walk into it. Now, you lucky, rare, very rare, extraordinarily rare.
So if you're watching this right now, I am currently in North Carolina visiting my sister.
Some of you old subscribers will know that I do that every now and then. I think I went there
last time during Thanksgiving. What am I talking about? I'm in this. I'm what? What? I'm in the
same room that I was. Come here. Oh, this must be the scheduled upload. A scheduled upload.
It was a really good time. It's a really beautiful house. Really beautiful place down there in North
Carolina. Before he gets that stupid thing off, I'm supposed to hit him. I don't even tell you the
load that I'm using either. I'm using my sister doesn't live in North Carolina anymore. Regular,
just standard flamethrower and the power jack. We need to push this point. We need to get rid
of that sentry. Can we take it out? Can I get it right now? Come on. Keep messing with that engineer.
Yes. How did I not hit him with that? I'm not going to say anything, but it's open. No.
Get on zip point. Hello. There you go. What's going on, medic? Thank you for the heels.
Much appreciate. Damn it. Shouldn't have done that. Mr. Winslow. Getting out of here after this,
I think. I think I'm done after this one. That's not the case. You can't be AFK, man.
God, that like, I drank water went down into my lungs. I just like raised in water. Why?
What was that lag? Oh, man. Oh, I was just choked. Wow. I can't believe I actually killed that son
of a bitch. Get rid of that sentry. Come on. Yeah. Tan him again. Do it again. Keep messing
with that engineer. Keep messing with him. Yes. What? I said a bad word. Need some help here.
This is post. Need some help here. Look, this is not the super meat boy playthrough. Get me out of
it. Damn it. I swore. Oh, heavies. It's in that cup. We got to get on that point. Big time. How
many sentries are over there? I'm going to go around the left side this time. No, no, no.
Where are you going? You're not going to. This guy's probably going to kill me. No, I'm going to miss,
but that's all right. Cause he's where is he? Where the hell does this guy go? I'll find you.
And when I find you, you're going to get your, your face ripped off. I'll take it. I'll take it.
How can I not hit the guy that's standing still? Why am I so red? Why are they both doing that?
Why are they both doing this? Fucking red. How many is it going to take to kill this son of a.
All right. Fine. I'll just smash you. You want to get smashed? Oh my God. That was terrifying.
Didn't even need to hit him. We're going to lose. Come on. I think I look better now.
Give me those heels. Just being honest. Turn around. Turn around, man. I got to try and kill
that engineer. That's what I wanted. Get him. Hit him. I'm trying to wait for him just to come
across the middle. It's a different person. This is not good. We're so dead. This is what happens
when you age. We're so dead. Like seven or eight years. Wait. Demoman, go. Quickly. Quickly.
Quickly. Quickly. Quick. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
This is called aging. Can I get there in 15 seconds? I don't think I'm going to be able to
get there in 15 seconds. This is seven years ago? What was it exactly? 2011? 2012? What? What? What
on earth? 2013 maybe? Pops? I landed on top of that guy's head. 2012. This is eight years ago.
Okay. That's the first time that's ever happened to me. Imagine if I had the man
treads on. That guy would have been tumor stomped. It's a defense. It looks like a little bit of a
defense. Nice sentry. Very good start. Sniper. Trying to shoot me in my face. Was I like a
jacked fuck at this point? Yeah, I was. Maybe he is. Look at the shoulder. Look at the chest.
I got to get behind him. If I stood up right now, people would just fucking fuck. Somebody just come
here. Two scouts. I'll wrap around you. Yeah. Give me a heal, man. I need a heal. Need a heal.
The old German would beat your ass. No, he wouldn't. You are a jumpy little freak. Because the
new German would run. Close him in here. Close him in big time. No, no, no. Don't think that
would happen. Everybody get blown out. This guy's got crits. I'm trying to blow people out. Oh,
run. Get him. Please. Please die. We're going to do 10 in a row. He's still alive. Five seconds
each. Oh, no. He died that far. That long after I shot him. It's felt like 20 minutes. This is a
10 minute video. By the way, this is a 10 minute video before doing a 10 minute video. People did
to game the fucking YouTube ad system. So don't look at that and be like, oh, what a dickhead.
He's got 10 minutes to get like the four ads. So this is 2012, dude. This is like before ads
even fucking existed. That medic is just standing back there. Oh, my God. That's the second sick
shot of the day. Wrap it up and give it to me for Christmas. Get away from the sentry. Get this
stuff away from the sentry. I got you. Don't worry, buddy. I got you. I was pretty good. I got you.
I was pretty good. What's next? Well, that's going to be plenty of that. Family feud. This is just
the shitty family feud. Who's going to play this? I'm going to try to win a game. Get fucking wasted.
No, no, just to have to get yourself small cup. Put in like 5% vodka and 95% cranberry juice.
Oh, Merry Christmas. Super spectacular. Which one of these games? Are you guys ready? Here's
the game of the night. Which one of these games? The only one cost money. One of these 41 games
was one dollar. Which one is it? Black and white. Part two. Yes. Let's go.
Where is Murius? I just want to see Murius's face once and I'll skip. All right. Let's see what
happens. Do they grow? How are we doing over here? I just want to see Murius's face. That's it. That's
all I care about. No one's even started building this yet. Where is everybody? This is part two.
We're not going to see him. Somebody build this. Why not? Yes, we will. All right. Jeff Keeley
build this. You're going to do it now. He was captured. Oh, no, that's right. He was being
tortured. Let's try to get another one. The Beagle boss here somewhere. Not going to get away.
Tokyo jungle. This game was really fun. Yep. Oblivion's on the first year of law school.
I'll hit you up eventually if I ever need you, you know, right? I'm a lawyer in chat.
You always got to have a good lawyer. Happiness being spread, tearing entire family apart.
Don't do it. You'll have to apologize if I do it. Oh, I'll do it. I'll do it. Do it.
This game is a really fun game. This is all just I wish that somebody like a AAA studio would make
this game. Plus, I keep the level has like 5000 hours to it. That's a good thing. And I keep the
moves. Monster Ranger. Oh, my goodness. Not good. You would play it again. I already beat it. And
I beat the whole game. I always got the stupid thing. Yep. Quest. Okay, marketing. It's five.
Okay. That's that's going to be the the one gas station. This game is so bad.
Yeah, you know, we got our fill in this game after about two hours, three hours. Excellent.
What do you mean? Wink Winks? They're not even possible to redeem. I want like a different
rifle. Maybe I shouldn't have spent all my money on fish. Get the buffet at the Golden Corral.
When I went yesterday with some other beers, I got a pile of fried chicken. But when I went to
go for the smiley face fries, I couldn't find any. Oh, here comes a complaint. I kind of just
try it. It's a cool way to switch. No complaint. That's great. On this game. But I need to charge
Community Isaac mod. I don't have any money. Anti birth. When did I do this? I'm gonna leave
it there for now. Who knows the hell that is? I've been around for so long that I did not play this
game. I did not play this. I didn't play this. Yeah, I used it. It didn't do anything. I've
been doing this shit for fucking almost 10 years. I did not play anti birth on stream. There's no
fucking way that I did. I want to play this right now. Blank card card. I want to play this right
now. Who knows this game? Okay, I'm gonna make a statement here that a lot of people may disagree
with and they might agree with. Here's the statement. Don't be so hard on yourself. You're
not gonna die right here. The Binding of Isaac might be within the top 10 of my favorite games
ever made. I think it might even be it could be top five of like the one of the most fun games
ever played. This is what I'd make that judgment based on how much time I have in a game. I
have put so many hours into this game. I love this game so much. I have like probably hundreds and
hundreds and hundreds maybe even a thousand hours in Binding of Isaac. I was gonna buy a heart but
you only do that with something that you just love and think it's so much fun. That'd be dumb.
Should I like start this again and play this again? I feel like this would be a lot of fun to do and
like not do it for like two hours. I actually played this game for like six to eight hours in
a stream. I just hit him with a tomato. He should have been vulnerable. It's career suicide. Why?
What? It's Binding of Isaac. Everybody loves Binding of Isaac. Skip. Skip. Stream in the corner.
How did we get this again? Am I playing this? Okay. Vampyr. Game sucks. Sounds pretty good.
And lastly, spooky things. All right. Now, uh, Jerma, as this is your show, would you like to
kick us off here? I'm gonna go first. You do? All right. Well, I think I'll take 17th century
poetry for 50, please. All right. Let's uh, let's see what we got here. Extend. John Calvin crafted
this Christian ideology ideology stressing God's power. I'm not gonna watch this whole thing. It's
like three and a half hour, four hour stream. Uh, what is, um, you got anything? Dr. Strange? Uh,
I have no idea. I put face cam on for this. It actually is.
Why don't I have face cam on for Sam and Mac?
Got it. The price of paranoia is eternal vigilance. Whoa. We're not going to do that.
We're not going to do that. That's like a spoiler. No, I don't think it's going to happen again.
This is like the, what the last level. There's no way it's going to happen again. All right. Two more.
I'm going to let, no, three more. And the third one is going to play to zero.
And that's it. And I'll see you tomorrow. One, two, three. No way, right? That's not actually
going to happen. Is it? Now what do I do? Okay. That should be enough for now that I can't believe
this. It was meant to be the Nintendo Labo. Nemo Slack. So this goes underneath in here.
Eight and a half hours. Bye, bye, bye, bye. And then up the hole. Why am I up there? Slide
the end of the spring through the eyelet from underneath. What the fuck are you doing? Oh,
that's right. I remember this. Everyone was talking about like my penis and shit. And I,
I put like a trash bag on my pants because people were talking about like my dick and stuff, right?
Like, I remember this. I've no, I remember this. Yeah. People were like fucking being chat was
like all fucked up tonight. Slots on the ocean. What the fuck? Yeah. I put like a plastic bag diaper
on because people wouldn't shut up about it. I remember this wrong way. What do you mean wrong
way? That's not the wrong way. This is the right way. This was so much fun. Thank you for watching
everybody. This we're going to, we're going to, we'll hang out and do the bits and subs and
everything. But this is very much a very impromptu. This is crazy. I didn't know I was doing this until
this is going to be an actually functioning fishing rod. No, thanks for watching. Thanks for joining
me. See, look at the rubber bands. All right. We're going to let it one more. I'm going to click
it five times in a row hysterical things that happened in this shit. This is like, if you,
if you just joined us, you're going to want to watch, you're going to want to watch it tomorrow.
What the heck? All right. It's time for some QWOP.
So what was my final death count? 25. Oh God. Wait, does it say? No, they've been counting in
the stream. I'm just looking over and glancing over and seeing. All right. Thanks a lot for playing
guys. If you played, I'll probably do this again. This was actually pretty damn fun. So thanks for
coming. If you joined into the game, into the session. So now we're going to play some QWOP.
And yeah, thanks so much guys. We're going to play. Oh, that was a shot in the face.
Pull up. How do I get out of here? All right. It's going to be a black screen until I get
QWOP loaded. Q W O P. QWOP. QWOP. QWOP. QWOP. QWOP. Hey, yo, I love Liberty City. This is ancient.
This might be one of the oldest things. QWOP is a flash game. It's a flash game where you
have to use QW and then O P to run. And it is incredibly difficult. Is this the first stream?
The screen's probably not going to go black. It's probably going to be just my background.
This has to be one of them. Just my desktop background. I still have that background. All
right. Let me pull up some QWOP. Let me make sure the stream thing is there. And people think I'm
bullshit. Oh man, that was funny. I'm bullshit. That was so damn funny. QWOP. QWOP. QWOP. QWOP.
Dermot, that's a lie. Is it? Why do you think about this? Oh, no, nevermind. I can't do this.
I got to think about this. I tried to queue it up. Good thing we didn't get to see QWOP.
Cuphead. No. Skip. Skip. Skip. Skip. Unrailed. Skip. Demon souls. Part one. Skip. This is
scary pictures. Activity book. Skip. Earth Defense Force. Skip. Dark Souls. Ring City DLC. Skip.
Boost game. Skip. Mind Show. All right. So, you know, when words just come out, but they mean
absolutely nothing. Words were just coming out of my mouth and they meant nothing. It was just
word swoop. It didn't mean anything. It wasn't going anywhere. It was just, it was a run on sentence.
That's the penis music thing. That's the penis music gift. Hold on. What are you talking about?
Isn't it? What? Hold on. Ready? Like, holy shit. It actually is. That's not synced.
Somebody linked up. What a great thing to end on. Game audio. That shouldn't be a thing.
Video has desync. All right. But how about how much? All right. I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Technical difficulties. All right. Thanks for watching, everybody. Seriously.
It was a wild night. Is Vinnie streaming right now? Because I did say that was going to happen
because it was part of... Okay. All right. We're going to raid Vinnie because it was part of the...
I did say it in one of the clips, so that's what we have to do. Anyways, let's go back.
Too early. Thanks for watching. Join us tomorrow. Ooh. Ow. I was a little too close. I got to back
up. Oh, fuck my hand. God damn it. I got to get a new mic set up. It's fucking freaking me out.
Okay. So let's, let's go back to earlier today. If you join us for community content night,
we've got two... We're just hanging out streams in a row. Community content night is people,
artwork, and videos that people have made based around stuff on the streams and community and
everything. So it's a good time. I will see you tomorrow. If you're taking off, if you're sticking
around for a little bit, we'll go over some of these things. I do the bits and the subs and
everything at the end of a stream. If you are a new viewer. And right now we're going to talk about
it. Uh, Freddy Dread, $500. Five fucking hundred dollars. That was within 10 minutes of the stream
starting, which is insane. Thank you, Freddy, for your five hundred fucking bucks and a hundred
community subs right after that, which is insane. Mitchell, thanks for the thousand bits. I wish I
had a hundred dollars to give you tonight, partially because you're a huge inspiration,
an awesome content creator, but also for that amazing Mario Kart rant in the first Sunshine
VOD. I would pay money to listen to you instead of just sitting in a room ripping bad games,
a new asshole. No, but here comes a new podcast. No, this is, this is a podcast. It's everything.
You know what I mean? It could be whatever the fuck we want. Sometimes the stream just stops
and for 20 straight minutes, we just talk about random shit. So I don't need to do a podcast
because this stream is such an erratic fucking mess that it just happens sometimes anyway.
But thank you for the 10 bucks. Goobery Juice, thanks for 250. Jerma Grin, thanks a lot.
Peaceful Haley, 250. Jeremy, I rated you at the beginning of the stream with 13 viewers and now
I feel stupid. And I mean, it's literally just your viewers anyway. Never again. That's all right.
Don't worry. Hey, 13. That's still people. That's still a lot of people. 10 people is a lot of
people. 100 people is a lot of people. Thousand people is a lot of people. That's fine. Don't
worry. Don't worry about that. Thanks for doing that. Hey, but more importantly, they were watching
you, not me. So give yourself a little bit of credit, right? And Anonymous Cheerer, thanks for
the thousand bits. No message, just a thousand bits. Foxy Grandpa, thanks for the five dollars.
No message. Back to back, no message, but just lots of money. Edmund Hakari, thanks for the five
dollars. Watching you melt the lines of old Jerma while pretending it was you was way funnier than
it should have been. And I thought it would be. 10 out of 10 meta stream. Hey, Icarus Gamers,
thanks for the 250. Hey, Jerma, I had a weird dream with you in it last night. More dreams.
You were in a play that was like Clue, where it was a murder mystery, but there was a different
murderer every time. But it was also competitive. So the actors were competing to get to be the
murderer. I was hanging out with you backstage and you're about to go to be the murderer,
but someone else did it first and you got wicked mad, like absolutely seething anger that you got
kill stole. It was really funny. Add it to the list of Jerma is a psychopath in your dreams.
Hey, Yenwen, thanks a lot for the 250. They say, hey, Jerma, do you know it's been over a year since
I sent you my first piece of artwork? Long time. It's pretty crazy when I think back on it,
especially since that drawing was never intentional. It was a random sketch that
turned into a fully fledged painting. During the past year, I resigned from being a bartender and
had begun training as a teacher. I'm really busy and need to go to bed early, so I haven't been
able to catch many streams nor draw anything serious. Thanks for joining the stream today,
as well as everyone from the pre-stream chat. It was a lot of fun. Here is the finished image
that I was working on. Let's put it on screen. If you don't know, Yenwen is an insanely talented
artist. Some of the most ridiculous paintings we've ever seen have come from Yenwen. I know
people probably have links of some of the insane shit. How do I save this? Am I this dumb? I don't
know how to save a photo. Oh, there we go. That was not it. Oh, yes, it was. Yes, it was. It's just
very high resolution. I was like, wait, it's gray. There we go. Why does Jax have to be so much bigger
than me? We're the same size. One of them's just smarter in video game knowledge. Thanks a lot,
Yenwen. This is good shit, as always. This is a big brother reveal. Thank you. It means a lot.
More great artwork from Yenwen. Goiki gave $50, 5000 bits. We did it, boys. This has me crying.
Thank you, Goiki. I'm not sure exactly what you were referring to, but I missed your $50,
and I want to make sure that I did touch upon it. So thank you. Hey, Razlik. Thanks, Razlik,
for the $5. Dermot, I've been rather ill for the past two months. Watching your streams and videos
helps me out so much on them sleepless nights. Thank you and much love to you in this community.
Such a wonderful place. Also, it's my wonderful Scottish friend's birthday today.
DK. If you could wish him a happy birthday, it'd be awesome. Hey, DK, have a fucking fantastic
birthday. Happy birthday, DK. Thanks a lot, Razlik. Pifflavor, thanks for the thousand bits. $10.
Not going to lie, these streams recently have been very epic, in my opinion. Thanks for that.
I've laughed this much in a while. Also, even though you have so many games on the list,
play Dead Space. Probably this Halloween. This October, I'll probably do at least one or two of
the Dead Spaces in a row. That's a Halloween stream. You know what I mean? That's a Halloween
time stream. Hey, Gnarly, thanks for the $2.50. This stream reminds me of the part in...
There's a spoiler for a movie. I'm not going to read it because I've got spoilers for a movie,
and I haven't seen that movie, so I'm not going to read it. Thanks, Gnarly, for the $2.50.
And then we had 500 community subs from MrGerma985, so thanks, whoever you are.
Thanks a lot, Germa. What a guy. When the stream is over, I'm going to have to go into my PayPal
account and turn off and check the fraud department and make sure they know that this is real.
I can do that right away. But in the middle of that, Goiki gave 20, Austin Atlantis gave 100,
Abe Cashim gave 100. So there were 200 community fucking subs that were added to that,
besides my little bet bingo with you guys. So thanks to Austin and to Abe for giving 200
fucking subs. That's a shitload, and you never expected to give that much money. He's going to
charge them back. No, I'm not. AveryDropDead gave five. Thank you. RobbieRevolver gave
a thousand bits. $10. Germa, thank you to you and your team for putting this event together.
It was fun, and this is why we love you. Looking forward to more creative events in the future.
This was just lazy Luke just threw this together and not even day. We were jokingly talking about
this fucking two days ago, and it was just like, oh, hey, by the way, you can just use it now and
it works flawlessly. By the way, flawlessly. It was not a single problem. Not a single hiccup.
It's not like, oh, it crashed. We reloaded. Shit worked fucking flawlessly. Everybody thank Lazy
Luke for throwing together just a goofy idea that we had in this pre-stream chat two days ago
and made it reality. That's what you should be thanking. But thank you Captain Nemo for the 300
bits. Germa, you should see if you can leave the random bot running when stream is offline so the
chat and stream can just be bopping constantly. Even if you aren't around. Well, you guys can
just use it. It's available at Germa.org slash random. You can just play with it right now.
That's not an exclusive thing to me. It just pulls data from YouTube and Twitch and everything. So
you can just play with it if you want. It's a really neat little tool. We are going to put
the subs on stream and it's going to be very, very, very, very ridiculous. This is going to
be very fast because I mean, I, I stacked the deck a little bit with 500, but there was still,
no, we're not doing mind show. That was the wrong, sorry, wrong scene. Sorry about that.
We're going this way. Although I may have stacked the deck, it still doesn't matter.
It was fucking hundreds and hundreds of community subs from other, other people like Freddy Dread,
Abe. There was a thousand fucking subs tonight. So let me get the credits rolling. This is going to
blow by pretty quickly. Let's see just how fast this goes. I wonder if you're able to even read
one name in three, two, one, roll them. Oh boy. Nope. Don't think so. Thanks guys. That's a lot
of people. That's probably more than a thousand today. Jesus. We also had blueberry juice 250.
Please set it to change every one second. Please. I'm not sure that it could even handle one second
changes. What's the sub count now? Uh, let's see, let's after tonight, let's see what it is.
The current sub count right now after today's insanity is 8,500 subs, 85, 81 to be exact after
today. So take away my 500, which we're just, you know, if you want to talk about stacking the deck,
so over 8,000, which is fucking crazy and still no new emotes. I know I'm fucking terrible, but
anyways, uh, it's still about four or five bits left to do. Uh, we have thick neck. Baby gave
1500 bits, 15 bucks, no message, just a bunch of money that they just slapped onto the stream.
Thank you. Uh, did we get Mr. Dask? Mr. Dask gave $10,000 bits to no message either. Thank you. Mr.
Dask Avery drop dead. $5 got home from work early and was able to catch all this amazing stream.
Thanks to him of being the best guy on Twitch. You're awesome. I'm glad you think that way.
Thank you. Thanks for saying that. I, that's all I can say. Shout out to the stream archive people.
That's correct. If the stream archive was not saving and uploading every single VOD ever,
this also doesn't happen. So huge shout out to the stream archive guys. I'm talking about hundreds
and hundreds, like 700 fucking uploads, 750 uploads. So thank them too. Uh, Violet Wanderer
$5. I've got like 700 hours in Binding of Isaac Rebirth. It's one of my favorites too. When is,
um, what's the new one coming out? Like Redemption or something? It hasn't been a new,
aren't they taking the anti-birth mod and making it a thing? They're officially putting it in the
game. What's it called? Like Repentance or something? Yeah, they're adding a final expansion. Repentance.
Well, when that comes, maybe when that comes out, I'll get back into Binding of Isaac on stream.
That sounds like a good time to start getting back into it. That sounds like a plan.
Thank you for the $5. Uh, Pink Karoo, thanks for the $5. Presto Extendo. Thank you.
Roguy, thanks for the $3. Bro, I finally saved up enough channel points to do a wink on Friday,
but I didn't do it because you already had face cam on. Now you disable wink. Please accept this
as entry into the Wink Club. Well, it's funny you bring that up because tomorrow,
on the stream tomorrow, Winks come back at an insanely discounted price. So you'll have a
chance to do it tomorrow. What's the price? We'll see. We'll see tomorrow. And then finally Rad,
Radshly, thanks for the $3. Free dolls. I'm going to be starting my new job next week,
so I won't be able to catch streams as often. Thank you for all the laughs these past few months.
Thanks for watching the past few months. Eh, community doesn't exist. Community doesn't exist,
but I love the people in the fucking community. So thanks for participating. This whole thing is
impossible without all of you. So thanks for watching. See you tomorrow for Community
Content Night. Take care. We are going to raid Vinny because obviously I said it earlier,
so you know, it's part of the deal. Go tell Vinny what's going to say something. See you guys
tomorrow. Take care. Good night. Thanks for experimenting in this experimental stream,
and we'll see you tomorrow. Good night, guys. See you soon.