Viewers dropping. Is that someone who just wrote it in all capitals?
No, I think they're only going up from here. Oh shit, man. Viewers dropping.
That's so funny. Hey, how you doing, guys? I'm doing pretty good. I'm just hanging out with my...
a little bit of a messed up throat, but who cares? We got Chibi-Robo to play.
It's hard to say this. Chibi-Robo. I'm going to be playing this fun game called Chibi-Robo.
This was an expensive game. Looks pretty cool. The GameCube discs. I remember them.
They're very, very cool. These are a collector's item at this point. It's not in the...
Yeah, I'm playing it on a Wii. I know. Get over it. Not the original GameCube. That's fine.
But yeah, I've heard a lot of good things. I want to play Chibi-Robo. I'm into it.
I heard it's a game where you clean, you prepare food, and you use a dustpan and stuff.
I'm going to love this game. How am I not going to like this?
But let me tweet this out, and we'll start in about two minutes.
Alright, are you guys ready? I haven't done it yet. I'm not going to until we're ready.
The best part of the Wii is the fact that you can insert a GameCube disc at the top of the tray
or at the bottom of the tray, and it still figures out where it is.
Now that's some real technology. Alright, let's go.
Are you ready? It's going in. Should I show the disc first? Yeah, this is a big moment for us.
We're not getting married. But still, this is a big moment. First GameCube game.
Why should it not work? Ready? Look at this. Chibi-Robo.
Going in. No brace? No, not today. I'm trying to... I've got to relax it a little bit.
I've been wearing it too much. Here it goes. Another reason why I wanted to wait,
because it's going to do the sound, right? Here it comes. Here it comes.
Okay, hold on. We've got to test something real quick.
Because this is a GameCube, so who knows if it's even going to work.
Are you going to tell me? Am I synced up? Is the sound synced up?
Start. We. Start. We. Start. We. Start. Get. Get. Get. Are we good?
Just got to make sure. No. The voice is hard to tell. Alright, are you ready?
I'm going to do a circle. Circle. One, two, beep. It's good. No? It's fine.
He's completely naked. Alright, let's go. Chibi-Robo time. I'm ready.
I'm ready. I've been looking forward to this for like a year at least.
What's going on? Oh, do you want to display the game in progressive scan mode?
Oh, fuck yeah. Are you serious? That's HD of 2004.
Warning. Important health. Before playing, read the health and safety book.
They did this for Chibi-Robo for the GameCube? Why? Do you have to move around?
I already got cartoon clown sounds. Chibi-Robo. Oh, wow.
Alright, the screen might be a little... I might fix it a little off.
Looks alright. Can we adjust it? Why do I know what you're talking about?
This is...
Why do I know... I only have one...
Hold on, it's a little loud for me.
Why... I only have like one... I only have one barometer for what penis music is.
There's that one song. So of course I'm going to think that's what this is.
There it is!
Okay, I gotta turn it down. It's really loud.
Okay, that's at a decent volume. Actual wink.
Good, get them out because they're going away forever in like three days.
Turn off.
Wait, you need a memory card for the Wii?
I'm just fucking kidding.
Oh, wait, what about slot B?
It's in slot B! Why does it have to be in slot A?
Corrupted. What? Let's go.
Format. What are you talking about?
What do you mean the memory card is corrupted? It's been formatted.
The memory card slot A is corrupted.
What do you mean it's corrupted? Is this alright?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Hold on, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, no, no, no. Just give me a second.
Why is the memory card corrupted?
Is this like fucking... is this lying to me?
Hold on. My Wii just went...
Ah! Ah!
What the fuck is... I swear to God, there's a ghost that haunts me.
There's no way. There's no way.
I get haunted by a fucking ghost when I turn my stream on.
You guys understand how stupid this is? How insane this is.
I tested this before the stream turned on.
I literally did this like 35 seconds before the stream started.
I'm haunted by a ghost. There's a ghost that's trying to kill me.
The memory card slot A must be formatted. Format it now.
Yes. If the memory card is formatted, all saved data will be erased.
Fucking do it!
Okay. Okay. Nintendo GameCube slots open.
20 out of 43.
From 2043.
Okay. Are we good? Is it okay?
Can I fucking play the game?
Okay. Let's go.
I have 2043 blocks of data.
Hey! Remember that sound?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Apologize. Apologize. Apologize.
That sounded slightly like the thing that I don't like.
It is an animated character. I don't like them.
Okay. Can I... This is gonna be fine, right?
Put in health and safety instructions.
Licensed by Nintendo. Bandai.
This is before they became Bandai Namco.
Alright.
It's been formatted.
What do I do? What do I do?
Choose yes.
The memory card slot A has been formatted.
The memory card slot A is corrupted.
I just did that because I had to.
Say yes. Say yes.
Just keep saying yes over and over again.
Blow on the memory card!
Blow on the memory card?
What? This is so sad.
I just... Why is...
512? What's wrong with that?
Alright. I pushed it in there like fucking hard.
Am I in slot B?
I can't do slot B because slot B...
I'm...
I can't do slot B because it doesn't let me choose slot B.
My form has slot A?
Alright. What's it?
Alright. It's in slot B.
Don't continue. Option.
Scream into it.
Alright. Hold on.
So now...
Bro, run to the store and buy a new memory card.
But the GameCube!
You want me to run to the store and get a
memory card for a console
that has been out of circulation for like
17 years!
You want me to run to the
store!
I'm going to...
I just want to play a game!
Wait a minute. Just don't say...
No! That's horrible!
I'll get it. No, I'm emulated!
This game was like a hundred
fucking dollars on eBay!
No! No, we're not emulating!
I have it! What a fucking
introduction!
Look at this! Oh! I can't wait to...
What can I say? Look!
Oh yeah! The GameCube disc!
Oh, remember? Oh, shh! Quiet!
Fucking joke.
I should have just fucking emulated the goddamn thing.
I should have just emulated literally everything.
Companies wonder why the fuck people do this shit.
I wonder why consumers
are downloading fake GameCube
game cards and ISOs.
No! It can't be!
It can't be because the shit don't work
when you're trying to use it for real!
What?!
It's right here! GameCube
slot A, slot B, it's right
fucking here! This shit works!
What? Oh!
I can't put it in slot A. Maybe the slot A
is corrupted? I don't... I had it in
slot A, we got to see the same image
in slot A. I don't...
You know what? I'm not
gonna turn the fucking stream off until I'm done with the game.
Let's go. I'm not spending
15 straight minutes on this nonsense.
I gotta remember to card in slot B.
I should be able to choose... God damn it.
Let's have a board meeting about what the
hell do people...
Correct me if I'm wrong, fellow
person...
People are downloading
the video games and they're playing them without our
permission. Is there a reason
why people are doing this without
my permission?
Just like, play this VOD
to that person.
I actually don't know anything. I just
watched. I don't know what that means either.
I've never played a video game, so
it's lost on me.
You just talked over the GameCube
setup. How to fix a corrupted GameCube
memory card. What?
Power off the console, remove the card,
replace it, see if the message comes back, save
any files that aren't corrupted.
Leave the card alone. Place the card
away from anything electronic
for a week.
Hold on.
Hold on. No.
Excuse me.
Look at this.
Are you trying to tell me that this
is a real website?
This is a copypasta of the streamer I
met the streamer at.
Fucking Walgreens.
Leave the card alone. Place the card away from
anything electronic for about a week.
The lack of electromagnetic interference could help
fix the card. Huh?
This can only be done on a GameCube
console. If these steps
don't work, it must be reformatted. It can only be done on
a GameCube console.
Let's go. Fucking TV
robot. I'm ready. There's no card in slot A.
Who cares?
Continue without saving. I'll
find a way. Hey,
chibi-robo. I can pick slot B
when I save the game. I guarantee it.
Happy birthday, Jenny.
Here you go. I got you this hat as a special
present from me.
I see a coin. I see a coin. I see a coin.
That's all I care about.
Don't like it? What's wrong?
Jenny, you're eight now. You can't run
in a frog costume all day. You need a real
hat.
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit.
Oh, Jenny.
Woof, woof.
Ruff, ruff.
Oh, I got a present
for her too. Do you, Tau?
I got a present for her too.
Do you, Tau? Dog has a
present? It's a bow!
Woof.
Wow, good dog. How did you ruff it?
Ribbit, ribbit.
Another 3D movie maker family.
All right, now it's my turn.
You're just going to love
my gift, Jenny.
Yeah, right.
By the way, what an interesting
t-shirt. It just says the three on it.
Don't you want that shirt?
What is that? You know we can't afford
it. Jenny
says she wanted one.
Ribbit. Oh, honey, you're not
fooling anyone. You only wanted one for yourself.
Is this a chibi robo?
The latest and greatest in household
robots?
We'll talk about this later.
What do you think, Jenny?
Do you love it? You love it, right?
Uh, Jenny's not
communicating.
My eyes?
Damn.
Get ready, chibi robo. It's almost
showtime. This is when I get out
and I'm going to be like, look at me!
I'm going to be like, look at me!
They're talking like sims,
but scary.
What do you think? Should I flip the switch?
Let's do it.
The movie's with Azadjara Taylor.
All right, get ready to
Azadjara robo.
Ratchet, ratchet. We got it.
Holy shit, it really is going on.
This is quite an introduction.
I can't wait to get the coin on the counter.
Yay, chibi robo.
Hello, hello.
Hello there.
Ribbit.
Arf.
We're here to make you happy.
I'm Telly and this is chibi robo.
Amazing!
Ribbit.
Woof.
Oh!
Hey, is this a birthday party?
You got that right.
Uh-oh, chibi robo.
It looks like we've come to the party empty-handed.
We need to find a present
for Jenny and fast.
Is this a children's game?
Oh. How about that flower,
chibi robo?
No. No.
Really? Are you sure?
I think it's perfect for Jenny.
No. I don't like,
I don't want to give that present.
Really? Are you sure? I think it's perfect
for Jenny. Oh, we're getting forced
into saying yes. Okay.
Yes, I do agree with you.
I'll leave the rest to you, chibi robo.
Whoa, the game just got way louder.
I have a big plug on my
back? Uh, chibi robo,
don't get that plug in any
water or any food.
Chibi, don't dunk the end
of the plug into the orange juice.
Alright, let's get it. How do I jump?
What?
They didn't tell me how to move.
So loud.
Jenny!
Alright, let's get it. I got it.
Okay, rose.
That fits in there?
Hot.
That's awesome.
Excellent. Chibi robo,
chibi robo. You should try using
your chibi copter.
It comes standard in all chibi robo models.
All you have to do is equip it.
You can't fly upwards with it, but
listen to this.
You can use it to slowly fall from high
places. That way you won't hurt this fall
damage. Press X to open the
equip screen.
Tilt left or right to select the chibi copter
and then press A to equip it.
It's on my go-go gadget.
Oh, and if you hold down A, you'll hover
horizontally for a short time.
It's handy when you want to fly over small gaps
or drop from high places. Hey,
listen up, chibi robo.
Use the chibi copter, okay?
I don't want you to take a nasty fall.
Alright, you've made it very clear.
Press B to put the copter away.
Okay, so that's it.
This toy sucks.
Imagine getting this on Christmas.
Oh, wow.
That's really cool.
Yes, I was trying to dunk the thing
in the orange juice. Alright, good.
Now what? Hurry up and give that
flower to- oh. Come here.
I got a flower for you.
I think Mrs. Sanderson made
this cake. You can't eat anything
anyway, chibi robo.
Oh. Sorry, I didn't mean to hurt
your feelings. Oh.
If you move next to an object and you see
the exclamation icon, press
A. I just did.
What feelings?
Oh, right. It's a robot.
Do I have to float over there?
Coin behind turkey? Oh, shit.
Got it.
What about the turkey? Looks like
chicken is on the menu tonight.
Chicken. That's a word that brings back some
really bad memories from me.
Oh, but maybe now isn't the time to talk about
that. What? Alright, we gotta float
over there. Take out the helicopter.
Let's go. Here we go. Float onto
the cake. On cake.
Here we go. Give rose.
I think Mrs.
can't eat anything anyway. How do I give the rose?
Do I have to equip it?
Wait. Frog ring?
I'm looking through my eyes.
Alright, how do I give you the-
I already did that.
Was I not close? Alright.
I tried to do that before. I guess I wasn't close enough.
Chibi Robo, give the rose to Jenny.
Yes.
Here you go.
This game is cute. It looks very cute.
You got 20 happy
points. Are they sad
points? And you got 120-
I don't know. What is that?
What kind of currency is that?
Spread the happiness.
Earn happy points in
Moolah by making people happy.
Of course, earning lots of happy points
will raise your Chibi Robo ranking.
Let's do our best to get you into
first place. Are there
items in the house?
Now for Jenny to blow out the candles. Do I have to compete
with the vacuum cleaner? And the
Lysol? Or what?
One. Two.
Yeah. Although I can't-
I really can't agree with their use of
candles on the cake. Blow it out on the cake.
That's disgusting. Now nobody wants to eat the cake because
the little kids spit all over the cake.
And what I'd like
to see is
a separate cupcake that has
a candle on it. You blow
the two or three candles on one little cupcake.
They blow them all over
the cupcake. Okay, cool. Now the cake is fine. Everyone can
eat it. Go to work, Chibi Robo.
You looked a bit
nervous at first, but you came through like a pro.
Put plastic over the cake?
Why would you-
Now listen, we need to make ourselves useful
to the Sandersons, right?
Okay.
Let's adjust your happy point total.
But it gets adjusted?
Your Chibi
ranking has gone from
1 million to
782 thousand. Why did I lose
happy points?
Oh, I'm gaining, right.
I'm gaining rank.
Get out there and earn a ton of happy points and
grab yourself the top Chibi ranking.
When you reach top
Chibi ranking, why
you'll be upgraded
to Super Chibi Robo.
Take it from me, TeleVision.
Ah, that's a good name. I'll do what I can
to lend you a hand. You can count on me.
TeleVision.
Professor E. Gadd.
Yes, I would love to save the game.
I would love to. And I'd like to do it in slot
B. Fuck.
Let's go.
I can't pick the slot.
Really, I can't.
Oh, this is so cool and cute.
Hold on. Can I not?
Yes, I want to save.
God damn it.
This is an ungrounded outlet.
I would like to save.
God damn it.
Okay.
I don't know what to do.
I know what I have to do,
which is unfortunate. I have to either beat the whole game in one
stream,
or I have to leave the fucking
Wii turned on and on overnight.
This is literally a two stream game.
God damn it.
Amazon one day
shipping.
Can I do Amazon same day?
Oh.
Please. Please.
No.
God damn it.
This is bad.
The game is upwards of like 14 hours.
How long is the game?
Blow into the port. 12 to 15 hours?
About 12 hours?
12 to 20 hours?
Okay.
It takes 15 hours to beat this game on a speedrun.
I don't believe that. I'm going to blow in the port.
We're going to try everything.
Make sure it's got good contact with the receptacles.
Good contact.
Good. I just like got it in there.
Let's try it again.
Just pretend you're not streaming
to the ghost leaves.
You just spit all over the cake. It's going to be alright.
I know. I know.
But happy points. Fuck.
Save the game. Come on. Right here.
Let's go. I just got good contact.
I had this problem before.
You literally have to smack it against something hard.
Like with a fucking hammer?
I need to hit my
GameCube memory card
with a hammer. Is that what you're telling me to do?
Hit it with a fucking hammer.
Are you serious? No.
That's not. It's true.
Shake it?
This is not doing anything.
Like go shake it.
Smack it around.
Save the game.
Yes, I would. Yes.
Leave the free turned on. That's so bad.
It looks good. Oh, I'm so fucking sad.
Leave the free turned on.
One last thing.
I'm going to try one last fucking thing.
I'm going to close it into the door.
He's going to get a hammer. MonkaS.
No, I'm not going to get a fucking hammer. I'm not stupid.
I'm not going to go get a fucking hammer.
What I'm going to do is I'm just going to close it into the closet.
Look.
I'm not naked. Don't worry.
I do have my nails already long so I can relax.
I don't want you to see the secret stash of GameCube games though.
Whatever.
Stay right there.
See in here?
See that?
It's in there right now. It's literally inside of here.
It's right there.
Can you see the GameCube?
Memory card?
Not harder. That's a bad idea.
Here we go. It's in.
It's not going to fucking do anything.
It's not going to work.
It's not going to happen.
This thing is fucked up.
I'm going to Amazon same day a fucking memory card.
What time is it?
Just turn off the Wii completely and unplug it.
What?
I already did that. I can't.
Turn the Wii off.
No. I guess we didn't do that much.
Should I try turning the Wii off?
Alright. You ready? Okay. Here we go.
Turn the Wii off?
No. Yes. No. Just neutralize.
What? Turn it upside down.
No. Yes. Make him go to GameStop.
No. You can't buy these anywhere.
It's alright.
I'm going to do one more fucking thing.
If this doesn't work, then fuck it.
I'm going to have to just play.
You have to restart the game.
You have to turn it off.
Hold on.
It was just a dumb tutorial.
We can wait. Buy a new one.
It's right here. Hold on.
I'm going to format the card in the Wii menu.
Turn the console off. Turn it back on.
Alright. That's the plan.
Right? Is that the way that I need to try?
It's not going to work?
No. Reset your Wi-Fi.
Reformat the card.
Hold on. Stop talking.
Nobody talk.
Stop talking.
Restart the console and a little warning should come up at the start.
The last thing the card needs to be formatted.
Reformat the card.
The card must be reformatted. This can only be done in a GameCube console.
All the data in the card must be deleted.
Restart the console and a little warning should come up.
This is the Wii.
Yes.
This reformatted card will work again
with both the GameCube and the Wii.
I need a GameCube to do this.
I already did this.
I'm just going to leave the fucking Wii on.
Guys, there's definitely no such thing as an Amazon
same day delivery for a GameCube
memory card.
I'm going to leave the fucking Wii turned on?
Same hour delivery.
What happens if I lose without a save file?
Leave the stream on too.
Alright. Well, I don't think so.
This is not a game where you like lose and die
and go to game over. I don't think so.
Call GameStop?
Guys, they're closing GameStops everywhere.
No one's going in them.
It just needs to be an SD card. How's that going to fit
in the top slot?
Oh, Mr. Sanderson. Tsk, tsk, tsk.
He had a little too much fun at the party.
I think he passed out from excitement.
It goes in the front slot. Yeah, for the Wii
you need a GameCube memory card to be able to save
GameCube games. The Wii is just
a GameCube. It's like the same hardware.
They just made it a little faster. Look, I've done
my research. Don't worry. It is. No, it isn't.
It is. And people that don't know that, the Wii
is just a GameCube with a new shell
that they made a little bit faster.
That's the truth. Go look it up right now. I want you to
look it up so you go, oh fuck, he was right. Holy shit.
SD cards work?
No, they don't. No, they don't because it's not going
to read that in slot A or B for
the GameCube. Trust me, I did my research.
Here's what's going to happen, okay?
I'm going to Amazon next
day for tomorrow, a new memory card.
The Wii is going to stay on.
Tomorrow morning when, you know,
here's the new memory card, I'm going
to put it in and save the game.
You'll see a sun symbol during the
day and the moon symbol at night.
The moon is out right now, so that means it's night
time. What if that card is corrupted,
dude? If that doesn't work
then I'm just going to play it.
It'll be on still.
And plus, I'm going to just fucking beat the game tonight.
Oh my god, I'm cleaning
up. Proper trash.
Always put refuse in a
proper receptacle.
Holy shit, I get to clean up?
Wow, unbelievable.
What's over here? This is trash.
Candy wrapper. Always put
refuse in a proper receptacle.
We get to pick up
trash. Oh, I love this game.
I'm so glad I can save it
with my fucking memory card that doesn't work.
Make sure to save your progress.
Yeah, it's called
leave the Wii turned on until I can
somehow get a memory card here
overnight. Coins?
When was the last time you saved?
Good question.
Well, that's why it doesn't make any sense because when I
reformatted on the Wii menu
it's like, oh, here you go.
2,043 blocks. And then I
turn this on and it's like, this thing's fucked up.
I can't use this.
I'm going to get whatever this is. Can I pull
this out? Oh, there we go.
Is it Amazon, I think?
Hold on, wait, wait.
Impatible for Wii GameCube.
I already, this is one of the, I bought one
of these. Free
one day
delivery. Alright, everyone, hold on.
Nobody move.
Free one day delivery.
He wants to put a two year protection
plan.
Sure.
I'll take a two year protection.
Should have bought the two year protection plan.
I'm losing power. Oh, shit, I am.
Hold on, pause again. Fuckin' joke.
Alright, let me, let me see.
Hold on, I'm buying something.
Hold on, I'm purchasing something. Give me
a sec. Tomorrow.
One day delivery.
Nah, this, yeah, I mean, but I, what
am I going to do? I have to get one for tomorrow.
Alright, fuck it.
Okay. Tomorrow night.
Beat it in one play through.
We have to, actually, we have to
test something. We have to test to see
if I like jump off a cliff and die.
Alright, what happens? I got a frog card.
We explodes.
It loads the last
save. We need to test it because
if that's the case, then I, I have to
like do something else today.
Does that hurt? You're playing hardcore
mode. You get sent back to
the chibi house. Don't worry. Okay. Alright.
Cookie crumbs.
So that actually is my power. So I have to plug
in. Why, why does every step have to
be another note? Get the
get the Jerma branded memory card.
Why the fuck is this? This is stupid.
You got two thousand forty
three blocks open. Okay, cool.
Just kidding. The whole thing is corrupted. You can't use it.
Goodbye.
It's a red bubble
memory card. Glad he had
a good time. Oh.
Walking around drains your battery.
Keep an eye on your energy.
If your battery starts to run out, plug into an outlet
and recharge. Oh, that's cool. What is
this thing? Is it combat?
Dear diary, tonight I'm in my usual
spot and the living room body
in the kitchen.
Pound neglected me again. Typical.
He usually drops me right over there.
But tonight he was lazy and now
I and now I can watch Drake
while he patrols. Oh, it's so
hard to watch him that knight in shiny armor.
Oh, Drake.
I'm sorry. I didn't see you. Perhaps you are
on love patrol.
Oh,
oh, those pupils.
Are you looking at my diary?
Stop it. Oh, what a cad.
Oh, who are you?
Hey, now what's all the racket?
Oh, what in the? That toy is talking.
That's just how things work in this house.
Isn't that how it works everywhere?
Really? Well, that's a bit of a shocker.
So I take it there are other toys.
How rude of me. My name is Television
and this is Chibi Robo.
My name is Sophie.
Well, we're pleased as punch to meet you.
I was just writing in my diary and I thought
you were trying to peek. You scared me.
No worries. Happens all the time. Chibi
Robo small, so it's easy for him to sneak up
on you. Please allow me to apologize
on his behalf. We're both sorry we startled
you. Well, as long as you didn't
read about my secret passionate love for
Drake Redcrest, it's fine.
Hey, why doesn't Chibi Robo apologize
himself? Oh, man.
Apologizing is a vital
component of the manager's work.
You're his manager? Seriously?
Oh, that's kind of weird.
Hold on. I need to record this moment so I don't
forget. I'm being mocked
right now. If I was in the diary, this
could be a while. I guess I'll be leaving.
Can I pick anything? What else can I do?
Anything else with you? Manager.
I've never heard the word in real life
before, but it sounds very important.
Chibi Robo and Tele seem very
close. It's nice to see good
friends like that. Also, Drake is
patrolling the area again. I love the way
his big boots clump around. It's so manly.
If Drake does his pose right
in front of me, I think I'll have to run away.
I'd be so embarrassed.
What the fuck is going on?
Are you trying to peek at my diary again?
God, you're a big creepo,
Chibi Robo.
More trash. Let's get it. Why, this is something
already plugged in. Can I unplug this?
Or I can climb it. I can climb up
that cord. What is that? Record player.
Should I jump off and die?
To make sure? What do you think?
Let's turn this on first.
It's a little box? What's in the box?
Wait, you can pull. Should I not have done that?
Why is it playing, like, drunk
music?
I want to pick this up.
Can I move this?
Waste time, though. Saving is only used when
loading from the main menu. You're fine if you never
close the game.
What does that mean? S?
S.
Chibi Robo?
Way to go. I think we can call it a day. I'm proud of the work
we've done. Well, the night has ended.
Let's return to the Chibi house.
Good morning.
Your Chibi ranking is still 782,000.
In order to get the next
bonus battery, you need 60 more happy points.
Get out there and earn more happy
so that you have to be in bed
during the day. Let's go.
Well, stop doing that. You're making
trash.
Would you like to save? Yeah, I would.
Wii options, data management, save data,
Nintendo GameCube. I already did
that. We saw that
it was actually working. And there
were blocks open. I've done that twice.
He's not going to work.
Let's get out here.
Living room. Let's go.
Alright, we're going to make happy points.
What's under here?
Oh, coins. I gotta climb that.
Get the trash. I thought that was
a Pepe face for a second. I was like, what the fuck?
Alright, let's go up.
Oh, I have a helicopter, don't I?
Okay, let's get that out.
Nice. Alright, put it away.
I'll just clean up after Dad?
Wink?
Alright, I gotta clean up after Dad's mess.
Alright, good.
Just go get a lot of happy points, okay?
Hell, I'm trying to
pick up the trash.
Take this cheese crumb.
Save their marriage.
Alright, we're doing a trash run
first, that's important. Candy bag.
Yep, into the trash.
Go marry his
wife. That's not how
that works.
Alright, what about
over here? Can I fly that far?
Clean up the couch
though, that's alright. Keep your batteries
running low. Oh, fuck.
Your body flashes red. Plug into an outlet, quick.
Where's the outlets in this god damn
house? I need an outlet
right now. Where are your outlets?
Where the fuck is any of your stuff
plugged in? There we go.
Is this a fake outlet?
Ugh.
You have 80% iPhone battery.
Alright, let's go.
More coins. Are those happy coins?
Or are they regular coins? Alright, I want to do
uh, what do I want to do?
Here's my house. Alright, can I get like a bird's
eye view? I guess I can look. Wait, wait, there's
trash under there. Where's the trash can?
Move
faster with the plug.
I give it the trash. It's you?
What? No, it's not.
It says put it in the proper
receptacle. Wait, am I the
trash? Am I the trash
can? No, there's a trash can over
here, right? No, I'm definitely not
the trash. There's trash right
here, right? That's trash can.
Lob it in with A. What?
Oh, nice.
That's right, you can also get happy points by
throwing garbage away. Look at
all the trash I have. I picked up
a ton of stuff. Look at all the cheese I
got. You got a total of 31
happy points. You got
310 bucks. Nice.
All right, it's almost time to go to bed. Let's get some more
trash. This is a janitor game?
It's my favorite kind of game. You can
use an SD card? How
difficult is it to use? I have an SD card
somewhere in this house.
How difficult is that to do?
Is that like hard to set that
up? No, you can't.
Why am I being lied to?
I can't throw it from here? Wow.
It has to be modded.
That's
way out of my
jurisdiction.
What about the girl?
Just jailbreak your console.
I feel like that's a day project.
You don't have to be like an all day project.
I'm going to jailbreak my Wii today.
It takes 20 minutes for
you. Plus, how am I ever going to
send it back for an official Nintendo
warranty inspection, guys?
Ribbit ribbit.
Can I do anything with this?
Should I get the frog coins?
Speaking of coins. All right, it's almost time for bed.
I got money this time.
I'm leaving her hanging. Ribbit ribbit.
She just goes
and just eats you.
I can draw ribbit.
Jenny just gave you 13 happy
points. Spread the happiness.
Drop it.
What are you going to draw?
Can I help? All right.
I got to get up here.
I got to climb on top of the coffee table.
13 happy points. It's nothing.
Look at all the shit that's up there. I want to get up here.
How much time do I have?
Am I going to PAX? I'm not
going to PAX. I will not
be at PAX. Uh oh. Time's up.
Get the trash quick.
Aww.
Chibi Robo. Time sure flies when you're
making folks happy.
Well, the day has ended. Let's return to the Chibi house.
Okay.
Great work out there.
Let's adjust your happy point total.
Your Chibi
ranking has gone from
7 to 82. That was a huge
increase. Good job, Chibi
Robo. You passed almost half
a million inactive accounts.
Great. In order to get the next bonus
battery, you need 13 more happy points.
If you ever reach the top of the rankings, you get to
become super Chibi Robo.
Super Chibi Frog.
Well, maybe I'm speaking too soon, but you'll be upgraded to the
super luxurious super Chibi
Frog Robo, or that's what I've heard.
Girlbots won't be able to leave you alone.
While you're here, Chibi Robo,
you like to save.
Maybe one time it'll work.
You know what I mean? What if it just works one of these times?
It might just work. I have an idea.
Format it. Erase all, save, and
format the data. Okay?
Memory card's been formatted. Now what if I pull it out?
Maybe if I pull it out?
Right?
Let me try this. Cause it's, oh, it's been formatted.
Now I'm gonna pull the card out.
Okay. Alright.
Now I wonder, does that
sound the Wii? No, it's the game.
Try slot B. I can't
put anything in slot B. The game doesn't recognize
slot B. You can't save to slot B
for some reason.
And this guide says all you have to do...
Wait, what? This guide says all you have to do is
download two things.
Why can't I scroll up anymore?
Download two things, Monka-esque.
No, it'll be alright.
I'll, I'll, I'll
figure it out. I'm just gonna have to just
leave it on until tomorrow and then put the
new card in.
Or, so after
when the stream is over, I might
go figure out how to get
that saved tonight before I
go to bed. You know what I'm saying? Like I'm gonna make sure
this is saved before I go to sleep.
Just please, for the love of God,
do not turn off, like,
the power. I, okay,
I hope the bill's been paid. It has.
But one of the, I'm freaking
up. Can I play a video game?
Welcome to the Chibi PC.
Recycletron.
Living room ladder?
Collect scrap to build utility bots.
Okay, how much scrap do I have?
A ladder that reaches
high places placed near the Chibi
Robo house. Build it.
I don't have any, oh, I don't have any scraps.
Online shop.
Timer 10, timer 15.
Pink flower seeds,
Chibi blaster. Oh, this is
cool. Alright, I don't have any money.
I don't have any points.
There are game over screens.
This is a ticking time bump.
There are game over screens that require a load.
You're gonna be very sad.
Uh...
No, don't say this.
Hold on.
Empty SD card, SD card reader for PC.
Download
Banner Bomb 2
from the download link.
Alright, I
can't do this right now.
That's not a virus.
I know, I know. Alright, I gotta
figure out what the fuck I wanna do here.
Um, shit. Okay.
I have an idea. I have an idea.
Let me just check something
real quick. Just play another game.
Yeah, we might have to come back
to this. I don't, I don't wanna
fuck this up. I don't wanna fuck this up.
We might
have to come back to this. I really
wanna play this. We might have to do this like tomorrow.
Ah, I really wanna play this.
Hold on, just a second.
I am very, very
confused because I remember
specifically playing
played Viewtiful Joe
on this system and used
this memory card for like
10 seconds to test the, to see
if it makes sure things worked. And it worked.
It'll still be here, don't spoil
the experience. Yeah, just
emulate it. Alright, that's not
just go download an ISO
of 5 parts of Chibi Robo and
combine them illegally and then use it.
That's gonna take like
half an hour for me to do that.
That's not something I can do right now.
Every place that has emulation
they, it's the download, they
like throttle you download and shit.
Trust me, I know. You download
from all these websites at like 600k
a second. Alright.
Alright, I'm ripping the Band-Aid off. I have to.
The Band-Aid's coming off. I'm gonna
put in Viewtiful Joe. And I'm gonna
see if this, what the fuck is going on here.
I'm ripping the Band-Aid off. I'll play this another day.
I can't, I already love the game.
I don't want to fucking tarnish it. I want to play it for real.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I really, I'm sorry
guys. I, we're gonna change
to something else. Give me one second. Let me just
I'm gonna put in Viewtiful Joe.
Viewtiful Joe is fucking equally as incredible.
And I think it does save to this card. Cause I
used it. Hold on.
I'll be right back. Fuck!