Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight, gonna be playing as the Pyro.
Now, this is not gonna be one straight gameplay in a row. It's gonna be a few clips of the Pyro back to back on various maps,
but just a couple of streaks here and there that I got with the Extinguisher and the Flare Gun.
You guys know the deal, but I'm using the Strange Degreaser, the Flare Gun, like I said, and the Extinguisher.
So the topic of this gameplay is going to be about communities, gameplay communities, or really communities in general,
and how they shape the world of gaming and why they are so important, and especially a game like Team Fortress 2, which is pretty old.
And I've done community videos before talking about, you know, why TF2 is lasting so long or why games are worth playing,
but I want to focus mostly on communities as a whole and why they need to be strengthened from the core to continue on in their legacy of their game franchises,
or just in general, just in the world of gaming. So let me define what I mean by the word community.
I know it has probably a couple of different contexts and a couple of different things, but this is what I see it as.
A community is a group of people that are all collectively in the same area or in the same interest field,
that are all trying to coexist together and strengthen themselves from the inside out to be a better place or a better group of people.
Now, gaming communities in specific here are very, very important to a game's lifespan.
I'm going to bring up Team Fortress 2, because of course we're playing Team Fortress 2.
Team Fortress 2 has lasted this long mainly because of its community.
Valve has done a great job of putting out all these updates and giving us all this free stuff
and giving us all these great things to play with in their games,
but it really is the people playing the reason why it's still going,
because if you don't have people playing the game, you don't have that active demand from the whole group of players,
there's no reason to keep supporting a title. You move on to the next big thing.
And really, this is where we come in. We do things like make mods for games or game mode modifications.
We make content, video content, like you're watching right now.
There's a lot of people that make YouTube videos on gaming content.
And even with something like the Steam Workshop, which adds items and artwork and 3D modeling into the game.
So you've got a lot of things going on with a community that if they were not there, think about this for a second.
If those things that I just mentioned were not there, would something like Team Fortress 2 have died years ago?
And the answer is I'm not sure, because Valve, like I said, has been actively updating this game
and actively putting a lot of developer support into it, that it's hard to tell.
But can you imagine a world where there was no Saxton Hale, there was no crazy mod servers with Prop Hunt or Balloon Race,
or nobody putting Steam Workshop items on the marketplace and having you go click and vote and watch
and see all the cool new things coming through the pipeline, if there were no YouTube videos, if people didn't make gaming?
And this is not just Team Fortress 2 exclusive. I have no idea what would happen.
But what I do know is when we get interested in something, it sparks interest from the developers.
When the developer gets sparked interest from the community, they start to make more stuff.
When they make more stuff, people buy it potentially, or they start playing more, the company makes more money, so on and so forth.
It is a love-love relationship that cannot really be broken.
And unfortunately, I can probably name you a handful of franchises that have really, really bad, bad relationships with their communities.
And you see this clash of heads all the time between developers and the people playing, it can get so out of hand.
People asking for bug fixes that never happen and content patches that are expensive and they don't really add a whole lot.
It's really bad sometimes.
But it is so important to have that backbone of people pushing for something because it allows you to shape the games you love to play.
As a group, as a collective, we have a voice that if it gets ignored in a lot of these cases with the developers not listening,
it causes massive problems because we won't buy the next game that comes out.
We won't pay for the really expensive DLC.
We won't do these things and it hurts the company.
If they don't play ball, play ball.
If they don't play ball, then we have a little bit of power because we won't do the things that they're asking us to do.
And a little earlier I brought up mods and game modifications and stuff like that.
And those are so awesome because it gets to, it lets people, when game companies, let me say this first,
when game companies allow us use of their game code to create new things and new ideas,
it is such an incredible thing for the whole collective.
It is unbelievable.
And I actually have a really big problem with companies that take their game code or take their stance on modifications and game changes and stuff.
And they put it in a box, close it and lock it and throw the key in the backyard.
I have a big problem with that because what you're effectively doing is we brought up having a voice in the community.
You're essentially silencing everybody and not letting anyone have an imagination with your fantastic product.
Because, I mean, a lot of people spend, I understand the argument that these companies put a lot of time in their work.
They don't want their game code to be exploited.
It's an intellectual property and it's copyrighted and sorry, screw you, go deal with it.
But I can name you three franchises right now that started as mods that became major, major wild successes.
Here you go.
League of Legends.
All those MOBA games started in Warcraft 3 as a Warcraft 3 custom map.
You've got something like DayZ.
DayZ is a mod.
And then you've got a little game called Team Fortress 2.
Team Fortress was a Quake mod.
Can you imagine if Quake did not allow mods to their games?
We would not even have Team Fortress 2.
And that's the point I'm going to make.
I'm going to end on that, guys.
And that's going to wrap up the video.
So let me know in the comments section what you think about all this.
And we will go from there.
Community, stay strong, baby.
And I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.