Hey, hey, how are you doing? How are you doing? Good. I'm gonna just make a tweet real quick.
Hey, Vod Watchers. What's up? Hold in ring. All right. Screaming. I'm not gonna scream today. I
need to save my voice because we're going, we're gonna go hard. I can't, I can't blow my voice out
day one out of like two or three in a row, like 10 hours. You know what I mean? We should be collected
today. Tomorrow, we can do whatever we can. I can be as loud as I want, right? Okay, how about
Elden Ring? I'm ready. That sounds good. It kind of makes it sound like I'm just starting the game,
though, doesn't it? Oh, well. Okay. Welcome back. It's been a few days. I definitely wanted to take
a few days. I thought I was only going to need to take two days, but I got up on the third day
and was like, maybe I should just relax. Just go chill. Not scream or yell or tense my body up.
Here's the thing about these games, right? When you play one of these games, you don't even
realize you're doing it, but you are exercising your entire body. You are exercising your blood
vessels to everything. Every inch of your body is doing a lifting routine. Your stomach tightens
up your arms, tighten up your neck, your jaw. Guys, I woke up like the third day, my teeth hurt.
It was weird. It was like, wow, my teeth were exercised somehow. How
cool. People think I'm fucking whatever. I'm just fucking kidding. All the grinding. Yeah,
I don't know what happened, man. My teeth got a workout. It's like, no, dude, you were
clenching your throat. But we're going to keep playing. I know that people are going to,
this is an Elden Ring channel. I know. But for the first time in about half a decade,
there's a game that I think is really interesting and I'm going to just play the hell out of it.
I expect way more streams, right? Like I'm going to do three, four plus days in a row with this game.
I do have to be careful because I don't want to go too crazy. I'm going to go too hard.
So we'll see how I feel tonight. How long we go. We might go long today. Very long.
Into the early evening hours, probably early evening. I mean, late evening, early morning.
We will after this weekend, even if I don't, I don't plan on beating this game
this weekend. Even if I go two, three hard kind of days in a row or like one day,
day off three days or something or two days, right? However, I'm going to do it.
Definitely not going to beat the game this weekend. So I got to figure out what I want
to do content wise with Elden Ring because just because there's no way I'm going to beat it.
So does this just become a permanent game that happens every week or so that, you know,
there's just going to be an Elden Ring stream that's just going to happen as we progress
through the game. And we just do other stuff too in the meantime. That's a possibility too.
But as it stands right now, this is what we're doing. This is the plan. I'm still super into it.
I have not played. I did make a new character because I wanted to play, but then I stepped
back because that new character was way different than the character that I play on stream. I have
about 12 minutes with a new character and I just got, it's like a big two-handed swing pattern.
I didn't want to get used to that. I want to just stay muscle memory with the guy that I have.
Astrologer? No, the name was Mee Strong and they look like a caveman and they have a big club.
That's my new, one of my new characters I've been playing with off stream.
But yeah, let's keep going. I, this is what we're doing for the next couple of days at least.
I need to study, but I can't stop playing Elden Ring. Yeah, it'll be here though. And it's,
there's a lot. We also have to clean up the notes because the notes look like shit. And I also want
to be, make it very, very clear before we get started. I got a big zit on my face. It's huge.
It's going to be incredibly distracting for me. It's going to be, it's going to be so distracting
for you. Just know that I shaved and I had like a bunch of Elden Ring stress sits. So it's, it
looks awful. It looks really bad. I just need to get it out there because the second I turn the
camera on, all I'm going to see is in all capitals, zit. So I'm just getting in front of it because
fuck it. You know what I mean? I'm in control now, right? Like I am in control now. Yeah, I don't
know. I'm getting the Elden Ring stress sits. All right. Hold on. It's almost time. Almost time.
Hold on. Wait a second. I'm really excited to play though, because I have not played
my character. I went in my character's inventory very briefly. Just looked at stuff for a few
minutes, but I have not walked away from the bonfire that I was at. We, I'm in that spot and
I can't hide it anymore. Can't hide it anymore. People are going to see my like freshly shaven
zit face and whatever. It's okay. I'm okay with it. I'm not, I'm okay with it. I'm okay with it.
It's a beauty mark. It's not a, it's a beauty mark. I already said, oh fuck. It's naughty. Look,
it's fine. And then like I made it so much worse because you know, you're in the mirror like,
what do I do about it? And then you make it so much worse. It gets infected.
I like accidentally shaved it off with the razor and I was like, God damn it. And then when it was
shaved off, I'm like, wait a minute, hold on. And then I, and now it's, it's over and now it's fine.
This is not, this is not herpes. What are you talking about? I don't have, this is not,
what are you, what? All right. Time that person up for fucking 10 seconds. It's herpes. You're
gonna, now I'm going to get angry. Are you sure you're 40? Dude, anybody can get, I don't really
get that many pieces of acne anymore. Like I'm sorry. Like this is, my cortisol levels while
I've been playing Elden Ring have been like a hundred, a hundred percent. So I mean, of course,
but my cortisol level is increasing and my like, I'm getting like very stressed and angry and it's
always really sweaty in here. And I shaved, it's going to happen. Like even though you,
I don't even matter how old I am. By the way, you never, never ask somebody how old they are.
Are you kidding me? All right, here we go. We're going to get started. Elden Ring part four. I
don't, I don't even, I have no idea. All right, let's load game. There's a, there's me strong
and I may have, I may have, okay, this is an hour, but that's not true. That's not true. I sat,
I sat there testing to see if I, my laptop could handle the game. And I was doing like a temperature
test because my laptop, I don't think it can handle it. Cause I was thinking I could play like in bed
with my laptop. So I just kind of sat there and did like a temperature test to see if I could like
even play the game. So you're not, you guys are never going to see me strong by the way. There's
no way it's never going to happen. That's the character that I play only off stream for me.
You're not going to get to see me strong. I'm really sorry. He's addicted. No, I was addicted
to trying to find out if I could play it potentially like not in the bathroom. All right,
here we go. So we've got, what do we got? Turn it up a little bit. I can't really hear it.
Why is his name Edgward? I don't know. This is the first thing that somebody said. He's gatekeeping
his character from us. No, I just, that's my off stream character and I didn't want to play as him
because the swing timings are so off that I would get used to over the last two days playing with
me strong. And I would, I would get on here and I would complain to you guys that I couldn't play
right. It would be so annoying. It'd be like, no, but you don't understand this, but the swing
timings on my other character are so different that that's why I got hit three times. I don't
want to give, even give you guys the firepower for that. All right. So last thing happened,
I beat Loretta. I got this, which is really cool. Those of you that missed it, this is the great
bow. Really, really interested in how this is going to work because I feel like that's going
to be cool. What's on your face? Yeah, whatever. I knew it was going to happen. That's why I got
in front of it. You're just in that, like, if I never said anything, it would just be like,
it would just be like zit. I told you, and this is that person just came to the spring like five
minutes ago. All right, let's go. So last thing that I did, I beat Loretta. There's way more stuff
going on here. So I didn't even, I didn't even look around this area. So let me look around.
Don't listen to them. I'm not going to listen to them. Let's see what's over this way. I have
been very itching and excited to play this. Okay. There's this, I can go up this way,
which seems to lead out. All right, hold on. Not yet. There's a place to go up here. We have a zit
cam. You mean you want me to zoom in, crop this and put it as big as the face cam and have it be
the zit. No, I want new viewers to not like write threads about how fucking annoying I am.
No, that's gross. That's just actually disgusting. That's actually gross. Like that would be that if
I saw somebody doing that, it'd be like, that's fucking okay. You're like trying, you're like
trying to really put this like, Oh, look at how gross and like weird we are. Like, no, that's
fucking I don't want to do that. Not happening. So what there's nothing here. I thought there'd be
something important here. I guess not. Big statue, rub pizza on it and see how big it gets.
All right. Well, we're going out here, put a sensor bar on it. I move around too much. It's
not going to happen. Okay. Here we go. Three sisters, three sisters, by the way, in case,
in case anybody thought there was a problem, I've got it. A lot of you just exhale the sigh of
relief. Of course I do. There's a giant, there's literally a, there's literally a giant dragon
over there on the left. I'm going to go on the right. I have my horse frame dropped. What?
Okay. I think it's okay. I think we're okay. That may have been temporary. It might show up again.
Remember you need lip fillers. Actually, thanks for reminding me, but I don't know where it is.
Frames aren't great. I don't know. That's weird. Sometimes randomly. It seems like the last like
few months, once every like few weeks, we'll get like an F for like 40 minutes and then it's fine
permanently. That's weird. Okay. Here we go. I want to go around this edge. Is this actually
the edge of the world or is there more? There's more all the way up here? No, there's not. Isn't
this the edge of the world? Oh, hold on. You sound like people that are interviewed to replace you.
Wait, you just distracted me. I said no yelling frozen armament. What is that? What is floating
over us? Why is it like a, why is there like a spaceship floating above us? That was weird. You
saw that? All right. All right. Get off. I got to check out rave side. I'm going to see what that
item is. Frozen thing. What level am I? I am. Oh shit. Hold on. Are you dead? I am level 51. 51.
Those of you that want to see what my loadout is, I will show it because there might be some new
people here that just are dropping by for the first time. Uh, I got the carrion night sword,
which scales with intelligence and dexterity, which is exactly what I'm doing. I've got the
carrion glint blade staff soon to be replaced with the Azores glint stone staff. I'm not
overleveled dot 51. You look younger. I'm doing like a half and half kind of deck slash int weapon
build. Very happy with it so far. And we're still gone. Okay. I'm just, so somebody actually just
say again, shut up. Noob sidebar. Ooh, everybody said that. Who is saying this? I don't know. I
saw guys sometimes have to fill in the blanks. I get shit sometimes because people go,
dude, he like read half of a sentence and then just like made up the rest. Yeah, I did because
like I can't read it that fast. So if you say in your message and I catch it and it's like,
Hey dude, I have such a huge fan of Bert and you're like, all I can see is the B you are.
I'm going to be like, Oh, Burger King. Like you're a huge fan of Burger King. All right, man.
Like that's cool. I guess I'm going to fill it in. I want to see what that spell is.
Rosen armament. Enchant arm is held in the right hand with frost. Really? But I can't
enchant this weapon. That's really cool though. I kind of wish I could. Will you ever use your
pouch? It's actually really super useful. Um, you mean like this here? Yeah, I got to,
I got to figure that out. I got to figure that out. All right. So this is going this way,
but I don't want to go this way. There seems to be a lot of stuff this year. I have 10,000 souls.
First of all, be careful. I don't want to die. I need more of this glove war. Yes, exactly what
I wanted. I need glove war too, which is exactly what I just got. All right. This is going to lead
to a whole new area. All right. There was more to do in that area back here. Let me know. I don't
want to get too overwhelmed. Don't overwhelm me. Stop overwhelming me. Still dropping frames. Is
it still happening? It'll, it'll even out. It evened out last time. Last time there was an issue,
it was at like four or five o'clock and it resolved itself in like 30 minutes. So it should be okay.
All right. So this is where we are. I want to go back here because there's an area to go this way.
Check it out. The zip and the shave makes you look like you're 20.
Could you do a Garfield impression? Yeah, I think I could. I could try. Yeah, maybe. That's the best
you're going to get. All right. This is where I want to be. Who am I in combat with? So I want to
go over here. Let's try here first because this looks, this looks pretty interesting. Let's go.
Yep. Yep. Something in here. I haven't go in here. Renna's rise locked shut for now.
What do you mean blocked shut for now? What? Okay. What about over here or over here? I want to check
these. Renna's rise frames. I know. I don't know why it's happening. It doesn't make any sense.
Okay. Let's check these places. I actually, right. I got to clean up the notepad. You're right. Let's
do that first. Uh, these, I already did this. This was that area that I got the, um,
that weird snake, uh, monster thing. I already did that. Uh, I already did that. Didn't do this
prawn guy. This sea offer thing. I did it already. This can stay and this can stay. All right. So
Renna, Renna's is closed for now. I, I guess. I don't know. It might be Twitch. I don't know.
It's not Twitch. This is definitely coming from my end. All right. So that's Renna's is closed
for now. And I guess that that's all I need to know. That's good. Let's go check out. Uh, yeah.
There's like a dragon over here. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. First of all,
like this, I got so much shit on my map. Get rid of that. What are the crap is on here? Just one.
I don't want any more than that. How do I get rid of all markers? Four and five of the, okay.
I don't want three anymore either. All right. This, this dragon here. What am I supposed to do
about this? Just kill this. What was it? Is it a dragon? It is. Okay. Wait, I don't want to fight
that right now. I have 10,000 souls. That'd be a mistake. I'm being so rude about it. This is it.
Yeah. Tell them are you going to beat every single boss? I don't think so because I really,
I kind of want another play through to be able to have stuff that I haven't seen, which is
kind of interesting to me. So I'm going to do the ones that I find or the ones that I'm interested
in. Right. What is that? Ranny's rise. Wait, Ranny, Brenna. Oh, the three sisters. Okay. Well,
this one's open. What the hell is this? Oh, someone's going to be mad about that.
Imagine somebody just w I can imagine I was just wasn't here. Somebody walked into my streaming
setup and just took a two-handed great sword and just crashed through the middle of it and then
left. And they didn't take anything. So what is going on in here? I wonder if I, you probably
have to fight the three sisters, right? I would be surprised if you didn't, especially because
there's a bonfire right here. Oh, I did my routine this morning, by the way. I did my,
I did my Elden Ring routine. The Elden Ring routine was I got up, I took a nice like warm shower.
I made a salad and this salad, by the way, is very healthy. It's half spinach, half spring mix.
And then just do a little bit of olive oil on that. Don't do anything else.
Eat that. Let that just get inside you. Let that like kind of coagulate inside of your body. Get
it good. Make a green tea. And here we are. Like I am actually like, I am full up. I'm ready to go.
Like that's how I play Elden Ring. I eat like a salad is absolutely awesome here. All right. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I need to level up. Do I have enough to level up though?
Probably not. What is this? How much is it for me to level up? 16, 17 thousand? I don't want to die
like five times. All right. I can get 50. I can get that right now. Just give me a sec. All right.
I can come right back here. Makes me want to have some more green. Does that even count as a salad?
Um, yeah, of course it does. Let me just get some souls. I don't want to go up here and die
and lose 15k. It'd be horrible. I have to fight the hand enemies again, which I said this is
actually not a bad idea. I, I, I was like very, very tired when I got here and very annoyed.
So I think now that I'm refreshed and ready to go, this is a guy I want to explore a little bit
here because this place with the hands that actually scared the fucking shit out of me.
That like, that was the worst one so far of the whole game, but I'm not kidding. That hurt.
That actually hurt my body. Damn it. These enemies suck so bad. These guys are the worst.
Yeah. Like, what was that? You get it? Like, what was that little like, it's, it's that,
what is it? You know what I mean? How do you can even tell what he's even doing?
All right. There we go. Finally. That was horrible. My whole, I hurt a lot.
Okay. So this is, yeah, this is good because I can actually explore over here and not just be a
dipshit. Don't. All right. Fine. No more huge ones. Attention streamer, attention streamer,
circle behind the hands. Dude, I have to get another flask upgrade. I'm at plus one still.
I got to get like a plus two or plus three attention streamer. Okay. I'll try it. It's
easier said than done when they take up the whole fucking goddamn screen. Don't lose these.
Oh my fucking God. These hands are the worst enemy in the whole game.
Without us, without a solitary doubt in my mind. Crystal bud. Yeah. Eat shit. Your hand.
Fuck. Yeah. You can't, you, you can't like how, what the these guys are fucking unbearable.
I couldn't even get around him. He, he, his hitbox is this. He goes, almost just dropped like a
bunch of stuff. All right. He's fire. I don't have fire. I don't have, I'm sorcery. All right. Go
ahead and come out of the ground. You fucking piece of shit. Where is he? He's like right here.
Really? Does not do very much. All right. Circle attention streamer, attention streamer,
get around his back. Thank you. Appreciate it. He's using the joke weapon. This is not,
how is this a joke weapon? This thing's awesome. This is not a joke weapon.
Joke weapon? These knight swords could serve as catalysts, letting them wield sorcerous
battle skills. Despite numbering fewer than 20, this power made them a match for even the champions
of gold in battle. It's a joke weapon? Where's the comedy paragraph? That is, this is a knight's
sword for a carrion knight. There's no joke paragraph. All right. I almost have enough.
Where is he? He's a great air. Where are you? Oh, hi. Hello. Hey, hey game. What the fuck was that?
Why can't I walk onto this guy? What the fuck? What? There's so many fucking trees in the goddamn
way. Somebody fucking rocks. Like I come down here so I can actually fight your dumb ass enemy.
Dude, stop turning around so fucking fast. I hate these things. These things just make me angry.
You know, you got that like one enemy in any of these souls games that just like makes you
remarkably fucking angry, remarkably angry. Like you, you can't stand being sitting in the seat
when you, when they show up is this guy. These, these, these big hands make me remarkably upset.
Like it's unbelievable how bad they make me. So let's see. What else did I not see over here?
I swear to God, I didn't even see it. All right. Just run. Like fuck, fuck this whole place. I
like, seriously, I don't care. They could literally be a sorcery item that kills every boss in one
hit literally over there. I don't even care. I don't want it. I don't want it. I don't want it.
I don't want it. I will do this though. I think it doesn't do that much damage. Oh, you bet your
ass. I'm going to sit here and do this. I need the souls. If he kills me, I'm going to be fucking
furious. How did you get in here? What? How did you get in here? Oh my God. I'm fucking mad. I
got to kill this guy because it's the only way that'll satiate my anger is killing this guy
right now. Holy shit. I'm going to cheese this shit out of this guy. I hate these fucking things.
I don't like, I don't like them, dude. I can't, it's just, I can't, I don't care. I'm leaving.
I'm leaving. He just moves too quickly. I don't care. Like I can run his head into the wall the
whole time. What do I have? 13? I need 15. Those guys don't even get that much souls either.
There's such a pain in the ass that you can't, it's, give me the other spot. Like down here
or somewhere else. Yeah. I'm, I'm leaving the world's worst area. This guy's back too. All
right. 34 minutes in and then the mauled has started. Oh, just those hands. That's it. I
promise. I won't get mad for another 30 minutes as long as no fucking hands are involved.
I got to, I got to find somebody to kill. When there's somebody like right out here,
this is where like the lightning stuff was happening. No, no, I'm back. I'm back here at
the end place. All right. No more complaining. I'm killing these hands right now. Get down here. No,
get down here. Get down here. Go. Not two. I don't want to, not two, not two, not two. I would have
done one. Oh my God. I hate these motherfuckers so much. I don't even want to be here, but like my
body keeps gravitating back here. Cause I fucking hate this place so much. I want to wipe this whole
place out. The boys betrayed you and I, it took too long to cast. All right. I'm just getting my
souls and leaving. I just need a few thousand. Get them right here. All right. Give me 2000 souls,
please. Thank you. Oh shit. Now let's get the boys involved too. Why not? I can upgrade the boys
again, by the way. Look at how much better of an idea this was. This is so much smarter. Why would
I even, why would I torture myself with the stupid hand enemy when I could just go on a like exp trip?
Oh, I got a helmet. All right, gone a little bit more. That's it. One more.
Everybody else die. I picked it to be you. All right. Goodbye. Thanks for the experience.
Appreciate it. All right. Let's go over there. They're chasing me. Okay. Well kill these guys.
What the fuck? He must have killed me in one hit. All right. Give me out. Let's go.
Okay. We're ready. We're good. Everything is fine. Everybody can relax.
Everything is good. Nothing is, there's no problem. Why are you getting zits at 42? Did you know that
it doesn't matter how old you are? You can still get pimples all the way through to your like 80.
Ooh, look what we can do now. I have a hundred mana. I have 100 mana. Oleg can actually show
up now. Okay. Let's give it a try. There's Oleg. I wonder how good Oleg is. It takes the entire
mana bar, by the way. Okay. Now I'm safe. I'm comfortable. I'm going to go up. Are you ready?
Use the pouch for the summons. You know what? What a fucking brilliant person you really are.
Let's take this off here and let's get those. Where's the pouch? Like equipment pouch, right?
Is this it? Where is it? How do I get a pouch? Is there a way to do it? Does it have to be in
the inventory? Which right? How do I do it? It's the first screen. How do I switch to the pouch?
Right side of the first screen. Oh shit. Okay. How do I assign something? Switch. Okay. I will go
right stick for Oleg, right D pad. We'll do left D pad for the boys and then down D pad for the
dogs. This is actually so much more useful. Why the hell did I not do this? Okay. So then I can
go like this. Yeah, that's much better. Cool. Thank you. I'm so glad that actually I haven't
streamed this in like three days. So you guys like know how to do like all like the actual quality
of life stuff that I didn't pay attention to because I know a shitload of you guys are at
least like a full day ahead of me now. So I'm grateful. All right, let's do it. All right.
Oh, it's you. What do you have? Oh, again, we cross paths. I believe I said my name was Renna.
Last we met. Is it a lie? It pleaseth me to see torrent hail and hearty,
but tarnished. What business hast thou here? I have no memory of ink and thee in invitation.
No particular reason. No particular reason in particular thou claimest. Intrigued,
then mayhaps fate have steered thee to this reunion. Wilt thou enter into my service?
I am the witch, Ronnie. I stole death long ago. Then you say name was Rana? I search now for the
dark path. What's your name? That I might wonder. What's this person's name? And the world of all
that came before. Has that roused thy interest? Serve Ronnie the witch. I don't, um, I don't know
if I should do this. I don't know what this does. I'm afraid. I'm afraid. I see. I did it. A choice
well made. Thou art a rare sword. Do I get witch sorceries? But I require as much of those under
my command. Why am I under your command? Good work from thee. I thought you were gonna,
I thought this was like I was gonna like do like a couple of little gigs for you. I didn't think I
was gonna be like under your command. Good. Then I ask we proceed with haste. There is in my service
a half-woven warrior by the name of Blythe. I would have thee join him in searching for
the hidden treasure of Nocron. The eternal treasure. I have called for Blythe to greet thee below.
What? Take from him the particulars. Wait, are we gonna like ride together somewhere? And there
will thou find E.G. or Canceller and Salavis, preceptor in the sorcerous arts also. Okay,
there's more people? Are we about to do like a, are we about to become like the wizard of Oz?
Are we gonna have like four people? Okay. Speak with the three who await below.
Okay, so they're just waiting for me below? I'm very interested. All right, let's go.
Are we gonna go kill the dragon together? I'm very interested right now. Is that them? Oh no,
that's just like a brass. Wait, who's this? What do you want? Is this the blacksmith?
Okay. Okay, what's your guidance? Don't underestimate me.
What? Okay, let us give all that we can. Sure. All right, well, what are you gonna,
what kind of potions are you gonna give me? Where's the sack of jewels that just are gonna
help us on our journey? All right, so are they outside? Am I drinking? That is matcha.
It's a green tea matcha powdered drink. Okay.
The well in the Mistwood. The well in the Mistwood. Let me write that down. Me.
I write that down? Okay. Well in the Mistwood. Okay. All right, well in the Mistwood for the
worgen guy. And then, wait, is that all you have to say? See if I can't. I won't, I won't,
I won't. Well, how can, well, how come, why are they force ghosts? I see. You must be Rani's new
I kind of like this person.
Celibus. I like this, I like this person.
I like this person. So where are you gonna be?
I reside in another tower.
Should you wish to be of actual service to Mistress Rani? If it were up to me,
I wouldn't waste my time on the likes of you. But who am I to stand against the wishes of my lady?
Okay, very cool. Turn the sound up. Yeah, it looks like it was a little low. I got you.
I got you. Sound going up. I reside in another tower. Because I reside in another tower.
Do I have to pick one of these three that I want to play with?
Oh, you're in one, you're in this one or this one? Does it matter?
Where's the Mistwood? Mistwood. Where is that? Have I not found that yet? Where's Mistwood?
It's east of Limgrave. Mistwood. Okay. He died, he did say Limgrave. But what about the guy with the
hat? What about the guy with the hat? This choice will have consequences. What? What about the big
guy? Did he even say where he was gonna be? Wait, I know where he is. Oh no, I have to pick one of
these three? So let me get- Okay, I've got a prediction. Oh no. There are no choices? Oh,
there's not a choice. Okay. All right. All right. All right. So if that doesn't matter,
I was kind of concerned. So I'm going to go to that. But first, I'm going to go to the tower
where this guy is. You don't get to pick. It's okay. All right. All right. So I want to go to
this tower. I think it's this one here. Unless it was the one that was closed before. But I'm going
to check this place out. That is so cool. I'm really excited. Because there's this one here.
Or choice matters. Well, all right. I'm gonna I'm literally gonna excuse me. What's going on here?
This is an invisible wall. That's odd. That shouldn't be here. I'm screwed up there. Go
talk to Ronnie first. Okay. Why can't I leave? It's because I can't. Why I can't leave the zone.
I have to go talk to Ronnie or I can't leave. Okay. This seems pretty cool. I'm actually pretty
excited for this. We're off to see the wizard. The wonderful wizard of Oz. Here is a hell of a
I don't know the lyrics. Ah, allow me to forewarn thee. I shall soon enter my slumber.
And it will be some time before I wake. This doll's body is not without its hindrances.
Still, I have high hopes for thee. I look forward to the good news when I what are we what are we
doing? I don't even know what the quest is. I shall soon enter and it will be what's what's the
quest? I hope I look for all she said is I'm gonna go to sleep. You're off to sell the treasure.
Right, right, right, right, right. All right. Here we go. It's time. We're gonna go explore.
I want to go see what is the deal. I want to see what the deal is at the tower because I want to
talk to they're all gone. But you know what I mean? Not fighting that dragon right now. We got
we got way bigger fish to fry. It's not a huge dragon. No, not even cool. Not even remotely
interesting. Let's go. Oh my god. I think I'm fine. I'm too excited. Fuck. We're off to see
the wizard. The wonderful wizard. What do we do now? I don't know. I'm not sure what we do now.
What do we do? What do we do? Okay. That it's hard to do that without the cringe. It is that the
lion is hard to do without absolute cringe. Do you understand how hard that is to do? Like it like
without everybody being like stop. Put a mob. Put a mob. What are you doing? Nobody can do that
without it. It has to be that bad actor like nobody else can. It's kind of like anybody
else doing that is cringing. You're the lion. No, I am not the lion. No, I would not be the lion.
And I would not be the mayor of munchkin land. Okay, so let's get that out of the way. I would
be the scarecrow. Get the fuck away from me. I would be the scarecrow. You know how I know
I'd be the scarecrow because the scarecrow does like little movements. He like goes like this and
like this and he like puts his hands like this and shit like that's me. That's me. I'm the scarecrow.
All right, there's this person. So here we go.
Cease to amaze. Okay. I suppose you're here now. Perhaps I'll give you something to do.
What do you do? I'd like you to find a woman called Nefeli to administer a potion.
Even you can do that much. Where are they? What do I do? I do it. I'll do it.
Okay, syllabus is potion. Find Nefeli and ensure she drinks it. Find Nefeli. I expect clad tidings
and soon. I have no time for idle shit. The only thing I will hear from you is a report of your
tasks completion. Are we understood? I have enough on it please. Oh, do you know what? Where are they?
I have no time. The only thing I have is I have enough. Does it say on the thing?
Where is it? What if I just like drink it in front of him? Where is it? It looks like a key item.
Oh, there it is. Small flask received from Perceptor Celvis containing a cloudy tonic
of bluish black. Find Nefeli and ensure she drinks it. I don't know where that person is.
I need to put it on my notepad. Okay. Sure. Maybe. But what if I don't? All right.
I don't confuse me. I'll just. It's the potion quest. Okay. Sounds good. What if it's poison?
I mean, it probably is poison and I'm gonna have to make a decision whether or not I want to keep
that person alive or not. All right. What if I just give him the potion? If I'm like, here,
how about a nice ice cold spray? Oh, thank you. Of course. And then I'll get his hat.
Ooh, good. Very good. Very good. Very good. Another spell slot. So what about,
can I go back in here though? Because now it's like, okay, maybe not. I could try. All right.
Mist. Where the mist is. The well in the mist would. Check it out. You wouldn't download a car.
No, I, you're right. I wouldn't. If I was a well, I would probably be like here somewhere.
There's a, that's a well. That is a well. Is it just, okay, down, is it just in Siofra?
Okay. How do I switch map to go down to? Okay. Let's do it. I need to like switch. Oh,
shit. All right. So where, where is he going to be? Just, I'll be down the well.
Just right in the front, front door. I'll be down the well. You'll find me by the well.
Right. Something like that. I don't think he's here. Riverbank. Maybe this is how to get here
with this, uh, with this fest this way. How can we read the most out of context messages?
We're just looking for him. He's going to be sitting somewhere in a weird spot.
His arms crossed. Just like sitting there. Frames. There he is. Frames. Right there. All right. I
found him. There you are. All right. Cool. He's really intimidating. Do you fight these guys?
What do you have to say about these guys that shoot the bow and arrows from across the whole
game? I mean, you, you could probably just kill them and you're going to kill them. Can I give,
will he die? All right. Fight them. Show me what you can do. Very intimidating. That's right. See
who I'm with. I'm with the guy that you don't want to fuck with and we're together and we're
coming to, we're, we're coming to the party together. Yeah. And that, and that's something.
And that's something. Yeah. Hey, I got this. Don't get up. Good to see you. Apologies, mate,
but I don't. I thought he killed me. I thought it was like a fucking scam. I thought it was a scam.
Like apologies. Like, sorry, mate. Like, boom, like arrow in the neck.
I missed that whole fucking thing. I just hear, oh, apologies, mate. Nothing to report so far. Boom.
Out. I fucking swear to God, I'm going to throw this guy. I'm going to just grab him by his legs
and just spin, spin, spin and throw him into a fucking bomb. I am trying to immerse myself
in the world. Leave me alone. And I don't care about your world immersion. I don't care about
your story arc. I care about that story arc of the big hairy guy. I don't give a shit about your
story. Can you repeat that whole thing? Because I missed everything. Damn it. Is he still going to
be there? Is he going to be there? Right? Is he still going to be there? He's still going to be
on the ledge. What if he's gone? It's because when you get on the horse, you move forward like,
okay, thank God you're still there. Please leave me alone. I don't want to aggro anything.
I already did, but whatever. Like I'll just kill them. Are you going to shoot an arrow from all
the way down there? You better not. Okay. He's shooting the arrow into a rocket. Just can we
walk this way? All right. I'll show you what I got. You're working with a saucer. Impressive.
Was that Loretta's grade bomb? I haven't seen that move in at least three or four years.
How did you come across such an incredible item? Well, well. I jest that far. Besides,
I should check on some things here. Leave this place to me. You just do what you feel is right.
If either of us learns anything, we tell the other. Right. What was the first thing you told me?
Leave this place to me. And if we reach a dead end, I suppose we go back to the source.
Some of us rarely gives a straight answer the first time.
God damn it. I keep thinking you're betraying me. I swear to God. Stop. Okay. What was the first
thing he said? I was freaking out. He was like, let's go up there and beat that person up. He
mentioned about us beating somebody up. Where did what did he say? He's like, oh, we go beat
that person up. He said to go talk. He meant syllabus. He said you go talk to syllabus. Okay.
Okay. All right. Okay. Damn it, man. Go talk to the sorcerer. Come back.
I have a potion from the sorcerer. Squeeze the sorcerer, right?
All right. We have new dialogue with syllabus. The syllabus is this one down here. This is cool.
Oh, mind the dragon. Hey, what info do you have?
Time for idle chit chat. The only thing I will hear from you is a report of your tasks completion.
Are we understood? I haven't. You're asking me about that. Are you? The task was left to you and
the mongrel, was it not? Not only are you incompetent, but shameless to boot. Dead if you keep going here,
bud. Now's as good a time as any. I let you in on it. What's going on? A glint stone sorcerer by the
name of selling in the grave. She owes me for the help I gave her when she was expelled from
the academy. Who's that? I asked her to look into the matter some time ago. I'll write you a letter
of introduction. Go ask. Is that the lady that I found in syllabus introduction? Okay. No time for
the only thing. Are we? And I haven't. Is that the lady, the burger queen? Yep. Okay. I gotta
remember where that was. Burger queen was where? Somewhere in one of these caves. Waypoint ruins?
It was really, really close to the start of the game. I think it's this one here. Waypoint ruins.
Am I still dropping frames? What the fuck? It's annoying. It shouldn't be doing that. Let me see.
It should even out. Why is it doing this? Yeah, I mean, I'm dropping frames on OBS,
but my internet connection's fine. I don't know. Maybe it's like my connection to the
um, it might be my connection to this, to Twitch servers. So because everything else seems perfectly
fine. It happens like every five to 10 minutes. Hmm. All right. Well, here we go. There you are,
my apprentice. Shall we commence the lesson? Son of us is not a name I ever wanted to hear again,
but fine. If it will help you, my apprentice, I offer my knowledge. Thank you. The stars alter
the fate of the Karyan royal family and the fate of your mistress Rani. Long ago,
General Radahn challenged the swirling constellations and in a crushing victory arrested their cycles.
Huh? Now he is the force that repulses the stars. If General Radahn were to die, the stars would
resume their movement and so too would Rani's destiny. Okay. Um, I'm going to hand you a piece
of paper and can you just write down a name and an X on where they are and then how,
you know what I mean? Like I don't, what does that mean? Ooh. All right. Ooh. Ooh.
That's new. Okay. So now we take that. We take that back to the source server guy or do I go
back to the wolf now? I think the wolf at this point. Yeah. Very cool. All right. So now we're
going to go talk to the wolf. You were here. This is crazy. Pepe laugh. Haha. Pepe laugh. All right.
Well, that's not good. He's the best boss in the game. New spell slot. You're exactly right,
but I can do it left here. What news? Oh shit. Don't kill him. I need him. I was seeing if he
would get angry. What if he just got hit in the head and died? Oh my God. That would be horrible.
I'm freaking out right now. Oh my fucking God. All right. I thought I actually fucked everything
up. I thought, I honestly thought I fucked up the whole game and I thought he was going to get
aggroed and like break his quest. Is this your first time playing? No, no. I beat every souls
game. I beat Sekiro on stream. Final boss in Sekiro, which is one of the hardest things I've
ever done. So don't worry. I'll get it eventually. He's still bragging about Sekiro. Yeah. I will
take that to the grave because I know people that abandoned, I know a shitload of people abandoned
Sekiro at the last like hour of the other game. I didn't. I beat it. I beat the last fucking guy.
And I know a bunch of people like, yeah, fuck that game. I'm not ever playing that ever again.
And I was like, yeah. And then I beat him. Do you guys have to seriously have an aggro range
that's this far? Just get out of here. Okay. We're good. What news? Here's the story. So Rani's
fate is kept in stasis by Starsgur's Radar. That reminds me of something I heard. What did you hear?
There's a festival being held at the castle on the southern edge of the Kaelid Wiles,
east of Limgrave. It's a festival of combat. And I heard that you can fight Radar himself.
He who's once called the strongest of all the Debbie gods. Maybe it's just a coincidence.
I think it's worth investigating. I'll be on my way to this festival of Radar.
Okay. In big F. I know. You're coming too, right? I'll meet you at Redmane Castle in
Kaelid. Redmane Castle in Kaelid. We fight sword and fire.
You understand like, why did this guy all do this? Why did he, he was de-aggroed.
These guys weren't even, it's been like, oh two minutes. Just get, you are way too level for
Radan. Oh, I still, Kaelid's all over there. I beat Radan. Okay. Well, at least I want to check,
maybe I'll check it out. Okay. So that is here. Probably up here somewhere. I haven't been over
here really at all. So I don't know. Maybe I, okay. I have that activated now. Maybe I continue to
trek this way. Cause there's still stuff apparently up here that I haven't done. Is it, it's visible
up on the map. Is it, it's not this over here. It's like the festival. Is it here? No, it's
probably there. I've been stuck on Radan for four days. Oh God, that's not encouraging.
That's it? Wait, it is this. It's this? Okay. What does this do? Where does this go?
Probably across the great bridge, right? I still, I'm just seeing what's here. It said impassable
bridge, but it's, it's, I can walk across it. I don't know what they mean. Why does it say that?
Is that going to take me just right to the, oh, I'm just here now. There's a tournament or
something going on. It's definitely right there in the halo theme song. Okay. Well I got this.
I kind of want to check out what's going on back there though. This festival. Yeah. Should I do
that? I kind of don't want to like have the frame rate. I don't want it like the internet to fuck
up in the middle of one of these fights, right? Cause then how am I supposed to prove if I beat
it? I'm kind of scared. Maybe I'll come back later. Is it actually a tournament arc?
What?
It's actually a tournament? This is insane. Do you, how many bosses do you fight?
Grab the great run.
Defeat the general in glory and great
and feel real bad for her. I've been practicing this new move to Loretta's great bow for anybody
that, you know, just in case somebody thought they were going to be at least even think they
could compete against me. And I mean, you know, I beat Loretta, killed Loretta mere hours ago,
got some pretty cool moves. You know, there's still time to back out of the tournament.
Fucking loser.
Fist of Alexander.
This is the pot.
Be sure to get a good vantage.
Look at that guy.
Oh, y'all should just go home. Okay. Who's that? Wait, what else do I have to say? This is crazy.
I like this. Get a good vantage. Okay. What about you? Do that. What do you have to say?
Then what's going on with your hand here? All right. All right. We've got to go through all these
clowns into the fray together. Let's see what you made into the fray together. So wait, is it,
it's like a tag team matches. Is it two V two? This is cool. Okay. I can't wait. This is actually
awesome. We're going to get two V twos into the fray together. Let's go. The prepared young chum,
the festival begin. Let's do it. I'm going to get my ass kicked. Wow. We begin.
Allow me to paint you the full picture. What? Long time ago. General Radon is cursed ever to wonder
inside by millennia scarlet rot. His wits are long gone.
Oh, now he gathers the corpses of former friends and foes alike, gorging on them like a dog
at the sky. But now we must make merry. Oh, gathering of champions. The rebels begin
the celebration of war.
I just started killing this guy next to me. Art and cry. Do I have to start fighting him?
Do I just start, do I backstab this guy? Is it everywhere for himself?
Past the church ahead on the shore. It's time to battle.
And howling at the sky. Okay. So he's through here. Oh, okay. So I get it. But wait, is there
anything else I can see? It might be something I can pick up. You guys are all on the same team.
What if I had backstabbed him? What would happen? Would I have just ruined this quest line?
Thank God I can actually upgrade this weapon now. It's been like six plus hours in game time.
Let me just check what's going on here. I don't want to just run out there,
but something in here. Anything? Yeah, there is smithing stone six. Nice. I don't think I've seen
one of those yet. What does this go? I was just trying to see what this does. Curious. Let's go
down road. Yeah. I'm going to upgrade my weapon. It goes down here. Okay. What is this?
Okay. Did I just like find something else? It's like a summoning thing here. There's definitely
a boss right here. I just like wandered away. Can I walk in this? I'm curious. What does this go?
Wait, I thought what happened to the tournament? I thought we were in a tournament. Star Scourge
for Dan. I thought we were in tournament together. What's all this shit? All right. I
got to get the timing down on this. I'm like confused. It's like travel so fast, but so slow
at the same time. Okay. Just don't drink. What is this shit on the ground? Oh shit. Let's go.
Wait, I can just bring everybody in here? I don't give a shit about the emote I just unlocked.
I don't care. Like put it in the fucking top left of the screen. You don't need to teach me
your dance move. Like when I press the button to... All right. I'm going to upgrade this shit.
Do I have enough to... I don't have enough souls to do it. I could probably sell some stuff. Yeah,
I will. Let me upgrade my weapon. That should be fun. Okay. If I summon each person and they
teach me a dance move, is that going to be annoying? Am I going to have to like hit,
like get it off the screen? Is that going to be annoying?
There you go. So let me get rid of some of this stuff. I know for a fact I'm not going to use...
I don't want to sell it though. I want this stuff. Okay. I have two of these. I don't want these
bug helmets. I'm not going to use them. I don't want to sell any of this. I need to sell something.
I'm going to sell some materials. Yeah. Oh, okay. Sell these. I don't need these. I need 800. Yeah.
Use this FP. Throw magic darts. What am I going to use those for? Okay. Here we go. This will get
this to plus five, which is way better than what it is right now. I need a somber smithing stone
six. All right. That looks good. Sick. Sick. Sick. Let me... I want to do like the actual tournament.
I don't want to just wander off to the beach and get killed. Look at me. He's purple.
I'm just... I don't know. Sometimes I turn purple. All right. Let's try it. All right. If I can't do
this... If I don't... If I'm not reliably going... Oh, I got this. That is the tournament. Oh,
what was this thing here with the... All right. Spell slot. I'm not going to use it against him.
I'm not going to use it for the boss anyways. It's okay. All right. I'm ready.
I'm ready. Do I have to do this every time? Is he going to have to tell me the story every time?
We don't. Okay. So I can... So what happens if I go through this? Does this just take you to that
area? What is like through this door? Or is this just blocked? Okay. So that's just blocked. Okay.
I don't know if you get to go through it or something. All right. Let's go. I'm going to
try it. I got to get that timing down. We... I got to... I got to dodge, summon, dodge, summon,
dodge, summon. Oh, right. Because there was that statue. You're right. Okay. What's this?
Anything here? All right. Let's go. Let's give it a try. The statue will be right here. All right.
Gaming begins. I don't think I'm going to use mana that much. We'll see. I really don't know.
But let's try it. Okay. It's time to fight this guy. All right. Dodge, summon, dodge,
summon. Let's go. Everybody. Everyone. There's more people? Oh, the jar. Oh, shit. Get in there.
All right. Get him. Get him. Get him. Summon Patches? Wait. Patches is here? Everybody's here.
Get in. Get in. Get in. Get in. Everybody get in. Oh, let me get the item. All right. Patches. Go.
It's like skin hanging off my mouth. Wait. Blade is dead. Why did Patches leave? Let's go.
Oh, shit. Everybody's dead. What is he? He's on a horse? He's on a horse. What the fuck?
Are you shitting me? That poor horse. Oh, nice. All right. Let's go. Oh, what the fuck?
I think that's a gravity move. Jump. Jump. Jump. Jump. Jump. I have no stamina. Did he drain my
stamina? Holy shit. Okay. You got to jump over that. I thought he was on wheels.
Burning through stamina here. I wonder why. Damn it, man. Oh, shit. I'm dead. It's over.
You can resummon people? Resummon in phase two? I was just eating through stamina unlike before.
I was just inhaling stamina. You can resummon indefinitely. I wonder if I should put more
mana on and just shoot him with a bow. He's stamina drains. Oh, that's what it is.
Can I just run through? How hard is it to dodge this on the horse? Okay. I'm fucking just roving
into it. Hold on a second. Let me get this down. Can I just go like this? Let me see. Hold on.
Yeah. Okay. I was testing to see if you could just run parallel to it. You cannot. Just kill me
because there's no reason to do this right now. I was seeing if you could just run like parallel,
all right? Perpendicular and not get hit by it, but he hits you with it no matter what.
Whatever. Say it. You know what I mean? The triangulation. Yeah. The sword ruins break one
hit. I think I got it. I think I got this. It's going to come down to just kind of running around
and being patient. Try Oleg. I got to be up a little closer, I think. Here we go. You, you,
you, you, you, you. Go, go, go, go, go. What the fuck are they doing? Why are they spinning around?
All right. Let's go. What happened? Hello? What happened? What happened? What's going on?
Where's my horse? What the fuck? Why did I die? What was that? Oh shit. That was dumb.
Was I falling? Oh shit. Okay. Well, whatever. All right. Get him again. So when you're saying
that when he, when the summons die, I can go. Jesus. So I can just run back and summon them all
again. I mean, that's, that's what we're doing. No. Everybody in. Everybody. Get on it. Get on.
Oh my God. I'm just like fucking spam. So those, those, those things follow you around.
Of course they do. So can I summon them on the horse? I wonder if I can just dodge that shit
and just run. See you guys in four days. No, no, no, no way. He has homing. I think I can,
I could try to avoid it. It's like getting off the horse and having that like one and a half seconds
of animation that you can't do anything with is what will get me killed if I get off the horse.
Let me see what happens if I do this. Like, can I, I'm just seeing if I can like dash like
right when it's there, right? We do it. It's a test run. That's run. So you physically cannot
avoid getting hit by that. Let's maybe jump over it. See, I didn't try dashing when it was right
there. I tried running. I'm going to try jumping. Let's try jumping. Yeah. That's a test run. Yeah.
I know I can use the scrap piles to block it. That's not what I'm concerned about. I'm concerned
about like needing to go all the fucking way over there. And when he does that stupid arrow homing
missile boom, let me see that happen. That ain't fucking happening. The dude literally has a homing
missile. It's like a 5,000 mile per hour homing missile. You can't do it. I just have to do what
I did before. Really? No shit. What happened? What? What? He, I got hit by like the spray.
Just run sideways. It, it, it still hits you. Even if you run sideways, you have to get lucky.
You're a bigger target on the horse. All right. So the play is to just run backwards and just let
them all run in. You have iframes while you summon the horse. How many though?
Hold on. Let's find out. Interesting. All right. Well, you don't have, you don't have iframes when
you get off the horse. How long do they last? Is it the whole time? It's actually really interesting.
Okay. No, you don't. Okay. You only have iframes when you get on the horse, not off.
I think I'm just going to have to do what I did last time. And that's just, I had just get on,
just do it on point. Let's do the stuff I think about. Oh, he's coming for me. All right. So you
said I can re-summon them now, but not yet. Spot's still alive. Okay. Oh, he's staggered,
but it's not going to help me. Don't do it. Okay. Here we go. So wait, I can summon them again.
I don't think I can. Nobody's there yet. I got to figure out like what a good time to go is.
Spot's still alive. Shit. I don't, I still don't know when to go.
Me, man. When I go in there, he just doesn't move. Are they not in the same place? I don't see any
summoning signs. Just have to be really careful and slow. This is one of those like 15 minute
boss encounters. I need to get to phase two. Okay. They come back for phase two. Okay.
Let's keep going with what I was doing. Like, please suck my ass.
You, you're not, what the fuck are you doing? Oh my God. Fuck off already. Good. Oh, fuck you.
Are you kidding me? Oh my God. What a hero. What a fucking hero. Who did that?
Who did that? I don't know who did that. Yes, should be the one on the right, not the left.
I shouldn't have to press left on the D pad. Of course I want to re-summon. Of course I want to
summon the fucking whores. What happened? There's meteors falling. Are we back? What's going on?
Where is he? Okay. There he is. Holy shit. Okay. I, what do those do? What do those things do?
What do the meatballs do? Do the meatballs fly out? What do the meatballs do? I don't, what do
the meatballs do? Bro, I don't fucking know. Are they going to shoot at me? Are you, are you fucking
kidding me? But they have a countdown timer of like two straight minutes. What? I'm sitting there
waiting for them to do anything and they just fucking sit there. Okay. Here's my play. Here's
the play. Uh, I'm going to put more mana potions in. Let's go. We're doing arrows. I don't want
to fight this guy normally. This is a very abnormal fight. This is a very weird fight.
I'm going to get on top of my horse and I'm going to fucking, I'm going to, I'm going to
meatball this guy. Cheese Andy. That's right. It's going to be a toasted fucking cheese sandwich
with a side of tomato soup. Before we begin, but now we, let's do it. It's time for some grade A
cheese. I cheese so hard. I didn't even have to hit him myself. I, you know, I really feel,
I really feel bad for the like 60 points in strength. Andy's was like, how the fuck do you
do this fight? This is probably so hard because you have to just get up in there and you've got
to get up in there. Oh man. I just spam summons and got the last hit to make myself feel better.
It's easy on strength. You just have to do a test. I wonder how much damage it does.
Do 600 damage per hit. Oh, that's like, that's good. All right. Should I bring out Oleg too?
I feel like that's too much mana. This is not the time. This is not the time for Oleg.
All right, here we go. Bullshit. Bullshit again. I, what? He didn't do that before.
What a dick. Oh my fucking God. I hate this fucking guy. He usually does the,
he does the fucking frame drop. The fuck? No, I don't want to like run like across the whole
game to fight the guy, to do a deal with his like trap shooting. Like, oh look, he's got like the
orcs must die trap that he shoots at you. I don't, I want to fight the guy.
Stop. What the fuck? All right. Get in there. Get in there. What are you waiting for?
Get in there and fight him. You guys are pissing me off. You guys are pissing me off. You're pissing
me off. Get in there. I'm a fucking raid leader. Yeah. Like what taking so long? Fucking get up
there and fight him. Get out the maiden. What are you doing? Get away from me. Go fight him.
He's literally in front of you. Where'd he go? Is he underground? Oh shit. No, dude. I'm so confused.
What is this person? I thought he was going to phase two. I don't, I'm so confused. I thought
he like went like away. He's a healer. I'm so fucking confused. I, oh my God. Okay. I'll get
him now. I'm going to get him. I'll get him. I'll get him now. Don't worry. Stupid ass encounter.
Watch the, I watched the clip after this. You guys, honestly, God, like I'm about to fucking scream.
Like just kill me already so I can start it again. I fucking, I fucking hate the fact that he's just
playing orcs must die. Like this is dark souls. Okay. This is an orc. I don't want to be an orc
and orcs must die. I just want to fucking go get them. I want to fight them. I want to fight this
guy. I don't want to, I don't want to get hit by like the spring trap. Like, oh, look out, watch out
the spikes that come out on the wall. I feel like he's playing tower defense and I'm like one of the
little shits. He didn't fucking do it. He usually does. You know what I'm saying. You know what I'm
fucking saying. And now I'm fucked. Fucking summon them. What the fuck? God, I hate this.
I like just summon them. Like I'm just running over them. Oh, I'm so mad right now. I didn't even
hit him. This is the guy that was in the E3 trailer. This is what you're going to do?
No, no, don't fight the fucking raid leader. Fight those, fight the other guys, fight the other people.
Ow. Oh shit. I just got really, really sloppy. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't be an idiot. God damn it. I'm not locked on. I don't even know
who the fuck he is. This is fucking, this is dumb. Okay. What do you want me to do?
Look at the clip. What's the clip? Let me get it. This is fucking dumb. I hate this. All right, let's go
I'm so I hate this. All right. What are we watching? Let's go
I don't want to fight this guy. I want to fucking just leave
Fuckin hate this guy. I want all right. I'm beating him right now. I'm fine. So bad. It's unvoking believable
All right
That didn't even look real that looked like a fake picture
That looked like I put I pumped that in on purpose. I fuck all right
Stop shut up. Fuck you. I'm gonna beat him right now. This is the one I promised
All right, he did the stupid orcs must die move and now I gotta get on the
Hurry, hurry, hurry
No, dude, get on the fucking horse
Why are you still shooting at me? There are people in front of you. Do you not see?
Get in there, please
All right, let's go. I'm gonna summon some more people
There's a stone. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god
I thought he was back. I thought he was turned to face the other guy
I thought he was turning the other way because the guy was in front of him. I hate this encounter
Oh my god, I hate it
This is not even about dodging the guy
it's just throw up a bunch of fucking action figures to like this like
The school bully that comes and stomps on him
Oh my how do I throw a grenade down at the ground and die?
Just throw a grenade to the ground like because i'm like I just wasted a estus
Even with sorcery too. You were here very early. You can do the fun stuff
I'm beating this guy out of spite. I'm gonna win
This guy is such a piece of shit
I'm going to beat him out of spite
All right
If in 10 tries I do not do it. I'm going to leave and we'll come back later
10 tries 10 tries
Fuck you. Where are they?
Oh my god eat
Eat it seriously. God fucking damn it. Like I just don't
Like I fucking hate it
Oh my god, the fucking turning radius on this stupid ass horse. Like give me a fucking goddamn break
If you if you were on the ground, how would you avoid that?
dude like
Help me help my god. How the fuck are you dodging the house?
Dead I can't get out of this. I can't animation cancel anything. I'm stuck. How are you still alive lady?
Is lady still alive?
She's just running behind him
What the fuck?
All right. I got some of these guys
I can't take my thing off of them. I gotta like get it like here
Come on lionel get over here. All right, there's another couple that respawned over here
Christ
Where are they? I can't take the lock on off of them. I gotta just run around
It's like right here somewhere. All right, turn around and fight
All right. All right. All right. Let's go. Let's go. Let's fight fight fight fight fight. I need more summons
Where are they everybody back?
Fucking horse what?
Huh? What happened? What?
What?
What does he land there? Does he land there? What what does he land? He land on me?
Does he land on the top of the hill?
Was it the meteor was that him landing? I don't know
In meteor. All right, that's one
I just keep summoning people
Yeah, like the worst part about that though is you need to just ride around like a dickhead
And like sometimes it's hard to know where they're gonna spawn and turning and turning you back to try to look and see if you're
In the right direction. It's just you're just gonna get hit by a fucking one of these dumb things
I okay. I need to figure out what the solution is here
Because if I get on the horse and he does the fucking purple thing i'm fucked
Like can I just out? I don't think I can outrun this and I
It's so hard to tell
I think I can
Like everybody
I don't know you really really like are you fucking kidding me, dude?
I think there's the ladies up here, right?
I don't know. I can't there's I can't turn my back
Man, come on. Is there any more signs?
Just drive around
I don't see any more signs
I wonder if they just recently
Get them more more more people more people
Oh shit, I lost him
God damn it
i'm fucking dead
I don't I don't understand why that move is it is that in this it seems like how the fuck me what are you supposed to do?
Like what how do you fucking avoid that move? Is it even possible?
How big that fucking move is I can dodge roll it but i'm on the fucking horse
I'm so dead
All right up on the hill
We're running around doing that. Well, I mean I can't it's hard to close the gap if i'm gonna hit him and do like fucking
40 damage
That moves dumb
You all know it
That's a dumb move
Let me just try to fight him
I'm gonna try to get up just to just to fight him either bleed or freeze
I feel like I can get him to at least phase two. I think the bow is takes way too long as as safe as you are
using the bow
Look at how long it takes. I mean, you don't need to see it, but it's just like one
two
three
Four five. It's like it's just you aren't you're in such a bad position. I'm just gonna fight him. I'm just gonna fucking fight
Let's go
I'm just gonna get in there and i'm gonna kick his ass
That's it. I'm just gonna go i'm gonna go kick the shit out of him face to face one on one
With a bunch of friends and then that's it
Can I outrun this?
Because getting on the horse is like such a bad idea right here because he'll do the purple shot
I can outrun it. All right, I don't need to get on the horse
Really?
You buddy let's go
Let's all get in there and fight him as one as a team
There's too much going on too many people
Way too many bodies
Uh, it's hard so many sound effects. It's almost I can't tell who's even doing move
You're supposed to get on the horse
All right. How many attempts is that before I just like never come back to this shitty piece of fucking garbage fight ever again
three, okay, just gotta do this seven more fucking times I
Fucking hate this
Just kill me like a what?
Somebody said this took them four days to do what the fuck
No, that counts that counts that counts
I'll summon oleg. I'm gonna summon oleg and let him get one hit killed
Dude, honestly, I think i'm gonna fight this boss without the hut too, by the way
You know what I mean? Like i'm just gonna turn the hut off because like what's all this info on the screen?
I don't want to fucking see it
47 fucking damage
Dude, will you stop fucking swinging? Oh my god
Is this like a fucking movie i'm watching or do I get to fight the guy oleg get out here
Get to be off the horse. How come I can't summon what?
Why not? I can't summon
I can't summon them here
Everyone yelling at me to summon oleg. I can't
I got a better idea
All right
new plan
New plan for the last five attempts
My hand goes through my monitor
new plan
uh
Do I have
I this is not gonna this is not gonna cut it. This might though. Hold on
Maybe I should just sit there and just like
These things happen quick swift ones
I don't think anything else is worth doing. I'm honest. I think I just eat
I think I just have yeah, I mean i'm gonna get i'm gonna lose but
I'm just gonna be an absolute coward and we're just gonna swift glintstone fucking run around and just pick them
Yeah, I I only have one sacred tier on these flasks, which is really awful
If I can't get it, i'm just i'm not ready for it
Activate rune arcs. Yeah, but if I die with a rune arc, isn't that just gonna delete the rune arc?
Wow, I wouldn't want to use that at a boss. I'm not comfortable getting 50% of his health down
Anything besides the bow is probably too short range
I'll try it. It's just a humanity
I cannot use my summons, but they're not allowed in that area
I can summon the people on the ground but the hardest part for me so far has been
All right, you summon everybody
You do the orcs must die bullshit in the first fucking minute and a half of the fight
I'm getting on my horse and like I gotta like go around and touch the summoning signs
But sometimes I'll lose the walk-on
And then I then he just I can't even fucking see him
All right
I'm gonna just be a wuss and we're gonna swift glintstone them over and over again
In fact, i'm gonna put the sword away. I'm not gonna use it. I was gonna hold this in two hands
Go take a csgo
Break
All right. I got five more attempts before i'm turning around and running away from this bullshit
The festival is nigh
I'm just gonna stay the fuck away from and just be very very cautious
Before we begin
I only have two heels though, which is bad
I don't need to talk to him. Oh, okay. It's good to know use the buffs bow and spam the bow
I I have to stand in the circle, which that's like just guaranteed to die
I have to stand inside of that little buff circle. It doesn't it's not it doesn't stay on me
I know i'm not supposed to be doing this. I'm not i'm under leveled. I know
I'm under geared. I'm coming in here at the wrong time. I know
I know i'm missing flasks. I know
What it's called being a stubborn little shit
Get out of the way
Eat my ass. I'm serious
I'm not even fucking kidding. Yeah, it's not it's bow. It's bow or nothing
Do it very slowly
slow
It's gonna find the other summoning sign right here
I don't know if I got it or not. It's so fucking hard to tell
Where is he?
I don't know what the fuck out god god god god god god
What the fuck dude, what are you curving around his fucking body?
What was that?
Damn it
Just the opportunity is so small to hurt him. I just have to run around and just don't even attack him
Just get the shots that I can get off and then half the summons hurt him. They keep spawning. I guess
I don't fucking know
Any more summons?
We're doing coward play right here. I don't care
It's real coward gameplay right now
I have no shame
Oh my god. I thought he was aiming the out way. I didn't think it was gonna come this way
All right more summoning symbols. Where are they?
Thought I saw one over here. No, fuck off. It's three people next to you dude. Get out of here
Summoning signs
Oh shit
Where is everybody
Why he baited me he fucking actually baited me
That was actual bait right there
Okay, watch over the meteor meteor meteor meteor watch over the meteor. Where's the meteor?
Where is it?
Where's the meteor?
Oh my god
I'm so scared. I don't want to go close to him. This is for the meatballs
You know, i'm terrified
I'm gonna shoot the bow and the meatballs gonna kill me
What the fuck you?
What killed the wolf?
Why did the both die?
Get on a horse
Dude, I fucking can't with that goddamn move
I was
Slow and steady if you're on you can't you're just gonna just do that fucking move and pull you in
Don't use the horse. Do you you understand how fast i'm gonna fucking die if I don't use the horse?
I I I have fucking 25 points in dexterity. I'm in trouble if I get off that fucking horse
The only way that I can do that off the horse is if I just just try to just learn all of it
But that's gonna be fucking impossible
I wonder how many people beat this off the horse. I feel like it's like you're not supposed to
Because he's on a horse and we've already seen if somebody's on a horse get on a horse
I just like
I freaked out. I fucking freaked out
You've got five people around you
All right summon fuck that's worked every other time just running sprinting
All right, how many is that how many is that I usually sprint diagonally and I don't get hit
I'm i'm gonna cut it short. I don't think I can do it without more upgrades
I don't think I can I don't think I can do without upgrades
I need at least like a plus three flask
and
I just want to fucking throw a grenade at this guy
I have a plus one flask. What am I my fucking idiot? Like I have to drink like six extra potions
Still don't understand that move. I just don't get it
It's it's that you can't avoid it on foot and if you get on the horse
You might get fucking hit by the purple thing if you get off the horse again
I can't dodge through it because it goes behind me. I don't I don't understand that
All right
So when I get on the horse if he does that move
And I outrun it with the horse and he does the purple charge beam as I he's gonna hit me with it
He's gonna fucking hit me with it. What what the fuck were they thinking?
I don't have a fucking regular ass weapon out. What are you thinking bro? What are you doing?
I don't have a fucking regular weapon out
Don't lose lock on
I don't know why I keep i'm freaking out about that one now
All right summon there's a couple up here
At least it should be right
No
Where is it?
It's back here somewhere
Where are they over there?
Fuck you. Fuck you. I can't avoid that. I have to get hit by it every time
Dude, no god damn it the fucking turning radius. Oh my god. I hate this fucking thing
I hate if you could even call it that if you could even call it that I like I turned but the horse went like
like
That way that one was going pretty well too. It's just you get like if you get like caught a tenth of a second
I just don't I don't I don't want to be a fucking mile away from a goddamn boss like fucking
See what I mean? He didn't do the fucking thing. He didn't do the thing. He did the purple shit instead
And he did the purple shit again
And now he's gonna do the I hate him. I fucking hate him. This guy gets a cap
Somebody invading the game. Why is there a red guy?
All right, right there back there
Get it. That is such a dog shit fucking
I tried to jump at the right time
You're running to you're running circles around him instead of running away
But if I run away I lose the lock on and I like turn that way and fucking sucks
Oh, that's
And he's also faster than me too. That's another thing
He pursues me. He's gonna close the gap because he's faster
Where are those summoning things over there?
Fuck you
This boss is from knack three they should have kept him there. I don't know summoning signs back behind me. I think
I'm not gonna beat him one. I'm gonna back. I'm gonna go here
It's a really stupid idea. But whatever
I don't know
I don't see me. Oh my goodness. This is bad. What the fuck did you come from? Well do something. What? Hey
What was that?
All right, I give up. I give up this guy sucks. I'll be back later
He's going in the air. All right
Meteor I don't know where it is. Where the fuck is it?
I don't know. I don't know
I can't do anything. I have to just run around
I can't even fight the guy. I just have to sit here and stare at him. Yeah, just go fight him. Fuck off everybody
Go fight him. I'll watch i'll watch the stupid ass thing. Go fight him
Eventually, maybe somebody will do enough chip damage where I can fucking be out of here
I'll stay all the fucking way back here. I don't give a shit
Is anyone hurting him? Oh, there we go. 193. You see that
Someone will kill him. Somebody will kill this guy
Are there any more summoning soap signs? I don't see any more. Oh shit. Oh, I can't see
What the fuck happened?
Where did that come from?
Oh this this little
fucker
I'm so upset at this
You gotta be fucking kidding me. Oh, I am I am very annoyed
Oh my god
Oh my fucking god
I'll be back. All right, can I do my tier list of worst soulsborne bosses ever made? All right, that guy's down at like
Okay, like I didn't even eat that brand of cereal, right? Like I want to put that guy all the way down
I want to put that guy like below f to like
Like oh, I I haven't even had this restaurant. You know what I mean? Like I haven't eaten this fucking restaurant. You know what i'm saying?
So we're gonna do something else
It's true
Poison's really good to get us out. Whoa. Whoa. No. Whoa, look what I got. I don't got poison. I got this shit
Okay
so
What we're going to do
Is i'm gonna i'm gonna leave there and i'm gonna explore the world of elden ring
i'm gonna come back there in like like 10 goddamn levels like what i like i'm supposed to
With an extra fucking flask
extra help
And i'm gonna pile driver that guy
I'm gonna fucking i'm gonna smother that guy with a pillow
I'm gonna fucking just kill him. He's dead real soon. I promise
So I need to find
I think i'm gonna go here
Am I still frame dropping what the that's also pissing me off
Why am I dropping so many frames?
I have I have fucking gigabit thousand thousand internet connection. What is going on?
This is like my internet connection can't get better than this
Like I physically can't get a better connection
Look at how sweaty I am. Holy shit
Why do you look like this because i'm deranged right now. Okay
I know what we can do. I have an idea. Let's go kill the dragon. Let's go kill the the dragon that's over here. That's good
That's something I can do
That sounds like fun
Because I I know I can kill the dragon. It's been a while
We do a brb. Uh, if I don't beat the dragon in three tries, I will be Rebecca. Oh my god. That's the vendor
Oh my god, that's the vendor. I just was like mad. So I just attacked a guy
No, don't kill the vendor, please
Okay, geez, I don't want to kill the vendor
It's been an age since I was custom. What do you got two imps
Crafting. Oh shit. All right
You got some good shit
There's a note here
Have a safe journey. I'm gonna mark this because that's actually pretty good. All right, i'm gonna mark this
Uh, like a vendor what would be vendor probably this
Next time you fight that boss, don't use the party finder. It's full of morons
Stop is it safe for me to drop down from here or i'm gonna die
Finder what's this? What's going on? What are you? What's this guy doing here?
All right, I gotta like get I gotta play dark souls again i've been literally riding around
Playing anti-tower defense the whole game
Like i've been on the horse for three hours trying to fight this stupid fucking random ass encounter
Jesus christ, dude
What the fuck?
Who the fuck is this guy? What are you doing over here?
What the oh is happening?
Who's this guy?
Get away from me. I'm trying to play
Celestial dude
carry out absolution at the church of vows
reversing all
antagonizations
Is this so I bring that to the turtle and I can reverse people that are angry
interesting
Okay, that's weird. It makes npcs not mad at you. Ah, all right
Uh, okay. I need to go
No, what's the fastest way to get there?
I think it probably
You still have plus a one flask. I know but like I don't
This world is so huge that it's like
I need to I don't know what they are
I think they're like churches, but like I need to where is it? I need to find a church
I'll get it soon. Don't worry. I feel like i've come across random churches. Maybe would they be on the map?
like that right
So like in here like but I feel like i've gotten that one already
Did I get this this is a church?
technically
No dragon. No, no, i'm going for the dragon right now
I just want to get a better uh place to do it
So if we go I gotta go this can I jump over this?
What's the best actual way to go to get here from probably one of these this one?
That's a cave
this one here
Because I can jump i'm trying to just not die because you die from the fall damage there
Yeah, it's this one here. Yeah. All right. Let me go kill this dragon. Let me try to
See if i'm gonna do it
Frames are still dropping. I I have no idea what's going on
That should not be happening
But it apparently is
I don't know if it's twitch server problem or I don't know if it's a connection my connection problem
but
I don't know it's weird
I'm gonna start connecting to a different twitch server
I feel like the one i'm connecting to is like a piece of shit. So i'm gonna connect something else
Next stream I will connect to a different ingest server
I feel like that's part of the problem
Okay, let me see if I can kill him. Here we go. Do it. What was that?
Is he gonna use me?
I don't like this place, but I don't like fighting him here
I don't want to fight him against the wall
Thank you for moving I appreciate
What are you doing?
What's he doing?
Being a weirdo. What are you doing?
Why are you being such a weirdo?
What are you doing?
Not against the wall get out of there
Watch out for the giant slug. Where'd he go? I'm not gonna fight a giant slug right now. Hey
All right. I'm good. Oh
Shit, I jumped. I didn't I jumped twice. What happened? He killed me in one hit
What happened what
What happened? I jumped I double jumped and hit him. I hit my head on the ceiling
What?
I died in one hit
That's no
No
He landed he landed but I like jumped and he landed I touched his like
Buddy
That was so sad one hit
Oh my god, i'm so defeated right now like what the
fuck
What?
I guess i'm gonna just somebody said be aggressive. Yeah, I was trying to be slow and smart
But fuck man if I can die in one hit am I like not supposed to be fighting this guy either
Go
How is what's going on
I've landed on this rock fucking a hundred times
What?
That doesn't count i've jumped on that rock three five thousand times in a row
What what the fuck is going on?
Where did you just put me?
No, it doesn't count. Jeremy, you are so stressed. Take a break
That was so that was horse shit
Why did I die in one hit?
I feel like i've gotten hit by that move. Okay. So tell me what the fuck is going on right now because literally i've
Is it the double jump?
I guess I
I'm just gonna be super aggressive and if it gets me killed whatever
Go directly south of the dragon
Right here. I want to see look. All right. I understand that you want to shoot a whole map full of fucking magic
But like look, can I please see my fucking map?
Thank god. I don't even fucking think about it. You're pushing my buttons right now
A little there's a little island here. I just you said there's one here
All right, save me
Did I beat the dragon? No, he killed me in one hit
I have full health which leads me to believe that I either got like omega stomped
Or I like wasn't i'm still not supposed to fight that guy
All right. Well, you said go to the island. What's on the island? I mean, it's lily
What's the island this island? Is there a flask thing on one of these islands?
Far out of the cell. You mean like you mean like all the way down here
Like way south i'm gonna go all the way down there
Okay, this is crazy. This is a whole nother content
Go this way
I thought this was like the end of the world. There's another way to go. That's fucking ridiculous
What's back here? I feel like i've done this part
Let me just check
Starlight shards
All right. So the what am I looking for down here? Is it gonna kill me?
I'm not okay
Southern island is is is pretty easy
Oh you you mean you want me to oh was this the way for you guys to get me away from like the hard shit?
That's making me want to fucking
Smash my webcam into 100 pieces
Oh, okay
All right. I can still be on the horse
I'm gonna get to one of those, uh gray states
All right, give me a bonfire so I can take a quick break
Smashing my fucking head against a wall fighting a boss i'm not supposed to be fighting
who has
a shit
Shit encounter i'm gonna go down here and i'm gonna have a great time
Okay, here we go. I've been holding my key i'm going i'm going i'm going let's go. Let's go. Let's go
All right, i'm right back
All right. I'm back. Let's try this again
Let's go for it. Hello. How are you? So where where am I?
bridge of sacrifice
shito, okay
where
Even is shito. I think so. All right, let's go
Let's do it. Let's do it. Let's do it. I'm gonna go back to the bridge and we go down
Or I gotta get all these markers. Is that how can I can I just clear all the markers that I have?
I I feel like this should be a fast way to do this
And I just like because if i'm gonna be down here
I don't want these on the map. Okay
uh
this way
Back in a new npc. Hello. Is somebody there? Might I bend your ear for a moment, please? My name is arena
I've escaped from castle
No, that's uh, that's laniya have rebelled
I can't be sure what it is
My eyesight's been weak since birth, you see but I swear I heard frightful howling from all over
My good father secreted me out the castle but decided himself to stay
He says it's his duty
As commander red nose, you can just see like that. Is it all the anger is hanging out right now? It's like here
I look like i'm fucking trashed
I look shit-faced. I look like i've had like seven beers today like I look trashed
The servants are full of wrath. They've since come for every one of the companions I escaped with
They haven't spared a soul
I fear it's no different at castle morning. Please don't mind taking a letter to my father and my soul wishes that he escaped
Even if his honor should be the price take a letter, please
I just want him to be safe. Okay
Uh, yeah, thank you i'll do it i'll deliver the letter then please
Marina's letter deliver it to my father who remains in the castle if you please
i'll try
Ah promise I won't read the note though
And promise i'm not going to read it
let's say
ah
Gorgeous silicon handkerchief lightly stained with blood words can be made out with that's not what's on the letter. That's what it's made out of
I'll read it
What if it says like assassinate the guy that gave you this letter? What if it says that?
Fucking hate that encounter. I feel like I feel like happy gilmore right now
Like i'm just like still mad about it
i'm still so fucking mad about it
I even like took a minute. I like put some water in my face and I was just like just relax, man
This looks like it's gonna be tricky. I think it's time to call in a little bit of support here. Oh leg the commander
Nice, okay
All right
big moves from oleg
Okay
oleg
Attack it's actually gonna be kind of all right. Wait wait clear it out clear it out clear it out clear it out clear it out
No bullshit. No bullshit
Bullshit is happening
Aren't they happening?
I love this guy. I'm getting this guy plus 10
I'm getting this guy plus 10
You're a little late
The comedy's back. We're good. We're back. We're back. We're back
Hey, we're back
Yeah, all right. And so instead of me going like this
Watch my eyes. All right next time that i'm in the fight and i'm like really like unhappy about the fight
Watch what my eyes do they go like this
Like I look up into my brain
That's how you know that it's not i'm not having a great time
because I go like
I do like to undertakerize
Is that an npc or is it a i've got to fight let's find out
Oleg you know what to do
What's wrong with this guy? All right, get him before he gets the sword out
Oh, yeah
Good team
All right. I definitely feel like I am a little bit leveled for this area
Morning star cool
Anything on this side? No. Oleg seems pretty basic. There he is
He's a new enemy
Oh, yeah, let's go let's just wipe the floor with this area
Okay, I thought that was Oleg for a second. I was like what are you doing, man?
Oh
Why is he even doing 25 damage?
I feel like he should be way more
Oh mighty shot mighty shot. What else we got?
Is Oleg gone?
Okay, Oleg is gone. I can stop biting my lip. Are we still dropping frames still?
Yeah
What the fuck man? I don't know what's going on with this bullshit. That's annoying
Why?
Everyone on twitch wait, is it wait are you serious?
Are you serious?
Really? It's twitch. It's happening to several streamers. Oh shit. All right, I feel fine then
Anytime internet problems pop up. I just get terrified because I just think oh fuck here we go again
merchant
One apple
Demi human mobs
Razor's max hp
I think I want to buy this thing
Did you rest at the bonfire until night for fun? Are you still a knight for fun?
Who the fuck are you?
Knights calvary
Oh, let's kill this guy first try because i'm probably so over leveled for this area
Oh my god. Yeah, let's kill this guy first shot
Don't miss every swing really it's doing better off the fucking horse
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa. Whoa, what? Oh my god, I killed his ass
Oh my god
Raid oh shit who raided what happened?
Omega low lost to germa that isn't wit raid. Why are you guys fucking with me? Where's the what raid? There's no raid
Asher bore barricade shield cool and knight riders flail. What is that thing?
X and strength
Oh my god, that's kind of cool. Actually
That's actually really really cool
I want to see what it looks like
This thing's actually really cool
Okay
I was wondering if there's gonna be more flails
All right, that's cool
Oh, I got a boss boss down guys
hug
Boss down. Oh, that's what you guys you want me to like make go make me feel better
You guys are sweet
If we tell him to go like instead of this bonfire and fight like the easy guy like he'll be happy again
You guys are sweet. You guys are nice
No, we have to get him away from that encounter because he's looking at me he's turning green
He's like turning fucking orange
All the blood is going to his nose. Get him out of there like suck him out unplug the matrix
so
Let's keep going dude. Sometimes you have to if you've got like, okay
there's been cases where
I'm playing it like with you're at like a friend's or like someone's playing a game
and they're
And they're just they're just trapped and they're just like no I can do it
It's like, uh, you don't have you can like come back later. It's like kind of the it's kind of hard
No, this game sucks. This encounter sucks. I fucking hate this game. It's like, yeah
Fuck he's
They're just like gonna keep doing this and then they keep doing it
They lose over and over again and then you kind of just have to reach over at some point
And you fucking alt tab when you hit like the escape button
And it's just like yeah
Hey, and it's just like dude. I'm sorry. I had to fucking do that and then they go
Oh, okay
Why foods here foods here?
You know what I mean? Like you got sometimes you just have to alt tab the person
And just be like take second and just like think about what's happening right now
And they go look in the mirror and their nose is like big fucking red nose
But you've got to start like playing something like music or something just start playing like I don't like fucking party in the usa behind them
and they'll be like
The hands up they're playing what's going on behind me and then they and then you got them they got you got them out
You got them out
Now here's the problem. I'm gonna go back in eventually
And uh, okay, so I was gonna have to come throw water on me eventually
Okay
Interesting
Okay, it's coming from the roof of that building
Okay, weeping peninsula map found let's go. Let's go
I sense a
little thing to increase
my flasks
See, I think I need one more. Oh now it's that guy
Is that gonna hit me if I sit here?
Dang
All right, let's go
Why is this health already on this guy?
Okay, we got a new map is this this is this spot here. What is this?
Very interesting. This looks ominous. What is this?
Siege of castle morn a lone hero fights for his vengeance only to follow the hand of lord godfrey
We killed that motherfucker. So we'll be fine
dessert
Your music is your music. Is that bat music?
That is berserk, huh?
That's the theme song to berserk, oh my god, we have fake fans here
Do we actually have fake fans here? Like you're not a real fan?
Everyone's telling me berserk berserk berserk and then I do the berserk theme song and all of a sudden
I'm like the weird cat puke guy
I wonder if I can use this
Damn it. I can't
Shit. All right. Well, whatever
I am going to use let's keep that one on that's fine
All right. So
Uh, where we at? Let's go
Fake fan. I own the manga
Yeah, that's really cool, man. You own you own the manga
mine's signed
No, it isn't this is a boss
Hey, sorry to interrupt
All right. Don't get cocky just because I have like extra levels for this dumb area. It's not dumb. I actually like this
You got help
germa and the red nose of anger
i'm just like kind of like
Oh my god, I made it a wax right now
Sometimes I look like a wax figurine. I'm sorry. It's like shaving and sweating and like I have my cortisol levels have been high
I've just been like fucking angry
Okay, there's something here it's gonna be like a major boss here what was that you hear that
I just bumped my elbow
What's this weird sound I keep hearing what's going on?
Fire grease I can make a bunch of those too
Remember, why do you kill so many people there's a better way than just violence. Um, okay. Well, here he is
Uh pumpkin, that's a pumpkin head guy
The guy didn't even get to stand up
Have you tried talking to the monsters?
Yeah, i've been going
Like waving and they don't do anything. I keep going like this
And I don't understand. I keep going like
And i'm just trying to wave to him. I don't know. Nobody seems to be like trying to communicate
Get it
They keep walking like kind of forward
And like maybe I hit them in like the face sometimes accidentally if it's not my fault. Like i'm just trying to say hi
Fucking wave at that guy
This game's fucking stupid like i'm trying to wave at people i'm trying not to hit anybody
That actually kind of pisses me off that you can't like just like, you know talk to them
Okay, at least the title of this stream is correct
For the first time in five streams, right?
Oh, hey
Hey, dude
Oh, not again
It keeps happening to me
Wave
Hit him with your sword
Wave at him harder
This is a youtube video stream
Like all of them could be
This is coping mechanism for me not to get mad. Don't you understand?
Contrary to what you guys might believe I am desperately trying not to eat a chunk of my monitor
Oh my goodness. That was a bad move
I want this item
What the hell is going on over there?
Yeah, it's called the big fish eat the little fish
I cut it in just like
Can you imagine there was something like that in like in humanity?
Like, you know the whale sharks that just like float forward just hold their mouths open and they eat like a hundred fucking million fish
Can you imagine him just you're just walking around outside and there was just this thing that was just moving slowly forward with his mouth open
be like
We're just we're just dead
Like this thing's gonna eat us like we're just gonna die. Like what do we do?
We're so lucky that spiders are as big as they are imagine spiders were as big as a house
Well, okay
But what do you do about that for you? There's a face i've not seen before
i'm edgar
Warden of this castle as ordained by lord godrigg himself edgar that you can see how things have turned out
The menials have all rebelled
They gave me good service or so. I thought
But it seems it was all an act
Foul creatures as it said and true enough they're foul inside getting quieter
I'm sorry to disappoint you
But whatever you come here to do castle mourn
Won't hold much longer
Take this by way of apology
Something wrong with my headphones. Why is he quiet? He's so quiet
Give the letter
Oh my audio has been fucked up the whole time
Even if the castle should fall
As commander I must remain
To ensure the treasured sword of mourn does not fall into the hold of the morning
Okay, if you see arena do tell her her father will come for her
Once he's fulfilled his duty
If you see her father
Wait
Where's the where's the money I want I don't want to twig I want money
Where is it?
Oh, I can upgrade my glass
Where is it? I don't know a little twig
It's an item. It's a talisman
Oh will be lost on okay
So if you die with this on you don't lose your rooms. Okay. Well, I found you
Uh, unfortunately, you won't you won't leave
So, uh, okay
Back into the castle
It did not go this way
Anything else over here?
Ah
Just need to take a moment. Okay
Take a cartoon bite out of your keyboard
What does this do for me? This i'm in like a bad spot. All right, whatever
I'm not gonna rest at that because I don't
Wait, what let's see if I can go this way
I don't think i'm gonna rest at that one. Maybe I should have it was a ball joke
You didn't I didn't even realize I could like that. Why isn't he doing it? Do what?
So what you want me to lift up my keyboard and take like a big bite and have it be the
ice cream bar packaging bite
Which is like the corner of the top of the ice cream
I can't do that right now. I'm sorry
I I I already ate a shoe
Eating keyboards
Let's not down that
Wait, let's not down that
All right, be careful. I don't want to something's gonna happen here
Yes, no
Okay, so what's here?
What else
My wife and baby would love to watch you eat your keyboard
Your baby doesn't understand anything besides that. There's colors on the screen
Twin blade talisman
final hit of chain attacks
A lot of cool stuff, but not for me
Okay, that's that
Maybe sensory yeah, your baby doesn't understand what i'm saying
all your baby hears is just like
Um
It's literally all your baby understands finally after like a year or two your baby can like
My ears are developed for me can hear things
Like their eyes don't you understand that like a baby's eyes?
It's like they they can't see
They're like constantly developing their their senses
Mars attack alien
Nothing down there. Oh, is this all that was over here?
No, that's before
What else is over nothing? Let's go should go down. I can't go down
Oh, that's right. Oh nice
All right, i'm stopping
That's enough. What's going on? What's going on over there is what I want to know
Who's over there? Oh, no father gravestone. Of course
I must fulfill my duty
I almost just I almost died. I jumped for no reason and it was the only thing that kept me alive
I actually just died right there
I must take my leave
What is the saying?
fear the blood
eat the blood
Drink the old blood
Uh willem I must go
No, the great you know, what's cool about um the souls games
these actors I feel like
They're they're just so good. There's some I wish I knew who they were
I feel like I don't know any of the other things that these actors have been in
I missed an item what I am
Did I was talking
Whip that's awesome, but I don't want it. Did I miss an item? I actually did
Okay, no more talking
I really missed an item. Whatever. It was a fucking smithereen smone. Whatever it is. It was I don't care
It was a smithing stone
Dude, tom brady voices the main character
Oh, yes elden won
You never noticed they get really close that when it's like a celebrity that doesn't really like do voice acting or act really
They're always super close to the microphone and they're just talking loudly
It's like loud talking is not acting but that's what they do
Oh my goodness. I can't believe what we're looking at here. No, you're not gonna get that by me
Loud talking always equals acting
Okay, I got 8200. Are you guys ready for me to one shot kill?
this
Oh, that's I gotta make sure I have at least one of those every like every 30 minutes or so
So the editors can make sure they get something funny like a clip like a funny clip or not
I gotta do like every like 30 minutes. I haven't done it in a while
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay
Anything else over this way? I'm just checking
Shut up
What are you doing over there? Shut up
Whoa, that's the edge of the world. Oh, I got a somber smithing stone
Can't go on the horse something over there
It's
Crab the huge crab
in every fucking zone
But I mean that's not even surprising anymore. It's not even surprising to me anymore. It's so bad. I'm gonna do it
Why should I do it?
I don't think I want to do it on camera. So i'll hide
No, i'm not gonna do it. Fuck
No, never mind
Is this gonna kill me?
Be serious. Will this kill me if I go down? No, I think it might i'm gonna go from the bridge
Oh those those actors are so goddamn funny
That was so fun
I don't I think I want to level up first
Yeah, let's just kill these guys until we level up. What do these guys give us? It's not very much
It's not a lot who has some decent amount of souls. It's too much to go die at a boss with
Because i'll probably die like once choice
I just need to get some souls here
Is that an item up there?
No, all right, you're gonna kill the guy this is literally the easiest boss in the game
Yeah, but I okay if it don't say that because then if I lose then I look bad
I'm that i'm not that far. I'm gonna kill the big giant guy
I don't know, man
Okay, there's 11 000 I got one of these
Boink
All right, getting there almost there almost there almost there. All right, i'll go kill him. Fine. Jeremy, please the boss is like pinwheel
Fine, okay, it's pinwheel. The boss is pinwheel
Fine, i'll go all this for a single level. I'll go get him right now. He's pinwheel. Well, let's show him. Let's show him his boss
It's literally pinwheel. All right. All right. All right. All right, relax. I'll go get him
This boss is the easiest boss in the game. Okay, fine
leonine
Misbegotten
I wouldn't call this guy pinwheel
This guy ain't fucking pinwheel
This guy ain't fucking pinwheel. This guy's got moves
Good thing I have like a good. Yeah, i'll get him. It's not that bad
Like I also I like where where
those
Fucking sacred tears. I thought they were down here. All right, relax
How have I only found one the whole time? I played this game. It's impossible
All right. Now i'm like trying too hard
Bump heads bumped into each other. That's weird
Crafted blade great sword
What the heck is that?
strength
Oh my goodness gracious
This looks like the shit that you pick out of your leg if you've been when you go into the woods
The things that like are just attached to your body
What does it move? Is it a block? That's pretty cool weapon
Uh, yeah, that guy wasn't that bad. But I mean I i'm obviously probably five plus levels leveled for it
Look with churches
I mean church I need to find a church
I mean
bro
Can I just get another one of those?
All right. Well, that's cool
That's a really cool fight
Nothing too. Nothing too fancy schmancy. Just gotta kill them
Okay, uh, so let's go from here
Is this a church right here? That looks kind of church ish
That looks kind of like the top of the church
Either that or here
That's not a church
What where's the church? I'm looking for a church. Is this a church?
They're marked on the map
That looks like a church
This looks like I there's no church here
It looked like ruins
This looks like it i'm gonna go to two
Why does everything look like a church to you?
Everything doesn't look like a church that I mean like if they're all buildings
That looks like a church
We're gonna check it out
Oh, let me go talk to um, what's that? The the girl?
I gotta go talk to the girl that I gave the letter
She's like give this letter to my father. He's right here, right?
There was she right here
It was right here somewhere
Is she at the rampart or was she at the gate?
Where is she?
She was back here, right?
Can you just take a shower?
Don't tell me when I need to clean. Okay
I assure you I am very clean
Do I have to really go to the other one?
Remember you too stressed out today. I'm fine run and jump. I said I just did that
She's right here. Where is she? Where is she? Isn't she right here?
I thought she was sitting like right over here somewhere
Wait, what?
She's dead
You mean she's dead
Somebody drop a sword on her from up there
All right. Oops
I'm gonna be in big fucking trouble
Frank I was never fucking on the rampart. Please you gotta help me
uh
Dad was over here. Dad was like up in the tower up there. She should level up. I will
Where was the dad up on the I just said my object permanence especially with the game with this 500 million places to go
Is he was up in one of these that one there? I think he was further in
so yeah, he was actually like inside the castle and
Lift I remember him just sitting on top of one of these things
Here, but like the rampart has a gotta go through and up to the left tower
Does this go up? I'm not in the castle right now
I remember doing this and then he's like up in there
I
Don't know. I have no idea where he is
You can't remember the dungeon. He just cleared it. No, dude. I can't because this it's it's so big
There's so much to see there's so much going on
I like it's so hard to remember everything
I have absolutely no idea how to get up there
Like if you gave me a 100 million dollars right now and said in 10 seconds show me on the map where he is
I wouldn't be able to do it. I physically wouldn't do it. I wouldn't be able to
What I should have done is I should have marked where he was
Because the the thing with the souls games for me and this probably happens to a lot of you guys too
is you have like an ever moving window of stuff that you know
and like
It just keeps moving like this and the and all you can remember and all you can do
Is the shit in this line here and it moves with you
So like you'll get through an area
And like you you start here
Oh, there he is. He's on top of the fucking rampart. I know where that guy is and then like a half an hour later
It's like that guy never existed. It's like you can't even go back that far. It's moving with you
So like now I now I remember where he is
Now I remember he's up there. I was gonna get them. It's the fastest way to get that this way
It's like there's an ever moving window
Of like stuff that I can remember in these games
Because remember in the back of my mind i'm thinking about like
All the whiz why do I where's my weapon?
There's so much other side info in the back of my head that I need to remember
That's just here
And they all get mixed up together and putt
That's what the notepad is for. Well, that's what the markers are for, but i'm not using them
Effectively. Okay, so he's like here all the way up there you motherfucker. How do I go over there?
Um, don't die for the love of god, please
Is he gonna die on here and then up we're good, right? Am I going the right way? There's something else here
Yeah, I found something else
Ooh a smithing stone. Okay, so he's like up there
Is he on this one or is he on the other one?
No, he's definitely on this one. This is right
Other way, I never got that item the east corner
He's like in here
What would it be at would he be at the fire?
Is there a ladder that I didn't see?
Bps needed this is not east
This is east
What are you talking about? Not south. I can't I can't go any more east
There's no more east I can go
Even here
He's dead dickheads over there. All right, fucking god. Damn it, man
I thought he was up in one of those like tower things
And there's like so many like roundabouts and like ladders you climb and then jump down and then drop down and go around the corner
It's it's kind of hard to navigate
There's not just a ladder sitting in front of that it's like
Go up climb up and then go around that side and then drop down and then go around the rock around the bridge
And then up and into the right
I can't just she's dead
What does that do?
Kill him. I don't think I want to kill he might show up later
I'm not gonna kill him now go back to her location
Freaking 100 million dollars
I chose duty over my daughter's safety
and
That is how fate has answered
Find them wretched responsible for this
I'll hunt them down and exterminate every last one of them
Rest assured
Arena, it will be done
Find the foul i'll hunt them down. Rest assured
Okay
Oh
Now what is that that's at the end of his little thing there
I don't think i'm gonna kill him
That's it kill him kill
Why would I kill him?
He definitely shows up later. Why wouldn't he? No, i'm not killing him
All right time to go to the church and get my god damn for the first time in history
A flask level up for the first time in history
We're going
to number three
Up here around the left
You should have plus four by the time you go back to really
Enter evergale
the area
market
No, no, no, no go to church. I know hold on
I lost my marker
What the fuck is happening with these markers four?
I feel like i'm gonna die if I drop don't kill me, please
Okay
I'm begging you read the map
That is 2d. It's hard to read this
Can I even get across there from I don't think I can make it from here. Maybe this way
Oh
Let's go
Hey, it's all good to find a way
Oh my god
This was kind of way out of the fucking way. My boys are way cooler
All right
Give me one
mausoleum prowls
Cradling the soulless demigod
Purchase pilgrimage
Sacred tear thank god. Thank the lord
upgrade
Upgrade upgrade upgrade time
Add a charge sacred tear. Let's go. Thank you
Okay
Uh, that's that church. I see a church right here. Is that a church? I think that's a church
How do I get over there?
Any more churches?
in this direct vicinity
would be
I'm gonna investigate these these could be
Four and five that's definitely a church over there. All right. Hell. Yeah, let's fucking come on man. Can we do this?
How many seats do I have that I that was my third so I i have zero now
This is definitely not a church, but that is so i'll have plus three
back here later
What is that? What the hell is that?
I don't I don't want to fuck with that thing right now
No, not yet, there's no heads
Give me another flask thing
This is definitely a church
Fourth church of marika. Oh, yeah
Okay, i'm in a much better position now. I played this whole damn game without this. How did I fucking do that?
Very nice. I'm gonna say
seven and two
Uh
Is there any more?
What about like here?
This looks kind of church-like
Investigate that tree
on the map
This do you mean this one? I think I already was over here
I think I want maybe let me wait and then I need to level up either health or more intelligence. Yeah
Go to the tower. That's here
The game just crashed going on you're gonna come back. Oh, it's the last thing that happened
Hold on if the stream dies, i'll be right back. I hope it doesn't hold on
Uh, that was weird
Um, I think i'm okay. I think i'm okay. Yeah, we're good. That was weird
I spammed the markers so they crashed my game. I'm annoying. Hopefully I didn't lose any progress or anything
Uh, there's an eldering save conflict. Uh, definitely the one from like 10 five two minutes ago
My computer's locking up now. What the fuck is going on?
What the fuck is happening dude?
I pressed
Put a marker down five times and then my whole computer's locking up
Fuck off windows update. No, no, it's just the game just died. Okay. Well, hope I didn't lose any progress
Let's come back
I don't think I lost any progress
Last save was the local file was from a minute ago. So
Let's hope not
Yeah, all right. We're fine. That was very odd
Yeah, I think we're good
So I needed to go down here
Okay, i'm gonna do that slower now
I think I clicked it too fast. So I want to go here
Maybe here
Let's go. Oh, it's a little house
Love love work
People just hanging out on the beach
Something in the water. What's that?
Oh, it's just a tree never mind game's sick
All right. Who's this person?
They all have such interesting stuff well, there's a lantern but I don't I don't need it
Another key. All right. Well, you're cool
Enjoy your shack
Okay. So is this a church up here?
Uh, I have the spell. I don't really need it three crunchies
three crunchies
Crunchy spot
Okay, that's what that is. So then what's this?
I'm really sorry, but I was afraid that you're gonna all people get me
All right. Well, it's not over here. I gotta go back up to like land
I can't like catch it
There we go. That thing is so weird. I gotta go see what that thing actually does
Stop bringing the bell. It's annoying me
All right, what's up here?
What a guy great dragon fly head
What do you got? This doesn't look like a church, but there's something here
our return
Climb you get to play the king's field games
No, not a chance
not a chance
I've seen gameplay of king's field and
It just looks I could I don't think I could do it
It seems like uh, what's that first person?
rpg game
It's a first person rpg. That's really really strange
Nope, actually, let's do it. Wait
Wait, nothing in there
I go i'm just gonna go i'm curious where it takes me lindell royal capital
Dear okay. Well, uh, okay. Where am I?
Somebody lying down
Oh, yeah, you're gonna get up obviously
There's a chest over there
stagger him
Jesus
Stop trying to squash me. Oh my god
This early end game area. Oh fuck I can beat this guy. Let me kill this guy
He probably drops like 20 000 souls. He's gonna fall off
I can't
I don't
He's gonna is he gonna fall?
Who falls first here? I don't know. Okay. Can he fall?
I don't think he can touch as I want him to
All right still not enough
Whoa, I didn't get it. I thought I staggered him I get it
Nope, I thought he was falling down. I'm good
I every time it goes like oh down to one knee. I keep I think i'm staggering you
Your face is red
I'm gonna try this one more time. I'm not supposed to be here. So i'm gonna leave
But I feel like I can do it. Fuck you, buddy
Yeah, fuck off. I'm taking you a freaking free shit
Thank you. Thanks for the talisman. I'm not supposed to be here. It don't matter
I'm i'm out. I got the item. I got the item. I'm not supposed to be here
There's a dead end mini boss
There's a portal on the other side
Does he actually drop anything?
I mean, I know this isn't a boss
These enemies that are like as big as the whole screen
It's just so hard to tell when they're gonna swing it
I'll get him
He's gonna stop being greedy hit him twice and run away. Otherwise, you physically cannot see what he's doing
They fall over. Yeah that but I need to do more damage
You got this tomato boy, shut up
I knew that was gonna happen
He was just too close to the edge. I thought he was gonna do the thing where he pulls up
Maybe i'll try jump attacking
I feel like I won't hit him in the ankle though
What actually worked?
I did that two times
That staggers that much. Oh my goodness. Are you kidding me, dude?
I don't stagger that much
Just made that not even a problem holy shit
Oh my goodness, okay. Well
That's one way I had to do that
That's more stagger than a fully charged right trigger
Well, there was no point in that but it was fun
All right. What was the talisman?
Slowly restores hp by how much?
I think I want that that's cool. All right. What was what was I doing? I was trying to get more flasks, right?
I think cool. Okay
I have a few options
option one
Go kill this goddamn dragon
option two
Go finish whatever's going on and carry a manor because I think I didn't complete it all
uh
option four
Head down here
Big tree, please
All right option five. I'll go to big tree. All right, big tree is at number one. Let's go
I wonder if I should mess around with this too
Oh, there it is the tower
Finally can return to our home bathed in rays of gold
I'm getting my revenge
No, the person said go to the okay. I'm gonna go to the tree
I'm gonna go to the tree. I'm gonna go to the tree. I'm gonna go to the tree
That person that just said dude go to the tree just almost flipped out
I'm going to the tree
Do the bell do the bell. I gotta do the tree before I gotta do the tree first
Don't go. I need to do the tree first. Trust me
I'm a i'm not a doctor. I don't want to say that. That's that's fake
I don't want somebody to be like, oh dude, what happened? What do you think about my bike?
The I got this like pimple on my back. I don't care
All right. I'm here
What's here?
What do we got? Minor urd tree
What do we got?
singing
What's here? There's nothing here. At least not that I can see
Is a go to the pots something on the pots
It's like a time of day thing
Who's that? Oh, this person's singing
urd tree avatar
Okay, let's go
The caster
It's like a tree trunk
This boss is kind of cool
Not bad. I see. Oh my god. Stop talking
Gerva stop talking
Stop talking
Line aside. Haha, stupid
Got it. He knows chat will make fun of him if we use magic
Okay, so that was
Opalene bubble tear and crimson burst crystal tear
Oh
That was worse than the boss. That was scary than the boss
Thank you game. Oh my god
okay
enhances charge attacks for
set sadly reduces hp
Significantly negates damage in mixed physique. What do these do?
What do these do?
flask of wondrous physique
I need a I still need the flask. I don't have
You can make potions with them. Oh cool. Okay
That was cool
All right. Now I gotta go to the tree you go to the tree cool. Okay, so now
That was pretty cool fight
It's time for I gotta get my revenge. I have to get my revenge
I have to kill this fucking dragon before I lose my mind back off the horse
All right, don't get one hit killed
This is it
I'm coming in here with knowledge with more flasks. I'm ready
I have three attempts. We're not angry. We're having a good time together
You and me are hanging out here
Got a little greedy. I thought I was gonna be able to sprint away from it
I thought I was gonna be able to sprint through
God damn man. That fucking insta kill is kind of horseshit if i'm honest
I was trying to do this like just sprint away from it
Okay, so I can't sprint. I can't jump because jumping i'll hit his body when he lands and instantly kills you
You game what?
Because when he like when he comes down, I wonder
Instead of running sideways run like forward
Okay, i'm stuck in his body
It's bad. All right. Here we go. Here we go
Forward straight straight straight straight
God, that's plain. Where'd you go? Don't be greedy. I'm gonna try not to i'm not gonna be greedy
Didn't fucking work that time. I was running straight
Just got lucky and went right between his legs
bad
No, don't do that again
Someone invade him. I'm not playing online
I'm not getting invaded
Get stamina stamina stamina. I'm such a coward. I'm too afraid
Don't freak out. It's bugs all over my fucking body
Oh, man
Get out of here
God that was fucking horrible. That wasn't even that bad. It was just smart
What did I drop?
The dragon heart?
Neutriconic power is available. Let's go
Let's go
Do you're pursing your lips so much they're turning purple
I'll get some blood back into it
It looks like i've been drinking wine for like four hours
The item dropped an item you look cold. I'm not cold. I'm actually burning up
Description is nonsense. Okay. Okay, all right. We cleaned up a little bit
I'm gonna level up and then I think it's time
It might be time. It was an item at your feet. Was there actually?
I mean, this is where I killed him. I don't see one
item item item item
We're
Dragon item. I mean I picked it up didn't I I don't see it on the ground
to the left
I just bait or are you guys serious?
I killed him right here
That's great
Okay, so now
That tied up that loose end. I'm just trying to tie up some loose ends. What time is it? What just happened?
That's fine. Okay, go back to where he spawned. Uh, I already got that item. I
I got that a long time ago
I mean somebody here. I already got this
Okay. So now i'm what i'm gonna do
Is i'm going to relax
i'm gonna chill i'm gonna just
Chill the heck out
i'm gonna level up
And i'm gonna try this guy
Two more times just two more times. I just want to try them two more times. That's it. I promise only two times
I'm only gonna try them two times. Oh upgrade. Oh look, uh, I can't really use them here anyways, but
How many souls do I actually have?
Okay, I have a lot
I spent all yesterday trying to beat him, but we got it done. All right, I gotta get him done
No more complaining
No complaints just
Beat him. I will go upgrade what I can upgrade and i'm gonna buy
Yeah
Yeah, okay
Give me a sec. So can I did I get anything else to upgrade? I kind of want to upgrade this other step
You need like 40 vigor to not get one shot
I feel like my health is kind of low. Maybe I should start focusing on it
I feel like i'm too spread out
Okay, i'm gonna use this eventually so i'm gonna level it up got a
Intelligence scaling i'm gonna get i'm gonna use this staff eventually
In fact, let me see what it is now. I think I can use it get the physique flask
Maybe i'll go check out that new dragon power
Maybe let me do my dumb shit first. Okay, i'm gonna buy this
I'm gonna buy that because i'm gonna use it and I can justify using it
Because I just bought it
Get the special flask
Somebody said it sucks
Because I so I just purchased that so i'm gonna turn it on
Where is it? So I have this one on
So let me activate it. I got 30 intelligence 25 decks
2020 let's see what happens. How do I use it? Here we go
Okay
35 intelligence
It's five plus five to everything
Okay
All right. All right. All right
um
I die though is a huge problem
That's a huge problem if I die should I even fight the boss?
I feel like I should not do that now and just do something else
All right. Here's what i'm gonna do
i'm gonna go
This way like here
either that
Or um, why is it still pointing down here?
This tree go to the earth tree
All right. What do you think?
up
south west
or north
flask
I don't want the flask
up three
Please get the flask
Drew, please. All right, just so chat stops yelling at me. Where's this flask?
They're going to get and stop screaming at me
It's where the
Port hate which was here
What here?
I'm not screaming
It's on the ship
In this ship right here
North of the mist wood like up here
here
Above the mist wood urn tree like somewhere like around here
I guess
Say that
All right, let's go there
That one is number five
Okay, you really need it. You'll be really glad that you got it
I'll give it a go
So this flask if I drink out of this
does it
Does it consume that little bubble?
Is it just a one and done or is it something I can just put on whenever I feel like it?
Sure punishes. Okay
Oh wait, this is also a church
I wonder if this is a sacred tier here as well
Oh, thank goodness. Okay good
and
Flask of wondrous physique you can find crystal tears at the basis of minor urn trees and elsewhere through the lands between
The size of grace you can mix two crystal tears in the flask of wondrous physique this will allow you to create elixirs the various custom effects
Okay
I mean he did all this without that. Yeah, dude. I don't know. I didn't I this this area this game is fucking huge
Uh, I I don't I didn't go to the one church
That had that I don't know. I've just been fucking run around
Don't get angry
Okay. So now what?
Mix wondrous physique
Restores half of total hp
Really boosts stamina significantly negates damage
damage and
and
stamina or damage and
um
damage and healing it's a one-time use
Bubble is basically a free hit
I would probably say
I don't know stamina is pretty big too, though
Healing over time is good. But stamina is also
I'm doing that. I'm doing I can take a hit and I have stamina
All right, go ahead and make it
work
so now
You can use it one time per death
What?
That's insane. So I can take a free hit and my stamina regenerates
It acts like a normal flask
No wonder everybody was screaming at me
Okay. Well, I got what I wanted
It's time to now decide
Do I want to try this guy?
again and get frustrated or do I
Get no i'll get killed and lose the buff
I'll go up from here
I'll check out this part this this place
I'm just gonna i'm gonna just ride in this direction and there's a big thing over there. Let's go that way
There's that area there. So what's over that? That's the I know that okay, but what about here?
I want to go like this way
Let me mark some stuff
Can I cross this?
I wonder I don't know
I don't
Okay, there's a bunch of these things down here
I wonder should I kill this thing? I feel like that that might be a bad thing
We're going that way. Is it safe to get anywhere from here? I think so
ah
Can I make that jump that's beautiful. Yeah, it's a beautiful view
What about over here very clearly is that death probably probably
Reliably
Okay, so how do I get down there reliably it has to be a way to get down there my buff
That sucks
Good thing at least I bought it
That's why I can never use that fucking thing
I never used humanities either because I would use them and just die in five seconds
Because I would just forget I turned it on or it would just be like I would fall off a building or something like
That's why I don't ever use them
I would use them for bosses like if I was about to fight a boss I would turn I would use the community
But uh, oh it turned on the humanity and then I would just like I would like answer the phone
Or I would like put a fucking cheeto in my mouth and forget everything and then just walk off the building
So I can't go that way
So how can I go out here?
I'm imagine i'm gonna okay i'm gonna go from here and i'm gonna go that way
See what I see this does what about the seal?
Wait
Wasn't that just to go back to the wasn't that just to go back to the academy? Isn't the seal to go back to the academy?
I already did the academy. Was it where was it? There were two seals
Oh, that's right. I walked up to one and it was like, sorry
wait
Telling me that I could literally just
I'm gonna appear at the end of the bridge aren't I?
Read my palm
And lift ahead
Or
Are you planning to throw this lady could be replaced with a wooden sign?
Okay, so this is a whole new area
Let's see how this plays out
All right. There's these knights here
Oh, he's beefy
I'm using the fucking tree
That hurts
This dude is definitely a milk drinker. It'd be me
I mean milk drinker. I don't I don't drink milk, man
That's I was just triangulated. I was literally triangulated
One, two, three, I couldn't fucking go anywhere
They like did I was like a fucking
Dirt hole trying to dig into a rock and animal crossing. Where even am I? Oh, fuck you really
All right. Yeah, we're bringing out oleg and not summon anybody here
Well, also I have a question
What is the criteria for summoning people? I feel like it's just like fucking random
What when can you summon when can I how come I can't summon people?
I feel like it's like oh, it's grayed out. Why why?
Has anybody figured that out yet?
Because there's a boss or a statue nearby really
What you're fucking kidding me, dude
Oh
Yeah, i'm talking about these I feel like this is just like kind of random times when you can't summon them
Kind of figure that that means
Okay, let's do this. This is what I wanted to do before before I got rudely interrupted
Fuck off already
Old man just sit on the ledge. I gotta get down. It's too hard to fight on the horse back here. I gotta just fight
I didn't do it. Oh, I didn't have any stamina. He broke it
Tried to jump inside
So wet
Like literally it's like I dumped my hand in the fucking sink like literally my hands are covered in fucking water
Jesus christ
There's a little stone spire nearby you can summon
There's a boss here
This is actually one of the only games where I would wear those like fingerless gamer gloves, you know
I mean the like biker. I want I want biker gloves
I'm gonna get them for next time
Like it would be embarrassing for me to shake somebody's hand right now. I would have to if it was no
No, no shake my hand right now jerma. It'd be like
I wouldn't do it
Racing gloves. Yeah
Is there anything on the it's not one of those map things I can get here, right?
Oh
Yep, yep, we found the the moon katana yet. I have not
We're gonna just keep going this way
I guess
dear any trouble we got
charm a pierced enemy or
You don't get very but you got a cool bow focus immunity now
I'll mark it because I should probably mark all these guys anyways
That's the merchant house, right? That's what i've been saying
Uh, okay. Yeah marking the merchants a good idea. Yeah
Okay, i'm gonna parry this fucking guy and i'm gonna stop being an embarrassing video game player
That begins now
Let's not parry on this
What else is down here? I gotta find a map fragment or something
Are you gonna cast a spell?
I feel like a lot of people are resistant to magic in this game. I feel like i'm running into all the places where they are
But i've been i've happened
I mean my weapon is intelligence. That's like the whole point right a little hut
All right. Give me a map
map fragment of some kind
Interesting. Where are we?
Have you tried cheese?
Formula cheese or whatever that is
Where is this?
ravine veiled village
I'm gonna go let's go up the map fragments are already on you. Yeah, usually they show up here
Like i'm looking for like that's one right there
I'm trying to see this one here
in this vicinity
Well shit
just go up
nothing, okay
for
romundo
I don't know what that is
Remember look like you look like you can't ride a bike
I mean I would get on and I would go like
Then I would straighten out and be fine
You're going
Try the new oreo shamrock with flurry. Is it good?
I feel like that's too much
That sounds like a lot
oreo shamrock
The shamrock flurry is kind of I don't know if i'm into it yet
It's kind of the first like two three sips is like, oh this is kind of good and then it's just like
Does it kind of feel like sludge?
It gets like that like sludge feeling like in the back of your mouth
It has way too much sugar. I think that's probably what it is
What's this guy doing? All right, i'll take the free kill. Why not?
poison
Oh, fuck you. It is poison. All right
Oh, this is a disaster. Okay. Uh, I think I have one of those things I need
It's rot, right?
It's not rot
What is it? It's wait what?
Poison do I not have anything that stops poison? I thought rot was poison. What the fuck is rot then?
Rot is different than poison. Um, I don't think I have anything
Can I craft something?
Blood loss cures rot buildup and it's not rot. I don't I don't have any I can't make any poison blocker thingy
Oh, well, you can outheal it rot is poison, but it's 10. Oh, okay. So rot is like the
How does that look man? What's that sleep?
These guys just throw like all the dust at you
I know hold on. I want to see what's down here
That was probably sleep. That was probably gonna be bad
And nothing can also make soap to reduce poison buildup before it's full
Can I wash it? No, I can't wash it off, right?
Um, that doesn't look like it not after it fills up wait this shit over there. Ah item
Remind me that that's there
I'm at a mana fuck
Cracked crystals, I don't think i've seen those before
Cracked crystal. Oh, that's not good
Lightning grease
My god guys, what the fuck slow down
You're gonna poison yourselves
In midair, okay lightning grease
It's down here. Oh, it's an exploder
We're good ruined strewn precipice
Okay, it was another way I could go in the cave. I think i'm gonna go back in the cave
Yeah, let's go back in the cave
There's something I did not explore in here
Yeah. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Oh watch it watch it watch it. Where the fuck did you come from?
Oh
What do you got?
Well, good. I replaced the one that I was a bonehead
The fucking thing into the dirt
Did I go everywhere?
Wait, there's that item that I wanted to get
On the elevator, let me get the item on the elevator
Which was there, right?
No, i'm an idiot
Right like here. Oh my god. It's not right there fucking come on, dude. Seriously. I thought I saw the light
I saw the light and I thought the light was the ledge. I was like, i'm not I don't want to miss it
It was way further down. It's right. It's okay. It's all right. It's right here
It's way lower. I saw the green light the green lantern thing
Wait, wait, what's going on? That's not what I want to do
What's going on here?
Wait, what's happening?
Why is that here?
Wait, what i'm confused
What's going on?
It was this cave. Yeah
Oh
We're good
Way higher
It looks like another way to go too. Yeah, I can't summon unless there's a boss or a statue nearby
That's it. I did not know that the whole time i'm playing
All right. Where is this fucking thing? Right here smithing stone. Very cool
I wish it was a six
Is that right?
Okay, that's it. So now, uh
Just go out
I want the souls. No problem
So now let's go over here
So should I go up or should I go?
Should I be here? Maybe I should just I wonder
What should I do? What should I do? Should I just go?
Should I go up?
I wonder if I should leave it just go
I don't know
There's two ways to go
I need them. Yeah, I also I need a map to fucking lost like this
10 000 souls. Don't be an idiot. I'm gonna go up. Was there something else that I could do here though? I feel like I could
But i'm just gonna go up
Yeah, this i'll i'll get it later
Not quite but i'll get there
Why did you turn it back? Uh, I see you up there you piece of shit land
Okay, did you drop where did the guy go? That guy where'd that guy go?
Climb this
Jump over there
Somber smithing stone three. That's not what I want
Nothing over fine. Okay, that's it now. Let's go down
Fall fall fall fall
I don't want to lose this many souls. So i'm gonna say no to the fall joke
Sorry
Maybe some of it that was one person that said that
Yeah, the fuck am I even going?
Okay
We're just gonna keep going up
Hey up there
Whoa
Wait, wait, what what? I thought it was an mpc
dude
Oh, no out of juice
Was that the person singing? All right, let's go motherfucker
You and me
Sand throwing sand in my eyes
Nice get over here
Uh, uh, oh, that's a big ruin. That's a huge one. Come on. I don't have sand
Uh, I don't think I ever got it six is uh, just 2,500. I can definitely level up now then
I knew it. I knew you were gonna show up
I just better get knocked off
I'm too nervous to go that way
Let me scale them out
There's gonna be some asshole up here. I know it
I'm gonna get to the top and it's gonna be a boss and i'm gonna kick its ass
I'm gonna help you. All right, don't clear everything out first. There's two of them. Yeah, creepy looking
Where are the slugs?
Oh
Get fucking stomped
Oh my goodness, dude
Yikes
I wish I had my fucking magic right now
That would be ideal
motherfucker
Ugh dick. No, no, no, no, no. I know that's gonna kill me. I'm gonna play very very very cautiously
Dude this little fucking turret bullshit like I swear to god if I had my magic you'd be toast
You wouldn't even live another single second of your life
You're lucky I don't have a mana potion you piece of crap you're lucky I don't have fucking flask
Get the fuck over here
I got it. I got it. That was kind of horrible
Okay, i'm glad I can at least replace some of those
I would have felt very
Over there. It's a big scary octopus thing. Let me check it out. I don't even think about it
I know what you're gonna do
You're not gonna kill me. Okay. Well, okay
Okay
Serpent god's curved sword
We ain't fucking with this guy right now. Nope. We are not
Oh, okay. We're good. Oh my god. He's still chasing me
See you later. Bye
You missed a smithing stone. I ain't going back up there for that. No, thank you
Continue going up. There's a fry on a flog on a log
There's a flea on the hair on the there's a flea on the hair on the frog on the dog on the dog
On the bog on the bottom of the seat
There's a flea on the hair on the dog on the frog on the log on the bog on the bottom of the seat
That's probably a boss up here
I need 17
17 what?
I'm definitely I gotta put points in health. It's it's getting pretty ugly
Do it without leaning forward. There's uh
A lee on the hair on the dog on the frog on the bog on the log at the bottom of the seat
Yep. All right, let's go. Who's there?
magma worm maker
He makes magma worms
Sorry, I've sneezed I those have been bothering me
I have fire resistance stuff on down. I can get some fire resistance stuff
Fire this one's 12
I want to keep this on right?
Fire anything better. I know I have a fire resistance shield. Okay, this is 49
Oh, I can't put it on. Okay
Okay, i'm gonna have to use
This one. Okay, let's try it again
So he just runs around and has a bunch of fire all over him
So I gotta wait don't go in yet. Just kind of let him do his thing
Are you how do you how do you feel about the sorcerer?
Not bad
very slow
What about melee?
Hey, my melee is way better against him. I let him do his thing
On a site with a pillar maybe
Oh, get out
Oh that reach
All right around the pillow. Let's go. Go. Go. Go. Go
It's low and steady
Oh get him under the water
It's genius
Watch that fire dude. Don't be an idiot
Holy shit, he went all the way around
I don't know where the fuck I just was
Fuck that's so long
If i'm on that pillar, I don't like it when you're over here
Get rid of the fire. He's gonna do his little bullshit move where he spins
What no
One fucking hit what?
No way
What?
Oh, I fucking dodged right through it
Damn it, man. I
I fucking had it right there, too
God, what's with the fucking instant kill bullshit?
I fucking had it. Oh my god
What a fucking goddamn eye roll
It looked like I dodged right through it, too
Not as short
I need like 10 more points
Seriously bad again with this bullshit
I'm so fucking annoyed. I can't believe I didn't want to kill him out of the fire
The camera maybe dodged backwards
Out of the fire out out of the fire
I don't dodge into it this time. Oh this fire there this fire over there
You can see
Dude, I fucking didn't what the fuck I can't see
Like I apparently I queued up a heel and I just I didn't have the animation time to dodge
God damn it
Okay, oleg's got to come out at second phase
It's just like when I dodged I I guess I pressed x and it just queues up the heel when you get up
And I was just fucked at that point
And that move kills you in one hit
All right, oleg comes out at phase two
Really? Oh you piece of garbage
I might reset
I
Yeah, I got I burnt through two flasks in the first 15 seconds. I gotta reset
Use the summon. I'm waiting for phase two, dude
phase two
He dies instantly in the fire here
You're gonna do it back to fucking time. Really?
Uh, I didn't mean to press x twice. I'm full tailed
You're not gonna do it three times. All right. Oh, you've got
Slides for a dick. He's going here. We go
Phase two, let's go. Go get him oleg
Come on, my boy
Oleg's no good here
That whole I can't even go to the whole right side
Come here. God damn it. I got yeah
God fucking damn it. I'm in fire too
Oh my god, fuck. Oh fuck me. No
Oh fuck
He caught me again
Oh fuck. Oh fuck
Fuck
Oh fuck
Shit
Porn sounds
Uh, it's just if he catches you with that but like trying to bait
Trying to bait out that attack
You get in and he swings three times. The third time is the horrible one
When you get in close to bait it
It's like you can't it's like look at it's like I feel like i'm gonna fall over
Like looking up at a fucking giant statue
That's the camera is your enemy in this game because when you're locked on you just your eyes are just pointing like this
I'm just like, okay. What when is he coming down?
Let's do this
Try this. I feel like there's a lot of time. I might be able to actually get one of these off
I wonder how much damage this does
I don't actually a lot but it takes a while
Nope
Oh takes too long
Takes too long takes too long
Doesn't really do enough damage either
Fuck on he really is gonna get stuck there
You guys can't shoot
Oh boy. No, no, no, no
I get caught sometimes he does it like three times in a row
Yeah, the magic's not the magic's not gonna cut it
Maybe at the end if I could stay back
Oh my god top to clean the front
This is a sloppy one
sloppy one
All right, so he's trying to see if he like
That's a sloppy one
How much damage is this?
I think it's time for jump r2s on this guy
But it'd be hard to do because he can't dodge through that is he gonna get hit by the hitbox that lasts?
Well, just practice
He's still alive
I just don't know where the fuck I am
Like he puts his hands all the way over his head. So even looking up. It's like I can't see his fucking arms
All right last try last try
Last try and then i'm gonna go eat some food. I need to eat something. I need to eat food
I have to come back refreshed
I waited so fucking long too. My god you guys take an eternity to do moves in this game
I knew you were gonna do that
Damn it. I tried to dodge through it again. It didn't do it
Can't dodge through that when he puts it in his mouth
No, whoa
Really?
Bye. Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye
Where the fuck am I come on?
Dude, what the fuck man?
That's a bad idea man. This is my friend
Dude, what the fuck am I?
seriously
Oh
Dude, I fucking it's so annoying. Like I just don't know where the fuck even is
Walking on not walking on his hands go all the way into the air into the ceiling
Get away from me you fucker
You fucker
You motherfucker
Eat cheese for breakfast you fucking piece of shit. You're gonna get diarrhea in the fucking morning. I guarantee it
No
Oh, oh no. I'm running out of juice
Fuck you. Stop missing
Goddamn it
I'm playing this so fucking safe. You have no idea
You're gonna give me the cheese hall of fame for this one
What? Oh shit. What does this weapon power do?
Fuck you game
I'm gonna smoke that cheese all the way to the bank
Oh my god
That was so scary
I would I cheesed him, but we know what whatever
What was that?
Agma worm scale sword d scaling agma guillotine
What? Let's see
But I need
Wait, I have to sit down
It's not cheese. Well, I I I 50 percent
What the hell
That's actually kind of cool. All right. I mean I I didn't really cheese him I
Pursued him correctly and I killed him. All right, let me level up and then um, let me think about eating something
Some of the moves are follow-up moves
Fire is supposed to come out. Maybe I can't I can't wield it
I'm trying to do a bunch of combinations
Yeah, I don't know. I I think I think it's a twitch problem because this has been happening consistently all night
I this is not an internet problem. Somebody said that other people are having problems, too
Yeah, I don't meet the requirements to use it. All right. So what what else is over here? What else is before I stop?
Let's check out over here
All right. So the plan is i'm probably gonna I want to try to kill that goddamn guy. All right. Here's the plan
I'm gonna give it like three attempts to go fight that other dude
We've got rep again. I'm gonna go try. Okay. I've got more flasks. I've got more health. I've got more everything
I'm gonna let me try it first. Let me atlas plateau. Okay, this is really pretty
Did I get me six smithing stones? I don't think I did
This is four
All right. Uh, let me just touch the bonfire here. There's probably one right here somewhere
There's okay. All right. I'm not gonna do this area. Not yet
What i'm gonna do is i'm gonna i'm gonna go check it out
See if I can do it reliably in like one or two attempts
Then i'm gonna stop stream i'm gonna eat and i'll be back tomorrow I think can I level anything up?
I did have a lot of those uh crushes. Yeah, I think I actually might be able to get there
Four thousand i'll be close
I need a little bit more. All right, let me just get i'll kill some people. Is there people out here like right here?
Just people like yeah, we're gonna go to the farming zone
Just enough to get I want to get vitality up another point
I'm trying to get I want to get like 25 or 30
You're like 18 000
Like that. All right. All right
Knocked me off my fucking horse
Oh, you don't even move that far get out of here
There's 14
Any headphones in because of being a dumbass
Ow
Stop it
Oh my god, they weren't even trying to kill me. They got me
All right. What am I needing now? I need like a thousand two thousand one or two more of these dogs will do it. I think
Let's go ahead and just make this easy on ourselves. Why don't we?
Back up back up back up run away. Whoa easy
Who the fuck are you?
Okay, we're almost there
Almost there
Put on your old uh gear. Yeah, that's a good point. That's a very good point
Let's just respawn everybody one more time
All right, we're giving it three attempts. That's it. I promise three attempts and that's it
I'm just gonna do the thing. I was doing before i'm gonna go for it. I'm gonna I got some extra levels
I can't do it. I'll i'll do it again another time
Okay, I think i'm there
I don't want to get too many
Yeah, i'm definitely all right. Let's go
I'm still getting chased
All right. Here we go. Let's give it a few tries. I'm only gonna try it a few times. I'm not gonna do anything stupid
Are you ready?
We good
I gotta change my flasks
Because what does that he he what man what kind of damage is he doing?
Very nice. Just think I think it's good all around
Would it be like
slashing
He has magic too though
He has that like wave of magic
Hmm
Uh, i'll put the these are good
Something drilling right? Yep
Yeah, that's good
Potency of sorceries restores hp. Do I have any like lightning damage?
Holy damage or something reduction
I think that's good
Okay, here we go. Are you okay? Um, yeah, i'm fine. The game's hard and frustrating
All right
Three attempts and then i'm calling it tonight
And then we'll come back to it probably tomorrow. I need to get some food through the dragon powers. We'll we'll do that tomorrow
I just want to see if I can get get this done. Sometimes you beat him on your first try. I mean
I'm still
I'm still gonna probably leave
Can I open these?
Uh, wait, what's going on?
Uh, do I have to say yes to him? I do don't I?
All right, everybody I need total silence for this
I need complete 100 total silence
We must make merry if anybody does a chat message. I'll hear it and it'll freak me out
No chatting no messages
done three attempts
Let's go
Oh fuck everybody get in. All right, let's go find some more summoning signs. Is that too far away? Nope
I need those signs right now, please
Where are the other ones here somewhere where's the meteor he falls away from me brand get him away
I need more summons. Where are they? I gotta go find them. It's only like three people there
They up on the top of the hill. Let's go
I don't know the hell that was but I don't want to be part of that
All right, there's one down there. All right, let's go see if I can get a couple hits
Where is it? Fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck
Oh man, here they go
What hit me I got like two of them
What?
Aye, aye, dude
All right. Well, this is a major problem. I'm already seeing here
Here's the here's the huge problem. I should not have seven fucking flasks. This is
a huge problem
It's a big problem
Uh, two healing potions. I should not be hit more than one or two times ever
Try it again one hits. Are you gonna get one shot?
Yeah, I
It's I it's weird because sometimes he gets into range and they don't attack me
They just kind of still sit there. I wonder what the actual timing is on having them actually attack
Sometimes it just feels kind of random
Because i'll be close to him and he won't nothing
the npcs
We're all over them and they weren't firing
Shouldn't even need to take one healing potion. Yeah, but you know, i'm gonna take two
Oh my god, I have to say
Yes to him again
Be sure if you get too far away
I mean, I sometimes i'm across the whole map
But now they don't fire if you're in melee range
Accurate he roars. That's how you know, he does it really
Do I have the right armor? I don't really have anything else. That's better
Like the carrion knight stuff, which is just kind of generally just good all around
You should use a rune arc for this. All right, i'm gonna use a rune arc and hopefully it doesn't come back and bite me in the ass
I'm using one right now
All right, if I die immediately to this first thing i'm gonna
I'm gonna be very upset
Okay, here we go. This is the one. This is actually the one we're gonna do it right here. This is the one
I'm this is copium and that's fine
I thought it was gonna hit me
and
What the fuck?
bro
Okay, bro
What are you fucking doing?
Are you fucking
Are you still alive up there? Who's even alive up there? I thought he was still alive
Okay, sorry
Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you. Where is he going?
I don't know which way he went. I don't know which way he went
We're good. I actually have no idea where the fuck he is
All right, dude, I don't know. I don't know
I'm not in melee range and they're not firing at me though
Why they're not firing? Let's say if you're if you're in not in melee range remember it was
Or if I get in melee range what happens I don't understand I'm fucked they only fire during certain moves
My god
Do I have to get off the horse?
Jesus
fucking hell man
Even if I didn't look at chat like I why did you stop shooting because I it's it's you stand so still
Roll them. I i'm on the horse
Get off the horse and roll them
Is that like worth getting off the horse and just like just sitting there and waiting till he fires them
I lost the ruinarc. I I I can't use a ruinarc until I get that down because like I just still don't understand
Is it just get off the horse?
I don't even know what the timing's like either
Shit my horse. How long does it take for the horse to respawn?
Without a heal
I'm hitting him with a fucking stab
Doesn't
That's not good
So i'm gonna get off the horse and i'm gonna dodge those things
Christ
Too far away, I think
Did I get it? I have no idea. I think so. They appear together
Let's fucking summon everybody. Whatever. Well, he's not gonna despawn
What the fuck you're coming for me still that's not cool
What do I do to you leave me alone?
Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right move move men
All right, get off the horse
Huh? Oh fuck
Oh
I can't get on the horse fast enough afterwards, dude
Oh like
Of course you have to do that move
Get back on the horse. Yeah, I it takes three or four seconds
Stay on the horse and dodge the meatballs. Can you though? I feel like they're homing missiles
fucking sorcery, man
Horse mount has eye frames
Could I theoretically okay, could I theoretically get on the horse when he shoots them?
Probably could right at least a second maybe I think that's the play
Dude I in the fucking heart was just kill me
It's so frustrating. It's like dude, like does it have to go home to my body going that fast?
Like I was trying to get it to hit the fucking thing hopping on the horse as the rolling eye frames
i'm gonna try to
dodge the first one
and then
Get on the horse when he shoots the second one that should do it and that should be it
That should be the one that should literally be the one. Oh, yeah, i'm i'm done after this. I would love to beat him
Do this bullshit tomorrow because I don't ever want to fucking fight this guy again
I'll put game charles in
And like skip this boss on my next play for you. You're not gonna do it again. Are you?
Yes, you are
All right, let's go
I got really screwed on the first few hours, too
I'm gonna start so i'm gonna stop and we're gonna move here
Come on, where are you at over here?
Where are they?
Oh, come on. Where are you?
Where are you? Where are you? Where are you? Where are you there?
Whoa more over here
Egads, I mean that's the egads like seriously
There he goes. He's going up
Every time I scream doesn't matter. Okay. Oh shit. Okay. Okay. Okay. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go
I think I can jump
Oh fuck he's coming for me
Don't work. Don't work. Don't work. You gotta
Dodge dodge call don't work
You have to attack him
I I know but I want to get summons
That second phase is so hard for this character because I have I don't i'm not I don't have that many points in like melee
I mean I i'm getting up in there, but then like the meatballs are gonna fire this guy just is fucking hell
Maybe I need more like endurance or something. I don't know
My ass
Are you gonna are you gonna do that shit again you're gonna fire you're gonna do it again, of course you are
Why would you do anything else? I didn't even summon these guys either. I can't even get fucking close
Like this next to so
I can't how how do I approach him?
Like I was gonna go and do melee attacks
It's like a fucking god fucking hell
Okay, I gotta stick with the same strategy because like honest to god
Melee might be a good idea
But hear me out. I fought this guy for four fucking hours and I have I have no idea what those timings are
I have to try to beat him the way with i'm doing the sorcery
It's probably like I could probably do it. Right, but he's on the horse though
I feel like he's moving around so much faster than you could
How do you close the gap if you do melee?
Just horse melee
I don't know like that's hard
Yeah, go forward on that
I gotta get at least one more decent attack before I call it. Yeah patches doesn't do anything. I don't why why am I even summoning patches?
He's a fucking piece of shit. It didn't do anything
Let's try I I gotta get at least I gotta get one more solid attempt
Somebody's gotta somebody's got a fucking backstab on what holy shit somebody just saved the day. All right, relax relax relax
Relax, where do I go?
Where does he come from?
Where does he come from? Where does he go? Where does he come from? Where does he go?
Where does he come from? Where does he go? There he is
Oh fucking come on not i'm not immediately
I need summons too. Oh, i'm in deep trouble now. Come on. Do it now. Let me dodge him both and get on the horse quick
You had to do that. I couldn't
It's fine. It's fine. Oh you fucking gotta be kidding me
Do it do the move, please do the move, please do the move
Asshole do it
Is that it? That's not it
What kill him
Oh
That was too hard it was too much I don't like that one i'm not doing that anymore
I'm not gonna play that one anymore. That was too hard
Too hard for me. I think i've i've done it. I look like shit man. I've looked like shit this whole fucking day
I look like shit
You know what it looks like this whole time i've been upside down and I haven't told you yet
You know what I mean? Like I look like my I look like i'm hanging upside down
Like all that's gonna happen is eventually this thing's gonna flip and you're gonna be like, holy shit
This guy's been live for seven and a half hours streaming upside down
Damn
Oh, that was fucking horrible. What a sick way to fight the glory of the clashes shared by radon
No, that guy was an asshole. I saw that was there was no glory in that afterwards falling star right before our own father
My radon was holding back something of that scale
He was a living legend if ever I saw one
And the path has now been cleared to nokla
Irani's fate would be decided
Let's meet where the falling star bit the earth
We'll take up our souls once more. You should get some food
I don't even know if this guy's name is
Okay
I have 70 000 souls
Let's keep talking. Hold on. We're not done. Let's meet with a falling star bit the earth
My only purpose is to fight for ronnie's fate
So okay, so we're gonna go with it with a star fell to the earth
I'm a final. Okay. What about the pot guy?
Hello there. It was a battle marvellously fought
You are well and truly a champion friend
I on the other hand
Have nothing but a croc one hit was all it will come back tomorrow strong and i'm gonna know i'm not gonna get angry tomorrow
I promise after that
hid like a coward and as such
Oddly stand to face one such as you
You did good pot
I want to know don't you think i've given up who?
Parried him
This whole stream, I don't know who it was
Somebody parried him mighty warrior again in no time like which one of you dickheads did that the body's found here
Who could expect any less? I want to look back and see who did that shattering
Just you wait and see friend i'll grow even stronger
Just you wait when next we meet we should be friends. I don't want to fight anybody anymore
Can't we can I just like go ahead i'll throw in the towel and just like kind of watch the rest of the time
Here like you just take my staff and i'll just like ride on your back and just you play and
Whatever. Yeah, you can be the elden lord. It's like this
It's it's way too much stress. You know what I mean? Like I did my I killed uh radan
When we did I know i'm taking credit for that which is kind of fucked up
That body's found who could expect any less from the very warriors who fought in the shattering
the greatest of all wars
Okay
Just you wait and just you wait
So i'm good. So let's activate this i'm gonna level up and then i'll see you tomorrow
He's too old from software anymore sage. He's too old for from software what?
This fight is so hard
It's just so much. It's like when you your brain like knows what you have to do
You just won't it won't do it and then I just want I I so badly wanted my brain to do certain things
And he's he's a he's a righteous piece of shit. Like i'll be honest
He is a righteous piece of shit. That was
That was just that was rough. That was rough. You guys are righteous piece of shit
I think
Uh, I think I gotta just stack vitality at this point. Let's try to get it to 30
Either that or we put up decks
Harder than sakiro
No, it's different
it's I don't know
it's definitely very difficult, but
They give you enough tools to make it so it you'll get it
in sakiro
Your only tool was being able to hit l1 at the right time. That was it
So, all right, you got these like summons. You got these like magical spells. You got a horse, right?
There's a lot of ways to go about playing
this game
Sakiro you had to do one thing and you had to do it. Well, otherwise it was over
You might kind of be able to get to that staff
Okay, i'm gonna do
I'm gonna regret that later, but fucking whatever
What do I need for some of this stuff?
That staff is 52
Which with my equipment on it's 33
This thing on it's 36
So I could definitely get there
Gotta get bigger to 25. Yeah, that's the plan now
All right. I'll see you guys tomorrow
It looks like it's stressed out. I'm just tired
Helm nerfs your strength that your hp and stamp. Yeah, it does
This is that was that was crazy. That's crazy. I definitely need some protein or something
I'm currently melting
I don't understand what's going on with the internet stuff. I think it's a twitch problem
But if it's not then that's kind of frustrating too
All right, i'll see you guys tomorrow we'll start at somewhere around four o'clock
And we'll go from there
That was elden ring
Art good night
Daylighter
It turned purple
I did
Beat the game what no
Not even close
i'm probably a thousand
Years away from beating it
I couldn't watch any of the stream because i'm playing it myself
But listening to this just sounded like you were on the water park ride from hell
That guy was hell
That was absolute hell
But he's dead and we can we can keep going
Yeah, this this is uh, this has been complain andy
i'm the guy that complains about uh
The game the whole time he's playing it what i'm known for
For all the streams and guy you'll see tomorrow. I'm playing andy part six. That's a good title
Yeah, see you tomorrow at four o'clock. I just love you. Thanks for hanging out
I know these go late
I'm very much in the grind set right now and i'm gonna be back prepared tomorrow tomorrow is gonna i'm gonna lock in
Tomorrow I I I wasn't locked in today. I gotta lock in tomorrow. I'll see you tomorrow. Thanks for watching
Thanks for putting up with my bullshit as always
See you tomorrow