Odd watchers, go back and watch Die Dallas encounter. I didn't say it, you did. Somebody did. Someone. Someone is.
You're gonna die over a handful of chickens.
Someone is.
Hi guys. Say Die Dallas the right way, please.
Um, Daedalus? Daedalus?
Spell it out phonetically for me. Daedalus?
Bugsnax?
Did I say it right?
Bugsnax.
Daedalus. That wasn't Mr. Satan.
No, it wasn't Mr. Satan. That was supposed to be like a half goofy.
Daed- Daed- Hold on, somebody has it here. Daedalus.
Daedalus.
The Daedalus encounter.
Now the Die Dallas is way better.
You guys ever get a word in your head that you pronounce wrong and you know it's not correct?
But you don't care because it's in your your own headcanon and that's how you pronounce it.
That happens frequently with me.
This game is just putting ketchup on ants. Stop.
That's kind of weird.
Ketchup on ants.
Fantasy book characters? Yeah.
Please eat my yummy bugs.
Yuck.
There's hot sauce. Wait, do you actually eat bugs in this game? Is this an actual bug eating video game?
I thought that was just the name.
Yes, you do. You eat insects.
I guess the game is called Bug Snacks.
It's not called like Bug Trapper.
Or Bug Farm. It's called Bug Snacks.
This game is dumb.
All right.
People, this was really requested. And plus it came out like what, last week?
And?
Ten million dollars
off the debt if he eats a real bug.
No, we're in pre-streamed chat. We're talking about this.
I'm not into the whole like eat bugs on camera and scream and cry and stuff when you're eating them.
Why do we think that's cool?
That's so strange. That's like bizarre and terrible.
For this challenge, you need to eat 12 scorpions in 15 seconds.
Why?
It's not like it's horrible. That sucks. It probably hurts.
And the person's just going like, no, I can't.
And then you're sitting on the couch going, yeah, cry. Cry, bitch.
What's wrong with people?
Why do we think that's interesting? That's like horrible.
Why would, why do people think that's cool?
I don't know, man. I don't think I could eat another cockroach.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You'll choke on that fucking cockroach, you piece of shit.
Where's the entertainment?
What's the value there?
Dude, stop. I'm not trying to get.
Jesus Christ.
Eating bugs is, all right. Oh, let's go.
We just got 50 bucks from, well, I say we, but I mean me.
We got, why is everything we? You know what I mean?
Okay. Are we going to, what are we going to do here?
We just got 50 bucks come in. No, that doesn't work like that, Jeremy.
Okay. So what are we going to do? You notice how a lot of streamers and YouTubers, we do that.
Well, it doesn't work. It doesn't work with the money part.
Split it.
No, no, that was 5,000 bits from Lucas, the unknown. Thank you, Lucas.
And Lucas says my first ever donation to any streamer. Thanks for being here.
And then I will always support you.
First ever donation. And it's a huge one.
Thanks, dude. For the massive bit drop.
First ever donation.
Give me my penny.
Your bit rate, what?
One bit per, all right. Can I talk about something for just a quick second?
You just reminded me of something.
Okay.
So there are, there are class action lawsuits, right?
Where some company, I got something in the mail.
Like, I don't know, like maybe a year ago.
And it's like, oh, I just want to let you know that you're the class action lawsuit for this you've been a part of.
Yeah, they won. They won. And you can claim your four or five dollars
from the lawsuit.
I'm just sitting there being like, you're gonna send me a check for like five bucks?
What?
Why don't, why don't we just have these guys like rebuild a bunch of schools?
Instead of sending everybody that was part of the class action lawsuit, like a few dollars in a check.
Just like fucking take like the 400 million dollars and like redo a whole city block.
I don't want the six dollars.
We should be able to vote on what happens to that money. I don't want the five dollars.
I want you to, I want you to redo a school.
Lawyer Jerma Sanders.
That's not, that's not that. No, it's not.
That's communist garbage.
It's not, no, it all, look, it already is doing that. They're giving all of us five dollars.
I'm just saying utilize that money in a better way. Instead of giving everybody five bucks,
let's redo the fucking like a city in, in a state and just pick one.
How do you even, would you, you cash a check for five dollars?
I'm going to go in there and be like, ah, yeah, here's, here's my check that I got for three dollars and 12 cents.
Uh, I'd like that in ones, please.
I'd like that, I'd like that in coins.
I'd like that in pennies.
And the person behind the counter is like, oh, you want that in ones? Oh shit.
Okay.
One,
two,
three. Oh, my fingers are
ow, kind of getting tight.
I almost want to like, I almost want to like mail it back and just write like fuck you on the back.
Right, fuck you, redo a school.
I'm waiting for, get on with it. All right. Yeah, I'm just telling you like we're talking, we're talking here.
That's lawful evil.
That's not.
Lawful evil would be I would try to find a way to get everybody else's check legally.
That's lawful evil.
Neutral evil.
Chaotic based hypers. All right, let's go.
Long story short, when a class session lawsuit pays out like four dollars a person, no, just like,
I'd rather you make like a game show and invite on like 25 people that were part of this lawsuit.
And make it like a 10 million dollar game show and put it on tv. Start the game, I'm about to.
Cole's lawsuit. All right, does this game suck?
Anybody know? It's based cringe. I don't know that that's an oxymoron. That doesn't make any sense.
Yeah, it's good. All right. This is called bugs.
That was a lot of, you hear that like,
uh, it's bug snacks. Ready? I'm ready. It's such a good game. It sucks, but it's cute.
I feel like a lot of you say that about me. So should be all right.
Okay, this is us. Is our map.
What?
Snacks.
Move.
The sir. Oh, that's that's gotta come down.
That's gotta come down. That's way too crazy.
30.
Uh, even more.
This is made in dreams.
It'd be kind of cool if it was actually.
All right, let's go with uh, 18. 18 feels all right.
Keep a little lower.
Still too high. 14. That's good. All right, here we go.
Get a raid.
We raided.
What's up?
Raid from...
Slime. It actually is a slime raid.
Slime sickle.
Slime sickle just raided the real slime.
This is a real slime raid.
Oh, spider.
Let's pick that up.
But thanks. Welcome everybody. We just, we literally just, I just turned the stream on.
So welcome. You do. You're in for a treat.
Thank you. Slime sickle.
Hope you had a good stream.
When are you going to be a slime tuber?
I don't know.
Okay.
I feel like I'm overusing that. Am I overusing like the monkey ass? I feel like I am.
I, I am. I feel like I am.
That's a crutch. That's like a comedy crutch and I'm not going to use it anymore.
Thought I was going to fall. First fall joke of the evening. Not going to get it here.
This game is, I don't even know.
I was going to say good, but I don't, I haven't played it yet.
That was a pizza.
That was a flying pizza.
Is it supposed to do something?
Two weeks earlier.
It's voice acted.
That's what happens when you mix a walrus and a dachshund.
These are Muffet characters.
Snack tooth island.
Oh, how many followers do you have?
I don't even get out of bed for anything less than a thousand.
That was rude.
Was it? Yeah.
That was wicked rude. You're right. Yeah, that was incredibly rude.
Half bug, half snacks.
No!
He missed!
Peace.
Boiling grump.
Are those weapons around the belt?
Soy.
Soy. Yeah, of course.
The three-letter word that creates immediate hilarious reaction.
Press on somebody to talk.
Oh, how about you? How about Clumby Clumbernut?
That's Justin Roiland name for a character if I've ever seen one.
I thought that was a cross around her neck.
I was like, oh shit.
Diplomacy only.
Reader repulsa.
You're already at a second chances.
Kinda sounds like her, yeah.
After 10,000 years, I'm free.
Remember that horse with grumplantis?
It's time to conquer Earth.
You know the best part about that song,
not that song, that intro,
was it pumped you up because that's when the big buildup started to happen.
That like...
I got so hyped up when I was a kid.
When she got out and she starts talking
and that fucking riff starts playing.
Oh, man. Nothing could wake you up on a Saturday morning
more than that riff.
You guys know the Simon from American Idol made that song up?
That's his legacy.
He wrote that song.
Yes, it's true.
Simon from fucking American Idol.
Simon, yeah, you look terrible.
That guy. He like made that song.
Go look it up, I swear to God.
Why don't you believe... I'm going.
Simon Cowell. Yes, he did.
Yes, he did.
Go, go Power Rangers.
Simon Cowell had a ton to do with it.
You know, nobody did the research.
Imagine auditioning for American Idol
and you do go, go Power Rangers
while just staring at Simon Cowell.
Like, you know you're going to lose.
You're going to be one of the joke contestants.
Not many people will get it, but you'll get it.
You'll be like, go, go Power Rangers
while staring right at Simon.
And then like when it's all done, you're like,
oh, I love that song. I really wish I could
give gratitude to the person that had like
produced it and created it.
And he would just be embarrassed and pretend like, snack!
DOV. Outer Wilds.
Yeah, we missed a ton of information.
But it's okay.
I feel like the FO... Is the FOV too small?
What is it at 90 right now? 90?
It's at 90. What about 95?
Did that even change? It's not doing anything.
Uh, there's no FOV difference.
That's weird. Is it broken?
I feel like it's not 90. This doesn't look like
90, does it? Doesn't look like 90 to me.
Do we have to restart the game?
Turn the game up. You got it.
I say you got it.
No.
Oh, this is way too fucking loud.
Let's stop listening to you guys.
Alright, who are you?
What are you doing here?
What happened?
Okay, where's Lizbert?
Mercy killed this guy?
You're gonna have to put him down.
Well, looks like you're not gonna make it, Filbert.
Ah, see you later.
See you in hell. Okay.
There's a bug snack right over there.
Did you get a good look at it?
There's a snack over here.
Scan the bug snack. Alright, new assignment started.
Press F to open the snack scope.
Oh, cool.
Strabby, a very simple snack.
Watch its walking pattern.
They're a little shy, but that's okay.
They just need some space.
Loves, um, coconuts or something.
Okay.
Report to Filbo.
I scanned it.
That one's pretty easy to catch.
Well, me anyway.
Simon Cowell had nothing to do with Power Rangers, you goon.
What?
Yes, he did. Yes, he did.
He, like, produced it.
Its tracks come out of this bush.
The snack trap down there.
He bought the rights.
Yes, he did. He had something to do with it.
He actually did.
Okay, you don't have your snack trap selected.
Hold Q to open the wheel. Snack trap.
Deploy snack trap.
Catch the bug snack.
Alright, deployed.
Oh, I scared him. Get out here and get eaten.
Filbo, what are we doing wrong?
Alright, put that down and hide.
Where is he?
Oh shit, I gotta get it before he gets out.
I got a Strabby.
I'm gonna do all these.
You know I'm gonna do all these voices.
I'm gonna do them. You know I am.
I can't help it.
It made noise. I have to.
Here, have a...
Wait, let me talk to you first.
I kinda wanna just push you in the river now.
What the fuck?
Don't eat those.
Poison.
Alright.
But I wanna do it
as if you were birds.
You're my baby bird. I'm gonna chew it up
and I'm gonna spit it into your mouth.
Are you into that? You okay with that?
You don't have your snack trap selected.
Alright, we need to get three bug snacks.
You're a monster.
Okay, let's get three bug snacks.
There's definitely gonna be some in here.
You see any strawberries? Alright, I see a peach snake.
What is that?
Alright, now go in there.
Got it. It's a Ruto.
Scan it. Oh shit.
Alright, now we have to get another...
Two more.
Didn't scan. You soft-locked it.
There's no such thing as a soft-lock
in a bug snack game.
Oh, up there. Scan it.
It's a green lollipop
that latches onto snacks and traps
with its unsettling long tongue.
Alright, how do I get that? Is there a way I can get that?
I need two more.
How do I get them?
I need a tool I don't have. Oh, alright, cool.
I'm into it.
Wait, there's another one. Alright, hold on.
I can scan it. Scan this carrot now.
It's a carrot. Burrows into the soil
when it's scared. Alright.
Put this down. Put this in your
field of view right there.
And hide. What?
What are you doing? Give me that back.
How do I get that?
Give me this back. Why did you do that?
What? What does it say?
Press E to get it back?
E, retrieve. E.
E. You're lucky I don't have
a fucking gun. Alright.
Get out of here.
Got two Roodles. Let's get one more.
Does this guy like Roodles?
What kind of food does this guy like?
You see anything? I don't see anything.
Oh, he hates them. Well, I'm sorry.
Beggars can't be choosers. If you tell me,
go get me food, but tell me what you don't want.
You don't give me the specifics, like your dietary
restrictions. Like if you say,
hey, go pick up a bunch of food for me. Alright, man.
You into, like,
you into peanuts?
Yeah, sure. Wait, no.
Let me redo that. Reset.
Three, two, one.
It's like if you got, like, hold on. Reset that again.
In three,
two, one. Okay.
So, like, if you were to order food for somebody,
and they said, get whatever, I don't care,
and then you come back with, like, a bag of peanuts, and they go,
dude, I'm allergic to peanuts. What the fuck's wrong with you?
It's like, dude, you should have told me what you were allergic to
before I went and got food.
Sign it. Ship that. Close it.
Cut point right there.
Thank you. Where's the joke? No, it wasn't a joke.
It was just, like, a cool reference to, like, cut to.
Alright.
I'm gonna feed this guy.
Mmm, carrots.
Oh, he's gonna have carrot legs.
That's a family guy.
No, it's not a family guy.
Why would that be awesome?
That would be terrible. That would suck.
Alright, well, is there any more rootles or strudels?
Ah!
Alright, that's the path.
Go ahead. Alright, place that. Hide.
Come on out.
Alright, let's move.
Is he gonna have a strawberry leg? He is.
Why'd I get that close?
Isn't one of the gremlins in Gremlins 2 like this?
The vegetable gremlin?
Oh, I'm here to investigate the bug snack.
Stop playing this fetish game.
Get out of here.
Alright.
Let's put this away.
You're running pretty damn fast, dude.
Alright, what's the right hook button?
Why not?
Who knows?
Maybe she will be there when we get back.
Is this the actual mayor?
Or is this a terrible
Halloween costume?
Like you're the mayor of Flavortown
and you're just in a white t-shirt and shit.
But you get to make the Guy Fieri joke
every night and people laugh at it
because they're like, oh, that's funny.
Okay, I get it, right?
Alright, through here.
Yeah.
Hahaha.
Why are you playing terrible games two days in a row?
This is, um, excuse me.
People love this game.
This is like a really popular game that people love.
Look, I accepted
yesterday, but not today.
Is that Chris Metzen?
It is. That's Chris Metzen.
That's Chris Metzen.
He's like, he gave his voice to the game.
He's a blizzard.
He clearly says
Wumfest.
That was weird.
Ketchup?
There's a hamburger bug.
Wait, there's hamburger bugs.
Bunger.
Alright, press on a nearby sauce farm.
Alright, let's get some sauce.
Ketchup.
Alright, fill it up. I have, how much ketchup do I need?
Might as well fill the whole thing.
Alright, now lower the
Bunger into the pen.
Come on over here, Bunger.
Bunger! Get in there.
We get to split this, right?
Bunger, Bunger, Bunger, Bunger.
I love this cheeseburger guy.
Alright.
Alright, check on Philbo.
Like fell down here, right?
They're like Pokemon.
Can they fall down here? Where is he?
Wait, scan that thing. Yeah, scan these.
Alright, it's a french fry bug.
Climbs onto high walls out of reach, but will come down
if it smells ketchup.
Hold on, let me do this right.
Got a fryer.
Alright, what about this thing? Something in here.
Wait, what was this one? Scan it first
before I catch it. It was a bush.
Alright, get out.
Tasty enemy fryer.
Alright, there's a burger snack.
Knocks away traps. It also tackles anything
covered in ketchup. Wait a minute.
Does it now? Does it now?
Come tackle this and
break this guy out of here.
Bunger. Hey.
Get over here. Check that out.
What's that? No!
We went the wrong way. I can't catch him?
Wait, give me this back.
Alright, cover that in ketchup.
Oh my fucking god, you idiot.
Alright, hold on. I'm gonna get this.
Alright, Bunger, this way.
Bunger, look.
Check that out. No, no, no, no.
Wrong way. Come back here.
This game is fucking dope.
Get back here.
Yes, yes.
Now go crash into that.
Here we go.
Oh, snipe.
I didn't scan him. Oops.
Shishkebug. Wait, there's a shishkebug over here.
Once this pest hides,
it won't come out of hiding until it's forced.
Yep, alright, cool.
Let's get this guy again.
Wait, he's pretty stupid. He might just walk into it.
Oh, stupid.
Break him out. Why can't I pick up
the burger bugs?
You're a stupid. Why am I stupid?
Alright, where's Philbo?
He fell off this bridge.
Hey. Oh, very nice.
Wait, there he is.
Do you want some food?
Need a different trap. Okay.
Okay.
I already got two of them.
You want some?
Got it already.
Oh man, your food has already arrived.
Your food already arrived.
I gave him a weapon.
I got those too.
Oh, he wants two of these?
Are these tomatoes?
They have tomato, garlic, butts, and beef bums?
Beef? I don't know.
They look like they're garlic and beef and mushrooms and bums.
How do I get them?
Okay. You got the bug net.
Now you can pick up bug snacks when they're stunned.
Really?
Oh, shit. Let me go.
Catch this thing with the net.
Where's the net?
Oh, you don't have to even equip it.
Alright, so how do I stun you?
How do you get stunned?
Get out of here.
What else? I had to set him up scarecrows
to give him something else to tackle.
Now look at this net that you just found.
Oh, alright.
Look at this net that I just found.
Okay, I get it.
Hey, how do I catch him?
Not on me!
Idiots!
Have you ever tried to catch
a real life superhero?
Have you ever used a disguise?
How do I catch this?
He didn't tell me how to like stun him.
I just rammed him to him.
Did I not put his head?
Hit him.
Wait, it rammed into like a pole.
Oh, that didn't work.
Alright, Bunger.
Into the wall. It didn't work.
Ram another Bunger.
Bunger versus Bunger.
Bunger.
Sounds like a shitty law firm.
Had Bunger and Bunger.
We take your case dead serious.
Alright, hit him.
Come over here. PvP time.
Go get that. Bunger.
Bunger! Bunger!
I don't think this is going to work.
Over there. Into a tree.
Smash into that tree.
Alright, Bunger.
Bunger? Okay.
Bunger! No!
Out of Bunger.
Here you go. I got it just for you, man.
What? You should get a hamburger head.
Justice is served.
How come when they get
bit down on, they don't go like...
Oh!
Well like...
More realistic that way.
Let's get moving right away.
You're a pretty good hunter.
Like Philbo said.
This is a kid's game.
Yeah, but I mean...
Is it?
It is.
Well, it's an E for everyone.
Is Mario a kid's game?
I disagree. I played those cube
levels in Mario Sunshine. I disagree.
Wait.
Will he get Bungered in the face?
Okay, follow Philbo
to Snackburg.
What's a squeeve?
Gold camera.
That thing's worth a lot of money.
Is it like a dweeb? Like you're a dweeb.
That's my friend you're talking about.
Don't worry. We'll get our revenge.
Slow and meticulous.
What do you know?
Here. Eat this. No!
You don't get any. I'm not giving you any food.
I haven't seen a new face in like forever.
I'm Bethica Winkle Snoot.
And I know everything about everybody.
It's pretty cool toupee hair.
Uncombed toupee.
Alright, can I help you?
I love your snack scope.
You and me are totes twinsies.
I bet you've seen lots of great stuff.
Let me take a peek at your journal.
No, it's mine.
You lost your journal?
No big deal. You can borrow
one of mine. I keep them in my
cave. Bring it here.
I'll show you how it's done.
Pick up the journal.
I got the journal.
Are we playing solitaire?
Wait. You're playing solitaire
by yourself in your house?
What filbert is the squeep?
Wait, you're gonna call somebody like a
squeeb and talk a bunch of shit and you're playing solitaire
on the ground in your house?
That's not okay.
Let's get a photo of this. She's projecting.
Hi, I've got the
diary and whatever it is.
You're a belly?
Oh, it tells you what you've caught so far.
This is cool. This is your Bugapedia.
You can scroll
through all the bug stacks you've scanned
with your snack scope.
You can also check on their likes, dislikes,
and hints on how to catch them.
Now check out the other pages to see what
they're all about. Loves
beating human hearts and
is afraid of bumper bug.
Ooh, what's this?
Loves apple juice.
Loves, that's like tequila.
Whatever that is. 4900
calories. Why are these so many calories?
30,000
calories? You'd be shitting
for days. 36,000
calories. The human body
doesn't even have like 2,000 calories.
You take in 2,000 calories
a day. That's like your total calorie count in your
body. What is this?
This is your grumpedia. It's like a
Bugapedia but for grumpises.
This blank space will fill up with your notes
once you get to know each grumpis better.
The self-appointed mayor, he seems to be
trying his best. Right, he loves
this person.
He hates you. Why do you hate her?
Who do you hate?
You hate everybody.
A sharp-tongued socialite snoop,
my bestie apparently, likes gossip,
photography, and breaking and entering.
Why do you hate him
so much? Have I met
this person? Oh, Lizbert. Okay.
This is your clues page. It's where you'll keep
all your progress in finding Lizbert. I don't give
a shit about that. I want to get interesting
bugs. There's clues here.
A report on Lizbert's
discovery of bug snacks.
What's this? This is your quest list.
You can get in-depth info on all
your ongoing quests. You can also
pin a quest to keep it visible while you're walking
around.
This is your snack pack. It's where you
keep the bug snacks you've caught.
This is your map of Snark-
Snarktooth. It's a map.
This is your list of
tools. Just a way to keep
track of all your snack-catching gear.
You thought it was gonna be another one.
Oh, alright. Now what?
Everything you scan with the
snack scope winds up in the journal.
I have more for you to do,
but Wambus is scaring all the snacks
away. You'll have to come back
later. Until then,
you should get Bilbo out of here.
Okay. Bilbo!
I'm ready to follow you.
Let's get this over with, buddy.
Ding! Crit sound.
Why was he bent over like that?
How come there was never a
slingshot added to TF2? Don't you feel like
that could be like a scout primary that they just
didn't capitalize on?
Not primary.
I think it could work.
That's the huntsman. No, no, no, no, different.
Different. Alright, so do
we live in Snackburg?
When do the side effects of eating those bug drugs
wear off? Cause he still has those
body parts. Does it ever wear off?
Or is that just who you are now?
Why don't I interview you?
This is where I say
here we go, we're recording.
I turn it off, and we just have a little conversation
and I say yeah, maybe I'll
use that somewhere.
Uh, hey, who are you?
Big quotes.
Deputy Mayor.
What else? Why did you come to Snack through the Island?
Simon Cowell? What?
Hey, how do you feel about bug
snacks?
Great. I mean, they taste good
and they make everybody happy
so what's not to love?
Until you come down.
What do you think about that?
Lizbert and me go way back. Lizbert was
is awesome.
She always knew what
to do and she brought out the best
in all of us.
Ooh, Mitch McConnell. Oh, what?
Why? Does that make any sense
right now? Okay.
So that's how you became mayor?
You're a deadly side effect.
His eyes are like all purple
and red.
Okay, why didn't it last long?
Isn't that how the dinosaurs died?
I think we're done.
I feel like that thing's gonna pop off and shoot me in the face.
Okay.
Alright.
I just turned his leg into
a piece of meat.
This is just fucking terrible
experiments I'm doing to these people.
Okay, we're gonna find Grimble
or go back to Becca.
No, Becca sucks.
I want Grimble.
Let's remove one of those letters.
Big fan.
This is locked.
All this stuff is locked. How do I break into people's things?
Stop right there!
You violated the law!
I go to the beach?
That's not the beach.
Is it? You didn't say criminal scum.
Minus two. Yeah, I'm just trying to keep you on your toes.
Alright, is this Grimble?
You're not Grimble.
Who are you?
What's that dog
with the big teeth that does that?
Who is Eggabelle?
Bulldog, yes.
I understand the internal mechanism behind
the molecular dissemination of snack
particles.
This is the Snack-tivator.
Info-ification.
What?
Foot turns into
Strabby. Understand?
Why did you...
Look at these arms.
Don't say...
What am I supposed to do?
Left foot? What I can choose?
What kind of weird experiments to do?
I don't even know what that is.
I don't know what that is.
I just read things. I'm a reader.
Where did you go? Where did you just go?
Oh, this is chocolate.
You have more than one kind of sauce.
What's that thing? It's a longnose.
A quibble. It follows things that it
likes. And it nudges them with
its spoon.
Let's take it.
Got it.
You have more than one kind of sauce.
Select your sauce slinger and then
select the sauce you want.
Chocolate sauce.
What does that weird lady want me to do?
I'm going to do something.
Look at all these...
strawberries.
There's a lot of strawberries here.
Scan. I already scanned the strawberries.
There's a floating macarito.
Oh, shit. Catch it.
This is their nest. I'll get like ten here.
Oh, crab.
It's a crapple.
This curious snack likes to dig things out
of the sand and bring them to its lair.
Oh, it's an apple crab.
Okay, so
can I catch you with this?
Get the crab? I mean, I'm going to try.
Maybe I have to net him.
I kind of want one of the dancing margaritas.
Seashell. No, no, no, no.
Wait. Get in there.
Does it like chocolate? Who likes chocolate?
Anybody like chocolate?
He loves chocolate. Hey, put that down.
Wait. Okay. I can get him.
Chocolate and then
crapple. You pick up seashells?
Oh, wait. I can. What can I do with
the seashell? All right. Get the
wevo.
Can I have six? She sells
seashells by the seashore. She sells
seashells by the seashore. She sells seashells
by the seashore. Almost.
Sometimes I can get it. What's that?
Put a ball in there.
Find grahamble on the beach.
Wait, wait, wait. There we go.
A snackery leaps in and out of the ocean
and needs to be caught in mid-leap. I don't
have a way to get that.
Wait. Can I like frisbee this
and hit it in the head? I probably can.
Damn it. All right.
Where's grahamble by the beach?
Wait. Do you like
chocolate? What's that thing?
It's a pineatella
that burrows into the sand to
hide. Perhaps another bug snack could dig
it out. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. Okay. So the crab digs that out and I can
catch them both. No.
What do you like? Loves
chocolate. Okay.
Here we go. I'm going to use you for
my own benefit. I'm going to coat
this with chocolate. No. Get away.
Get away.
Dig him out. Dig him out.
No. No.
All right. Well, whatever. I got you.
Oh, and my inventory's
full. Can I eat them myself?
Shit. I got to feed somebody. What do I do with
the bugs? What do I do with them?
Can I eat them? You have to find
grahamble. Find grahamble near
the beach. Who the fuck is
this person? Near the
founder. There's grahamble
and then there's somebody else.
Wiggle. This is KK
Slider. I can't wait for like the
quack, quack, quack, quack.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but...
You're going to eat those?
Inspiration
is so hard to find.
I just have to sing
wherever it strikes me.
I feel that way too. I like this character.
Maybe it could strike you
over there. Oh, I'd hate
to go alone.
Won't you join me for a
long walk on the beach?
Like date?
Of course, darling.
It would just be you,
me, and
your delectable Strabby.
Singing the night away until
we drift off to sleep.
SpongeBob and Mrs. Puff.
Sorry.
Every time I go to sleep... Like artist depiction of
a new...
So no to all that.
But the date's still a maybe.
Very well.
I will go and
take my inspiration
home.
Mmm...
Tom, my dear.
Calm down, little ones.
Wiggle means well.
She just don't understand what I do.
Who are you?
You best turn back. These little ones
are my kin.
Well, that's a relief.
Sorry I'm short with that.
I'm Graham Wiggle. I'm an aspiring
Bugsnax breeder. Not too keen
on going to town, but I'm running
out of room back to my barn.
Trouble is, some of my snacks went
missing. I'm not going back
till they're all home. If you want
to help me, then I got a friend
to introduce you to. Follow me!
Bugsnax. Make him eat one.
Oh, shit. I can't
carry anymore.
See that, Strabby? That there's
Sprout. I've been training him to follow my
pointer in his buggy ball. Monkey ball!
We were in the middle of training. See if you can
guide Sprout back here to us.
Have a ball. Alright. Guide the
buggy ball through the course.
You got the buggy ball. Switch to it with
Q. Buggy ball?
Guide it. This is so cool.
Keep going. You can do it.
You can do it. Oh, that's
the worst part of the Wario level in
the N64 Wario Kart. I know.
Nice work, though. Keep going.
Nice. Keep going. You're almost there.
Up there.
You did it. Come on. Yes.
Bug, I did it.
Peel bugs.
Eat him. Wait, and pick up
this guy and eat him?
But I have...
I have too much stuff in my inventory.
Do I have a storage unit or
something? How do I...
How would I...
Wow. I want that one.
Release them. Release them. No.
They're mine. Feed the dude in
town.
Alright, I'll release...
Okay. I will release
one of each. We're doing it
fair. I'm picking them at random.
There. Okay, now I need to get
three of these guys as his peel bugs.
He said that this is randomly... They're in holes
on the beach. Holes on the beach.
Peel bug.
You eat them. I don't know how.
I didn't learn how to do that.
Is that a peel bug? No.
That's a pinata.
Holes on the ground.
Gigantic bits. Oh, shit.
Gigantic bits did come in. And also,
let's start with
Red Lemonade gave five community subs,
but they were Tier 2.
That's Tier 2 community subs from Red Lemonade.
That's nuts.
Thank you for those. And then
ten thousand bits.
A hundred bucks in bits from
I'm...
I'm Omo89.
Thank you, Omo. Thanks for the hundred fucking dollars.
Jeremy, thanks for all the constant entertainment
throughout all these years. It's impossible to quantify
how much happiness you've provided.
So consider this a small token of my appreciation.
I...
You're never under any obligation to give me
a cent. So
you just hanging out here is enough for me.
Thank you nonetheless and happy to have you.
Now let's kill some bugs.
Thanks for the hundred bucks.
That's a lot of money. I don't see any holes on the
beach, do you? Wait.
Like, is that a peel bug?
Catch lost peal...
It's definitely there. It's like the basketball bug.
That's a peel bug. It rolls up
and hides inside holes or logs. They'll have to
be pushed out somehow. Oh, I know
what to do. Wait.
Oh, shit. All right. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait. All right. Push him out.
Come here. Oh, wait.
Is there a way I can quickly activate this
instead of switching? Or do I have
to switch to it? All right. This one.
Get away from me.
For another peel bug. I like the orange peel bugs.
They look delicious.
Is there a peel bug in there? Nope. Just a squidward.
Number keys are tools.
Oh, okay. Come on over here.
I need you. Come here.
Two. Come on over here.
Outside of memes, how is...
How good is this game?
It's kind of good.
It's just relaxing and
fun. This is a chill game.
I like it. What about Elden Ring?
What about Elden Ring?
I haven't played... I'm not
currently playing Elden Ring. Come on.
I need one more. True. True.
True. What do you mean true?
Do I have to reload the area? I don't see
any more orange bugs. Where are they?
Hello? You only needed
two? No, I need one more.
Look around more, you dingus.
I'm, you know, on the beach. What are you talking about?
Clefairy.
Every time I say a mean comment, I'm going to do
Clefairy. In here?
There's definitely one in here. Fuck off.
Oh, yeah? Clefairy. How does
that sound? Oh, another one. Clefairy.
Oh, another one. I know. You call me
a dickhead? Clefairy.
I can go all day, man.
Elemo Cleary. I've got
your snacks. You got my
snacks. I have the embodiment of the Stinky
Cheese emote. No.
What? How? Explain.
Why do I get that
but I don't get it?
Get out of here. That's bullshit.
I thought this guy didn't like eating these things.
Sauce
Buggy Ball with Chocolate lead to
quibbles to grumble without trapping them.
That's fun.
All right. Come on.
Come on, quibble.
Get over here. Chocolate.
All right. Come get it.
Where are the quibbles?
Quibble. He loves it.
Bacon, bacon, bacon, bacon, bacon, bacon, bacon.
It's bacon.
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum.
Bacon, bacon, bacon.
Dogs don't know it's not bacon. It's
bacon. Get in there.
I used to
love that commercial when I was younger.
I thought it was the funniest goddamn thing in the world.
It was like the GoPro
POV of the dog nose running around going
bacon, bacon, bacon, bacon.
It's such a great commercial.
Began Strips. Yeah.
Show it? Hold on.
Dogs don't know
it's not bacon. It's bacon.
Began Strips
commercial.
What's the right one?
It's definitely this one.
Bacon.
Here you go. It's Began Strips.
Brand dog snack from Purina.
Began Strips. Dogs don't know it's not bacon.
It's bacon.
Wait.
There's a 20. They redid it.
All right. We're going to see if the remake is any better.
Hold on. Let's see if the remake is any better.
Nope. Not as good.
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum. It's done.
No, not even close.
No, no, no, no. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Wait, there's another one?
No, it's not as good.
Is there another one?
Where's the original one? No, fuck these new ones.
I want the old voice.
Do it.
What the hell? It's frozen.
There we go. Okay.
Let's compare the voices. It's much better.
It's bacon.
There you go.
No, it's Began Strips. Brand dog snack from Purina.
Began Strips.
Dogs don't know it's not bacon.
It's bacon.
It's way better.
Is it John Madden?
It actually does sound like John Madden.
What if it was him?
It's John Madden. Get away from my ball.
That's not for you.
That's for the other dogs.
All right. Where, where, where, where, where?
I need another nose guy.
Excuse me.
I can't whistles. You know the one that goes
I can't do it.
But like, you know exactly what I'm trying to do.
Like that.
Come here.
There you are.
Like what I got. A tasty snack.
Let me go first.
I gotta have that bacon. Bacon, bacon, bacon, bacon.
Smoky bacon.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Doesn't it stink? You love things that stink.
Go in there.
Ashley, you're back.
Don't you ever leave me again.
All right.
Where's my money?
You did it.
My kin are all together again.
I'm so happy I could cry.
Here goes.
Ew.
I'm ready to head back to the ranch.
Thanks for all your help.
Sprout.
Is this the ball?
It's really loud now because I turned it up.
Yeah, we're good now.
A little bit lower. We're good.
Is there oxygen in there?
Okay.
Go see what Befika wants.
Look at this.
Cool.
Look at this little happy family.
All right. We'll go talk to Befika.
Throw the sprout in the ocean and never come back.
This guy here.
That guy. There he is.
That's the one.
I'm going good.
And I've got something for you.
I've got a crab apple
for you. You're going to love it.
Oh, wow. That looks uncomfortable.
Hey, come here.
Let's make you even more of a monster.
We have huge teeth.
So is this like the way to show your wealth
in this society?
There's a guy with a bunch of fruits all over him
and vegetable noses and stuff.
Is that kind of like the top hat of this society?
The people that are walking around
with just regular clothes and no fruits.
They're like lower on society.
Wait.
We've got some drama.
You made that man an elite.
Not really.
I had that guy win
a car on a game show.
But he didn't realize
that you have to pay taxes on the car.
Don't ever take the car
on a game show if you're ever on one.
Take the money.
You guys have a problem. What is it?
Let's interview this guy.
Who are you?
Why did you come to Snark Tooth Island?
Why did you not do a farm back home?
I didn't take the house on the game show
like you did.
Thoughts on bug snacks?
What's so confusing about them?
It's Arthur Morgan.
Well eat them raw or
that's the really nice way to say eat them alive.
So we would have been fine on
bug snacks if it weren't for Gramble.
That weepy little
rancher thinks all
bug snacks are his pets.
That's good.
Thank god that's not recorded.
We're good.
Thank god.
I'm so happy
that it didn't get recorded.
What did you do?
You must know.
After that sound happened
I waited about like a half a second
and I went
It was disgusting.
Worse?
Well that's why I'm glad it didn't get picked up.
It's fun to talk about it
but it's not fun to live it.
Okay
snooze boring.
Thanks for your time.
What is this?
Wambus gave you notes about
a strange device.
Strange device
now we're getting intriguing.
What the heck?
What is this?
Let me see.
An activator.
I have this?
Where is it?
Okay.
The door is attached to some ancient mechanisms.
It looks like
it might take at least three grumpuses
to activate these.
Okay.
You know what's funny?
It doesn't matter what game I'm playing.
I always think it's funny to look over here
and say
why are you playing this?
I don't know. Why do anything?
At least a few times
I'll look over here and just see
why are you playing this?
I want to make this video games release
and I play them when they come out sometimes
and I just play games.
I don't know.
Why are you still playing this?
This is another good one.
I came back from a shower
and went out with my friends
and said why are you still playing this?
I don't know man. It would be nice to go out
with your friends, huh?
I'm trapped here.
You need help.
Go outside.
That was everyone last stream.
Yeah, that had to have been the most
ever.
Of the like why are you still here?
You're torturing us. We don't talk about
yesterday's stream.
Yesterday's stream.
What's the
not breaking
bad
what's it called?
Big Bang Theory.
Math, science, history. It's all of the history.
It all started. That doesn't make any sense.
What am I trying to say to you guys?
Isn't there a line in the
Big Bang Theory that's like
oh history but
Ford is a mystery or something?
It's like a song. What we have here
is history like Ford is a mystery.
What is it from?
That's from Kung Fu Panda. That's from
Karazhan. What is it?
Math, science, history unraveling the mystery.
No no but there's another one.
I made it up. No I didn't.
Yesterday was history. Tomorrow is a
mystery. Yeah what is it? Who said that?
Like Mark Twain? Who said that?
Seems promising to me.
All I need to start off is a root
and a fruit.
It's Kung Fu Panda.
Another fine day behind us.
Okay from Kung Fu Panda when
whatever the snake says that.
Fine day behind us.
That was a second video. The second
Jerma video title. Wait what?
Is that where his memory is coming from?
That's a video title.
And I thought it was
the intro to the Big Bang Theory.
These memories are
insane. Okay so wait that was just
a second Jerma title?
It's from a thumbnail.
Wait it's from this one.
Wait wait wait wait wait wait.
I need to see.
This video is called
Yesterday is history. Tomorrow
is a mystery.
It all started with a Big Bang.
Oh boy
oh boy. It's not from Kung
Fu Panda. What are you talking about?
It's a title of one of my videos.
Okay plant a root
bug snack in the garden.
I missed all that because I was like having
trouble. Alright what am I doing?
Plant a fruit bug snack
in the garden. Okay I gotta plant fruits
in the garden. Where's the garden?
Another fine day behind us. Quiet.
Where's the garden?
Is all going well?
Where's the garden? Garden?
Alright garden. Garden Grove.
Alright I gotta go to Garden Grove.
Snackberg. This is Garden Grove coming up here?
Nope. What's this?
Garden Grove? Garden Grove.
You went right past it.
Wait the garden. Not this.
We gotta talk to you anyways.
Okay.
Jerma the fucking link. Jerma the fucking link.
You guys need to calm down
before you get me angry. Link.
This is from
Kung Fu Panda.
Yesterday
is history.
Tomorrow is a mystery.
But today is a gift.
That is why it is called
the present.
Oh I didn't do the second half.
I stole that from
Kung Fu Panda. No I didn't.
I remembered it from the Big Bang
theory but I actually remembered
it from the title of one of my videos.
But it's truly
from Kung Fu Panda.
You understand? Scan six
types of bug snacks in Garden Grove.
Got it.
I already got that one.
Who am I missing? What's this?
Candy Patch?
Apologize. Why?
Some bugs only come out at night.
So it's kind of like Stardew Valley fishing.
That's cool. I'm gonna
do this. What about in the cave?
I already got the fries.
I already got the burger.
Oh and that's you. Okay.
Um how do I get any other
bugs to come out?
Wait hold on. Oh that's a different one.
That's a white strappy.
That's a scare snack.
Okay so it scares away the snacks.
It's a poop pile.
Buried bug snack. These bug snacks have been
planted in the ground like crops.
Is that a hot dog? Oh my god.
It's a hot dog.
I need one more. But wait I want to get a hot dog.
I love him.
I love him. What's wrong with him?
He loves ketchup.
Okay. You love ketchup so much. We'll go over there.
Get the glissy.
Glissy. What's a glissy?
What's a glissy? Glissy?
I want this thing though.
What do you like? What are your interests?
You like chocolate? You love
chocolate. Well I don't think I even need to get
that. It's ketchup.
Hey a white strappy.
Where do I go?
Okay over here.
Do I pick up one of the poop guys?
It's a pickle.
Hinkle. Oh let's dig him up.
Is he dead? No I don't want to go to
Flavor Falls. That's a killer.
Oh man. He knocked it out of the
park man. We're at a joint.
Oh that's a killer.
Hey you guys know that
I've watched a few diners drive-ins
and dives recently.
And he's really trying to get his son to take over.
I don't want to fucking do that anymore.
He keeps like putting his kind of older
son into the camera and stuff. It's like
oh this is my son Hunter.
And Hunter's like oh man that's delicious.
Flavor Town. He's like training his son
to take over the business so he can stop doing diners
drive-ins and dives. It's actually
kind of funny. It's like kind of wholesome in a way.
Because his son is
old enough now where he's kind of getting more
comfortable on camera and they both have like similar
catch phrases. You can tell he's like kind of
doing the catch phrases.
Oh man, you totally killed it.
You knocked it out of the park man.
Yeah you knocked it out of the park. Right Hunter?
And then eventually like he'll
he's gonna, but is he gonna have the hair?
I really hope
that they do a full, a full complete
transition from like father to son.
And he gets the hair and he gets
the blonde hair and the blonde goatee.
That would be unbelievable.
I would watch every episode.
They must always be a lich
king. Yes, they must always
be a lich king.
Otherwise the whole society collapses.
Without a
Guy Fieri
the whole thing comes down.
They must, oh I love that.
Fucking mod that guy for an hour.
Flavor King.
Where is this other bug?
I don't know where this other bug is.
Dude, don't put it past him man. World of
Warcraft's running out of shit to talk about.
Do not be surprised
if in ten years when World of Warcraft
is on its 30th expansion.
It's like, well, I guess like we
went to the place where everybody was dead.
We went to space.
We went to the center
of the fucking earth. We went
to hell. We went to heaven. I guess we're
gonna go to Flavortown. That's
what's left. And like Disney.
Like Disney World. Now should
I dig this up? Where this last
is one more bug? Where's this pickle bug?
Something in there.
I would play that expansion. That
would be the only thing that would bring me back to well.
And I'm talking about a fully
voice acted, but still in
kind of like the shitty World of Warcraft
engine Guy Fieri. And it's just
a human model. Just the standard
human model that they just gave a
blonde goatee and spiky blonde
hair to. Cause that's what they're
capable of doing. I got a pee.
I'll be right back. It's pee time.
You know, I don't understand how it gets so hot
in here. When I'm sitting in
this room, do I just
eliminate heat?
Inside of this room, it has
to be 10 degrees hotter
than the next room out of this
door. Wow.
It's cold. Let's go.
World of Warcraft.
Can you imagine? Sorry.
Where was I? I need to get six bugs.
It's cold in Nevada. Oh yeah.
It gets really cold in Nevada.
That's a sweetie fly.
It eventually sits down to
rest. Where? Up in the
sky. Remember, Nevada's the desert.
So it gets really, really, really
hot and really, really, really cold.
There's really no in-between in Nevada.
I scanned all the things.
Click the link, please.
Here's the- but I don't understand.
Why is he not like a dwarf
or a human?
I don't think- I wouldn't consider Guy
Fieri to be a- like a blood elf.
Would you?
Hold on, what can I- where is this?
Oh, there we go. Yeah, I don't think-
I don't see this to be actually
an actual bug.
I don't see this to be an actual
bug.
I don't think- I don't see
this to be accurate.
That's Guy Fieri.
Guy Fireeye.
No, no, that's all wrong.
This needs to be a dwarf.
No, but they need to take the dwarf and
stretch the dwarf out longer.
Have it be the only model in the game
that has a Gumby body.
Just stretch out the legs and the torso
and give him the goatee and the hair.
Oh, by the way,
see you guys in like probably a couple
times back. We're gonna get
new 2021-2022
Gumby. They're gonna bring it back.
You know that's up next.
I'll just stamp this.
It's definitely coming up next for the things
we're bringing back as a group.
Not me and you, but them.
Alright, what's your favorite?
The establishment, yep.
The establishment.
The Illuminati.
The TV Illuminati.
What do we bring back next?
How about...
Elmo. Wait, no, he's already here.
He's already here permanently.
Maybe...
What was that little bald kid's name?
Bring him back too.
Caillou.
Doesn't everybody hate Caillou?
I was under the assumption that Caillou was horrible.
And kids were like being
naughty and stuff after they watched Caillou.
Am I making that up?
Feed her favorite
bug snack. I hope it's hot dogs.
I didn't pay attention.
Is that a hot dog arm?
Totally mysterious before he goes to bed
around 10 every night.
I want you to find out
what he's up to. And tell me.
If you don't want to wait around
you can always just take a nap until it's time.
Wait, you can sleep?
Okay, find out what Wampus does between
10 PM and 1 AM.
I didn't know you could sleep. Alright.
Between 10 PM and 1 AM we're gonna
find out what Wampus is doing.
Okay, sleep until
5 PM.
Watch? Oh, it's down the lower left. Okay. Between
10 and 1. We're gonna go find
Wampus. Zerking off
for 3 hours.
I love how you guys have found this great
way. And I'll be honest, me too.
Of like getting around the sensors.
I didn't say
that. I said zerking off. It's
different.
Dude, you look like a clown.
Alright, what do you want me to do?
Well, buddy.
Well, if you don't mind,
I'd love to fly it someday.
Okay, sure. Maybe one day
you'll fly this. Should we tell
him? Should we tell him?
That's not ever gonna happen. Alright, I got another thing
for you to eat. Look, I've got a
strawberry and I'm gonna put it on your
eye. Oh.
We're only gonna feed this guy
and make him like the top dog.
We're gonna make this guy the alpha.
Ooh, plant!
Okay. Pick a bug snack
to plant. Oh, shit.
We shouldn't have. Alright.
I mean, I'll remember where this is.
But I need to spy on this guy between, alright.
We need to wait till 10 PM.
Okay, he loves
the green guy. How much is it?
Six. Shit, I got here really early.
Just sleep.
No, I can't. How long would it take
for you to read the entire Bible?
Um, that's probably a pretty long
time. Probably
a few, at least a few days.
I can't, I have trouble
I can't read the Bible. It's just, the way
that it's worded and the way that it's
spread out and the paragraphing and
I can't follow it. It just feels like somebody's
speaking at me while I
have my ears covered. You know what I mean? It's like I'm kind of
hearing what you're saying but I don't get it. I can't comprehend
it. I'm gonna read a
kid's Bible. No, of that
kids edition?
Kids edition.
Read the Bible
Manga. Bible picture
book. Why are you guys on the Bible
right now? What about you here?
Alright, it's 8pm. I'm
gonna follow this guy. Read the
Minecraft Bible. Is this a Minecraft
Bible? Lego
Bible. Who's
that?
Fortnite Bible. Holy shit, I saw
the Lego Bible at Costco one time.
You made that up. That's a glory,
the best part about the internet. You can just write
anything and just say it's real.
8.30. It's not real.
It's not real. There's no Lego Bible.
It wouldn't surprise me though because it's
Lego everything. Brick
Testament. Yeah, but I think
that- shh, quiet.
What you doing? It's 9.30.
It's too early. Don't go
in. Oh shit, okay. 9.45.
9.50.
He's getting ready to do
something. He's getting ready
to do something. I'm not gonna look at him anymore.
I'm not gonna look at him anymore.
I'm not gonna look at him anymore through the window until 10.
Okay, it's 10. What does it do?
I can't look through this window from this
perspective. I can't.
I just can't do it. What is he doing?
What are you doing?
What is he doing?
Alright, we got it.
Hey.
Talk to him through his window that I've been spying
on him through.
Alright, let's go report back.
I need a root and a fruit. Why are you doing
all this shit for her?
Because it's a quest and you get experience.
Plus, we're gonna double cross this lady.
Ugh,
Snaxburg sounds way more fun than sitting around
in this cave. I thought it
would be relaxing, but it's totes boring.
Like boring like playing
solitaire by yourself and you've been
on the floor? Oh, sorry. I've got a little bit
my chest is a little itchy.
Okay. I have to plant a root.
Alright, we gotta get some bugs.
Plant a root and plant a fruit.
What is that? That's a diet
coke. That's a floating diet coke.
That's a Dr. Sody.
Okay, I have to have Dr. Sody.
There's no way I don't get Dr.
Sody. Are you kidding me?
Aww, Dr. Sody!
Yes!
Awesome. Alright, who gets
to drink Dr. Sody?
We need a fruit though. Alright, I need a
strawberry and what's a root?
This is all fast food. This is the fast food
section. I need a
carrot. Carrot and a
Alright, we gotta go back to the other area. This is the fast food
area. French fries are not a root.
It's a potato.
That's like saying pizza is tomato.
No, that's not a tomato.
Tomato is part of it.
Pizza's not a vegetable because there's tomato on it.
They tried that like ten years ago. I remember.
Who should we give this to?
Who are you to decide?
Um, I don't know. I just did.
Alright, soda. You want the soda?
You. Ramble.
Wake up.
Let's turn this guy into a Dr. Pepper.
No, get over here. Eat.
Okay. Oh, wait. No, no, no. You don't
eat these animals, right? Or these bugs.
Never done an interview before.
How's it work?
Is it soda? I guess it has
eyes. Does it make it alive?
Okay. Who are you?
Heard Lizbert was gathering up some grumps
to be part of her new family. Use one
of those. Swimming and crawling. Alright, yeah.
Who are you though?
Ramble? Giggle funny. I look after
all the bugsnacks in town and make sure they don't
wander off. You don't have a family?
I did. When they
we talk about something else.
Well, they're just the cutest little
things, aren't they? I don't
understand how anybody could look into their
googly little eyes and want to eat them.
But, yeah,
everybody does eat them though.
Well, they don't eat none and that's what counts.
Why did you leave?
Liz, to bring in snacks, everybody got
mighty hunted. Untreated my barn
like a grocery store.
I held him off for a while,
but I should have known Wambus never quits.
Next
night I woke up to him throwing my snacks into a sack.
And I let the rest go free.
Broke my heart,
but it's better than them getting eaten.
I left that night for the beach
and started rebuilding my family.
The Siege of the Barn.
The eagle's a lot,
but she's got a good heart.
If she really likes me, she'll learn to love
bugsnacks the way I do.
Alright, what about Lizbert?
Where did she go?
Aww.
Bugtacks?
Alright, but what happened to Lizbert?
Did you sleepwalk kill Lizbert?
You're getting really defensive when we bring up Lizbert.
You don't eat bugsnacks,
but that doesn't mean you don't eat
puppet humans.
Oh, a key.
Oh, what?
Oh.
Okay, I got it. Oh.
Oh, I got it.
What happened?
Philbo wants to talk to you.
I'm here.
What can I do for you, Philbert?
Oh, you have something to tell me.
Among us stream when?
I've never.
I will never play that game on stream.
Not one time.
I plan on trying it tomorrow.
Alright, donate six bugsnacks
to the ranch.
I already have a soda snack.
Wait, do you want this? Here, drink this.
Okay.
Look what I got.
Try that.
A straw mustache.
Cool.
Practice your lying.
Do I really need to do that?
I lie to you guys literally every single day.
Do I need to practice?
Guys,
my first name is Dan.
I'm like, can we be real about this?
Okay, let's go.
Dance party.
Somebody go over there and start talking to him.
Somebody go over there and start talking to him so he stops.
Somebody just go talk to him so he stops.
Hey, man, what's up?
Come over here, I gotta talk to you.
Wait, I only made like two friends.
The farmer,
the serial killer,
the weirdo, and the mean girl.
This is quite the Wizard of Oz group.
Oh, this is disgusting.
I don't know why, I just felt like I was in VR.
Oh, look, I picked up this cup.
Shake it around, throw it. Ooh, VR.
Okay, what are we doing?
Some kind of suicide squad.
Yeah, we all die in the first two minutes of the movie.
How's the butt juice?
Isn't this just water?
Well, uh, it's bug
infused.
Why do I feel like we're gonna get a South Park Stan
and Wendy puking his mouth scenario?
Remember they used to do that?
Every time Stan talked to Wendy,
he puked in her
fucking face.
They did it for so long, too.
Did they give up doing that?
That was a thing they did for 10 to 15 straight years.
Do they still do that?
Yes, they stopped.
They stopped doing it when they started dating.
Oh, that show is
insane.
They stopped it in like 2004.
South Park games?
It was on the website,
those little flash games, right?
Who else should I talk to?
Alright, I didn't talk to the farmer.
Can I change the radio? This party sucks.
This is the kind of party that you show up to
and you realize what's going on
and you
grab like a water
and you're like, yeah, I'll take a water.
This is a water party.
I'll be dipping out in probably 40 minutes.
Maybe an hour.
Yeah, I've already mingled.
Now what?
Oh, that's unfortunate.
Hey, bro.
You've been drinking water, right?
Yeah, yeah, I've been drinking water.
Yeah, I'm just
checking to see if we're on the same page.
Is somebody
reacting to my ass? I don't know.
Wrong link.
It was the wrong link.
I feel like it wasn't.
This one, right?
Links are getting obliterated.
No, not that one.
How is it wrong?
It's like being spammed.
There's no such thing as a wrong link.
Okay, this is scary.
Is this the one?
Alright, I'm going to do an experiment.
Everybody quiet. Don't type.
I'm serious, like do not, just don't type at all.
Don't even do like the dot dot dots.
Nobody chat. Quiet.
Sit here. I want some new people to come in.
This is a 10k concurrent stream.
People are going to think this is
going to come, people are going to think this is like a
botted channel. This channel is going to get like reported.
Yeah, Twitch, this is like a botted channel
just with this like weird scary imposter
thing on this botted viewbot channel.
Shut it down.
I don't know who the fuck this guy is.
That joke is a month old.
Wait, somebody made that a month ago and I didn't see it?
Yo, bro.
You drinking water?
Okay, dude, just making sure we're on the same fucking page.
Don't act like you're in charge.
If you had the spine to lead us,
everybody would still be here.
Don't you mean, Trippany
would still be here?
Fine, all y'all gang up on me.
Don't make me wrong.
You all want Trippany back so bad?
Go find her yourself.
Yo, bro, you want to get out of here?
Let's get the fuck out of here.
This party, I knew it, it was a bad party.
Yeah, skimmy.
You sure have had quite a few though.
Wow.
A whole strabby.
It is drugs.
Wait, food poisoning?
Poisoned.
Get away from me, give me some space.
What the hell?
Philbo, what the heck?
Alright, I need to donate six snacks.
It's Jeff from American Dead.
It's Jeff.
Have it, Jeff.
Shut up.
Mr. S.
Jeff, you're an idiot, and you're a complete embarrassment to this family.
Look down.
Roger, do Roger.
Stan, I'm having some trouble with this, Stan.
Yeah, I'm gonna have to need you to get out of here, Stan.
Give me another one.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Alright, alright.
Go, go, go.
The fish?
My name is Klaus, and I'm stuck in a bowl.
Patrick Stewart.
I'm Patrick Stewart, and I think that you deserve to be fired.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Barney.
I don't know, Barney from what?
Barney the dinosaur?
It's me, Barney.
Go, go, go, go.
Obama.
I think that we all need to come together.
To take care of this.
I will take care of that.
Don't worry about that.
Go, go, anymore.
Framer.
I'm gonna spell that.
Squidward.
Luigi.
Joe Biden.
Now look, here's the deal.
We are going to solve America.
Give me another one.
Not that one, not that one.
Tingle.
I've never played Zelda, I don't know what he sounds like.
Next one.
Marge.
Hercules.
Costanza.
Jerry.
Get going crazy here.
Meatwad.
I don't want to know, I just got away from it.
Homer.
It's me, Homer.
Shrek.
It's me, Shrek.
Cosmo and Wanda.
Okay, here's Cosmo.
Wanda.
Sans.
Donkey Kong.
Snake.
Al Gore.
The planet is under attack.
Kirby.
Trump.
Okay.
I didn't do anything wrong.
It's a fake media.
Megamind.
I don't know.
Dana White?
Like from UFC?
It's the tale of the tape.
We've got these two fighters.
Why do you want me to do a Dana White impression?
I don't get it, that doesn't make any sense.
It's just a normal guy talking.
Macho Man, got it.
I just want to...
Hold on, I'll get it.
Can you hear anything we're talking about, Minji?
I just want to say the cream of the crop.
Next.
Dr. Evil.
Alex Jones.
Mr. Krabs.
Kanye.
Hey!
I'm moving, I'm moving, I'm moving.
Joe Rogan.
Yeah.
Right, man.
Eric Cartman.
My name's Eric Cartman, I don't like you.
And hey, Kenny.
No, Kenny.
Wombus.
I only came here for Triffy.
Sometimes I wonder if she'd do the same for me.
Popeye.
Well, I am a cellular man.
I'm a cellular man.
The Medic.
Okay, people are going to leave, I have to stop.
Let's play the game.
This dude's going off.
You're dropping viewers.
Hey, we'll see you next week.
When they decide to come back after they're...
The ultimate small doses streamer.
Yeah, I peek in from time to time.
I have small doses, I can handle them.
All right, I gotta go find things to plant here.
Do Mr. Satan.
You guys already know my Mr. Satan.
I don't have to do it again.
Okay, excuse me.
You think you're not the strongest man in the world?
I'm the strongest man in the world, Goku.
And I'll take you on in a fight one on one.
You want to fight me one on one, Goku?
Come on at me.
Send him to hell.
Send who to hell?
I am not even playing the game.
I'm just stuck in the mirror.
This is what I do in the mirror.
I already get stuck like this
two or three times a day.
You put me in front of a mirror, I'm going to see myself
and go, oh, it's a person. Who's that?
Goku.
Don't put me in front of a mirror. I get trapped.
What do I do?
I need vegetables.
Wait, I can just get bugs. Let's get bugs.
All right, check this out.
I'm going to have you.
Hey, don't do that shit.
I'm going to donate six bugs to the ranch.
I'll just get them from here.
Do I not have a tool
that I can go in the air with?
I feel like it's been a while.
All right, let's get this bug. Ketchup bug.
I'll put that down there.
Get some ketchup, please. Thank you.
Let's get them. Do G-men and I'll...
Wait, do G-men and I'll give 100,000 subs.
Uh...
Mr. Freeman.
That's not right. That's the scientist.
Let me do it again.
The thing about that, Gordon,
you abandoned
the wrong place at the right time.
You could make all
the difference.
Open the briefcase, Gordon.
100,000 subs. Thank you.
You know, this is just
what I think would happen
when the really, really hyperactive
kid in Show and Tell didn't bring
anything to Show and Tell, and the teacher
just knows he's fucking out of
his mind. So they just go, you know
what? Okay, go ahead.
And I brought my impressions today.
And everyone just has to put up
with this for the five to ten
minutes that happens. What do you
like? Maybe I can lure you over with some
candy. Right?
Because it's a candy fly, and there's candy
here. Does the
candy fly like candy?
That would make sense, right?
What do you like, though? Don't be a
sucker. What do you like? You don't have
any likes or dislikes.
Come on. Hey, Phallus extends to the five
community subs. A little short of 100,000,
but, you know, we make bets here that we don't go through
with. Like me?
Like you? I need two hamburgers
to fight each other. I can do that.
Come here.
Hamburger. You.
Follow. Oh, alright, come on.
Come on, Bunger.
Bunger! Nice sick, nice sick,
sick, sick, nice sick.
Any more Bungers? You owe us the dump
truck emote. I don't know, I don't.
Maybe eventually you'll get it if you behave.
Well, I have four. Let me just go
back and donate these.
You told us three new emotes.
Yeah, like within the next seven to ten days,
it's been like five. I got plenty
of time. Meanyworm.
Oh, wait, here's a fruit.
Get back there, because then I can plant
the fruit and then I need a carrot.
Can I actually
plant the french fries? Does that not work?
Four part dump truck ass
emote. I'm gonna get kicked off
a twitch. Baku tail, thanks
to the five. No, six community subs, actually.
I read that wrong.
I don't think I've even been to Flavor Falls.
Got that. Yeah, that's a good olive.
Holy shit. What
the hell is that? It's a sub sandwich?
That's my favorite.
I love them. How do
I get a sandwich bug thing?
How do I get the Super Bowl party
sandwich? What is that?
A veggie bit. No,
you. A white rootle. Oh,
shit. Alright, hold on. I have to
release some of these. I have too many
french fries. Release. Hey.
Release you. Go to the farm.
Yeah, I want to catch this
one, because that's a veggie.
This game is really cute.
There's my vegetable. There's my
loves.
Speeds along crashing into things.
It won't slow down until it's broken up.
What is it? Love? Orange
juice? I'll come back for you.
Is that a pretzel?
What is it? Tasty, twisty snack
pod? What?
Alright, get rid of the french fries.
Another ten community subs.
It's just a bag of chips, but it's
alive. What?
Uh, Flutter.
Looter, thanks for the ten community subs.
Alright, I gotta deliver these. I missed other subs,
did I? Oh, shit, we had a lot.
Ah, we did, right. Felsix gave five.
Jubelube
Tube gave five.
And then Captain Nemo gave a hundred bucks.
Thanks for the ten thousand bits.
This is huge money today. There's been like
three or four of these.
Too much money. And Captain Nemo
says dump truck emote tomorrow,
or I will freeze this card before it goes
through. Uh, well, I don't...
Well, you're gonna be getting...
You're gonna be hearing from your bank. Cause I don't think
it's gonna be here tomorrow.
I'm gonna freeze my card.
Yes, this is uh, this is bank.
I'm gonna help you. I'd like to
freeze my credit card. I'd like to report a
freeze of the purchase that just happened.
And what purchase would that be?
A hundred dollars to an e-clown.
Oh, you didn't make that purchase?
No. You didn't, cause you confirmed it
twice. No, um,
I did, but he
said he wasn't gonna make a German ass
dump truck emote, so
I have to refund it. Okay.
Um, no.
I'm switching banks. I'm switching
banks. Bullshit, I'm switching banks.
Cool.
I planted the snacks.
He's destroying... No, I'm not.
Wait, I have some more stuff.
Alright, you eat. What about this pretzel snack pod?
I did this stuff in the lunchroom
in like the fourth grade.
You put the pretzel sticks in your mouth and you go
Alright, what about burger?
Nice.
Donate. Oh, right, you're right, right, right, right, right.
Donate you.
Donate Dr. Soda.
Oh, look! They actually come out and
play. I love this
guy. Is it weird that
this part of my brain sees this as
some weird post-apocalyptic
polluted earth shit?
This is gonna be real.
I don't like looking at that anymore. Alright.
I need four more snacks.
Hey, don't annoy me.
And we're voting you off the island.
What do you mean personal issues?
Aren't I doing that already?
I was gonna just try to do a millhouse from
Simpson's voice, but that would be way too hard.
Following me?
I still gotta get some more.
You have something that's... Wait, interview.
Bilbo gave you...
That's the fucking bugs.
Holy shit. I don't know if you could even...
Hold on.
What do you do professionally though?
Is this a spy?
Is that fun fact unrelated?
Oh.
Oh shit, I ain't even recording.
Oh well, she won't even fucking notice.
I'm not even recording.
Drama? Oh my god.
Feed me.
So you're an international criminal
and you steal from the farmer.
That's a grade A awful.
Where's Lizbert?
Tell me.
You wanna go to jail?
What is it?
Hamburger bug snacks.
That's everybody's weakness though.
I don't buy that.
Uh oh.
Egobel, suspicious.
Egobel,
you could shorten that a little
and say something about how suspicious
Egobel is.
Oh, I have a key.
I have two keys.
Alright, so I have two.
Let me try to open that door.
Walking my way out.
Fine, I'll just barrel through.
Where's this little cabin somewhere?
Wait, what's this way? This is like a desert.
We're gonna get some desert bugs?
Wrong way?
Yeah, I haven't seen anything over here.
Scorched gorge.
Oh, it's a chili pepper, a scorpeno.
The snack wabs fiery peppers
at anything that catches its attention.
I like that one.
What's that thing?
Weird.
A pop tick. They are too small to catch in a trap
but maybe some heat will puff them up.
Alright, hold on. What about you?
What does a scorpeno like?
Loves? What's the orange thing?
So I can have them kind of pop the popcorns.
It's mustard?
Why do you get mustard?
What's that? A spuddy.
It protects its territory by charging intruders
with its powerful jaws.
It loves ketchup.
Let's catch this motherfucker.
Is it too big?
We got a good link. Hold on.
It's too big.
He just smashed into the wall.
Do that again.
Whoa, whoa! There's a secret in here!
What the hell is this?
A mural depicts grumpuses opening a section
of wall near the river there carrying
some sort of parcel.
That's the pizza demon that we saw earlier.
It's Laura. Secret Laura.
We got a quest over here.
Oh my god, it's like a rib.
Ribble.
Ribble-pede.
It likes to hide and sit still. Maybe some sauce
could get it to move.
Like barbecue sauce?
Will you fucking leave me alone?
You like ketchup?
Oh, I covered him in ketchup and he hated it.
I got a ribble-pede.
How do I stop you from doing this?
What am I supposed to do with you?
He's covered in ketchup. Does it make him mad?
There's a butterfly up there. Hold on.
Oh, it's Tiffany. Everyone talks shit about you.
Hit the bug. Wait, wait, hold on.
Hold on. Somebody got a link.
That's a good one. This one's not bad.
It's not bad. It's pretty good.
I don't know if I love chocolate though.
I like chocolate. I don't know if I love chocolate.
Ooh, I got one of those.
Ooh, how many do you want? Three?
I can do that.
Let's go.
I wanted to get people to come back to town.
Alright, ribble-pedes.
There's one right there. What's your trajectory?
Alright, that's the trajectory.
Get that shit down. Let's go.
Toss him up.
Where'd you go?
Oh wait, you went all the way around.
Really strange path you have.
Alright, one more.
I like the voice.
I can't wait for the one that's like
ribble-peded.
That will be my favorite.
Okay, every goblin from
Warcraft and Hearthstone.
Where do you want me to go? Who is this talking?
Oh, it's you.
Wait, a white cheepoof.
It's a cheese puff.
You're annoying. Stop doing that.
Danny DeVito? That would be great.
Wait, my ball.
Oh man, I left the ball all the way back there.
I'm a bad father.
Come on, I'm back. Wait, he loves this.
He loves that.
What do I do with that information?
Hmm, what does it say?
Some assembly required. Buy at your own risk.
All sales are final.
Offer void where prohibited. Shirt and shoes optional.
May contain nuts or shellfish. Guarantees not guaranteed.
Bridge for sale.
Did you make it up?
I thought he was covered in blood for a second.
Oh, what a journey you were on.
Get away from me. Actually, you know what?
Come over here. Get over here.
Come light me up.
Do that over here.
Okay, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop.
Pop over here. Pop over here.
Oh, it's a popcorn! Go, go, go, over here.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, okay, that's awesome. It's a live popcorn.
I love it. Give me this back.
Yes. A pop tick.
Nice.
Alright, hold on. I gotta pee again.
Piss day, for some reason.
I'll be right back.
Who's ready to snack?
Okay.
Oh, did I not even put it on the VRB screen?
I just walked away.
Shit.
I thought I did.
I didn't even switch it.
Whoops.
All right, we need one more Ribble pea.
I got the popcorn one, so that's good.
I'm happy about that.
All right, they're in the ruins, the ancient ruins.
We got the one in here.
What about the one over here?
Is there more than one in here?
Yep.
Oh, hey, hey, hey, hey.
What was the name of that game
that everybody told me to play?
That was the photography game.
Have we played that game, Africa?
I completely forgot the name of the game.
No, no, no, it's, it's, it's, it's some, it's a,
it's like, oh, he loves taking pictures.
It's a picture of a take photos game.
No, not Dragon Rampa, something else.
It's like, no, not Pokemon Snap.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, not horror.
It's, it's like a,
the color scheme is like this.
It looks like this.
The color scheme is like pink, teal, and electrified.
And it has a Uru, Uru Gami Generation.
That's the one, right?
That's it.
Uru Ga, or Uru Gami Generation.
All right, is that game any good?
Did I play that game?
People kept telling me it was like the,
it was a photo game.
You have to play Dragon Rampa.
I probably won't.
All right, let's go back and deliver.
Uh, wait, do you want to eat these?
Have a good one.
You want, you want to eat these?
I thought you wanted to study them.
This just looks like you,
you got your arms and legs cut off.
Yes, Rivelpedes only look like they have bones.
They're squishy all the way through.
So what did these fellas eat then?
Well, like grandma always said,
if you want answers, dig through their sock drawer.
I want to get into that dwelling over there,
but the door's blocked up.
I already opened it.
If you could do something to get that door open.
I'll go in.
I opened it accidentally.
I'm like Mr. Magood into the ruins.
So go ahead.
What the fuck are you going to do about it?
Oh, look at me, I can charge.
Look at me, I'm so fast.
Yeah, what are you going to do?
Ha ha ha.
Get out.
These murals are still preserved.
As far as I know,
we were the first grumps to settle this island.
But here we got a thousand years of history
and accounted for.
There were a thousand grumps before us.
Generations of grumpuses who hunted and ate bug snacks.
Just a cosmic reminder that nothing really lasts, eh?
Bug snacks.
What's this?
Looks like there's a hidden chamber somewhere in the canyon.
Could that be where they stored bug snacks?
Would you mind finding that chamber?
And if there's bug snacks there,
please bring them to me.
Bye bye.
Find and enter the hidden ruins.
How am I supposed to do that?
That's not a whole lot of info.
Opening a section of wall near the river.
They're carrying a parcel.
Section of wall near the river.
Okay, let's go find it.
Find a river.
Scan the moth painting.
Oh, I'm so, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I already did.
Donate the popcorn?
I will once I find the hidden ruins
and do this for Green Grover.
All right, hidden, here's the river.
Is the arrow pointing me to where the, no.
All right, there's a section of this wall
somewhere over here.
It needs to be, it's probably right there.
You, I need you to run at me really fast.
Come over here.
Hey, don't you like sauce?
I got lots of sauce.
I got lots of red sauce inside of my body.
What's wrong?
Wait, let me just double check.
Near the river.
Ah, I found it.
Right here.
Look at me.
I'm covered in sauce.
Oh, whoa, whoa.
Okay, no, nobody, I can't get the door open now.
I'll get, hold on, I'll get another one.
There's one back here, right?
Just cover the ball in sauce and it'll follow me around.
There you go, okay, cover this ball in sauce.
Follow me.
Wait, there's another popcorn.
Am I gonna die?
You shithead.
Come over here.
No.
Whatever, I don't need another popcorn, I don't care.
Give me this back.
Where'd he go?
Where's my, where is he, where is he?
Crying, Jerma, I'm sorry that you're crying.
What happened?
Where did that guy go?
Where did he go?
Am I insane?
Oh, you went all the way down here, perfect, okay.
Keep going.
No, no, no, no, no, no, follow me.
No, no, no, no, please.
Break it.
Yeah, now get out of here.
Is that extra dogs?
What are those?
Now you're in here with me
and I don't want you in here with me.
Catch one weenie worm.
What do you like?
Oh, you're very dirty.
It's only motivated by its hatred of ketchup.
Okay, well, you don't like ketchup, then I'm sorry,
but why don't you get away from that?
Oh, you don't like ketchup.
Oh, shit.
Wait a minute, I just covered him with,
why did he just get big and red?
He got big and red.
Holy shit, okay, I got him.
Okay, catch one weenie worm, feed.
Oh, eat what?
Let me look at my book.
What's with you?
Weenie worm loves mustard, hates ketchup.
It's only motivated by its hatred of ketchup.
What does it eat?
Eat it to her.
Oh, right, okay.
I think I want another Steak'em's.
I wanna give somebody a Steak'em's
and have it be like their Steak'em's brain.
Give it in their head.
It's your trajectory, right?
Here, look at that.
Okay, get ready.
And shoot you, and I'll take one, please.
Now we have full inventory, let's go.
Oh, wait, there's this weird guy up here.
What's his problem?
Pacing you?
Oh, it's anger from inside out.
Hello, friend, welcome, but take a look.
I assure you, you won't be disappointed.
The name's Cromdo Face,
the one and only salesman in paradise.
Let's eat.
Okay, what do you like to eat?
Friend, have I got a bridge to sell you.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Did I weenie dog him?
New construction, huh?
Oh, baby, what a bridge.
All yours for just 100 bucks next.
What do you say?
I can't even carry that much.
Can't afford it, no problem.
I got a specialty item just for you.
Cheap as free, follow me, pal.
I think I wanna follow you.
Feast your eyes on this beautiful lunch pad.
Totally for sale and not at all stolen.
You're itching to try it out, I can tell.
Does it bounce, pal?
My windmills over there got stuck.
Why don't you take it for a spin
and knock him into shape?
Yeah, will you go back to town?
Switch to it with Q.
Wait, aim.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, what?
Why was that not ready?
God damn it, wait, I'll be back.
I feel like I'm playing 007, GoldenEye.
Isn't there a watch that you can laser people?
All right, aim, launch.
You understand what the fuck just happened?
Why is it changing?
I'm aiming and then I'm just, I'm launching.
Too heavy, okay.
Aim, what?
Why can I not do this?
See ya.
No, deploy.
No, you don't.
Pick this up.
Bingo.
And one more.
I thought it wanted me to launch myself at it.
Sorry, I don't have one of those fancy science degrees.
I just hurt my throat doing that, I don't know why.
Oh, I feel that hot, sweaty breeze.
Now it's time to pay up.
What, you used it, you bought it.
There's no such thing as a free lunch.
Hey, hey, you can pay me three of those cheap hoops.
Cheap hoops?
Oh, great, fly it around.
Let's see how they like flying into my mouth.
Do I have to catch the cheap hoops?
Five, four, three, two, one.
No, what happened?
Oh, okay.
I can't do this yet.
I have to deliver this stuff.
I'll come back into this later.
Yeah, I got priorities.
Where is she?
Digging over here.
His eyes may as well be closed.
He has no idea what he's doing.
What are you talking about?
I have a weenie dog right here.
I found a lot of corpses.
Spender Otto, I did not.
Well, I gotta solve this mystery.
Sorry, but I won't be going back to Snaxburg.
You will, eventually.
If Wambus wants me back,
well, he can come out here and tell me himself.
You might have heard things haven't been too good
between us.
I keep telling myself I'll get around to C&M,
but it's just easier to stay out here with the bone.
Weird lady, weird lady, weird lady, weird lady,
weird lady, weird lady.
Get out.
What?
She's going back, I did it.
I win.
I did it.
I thought she said she wasn't gonna be going back
to Snaxburg.
Your mind changed immediately.
All right, I gotta donate these.
We told her about the cactus wipe, I did.
I did good.
She would be good at Among Us, unlike you.
Is that supposed to be an insult?
It doesn't insult me.
I don't care.
If I played Among Us and I got imposter,
I would just immediately just start killing everybody
at the spawn while cackling like,
ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, until I was removed from the lobby
and then I would end my stream.
And then I would write on Twitter.
Kind of pissed off that people don't wanna play with me
and it's annoying.
What the fuck?
What did I do?
You're like, that's bullshit.
I wanna, why?
Why'd they kick me out?
I would just start a ton of problems.
Teenage girl.
Oh, look, we did good.
Time for the interview.
Sounds like a real hoot.
He's been fucking a cactus?
Ow.
All right, who are you?
Oh, I go digging up bits of history
and try to piece them back together.
It's usually not so dramatic.
Just an old coin or a severed toe under a rock.
But this island's chock full of fines.
What was your name?
Oh, goodness, my name.
I'm Trifoni Lottoblog.
That's just, it's just Steve Bruhl.
Hey, Trifoni.
Trifoni Lottoblog.
All right, who's grandma?
Lisbur.
Sounds like Sarah Palin.
Pfft.
It's just, yeah, it's just like generic mid-western.
It's not Norwegian.
What do you mean Norwegian accent?
I want this accent to tell me nursery rhymes.
Oh, fuck that, this is my accent.
We'll go on, start reading us some Hansel and Gretel
or whatever.
Our grizzliest scars.
Adventuring is a dangerous business.
Archaeology less so, but the Lottoblog method
can be unconventional.
Bug the heck out of Agabelle.
She never liked to see anyone hurt.
Least of all, Liz.
What the fuck are you talking about?
I hope that she doesn't die in a QTE.
Ha ha ha.
That's very, very specific.
Ha, I think it's still funny.
That's very specific, but I really do think
that what you just said is funny.
Thanks, Tiffany, I learned a lot.
Have fun, have an easy one, bye.
You might have better luck with it.
Anywho, I've nearly talked your ear off.
This is shit load of subs.
Better get back to work, eh?
WTR6K4DA, these are the 20 community subs.
20 subs, thank you.
WTR6K4DA, thank you.
Pick a diary, Liz's cabinet key.
Oh, how about the diary?
Oh, what's in there?
You picked up Liz's notes on a secret code.
Holy crap.
Looks like I need to weigh down the pressure plates
in order, first left, and then we don't know.
Holy crapple.
Here, why don't you eat, here, have some,
have some baked potato in the tinfoil.
Oh, God.
Ah, those of you guys with fillings,
putting tinfoil in your mouth is just,
get it out and get it away.
Oh my God, that's horrible.
Ah, I hate it.
Why would they do that?
Okay, let's donate a Ripplepeed.
A, we have to do them all.
Shy, Weenie, Worm, Spuddy, and a Poptick.
Size of your heart has grown and so has your inventory.
Oh, there we go.
By how much?
By two?
12 donations now.
Look, we can see they're all friends.
Look at them.
That's my favorite.
Move.
Move, streamer, I wanna see Otto.
They're gonna, we're having so much fun.
They're having so much fun in here.
All right, now, what do I actually have for quests?
There's a lot of world here.
Okay, quests.
I can do the cheesy poofs.
Wiggle would like to talk to you about something
at the beach.
Turn the grumps to snackberg.
Okay, so I have to get everyone to come back
and then interview everyone.
That's the main quest.
What about this one?
Do I enjoy this game so far?
Yeah, it's good.
Well, I'm gonna, let's go to this one.
Let's track that one.
Let's go to the beach.
Why are you playing this?
It's very cute.
I could see how this would be relaxing and fun to play.
All right, we're looking for the guitar player.
Sweetie fly zips around fast to evade traps
but eventually it sets down to rest.
I kinda wanna catch it.
Where do you land?
Land over on that rock there.
All right, let me get your ass.
What do you like?
Catch up?
No, all right, you'll come down here and land.
I'll be ready.
Aha, we got a lovely sweetie fly.
Are there legendaries in this game
where shiny is like Pokemon?
Oh, hi darling.
Welcome to wiggle, wiggle bottom steamy walking tour.
Lucky you.
It's an ooey gooey sweetie fly.
Oh, I can see you're utterly starstruck.
Don't fret, darling.
I always have time for my fans.
Go back to, uh, Sackberg.
Darling, it will have to wait.
I simply cannot rest until I find my muse.
And by muse, I mean butt snacks.
What's your favorite?
I might have it.
Change starts from the outside in, darling.
If I want new ideas, I need a new look.
How about a wild new hairdo?
A pine-a-tula.
Get me a pine-a-tula and we'll see what we can do.
Okay, you want pine-a-tula hair.
What about a sweetie fly beard?
Oh, cool.
But how can you ever play the guitar again?
All right, let's dig one up.
Ruined her career, kind of.
Your trajectory is here.
Get dug out of the ground.
Cover you in, I believe it's chocolate.
Ow.
All right, somebody dig that up.
Chocolate.
Right there.
You think I'm gonna both?
Oh, I doubled it up.
I didn't know you could do that.
I thought only one could fit in there.
That's cool to know.
All right, here you go.
Pineapple head.
Struck a chord.
With a new head, I can think no thoughts.
That's the magic of bug snacks.
Now my creative juices can flow.
This is my favorite character.
Hmm, I know I'm flowing, I'm flowing.
Hmm, hmm, hmm, ooh, ooh, ooh.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la.
You and me are gonna be really, really good friends.
I can already tell.
This flow is more of a dribble.
Need you to turn it up, darling.
Buy me a grape skeeter.
They're too fast for Granville or I to catch,
but maybe you can find a way to slow them down.
Grape skeeto?
Some bug snacks are only around at certain times.
You can scan evidence in the environment
to get a clue about when to find them.
Bug, okay, a grape skeeto.
I gotta find like grape juice on the ground?
Evidence.
Fruity goop.
This fruity, leafy glob is evidence of a bug snack.
This bug snack seems to appear at night,
but not when it's raining.
Hmm, all right, let's sleep with that grape skeeto.
Do you have a bed in your house?
Where's the bed?
Is there a bed in here?
All right, sleep until midnight.
I just heard it.
Somebody just said their name.
It's for free.
That's free.
All right, grape skeeto.
Just heard it.
That would be a grape skeeto.
This one plumps up and slows down
if it eats another bug snack and it loves chocolate.
So let's cover this in chocolate.
Go eat it.
Let's get him.
There you go, there's your grape skeeto.
Why is the cap a gold?
I don't know.
Haven't figured that out yet.
Okay, here's your grape skeeto.
What did you want it?
Did you want it on your hand?
You never played the guitar again.
I bandaged up both of your hands.
And now the ideas will flow.
Mm-hmm, they gon' flow.
Ooh, any second now, come on now.
I assure you.
You're my favorite political streamer.
I have nothing.
Thanks, man.
You go over the issues here.
Back on this beach that can give me the inspiration
that I need, which is why you should look in the desert.
I need a look that pops, a look that's hot.
That's why you're here.
Listen to me talk about the issues.
If you could go to the Scorched Gorge
and catch two Pop Sticks.
Ooh, catch two Pop Sticks.
From a fix America.
I'm just a clown.
I'm just a clown, man.
I can't fix anything.
Like Bozo the Clown, like fucking Richard Nixon
didn't pull Bozo the Clown in and go,
we need to fight, excuse me, Bozo.
Well, how do you feel about foreign policy?
No, I just entertain children.
Perfect, you get on the board.
You're perfect for us.
Not implying that you guys are children.
I'm implying that you're children.
None of you guys, maybe some of you are.
But you had to click that 18 plus logo
when you got to the stream first.
So you might be lying.
Don't lie, that's not good.
Pop Sticks.
Wait, is that the popcorn?
All right, I gotta get two Pop Sticks.
I'm out.
I gotta go to the Fire Land.
Does this game ever get interesting?
I mean, that depends on what you think is interesting.
You think collecting bugs
and taking pictures is interesting?
Then you're gonna love it.
You think this is dumb?
I think you probably wouldn't wanna play it
if you don't think that like picking up food bugs is cool.
This is not the game for you.
Let's just complete this now
because I know that it's available.
So let's go to Burning Gorge.
And yesterday is history, tomorrow is a mystery.
I can't even.
All right, let's get these two.
Fire, fire!
No, you burnt my thing.
All right, you'll come out eventually.
Did you just torch my shit?
No!
Is he gonna burn?
Why are you doing this, dude?
The bush is on fire.
Oh no, it's okay.
Just burn all the bushes so they can't run away.
Stop!
What the fuck?
Stop burning them.
Stop lighting them on fire.
I put them out?
I can't put them out.
Hey, you, fuck off.
Lead them to the river.
Oh, there we go.
Oh my God, stop.
Kill the scorpion?
I can't.
How am I supposed to kill it?
Throw poop.
Launch pad.
Okay, I'm gonna throw a rock at this motherfucker.
I swear to God.
What do you hate?
You hate spicy food, but you love mustard food.
I don't have any of that stuff.
He's distracted.
No!
Sauce near Danny.
Who the fuck is Danny?
How do I lure these guys away?
What do you guys hate?
They love chocolate.
Fuck, what am I doing?
No, do you not see the sauce right here, man?
Where's the other one?
I think the other one burnt to death.
Don't worry, there's more.
There's one right here.
All right, pop this guy.
And actually, pop them both.
No, don't shoot me with that fire.
No, don't.
Oh, you got me with the fire.
Oh, you got me.
He actually is getting me and not these.
Dude, aim at this.
Pop.
There's water here.
I can't pop this.
Go eat the chocolate.
Chocolate.
Can I get them un-popped?
No, they gotta be popped.
This is a really shitty place to do this.
How about over here?
Build a sentry.
Go get mustard from the store.
I feel like I can get one of these.
How can you be bad at bug snacks?
I'm not bad at bug snacks.
This is weird and I'm not bad at bug snacks.
Bad, you can't be bad at everything, okay?
There it is.
All right, he's gonna turn into a popcorn.
Don't let him, don't let him.
All right, good, good, good, good, good.
Okay, now put him in.
Go, okay, now chocolate over here.
Follow me.
No, give me that back.
Don't touch that, it's not yours.
All right, watch this, ready?
Okay.
Chocolate.
Get him.
Fucking piece of shit, I swear to God.
I have no more sauce.
Did I eat the bullet?
Yeah, can I just grab him with a net?
Yes, okay, okay, we're good, we're good.
Deliver.
I am to make a delivery.
Mad because bad, mad because bad, mad because bad,
mad because bad, mad because bad.
Wait, that's a Cheeto puff.
I need three of these.
What does it say?
These things never land
if only there was a way to catch them midair.
It's called throw rock at them.
Hear me out on this one.
Give me this.
Give this to me.
Can't pick up his rock?
No, I can't even pick the rock up.
Whatever, I'll be back.
We gotta feed the Pop Ticks to a guitar person.
I might be able to bounce myself.
I'm gonna donate the other ones
and I'll bring the two Pop Ticks to the lady.
So donate, donate, donate.
And we gotta go to the beach.
Get away from me.
Oh, yeah.
They're all so cute.
Thank you so much.
Hopefully my little ones will settle down.
Maybe I can even start training them again.
Quest complete.
Now to the beach.
Maybe this will be enough for her to go back to town.
Everybody in this game is creepy.
Yeah, a little.
Where'd you go?
Where is she?
She's in her house like right here.
She's dead.
No, she's not right here.
Okay, two Pop Ticks.
I guess you're gonna have popcorn feet.
That's the only thing that's available, right?
All these feet.
Ridiculous.
And I don't have a single new tune in my head.
Oh, full journey I've taken.
Darling, I apologize for putting you through such an ordeal.
It was all for the sake of art.
What do we think of the theme song?
And art is priceless.
Is there a theme song to this game?
Has she heard it?
You want to do full, total,
just transformation to bug snack?
Every limb, every appendage?
Oh no, you're going back, good.
Ow, ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow!
Ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
oh oh oh oh what other quest okay the cheese poofs anybody else have anything to do maybe
somebody back in town will have something because the cheese food but i don't want it who cares
make her all popcorn i'm sure you could do that to somebody all right let's go wait the new no
no i'm gonna try to do the cheese poop thing we'll get the sub i'm not sure i'm ready for the sub
listen to the theme song what would it where would mean the theme song oh i got a new assignment
ghost stories see all right hold on is it can i was it on like youtube bug snacks theme song
hero hero bonito it's bug snacks see you in three days when you get banned how would i get banned
this is like tos all right emca what isn't that in the game it has singing it's dean wait isn't
that song in this game so what's the difference if i if the song is in this game versus i play it on
youtube is it no all right that wasn't in game i have was all kind of computers that's determined
hey guys we just listened to the caro caro bonito song it's bug snacks
yeah none of you will ever buy music ever again that's right that makes sense to you doesn't it
hey i just listened to um i just listened to this the song that i really like i'm canceling my
spotify i'm never paying for music ever again because of that because i listened to that song
what what's the logic behind this i don't understand snacksburg is looking pretty
busy tonight seems like a great time to gather everybody around the old campfire it's exactly
that's exactly it it's really weird because i feel like they're just throwing out a gigantic net to
hopefully make like pennies on every dollar you know what i mean and if you do that enough times
if you just throw out a gigantic net when you when you make potentially like a quarter of a
penny from like 600 million things is worth it apparently wait we're doing a party and by the way
why put this shit on youtube feet sitting in the dark i'll tell you there's some spooky stuff out
there there ain't nothing out there just why upload these songs to youtube are we never are
we not allowed to listen to these these songs list we're like fucking locked in our basements with
all the lights are all off and our windows are all closed
i've seen something similar up on top of the canyon real curious probably just a wild animal
darling there are no animals here none but we oh we're missing somebody come out something else
you know the desert grumps oh shit guys guys guys dying and
seal them in six caves whatever for were the dead going to rise from the grave no not as
shit it's more the bodies would just somebody gotta pick that up pick that up pick that up pick
that up i don't want something smells delicious what's that it smells like roasted strawberry
oh it's me even if they bury come on come on that's in every cartoon
body wouldn't be there the next day though some of the time there'd be a little left
just a few bones and then she'll just thinking about it you're getting the
chill because the fire's gone out you're right uh hey buddy would you mind picking up some firewood
it's over by the mill oh we had some does this count oh what'd you say oh that
oh what about you you got something to say a bit yeah line it up real good here just line it up
let all right we're gonna go to the old mill where's the old mill here it is all right let's
get some wood get some firewood oh this is the part where i go what's that
it's me with the firewood here you go and then everybody hears the real sound
on okay i've seen every cartoon ever every fucking tv show every movie
no zombies listen spooky is the disappearing stiffs maybe that's just a story i read on a
wall we got goofing around and play the game this whole game is goofing around you pick up
bugs and fucking feed them to people obviously we're not the first i'm not playing bioshock
so what makes us think all the others are dead i've seen those chewed up skeletons around the
island we all know something kills grumpuses out there and it has teeth bug snacks don't have teeth
and like wiggle said there aren't animals out here other than us she's not wrong about the
bones ah ah uh time i gotta use a little crumple now hold on you saying grumpus's turn cannibal
oh it's true that's sus one night i saw floofy dragging it's really all like among us characters
okay i saw what it was dude blue leg they have funny like hamburger hats they took a bite
mess with my head bev gonna scare me snackless is he gonna do the thing that i just did all right
everybody smile that we just lost one of our good friends he might be dead perfect i'll put that on
insta back in the bathroom whose bathroom the bathroom okay that's not the bathroom he ran
over here where's the bathroom jesus go to the bathroom like the bathroom i where is the bathroom
he got up and he ran this way he went oh sorry i got a little too spooked so if you're there
then who's in there huh i i don't know what you're talking about buddy somebody drowned in there
are you feeling okay you look like you've seen a ghost well let's get together and get back to the
fire uh yeah somebody somebody fell in here and drowned in this poop water that wasn't a monster
that was somebody's final gasps of poop air damn oh well you have a wicked bad beer belly
sorry about that what i miss can we just quit it with the spooky stuff i don't think i could
get any sleep darling calm yourself is there an echo
or i know what lurks in the shadows it's the queen of bug snacks a bug snack bigger than any we've
ever seen pizza one fibers and threat protection windows defender summary windows defender did
not find any threats on your computer what is that part of the what is this why did i get that
alert safe she gobbles us up precisely right darling this story makes no sense why would
bug snacks have a monarchy oh wham this is just the title i've seen bug snacks big enough to
eclipse the moon what else would you call that um a hallucination believe what you will wham this
regardless of what sort of monster you believe in something is lurking out there
i love this game it's great let's do a music video
snacks it's coming for us where where
something safe so funny looking i'm not getting eaten by some monster or floofy
just because you won't admit you're scared don't worry grimble we'll go check it out if something
goes wrong sacrifice left for dead left for dead mod with extra players uh left for dead let's go
that's a pretty good start to like the video you know what i mean like step step step step
to the beat to the first drum beat all right no no now walk around and like eat a bunch of
food from the mall okay yeah eat like the be like the audience pretzels investigate the noise in
the mill oh there's a mill play the game i think that sound came from the mill maybe there's a
trail we can follow their trail oh new character chad low a brawny builder bro
and somebody new hey how are you doing better these days yeah uh snacks burg is coming back
together i noticed i saw the fire and i thought whoa snacks burg's on fire so i came down here
to check on it then i remembered i left some stuff at the mill so here i am is sheldon around
oh no nobody's seen sheldon since the the fight major bummer bro i could use her wisdom right now
anyway can't stay and hang this is youtube germa back to snorpy right away you know how he gets
don't you at least want to say hi to everybody if i do that they're gonna want me to stay
catch you later bros but but i do want you to stay oh darn it oh well let's get back and
hire one dude you know i i don't think i've laughed harder at like a video or a sequence
of the day in the life of tyler one when he's like hiding behind the wall and those like
cg enemies are walking towards him and he like turns the corner with his little gun just like
and it's like 10 seconds later one of them falls over and dies it's like the funniest
fucking thing ever don't worry folks i'm fine it's so funny and like he doesn't even shoot at one
point and like two more of them just fall down you just like didn't match it up right things are good
and boring who's the queen of bugsnacks it's like 40 minutes long yeah it's pretty long required
for royalty yeah if anybody's clowns here it's me you know the desert grumps had a history of
matriarchal leadership real fascinating system they had every year the ladies would go hunting
carlin one also did this thing one time bugsnack was that it's just unfucking believable i think
he was at like some tournament or something i don't i don't follow league at all but you know
i think he's funny yeah he was on stage doing like an uh the analyst desk and he shouted out his
website to like his merch site they're like oh so where'd you get that shirt and he's like
he says www.tilerone.com discount code alpha he says it's so unbelievably fast like five times
in a row it's like it's like and it's not even like a joke it's not even oh wow you
messed that up a little bit he said it perfectly three times in like one like two tenths of a second
i could and if you slow the video down to like 20 percentile it's perfect and then like the
analyst at the desk are like all right man like okay that's where you get that you're simping no
i'm though i what i can't say to somebody like that somebody says like funny content that's also
funny well i you've heard me talk about other streamers before that i thought were funny
what i can't talk about another one i can't even do it it's impossible i don't know how he did it
oh bestie it was just looking for you now that wiggles back snacksburg is finally interesting
again i mean also because there are other streamers that i think are funny too you've heard me talk
about everybody here gets all quiet when i'm around but they trust you right bestie so here's
please i'm begging you no i'm not gonna watch like a 45 minute video and maybe i'll tell you
something good in return no watch the sir there are 30 second one rave react wait wait wait wait
wait wait what are you doing put that down put it down put it down drop it put it down here's
here's the video hold on is this the video maybe next time okay this is it all right we're gonna
watch this it's it's crazy how how good this is all right ready maybe next time you wear that tuck
shirt you got going on though all right we dress up here on the analyst deck i like the dress
sleeveless suit wait a minute where'd i get this there go i don't know where did you get it tyler
oh let me tell you
boom there it is
watch this watch this
too fast it's too fast it's still too fast it's still too fast to even hear it
the concentration yeah i just locked it viewers are leaving why what come on and the thing is
that takes a lot of concentration to do that especially to do that on camera with like
thousands of people in a stadium you gotta get that right and he did sorry i can't gotta watch
my little ones of course you do well surely you can take a night off nobody's desperate to steal
from you anymore maybe but even still my kin might wander off if i'm not here this is gonna
take a twist i don't think it is i think this is just a fun game that you relax and play for fun
to return to the watch don't say that this is their home they they love it here
whatever you say darling let me know if you're ever free
there'll be a dark twist i don't think this is gonna be a dark twist all right we're gonna
find out what you do at midnight what time is it all right let's go sleep how's it going
what do you do at midnight all right i'm gonna sleep until midnight we're gonna run out quick
where'd you go are the people in two people wait shit don't look at me what do you do at midnight
she's going into the barn we go
go feet dab wink on screen more what are you doing here none of those things are gonna happen
what are you doing here uh well i'm just looking to spend some time with ramble alone
just she's not happy all right well we have to interview no stranger to interviews darling
hit me with your best shot all right who are you you've certainly heard my number one single
do the wiggle was stuck in my head for a month you see wiggle wiggle bottom needs no introduction
darling why did you come here well i'm here to gorge myself on a new spirit to get creative
juices glowing as it were uh why is juice not flaunt you know no hit can stay on top forever
afraid the audience guilty for wiggles world this isn't an interrogation maybe one more time
it's an interview i've been accused of being a one-hit wiggle tastes like a star going super
nova inside my creative energy like i've never felt before i love the wiggles whatever price
hey darling bug snacks are forbidden fruits darling i believe something exists to keep us
from them she will come for me one day but not before i dazzle the world once more okay what do
why'd you leave that simple what happened to liz what are you doing here why are you
constantly wiggling goodness no i love ramble i would never are too sweet because it's in her
name no i would never take advantage of him you wiggle in your sleep you wiggle while you're on
the toilet you go to the bathroom and wiggle she and eggy bell were big fans of mine you know i
met them backstage at my first farewell tour they didn't have passes mind you liz climbed in
through the air ducts he wiggle during surgery but if somebody breaks the law out of who am i to
turn them away we said shut up in all capitals all right all right all right so what happened
to her let's get more info that night when liz went missing i ran into the woods looking for her
but instead i found something terrifying towering over the trees would you guys think
it was funny if i did a stream where every single person in chat was modded her screech
what definitely and i just had the webcam full cam screaming with like the flight of the bumblebee
in the background i can't be sure anything said that thing that would be the last stream well
could be part of the retirement stream whenever that is i feel the warm glow whenever the
retirement stream is however long that is away we'll do it then in 40 years it's true if you
don't believe me go and see for yourself now if you'll excuse me i've got music to make
i want this character in smash brothers all right wiggle gave you a map to liz's last location
that's intriguing all right we found that we're gonna go back to becca and then wiggle would like
to talk to you about something she would what the hell are you lying on the bed frame like the
headboard that's some discipline if you're not busy darling i could use a helping paw it seems
like your run-of-the-mill bug snacks aren't getting my creative juices flowing i need something oh
spectacular i overheard wambus talking about a sando pee oh you want the sub sandwich of many
pieces working in that's gonna be tricky that may be just what i need okay we need to go get
sando beads i don't want to do that yet i want to do let's go complete this one and then i want
wasn't was that map with uh the new info on it it's the last location i saw lizbert looking down
on camp from between the trees beneath the snow line sugar pine woods the hella we know
we haven't been there yet this is a minus two terrible link is it your margaret thatcher um
that's uh yeah why do you what do you want to show that on stream ah all right i want to go back to
back uh let's go back to becca wherever she is she's here somewhere let's wake her up go on charwee
just follow papa's pointer or or don't that's fine too you know it's weird i don't really like
this guy but i like this guy i don't hate seeing him show up even though i don't like him off to
a bit of a slow start i went so easy with sprout i just know what's going wrong now maybe maybe
sprout can help i'm sure he could show charwee the ropes what do you say uh yeah let's do it
okay here we go training day ready go why are you not going i don't have any chocolate
oh yes i do all right lead him back did you just kick it why did you kick it what was that for
it was rude all right let's avoid her she's a problem hang a right oh didn't mean fall
all right to the finish where's the finish line in here up and over the thing
you did it throwing for content you can hold the dragon it's all right long ways off from
teaching them to spell out we love what did that get me i have to cover myself in sauce every
morning just to get them to pay attention to me but that's just the way it goes for every little
bit of love you got i feel like i know people that look like this guy is it weird to say all
right what were we doing i was going i was talking to becca hanging out somewhere around here where
is becca didn't she live in a cave somewhere didn't she moved here didn't she thought she
moved in here she lives in a cave but i feel didn't everybody come back to town like a campfire
that's her house where is she for the purple house dude ah this is nothing like holding that
camera the whole time omg sounds like wiggle has a nasty habit you say bug snacks i feel bad
probably have a hundred times this last four hours old life i would have killed to get dirt
on wiggle wiggle bottom i used to take pictures for gmz you know and whoever else might be buying
how much would have okay if you had a camera and you're outside my walmart or something and
you found me and you videotape me being like jeremy jerva jerva uh how's the new stream coming
how's stream going i was like the fuck away from me fuck off and i got in my car and drove away i
would how much would that get you on like tmz i was like i got places to be leave me the fuck
alone get the fuck away from me what would it be worth 1500 bucks that's kind of a lot considering
i wouldn't be on the tmz front page i'd be on tmz too they're the best snack ever because they
don't even move that would be a sunday article if you aren't observant like me
that wouldn't be a prime time like thursday afternoon
that's a sunday at sunday like i don't like 4 a.m that's one crispy snack pod where's the
best place to get a crispy snack pod did you just tell me and i wasn't paying attention
probably i would assume that's what happened ethica told me about a snack that hides in her
old cave okay we gotta go back to her where's her old cave nice night out this way right
is it up this way it's this way right you get on the front page all right so if we're not not oh
hey uh mr alberson can we get a moment what if i okay here's another story so instead of hey get
the fuck out here fuck off i say hey get the fuck out of here fuck off and then i get my car
and just start doing donuts in the parking lot with the middle finger out the window window at you
does that improve my chances like get like on get some traction there you just get arrested
yeah but officer i just wanted to get on tmc all right where's this bug is a secret snack pod
oh shit there it is that's how you get on tmz yeah but then my entire career is over
career career in quotes he said career oh new quest what do we get to turn this in first where
are you where are you where are you where are you freed feed one crispy snack they're all doing the
walk hey buddy hey this is wiggle's house where's uh where is she bilbo's house there she's oh there
she's i brought your old bag of potato chips oh i can't say i miss that cave but i do miss these
thanks bestie oh i don't i wish i didn't do anything for you ever uh waldo has something
oh wampo wampus rompus whatever his name is he doesn't have a quest he was just right here
where you go hey hey man oh dude i see you're on a temperpetic journey you can move around all you
want your partner will never feel it and never see it take a look at this egg take a look at
this wine glass get wake up i'm talking to you nothing yet i think something might be wrong
with the soil too dry or maybe too well is there no bed sheet on this bed something needs fixing
why don't you fetch me a big old fibrous bug spuddy like a spuddy i got a plan okay catch a
spuddy that's uh out in um creek canyon these this meat body parts do you think they smell
i feel like after a few days that she's just gonna stink it would just smell like the inside
of a fucking restaurant kitchen everywhere all right get a spuddy from uh creek canyon
get some sauce that's a good call that is a good call i'll get some attention streamer attention
what is it fetish alert sure okay whatever you say whatever you say all right that should be enough
it always hurts whenever you sound does ever sounds defeated defeated how why am i defeated
i'm energized not really but i could be all right there's a spuddy to get a spuddy you need to
spuddy to attack another spuddy oh here you go you two fight each other and i'll get two
follow me wait what do you guys hate hate each other right who's gonna get the ketchup this
fresh ketchup here who's gonna get it what i got hey look what i got over here
all this trick in the book oh this is hot sauce finally it's not even the oldest trick in the
book i just said that because it was easy all right but you i get you i feel like i probably
can't just jump and catch it i'll try damn it i need three of those right that was a completeness
i don't think i can do this yes i can white cheap poop that's not a regular cheap will you take
a white cheap roof oh yeah you i can i can do more than one of the regular in white all right
let's go i'll get this one here too launch pad this oh there's one right here wait pick up this
stuff pirate's booty that shit is unbelievable by the way i love pirate's booty i never buy it
though shit hurry all right one more no one over here yeah smart food used to be really good but
i don't know it's a little too messy pirate's booty is the same flavor as uh smart food but
less gross shit all over your hands you still get that great white cheddar flavor but without the
mess it's great i love it where do you go i don't need hipster food pirate's booty hipster food
explain that one to me somehow maybe i can catch the peppers like that maybe that's just french
fry that's a sweet potato french fry oh what the hell all right sweet potato french fry got it
all right i need one more cheese poop oh hey oh hey and there's the cheesy poop right there
let's get up here so this guy cannot keep ramming me that's not fair and it's annoying and it makes
me angry all right right here damn it that's three all right i got two quests done just like
that are you gonna go back to town but don't feed them yeah actually do feed them feed them
three cheesy poops one and the two legs all right good okay it's gonna get your paws on that bridge
so i'll cut you a deal friend this to get to a new area rider but it's on this ridiculously
tall rock i wasn't exactly blessed with stills wouldn't have it to be a sweet friday would it
it would pleasure doing business with you hey you're my best friend only customer i'm starting
to think i should get a better location back in snacksburg but uh moving all this inventory
across the desert is real sweaty work i get the bridge now cool if you make both my feet
into big popsicle popsicle then walk in the hot sands would be a breeze snow zone i gotta warn
you you won't find popsicles in the desert better look elsewhere pal i need a snow zone
okay i need to turn your feet into bobsicles so does everybody get that reference really
that's sad that nobody knows what that is that's sad maybe next time you wear
it
oh he put the bridge down wait that's a that's a different kind of burger that's a sesame seed
bun burger that's a bacon burger i want the bacon bunker burger i want to put this hold on bacon
bunker burger i need to knock you out follow me what do you love it's a barbecue bonger that's
a barbecue bacon bonger burger this barbecue bacon bonger burger is does he like this barbecue
bacon bonger burger is much more aggressive than this forest cousin it loves ketchup all right
let's start a fight go off the cliff off the cliff no not me oh not me it's my launch pad
what the fuck all right launch pad hey get over here you barbecue bacon bonger burger
so what you're still fine you guys fight got it i got the barbecue bacon bunker burger
i'm saving that one what else did i have to do let's see soiled wampus is looking for some
material okay i had this buddy and then i gotta catch the sub all right let's return this buddy
and somebody said to try this let's see if this works if this works that's pretty cool
oh i could go i could go for a barbecue bacon bonger burger right now who has the best bacon
burger out of the fast food restaurants wendy's but i don't like the wendy's bacon is like kind
of cold and shitty i love wendy's burgers but if you get bacon on them they're kind of cold
five guys that's true five guys could be pretty good five guys bacon burger probably is the best
bet i would say but that's not really fast that's kind of a tear up hey guess what i'm
saying no that's my barbecue bacon bonger burger not yours you heartless monster stop
besides i thought you wanted more bug snacks you know that's not what i meant
and that's not gonna work anyhow that's so dave single let me know when your pets are expecting
i you i really do like the the junior bacon cheeseburger but it's weird and this might just
be my problem but i don't think it is almost every time i've ordered a junior bacon cheeseburger from
wendy's it's been cold just is i've ordered probably it hundreds of times over the last
10 15 years at least 100 times it's always cold it tastes great and it's really good
you know out of my face stop wiggling in my face it's not for you go and feed that to filbo then
hold up by the outhouse for a spell wait when his business is we deliberately giving this guy
diarrhea the night soil waste spud cruds don't make me get crude now no shit i figured it out
he's every funny dad at the dinner table at a restaurant you know he puts the pretzels in he
puts the straw on his nose and he has like he leans in and goes like and it's like dave stop
here eat one of these bootleg reindeer though suddenly i'm feeling nature call sorry gotta go
all right then we scoop up the this is gross i didn't have enough time but it would have been
let's eat let's eat it till next time i'm sorry but the first thing that somebody says to you
when you come out of the bathroom after diarrhea should not be let's eat and i'm standing right in
front of the door that he came out of howdy hey how's it going oh you want this here's your
fertilizer that stink could raise the dead that's bound to be potent enough for my soil thanks
stranger feed him the bag you can't no that's my big barbecue bacon bunker burger give me a lot
give me more bees i want like at least 10 to 15 b descriptions i'm keeping this forever there he
is bodacious bountiful yeah but i want it in a row boneless give me i want the whole thing
big beautiful buffalo no more i want the whole thing bodacious beyond belief that this bumbling
butt head can't brush up his bug catching busts no no i want give it to me in succession big
beautiful boneless bar buffalo barbecue burger no more than that you guys only do it like five
at a time it's shakespeare in chat big butter big buttery boneless boy barbecue bacon burger
i feel like this is just a menu at ruby tuesdays bigger better buttery beautiful bodacious
bumbling bulbous butter butt beater bubbling bubbling bunker big barbecue bunker burger
bioengineering business person bioremodation bronchitis black smith black for me by benzo
no you're doing it wrong i'll do it myself you just can't link everywhere that starts with b
big beautiful booty bodacious big businessman borderland three burger big beautiful big
beautiful boisterous boomerang bird no you guys are so not good at this borderlands three burger
link me the letter b in the dictionary bodaciously bountiful barbecue bacon butter brilliantly
baked before being bitten burger what the fuck is happening peter piper picked a peck of pickled
peppers big baby back bodacious butt eating booby bunker barbecue burger big beautiful
buttery barbecue bacon bumble burger bigger butt better best beef big prepping butt burger
barbecue bacon bunker burger burned brilliantly beyond bountless beautiful buxom buddies oh i'm
having big bitter bizarre blaring bleeding bloody blooming blue blunting blur boiling olivian
bunker burger well i'm having too much fun with this beautiful bodacious bonafide bountiful
buttery big busting booty barbecue bacon bunker burger okay i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done
i'm done i'm done okay i will read a few more of these as birdie said yes uh i'm here at ruby
tuesdays uh do a small uh campaign meet and greet uh what do we have on the menu here let me see
uh yes uh ma'am ma'am i will take the big beautiful boundless beefy beastly booty
eaten bacon barbecue bunker burger please and can i order one of those for the entire restaurant
i'll take two for every person that is here
excuse everybody in the restaurant please if you i'm gonna have total silence when i order
the food that i'm gonna order for everyone here what's gonna happen i'm gonna be ordering
the big wrapping beater beautiful butt eating booby bunging bodacious buttery
bunker back baby bernie sanders approved bitten boundless beyond burger it's vegetarian what
happened oh a new quest hello what does he want oh no that's that's a completed quest
yeah bernie bernie bernie stop ordering hamburgers stop ordering burgers you've already
ordered like 30 different ones but there's so many on this menu i have to order them all i gotta try
where are we going all right we gotta get that sub all right where's that sub sandwich bernie
you're getting too big somebody said big beautiful binding of a isaac burger you can't get the sub
yet oh so what the hell am i supposed to do if anybody else have any more quest for me to do
how's it going it looks like you just got out of surgery man like you got like an ear wrapped up
you got like your feet all wrapped up you have anything new nobody has anything new for me
what else am i what am i on all right this cold feet thing i need some big bobsicles
no not again how do i get to like a new area should i go up from garden or out from here
what about up there this looks like a new area sugar pine woods sugar pine woods dee kong racing
i figured it out that's a cookie so fast that evades capture there must be a way to trip it up
it's a cookie what are these una bees cool these snacks will stick to just about anything
including a trap cool what else is there cookie poop this gooey ooey gooey crackery mess is evidence
of a bug snack it only appears at night there's a s'more bug s'more is my favorite dessert i love
those things so much there's a s'more bug i can't wait to get it coming back here at night any others
what's that this sticky glob of honey is evidence of a bug snack these whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa can i go to the top of the mountain oh there's chad hey chad snorpy snorpy bro snorpy get out
here i'm sorry chandler i'm not coming outside i'm close to finishing my next invention return
to your lifting in peace snorpy we talked about this they made a glitch con emote after you
outside at least one hour a day did gotta get some fresh air dog yes what i'll get is the attention
there's nobody out here but us bro better to work in the shadows what i cannot be seen
they did no they didn't i would have been told about that bro if you're not coming outside
i'm bringing the outside to you right he's gonna break his house down
what you cannot lift my entire house oh yes i can i'ma lift your crib dog do not lift my crib
chandler i have delicate instruments in here and lift in your crib dog there i'm out in the fresh
air i can smell the chemtrails the thing about being one of these creatures
is you can't hide that you ate something you know like he has a cinnamon roll on his leg he can't
pretend he didn't eat a cinnamon roll oh hey dude uh you still on that diet still on the diet right
yes of course i'm on my diet right what's the diet consist of fruit fruit bugs and vegetable bugs and
uh exercise right well keep at it seems like it's working pretty well move along interloper
whatever sort of spy or counter agent you are i'm not about to fall for your tricks
there's chemtrails in the in the snack bug world why did i read that move along interloper
haha i don't see any you lied to me
how's that sweet mountain air treating you bro he said it yeah i know he said it i'm so stupid
anyway
i thought you just said that to be funny i didn't even listen to guys they may as well be speaking
a different language i haven't paid attention in three and a half hours i just see funny like green
cartoon character that feed him insects that's all i know i mean i like being in town but it gives
snorpy mad anxiety why don't you talk to him he's not good with strangers so
tell him i sent you okay so i'll talk to snorpy oh he did did he my poor sweet chandler has always
been too trusting what is your business with me your glasses for your glasses i'm not disinterested
but you're still a suspicious individual i propose a test here take my newest invention
the snack grabler i built it so that i could help chandler with his basket bowling problem
it's a backseating i forgot that meant going outside so you do it and then maybe we'll talk
okay you got the snack grapplers switch to your snack grappler by holding q
oh wait can you tell me i can just grab shit out of the air now what's that thing what the
hell is that thing give it to me i want it it's a charm alo this snack is literally on fire it's
from water or ice i love it oh i love it i hear another one what do i hear a sprinkle pede it
likes to climb high on structure maybe move some sauce where is it where where's this thing where's
a sprinkle pede conspiracy board tower uh well wait snail a sina snail very slow very sticky
it likes to stay far out of reach not for long how do i how do i grab it how do i pull it from here
how do you get it it's too sticky well i know what to do oh shit i gotta go over there too launch me
what happened who's this break free what freezes shit don't touch me don't touch me bro all right i
need to use the sticky thing to trap him but then how do i you come here oh i need a bobsicle
freeze anything that touches it there must be a way to melt its icy armor
oh my god you little weirdo come here give this back
fuck fuck fuck hey bobsicle popsicle popsicle all right come here freeze him
bobsicle cookie cookie bobsicle cookie cookies he's laughing at him get him oh my god
okay now what do i do to you don't what use the net i can't pick him up need to melt him
wait what do you like you love chocolate oh my god you love chocolate get him okay now we have
to flip him over who's it what who'd you just oh you just cookie launched him got him all right
now i have to what do i how do i stop you from what do i do for you somebody died over here
i gotta i gotta talk to me and deal i got them i got them both that worked out that worked out
holy shit that worked out really well yeah i need these bobsicles don't i for uh the little red
guy turn chrome to speed into big bobsicles what do i have now these are bobsicles right how can i
tell you need big bobsicles not regular bobsicles you have the treasure map to here that's right
hold on what's that thing okay looking down on camp from between the trees beneath the snow line
i mean the trees beneath the snow line beneath the snow line here come in there that's a yellow
peel bug you literally can't follow a map what are you talking i hold on man all right so there's
the water it's over here behind a big rock is the water with the cabin and then the big rock okay
where's the water in the cabin right there over here okay found it there it is you picked up a
video diary wrong with my watch hey bro it's my turn on the xbox you'll get your turn soon enough
die if you go down there all right this is a sin of snail this is my chance wait a basketball
who like do you like basketballs oh shit wait you get anything for scoring a point
did i win another one no no give me that how are you doing yes who cares what does that even do
okay uh here we go i'm gonna get that and then i'm gonna catch him down here you ready watch my plan
check this out ready i can't stand there never mind wait all right cool i got one i got a i got
a cinnamon snake or snail whatever that's cool all right i have to turn something into one of
these guys right nice dog and then i have the two bobsicles that'll take me to the bobsicle guy
help chandlo oh hello hello where'd you go where's chandlo he ran away and low where'd you go
it said follow i know but i was i wanted to where'd he go i have no idea where he is
follow me i turned and go completely opposite way and talked to guy in cabin where'd he go he
went to basketball um where's basketball again this way launch oh there he is oh hey man check it out
my own personal dunk zone problem is i lost my balls they're stuck all over the place
i'm sure i could get them down without your help but snorphy made that grapple thing okay let's
get the grapple these guys are gonna go back to town i put chandlo's basketballs into the basket
thanks dude you know in an nba jam for the super nintendo if you went all the way to the edge like
this it was almost a guaranteed swish every single time as long as you held the button for
like one second fuck is going on hey i did it all right chandlo come on whatever chandler let's go
i bet it can grab all kinds of stuff check it out there's a sinner snail right over there
i know it looks like a sticky dump truck full of cars he must have fallen off actually a master
climber no that was just a way to trick me see then he runs away he's trying to get rid of me
hey look over there catch me that's in a snail bro
oh yeah i feel stronger already it's dump truck bro climb right out of here
race you back to the cabin fuck out of the way i take this dead serious man
wait oh shit what are you doing i'm trying launches left click race you bro
ice you made it fast for a newbie me i got the same time i always get
i guess one bug snack isn't enough to push my limits there's got to be more
sinner snails around this mountain dog this guy kind of guy fury isn't he i catch two
sinner snails i will but not yet help chandler all right let's get some sinner snails this one
right there okay pretty cool launch or please stop talking about guy fury he's like one of my
favorite actors how can i not on basketball hey drink bro where's it i need another there's
another sinner snail oh dumb sinner snails into my mouth hoop dog i got on the flip-flop bro i kind
of hate this guy actually all right two sinner snails and then we'll give you a sinner snail uh
toe yeah that's what i'm talking about i can't wait to check my gains but before that i got a
situation honeybees flew off with my backup balls now my balls are up in the sky no matter how
shredded i get i can't fly believe me i've tried you gotta be my wings dog master that grabber
catch me those honeybees just do it yourself i'm gonna hate you fuck you i knew everyone was
gonna freak out okay they'll stick to anything so i gotta launch traps up there they'll stick to
anything even traps all right well i have that one locked on here we go it's one take two all right
here again stay on hey launch it to add to make the honeybee noise honeybee honeybee
let's give him gooey knees
arbo load
you really did me a solid if you want me back in town i'll be there all right see you there
i ain't going anywhere without my main dog snorpy he'd be lost without me i can't get
snorpy to leave though i'm sure i'll find a way to make him leave keeping him here he doesn't
want to talk but i got all the info i needed by the way fucking launched hey you have a secret
project yes i wish i could tell chandlo everything but knowing the truth would only put him in more
danger anyway you have my thanks for helping him perhaps i can trust you after all i am
suck all the air out of a basketball engineer and seeker of truth you want here new chum lean
in close so that i may bestow a hug on you ah ah what an excellent hugging experience that was
we shall have to do that many more times now i need your help are you willing to risk your life
for the greater good no i would die for you splendid there is another device you will need
i've hidden it inside the bug watch tower once you have it i will tell you more okay get the
tool from the bug watch tower tower power that back don't take that from me hello hello can you
yes that's right i planted a radio tracking device on you during our mutual hugging
now we can communicate securely
what's this
oh final tool i just tried to hit right click to aim down sights you got the trip shot that's i
didn't shoot it why did i have fires deploy oh it's not a gun it's like a century okay i get it
what's happening yawn now we gotta wait get that oh shit's fire forgot cookie help me stop bro such
a craving for cookies why my craving is so terrible that i would like my teeth to be cookies so that i
may taste my own teeth you see there was an old story about this kid that anything that he ate
was chocolate didn't matter what it was anything he put in his mouth it turned to chocolate and
he ate it and he ended up hating it after a while he would drink out of a fountain it would be
chocolate milk in his mouth a chocolate in his mouth and there was some lesson there that he
had to learn and it was something like um if you eat the same food over and over again it sucks and
you get sick of it he killed his mother by accident and he ate his mother oh well i don't
remember that part of the story all right we need uh i actually i have i have a cookie cannot attach
to snow sand or i have a cookie it's splendid i no longer have to worry about psychotronic
torture or cavity kissed his mother and she turns into chocolate for charmallows he eats her have
enough charmallows catch two charmallows okay so then we we gotta i it was just kind of chaos
the last time i did this i don't remember how to do any of this okay where's the i gotta bring you
to cool them off what do they like they're obsessed with something what the hell is that
okay you love chocolate come over here okay wait you have your objects in mirror way closer than
they appear never mind aren't there something over here i swear there was one that was flying
around here maybe not i guess i'm gonna have to lure that other one with i'm gonna cover myself
with chocolate and run around in a circle game gives you heartburn this game makes me hungry
i need a popsicle there we go all right you follow me come on bobsicle okay now chocolate is selected
he's very chocolatey take a look are you too high to understand this hey all right come here
what did you do wait why you like chocolate too what the fuck just happened
what happened did i get him pick him up pick him up pick him up why can i pick him up is he okay
i can't pick him up oh dear he's dead oh hello yeah he's dead he ain't getting up from that one
sorry bobsicle you wouldn't mean i killed him he he jumped on the trampoline and killed himself
i didn't do anything all right two charmeleons marshmallow nose oh i like you you're gonna look
really goofy a graham cracker head and a marshmallow nose blind spot in place i can safely return to
snacksburg meet me outside this guy seems cleared of danger i suppose it's now or never
snorpy's ready to go we got two all right dog let's do this in just a moment chandler
you've been an invaluable ally i'm even tempted to call you a friend but quietly so i'm not
overheard bro if i didn't think it would crush you like a tin can i would hug the grump out of you
oh what the grump here it comes these two are just they want to hug expert hugging that is
you do that hug yeah you're doing a real good job of hugging me back to town snork dog
don't please don't make me run with you chandler i'll go weaken the knees if you're not up for it i
could always carry you no no that's quite all right your loss see you back in town bro
hello you did it i think he's okay up there i help him down he doesn't know how to get down
it's like a cat in a tree fuck him okay he hates those things all right well come on let's go
let's go move oh oh get down get down what about hot sauce you like hot sauce
so
i saved him see now he's like an orange creamsicle he's fine i thought he was gonna do it again
is this annoying you is this annoying you is this annoying you belong up there is that a crying face
emoji all right i got the bobsicles he cannot reintegrate into society after being up there
why what he's going good all right no no no no don't get distracted i need to first of all i
want to feed this potato to somebody make them look weird not you um yeah we're almost done with
making you look totally weird here take another one of these spuds uh spud elbow yeah okay you
look nice and weird how's it hanging no too many quests i have to go do i gotta go get the other
there's one more guy we have to get down here turn his feet into bobsicles just he just ate
aluminum obstacle zone all right i got your legs here we go my obstacle leg obstacle leg
you look great his feet oops i take them off i take them off can i say can i rip them off
see ya it's his feet oh big beautiful big burger barbecue burger bunco burger
reload this game auto saves probably every five seconds oh he's recycling jokes he's desperate
a desperate man big beefy beer battered bong water wrapper barbecue burger no we're not doing
this shit again just give me one more obstacle and get me out of here there's no ruby tuesdays in
vermont don't be sad about that that place sucks don't like be annoyed by that that's like oh no
too bad i can't go to ruby tuesdays the place is like not even good is he still up here go off on
ruby no go off i'm not no but okay i've eaten look i've eaten at ruby tuesdays three times
and it was it was uh it was it was passable it was okay it was like oh it was all right
it was like okay i wouldn't say it's the greatest it was good bad kind of but like not terrible
the waiter was nice there was like a nice place all right i need to burn this guy but if i'm gonna
get it if i if i'm gonna get a burger from a restaurant i'm gonna go to a restaurant that
has good burgers i know you go to ruby tuesdays for the burgers but i don't know i don't consider
them to be like that good oh there's another box to go down here not mcdonald's no ruby tuesdays
better than mcdonald's ruby tuesdays is probably better than any fast food restaurant i would say
probably but not by very much all right i need a fire fire you're new who are you that's a rainbow
sweetie fly ruby tuesdays is for the salad not the burgers somebody lied to you put him in the hot
water there how come there's no um with those flies anywhere
hurry up you like ketchup all right he's now i have to knock him out
knock him out knock him out knock him out okay i got him i got a big butt a big okay i need
another one that's a much better strategy isn't there another one down here need another bobsicle
please all right morty relax oh and you know like i like rick and morty is just like
poison to you guys why i found all right i'm trying to figure this out why is rick and morty
just just poison to your ears what what happened tell me if i hear like oh rick and morty
oh
it's because it has our reddit fan base yes so does every fucking tv show cartoon video game
but our smash brothers are uh the kid Icarus are so look everything has a subreddit we're talking
about our germa 985 our family guy our american dad our dexter shows that haven't been on the
air for like five years guys still have reddit fan bases that still stick around oh there we go
i'm here where's the other bobsicle remember watches dexter omega lol no the point is i
haven't watched it in like 10 years i need another bobsicle at night time fine because of the sauce
what sauce what the hell garfield oh i got i need a bobsicle bob found a bobsicle bobsicle
bobsicle all right knock him out knock him out into the tree what the fuck you're right
oh shit he exploded oops no i need you to be big can you guys combine give me my sauce what
sauce are you talking about i need another bobsicle give me the mcdonald sauce oh give
me my okay i see what you're doing give me my sauce give me my sauce what the fuck is that thing
hey why didn't i take a picture of it i should just take a picture of it i was frozen in fear
happened what was that oh i know what happened to liz that's her that's liz i get it okay so
like yeah she ate a ton of these and became that i get it i understand the game now still need a
bobsicle though and we are all becoming that by eating the bar of the bubsicles too much i see
because we're slowly all going to turn into that kind of shit i see all right it's just like that
story of the chocolate the kid the kid that could eat anything that would become chocolate in his
mouth give me a bobsicle please god before i freak out i can't believe i didn't get a picture of it
that's so sad i didn't get a photo i have just sitting there just staring into nothing
to leave the area yeah just this gloop Augustus gloop Augustus gloop end of the stream voice
probably soon after i do these quests probably no i don't know the lyrics every song in the
remake of Willy Wonka was just it said the character's name like three or four times
to a catchy beat Willy Wonka Willy Wonka a famous chocolatier Augustus gloop Augustus gloop
he did something he did this Elvira Elvira Elvira you're in trouble i hear a bobsicle yes i do
he didn't get put out all right bobsicles my favorite character so far i want a good photo
look at me look at me hey he didn't even care get over here all right he's been out
flip him over hey hey hey look at me get angry get angry get angry let's go
i got two crunchy bags oh what am i gonna get what am i gonna get i need food what is it gonna be
bacon bungo burger maybe why are you not getting the new sauce um i don't know plan on it
taco sauce Wendy has that pretzel burger that's true i wanted to try that for a while now one of
you guys told me that it wasn't that good though somebody said it was okay it wasn't that great
so i don't know is it any good all right big bobsicle feet big bobsicle feet
now you can walk on acid and fire these things better not melt off anyway a deal's a deal friend
the bridge is yours some assembly required the pretzel burger is good but if you burp after you
will fucking die and so you know it makes me not want to eat it for any loss or injury something
of the use of it i i know what you mean by that and that scares me anything at all please please
please call your friend what does that mean that i am when in my mind i assume that you didn't
even fix the bridge you didn't do anything what i feel okay if after you eat like a bunch of
cheese and pretzel and bacon and pub cheese i can imagine the burps would come up and it would be
number one they would stink right like don't let's be real but be realistic with ourselves
they probably smell horrible and it would probably burn too like a little like painful and like
acidity hurt your throat too yeah probably what the fuck is pub cheese you know i don't know what
it is it's this orange spreadable cream cheese shit that has this odd taste to it what is pub
cheese it's cheese and alcohol he's from beer no no i don't think it is pub cheese is human vomit
that's gross it's beer cheese hold on wait wait wait i need to look at this i'm gonna wrap it up
here by the way pub cheese i'm just curious what this is okay what is pub cheese pub cheese is a
type of soft cheese spread and dip prepared using cheese as a primary ingredient and usually with
some type of beer or ale so you were right okay it's beer cheese but it's not i've had pub cheese
a bunch of times before it i've had specifically beer cheese before and beer cheese to me is way
better pub cheese doesn't taste like beer cheese to me for some reason now i don't i know everything
about wendy's well that's interesting because your name is mcgriddle tony you seem to be dabbling in
the competition as well tony this you're a traitor that's what you are
that's a great name though mcgriddle tony i know everything about wendy's but here's the thing
you might know everything about everything about all the fast food places and the mcgriddle might
just be your favorite so okay i think i get it it is a good name it really is i haven't had a mcgriddle
in so long they still make them it's like two little pancakes with the bacon egg and cheese
in the middle they're actually really good all right i'll uh i'll see you guys uh tomorrow
tomorrow monday let's see maybe monday tuesday let's check the sauce probably tomorrow let's see
tomorrow for some reason i don't stream tomorrow i'll stream monday but i'll be playing on tomorrow
starting around probably the same time somewhere around two thanks for watching this has been
i don't i'm may or may not play this again tomorrow kind of invested we'll see i'll see
you guys tomorrow regardless whatever we do take care of yourselves let's go let's take a look at
the credits there are all the wonderful subs subscriptions multi-month multi-year
subscriptions thanks guys i had fun i think it's a good game uh wtr6k4da gave 20 community subs
we caught that but we did not see the 100 fucking dollars that they also gave they said thanks for
all the laughs of the years jeremy your content is really uplifting also game sucks with a santa cappa
game sucks i don't think the game sucks i think the game is pretty cool actually game does not
suck i want to see the ending yeah i do too we're probably gonna play this tomorrow we'll play
tomorrow we're gonna i want to complete bug snacks all right i'm getting a little tight so i gotta
get up i will see you guys tomorrow well bug snacks too have a great rest of your night take care guys