Alright, let me get, I need to have my Chrome. Google Chrome. Look at that. Um, give me one second.
Turn on cam, turn on cam, turn on cam, turn on cam. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I have to change to just chatting too. Where the heck? And I gotta have music too. I can't just
sit here silent. We need like a music. I'll turn the camera on, but it's not right. I need music.
Face cam, please. I'm going to put it on. I'm very sweaty though. Okay. Let's do this condiments and
sauces. Okay. And then world of Warcraft expansions. This one's going to be really fun. I can't wait to
do this one. What's this? This is YouTube link. Why did I just click? I'm not, why did I just click
that? That's why would I click the first link in chat? Am I insane? I'm not playing Joel's
3d movie maker movie for background noise. I want to watch it on the video stream.
It's not, that's not music. What's this? This is the same one. I'm just going to put on my own.
Okay. We, how about, uh, no, I'm not watching it. No, we're going to watch it during the
watch movies stream. Cause that's a, that's a movie. It'll be in between two public domain
movies. All right. What do I want to listen to? How about let's go back to here. Oh no. It's,
oh shit. My shit's broken. Can I do this? Let's get that window, window capture.
Oh no, Jeremy, your stream. It's all right. It'll be fine. Don't worry. Everybody relax.
Condiments and tier lists. Let's shrink this, shrink that so we can see it better.
I'll put my camera up here. I look wicked ugly. No, I don't look pretty handsome. Okay.
Let's take a look. How do I look right now? I think I've ever had like some stains on my shirt,
but what am I going to do? Can you see me? Why is the camera so big? Oh right. I was doing that.
Thank you. Look at how big. Oh, hi guys. I know I'm not a single and there we go. Wait, let me
apply. No, who cares? All right. So let's go. Jeremy lied about wicked ugly. Uh, I'm going to say,
first of all, let's add actually, no, this is just D is just D already off the bat. I, well,
I'm not even in just chatting. How do I change that? Hold on. Can I first close this? What the
fuck am I doing? Just chatting. Just how about just tears? I mean, that's what we're doing.
That looks good. Tears. We're in the right category. I got to get a haircut too. Thanks
for reminding me. All right. So we've got sriracha. I hate it. Honey. Let's put a honey and B for now.
I didn't even put on any music either. It'll come later. Mayonnaise. But the thing is about
mayonnaise. I don't, I don't eat. I don't put it on everything. I only put it on some stuff.
This just hurts. I did it when something hurts to eat it. I don't want it. This is mayonnaise,
right? Okay. Ranch. I think ranch is overrated, but I still like it.
I've not made my decision. Honey is in B. I hold on. I'm just getting, I'm just getting it up here.
I'm not ready yet. Hummus is somewhere between A and S. It's I lived off that stuff in college.
Tomato, like pizza sauce. Why is there like tomato sauce? It's like spaghetti. This is pesto.
It's okay. This is Dijon mustard. I'm just getting it up there. This is barbecue sauce.
Hold on. Just to keep it, keep it in B. Tartar sauce. B. Frank's Red Hot is the worst condiment
in the world. It is absolutely fucking revolting. It does not know what it wants to be.
It so desperately wants to be a hot sauce, but it just tastes like buttery, gross liquid. It's
like that hot flavor, right? No, it's awful. It's hot sauce that's not hot. It's just like
the buffalo flavor. That's the worst one in the whole list. So I would eat Sriracha five
times before I had Frank's once. Regular default, yellow mustard. I like Dijon better.
Thousand Island is all right. Ketchup is good, but I'm going to have a lot of B's.
Jack Daniel's. Just Jack Daniel's barbecue sauce or like just drinking Jack Daniel's?
Honey mustard, that goes up here. This is guacamole. Guacamole, it really depends on what
kind of guacamole and who made it because guacamole can be down here or guacamole can be up here.
So I'm going to take the average and I'm going to say somewhere around here, like here. Okay, now
salsa is S. I eat salsa all the fucking time. I love salsa. It's, yeah. Salsa is one of the
only things you could just eat every day and probably not care and not get sick of it.
That and this is a Cholula. Cholula is good. Cholula is better than Sriracha. In my opinion,
rather have to say that is better than guacamole. This is not even done. This is not even correct.
This is not accurate. Maple syrup. What is this? Relish. And then this is Worcestershire sauce.
I don't put it on anything. All right. Let me, okay. I need music.
Give me music. Turn that camera off first. You marinate. Yeah, but it's on a, is that condiment?
Oh, it's soy sauce. Right. Okay. If it's soy sauce, I don't like it. I actually really don't like soy
sauce at all. I'm sorry. I know people are getting mad about that. It's not that far down though.
It's, I would rather have soy sauce than like Jack Daniel's fucking garbage can barbecue sauce.
All right. I need music. Just chill music. Chill out music. I did click on the first one, which
means, is this point your camera out the window airplane vlog? I don't know. Is it? This is like
a regular song. Chill step. There's something called chill step. What is that genre? I like
this. This is fine. This can stay. Come back. So let me, let me narrow this down. Honey should be
up here. Pesto is good for three bites. And then you start, it's just be, you hate it. Seriously,
like the first two or three bites of something with pesto on it, you go, holy shit, that's
fucking incredible. And then after that, you do like, I don't want to eat this anymore.
I would definitely rather have tomato sauce on something than ranch. I would never eat this.
No, they would never, I would never eat that ever. Pesto is a condiment for an obese college student.
What? Hold on. I got to fix my like Lego hair. It's a little better. Tartar sauce is not better
than barbecue sauce. It's good. It's close. It's really close. I'm trying to figure out this is
S or A. They both S. Would I rather like, no, sausage is S. Sausage complete S.
Honey is better than Thomas. I have a rule that I cannot have more than two or three S's. So it,
otherwise, like what the hell do you think you're doing? Oh, I would put, I would use it. I would
use both of them. Ketchup is better than mustard. I'm talking regular, just yellow mustard. I think
I'm good. I think this is it. No, it's not true. I'm done. Why is soy so low? I just, I don't know.
I don't like it. It just tastes, it just tastes like salty, dirty water to me. I know. Everybody
hates me now. I know. But I, but look, it's not, I, this is, I would still eat it. I would still
like it. I wouldn't mind it if it was like part of something, if it was on something already,
but adding soy sauce is just like salt water. It's just like, it's like taking a, you're dipping
a cup in the ocean and like sipping the cup. It's just like salt bomb. If it's on something and I,
dipping like sushi in it, that's pretty good. But honey is gross. Well, we have different opinions
and I'm so happy about that. Hey, I like soy sauce more than I like relish. In fact, that's not fair
because I would rather have this than, now it's ready. I'd rather have Cholula than soy sauce.
I'd rather have tomato sauce than soy sauce. I'd rather have guacamole than soy sauce. I'd rather
have, this is not true. That's completely untrue. I actually would not, I would rather have soy
sauce than pesto. No, I wouldn't. Guacamole, no. Okay. I'm done. Uh, Joel just, Joel just rated me.
What's up, Joel? Your movie was fucking sick. I saw your movie. It was fucking sick.
My favorite part is when, I mean, he did, liar, liar. What? Don't, don't mess around like that.
Joel, what do you think of my list and those viewers that came from, Joel, what do you think
of this list? People, Joel, mayonnaise, right? It's an English thing. Joel's not from England.
Don't even, why I said that? Um, not even close. Same, same like continent. Okay. Um, I'm, it's
an English, that's a, that's a European thing. That's what I was told. I was, I told the fries in,
in, I almost said oregano. Fries and mayonnaise is an, is a European thing. Joel, please quantify
this. Mayo on fries is definitely a European thing. Joel, do you do this? Joel, I'm not going
to move on until you answer me. You're not even here. I got long ass fingernails. Uh, he's not
even here. He's not here. Oh, well, thanks for the, no, really, thanks for the host or the raid,
whatever it was. I hope you guys had a fun time. He did respond. Thank you, Dad, for the 10 community
subs. We got him, oh yeah, World of Warcraft expansions. Right, that's the other one.
Here we go. Ready? I'll do this with my eyes closed. I think I'm probably gonna get it right.
Let me just see where they are. Like, no, I didn't even have to look at it. I, okay.
World of Warcraft expansion tier list and just game tier list. I'm not even paying attention.
I don't even know what I'm looking at. Where, okay, where, where, where is, where are we?
Where's Burning Crusade? Where's Burning Crusade? Fast as lightning. The panda is in A? No, no, no,
no, it's not. Uh, this is where the game started to be bad. This is, I remember, I remember,
I remember loading up World of Warcraft during that expansion and playing for like six hours and
going, this is, this game's not fun anymore. That's where I started to stop playing. Then,
you're probably wondering, Jeremo, what the fuck is Legion doing? I think Legion was the best,
like, the best expansion that came out recently in the last, like, 10 years. How long, well,
this is two expansions ago, right? Legion brought me back to the game and I thought it was really,
really, really great. Not as good as that when you first played on classic. Wrath of the Lich King,
best expansion pack. I think that's not an unpopular opinion and Burning Crusade, very
classic. These were, these were, these were so awful, I'm gonna give them a mention. I'm
not even sure this is even the right one, but I know it's not one of these, so it's, it belongs
down here. All right, any more? Official TF2 maps. You want to do TF2 maps? Chex mix. I don't think
I can do the TF2 maps. It's been a long time. Why can I not? Computers are so bad. I can't even
right-click in the chat that's in Streamlabs OBS. Have I said anything good about Streamlabs OBS?
Why do I still use it? Is there a reason why I'm still using this? This is free. No, so I'm not
talking about it, right? Yeah, I guess. Uh, there's so many maps in TF2. This is gonna, I don't know
if I can, I might have to do, this is gonna be sloppy. Not using XSplit. I tried to use XSplit,
it's way worse. And you have to pay for XSplit. Remember, JetBlue is the only company I like.
All right, where was it? TF2 maps. Let me see it again. Foldmetal Alchemist characters. All right,
let's do Chex Mix. God damn it, give me a break. Uh, Chex Mix. Okay. Chex are gross. I dare,
they're not good. They're very, they're very bad. Now I'm done. This has to be like a generational
change thing. You ate around the Chex when I was younger. You didn't eat the Chex. It's like, just
do Foldmetal Alchemist. Why do you want me to do Foldmetal Alchemist? Call of Duty games? I've
played three of them. I can't do this one. Official TF2 maps. Well, why not? Let's do this one. This
sounds like interesting for a little bit. Oh my God. I'm kind of getting into the, into the weeds
here. Uh, are these five CP or? Okay. I don't, no opinion. I don't have any opinion. Manpower?
No, no, no, no. Thunder Mountain Manpower. What do you, what does this, what does that mean?
Tuber Town? Thunder Mountain Manpower. It's just Thunder Mountain. Okay.
I don't remember. Hydro? F. Doomsday? F. Snowplow? I actually kind of remember this being, okay.
Upward. Did I have more fun on Gorge or upward? That's accurate. Now I love Gorge. Attack Defend
Gorge is like the best map they've ever made. I love for Gorge. It's so much. Um, where's Dust
Bull? Yeah. Call me a loser. Call me like an idiot. That's fine. That's one of my favorite
maps. Original, original team for you. It doesn't even play TF Classic. You understand.
This is Team Fortress 2. I know. Badwater is up there, but it's okay. It's okay. Nightfall.
I don't, Banana Bay. Don't know. Two Ford Invasion. I played it like once or twice.
Barn Blitz. Get up there. It leads to B. It's an A. No, it's not. Probed. Frontier. Get up there.
Frontier is not better than Badwater. Yes, it is. It's better than Badwater. Better than Barn Blitz.
Um, Viaduct. This is not fair though because this is different game modes. Like I think Viaduct is
awesome, but I don't know if I would put Viaduct in the same category as like upward. You know what
I mean? They're like they're completely different game modes. That's just tricky. This is not
accurate. I'll keep doing it though. Um, I know a lot of people that play comp are going to hate my
guts, but I really don't like any of the comp maps. I really don't like them that much. I just don't.
Two Ford sucks, but it's fun just to snipe. Granary is not that low. I know, but Lakeside.
I love Lakeside, but not how much though. Not that much. I've never been to Brazil.
Snowy Coast. It's taken me a while to remember these though. Snakewater? No.
No. Wait, Snakewater was... No, that's Badlands.
Powerhouse? Well, no. I don't really... Where's the one that I really don't like?
It's Harvest. Yes, can you tell? I just played Harvest for like six hours straight. Like three
days a week. I just like... What do you... Oh, there's... There it is. Where... What does it do?
Tack Defend Gorge. There it is. Sawmill. Sawmill. Sawmill. Sawmill is good, but I don't know if I
would put sawmill up where Nucleus is. I really don't think so. Egypt. Awful. King of the Hill
Badlands. Do I remember playing this? Where is the... Where is the... Where is it? Not Junction.
It was one of the fairly newer ones when I... Right before I stopped playing.
Is this Payload Thunder Mountain? Yeah. Get this out of here. Manpower. What was it called?
Was it Borneo? I think it was Borneo. I really liked this one, if I'm remembering correctly.
This is the one where it... Where it turns the corner and there's always a sentry in the little
house? Yeah, this one's great. I was... I was that guy. I was the one doing the sentry in the little
house. It worked every time. What a great game. This game's so good. Why can... Why can nothing
ever replace this? No, I didn't really like the Sawmill map. I don't know what Watergate is.
I think these are Manver's Machine Maps. I can't... Don't know opinion on it, really.
Kong King was not very good. I really don't like Kong King. People are going to hate me for this
one. I actually really like Turbine. It's a mess. Well, I don't really like it. I like it enough.
Mercenary Park. Lazarus Pipeline. I remember Pipeline. What is the one that never ends?
What is Hightower? There it is. Okay. Hightower also comes up a little bit higher than Turbine,
for sure. New maps are good. Timbertown. Oh, I really hated Steel. I remember every time
it would change to Steel, I would instantly hit cancel. I'd spam, spam, spam, because the game,
when it was loading, you couldn't do anything. And I remember just trying desperately to make
sure I hit cancel so I could go back to the other, to the service screen. Every time.
Process was okay. I don't remember it enough, though. How could I forget this? I love Hoodoo.
Bypass. Manhattan. Degroud Key was... It's better than Steel, and it's better than... Yeah, it's not
like it's better than Kong King, though. Tsukimaki. Junction. Don't like it at all.
Better than Steel, though. And better than Degroud Key. Vanguard. I don't... Powerhouse,
I don't... I played it, but I don't... Not enough. What's the one with the two that cross in the
middle? The payload war. Is that Nightfall? That's Nightfall, right? Better than Granary. I had fun
on it. Same with Pipeline. I don't remember which one I like more. A lot of you were waiting for
this one. I have days and days, probably dozens and dozens and dozens of days played on Gold Rush.
So much time just doing the same thing, but it was so fun. That's the thing with Team Fortress 2
that no game since has been able to do, and that's doing the same fucking thing every time you play
was always fun because there were so many variables in the game to make it so it didn't matter that
the same goal was happening. There were so many things happening inside of that game.
Nobody's been able to do it since. Not sad music. Well, it should be. Building a century in TF2
in the same spot in Gold Rush. I know where it is. I can see it. Hundreds of times. Every single time
was fun. Every time. That's not the same for other games. Even when Overwatch came out and I played
Overwatch, the thing that really grabbed me in Overwatch that I really, really liked, I thought
it was really, really awesome, was the pig guy. What was his name? Hogwash? What's the guy's name?
Roadhog. The chain was, I loved it. I loved it. I loved the chain so much. And Zenyatta's orbs.
Putting the healing orb on people and the chain where those do it every single time, do it every
single game. And it's always fun. But it was the only two things that I really can pull out that
I thought were that fun. And maybe running around as Lucio. But something about the maps and how
messy it got. It got real messy. TF2 got messy. But not like shields and everywhere. There's a
million people. It's like less people but more bullshit. It's just kind of hard to look at
sometimes. You could have 30 people in a TF2 server and you would still almost be at the crest
of the amount of just weird bullshit on the screen that happens with one 5v5 Overwatch match.
Nobody's been able to really come that close. Overwatch was really damn close though.
I had a lot of fun playing the first four or five months of that game. I really did.
But it just didn't hold me. It held me for about six months. And then I was like,
but that's still... I mean in the grand scheme of things. Playing a game for like
four or five six months straight. I mean that's pretty good. I would have loved to have it hold
me forever. Held me for about three or four months. Same. Yeah. I think that's really what
it comes down to that's wrong with Overwatch. There's only 12 people in an Overwatch game.
But there's 10 times more bullshit than having 60 people be in a TF2 game.
I mean you can make fun of Valve as much as you want. But they took almost a decade to make this
game. Changing things. Redoing things. They took almost 10 fucking years to make this. So it had
everything they wanted. The classics will always remain timeless. Yeah. But TF2 is probably the
last game that I really really wanted to play every day. Feels bad, man. Feels bad, man.
Because now this stuff holds my... Pay no attention to that. Stuff holds my attention now.
Like I'm sure a lot of you can agree. But I'm not into the... I'm really not into VR at all.
And that's what's currently like holding a bunch of people's attention is like stuff like Fortnite,
Apex, the Call of Duty stuff. I just don't... It doesn't do it for me. Same thing with MOBAs too.
Smite was probably the last one that I thought was actually pretty fun. But like Beta Smite. And
like maybe just barely after release Smite was awesome. And then I don't know. I wasn't really
into it after a while. Same deal like another like four to six months and that was it. I gave up on
it. Beta Smite was perfect. It was so good. VR is just temporary fad. It will die in the next few
years. I'm not so sure about that. People were saying that when stuff like DayZ was kind of
getting to be really popular and they were like ah this is this is just fad. This would be gone
in a few years. And then Fortnite is still huge. PUBG. Yeah PUBG came after DayZ. And I wish I...
I wish I liked those games. I really do. Because I would be playing them. And like stuff like
Counter-Strike is always going to be around. CS GO is just always going to be popular. It's a
high kind of skill ceiling team FPS. I mean people love CS GO. I just... Not for me.
Never played Tribes Ascend. Yes it was fantastic. Hi-Rez did this really really great
job on the first like six months of their games being released. And then they kind of didn't...
They went to shit. The first like four to six months of Tribes Ascend. What an un-fucking
believable experience. The first like four to six months of Smite. What an un-fucking believable
experience. I think that Hi-Rez has made like just base video game has made some of the better
video games in the last decade. Like just straight up just like Tribes Ascend as a video game.
Forget about like any patches of what they did. But like when that first released
it was amazing. Video game. Video game. Video game. When they made a video game. All right I'm
gonna get back to this. Hi-Rez abandoned their games. I don't think... No they didn't. They just
focused on other stuff. They kind of spread themselves out. Focused on the new thing. Focused
on the new thing. No they... Well they did... Yeah Tribes. Yeah you're right. They did. They kind of
just gave up on Tribes. They actually abandoned Tribes. Yes they did. If Tribes got the same kind
of TF2 treatment I would probably still be playing it. Anyways let's continue. Dirty Bomb. I actually
never played Dirty Bomb. Maybe for like a... No I never played Dirty Bomb. I remember. I couldn't
install it. What happened? Some of you guys might remember this. This was on stream like six years
ago. What happened? Remember? Who was around for that? I tried to play it. I got like locked out.
I couldn't install it. Me and Star were playing it. Like he was playing it. I was just watching
this. I couldn't install it. You made a meme during Star's video about what a shitty dream
playing Dirty Bomb would be. I don't remember. I don't remember. I never played Lawbreakers. No.
Because I saw the writing on the wall with Lawbreakers from the second they announced it.
I knew if I got into it that the thing was just going to be dead anyways. Like I just knew I could
see it from a mile away. That first gameplay trailer I was like that's probably going to be
a failure. But it looks... I'm not going to invest into that. Because if you do... Let's say you
invest a shitload of time into a game. Like this probably people that... That's not to say I don't
think the game was any good. I don't have an opinion. I can't have an opinion on it because
I didn't play it. But if you really liked Lawbreakers, you were a huge fan of Lawbreakers.
That got to hurt if you were one of the people that like really cared about that game.
And you put a bunch of time into it. And you played a bunch of it. And then they're just like
yeah that's it. Like oh well fuck I really liked this. Halo on PC in two weeks. That's another
thing to be excited for. If you're one of the 19 players. That's mean. That's mean. Oh Joel's in
the chat. Joel's in the chat. What's up Joel? What do you... What do you got? You got something for me?
Huh? Hmm. Why you not VIP'd so I could like see what you're writing? VIP Varg Skelethor.
That's correct right? Varg Skelethor. All right what's up? Would you be up for playing
Tribes Ascend with our viewers? Let's revive it man. We have the power. Is the game still turned on?
The switch is still on in that game. Is it? Yeah is it? Did they turn off the servers? Why do I
feel like they did? I would I would play Tribes. What's your schedule look like? It's unlisted on
Steam. Is it unlisted? I think you have to get it right from Hi-Rez right? Play Titanfall 2 instead.
Hey hit me DM me on Discord. We'll talk about it. Titanfall 2 is good. Titanfall 2 campaign.
What you want to do the Titanfall 2 co-op campaign? Does that exist? That doesn't exist right?
There's no co-op. Oh the game sucks then. All right let me finish this up but hit me up. I'll
message you on Discord. I also heard you watched my 3d movie maker thing. It was fucking fantastic.
Seriously it was fucking great. I loved every second of it. When we watch it in the future?
Oh I will. What better time to watch Joel's movie than when he's here?
No no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no. Joel he's got to go. He just said he
had to leave. Joel what you got an appointment? He just said in the chat I've got a I've got an
appointment I have to get to. I need to respect that. What's a ping like from Sweden to Nevada?
Yes my appointment at 4am. See can we like even play games together? Oh we're gonna have like
700 ping. Sorry you can host. I'll take the disadvantage. You know what I mean? Madagascar
lion move. All right fast lane I don't know. Surgeon I don't know. Swift water pretty good.
Double cross not good. Foundry don't like it. But not yeah it's actually except everything's
better than steel. So cold front yeah that goes up here. Pretty good map. High pass I don't remember
really. I don't but I probably should. Gullywash I don't remember. I do though. It's been a long
time. Mountain lab I really did not like mountain lab. Thought it was too. Moss rock don't know.
Gravel pit. One of the only maps with more than two points that's going to be up past AB. Ghost
town don't know. Standen don't know. Decoy I don't know. Metalworks I have no idea. Coaltown don't
know. Snowy coast probably played it maybe once. Manworks don't remember. Enclosure don't remember.
Yukon don't remember. Yeah I do but it wasn't very good. Freight no. Sunshine don't know. Landfall
don't know. Big rock don't know. Brickyard don't know. Okay let's get this right. Best map in the
whole game. The best team fortress 2 map is gorge. Then thunder mountain. Then gold rush. Then dust
bowl. Then upward. Then hoodoo. Then nucleus. Then harvard. Then frontier. No front no. Then
bat no. Then bad water. Then borneo. Then barn blitz. Then gravel pit. Then high tower. No then
lakeside no. Lakeside sucks actually get it down here. Um then viaduct. Then high tower. Then
turbine. Then twofort. Then nightfall. Cold front is better than twofort. Lakeside is better than
pipeline and nightfall. Swift water is better than all these I remember. Process is probably
better than this. Five gorge is still gorge so it belongs at least in head granary. Uh the rest of
these can stay in the same spot. What is the worst map that I've played in team fortress 2? It is
probably it's steel. Steel junction are the two worst. Double cross is also awful because it's
that big road with the one way to get in. You have to go down. Yeah double cross is terrible.
Um digroot keep. Mountain lab should be down here too. Better than digroot. No it's not. Hydro.
Doomsday sucks. Doomsday really sucks. And it's not even the map's fault. It's the terrible
game mode that it's on. Last. Doomsday is worse than steel. I don't know though. I don't think
it's the worst thing in the whole game. I'm trying to think if I see it pop up in the server changing
map loading screen. How fast am I leaving? It's pretty close probably. I don't want to play
doomsday. Digroot keep as well. I just don't want to play it. It was fun for like a week or two and
it was melee only. Storm the castle was fun but not after like a month. You just don't want to
play it anymore. Uh I think this is good. Yukon is okay. Yukon actually is kind of good.
Yeah Yukon's actually all right. Yukon actually I'm remembering now actually Yukon should probably
be up here. Yukon's better than these two. Is Yukon better than the lakeside though?
No that's actually worse than pipeline. Okay so that's it. I'm good. Here's your list. Hydro never
got a chance. I'd still rather play Hydro than steel. I'd rather play Hydro than Egypt. No that's
not true. I'd rather play Egypt than Hydro. I'd rather play Kong King than Hydro. Guys I really
want to bring all and I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna do it. Yeah I'm gonna bring every five CP map down
to F. I would rather play Egypt than well CP. I'd rather play Kong King than five gorge. Goodbye.
Sawmill Coff is okay and stay. Lakeside where are we at? Swiftwater process.
I just would not play it. Sawmill's capture the flag is just turtle mania. You just get two
engineers that sit in the room. The fucking tiny little room that you get the actual briefcase from
and they just have two engineers there. And nope you can't win. Nobody you can't play the game.
So it's not right. I hate it. Ah now I gotta fix this. I'd rather play Sawmill King of the Hill
than these two. I'd rather play Yukon than those two. I'd rather play I don't have any E's left.
Yes I will. Kong King, Hydro all the way to the bottom. I would definitely not rather play
Mountain Lab. Sawmill capture the flag I'd rather do besides the like competitive five CP maps.
Let's get these all the way at the bottom where they belong though. Five gorge is gorge so it
gets to be up to the highest. There you go. Wait I'd rather play Snakewater and Swiftwater
than Pipeline and Nightfall. They belong down here. They're trash. They're not good. Done. No.
I hate Egypt but I don't mind it. All right it's official. It's official. There you are.
I'll go slow so you can see. I'm malding right now from this list. Well look everybody knows
just everybody. Oops don't break anything. Sorry I was doing like the like I'm a magician like
magic act with my hands. Um everybody these the S and from S to B everybody loves these.
Maybe you don't have them in the same spot but this is like these are the top maps of the game.
I think that's a pretty fair S through B. I just don't like five CP and that's my preference you
know. I'm a king of the hill and a uh attack defense in payload. Mostly king of the hill in
payload. Two fourths too high. That's just because I have a love-hate relationship with
it. Same with Dustbowl. What's next? This is fun. This is like I'm having this is chill man. This
is cool. I haven't met anyone ever that likes Turbine. German tier list? No I remember that
from last time. I'm not doing it. Full metal alchemist characters. I don't think oh Bloodborne
trick weapons. Hell yeah. Let's do this one. Spoilers for Bloodborne if you've never seen it.
Does this have the DLC in it too? Uh okay let's go. All right man now this is not what I think the
best weapon in the game is. This is what I think I like to play with the most. Fuck the cane.
I hate the cane. Uh it's gonna be tricky. Where's the where's the where's the moonlit sword?
Is that is that the moonlit sword? Uh I desperately tried to get this
but I didn't I I gave up. Making a magic character in Bloodborne was
just I hate it. I am having just all arcane. You get like two or three different options.
I wish I could use it. I haven't I can't use it. This thing was good but I wouldn't want to use
it the whole time. The whirligig saw was I mean just cool but I wouldn't want to use it.
Uh I never got a chance to use the bow so I'm just gonna never done it. I have to make a new
category. All right D is the category I have never used it. Where's the my favorite weapon?
There it is. I love this thing. The big like chain swing weapon. Oh this is the side right?
Where's the bow? Am I stupid? This is it right here. That's the bow right? Yeah I never played
with the side. I did use the wheel for a little bit but it was bad. It was fun for a little bit.
Uh I didn't. Where's this the the best the best weapon in the game? This one right here right?
All these were good. Bad. The saw spear. I have that. Is that incorrect? Oh that's the wrong one
yeah. These are all great. These are boring choices. I know but this is not this is not a boring
choice. This is like one of the cool DLC weapons. Pizza cutter is better than the saw spear. Yeah
also I like this too. This was a lot of fun to use because you could actually play for the first
like two-thirds of the game with arcane. Uh this one was cool but not that useful. This is the um
that weird arm weapon. Yeah we're gonna put we'll put the boring ones down here. I mean these are
just like those are the best weapons but they're boring. I did never use the blood uh tinge weapons.
Although I did I actually used this one for a little while. This is a strength one.
It was all right. The boom hammer sucks. It's like it's probably worse than the cane.
It's fun to use. Uh this one I'm gonna put it down here because every single person that ever plays
Bloodborne uses this weapon for the whole game. I was one of them on my first playthrough. Um it's
either this one or this one. I'm gonna put them down here. So I just imagine like I didn't play
with these. They're fantastic weapons but like everybody plays with them. So actually you know
they actually belong up here with the boring ones because they just be they're just good. Now the
gun blade stuff is something that I have no experience with because I never really did it.
This is the weird hand arm thing. I thought it wasn't I hated this thing. You have to get
that one specific holding R2 with the little arm comes out and stabs him the head. It's hard to use.
I know this is probably the best weapon at least from the DLC in the game but I would probably
rather use all these instead of the the default ones and this too. This is just fun. That arm
is god tier. Yeah but it's just I didn't like using it. It was like the boom hammer. It was that one
gimmick with the little thing that comes out. Like this has a gimmick but I can still use it as like
a sword. I know this is a club too. This makes me want to play the game again for like the
sixth time. How do I fast forward to the next list? It'll be done very soon don't worry.
Um I don't remember these. The gun spear I don't know. I didn't really use them.
No. If I ever played through Bloodborne again I would use one of these weapons.
This is the these things were awesome and I remember getting so angry trying to get these.
The maddest I've ever been probably in a video game. Spoiler alert for the DLC.
When you go like just mute the stream fucking hurry up.
Getting this weapon was one of the most rage inducing moments ever. This is the the dual
blades thing that you get but there's two of those weird huge sliding shark face monster people down
there. Wrong weapon? Wait is it? No it's not. No it's not. This is the the the dual weapons right?
No right right right right right right. The one that's down there. Which one is it?
This is that's the crow. Yeah right right right. Stay muted. We're talking about spoilers here.
Yes that's a crow. That's this one. What it's the which one is it? It's this one here right?
Yeah okay and I wanted to use it because it was so interesting so cool but those trying to fight
those two things at the same time was so painful. All right now you can unmute but holy shit that
was I remember being so angry at that game fighting two of those things. Shaman bone I know
but holy fuck I if you don't know that you are in deep shit. I love Bloodborne but haven't used
like half the weapons. Isn't that part of the fun? Isn't part of like oh okay playthrough one used
uh let's see what I'll go through every playthrough. You ready?
First playthrough of Bloodborne. So take your screenshot this is what I have to say okay now
this is the first playthrough up here. This is my first playthrough. I use these two. Second
playthrough. Vita holy shit this game's fucking like game best game I've ever played my whole life.
Second playthrough. These two. Oh wow this is amazing. So much fun. Third playthrough.
I was I think I was just like a normal asshole. Third playthrough I remember specifically
desperately wanting to get this and I think I probably used I think I actually used the hammer
and then I gave up at like the spoiler alert. If you give up at this point here you've already
played through the whole damn game. I just spoiled it whatever. Yes yes because I got to the point
where I was trying to fight orphan with a fucking boom hammer and I was like this is like this is
not possible to do. I'm done. Quick remute. Okay so that's playthrough number one two three four.
Playthrough number five. I did a let's do I did like a comedy playthrough so I wanted this is
these are the two I did. Done. I've played through the game like five times. I mean I've I used these
which have I not actually physically touched. Everything down here is what I have not even
physically used. Oh no no no no no this this is up this was during the comedy run. This is what I
ended up with during like the strength comedy run. Okay yeah I have not equipped any of the
weapons below because I didn't I like didn't have time wasn't doing the build or didn't want to use
it. Show us your saves to prove this. I have not had this PlayStation 4 in probably three and a
half years. What about the steak driver? Where is it? It's uh the oh right yeah okay yeah sorry sorry
I've used it but maybe for like 30 minutes. Can I unmute? You can yes unmute. You played the game
five times and never touched half the weapons? I mean I physically maybe had them in my inventory
but I never used them because you have to level up stuff. You have to upgrade your weapons and I
just was like I don't feel like using that. That's kind of cool you know you get a weapon in these
games and you take like two or three swings and you go nah and then you just put it away.
Respecs make it harder. Yeah yeah you have to you can't just be doing a strength build and then all
of a sudden be like you know what I want to use the bow. There you go. I mean this is this is not
my tier list. We already went over that. Now give me another one. It's the type of game where you can
just beat it with the whole game with one weapon. Yeah. Bloodborne bosses? Hey this is spoilers
though. That was really fast. A lot of people like did like a boss ranking thing. That was quick.
But if you haven't played Bloodborne or you don't do you really all souls Bloodborne all souls bosses?
I don't even remember half of these. The every souls boss. Um wrong one. Can we uh
possible emotes? Nah we're gonna do that later. We're gonna do that a different day.
We're gonna do like another emote contest like soon here probably early 2020 but don't worry.
Dead rising all psychos. How does that exist? What the fuck is this? Uh look at the url on this one.
What the fuck? Page unresponsive. What the fuck are you talking about? Did you just give me like
a virus? All right give me another one. I like this. This is fun. Virus until you watch the movie
then your like a desktop gets unlocked again. Terraria bosses? No I can't do that one.
Just so people stop spamming this. This is like spoilers too. You can't do tier list without
spoilers. Okay um full metal alchemist characters. Dog dog dog yes I never went dog. Okay um this is
spoilers for the whole show just in case anyone's curious. The actual entire every character in the
whole show is here. Kim, Kimbley's the worst character in this whole show. Kimbley's whole
character can be described as wow wow wow wow wow. Not a fan. Grab a fucking S tier.
I kind of don't remember half these people. I know putting like the title characters down here
is like you know you're gonna be like well the name of the show is full metal alchemist.
Um doctor oh this is doc doc doctor Dr. Marco. I remember Dr. Marco. The character sucked.
Uh this is gonna be hard. If I don't do that then people will leave. All right um no you're like
cooler than these guys just were kind of there. No you're like are you better than are you cool.
Spoilers for this whole show. Spoilers for the like actual entire show. I'm gonna spoil the entire
show. If you've never seen full metal alchemist and at this point like you the whole you don't
know the whole show. Where is he? There he is. I mean I got up with a joke. Why are they even on
here? Like like why are they even on here? Can they be like a dog category? Like that's they're
just dogs. I knew that people were gonna do this. I knew it. They're better than Kimlin. D for dog
right? Mustang was cool but he's kind of annoying. Where's uh where's Hughes? There you are. I know
and I know they look they look they kind of look the same but I do I like I like them both. By the
way um hold on a second here um whoa those of you that remember this is spoilers for the whole show
so if you're still here then that means you've probably seen or you don't care um greed but
excuse me isn't but this is this different this is different uh I I know that I just said I'm
spoiling the whole show but like I can't do it I'm so I'm having trouble like giving the full
spoilers because like I'm scared that somebody's like tabbed and like they're muted and they're
gonna hit the button they're gonna go they're gonna get the whole thing who cares okay here
we go this is a full Metal Alchemist stream from here on out which greed because I mean this greed
was like funnier but this greed was cooler that's tricky that's Ling uncultured fucking stupid dumb
fucking idiot stream wait what version is this it has to be all right where's where's um there
okay yeah you're cool are you cooler than Barry the Chopper though you're definitely cool Sloth
why are you even up here just a little bit cooler this this dude was this dude was in one like what
two episodes I don't even like remember who any of these people are like who is this person
wait wait a minute wait a minute where's the um where's the Wizard of Oz the like the lion
the the the frog where's the Wizard of Oz this guy this is yeah I loved these guys absolutely
yeah do they even have all the characters put Al in a I wasn't a fan missing the third dog
there's no third dog all right I know spoilers spoilers spoilers but I what do I care envy fuck
no you envy was cool for the first like 12 episodes and then then they just got like stupid
there's one specific reason why it because it was just like okay you okay you so you
spoiler alert spoiler alert is your you uh so because fucking I can't do I need to put like
a thing on screen I'm so I know I'm sorry we've all you haven't seen it I know but people just
somebody just came and said hey what are you doing okay spoilers for the whole show so at the first
like 12 episodes okay cool but like the rest of you are fucking like dumb caterpillar like
what a stoop I hated it deep I just said it I did it she was kind of annoying
yeah she's cool but like what do you mean what is this the right person whom I think
what do you mean take that back whoa holy shit I just like I just like fucking put oxygen into a
fire this is Hawkeye oh right gun with the gun okay it's been like seven years since I've seen
the show all right I don't I don't even I don't know who I don't know who these people are
where's um I was just moved I don't know who this is I don't I don't who who's like the
the big bearded guy is this wait is this who's this all right D is like I don't remember who
you are this is part of the the group of these like four guys right this is the same person
this is the same person I don't remember wait wait wait wait wait wait hold on wait wait wait
wait wait wait turn who are these people this is the lion where's the whistle who is the frog
where's the frog there's a frog yeah there's no frog or scar yeah there was this scar
that's not scar the scar was already up here right here that's not scar that scar is brother well
fucking what do you want there's no scar here wait was this the oh no no no wait a minute
this is these two I remember these two in fact you guys are way cooler than the main characters
they should just make the show about YouTube because they're way more interesting
um this is library book book did like I've got a lot of books in my hands and I fell down right
okay let me break this down I can't believe the fucking frogs know here that's unbelievable
where you go where's scar I don't know I'm work I'm working on this you I like the force
now I wasn't a fan of like the the bounce off dialogue from the main characters
quadruple here these guys were only in the room to like have somebody to respond to the main
character when they talked it was still like have dialogue a dialogue b dialogue a dialogue b
I mean they went they went they went bad characters or anything it's just but that
you're better than pride I was sloth I'm working on it I'm working on it I don't know who half of
these people are down here this is like the same person is this supposed to be scar you're you're
you're like probably up here then no well whatever scars not on this list okay from
okay from envy over no from okay from priest guy over I don't really remember any of these people
really work where would I put scar probably a little bit past uh hoenheim or maybe right
before hoenheim I'm actually doing this list is it am I good this is a dream yeah this trio
didn't whatever but let's be fair you're cool than the fucking little panda okay done I just
did it where's scar uh he's like over here you know what that's better is it though all right
okay this is a dog shit list the fuck do you know about full metal I've seen both tv series
I've read all the manga you're really doing scars brother like this no this is just like I don't
okay okay and then I remember who that is yeah that you are definitely cooler than Dr Marco
Dr Marco is like the worst of all like the characters that have been in more than 10
episodes all right I'm done give me another one what time is it holy shit I've been doing
this for a long time animals at the zoo that's actually pretty fucking sick I'm gonna do animals
at the zoo this is gonna be tricky this is actually gonna be very hard to do uh all right
you're gonna but why why are why are tigers and cats so low because it's that and like dogs like
wolves are low too just because that's not that big it's like not that big of a deal to see like
a lot like a tiger at a zoo like a lion at the zoo that's if you saw an armadillo or like a
monitor lizard at the zoo that's pretty cool I mean it's cool but I don't know that I don't
hate that I think it's interesting a pig at the zoo but pigs are like one of my favorite animals
these are awesome yes I know but if I'm going to the zoo I'm going right to the pig den
it's hard to it's hard to put any of these in the hate category I don't hate any of these animals
no I don't I don't hate otter no I don't hate any of these how could you hate something like this
this is just the pictures kind of pictures I take when I go on vacation
uh iguana is s-tier I don't I disagree monitor lizard is s-tier let me correct that quickly for
you koalas hippopotamus I don't I can't put anything down in hate all right let's just get
this over with okay all the cats are in one spot that would be cool that'd be really cool actually
I don't hate it I don't hate like geese or whatever a swan but that's not that that's not
that interesting to me it's that's a swan that's you can see swans everywhere we're talking about
at the zoo if you go to the zoo I want to see something besides a fucking goose it's a pelican
it's staying now that's fucking cool llama that's all right now I'm sticking with it
I'll tell you why because I go a llama you can go to a petting you it's not that
and they spit on you yes I'm only going by going to the zoo the petting zoo is a zoo I don't want
to get spit on I don't want to get spit on I don't I'm changing this to a different I don't
like okay then this is going to be like I would just I would walk by and go look at the lion
all right let's get going it's a moose I mean I just I would enjoy it elephants that's pretty
fucking cool platypus get the fuck up there not all the way that's where the monitor wizard
hippopotamus is pretty cool I mean the seals I would probably just I mean they're cool but
I would just look for a few seconds I would just sit there and be like all right let's go
zebras same thing um zebra's ass same thing I feel like you can only look at uh I've never I've
never seen I've never gone to one I've never seen an orca like I don't I don't know what my
reaction would be because I've never seen one indifferent indifferent uh no this is just the
dinosaur in Jurassic Park that runs around really small and the t-rex eats them I don't I don't I'm
not gonna I don't care it's like I guess it's okay it's a filler animal yeah but a panda would be
kind of cool I'll fix this gorilla yeah all the apes just do cool shit they do funny interesting
shit they're just interesting this thing is just gonna float around they just go forward and I love
birds I got a peacock up here but you'll sit and watch the orangutan like eat an orange for five
minutes straight just because you're gonna do that they've even I've never even I've never seen
polar bears are cool but I don't think I've ever seen one what is this a dolphin isn't this cool
koala I mean that's really cool but I I love turtles and I this is something coming from
somebody that is a reptile fan but they're pretty boring at the zoo at the zoo at the zoo remember
at the zoo the turtles are all just gonna sit and look at you
don't tell me that I don't like reptiles I've got a monitor and that is number one
I'd do it for 15 seconds um foxes are cool I'm gonna I'll fix it wait isn't this a seal
what's this then wait isn't there another seal that's okay that's an otter seal with the element
what's that that's a sea lion no I would look for 15 seconds they're kind of no that's kind
of higher up too I'm gonna fix it bears I mean I bears are cool I love bears was this a vulture
I probably looked for 15 seconds hyena they're pretty cool lemur pretty cool other like super
pig yep this is like this is piggy and then like piggy otto and then oh mega pig these are all
right all right now let me get this right that's that's the real timeline right there that's the
real omega pig okay so how do I what do I change here people is a titan pig
yeah uh yeah that's correct let's just stay all right let's get this one right monitor lizard
yeah I'm gonna have one of these before I before I die I will make a promise to me before the day
I die I'm going to own a like two to three foot long fucking monitor lizard maybe not a monitor
but like at least a one to two foot long lizard like a tegu or a maybe even a monitor
before the day I die they're so interesting tegu is the way to go monitors suck I've been in my
research tegus are huge yeah I know I know okay ostrich platypus what a cool animal that god just
said fuck it and like threw a bunch of shit in a blender and then dumped it on the ground like
that's so what an awesome what an interesting animal the god was late for class and like had
to do his homework real quick uh yeah cool one of the coolest animals on earth these huge birds are
just so interesting too what are you doing up here get out of here oh wait that's an otter
yeah I think otters are cooler than the omega pig titan pig evolution but I still love them peacock
is gonna come down a little uh orang-tangs are awesome gorillas are really really cool uh iguanas
alligators are fucking cool too though I wouldn't put them I would rather go look at a giraffe and
an elephant than an alligator though because they kind of just stand around they just sit there I
don't think that's fair I would just look at the snake for 15 seconds the snakes don't do anything
alligators don't do anything but they're huge monitors are actually really interesting they
run around they stay like they like have their big tongues that come out they like look at you
they're they're very very excited what a way cooler version of a lion this is a lion with scales
and a big tongue that comes up they have chain male skeletons that's wow that's pretty dope
okay but I don't really snakes don't I love reptiles and amphibians but snakes don't do
it for me they they're really really cool they're really interesting they have a lot of really
they have great designs on their skin and stuff and so many different types they have some fun
personalities uh they're not really plus they're the devil that should be down here guys I'm sorry
if you can walk into a pet smart and see this that's not something that's that cool to look
at at the zoo they're different don't I don't hate any none of these animals I love all of
these animals all of them it's just who I prefer then put them under love but that's not how a
tier list works okay let's keep this going I want to get this right s is correct uh a is needs a
little bit of work that's correct yeah that's correct it's even more correct close done all
right down if they like ah these are cool I like these animals they're pretty cool the only reason
why people really like these is because they're in a bunch of animated movies and then everything
that they always just show up for like a minute corals are fucking horrible animals they have one
of the smallest brains to body ratios of any mammal additionally their brains are smooth the
brain is folded to increase the surface for neurons if you present a koala if you present
a koala with leaves plucked from a branch laid on a flat surface the koala will not recognize it as
food they are too thick to adapt their feeding behavior to cope with change in a room full of
food they can literally starve to death so what is that they're stupid as fuck they only survive
because their food what was it they only survive because they're because their food makes them
poisonous but look at their ears they should be extinct holy shit that's rough
flamingo is pretty cool dolphins I mean just dolphins should probably be up there yeah yeah
yeah bump bump bump bump bump bump I mean camels are cool though camel cool than a polar bear
polar bear cooler than a buff fox what's this one this is pixar fox versus hbo fox which one you
don't know what a red panda is apparently not and for that reason I'm out I'll take the pixar fox
over the fox it's cool kind of cool than an iguana is it though they both belong up here
no they don't koala brain no I thought I would I eat food if it's in front of me
okay there's the rest of this correct almost yeah yeah yeah I guess no I would rather see these
no I'd rather like see a koala though I never get to see them okay would look for 15 seconds
who would I look for 16 seconds vultures and then the lions because there you go to the lions and
you see the lions that's not a vulture what it's an anteater it's not like a like wings laid out
like like this going down assume like it's wings up see like wing up wing up just swooped down
landing grabbing something this is okay wrong that's an anteater all right those things are
awesome uh all right I would look for 15 seconds at the lion probably the most and then honestly
probably the turtle my reasoning for that is I would just open up my phone and it's this would
be where like I would be texting somebody I could probably sit there for like five straight minutes
this is my I'm taking a break section of the zoo I'd be there for 15 seconds uh it's a bobcat
slightly larger than house cat cat cool and they've got the bear beards and stuff I love them
that's a lynx isn't a link wait what do you mean it's a lynx the lynx is known by the tuft of black
hair on the tips of its ears and it's short of bobbed tail in fact one species of lynx is called
a bobcat fucking stupid goddamn fucking stupid fucking idiot fucking goddamn one species
it's still correct and for that go get a haircut that one isn't the bobcat lynxes are a bobcat
a bobcat is a lynx it's that's a bobcat it could be a bobcat just because it's a specific lynx it
could be a bobcat bobcat is a lynx lynx is a bobcat there's a species that is the bobcat
they're not entered not all lynx is a bobcat but not all but all bobcats are lynxes thank you uh
thank you appreciate it thank you can we disagree that the t-rex food is down here all right I would
look at a whale for 15 seconds I would probably weigh more than a lion all right let's finish
this up let's go with just a manatee cool you don't have to go to the zoo just live in maine
and look out your window they're huge and they're majestic but I don't not that big whatever I'm
not sure what this is just a horse or is it a zebra why the what's it what is this animal
why does it has a saddle on it that's an okapi yeah it's a fucking okapi of the zebra I'm so
sorry I'm sorry I have a hundred people leave I get it they have blue tongues
I think I'm good I think this is the list but which one of the cats besides a lion would I
want to see the most it probably that or that no that no no this is just a chat just that's
just a tiger right this is just that's that's a tiger I would pretty I would like to see that
links fuck done animal tier list complete actually done there you go Kanye West albums I can't I don't
I can't I cannot do that Star Wars films already did it days of the week um obviously like Friday
and Saturday the best days of the week Sunday's the worst day in the week because everything's
closed Sundays actually suck Sundays are worse than Mondays at least shit's open on Monday
do bugs all right I'm gonna do bugs and then it's been six and a half hours
what have we been doing this for three and a half hours when did I stop playing Katamari
like two that wow uh yeah I'm not a big fan of Sundays Sundays just remind you
that it's over the week is the week is over it's time for a new one I don't want a new one I want
to stay on the old one do we have any bugs do is there is there a bug tier list I know I'm not
doing Nicktoons that'll take like three hours cooked eggs I'll do the cooked eggs one wait give
me the cooked eggs one again I'm not clicking on the cartoon one Yoshi design tier list Super
Mario World done everything else is not as good beetle tier list cooked eggs all right give me
the cooked eggs one what I just do Dark Souls 3 power ranking I know I don't want no more Dark
Souls I want cooked eggs how many different kinds of cooked eggs are there I can do this one pretty
quick raw I'm not gonna eat a raw egg this is just they're both scrambled eggs okay done this
list sucks bread types you guys must be hungry how hungry are you guys I'm getting like pizza
toppings bread crusts actually this is pretty good choice good choice I mean that awful uh
pretty damn great bagels sourdough I have to be in the mood for it pita bread up here flat flat
bread somewhere up here brioche it's oatmeal bread d whole wheat bread f rye bread somewhere in a
croissant s biscuit a potato bread is s2 no it's potato bread is a god tier absolute god tier
was uh banana bread fucking absolute god tier cornbread close but not better than pita bread
none up there pretzel bread not even close it's not this is not even a competition
English muffin I hate English muffins I don't like cinnamon bread any sweet bread don't like
it zucchini bread stop it's in there with the same like the oatmeal pumpernickel is
better than my friend and sourdough french bread get it up here we'll we'll fix it red stick
depends from where from where homemade or from olive garden because from the olive garden
okay little caesars I don't know about that homemade better uh I know what is what is
butter bread I don't think I've ever had this before yeast bread I butter bread butter bread
and what did yeast bread go it's just that just bread all right let's fix this I potato bread
pretzel bread I don't know how you could eat potato bread or pretzel bread and say that's
not the best thing I've ever had in my life that was made from bread huh I don't know you know
what I'm trying to say uh banana bread doesn't belong up here it was it that was a knee-jerk
reaction it should be this close it's a plus plus Hawaiian rolls better than rye pita bread
better than rye cord bread and rye are above the same naan and pita bread fantastic tortilla
flat I would actually put flat bread up above rye and we're gonna put we're gonna put rye down
here I'd rather have flour tortilla than rye garlic bread it's good but it's just a bit basic
it is I this is like snack bread it's just it's snack bread garlic bread breadsticks
it's good it's very good it's exceptional but I mean it's it's good but it's snack bread
snacks are good yes they are but would I rather have garlic bread or would I rather have
a nice french bread like with oil that's the top tier snack bread I thought I would rather have
no I would rather have bagel than garlic bread you have to be in the mood for you got to be in the
mood for garlic bread it's very heavy like really dense and cheesy sometimes and really heavy garlic
and oil it's not a light snack crude oil what the fuck are you talking about what kind of garlic
bread are you guys eating that isn't like soaked in oil and cheese that's how you make garlic bread
you put a bunch of garlic and oil on it no cheese on garlic bread it's still got oil on it you eat
what you don't have you don't put oil on your garlic bread what do you just put a clove of
garlic on a piece of bread and eat it where the fuck is their cheese on garlic bread I feel like
I'm on another planet right now am I on another planet where the fuck is their cheese and oil on
garlic bread every single restaurant that I've ever been to parmesan oil garlic oil cheese I'm
not talking about like fucking cheese whiz but what like like American slices what is happening
garlic bread recipe this is from delish.com four cloves of garlic one stick of butter
it's a it's a light snack though one french bread baguette kosher salt two tablespoons of parsley
and a fourth cup of grated parmesan cheese this is the number one thing this is the number one
recipe that you that you find I have to be an alien a half a stick of butter how many how many
days a week are you eating this no no you're not gonna pull the parmesan cheese bullshit off it's
cheese parmesan cheese is cheese just because you dust it and it's on it's cheese that's fucking
cheese it's sawdust it's different they're different parmesan or reggiano sorry what did I say
parmesan I've never had parmesan cheese on garlic bread I'm okay when I talk I feel like I'm talking
to like five different cultures here how many Americans we have in the chat press a all right
how many people from Norway we got in the chat right now press and a lot of Norwegians
can I ask the Norwegian something very very specific do you put cheese on your garlic bread
can always can always count on the Norwegians anyways no I can't do that in good conscience
would I rather have a girl would I rather have a heavy ass cheesy ass oily fucking sweaty
dumped with fucking garlic and grease or would I rather have a bagel lightly toasted with hints
of sesame with little little little chips little little sesame chips and and poppy seeds fresh
not out of a fucking bag that's right I got you I got you guys how many of you guys ate your
garlic bread out of a bag the bag that you just and you take the garlic bread out of the bag
and you've put it in the oven I know at least at least 20 30 percent of you guys eat the bag
garlic bread and right now you're going like so you got it in your mouth and the bag is right
there and you're like oh fuck oh you will idiot boomer and then you go oh fuck you got me brioche
is better than rye all right I know I'm like oh you put cheese on your bread what are you dope
where's the oil coming from what are you stupid you gotta get organic garlic whatever but can
you please agree with me that the potato bread is iced here oh shit Kim made zucchini bread like
last week and she just wrote in the chat uh she's like wait you don't fucking like the
zucchini bread downstairs that's not true I haven't gotten here yet
zucchini bread is your zucchini bread is fucking very good but I'm trying to figure out I'm just
going through the list I bought a potato bread is my favorite thing that's like it's like my
favorite thing in the world I don't think zucchini bread is s-tier banana look at banana bread though
he's not I'm not no I it's it's better than white bread it was stress burp I'm done this is
correct I'm done perhaps a bad croissant potato bread whatever the music was I listened to chill
I listen I'm in a fucking time machine that was a two hour long playlist didn't I just click the
play button like five minutes ago why is everybody saying monka s I like zucchini bread this is just
like my favorite breads zucchini look zucchini bread is is is good it's not down here I I like
zucchini bread oh he's going Larry David but all right hold on a second here Kim you're telling me
that zucchini bread is better than crusties with oil that's like one of my favorite things guy
that's gonna be up there bagels like a nice crunchy crispy bagel but we're talking about
zucchini bread like from the store I would not buy zucchini bread from the store but if Kim made
it it's actually really good no joke no fucking around and did I just replay the chill step mix
I think it's time to go zucchini bread is better than sourdough and pumpernickel I didn't even get
down here yet I didn't even get down to this portion I just they were they were in a row
to be fair though I've had zucchini bread twice once from Kim once from my mother and they were
great but I don't like I'm not gonna put a I'm not gonna put like turkey on a zucchini sandwich
he's sweating you know you don't understand I like it it's actually really good
monka s all right well that's the end of the tier list episode was almost seven hours what
out of that happened mom's making zucchini bread from Baskin Robbins keep digging the hole
shit Vegas tier list no no no no no no I'll see you tomorrow where we were gonna play bumbo
but uh turned out uh that bumbo got bumped to tomorrow I'm not done that's not making a joke
look I'm gonna go eat a fucking like I'm gonna eat like five servings of zucchini bread downstairs
I'm just saying bumped in but it made sense to me in my brain you're a dope hey easy with that
language around here all right I'll see you guys tomorrow we'll play bumbo tomorrow I'm not sure
how long it looks fun though thanks for joining me on tonight's stream we'll see you soon if you're
gonna show up tomorrow then hell yeah maybe we'll see you there all day bumbo I don't know it depends
I really really like binding of Isaac when I really first started playing that game
I got into it so we'll see what time tomorrow uh somewhere around one to two p.m. pacific time
take care see you tomorrow those of you sticking around let's do the bits just take a look okay
it's never changed all right earlier uh for those of you that weren't here earlier we had a huge
sub and bit a thon that just went crazy there was a train that was about that was at least
a few hundred subs in a row so thank you so much all of you hopefully I caught y'all
but in the bit department we had uh Louie thank you Louie for the 500 bits did you say hello hello
thank you uh none uh none ar thanks for the 250 I can finally donate to the best streamer on twitch
I'm moving to Vegas in January to attend UNLV nice any advice or things I should know also do
you think you will ever play Danganronpa it's one of my favorite franchises I think people brought
that up before I don't really remember what it was but uh I'm gonna say probably not but
I'm open to anything never in his life will he play Danganronpa well you don't know that
it's a murder mystery visual novel is it good yes no ace attorney is just better if you won't play
if you won't play ace attorney how dare you play this one easy but yeah uh welcome to Las Vegas
soon any advice or things you would about Vegas um stay away from the tables don't spend all
your money yeah thanks dad no um all right here you go I'm assuming if you're going to college
I'm assuming that I mean maybe I shouldn't assume this but I don't know how old you are
but now what are you 19 18 all right well don't go in the casinos then 20 how old are you when
you start college 18 17 all right don't go in the casinos there's a lot to do and a lot to see that
another casinos go to all the different wonderful wonderful wildlife and hiking places there's a
lot of them we're surrounded by them you don't have to go to the damn casino go to all the did
you say the boring parts holy god you promised Joel's movie actually I said like 50 times that
we were gonna watch Joel's movie during the movie night that I do I said it like 30 or 40 times
now we'll watch it I'm gonna give tons of critiques to just you wait I'm sure it is funny
Joel's a funny guy it wouldn't surprise me if it was funny funny people do funny things thinking
face but uh welcome to Vegas just don't get too overwhelmed it's pretty easy to have that happen
to you especially initially a lot of stuff to look at a lot of things going on a lot of places to go
a lot of food to eat just take it slow one step at a time take it in very small baby steps it's
a great city I love it dark soul thanks for the 250 70 hour work week coming up it's the last
biddies for a while also while I hate playing internet doctor have you been tested for celiac
I have causes an autoimmune reaction in your stomach and small intestines yes I have been
tested for celiac that's initially what I thought was going on but that's not what's going on
70 hours though yeah that is a long fucking time hope you get some time off after that
70 I really do hope you get some time off though it's never fun to have to spend
over over over time you can get really over tired but uh yeah in regards to medical stuff
I'm still trying to figure it out I have some idea but I don't really there's not much to talk
about because I have another procedure that's coming up to try to really put the nail in the
coffin here so it's not like I'm gonna be like hey guys let's talk about my last visit and the
visit before that the visit before it no it's it's not worth really talking about it isn't
but it is not celiac kind of at some point over the last seven or eight months wish it was that
easy to be honest because it's been sort of just a random uh symptomatic of what's wrong with me
so it's not enough to cause any concern though it's just like an irritating little thing that's
just sticking around not enough to cause a problem but it's enough to be annoying I should have a
real real answers over the next probably three or four weeks we'll see but I appreciate it thank
you dark soul uh stefunky chicken next to the 250 hey germ I just finished shooting a short film
I directed last weekend and above all the production challenges I now know the true
power of catering we're in post now but I want to say that watching all the effort you put into
your streams has really inspired me to apply myself in the work that I do thank you yes
uh once you start crossing the amount of people that are on a project once there's three four
five six seven eight nine ten people on a project that's you have to people have to eat
did you drink all your green juice I did it was absolutely fucking delicious
thank you thank you for that green juice monkey s yes it's green juice it's like spinach and kale
and agave I don't know it's very good uh but yeah when you have to feed people it's it's hard it's
really easy just to be like uh should we have somebody to go to taco bell and just get 60
crunch wraps so catering really is so good uh I wish you luck in your post and I am honored
to be inspiration for anything that you're doing so thank you German lied about the ghost pepper
thanks for the 300 bits looked it up for you there's a place called Joe Joe's Jerky in Vegas
and it sells ghost peppers you're welcome hey thanks appreciate it I ain't gonna eat a ghost
pepper on stream it's not gonna happen I need to get I'm gonna I need to get a clean bill of health
from my current doctors before I die on stream eating a ghost pepper not gonna happen thank you
though appreciate it you got a great username because that's gonna be that will be relevant
until the stream is off I mean like off off but thank you appreciate that thank you thank you
grim for the five dollars hope you fall in the black hole again yeah not kidding fall in the
hole again I did like four times and then we had a shitload of community subs you guys sometimes
you just go on a roll and I get like 400 that's ridiculous that's ridiculous I appreciate every
single one of them in fact let's take a look and see how many people it was here we go
ow wait I need to log into here shit uh-oh no oh we're fine no we're not fucking stream blabs
I have so many like bad things to say about stream labs ah okay here we go that's a lot
there's a lot of people thank you all of you thank you specifically to not only the people
that are in that list but also the people that made the two three hundred today even happen thank
you everybody that stays subbed that subs ever that may be subbed like three years ago never again
thanks forever ever thank you thank you and on the list for the 300 bits hey germa it's the
animal rescue guy this will be my final message for a while is the rescue got more animals than
expected so I have a I have to use a bunch of my money good very good anyway here's a picture of
six baby ducks that I have hatched whose parents are the ones that you and it's out it's named
I'd say if you or chat want to name others feel free oh for reptiles check out a leatherback
bearded dragon it's a new morph and is even tamer than regular beardies I'm sorry I did not hear
huge monitor lizard in there that that's really good info though actually because I was actually
thinking about getting a bearded dragon oh look at these ducks ducks are so precious look at these
they're so precious here is image one I'll show after the credits roll but we'll put these on
screen thank you so much and beautiful awesome ducks thank you and on a list and I will look
into leatherback bearded dragon because it was one of the things I was thinking about getting
here they go here's duck image one and it's actually a lot bigger so let's just get it up
on the front wait wait there's more hold on look at these they're all just huddled into a corner
just keeping each other warm it's a fuzz pile it's what happens when you get your haircut at
the barber that's just what's on the ground that's so cute hell yeah wow I wish you luck
keep doing the good stuff thank you and on a list hey for let me thanks for the hundred times
10 thanks for a thousand bits make sure to get some chick stuff in uranus thank you for let me
I think I got a lot of cool things I remember I did that I did that very should I oh what
thanks for the thousand bits gnarly thanks for the 250 one time I put Tabasco on some ice cream at
work at a work Christmas party as a joke for my friends it wasn't good I think my boss saw me do
it and he cringed I get all right like that's that kind of embarrassing kind of cringy what
is this thoughts on Dijon wait wait wait what does somebody like the clip apparently there's
audio here I need to listen to this says thoughts on Dijon mustard from stinky beaver thanks to the
250 and it's a clip what is it oh you guys can't hear it Wyoming Nevada what am I supposed to do
about this Nevada there's nothing to see it's it's just the sound that says derma horse here
save yourself I guess it's kind of horse like yeah thanks thoughts on Dijon mustard you saw where
it was on that list it's very high it's great thank you for the 250 but let me thanks to the
300 bits they say ayaya Dave saved it gave 5,000 bits I think I caught this but just in case I
didn't thank you Dave and they just say derma hearts thank you pretty sure I touched upon it
but if I didn't I'm sorry it's a lot of money to miss I don't think I did though and then you get
five community subs right after that so like you just thank you but let me again thanks for the
300 bits derma this does sound really fun but if you're a fool you're a fool if you think I'm not
putting a bounty on the king's head that's fine yeah I you don't think I what do you mean you
don't think I've got a vault full of gold behind me somebody comes in with the bow pointed at my
head I'll double it what do you pay what are you getting paid I'll double it no no no fuck that
I'll triple it go back and and kill the man that sent you and I want proof bring me his diamond
pickaxe oh snoozing copter thanks for the 250 the video game tier list was a really nice trip down
memory lane bloodborne and tf2 were the two games I would spend a ton of money on for a mind eraser
frog yeah imagine picking up team fortress 2 for the first time ever right now you just there's so
much to see I feel like it would actually be hard though because we got all that stuff trickled in
over years it's almost like the game has changed a lot since then it would be it might be actually
pretty difficult but god I wish that they would just make team fortress colon man versus machine
only I would have loved them to just to make just a just I'll pay for it I'll buy it just
let's sell it to me I'll it's 40 39.99 59.99 I'll buy it I just give it to me overwatch 2 is doing
that we don't know that for certain though we know it's a pve game like that but is it going
to be as good as man versus machine was will it be as challenging will it be as fun will it be as
much stuff to upgrade and enough enough in it see that's what I mean we don't know I'm not willing
to judge until something's around you know I'm saying hey I just made uh I just made a burger
and I think the salad I used is a bit old three months old we don't eat it just eat the burger
but uh it's been years since I played the dlc in bloodborne and here comes a bloodborne spoiler
close your ears if you haven't played it yet here it comes three two one I still haven't beaten the
orphan yet I started the dlc in new game plus and later found out that new game plus orphan is
apparently much harder than normal orphan at this point I'll have to see it well a full day to beat
it fuck me I just mute me feel 64 thanks to the five community subs and thank you snoozing
copter for the 250 yes orphan was horrendous I still would put him in the top two top three
of hardest bosses they've ever made number one is by all means is the final boss in sakiro
was insane that last true encounter in sakiro was so much to learn and so much patience
it was crazy that was an entire stream wasn't it just to try to beat that final boss
I sat there I was at that boss for at least four hours five hours right something like that
was it 50 something attempts 58 60 attempts oh but hey it was I still did it and I still enjoyed it
hey the great angel thanks for the 250 great tier segment nice to see your love of reptiles
on full display a true scaly through and through this next one is from cyanide thanks for the 500
bits you sound like a cockatoo when you swear how to fix a round cage this video has 12 million views
I think we got it we got it that's that's
that's just the that is you're right that is the
fucking stupid got it fucking dumb fucking thing
fucking got it fucking stupid fucking thing fucking uh that's so funny that's true
I rate donald duck and then finally thank you for let me for the 300 bits it's a clip
it is a audio clip see that thanks fuck you have to have the context of whatever
all right I see you guys tomorrow we're gonna play bumbo so that's either gonna be a three hour
two hour stream or a like 10 hour stream I'm not sure thanks again for all the insane support
earlier we've reached the end see you tomorrow good night everybody