It's the end of a year, and the beginning of a new adventure. Welcome everyone, to Turma Rumble 3. Excitement, awe, and inspiring motions will get you on your feet tonight, I can promise you that.
But before we get started, please join me in a moment of silence to remember all those wrestlers who we lost this past year.
And now, ladies and gentlemen, if you could please rise and welcome Grandpa to sing our national anthem.
Oh, say can you see, by the drop of my smokey, my poor meatball, bursting in air, bursting in air.
Turn on my mic!
Turn my mic on! Grandpa! Oh no, that's Demon Lord Zaraxos, ladies and gentlemen. I can't even, he's got a chocolate!
Whoa! He just did, just fire underneath that ring.
Okay, um, hey everybody, welcome to Turma Rumble 3. I'm Turma. While I try to compose myself after what just happened, Sonic the Hedgehog is now coming down to the ring.
He's supposed to come in 16th. What the fuck is going on?
I'm gonna have to do some jumbling around of the scheduler and see who's coming in next, but anyways, visibly drunk and spitting at people in the audience is Sonic the Hedgehog.
Look, we get it. We know Sonic Boom wasn't a good success. We know that Germania 2014, you lost, but that is no excuse for this type of behavior.
Get your act together. Please ring that bell. Let's start Turma Rumble 3. My god.
No, he's uh, he's dead.
Uh, that's the second person Zaraxos has killed in two minutes.
And, uh, I carried the button. We started, guys. We have started two or three minutes ago, so that means another contestant has to come down to the arena.
And we'll get this guy introduced as quickly as possible. This is Turtimus the Adolescent Warrior, and he's got a task ahead of him.
If he's going to be number three, that's gonna die, and he's gonna show off for the cameras a little bit here.
If he is number three to die in a row by Demon Lord Zaraxos, I really don't know what to say. I'm not exactly sure how we're going to continue the rumble,
but Turtimus, if Master Splintoad has taught you anything at all, please use it immediately.
Because it would be bad if Demon Lord Zaraxos just eliminated himself.
Why? What? What?
I have no idea why that just happened.
But regardless, we have to send another person in prematurely, so whoever is next on the list, send them on out here.
And it's gonna be, ladies and gentlemen, it's a good one, it's the 1997 Boston Celtics Champion, Frank Pizza,
running down here with his patented, I have a dump in my pants run. Here he comes, and let's get started.
Welcome to actual wrestlers in the ring now.
We're going to actually talk about technical rasslin', rather than people just instantly dying when they come into the ring.
Turtimus, the teenage adolescent mutant warrior, or whatever, what did I call him? Something like that.
And Frank Pizza of the Boston Celtics, wearing his 1997 authentic championship jersey.
Turtimus was looking for a early elimination there, but cannot even get him over the first turnbuckle.
Well, Frank Pizza's now hanging on the ice, reverse elbow, and a flying shoulder tackle onto Turtimus for his troubles.
But Frank Pizza gets his leg caught, gets spun around on his back, and here comes another contestant.
If you forget how this works, every minute or so, another competitor is going to come down, and here comes a familiar face indeed.
You had to have thought that after Captain Crunch's victory at Germania 2014, we'd see more serial characters.
And here's Count Chocula, coming down to the German arena for the first time ever.
And unfortunately, his serial leg doesn't even exist anymore.
You can only get Count Chocula on Halloween. That's how much this guy sucks.
But he's in the German Rumble for the first time ever.
Let's see if he's got any tricks up his sleeve, besides, of course, turning your milk into chocolate milk.
And it's not even really chocolate milk. It's like a weird inside of a dog's ass chocolate milk.
It tastes like it's just like sugar. It's all right.
Look, I'm not going to blast Count Chocula, because I used to eat it every other day when I was a kid.
I'd eat Captain Crunch. I'd eat Count Chocula. I'd eat like Boo Berry. All these old cereals.
I ate them all when I was younger, so I can't be biased against any of them.
But we got another contestant coming in right now.
Confidently walking down to the arena is everybody's favorite shit character.
It is none other than Gabe, the Glueman Dick Rossi.
Fireworks. I don't know why he bought fireworks.
He spent like 60 bucks for no reason, because nobody cares.
Nobody cares about you, Glueman. Just get in here and win for fucking once in your life.
Four people in the arena. Now we get Glueman, Captain Crunch.
Oh, I almost just said Captain Crunch. That's Count Chocula. Get your cereals right.
That's Count Chocula, Glueman, Frank Pizza, and Turtimus the Teenage Warrior.
No eliminations whatsoever. Not yet, at least.
And pay attention to the left side of your screen right now.
Gabe, the Glueman Dick Rossi, and Frank Pizza, former teammates on the Celtics, are fighting right now for some reason.
Turtimus is gone. Turtimus has just been eliminated from the competition by Count Chocula.
And Glueman now. Glueman looks like he just got in.
That would be a terribly sad story if Frank Pizza and Count Chocula try to help.
He doesn't really...Count Chocula didn't do anything there, let's be honest.
Are they actually going to try to double-team Glueman out of here?
Another person coming down to the arena right now. Who's it going to be while they're tag-teaming Glueman?
That's Dick Dastardly Richard from the Rat Movie.
One of the most notorious gem thieves and artifact stealers.
This side of the Mississippi, folks. This is a dangerous man.
Keep your eye on him for the remainder of the Rumble, because frankly, he is terrifying.
And here he comes.
Surprisingly a lot bigger than I thought he was going to be.
I thought he was only going to be, like, five-five.
He's a...but how big is Count Chocula?
Isn't Count Chocula, like, three feet tall?
Well, no, Glueman's, like, six-something, I think, right? I have no idea.
All I know is that Frank Pizza just gave Glueman three or four punches,
and Glueman accidentally just slobber-knocked Count Chocula in the face.
He was going for Frank Pizza, but he ended up getting...
Well, then, Frank Pizza now gets a chin smash into a hip toss
and then into a flipping heel kick onto Frank Pizza.
Count Chocula is doing some work here.
Count Chocula and Glueman doing their respective work.
Frank Pizza looks like he could be on the verge here of getting eliminated.
So does Dick Dastardly Richard. No, gets the punch.
Is Captain Cork-Cocula...Cork-Cocula gets it. I said his name wrong.
Frank Pizza is now eliminated with a drop kick to his face over the ropes.
And we've got another contestant coming down to the arena.
It's the Candyman from Lethal League.
If you've never played Lethal League, in my opinion,
it is one of the best indie games of 2014.
I suggest you check it out. He is represented here for the first time ever.
Welcome, Candyman.
Without his cane that he typically uses,
and immediately goes for Dick Dastardly Richard, who throws him over the ropes.
Dick, could he immediately get eliminated for his first appearance in the German arena?
No. Dick Dastardly Richard with a very rare sign of empathy and sympathy there,
letting him get up. You don't technically see that ever by Dick.
And he could really suffer because of that.
He just gave him a little bit of sympathy.
You don't give that kind of sympathy to the Candyman.
Is Dick Dastardly Richard going out Candyman?
Cork-Cocula, how many fucking times am I going to miss?
For now, it's Cork-Cocula's name.
And just barely, just barely, he gets up.
Dick Dastardly Richard survives another day.
But is he going to, right after surviving that,
he's going to go, oh, we've got another contestant coming in right now.
And Dick Dastardly Richard vines.
I can't, I'm going to fucking change that name.
And here comes the Giant Rat.
That's the Giant Rat rolling his way down here.
Look at him go.
I've never seen such a huge rat in my entire life.
He definitely prays at night.
He definitely stalks at night.
You can tell by just by the way he looks.
And he's in the arena right now as Glooman is about to get,
he's going right by, what a ball dog by the Giant Rat.
And he is, me means business.
You've got to figure, he's definitely a top seed.
Ladies and gentlemen, if I were to say so myself,
the Giant Rat is now in along with Dick Dastardly Richard,
which makes it, no, he's gone.
Dick Richard is gone.
He has been eliminated.
Well, the Giant Rat and Count Chocula are trying to push Glooman out.
Are they going to Glock?
Glooman has been eliminated.
Glooman is out of the competition
per use of the Giant Rat
and Count Chocula.
What a terrible thing to see.
And we've got another person coming out almost immediately already.
It's crazy to me
how fast people come out in this game.
Has it really been like 30 to 60 seconds?
I feel like somebody just came in.
But whatever, sorry, because it's Earthworm Jim
showing off his dance moves.
He's ready, he's a veteran of the German Rumbles
and he's here to prove himself.
He's here to dance. He's here to point.
And he's here to win.
Welcome Earthworm Jim to the rumble.
As we've got Count Chocula patiently awaiting his arrival
while the Giant Rat and Candy Man are fighting in their own right.
And Earthworm Jim, right when he gets in,
does a headbutt to Count Chocula's stomach.
Would that even hurt?
Isn't Earthworm Jim a worm?
Is there any bones? I don't think worms don't even have any bones, do they?
So I don't know why.
That would just kind of feel like squishy goo
pushing up against your stomach.
Anyways, we've got Count Chocula already.
Count Chocula just eliminated Earthworm Jim
with a clothesline over the top ropes.
Immediately when he gets in.
Oh, I had high hopes for you, Earthworm Jim.
Every time you get screwed.
And Candy Man, speaking of people getting screwed,
Candy Man now looks like he can, no, he's going to stay in.
He is going to get rid of that double team
while we have another person coming in.
He just throws over the giant rat, which is surprising
because he is a top seed.
Count Chocula lining up the big boot!
And he's gone! And here comes the mime!
You know, every Jerma Rumble
we visit a thing where
he's the shit character.
You know how there's always the worst character
that's made? This is the one.
But here he comes, he jumps over the top ropes.
There are only three people in the
ring at the moment. You've got Count Chocula,
Candy Man, and now the mime. What's that?
Are you serious?
As I'm getting word right now, we're going to be joined
at ringside right now
by Demon Lord Zaraxos at the commentary table.
Okay, I don't know.
Okay.
We're going to have to get another seed over here so we can move
a couple things while the action
is still going on. I want to be able to still cast the game.
But ladies and gentlemen, please welcome
Demon Lord Zaraxos.
Once you have a seat, we pulled a chair up here for you.
Please tell us what's on your mind,
I guess.
Man, I was fucking bored back there.
Alright, I don't want to cut you off,
but we do have another entrant to come in, Demon Lord.
It is a 90's icon.
You know him as the Slim Jim Guy.
Snap into a Slim Jim, oh yeah,
baby. Here he is.
Making his first ever appearance. The Slim Jim Guy is in this?
Yeah.
I hate this guy.
I've had a feud with this guy for the last like
2,000 years.
You've had a feud with the Slim Jim Guy for
two... That doesn't make any... I'm going to move on.
So, we have Slim Jim Guy
coming in. You really threw me off there, dude.
We have Slim Jim Guy coming in. We have the Mime,
Count Chocula, and Candyman
now, all fighting for
dominance in Jerma Rumble 3. Welcome, Slim Jim Guy.
And I guess while I have you
here, Zaraxos, I do have a couple of questions for you.
I'll get to those in a minute, but I do want to
focus on what's going on in the ring. We've got Slim Jim
now on the ropes, and a backhanded
slap to Candyman,
who is calling for time out right now
for some reason. People tend to do that.
Why do people call for time out in the middle
of a Royal Rumble? You're not going to get it.
There is no time out. What do you think there's a referee here?
And there goes Candyman! No, just barely.
Count Chocula almost eliminates him while
we have another contestant coming out. This
guy does not need an introduction.
He's the most miserable person on Earth.
Miserable, Mikey. And he's
all the way from the Quizney Channel, the most
miserable place on Earth. And
here he is, to show that he's ready
to take on everybody in the Jerma
Arena. He's huge, by the way. He's
like another giant rat. Anyways, now we're getting
a little crowded here as he goes for
Count Chocula with a couple of swift elbows
to his face. Nearly takes
his skull off, his huge skull,
mind you. And now that we have sort of a second
here where I can ask you, Xeraxos, I have
one question, just one simple question.
What the hell was going on in the beginning
there? Why did you eliminate yourself?
What are you doing? You honestly think
I belong here? It just wasn't fair.
You're going to put like Candyman and
Count Chocula versus me?
I'm the lord of all hells. None of
these little dipshits can do anything against me.
Why would I be in it? God, I fucking
hate the Slim Jim guy. You need to
calm down. Okay, you're seriously stressing
me out. I'm sorry, I'm sorry. So we got another entrance
to do, guys. Another buzzer. That means number 12
is going to be coming in. And it's
you know him. You love him.
The egg is coming down
for the fourth time. You know,
I am actually, I hate to say this,
but I actually am pleasantly surprised to see the egg.
I thought he was going to die or something. I thought he
would be one of the people in the beginning that was dead.
But no, he ends up being here. And
hopefully he goes far because he always
loses. So welcome egg to the German Rumble
and we've got a lot of stuff going on. Candyman
now is owing the ropes. He may
in fact, no, not going to get eliminated by Miserable Mikey.
I can't get over the fact that the
Slim Jim guy is in this. Will you
stop? I'm pissing me off. You need to stop
interrupting me. Okay, you're really derailing this
whole thing. I'm going back in. Fuck this guy. No, no, no, no.
You can't do that. Fucking Slim Jim guy. Zaraxos
no. Zaraxos.
Oh no, no, no, no. Don't do it.
Don't do it. No, we're going to get.
All right, get security. Get security.
Somebody call the fire department. Call security.
No, what do the Mayan have to do with
this? I'm not going to have this asshole
rule the whole German Rumble. There's another person dead.
Zaraxos is killing everybody in the
ring. Candyman, no. No, he's going
down. We need some help. The egg.
What the fuck egg? No, no, count Chocula.
All right, we need to get like the army
or something. How do you deal with the demon lord?
I have no idea. But somebody
has to get down there. Somebody has to stop this.
The egg and Mickey Mouse are
really starting. They're plotting who's
going to take on. You're not going to be able to take him on.
Are you crazy? I don't know what to do.
We're going to have to cancel the whole event, guys. I'm really
sorry about this. But wait a minute.
Who is that? Is that who
I think it is? That's Mr. Sneak Man.
It's me, Mr. Sneak Man.
Oh no.
No.
He came and he was trying to rescue this
event and he got stopped by
Demon Lord Zaraxos. This is just ridiculous
guys. And now Demon Lord can do whatever he
wants now. He cleared the ring pretty much.
And hold on a second.
Hold on a second.
Kitty, he's going to do it.
Through the table. Mr. Sneak Man
has just eliminated Demon Lord Zaraxos
and himself in the process.
Oh my God.
What have we just witnessed?
And also Bat Boy is, who fucking
cares about this guy? This guy sucks.
What really matters is Mr.
Sneak Man saves the
day and lets the rumble continue
sacrificing himself
for the greater good.
Thank you Mr. Sneak Man. Your
duty will not go unnoticed.
It seems like Zaraxos is very slow
to get up here. Needing the attention
of medical staff to bring him out.
I think he might have broken his leg on
that table. Yeah, he's pointing at his leg here.
Let's hope he does not recover
because fuck this guy. He ruined the whole rumble.
And after that entire ordeal
we are left with just three
competitors in the ring and what a shame
it is that it's these three
guys. You're telling me you couldn't have
chokeslammed Miserable Mikey into hell?
Like what is he still doing here?
You picked Count Chocula. He was doing
fantastic. Why would, now there's like three
dickheads in the ring. And now they're gonna
be double teaming. Now they're gonna do Miserable Mikey
holding the egg back while Bat Boy punches
him in the stomach and calling for time
out. It doesn't work. Stop calling time out.
It doesn't do it. Now Bat Boy is being held back by
the egg. These guys are idiots.
And now here comes the king
of all the idiots.
Ladies and gentlemen, please put your
hands together for the greatest
video game character to ever live.
I'm talking about Pac-Man.
Here he comes.
Coming in at number 14
to Jerma Rumble 3. And he's
got a great advantage. If you come in
in the last five or six you have such
a huge one up on
every other competitor that has come in
so far. He's refreshed.
He's naked and he's ready to go.
And his first order of business is to throw
Mikey over the ropes.
Not necessarily going for any
elimination while Bat Boy just did a roundhouse
kick and completely missed the egg.
I don't know if anybody saw that but I'm sure you did.
What a block by Pac-Man. One punch
and here comes the second. What a blast
to his face knocking him clean unconscious
while the egg is gonna get thrown over.
The egg has been eliminated by Bat
Boy. Embarrassing egg
hit the showers. You just got eliminated
by Bat Boy. And speaking of eliminations
we've got potentially Mikey
going over here by Pac-Man and Bat Boy. Is he gonna
go over? There holding up by his butt cheeks
and he doesn't go over just
barely. And here comes number 15.
All the way from your
neighborhood classroom. He's
here. He's primed. He's ready.
He's sharpened. He is.
The pencil.
First time ever seeing him in the
Jerma arena making his way down
really confident. He is stoked
to be here. He said he sharpened
his head to the point where he could stab
somebody through the heart and instantly
kill them. Let's hope he doesn't do that because that
would be terrible and we don't want to see any
more characters die at the hands
of somebody in this arena tonight.
Well Pac-Man gets a Larry by Mikey. Pac-Man has
been eliminated. And
look at this temper tantrum. He's starting to throw
at ringside right now. Usually a
pretty happy-go-lucky guy. Not
tonight though. Unfortunately
Pac-Man you have to go home. I
don't even know where that is. And the pencil
could get eliminated as well. No pencil
still hangs on to a double
attempt at elimination.
And now it's back to three.
There has been three in the ring
for the last few minutes now. We have not
seen a crowded ring since Zaraxos
destroyed everyone.
But now we've got number 16
coming in while Batboy is just
looking back and forth like he's at a tennis match.
I'm not exactly sure what the hell he's doing.
And that's, that's Jerma.
Looks a little different. Has he lost
weight? Has he not been going to the gym?
I don't know. Does he?
Oh no. Here we go. Let's see a couple of push-ups by you Jerma.
Let's show everybody you can do them.
You did one. You did one. Okay.
Very good. Get in the ring.
Batboy is still just looking left and right
while Mikey is being pushed over the
ropes by the pencil. Is he gonna get it?
He's gonna get it! He just tossed Mikey
over. That's it. Mikey is gone. He was in there
for a little while. He survived. The
final survivor of the Zaraxos
Tyrade has been eliminated.
And pay attention to these guys
that are in here right now everybody
because these three have a huge
percentage chance to win
the Jerma Rumble. There are only four
other contestants physically that are
going to come in and what a toss
by Batboy on the pencil.
I gotta say, we have seen some pretty
impressive moves by Batboy today.
I have talked a lot of shit about this guy
but he has done very well
with his time in the ring so far.
And what a block. What a reverse block by pencil
and a punch to the face by Jerma. Could we see Jerma get
eliminated? No, he reverses it and
tosses pencil into the corner there while we have
another person coming in at
number 17. Take a look
at this guy. Do you see the
intensity on that face? You can breathe
in the determination. He's looking for
redemption. Can you hear that roar?
That's Gabe Newell. Gabe
Newell is here at number 17.
The sailor of the ship.
The queen of Valve. The king of
Valve. He is everything. He is one.
He is the only Gabe Newell.
And you gotta figure shit is gonna hit
the fan when he gets in the ring here. He is
not happy with Jerma. What a duck by Jerma.
Gets him in a German suplex and throws him.
Unbelievable reversal there by Jerma.
Here comes the grudge match. TF2
community versus Valve. All the
shit that we talked about end of the line. It got
to Gabe Newell. He's pissed about it. What a punch.
And one, two, three. What
a series of combinations. Gabe Newell has
a vendetta and he is just
taking it out on Jerma's face right now.
Another right hand. Oh no he gets
a block. Gets a reversal here. Jerma going
for a wrist twist. It's not gonna happen.
Gabe Newell is running on pure adrenaline
right now. Tosses Jerma over the ropes.
Are we gonna see an elimination? Gabe
Newell is going to eliminate Jerma.
He's gone. Gabe Newell is cheering
into the crowd right now of his elimination
of Jerma. And we have another person
to call in. What a series of
events that just was.
I seriously can't believe
that Gabe Newell just came in and kicked the
shit out of me. Like he went right
for me. I didn't program that.
That like happened. He just beat the absolute bag
out of me and then threw me out.
I didn't script that. Anyways
here comes Abierre. And he's gonna go
right for Gabe Newell. Gabe Newell spins him around
and slams him on his back while the pencil
almost falls out of the ring
after being tossed over by Batboy
who still I can't believe is in it.
I cannot believe this. Guys
Batboy's like median attributes
are like 13 out of 100.
His like strength and grappling
and dexterity and all that shit
is less than 20 for every single one.
He should have been eliminated a long
time ago, but he's still in it for some reason.
Hey, maybe not for long.
Pencil's got him on the corner. You're gonna possibly throw him
over. No!
He gets a hand in the mouth right into
what is, what is Abierre doing?
What the hell is that? He was just like making origami
in front of him. He wasn't even like touching him.
And here comes number 18.
Sorry.
You didn't think there was gonna be
any more serial characters
did you? You didn't think that Sonny
the Cocoa Puffs Bird was gonna make an
appearance at number 19 in the
Jerma Rumble. Here he is. Sonny.
He's Cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs
and he's Cuckoo for the audience too. Look at him
riling him up, pointing and shouting. Everyone's
getting so fired up from Cuckoo the Cocoa Puffs
Sonny the Bird. And now he's in the ring
diving over with a beautiful display. They're going
right for Batboy. Strangely
enough, why did he go right for Batboy?
Batboy and Gabe Newell were in
sort of a little tussle there, but he
he may have been listening to me backstage.
There's a monitor back there. He just definitely
heard me talking about his low attributes
and he's gonna go, he's gonna take this to his advantage.
He's gonna push over Batboy. Is Sonny the Bird gonna do it?
Sonny the Bird's gonna toss him. He tosses
him. That's it. Batboy has been eliminated.
Sonny using
insider trading to be
able to throw Batboy over
the ropes there, which is sort of unfortunate
for Batboy because he went far. And now
Sonny is sort of just standing around not doing
anything. He went for the easy route
and now he's just chilling out while we have another
competitor coming in. This is the final
competitor, the final person in
JermaRumble 3 is
it's Tony the Tiger!
Do you hear this crowd right now?
This is the loudest I've ever heard
the Germania crowd screaming for
Tony the Tiger, the most physically
fit, the most positively influenceable,
the best serial character in
a lot of people's opinions. Here he comes
for the first time ever, Tony the Tiger
rounding out the number 20 spot.
Finally, the last person is
in and one of these
five is going to be crowned
JermaRumble 3 champion.
And there is a high chance
it's gonna be another serial
character. So place
your bets now. Somebody in
this ring is going to win.
Will it be the much deserved
Gabe Newell victory that we've all
been waiting for? Could it be a revival
of the Biaz? Could the Biaz
take it? Could Gabe Newell just clothesline
Sonny the Bird over the top ropes? Yes he will!
See you later, Sonny!
And now there are four.
You see, this is where fatigue,
this is where the nerves, this is where the
computer AI, which one isn't a moron,
this, all this stuff comes into play
at the very end of a JermaRumble.
You see we've got the Bia now and Gabe Newell in the
corner, two very heavy characters.
The Bia and Gabe Newell,
very large characters. Gabe Newell with ease
seems to pick up the Bia on the top
turnbuckle. Can he do it? He's very heavy!
Is he that strong?
He is! Gabe Newell just eliminated
Bia 846. That's another
elimination that you can tally
onto Gabe Newell. He has been
on a spree. It looks like him and Tony
the Tiger are going to- No! It's a reversal!
The pencil just reversed that double
DDT attempt. What a fantastic
double reversal that
was by the pencil. You just don't see
reversals like that anymore, let
alone from a character that's as shitty as
the pencil. Now Gabe Newell, Gabe Newell
on the defensive. Gabe Newell might be eliminated
right here by two of these assholes! No, he
ends up getting out of punches and both in the head
and for Tony the Tiger's trouble, he's going to
get thrown over. Could Gabe Newell get
another elimination here? Could it be possible?
Is Tony the Tiger going to fight back? Is the pencil
going to rescue him? No! Gabe Newell has
just eliminated Tony the Tiger as well!
Unbelievable!
Gabe Newell, that's like five
eliminations almost in a roll
for Gabe Newell and now we are down to
the final two. These are the final
competitors, the pencil
and Gabe Newell. One of
these two is going to be crowned
German Rumble 3 champion. Will it be
the shit character or will it be the most
beloved man in the history
of PC gaming? And he throws over
the pencil, body to back suplex,
and he might have possibly injured his face
on that somehow. What a
reversal. What a block and an elbow to Gabe Newell's face!
Almost blinding him, punching him in the eye,
only seeming to irritate Gabe
Newell just a little bit while he
gets him with a big boot right to his gut there.
Throws him over the ropes and they both bounce into
each other. I think Gabe Newell had a different
strategy there and he didn't utilize it.
Maybe going for a powerbomb, his patented finishing
move, the powerbomb, no! Going to
try and maybe end this right now.
No, he's just taunting, maybe catching his breath a little
bit after all that. He did eliminate a bunch of people
after all. And the pencil was probably
very low on his priorities
for who he should eliminate. And
dear God, he just threw him across the
entire ring. And the
pencil is hurt. The pencil is
really hurt right now. May have a broken
leg. Gabe Newell being a good guy, checking
on him, making sure. No!
No! What a cheap
shot that was. He cheap
shot him. He hit Gabe Newell right in his family
jewels. No, this can't be it.
It can't end like this. Gabe Newell
is holding up a dear life. Can the pencil eliminate
Gabe Newell after that cheap shot?
That's the end. The pencil
has won Jerma Rumble 3 on
a cheap, low
blow. Oh, you've
got to be kidding me. You've
got to be kidding me. Gabe Newell cannot believe
what just happened, and neither can
I, and neither can this crowd.
Do we really have to
crown this guy Jerma Rumble champion?
In the rule books, we do.
Ladies and gentlemen, your
Jerma Rumble 3 champion,
the pencil.
Jerma Rumble 3 is in the books,
and I'll see you at the next event.