Hey, howdy doody. Oh, how diddley do neighbor, right? What's that guy's name? Flanders.
We're gonna play more Blitz The League 2 today, because I think it's a great game. It's a lot
of fun. Can I build another birdhouse? I think one is enough. I think one birdhouse is a pretty
good quota for 10 years. Last time I built a birdhouse, I was probably... I would say every
time I get a tetanus shot is when a birdhouse should be built. So, you know, go get a tetanus
shot. Now, you know what? I actually think I probably do for one. Oh my... what's going on
with this? What's going on with the sub notifications? Oh wait, I heard about this. I heard about
this. Yeah, I might have to do... I might have to turn off stream labs. I heard that it's
like broken, right? The stream labs. It's intended. Oh, oh my god. Okay, well,
that's like... that's more resubs than chat. Welcome to the stream. But yeah, we're gonna
play more Blitz The League. And I have something very unfortunate to tell you guys.
I know you guys aren't... no one's gonna want to hear this, but I have to say it.
Unfortunately, this is one of those weeks where I have a lot of shit to do. The last couple days,
I've been doing things. I've been taking care of some stuff. And I gotta do my taxes.
I gotta get it done. So, this is pretty much the only stream until like probably Friday or
Saturday. Because I gotta get that shit taken care of. So, this is like the week that was
gonna be kind of hard for me to stream that much. So, we'll go for... I'm gonna try to go
as long as I can tonight. Just commit tax fraud. No, I gotta make sure I get it right. Every
year I take at least a day or two. And it happened to fall. I talked to my CPA and there's
a lot of shit that I gotta do and take care of. Because I moved and it's very confusing for me
because I live in a different state and I have to file like twice or something. I don't know.
It's a lot of random shit that I haven't ever had to deal with before. So, I need to give
the time necessary to get it right. So, you'll see me again. The stream's not like over. What
am I doing? You'll see me again. Hey, I'll see you right now. This is the play. Here we go.
All right. So, I got the ball. Not all. Almost interception. Just don't pay your taxes.
That's not how it works. Just don't pay. That's so... That is such bad advice.
All right. We're gonna play Blitz League 2, but I want to make do... There's only been one
stream this week and I just want to make sure people are prepared for it. Fucking
responsibilities. You know, they're being 33. Why can't I... I want to be like 12 again.
I didn't have to do taxes when I was 12. I didn't have to like take care. I didn't have to have
to have like a repairman. No, I... When I was 12, I just was 12. When I was 12, I wanted to be 33.
That's weird how that works. 12-hour stream for a 12-year-old streamer.
All right. Did I actually miss the window to press this again?
But yeah. I gotta be a good boy and get all my taxes done.
And I was trying to find a place to do it and it's always like doing your taxes, especially
somebody that gets the kind of income that I get. You know, you just... It's called 1099
for those of you that are just curious. I have to do them all myself with the help of obviously
like a CPA. So I always... It's always like, all right, I'm gonna do my taxes.
Oh, I don't want... I don't wanna. Like I'll do it another day.
And then like another like month goes by. No, but I... But I took a time. I can do it like
next month. No, you gotta get done. So I have to pick the day that I lock myself
in my room for like at least a day or two. And that's tomorrow. So we're gonna pick up. This
is the... Unfortunately, this joke doesn't really mean anything anymore because we're
Mr. Super Bowl and playing as the Las Vegas Super Bowlers. So that's kind of...
It's not gonna really be... That's not funny anymore. I can't edit this team's name either.
We can't go in and be like, oh, you know what? I want to change up to like the Las Vegas
Dealers. What it should have been. But I listened to the one guy twice for the name of
the character and the name of the team. Your mom is so stupid she brought cereal to the Super
Bowl. Get that guy out of here. Talk about my mother like that? Get him out of here. All
right. So this is Division two. We just leveled up. We just won the Division three
championship. Is there anything we need to do? Somebody's injured. Isn't one of our good players
injured? Yeah. Halfback D. Sullivan is out for one more game. Unfortunately, we don't have a
good halfback. So that's just the way it is. How much money do I have? It's $17,000.
We want to know in Division two. I don't understand how American football is played.
Keywell, you don't have to. This game... Take away everything you know about sports.
This has just hurt each other the game. Okay. Can you hurt somebody else? If the answer is like,
are you like, could you like punch a guy in the face? You could play this game.
But hi, Keywell. How you doing? Here comes another beer chug. Yeah. Yeah. You're going
to see it like five times. All right. We're going to get our ass kicked here because
no, always the best teams are always the ones that I beat without a problem at all.
Drunk streamer? What? 1-0 versus the Crossfire. Every time I don't make a bet either. You know
what? Let's go all in. Fuck it. I need to win by 19 points. Let's go.
Okay. So provoke him.
So instead of provoke him, we need to get rid of him. Why is he like an, why is he like an animal?
What? Was that a lion? How on earth did this get a sequel? Because it's the best game ever.
I'm actually sad that there's not a third one. Hello everybody.
It's the Las Vegas Craigsicles. So those of you that weren't here the last stream,
you're probably wondering, he's playing a football game. Oh, how cool is that?
Well, you're about to find out why that is. No, it ain't not. You will eventually. You'll find out.
Why do you have monsters ink colors? Because that's my favorite movie ever made.
All right. I'm the safety. This is my main character here is the character that is the
character in the campaign. Oh, I didn't get it. And this is why we play this game guys.
You're about to find out. It's just a strain. It's just a neck strain. He's got his brain
neck. We got to get him out of here. How long was he out for? Yeah. Get the card out here.
That wasn't their star player, was it? I don't think it was. Four plays. That's not bad.
All right. I got to stay back. No first down. Don't throw up over there. What are you
doing? What's wrong with you? So in the top left and top right, you can see a meter
and depending on how much media you have, you can do certain things.
So when you get a full meter and it says unleashed is when you can really hurt somebody on these.
We're talking like broken neck. We're talking snapping their collarbone off. We're talking
like awful shit. They didn't get a first down? Okay. We're fourth down. The fourth
down right now in inches. We're going to go with like a field goal block.
No, no, no, no. Like this. Oh, fuck. What are they doing? They're punting. Shit. Why?
Inches. You have to just walk. Not even. All right. Come on, Raymer. Here we go. Watch this shit.
Oh no. Who was that? Was that me? Oh, it's just a sprained knee. It's all right.
I got it. Don't worry. Sprained knee. More like you are not going to walk again.
Holy shit. We haven't seen that one. How is that a sprain?
Okay. That guy, was that guy like an important player? I don't think he was.
Nobody's here. Nobody's here. Stop him. Stop him. That is such a huge gain. We've just got so
many yards. No, and there's also like these weird cheerleaders that did the same animation
every time. Somebody cut. Cut. God damn it. That's such horseshit. How? I should have just
punched him. It's all right. You got a long way to go. Kick his helmet off. Beat it. Go, go, go, go.
Chad is now in re. Oh yeah, that's right. Like don't you should. I think I. Do I have to turn
this off? I think I have to turn off the recepts, right? Do I? Get it.
How do you not pick up that fumble? Why would I do that? I don't know if it was like a
thing that I should do. I don't know. I won't turn it off. I don't know how you
catch that ball. That went through four people. Those guys have made it a fucking.
That's the end of the first quarter as we're scoreless.
How did that happen? I need to see that again. So I got one, two, three, four defenders. I sack
him. He gets the ball out and I ghost through this guy. Three people can't stop him from
catching that. That's what we call in the fucking. Hey, that's what we call in this
industry baloney. Well, it's still four down. Sorry. This is the one. Watch this. All right.
Now I can't fuck this up. Why? What the hell? Didn't we give them hand lotion last time?
I thought I upgraded their hands. Why am I fumbling every single time? Thankfully,
they haven't scored any points. There we go. That's what I'm talking about.
All right. It's like it never happened. It never should have happened in the first place.
All right. Let's go for a run. I don't want to unleash yet. Not unless I need to.
All right. I'm afraid to do like a QB sneak here. We're going to go with a pass.
All right. I need to get him. Come on. Speed. I'm unleashing here. How do you stop
an unleash? That's impossible. Fuck. Okay. Don't fuck it up. Field goal. Okay. That's enough.
What? How did that not go through? That didn't go through. How is that not going through?
No good. No good. Bad field goal. What? All right. Stick. Who's the guy I need to be
looking for? What team are they on? I mean, their team. Are they on offense or defense?
Not going to happen. So they're on defense. Okay. You got to break all their legs. I'm going to
score a point. Oh, by the way, I heard that Vinnie hosted me for like 30 seconds or something
last stream during I think somebody's brain exploding. And then he immediately unhosted
and went live. So everybody got to see like five seconds of somebody's like brain blowing
up. And then like Vinnie's stream started. I was when somebody told me that I was fucking
laughing like something bad happened. Whoa, I got to catch this. Oh, stand up.
Is Cox be acting up here? Nice. Nice taco bell uniform.
Oh, I had the ball too. No, why did you say something so funny?
I didn't use any time. Oh, my God. Taco Bell. The Las Vegas Taco Bell.
Just patted that guy in the back. The Las Vegas Baja Blasters.
No, these are the official German 985 colors.
I wish I was just sitting down there with a hot babe. Oh, shut up.
I can't. Oh, my God. What? Oh, tell me that wasn't his fucking hell. All right. Come on.
We got to go for X. Bang.
Their defense is so good. All right. Fuck it. I'm going for it. Watch this shit.
What can we do? We got to boot it. I'm going for it.
The defense is so good. They're too good on defense. I have to play defense as good as they
are. I have to be as good as they are. The offense looking at first and 30. They're not
going to get shit. All right. That's fine. Not a significant game.
He's recovered from his broken ribs. Yeah, that's usually how it happens. Get it.
I'm going to play defense better than them. 12 is significant, but they still have 18
yards to go. They're going to kick a field goal here and they're going to miss it.
Good luck on your field goal attempt because I'm blocking it.
We're a special field goal block. He's the guy who needs it. He needs close.
No, they're going for it. Oh, shit. I got to change this.
I can't believe he got it. He used his unleash. That's why.
So stupid. Oh, it's all right. One. I thought the AI never goes forward on fourth down.
You've seen that. Come on. Well, good. Fuck you. You don't get extra point. Now
I can win the game easily. This is the one. All right. That's such a huge game.
I need to take a capitalized ization on this. We're going cold smoke. First and goal. It's
gut check time. How did he even get in here? How did he even get the fuck in here?
Second and goal. Desperate. Desperate. Here we go. Here I squeezed on his spleen.
That's it. Good old cocks. Beer chug, right? I don't think that was beer chug,
but I'll be ahead now. I ain't losing this game. When did I get my own stadium?
I think I just had one, right? I just had one. Come on. We're the Las Vegas cocks.
I'll bust his ankle up for the whole year. Broken foot. Bring out the cart.
See you later. All right. Let's play deep. That was going to give him a new foot.
End of the quarter. As we reach the end of the third quarter, Las Vegas leads by a point.
How is that a minor injury? Well, in this universe, I think your limbs just,
there's like drugs that you inject where it makes your limbs grow back.
They're down and I get the ball and I will make a touchdown and the game will be
unreachable and we'll be, we'll be eight and one. All right. Watch this guy number 15.
Get out of my fucking life.
And I have an unleash.
Boomer announcer. Now you're going to punt it. Oh fuck. Somebody has to get back there.
Get back there. Somebody, anyone, you know, you're like small. Okay. Check it.
All right. We still have an unleash. I'm so ready for this.
That's what that is right there. Why would I fake field bill? HB float left down and 30.
I don't even need them star player and I still have it. So do they though. All right.
I got to get a touchdown right now. We'll go with a trick play. We're going to do maniac.
Check that top left corner into the end zone, into the dice
with an unleashing to do an unleashed catch. What just happened?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, hold on. Hold on. Come on. What happened?
How did they intercept the ball? I am so confused right now. I can't even like laugh at that.
I have no replay. Did he steal the handoff?
He ran into the handoff. I have no fucking idea what happened there.
I can't believe it. How do you intercept a handoff? Walk it again.
It's all right. I just need a touchdown and I win the game. Just get a touchdown and the
game's over. This is a good position to be in. I got two timeouts. I have no meter,
but that's okay. Just don't fumble the goddamn ball. Okay. Here we go.
Holy. Good thing he's got insurance. We're going to go intertwine.
Gets rid of it. Got it. Come on. Come on. Stay up. He's brought down 38 yard line. Las Vegas
and everyone on the same page there. Okay. I got meter. With a very nice game.
Just keep it going. First down 30 yards to go. Wall at the 38.
Looking for room on the right side. Damn it. I got to get it right now. Come on.
This is it. Right here into the end zone. Recovered in the end zone. That deserves a
shot of a beer. Look at that. Just get a field goal and I win the game properly. That
felt good. That one felt good. Seven seconds to get a field goal. That ain't going to happen.
I got meter. He doesn't. Just get a tackle. Two, one. He's okay. He's got one play.
He doesn't have an unleash. He has one play. We're just going to do full coverage here.
Complete. Just coverage. Just lock it down. Man up. I don't care how many yards they get.
Just stay in the back. See you later. Game over. I win. 14-13. There it is.
How much money am I going to get for this one? Off to a good start.
I wagered a lot of money, didn't I? Yeah. Oh well. Oh well. 200 grand.
I guess that was a really low scoring game, huh? You pulled that one out of your ass and I
respect that. I tried. Thanks. Watch the movies. These are the team intros.
When they'd introduce the captain of the team. All right. Tara, what's up?
Hey there, franchise. I hear you've been asking about me. I think it's time we met
face to face. Cut scene. See you at the club tonight. Okay. Here we go.
Damn. You came ready to play. Franchise. You look short for a football player.
Oh, don't play me. I've got all you'll ever need. I'm sure you do, honey,
but can you keep up? You'll need to prove it first. Prove it? What are we talking about
here? Show me what you've got on Sunday. Play hard on that field and you can play hard on mine.
I like a man who can dish it out. You better be ready. It's gonna get rough.
God. I'm looking forward to it. So what do I have to do? Franchise must cause an injury
next game. That's what you want me to do? Go hurt someone. That's how you gain my respect.
Okay. I think I can handle that. How are we doing on injuries?
Sullivan is still up for two games. How? He had, he already had, it's already been one game. He had
medical staff on him. What the hell was that all about? I don't know. I don't think I have
enough money for anything. 260, 220. I don't have any money. What about drugs? Let's see.
Generate two stamina. Increases the severity of injuries caused by juiced player. So I'm
gonna take this and I'm just gonna try to hurt as many. That's a high risk though.
I can't do the, look at the risk. I can't do it. It's all, it's maxed out right now. Yeah,
I can't do that. I wish I could get my half back back to, you know, who's the,
Atlanta 404 is the next team. Just take the legal ones. Take the legal ones.
All of these are illegal. On the left? It's one of the cheapest over-the-counter drugs.
Yeah, but I mean, they're gonna be searching my bag. It's illegal. Yeah, but I, so,
fine. I'll take it. I'll take the legal drug. It says legal. I know, but just because it's legal
doesn't mean I can do it. They're checking. I just got out of prison. Let's go. Atlanta 404.
They have insane defense. I'm not betting on this game. They almost have a maxed out defense.
Next up, we got the Atlanta 404. This team's only been in the league for three years,
but their defense is so destructive, they've already made it into division two.
The guy who anchors their defense is Keno Talopa. This guy is a destroyer.
6'5", 3'40", fast as hell. The son of a bitch's head should be a registered weapon.
When he hits you, it's like a wrecking ball. Do yourself a favor and keep a safe distance.
I gotta be aware of this. I gotta be careful.
Best defense in the league. You're under arrest for buying those groceries legally.
You just never know. He just launches himself into someone. He probably causes a lot of
injuries. So, lockdown defense, and they're a defense team. So, I just have to score a
shitload of points or prevent them from scoring. I get the kickoff. Let's make it happen.
Watch out for the guy.
He just hit me so hard, I started to T-pose. This is not going to go well.
Okay. We're going to go with... I don't want to do pass plays. Jesus!
Horatious. You gotta wonder how he's going to continue playing after that.
All right. Plan B. Oh my god. Oh, this is bad.
That defense is so good. They just knock it out of you. Oh, you fucking idiot. What to
happen? Okay, I blame that on where my hands were on the controller. I blame where my
hands were. My, like, cold sweat slippery hands. Jesus Christ. Okay. Well, let's get
over the fact that I just lost 20% stamina on two people and then got an interception.
You can't stop them. They can't be stopped. It's gotten unleashed, too. This is really bad.
I'm so afraid of that. Oh, he's going to unleash and kill somebody.
Oh no! Thank god you held onto the ball, Cox. That was a full drop kick.
All right. Well, thank god. How the hell am I going to deal with this?
Okay. I have to punt it. I have to. I can't go down by 14 points immediately.
Atlanta's making you look like a CPU. Well, they did have double my stats. So,
you know, there's only so much you can work with here. I'll sit him in the championship
and I'll beat him. That's the quarter. That's all right. That's not out of reach.
I have to hurt somebody, right? I got to impress my new girlfriend.
Who's gonna get hurt? Huh? How did you catch that ball?
Hurt him. Come on. Hurt. Damn it. That was an opportunity to hurt him. I didn't get it,
though. I do have an unleash. It's four down. They're probably gonna punt.
Yeah. Here's my chance to get it back. Bryant, let's go. I wasn't gonna use it there.
All right. I need to get a touchdown. I'm gonna go with world record crisscross.
First down, 30 yards to go. And he's knocked down. Mercury. Deep pass.
I tried to do an unleash but it wouldn't happen. Fuck. I've got to go for a run.
I got to unleash run. Good. There it is. No, get up. Get up. You have a broken humorism.
Just get the field goal. Tag him. Dab. It's like it never happens. All the way back. Great kick.
Injure. Injure. Injure. Uh-oh. What the fuck happened? Why do they all just freak out?
They all like... Because I was trying to get... Okay. I see what happened. I was trying to
get the... I'm trying to get him. Injured. I know. I'm trying. I'm trying to injure somebody.
I'm afraid to do a blitz but, you know, I'm just gonna stay back.
Injure. Excuse me? Excuse me? Why did he dive through? Hold on. What was that?
I fucking dove through him. Look at him. I'm waiting for him. Waiting for him.
What the hell? Cartoon dog shit. Whatever. I can't believe it just happened.
And the extra point is good. I got his iframe. He dodge rolled me. He was already in a tackle
parry. Damn it. I need to... He's gonna get the ball too. I'm gonna have to score a touchdown
right now. And he has an unleash. Get to the fucking outside. And what am I gonna do with
this? I wonder if I can get him to burn his unleash. That would be ideal. Cut it. Cut it.
Cut out. Cut out. All right. Get it. It's okay. Go outside. Out of bounds. No.
Who is this? Oh, it's Ashley. They'll be all right. Out for six games. Fuck. Okay. I still
have a chance here. I got timeout after this. Drop middle. Come on. I gotta get this.
Shit. I got him. Okay. We're gonna fake field goal. Touchdown.
Uh, oh well. What were you thinking? I don't know. I don't know why I did that. Injury.
Could have done square. Yeah, but I... Every time I've thrown it to a guy that crosses.
Just caught my foot. It's extra challenging throwing the guys at three defenders. Injury.
Damn it. That was such a good hit too. There it is. It's the quarterback too. He's in deep shit.
That was the painful one. And I have an unleash. So third and 26. Just a minor injury
to the balls. I don't think so. Not gonna happen. Fourth down. Give me the ball.
All right. I'm going to play safe here. Just prevent. Oh, God damn it. He's punting it.
I always think he's going to go for it. And then when it, when he doesn't go for it.
It's okay. Check it. Why would he not punt on fourth and 20?
Because this game is insane and they do insane things.
First down and 30.
Pretty good mud physics. This game stands up. It does. And so we're back to a tie game.
No, I actually forget the beer jug code. I think it's XX circle circle. Rev up the Friars.
I'm in a good spot. The cheerleaders in this game look dead inside.
They do have that kind of just stone cold face, don't they?
First down 30 yards to go. Ball at the 27 yard line.
Watch the left side. I got nothing. I would be too if I was dancing in this weather.
Yeah. Balance. We're going to go with jammer. I don't even know.
Guys, I just want to make sure this is clear with everybody watching.
I, I don't know what any of these mean. I mean, I have a general idea, but I don't really follow
football that much. I don't know. Like for instance, I know like cover and blitz and
zone. I don't know what any of these things really mean though.
I'm doing the thing where you play Madden against your friend and neither one of you
know what the fuck you're doing. You're just picking random plays.
Having a great time though. I have no idea. Does it matter? Not really.
Okay. This is fourth and 31. I wonder if he's going to punt it.
Why are you allowed just to beat people up? Because this is blitz.
I might be able to run this back for touchdown. Possible.
There we go. Touchdown. Got it. Oh, I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
And he's in. Touchdown. Have to say this guy puts the special in special teams. Why the heaven?
All right. Good. Good. Good. Turn on the face cam. I don't have any clothes on. I can't.
Do I just say fuck it and try to go for it? Fuck it. Right up the middle.
That was a mistake. Yeah, it was. I tend to make those here.
And so with three quarters gone, Las Vegas leads by six. I wanted to try to make it so if you got
a touchdown, it wouldn't have mattered. But now all he needs is a touchdown to win.
And I'm embarrassed. I'm ashamed. First and 30. Ball at the 25 yard line.
Do you have a six pack? Yeah, dude. Bullshit. Yeah, dude. Let's go with deep zones.
Jerma works out every night. No, I mean, I did 500 crunches a day.
Half a dozen donuts is not six pack. Yes, it is. I do at least five. I probably do. No,
you know, I probably do a thousand crunches a day. No, no, no, no, no. How is it fucking
possible? That auto of all people. How many tackles are you going to break after a fumble?
Really? What? This is un fucking believable. That's unbelievable. He broke like seven or
eight different tackles. After a fucking fumble. Guy gets it and just covers himself in oil and
then runs through. Fuck. Second and goal. Bad. Pumple. I popped his fucking water balloon.
Good. I haven't unleashed to third and goal. This is the game right here. I have to,
I have to unleash right here. He's got to be because he's going to get a field goal,
right? Unleash it. Why were they walking off the field? We need to stop them right here,
right now. Okay. Um, are they going for it? It's all or nothing.
Nothing. Yeah. He's tackled at the two yard line and they turn the ball over. Now they
could have used some points right there, but the defense said, no way. I got an unleash too.
Surprised. I actually, um, didn't unleash that one. Same deal. Run it before the game,
huh? Run it. They don't got any more time outs and then fucking punt it if I have to.
See you later. Break the tackle. I just like fell down. Game over. I win.
Keep that record going. Did I just walk across the field and sprinkle somebody?
I think I, yeah, I just, that was awesome. That's a win. Another close call, but still
able to keep it going. Now I got $430,000. I injured somebody. So I'm going to get a new
girlfriend, right? Man enough for Tara. $5,000 cash. Okay. Let's see what that means. Here's
Tara. You do know how to, let's get together tonight so you can try some of your moves on
me. What? No. Well, uh, sure. I guess hope this might be bad. I might have to, uh,
okay. Let's, uh, hope you don't mind. I brought a friend.
And incoming sensor ruptured spleen. I'm going to like fall out of bed and rupture my spleen.
I'm going to roll out of bed and like explode my collarbone.
You're taking them on two at a time now? You got to pace yourself, brother.
Next time since I'm that booty my way. Yeah.
Son, do you know how fast you were going? I was going 70. 68.
Oh, this is not good. Do I answer this phone? Oh, real nice. You jerk. I can't believe you
did this to me. And with her, don't call me again. Hey killer. How are you doing?
You need anything besides me? That is look, I know people, people who can get me the stuff
I already had it. And I could get it at cost. Just don't ask me where or how.
Let me know what you need and how much. I don't want, I don't want like an illegal
girlfriend. You know what I mean? Like do any legal things. Kim was by the book. This is like
illegal girlfriend. Oh, I did. I do things illegally. No, I want my, I, where's, I want
Kim back. Tara gets you drug discounts. I'm in love. Those are expensive. Okay. We need
some resist injury, break tackle, maybe, or strength. This game is something else.
It is a timeless classic. I'm going to say strength and these two weights. Yeah. Strength.
I got 150. How much of a discount though? That's all I can do. Who's still injured? Okay.
Oh man. Oh man. That's not good. Five games. Okay. So we got the,
our good halfback is in the game again. I need some more medical staff. How much is
the point? Yeah, I just get it. Good. Juicing. Let's see how much of a discount it is.
Seven. That's, that's a monumental discount. This was like what? 60. This was like 50 or
60 thousand dollars before. This is so cheap now. Juiced player is immune to injury. It
wasn't like that before, was it? Well, I'll take the legal one. I'm going to give the
halfback, I'm going to get the halfback a legal drug too. Everyone's going to take aspirin.
What the hell this is? What? Okay. What about the catcher? Should the catcher have something?
Lame streamer. Look at the team risk. If I take an illegal drug right now. Who's up next? We
got the Washington Redhawks. Okay. Scroll down on the injuries. Oh shit. That's right.
No, this is the only two. That was the only two that are there. All right. I got to,
hey, it's been an hour. That means I got to pee. So welcome to the, the,
the bi-hourly, but quarterly hourly piss. First one of the night. See you in a minute.
How did he go? So we're a new game versus the, uh, versus Washington. All right. Not as awful
as, oh and three. Hmm. Win by more than 10 points. Did I wash my hands? Yeah. I rinsed
them and I did soap. 25,000 max bet to a team that's oh and three.
They're not very, the stat wise, they're not that much better. I'm max betting it.
Let's try. The Washington Redhawks have one of the most explosive offenses in the league.
Quarterback Clayton West got with the league MVP. Now he's recording his own rap album.
He is still a damn good quarterback. Fame's gone straight to his head.
The former face of the league is now a giant douchebag. In other words, he's just right
in with the rest of the Redhawks. So, Andrew, is what you're saying. Break him, break him.
Look, I'm going to try. That's what I do every game. I go for, I go for the attack.
Good evening everyone. I'm not going to ever be able to think about anything besides Taco Bell
now. I laughed about it even on the way downstairs. Break his neck. I'm, look, I'm
going to try to do whatever I can. Ow. He's a quarterback, right?
Good thing he's got insurance. Let's start off with just a
fucked up trick play. I didn't, did I not pick one?
Fumble it again. Fumble. Fumble, fumble, fumble, fumble. Give it back.
That was loud and scary. I tried to go in for the kill there.
A little more juice. Shit. Why did I, I did like a bomb pass the first play of the game.
Blade hit. Gun unleashed. I think I gotta go for it here.
Got it. Oh, watch this one. Run it back for a touchdown right now. See you later.
Yes. Let's make them 0 and 4.
Really pushing your luck there. Well, if I had got tackled, I would have blamed it in the end.
That's not a good kick at all. Fumble. Drunk Madden. He has no commentary at all.
By the way, there is no commentary. First down and 30. The guy just says the name of the
play, what yardage it is. And then drunk John Madden talks about like diapers.
Fumble. Oh, fumble. I killed him, but he didn't fumble the ball. Spinal cord. No,
he's not dead. They got somebody yards on that too. I ain't gonna happen. Get that late hit.
Let's go to the bottom edge. I gotta go for an injury here. I'm not gonna get it. He's in a
bad spot right now. He's in like 73, 74. And I have an unleash. Third and goal. Hmm. Question
is do I use the unleash now and try to prevent a touchdown, but they'll get a field goal or do I?
I'll take it. Didn't even need to use it. I got my halfback back.
28 is back. Let's get out of the fucking end zone. Get out. Oh, look at me.
Wow. That was awesome. That is exactly what I wanted to have happen. 99 yard run.
Fumble with MVP. Yeah. We didn't have him for at least two or three games straight.
That was a 100 yard. That guy deserves extra drugs after this game. Yeah, definitely. He
deserves extra drugs. First down, 30 yards to go. You know, Mr. Super Bowl. I'm kind of surprised
that he got away from that. He's really fast. No. Let's go over like a blitz. Goodbye. See
you later. That deserves a chuck. I'm up by so much now. Well, I told you there's a reason why
you're only free. Let's go for it. 22 to zero. Have you considered becoming a professional NFL
blitz player? Yeah, I have. There's only one problem though. I think I'm the only person
that owns this game right now. So I would be, it'd be an AI tournament. If the NFL blitz the league
two tournament series, it would just be me against AI opponents in a giant stadium.
See you later to the quarterback. That's like a broken tailbone.
That's the guy that I had to go after. Five games. There's the start player. They don't
have a chance trying to injure their other quarterback. What happens if you run into all
quarterbacks? Do you have to have like the safety play quarterback? Fourth down. You're
gonna have to punt it. All right, punch that guy in the face. Get him. Do it.
There goes my appetite. Yeah, this is probably in a good game to eat too.
I'm about to get the ball back again.
Good thing he's not pregnant. First and 30. I'm gonna go with the, uh, try.
Uh-oh. No, not 28. Not 28 again. He's fine. Thank God. He would have been out
for four games. Awesome juke. Thank God. Time out. Let me get, let me get a touchdown here.
Crucial series of downs here. Ball spotted at the 13 yard line.
Two point conversion again. I bet on this game, didn't I? Yeah, I did.
I put max at $25,000 on this game.
Fuck, now I gotta kick it off. Idiot. Three seconds for them to score a touchdown.
Let's just prevent. We're gonna go just straight up,
four men in the backfield. They're going for a bomb pass.
The announcer's Frank Galliendo. I gotta get more. This is the kind of game you have to make
money because this team sucks. So I already have at least 50 grand coming in from the bet.
Somebody pick it up. That's what I'm talking about. Just get like fucking 500 grand from
this game. Shut out. It's all right. It's still game. Let's run it in there.
It's all right. Just get in there slowly. Turn up the difficulty.
Easy. Now I have to win these by a lot. Do the beer chug on cam. He flew in the air.
I'm gonna take the shot. I'm gonna try to win by 50 points. 50 to 0. That's what I'm going for
here. This guy's down at 60%. One bad injury to this guy. He'll have a play again. Crush,
we're going with the Blitz. Just take everybody over here. No fumble. Can somebody actually get
murdered? Yeah, they can go out for the whole year. Or forever, I think. My character
like died in the game, didn't he? Technically. Who caught it? Um, excuse me. I don't. There's
no explanation for what just happened. I don't. Who caught that ball? Okay, he dodges that
and then threw it over here. The guy behind him caught it without looking. It went into
his hands. I was trying to tackle that guy and I did tackle that guy. He's weird. He
was running the opposite direction without looking. It went right into his hand. How do
you miss that? Both of you. It's okay. No shut out, bud. Jeremy, you've landed like 50 punches on
camera. All right, let's go with the run. Here comes his unleash. It's probably going to be
a fumble or an injured player. So I don't know why I'm giving it to my star player.
I'm so terrified of it. Don't give the ball to that. It's time to just play
easy. No reason to give it to the halfback anymore. Not at this point.
And I gave it to him! Red zone stood again. Uh, this time we're gonna do Bolton. Hide in.
Oh well. It was worth a shot. Forget it. 1,000 yards season. That's my star player.
Thank god. I think if franchise gets an injury, the game ends. So just keep that in mind. That's
why I was a little concerned there. How did I not get that? Still got it. I don't know how.
Wow. 50 points.
What do you say you chug it? 50 points. Let's go again. Quarterback dash. There's no way he's
gonna do that twice in a row, right? Things are going well 50 to 6. And I still haven't
unleashed it. I'm going to use it right now. What percentage is this guy at right now? How
can you still be standing? It's alright. Why did he just die?
The guy that fell down is the one that got the hit. I love him. This is on PlayStation 3.
Yeah, not on Xbox right now. PS3. Oh yeah! He deserves it. You deserve it. Yeah, you
deserve it. You're not kicking a field goal. Run the whole thing back. Come on. What does
this mean? This is just a failed conversion. I was trying to build up points. Well, it
doesn't matter. Dermot, that's two points. I thought it was just a, no, it's a two-point
conversion, right? So I thought that's just a failed conversion. Not the halfback, please.
God damn it. First game, you come back. Of the seven games. God, Jesus. What?
That sucks. That actually sucks. Triangle, triangle, triangle, X. I'll try it.
He's gonna get it. I don't care. I'm just, I'm playing like a clown right now because it
doesn't matter. Some kind of currency thing. Is it? I don't know. How long is the story mode?
Uh, we are currently in the second division of one more division. So the division two,
division one. And I'm assuming like the championship of the whole game. So it seems
like we're halfway through the second division we're all about to be.
End them right now or I'm gonna leave, or I'm going. Um, I've, I've taken out at least like
four people on their team. You can't leave now. You can't leave. I just silly potted that guy's
back. Look at me. This is embarrassing.
58 to 12. Fucking cares. Oh, I was trying to be like, I was trying to BM their team.
They'll help with this for the ultimate BM. No, he's still, still okay. First and 30.
All right, let me BM their quarterback. Yeah, whatever. Let them have it. You got a touchdown.
Congratulations. Las Vegas will take this one. Oh no, I'm gonna make so much money.
64, 128,000, 45,000, 36. Oh wow. Look at that. 433 grand.
Okay, now let's go see how the halfback is doing. Also, uh, 25 minutes ago or so,
Great Canadian Fuck Club gave, uh, I think eight community subs here.
Thank you, Great Canadian. Lifestyle. Girlfriends. Tarot. Okay, you can go get
almost any type of juice at discounted rates. Do I even have any sponsors anymore?
I guess so. All right, let's go to injuries. Six games. One game. The whole,
good, that's, that's fine. Here's a problem though. This is my backup halfback. This
is my main halfback. I got, I got the third replacement here. I got the second backup
in the game. That's not good. All those halfback plays I'm gonna have to slow down on.
What do you think? Hands maybe? Block? Yeah, we need better blocks. Either that or better
break tackle. Resist injury. That's another good one. Yeah, it's important. And then block.
53 grand. Let's take a look at juicing. What have we got? Team risk is still pretty damn
high. Just take the ones that you know. Hey, look, this guy like Baxter. It's legal. Don't
worry. So 4-0. Wins to advance one. So I just have to win one more game. And I'm guaranteed
to be able to play to advance. 4-0. Chicago Marauders are the next team.
So there's three more games. I just got to win one more of these games. Shouldn't be too big
of a problem. Let's go. Defense got better. No, no, that's, oh, that's us. No, no, no,
I'm 4-0. I still got a better team. More than 23 points. I'll put 10 grand on it. I already
played, I think, the best team in the division. Max bet? Sure. We're taking on the Chicago Marauder.
Quarterback Shane Spade is a gladiator in the Windy City. 18 years in the league and still
battling. Spade may not scramble like he used to. Just make sure you get to him before he
makes the throw. A lot of quarterbacks as captains in this division. We're gonna have
to take care of them. That guy's form is really bad. Yeah, that guy has the same amount of
skill and form that I do when I go to the driving range. How many guys play golf?
How many guys don't play golf and just go and swing away at the driving range?
I used to all the time. It was so much fun. The division two campaign is well underway
and most people around this team are feeling good about their chances going forward. And
now let's get ready for the kickoff. I haven't in a long time. Nobody plays golf with it,
but people still go to the range. And please. Thank you, Sans. Already chanting bullshit.
That was the kickoff return. Fuck. That's good, good, good, good, good. No, no, no.
They got a break. Be back in like two plays. Four plays. Always goes for the ass.
Crucial series of downs here. Ball at the 17 yard line.
Guys, can somebody tackle him? That was almost the whole team. Blitz is my guy.
Shit. It's okay. Whole team can stop one guy. Usually how it works, right? Max bet. Don't
worry. Shit. All right. I got the ball. He definitely is not going to remember.
We're going to go disaster and right in the middle. No, what?
What are you doing? Why? Not good. This is not good.
Well, this is not good. Whose head is this? I bumped my head on him and he broke it.
And he's still up. Oh my God. Why? What the fuck? Why are they so good? They're
on a bunch of drugs. They have to be. Well, I don't have my good halfback.
Okay. I keep forgetting. Don't do any plays that require the halfback to run.
That is the second replacement halfback. Why would I do that?
So if I don't have any halfbacks, who is the halfback? All right. Come on. No.
That's why I was hugging the right side.
Okay. First down. Guards to go. Here we go. I can come back. Just play smart.
Don't do anything fancy. Just do smart plays. I wish I wasn't so hung over.
I'm going to drag across. Let's see if we can get the guy across. Bingo. Got it.
Just fucking play smart. I just got to get a few more yards. Third and nine.
Fuck it. Down. Down yourself. Down yourself. Slowly but surely. End of the quarter.
And that's the end of the first quarter as Chicago leads by 13. He's getting nervous.
Yeah. When you're down by 13, you've got to... Of course I'm going to be nervous.
Let's go with lightning. First and 30. Sir, don't let him catch that.
Let's try this one. Why? That could have been a big play if the ball would have gotten
to him before the defender. Fucking halfback. No. I can't do any halfback plays. He's so bad.
Get out of my life. Oh. Beer truck. Right? I don't know. How's the halfback going to
get better if you don't use him? He's not supposed to be in the game.
I need this. Get up. Fuck. Get a fumble. Look at how hurt he is. Fumble. Strip it.
This guy's at 48%. How the hell are you holding onto the ball?
48%. And he got unleashed. Nobody can hold onto that. I'm not sure there's anybody on Earth.
Who got the ball at the... Thank you. Somebody came across and made it happen.
Third and 19. I'm going to just lock it down. I'm going to hang out back here.
They're gonna punt it. See what... I can't late hit him. Punt. Although Bryant's not looking so good.
Oh, that was embarrassing. It's okay. Let's try this one.
Wide receiver. They got a lot of... Let's go right side then. Bingo. Who gets the ball to half?
Me? Hurry up. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Nice. Power wide. Is this going to
the halfback? All right. Time to shine, halfback. Come on, Baxter. Baxter, I love you.
Okay. I'm just going to go for a tie game. The chug joke is getting old. It's not a joke.
It's just in the three seconds that I have to do that, it's the only one that I've
completely memorized. Totally. Why does it keep doing the same shit? All right. Time for an
injury. Oh. How are you back in two plays? I don't know how that's possible, but okay.
Shattered bones. Where are you going? Where are you going? Give me a touchdown right now.
Oh, get out of my fucking face. No, why did you run outside? Oh, I'm so annoyed by that.
Why did you go outside? Unbelievable. That sucks. He drop kicked him in the face and
ended up running outside on his own. I didn't do that because I did the drop kick.
I'm very, very upset about that. Fucking asshole. Oh, damn it. The game hates me.
I had an opportunity to be up and now like a fucking interception
because I kicked a guy in the face and jumped out of bounds.
Fuck you. Recovered from a broken forearm. There's a lot of drugs involved guys.
I thought I had it. You don't catch that. It's impossible. You're both are putting your
hands in the air. Stop it. Block this. We got a game now. It's been a while. It's
been at least two or three games since we've had a game. Oh, their defense is so good for
some reason. And they have a fucking unleashed. I gotta watch this shit. Oops, a daisy is bad.
Fucking Sullivan has to be hurt again. Just fucking
on that plate. It's so stupid. I don't deserve it, but I'll take it. That's fine with me.
You know, I talked a lot of shit about Baxter, but he really is the only person
that's what's the, what is the code? Triangle, three triangles in one X,
triangle square XO, triangle square XO, triangle square XO. That's what somebody said.
One guy did say that. You're right. Triangle square XO.
Is that the joke that it's stuck to me? We got a game. The touchdown codes are in the menu.
Yeah, I only have four of them. I don't think you can do any of them unless they're here
because we tried them before. Beer Chug really is the best one of these four.
There's only four codes. You have to unlock them. That's what I figured.
Looks like it's gonna be Beer Chug. Don't hurt him. Not good. Drop that ball.
Bumble. Oh, I'm sorry.
And ruin that guy's life. Well, we're in Blitz. We're in the Blitz League.
Just give me one second here.
At least he's going for a few games instead of a few plays. Yeah, that's true.
Was it third down? Second down. Second to 17. Not gonna happen. Third down.
Got an unleash. I'm gonna hold on to it. It's 20-20. Stay. Let's go. Just deep zones.
Quarterback passes all the damn time. Just gonna block it.
I can't fucking believe that just happens. What happened here?
I was ready for him right here. Okay, here's the chain of events here.
This guy doesn't tackle. Instead, I come across with franchise. Try to do the tackle. Don't
get it. This guy tackles franchise. And that guy fell down because I grabbed his toe. Great.
Good work, guys. As we reach the end of the third quarter, we're tied.
I don't want to use the unleash, though. Make him kick a field goal and then I can
use the unleash to get a touchdown. Don't let him get it. No unleash. Not necessary. Don't do it.
Use unleash to defend? I don't think I need to right now. See you later. That's the
quarterback. Oh, Brake is back. Best thing that could have happened. Get their backup quarterback
in here. Fourth goal. They're going for a field goal? I don't know. What are they doing?
They're going for a field goal. Block it. Don't go. No go. No good. No, it wasn't.
It bounced off the middle. What? Oh, it bounced in. Touchdown wins the game. All right.
I got a false set of downs here to get at least a field goal.
Rip the bet. Yeah, that's all right. I need to win the game. How many yards is that?
Eight? Not very much. Wide open. Why would you jump and land on your back?
What did you do that for? Why would you do that? Catch it and turn around. I don't need
to use time up, but I panicked. I just did. I gotta play defense. That should be the game.
Field goal won't win it. Don't get this blocked. Defense. They have no unleash.
Play smart. You gotta be fucking kidding me. You've gotta be kidding me. No, somebody get him.
Oh, I can't believe it. It's a fake. Okay. All right. All right. 27 great. I need a field goal.
Field goal is all I need. Just get there. No, run it back for a fucking touchdown right now.
Get into field goal range. Am I field goal range? I'm so fucked. My heart is just
pounding right now. What the hell? I have one time out. Oh, come on. I'm just panicking.
I gotta kick a field goal. Fuck. How far am I away? I'm fucked.
I shouldn't have lost that fucking game. The run back for a touchdown just gets slippery
bullshit. I make like two tackles and he just bribes it. Fuck off. All right. I'm
nine and two right now, agent. I'm so mad right now. Fucking hell. Miami Hammerheads. I'm so
unreasonably upset. Yeah. All right. Injuries. Finally, I get my halfback who is one of the best
halfbacks in the league and he's in the game. I wonder if I'll have him for one game and then
he'll break a bone and be gone for two games. Baxter is great. Don't fuck Baxter. Go back
to experimenting on flies and the Ninja Turtles. I don't think it can do anything. 2-11. No,
fuck you, Gerva. No, I'm kidding. Baxter was the only one that did anything, but I can't
believe they ran it back for a touchdown. I can't believe it. All I had to do is just
tackle and they broke every tackle. Why is the team risk always so high?
Screw it. Ball carrier gets a clash icon for every 30 yards gained in a play.
That's actually kind of insane. I don't give a shit. Send me to jail.
Miami Hammerheads. They're a good team too. Same record. That was such a hard one to swallow.
It's all right. I'm still one of the best teams in the league. Miami Hammerheads. Let's
go. The Hammerheads used to be a team going nowhere. Now they're on everyone's radar. Their
fortunes change when they move from Orlando to Miami and the biggest salary in the league
and his precision guided attack is worth that. He's so expensive they can't afford
to repair the hurricane damage to the stadium. Why are they dropping? When he's not bombing
defenses through the air, he's burning them up. Look at the stadium. He's too much money.
So they can't repair the stadium. That's really fucking ridiculous. The stadium is
in complete disarray and they don't have the money to repair it.
Bad in the trenches and they have a good spread offense. Good evening and welcome.
Gotta hold Williams down to 200 yards. Good luck. It's all right. We're in the home game.
Started off good. That's a good fucking way to start it I would say. With a touchdown.
With a touchdown I would say. With a touchdown I would say. No. Got the half back as well.
It's gut check time. It's all right. Asshole. Let's go with the bolt. Tight end bolt. Nice job.
Nice job Schloser or whatever his name is. First touchdown of the game.
We said 5,000 bits just came in. 50 bucks from La Cranda. Thank you La Cranda for the 50,
5, 0, 0, 0, 5,000 bits. And you say, what do you say? Let's see. Hey Jeremy,
it's clear what you have to do. Just run the ball all the way to the right and get
a touchdown. It's just that easy. You mean like this guy's doing right now.
Except he's going left. Thank you so much La Cranda. It's a lot of money.
And I already got an unleashed. Let's see if we can get a fumble right now.
Let's just go with the all out blitz. We're talking like literal all out just blitz.
Everybody on the team. Get everyone over here. Choke slam. Oh that was really cool.
Like I didn't drop it. They got a long way to go. Let's just do some
kind of a waste of a little unleash unfortunately. What are you throwing?
Asshole. I didn't have a meter. I burnt the meter.
What the hell were you doing? I got absolutely, I got a second and goal.
No meter at all. I'm going to get a dirty hit. I thought he was going to throw it.
I was waiting for it. Let's uh bomb edge it. Nothing. Fourth down. Good luck.
Get a field goal dude. Hold them to a field goal. I'll be happy.
These super bowlers sure are good.
What are they chanting? Are they saying Yankees suck?
Why would they be doing that? Who's injured? Shoulder dislocation.
Oh, slippery hands. Slippery. He's gone. It's all right. Slippery fucking fingers. It's okay.
It's like quadruple coverage. He's still gone.
Let's do a run this way with the halfback.
I juked that one. Minecraft Steve. It is kind of Minecraft Steve.
Yeah that was a good, that was a good play. See this is why we need Sullivan.
Because if that was Baxter, he probably would have fallen down.
Baxter doesn't make that play. We don't get that touchdown. Fumble. Yep.
Oh this is good. Did I max bet? I don't think I max bet. Did I?
Touchdown. Just right up the middle. Just jump over the edge.
Did I bet though? I don't remember.
I didn't bet at all. Oh well. Don't get comfortable though. This team is really good.
It's like the only other four-in-one team in the league.
See you. On leash is back. Good. Standard cover play. I think that sounds good for me.
He's going to throw it. No he's not. Oh unbelievable. Unbelievable. Same thing. Do it again.
See ya. All right. Play smart. That's all I gotta do. This will take me to the championship.
Miami sucks. But they don't. They're four-in-one just like me. Just getting good turnovers.
And yeah we have Sullivan. It's a completely different team like somebody just said.
This is one of the best players on the team and in the league. And they've been absent.
If Sullivan is on the team we win by 40 points. That's just how it works.
I'm on easy difficulty. I don't think. Is there even a difficulty slider in this game?
I don't think there is. I haven't used it. This is just the campaign.
Yeah it's on easy. What? There is. There is no difficulty. Easy. Turn the music on. I can't.
The whole stream will be muted. It is just constant 100% copyright and music the whole game.
So no one will be able to watch this vlog. That's fourth down. And they got two seconds.
Five seconds. They're gonna. You have to go for it. Right? Yeah. Get back here. Oh!
He's gonna make it. He made it. Oh why did I let that happen? It's because I. Punt.
Why did I do punt return? Oh my fucking god. Punt return. Great job. Yeah it's. There's
like five seconds fucking left. And so at halftime Las Vegas leads by 17.
It's okay. Fuck me. Why do I always let the most bogus shit happen?
With five seconds left I'm gonna run the whole field. Just fucking kill this guy.
First down 30 yards to go. Sheep pass and it's caught at the three and they bring him down.
Like I will beat this guy in a football match. But you give somebody a chance to like
fucking throw up down the field and like run by everybody with two seconds left it'll happen every
time. It was like fucking quadruple cover. Nobody got that. I don't have a meter either.
All right. That's why I said it can't get comfortable to four in one team. Let's go.
Can't get comfy. Play smart. See? Just playing. Don't go in for anything crazy.
Fucking murdering. I'm trying to play smart. I'm trying to build meter. Fourth down. See?
They didn't get shit. Now are you gonna go for it? Right now. They are. They're going for it on
fourth down. Turnover on downs. Exactly what I needed to have happen. Let's just go with
some short passes. NV coach. What's wrong with the Nevada coach? That was a little bit of
game. Just a little bit. I'm gonna run it. I'm gonna get the half back situation right here.
Float left. I got a little bit of meter. Let's go. Right up the middle. Straight through. Just
run. QB dash. Just walk over the line. Don't want to get tackled though. All it takes
is a broken skull and I have to delete the game. Really? All right. I gotta unleash this.
I'm going for an actual unleash. Oh no!
Turbo boomer activated. What does that mean? Look at me! Now I can relax. I'm up by way too
much. Las Vegas refuses to call off the dogs as they add to their lead. Insult. Let's insult
them. 43-11. Where was this yesterday? And by yesterday I mean in the video game. I couldn't
do anything. Couldn't get a fumble. Couldn't get a turnover. Good thing there's no injury
there. What difficulty am I playing on? There is no difficulty. I don't know. Normal? Regular?
Watch this. I just want everyone to be aware of this. One, two, three, four people here. And he
we synchronized swam and he caught the ball. Punch somebody. Swam? A word? Yeah. Swam. I swam
there. You didn't. You swam. That's word. I swam. I swam. I swam. I swam. What is it? Swan?
I swam. I swam there. No it's not swum. It's swam. Swimmed? Now you're just fucking around.
Okay. No. I got. Let's burn the clock. He's now over the 100 yard mark. Swimmed. Swum.
Anybody that joins the stream right now and looks at chat are probably going to be like,
is this like a funny in-joke that this guy has in the stream?
Injury. Nope.
That's a pretty good point.
It's pretty much what we just heard. Smart announcer.
Okay. John Fadden is a BF. He kind of is. In a way. That's not a safety.
All right. This is the opportunity. We're going to hurt someone. Just go full. I don't
even care if they score a touchdown. Who cares? We're going to go special teams and field goal
block. Got it. That's it. I'll take the ball. Well that's a good
achievement for that somehow. Oh well. 45-17. I'll take the win. Now we qualify for the division
two championship. Moving on to the championship game. I don't think he got 200 yards did he?
Should have wagered. Safety dance. New trophy. Half of the second Super Bowl.
Division two Super Bowl. Well not yet. There's still one more game in the division.
If you want I can arrange to have them party with ace's captain Amos Newell.
Maybe wear him out before the game. It's going to cost but you know I got it.
Just let me know. Sabotaging the other team? Yeah. I think so. That's a good idea. Do it.
National ad campaign. So what does that mean? Play next game at Las Vegas Aces.
So with the Las Vegas Aces versus the Las Vegas Super Bowls. Who's the real Vegas team?
I was going to name my team the Las Vegas Aces. You remember? It was going to be the Las Vegas
Aces versus the Las Vegas Aces. That's too bad. So we'll find out who the best team in Vegas is.
But first. Okay let's go to upgrades. Agility. Get everything to two. Agility. Juicing. Mr.
Super Bowl. We're going to give you something good. Successful clash moves drain clash from
opponent's clash bar. That's pretty good. Regenerate two stamina each player on the
field. He's on every play. Let's give Sullivan something. Turbobar drains 50% slower. Yeah I
think so. Somebody on defense too. J. Cruz. Give you something easy. Training is fine.
Everything looks all right. All right. Here we go. Las Vegas Aces versus the Las Vegas
Super Bowls. Good luck. They're not a bad team. I do have to max bet on the Las Vegas
game though. Why wouldn't I do that? Five and one. Three and three. They're not a bad team.
Let's go. Las Vegas Aces and the new home of Amos Newell. Linebacker. Okay. Where are we
playing? We playing in my Vegas stadium or their Vegas stadium? Both at the same time.
You share one. That's a cool logo. Good evening and welcome. Take a look at that crowd.
You can see who they really support in that audience. We're on their home turf and they are
wearing my colors. Look at that. People's champion is right here. Absolutely. That's not
good. That's a fumble. No it's not. If it's Las Vegas versus Las Vegas who is it in a way
game for? First and 30. I don't know. Apparently me. Damn it. Fumble out of bounds. All right.
Take it seriously. This is a good team. Even though I already clinched the playoffs. It's
fine. No balance. Balance deep. Third and seven. How much time are you going to give them?
Oh boy. Bullshit. Let's do a trick play here. Maniac. I couldn't get rid of it. He's
going in a circle. I tricked myself. Third and 33 is long. Holy fucking triangle.
See you later. Sullivan's got it. Touchdown. He extended that reception all the way into
the end zone. Nice yards after the catch. This is the last game of the season.
This is just a fun game because it doesn't matter if I win or lose.
I already clinched the playoffs. That would have been embarrassing. It's all good.
$25,000 bet. I needed to win by, what was it? 17? 18? Let's go for the head. Drop of the ball.
Wide receiver. That's pretty good. This is the championship. What is this though?
This might be the local championship. It's Vegas Vegas. I couldn't go anywhere.
It's the Vegas bowl. Two Vegas teams in the same division. Hold them here. Should be able
to do it. That was a trick play. Franchise performs 30 or more dirty hits. What was that?
I didn't see what that said. And that's the end of the first quarter as Las Vegas leads by seven.
But which Las Vegas? Fourth and 16. They're gonna punt it. I gotta stop jumping. If you
jump in the area and get tackled, you have a much higher percentage chance to get hurt
or drop the ball. And though it does work sometimes. You've seen me jump over tackles
before. Who is it? Drop it. Give me this back. That sucks. Broken humors. Here we go again.
I get the ball at the half. So they do all these weird. What the fuck was that?
Why did he just fall on his back? Whatever. I got meter. I'll probably use it.
Goodbye. Quarterback is gone. Two plays. What have I happened to like the skull contusions?
Second pick off. Really? Is this a wrestling game? It's whatever you want it to be.
You have to stop aiming for their ass. It's just so easy to do that though.
Fuck it. Let's go. Thought I could push him. Cut across. God damn it.
I get the ball in 13 seconds. So here's what we're gonna do.
I could have kicked the field but I wanted to. Look this game doesn't matter. I can just do
whatever I want. That's a touchdown. Thanks. Okay we're good. 86 yard return. Let's just get in
their red zone. Power wide. Another leash. I'm just gonna kick the field goal. I did bet too
right? I did a max bet. We gotta get that money. Let Baxter play. Can you even do
substitutions in this game? I don't think you can. If I go up by 30 points then he'll come in.
Cooler guy. Out for one play. This guy is made out of clay. That's it he's back.
Welcome back. Zack. No there he is. No he had a concussion already didn't he?
I'm so confused. Oh and his throwing arm too. Two three plays. I'm making a lot of good
injury plays and they're not really doing very much. Whoops a daisy. This is my opportunity to
get the money. I hate when that happens. It's so stupid. Seriously when it bounces off the
fucking ground. I need to win by 17 points. Who was it? Broken ribs. Oh Mims is good.
Two plays good. Out for 200 games. Get in there. I think I'm going for a QB.
First and goal. It's gut check. Walk across the line. Three two one go.
Seriously. Do it again. Three two one go. Las Vegas widens the gap. Somebody just wrote stop.
Another unleash meter and I'm up by 17. Triangle square x circle.
I don't think any of the other codes work because I have to unlock them.
Right in his neck. His chest. What is this going to be? Four games.
Zynar. Las Vegas needs to do something here to get their offense in motion.
He's going long and it's complete at the 45 yard line.
Saw something in the defense and jumped out of the big game. Sets them up in nice field
position and so with three quarters gone leads by 22. Collar bones are made out of dry
spaghetti and it might be second best chat comment of the night behind Taco Bell.
I got baited into tackling the wrong guy. It makes the same noise too.
If you take a handful of like angel hair pasta and crush it it'll sound like that.
Looks like they'll have four more downs to work with. The offense is looking good.
They're driving. It's the coach's favorite place on the field. The red zone.
Tackleman coming one two three. I gotta get another touchdown now to get that money.
They're going for it. Good go for it. That means nope they ain't gonna get it. So that's
six. I need to get a field goal. And it looks like they'll try an onside kick here.
Um why are you so bad at this game? I'm nine and two. What? No not the same guy. Holy shit.
They just like squished me. No no. Same guy.
They just put me in a vice and crushed my body. Thank god I picked it up so I can get
the point. He's going for eight games. Don't stumble like that.
28. That's plenty. Just uh just try to be who cares. Rub it in.
That's two dead players for the Super Bowlers now. Late hit. Mims is gonna have to retire
after this one. Yeah there's a lot of broken bones. A lot of shattered spleens unfortunately.
Watch this. Jade's got 84. I've had it. Always go for the head every time.
Oh that hurts. I've been knocking him up for like one to two plays this whole game.
I love this game. The noises, the sounds, the close-ups.
Watch this. This guy's dead. Get up. Go ahead. I was hoping for something devastating there.
Hey that's me. Now you try to tell me in the easiest possible language here.
How did he not go down from that? That's the worst one. What happened? Right here. Guy on
the left. I haven't selected. Crush right into his body. No. I need one point. I need one
point. Just get close enough. First down and 30. No not 28. Thank goodness.
Oh every time. Good. Use your timeouts. I'm okay with that. Okay almost there.
Who needs that when you just get a fucking touchdown right?
Franchise finds the end zone once again.
Okay now do not let them score. Let them go. Let them run for five seconds. Larsen this
is up to you. I want this to be over now. Shit they get one play. I'm going all the way back
here. I'll be ready for him. Who do we even do that to? And I got the bet.
Pretty good. That was a $25,000 bet. Time for the division two championship. New sponsor,
the enforcer. Dura shock gloves. Cool. League MVP. How am I not the MVP?
How many touchdowns do I have? I have like 60 touchdowns.
I told them. Hey hold that thought. This is my boy. Franchise. One game buddy. One more
and it's division one. The big time. You get this done and we're gonna have a license to
print money. Okay here comes the D2 championship. Tara wants to hang out.
Rough boy. Already fighting for a spot in division one.
Just remember what you've got waiting for you if you make it.
Okay. Hey Franch, can you believe it? The sponsor decided to take a pass on you and
went with grace for their ad campaign. Don't take it too hard buddy. She's only the hottest
athlete turned supermodel. I just hung up on him. Hey it's me. Man I gotta tell you every
time you lay a dirty hit on some stupid SOB it's pure money and you've gotten 30 of them
already this season. That caught the attention of our new sponsor who by the way is sending
some sweet new gear to your team's clubhouse as we speak. Okay let's take one. Sponsor
let's see. New gloves all right. Plus six hands. That's really really good actually.
What's going on with the girlfriend front here? Okay injuries. Who is it? Seven. Gonna
have to give a game crashed. Please tell me it's saved. Did you crash or are you
just having a little slow down period here? I think it autosaves so we might have to listen
to those phone calls again. Okay well let's reset it. Let me just let's try again.
Maybe I clicked too fast. What does that mean? No we're good. Sort of weird but
whatever. Is it yellow? No no it's not yellow. Odd. Hopefully it saved the game.
Now that means it's an actual full-on crash if it's yellow. No I think it was just a disk
read problem. Just kind of ran into itself. Let's see if that worked. That's not the correct
image. Yeah that we definitely saw that so it should be fine. Powered by GameSpy. They
don't exist anymore. It's been a while since they've existed. Is Jerma old enough to be
playing this? No. All right wait a minute. Let me see. X trees. Touchdown codes. Here we go.
How do I unlock them? Yeah I can't do any of these. These have to be unlocked. So it's
either beer chug or ball spike knockout. Continue. Select yeah Super Bowls. Hopefully
if we don't do the last game again. There we go. Okay good.
Hey it's me. Man I got. Okay so I went here to the trainer to go to injuries and we had a problem.
I want to assign staff here. There we go. Everybody for the ruptured spleen. Let's go
to upgrades. Passing is definitely everything will be at two. If we can work from there.
I'm gonna do probably tackle and break tackle after this. Points automatically.
Risk is high. So just do the legal one. Let's get on some defense to uh J. Cruz.
Let's get Sullivan some of this as well. All right so this is the this is the championship
for with the Miami Hammerheads. I think I'll get a piss first. It's been it's been a
bi-quarterly two hours. So it's time for me to pee one more time. I'm not like drinking
anymore coffee so don't worry. Be right back. Championship game. What do you say?
Oh did I beat this team last time? Overall they're a little better. Not really though.
They have a better offense. Great Canadian Fuck Club. Thanks for five community subs
on top of the nearly 10 that you gave earlier. Thank you so much for the super subs. That's a
lot. I'm not betting. Let's go. D2 championship. Jeremy you may win the Super Bowl but have you
won six? I have not. I have not won the Super Bowl that many times. Good evening ever. It's
the Division 2 championship and we are rearing. There we go. I mean there's a lot of places I
could be but I mean this is gonna be unbelievable. Light and a thunder and lightning storm too.
Right off the bat. That was a good hit. When he does that John Madden impression it just
sounds like he's about to burp the whole time he's talking. He's fighting back burps.
It's an opportunity. Really? That was just he did a really great job there.
Second down and about a mile. No first down. Your offense is the best part.
I gotta play better defense. The quarterback is really good. Injure the quarterback.
No! We're good. Who is it? 41. Dupree. It's all right. Two plays. He intercepted that play.
Not with his hands. That's right. First down. 30 yards to go. Capitalize on an
intercepted. It's a championship game for god's sakes. Don't throw it into triple coverage.
Oh my god. I haven't unleashed. Go for the quarterback.
If I can get that quarterback here. I would have had it too. This is bad.
God damn it. I would have had it too. I was a tenth of a second late on the sack. I thought I
could get it. Interception into an interception. I picked the play. Let's go. I have to be careful
because he has it unleashed. He could strip the ball from me right now if he really wanted to.
Great blocking. Okay. Get it to Sullivan.
Fuck. I can't get anything going. I'm trying to activate the
unleashed but they keep denying it. Right over him. That should be a touchdown.
There it is. Don't just score. Score, score, score. He landed on his keys.
I've been caught on TV doing the most moves I'd like to have. You know,
head fake your dance partner one way and then juke him the next and then bam.
Yeah, I wasn't going to taunt. Sat it against him. Brand new ball game.
How did you miss that one? Sir, honest to god. How did I miss the first one?
How is it even, whatever. I'm fine. And I just did a goal line play.
There it is. I got it all back. I'm getting killed though on every category.
Second and 40. They got a long way to go. It's not far enough. Same deal. Third and 31.
They're in field goal range though I think. There it is. Hold them to field goal.
My computer just blue screened after that Madden joke. I'm sorry to hear that.
By the way, I'm doing a punt return. He's gonna miss it.
It's alright. Everything's good. I might be able to get a touchdown here if I play
the cards right. You can't. Come on. Hammer through that.
Looking for a first down here. That was good. Electrocute his brain.
Get him out of the game for now. It didn't even do much for me either.
That guy was right in front of me. Where are my blockers? Second and 18.
Oh god. This is bad. Third down. Back spasms. You should be back in like one play.
Four plays.
Can I get it? Got it. That guy was just barely about to not be open. I got really lucky there.
Unleash the scare and the shit out of me.
Almost halftime. Yeah. Coming up. I got him. I have to score at least once here.
Get a close enough for a field goal. It's hard to aim this.
Fucking god damn it. It's so hard to do that with the analog.
The analog is so sloppy. You have no idea how difficult that is to move that.
You can't. It moves so much. Trust me when I say that. That's not easy to do that.
No timeouts. I gotta get another fucking field goal. Another one right here. Debris.
Miss it. Of course they can do it perfect. AI's gonna do it fucking perfect every time.
Ah fuck. At least I get the ball.
The AI's not blaming its controller. No aiming with a field goal. Go get this game and do it
and we'll have a discussion about it. My defense is so good.
Very fucking down. Get across. Bingo. Right there. Just run it in.
We got good meter.
Almost there. Just walk it in. You know my favorite play.
Hey I got it. All that matters is the art.
Yeah I crossed the plane. We crossed the plane. We're good. Meter. See if I can get a fumble.
Where are we? Goal line. Balanced. Crush. No. Balanced. Safe to push. No dog shit.
It's a close game. It's gonna stay that way. And that was my tackle when I was supposed to
get him. He snuck right through and got like 10 yards. No field goal. No more game. No first
down. Thank you very much. I'll take it. Yes. It took too long to throw it.
Before you know it those kids are in the grind. What the hell is he talking about?
Almost. Fourth quarter. Division two championship. I am focused. I'm alert and I'm ready.
Second and 24. Let's try to get a quick pass over here on the left. How could you let that
happen? Yes.
21-13. He needs a touchdown and a two-point conversion. Or it's over. And I win the
goddamn championship. No bullshit. No bogus plays where he runs back the whole thing.
First down and 30. I can try to strip it. That's perfect. That's exactly what I needed right now.
That's two interceptions. Las Vegas leads by eight. Who is that? No not Sullivan again.
No this is the championship game. I can't lose him for like five games again. Okay don't
blow this. He'll come back in like three plays. One play. Thank god. That would have
been the whole game probably if I fucked that up. Nice. Can't let them catch their breath. I say
we test the corner. Second and goal. Hold it. Hold it. Hold it. Going for my favorite play
right in the middle. Just sneak it in. Third and goal. That's how you get hurt but it's okay.
28-13. Just round the clock. They made all these sound effects with him mouth.
That'd be actually pretty ridiculous. It'd be 31 if I made that field goal. We don't need it
though. First down 30 yards to go. I made up for the fact that we don't need that field goal.
Powerball. That goes to their quarterback. Brew's kidney. Out for three plays and that's
going to be the three plays that you need the most. So you definitely lost.
Try to do. Let's hurt this guy too. No ball explosion. We've seen it like three or four
times tonight though. Third and short for this offense. Damn it. It's all right. Let him have
one. And he's in the end zone. I'm just going to run the clock out and the game's going
to end. It's the very end of the game. It's all right. Nice. What do we want to do here?
Just run. Burn the timeouts. Oh my fucking god. It's okay. It's going to be for like
the whole season. Seven games but there's no more games to play. Don't just injure my whole
team and make this fucking whole thing. Oh Jesus Christ. You didn't even aim. You aimed for the
head. That's half back half back. How many half backs do I have? Why do you guys have to share
the same problem? Who's the half back now? Just give it to them. Who the fuck is this? Peter?
Fuck. It's fourth down. Am I in field goal range? Am I about to fucking have a meltdown?
All right. What was wrong with that? What was wrong with that?
This is not good. All they need is a touchdown and they're not going to get it.
Yes. Dead. That was Williams. That was the star quarterback.
That should seal the deal right there. Now just play prevention. Just play smart.
This quarterback sucks. Oh my fucking god.
Not this time. Same deal. Just man. Just prevent. Just cover everything. Just stay out.
Last play of the game.
Fuck you game over. I win championship. Division two championship.
More touchdowns. I unlocked everything. Moving on to D1. LT session. Loader. Silver.
New touchdown code. Circle XX circle is pylon kick. Finally took long enough. It took
six and a half hours for me to get a new one. More than that.
Uh oh. Here comes the scumbag.
Oh shit. Here it comes.
The LA Riot.
Oh wow. Is that what we just won? We just won the championship. That doesn't make any sense.
They didn't win the championship. What's up Carl?
Oh yes.
Yes. Absolutely. The draft. There it is. We get to pick a new player.
Remember this guy from prison? Right defensive end. Look at this. No this is it. I just can
either accept him or not accept him. Look at that speed agility. I just get him. A hundred
resist injury. He's never gonna get hurt. Yeah. I can't select anybody else right? There's no
other options. It's just this. Let's go.
200 plus combined yards. All right here we're in D1. Just to make sure everyone's in the right
spot. Quarterback. That's me. Halfback got Sullivan. Ashford sure has kind of climbed
the rankings here. A minus. A plus punter. Whenever you have to use him. Let's take a
look. Cruz and Tirpitz. This is a pretty great team. I'm happy about it. Mexico City
Aztecs is the next team. Let's see what I got. Plus six hands plus two speed.
Okay I don't have enough money to do anything. I don't think so at least. No. Resist injury.
Yeah massage therapy that's maxed out now. All right let's go.
Well that is a create a character cheat team. Good luck. I'm not betting any money here.
We're gonna get our asses kicked. We're gonna lose real bad. That's the spirit. This is D1.
Tight end. I gotta win five games. And thanks for joining us. 200 plus combined yards this game.
The heat is a factor. You see the uh the waves there.
No he made it here on time. Corner look. First down 30 yards to go. That haze.
26 yard line. I wonder how that affects. Heat is a factor in Mexico but not in Las Vegas.
Yeah I'm not sure how. I'm gonna go with go with a good pass here.
I might just sneak over. What the hell was that? Damn it. I thought I could sneak over there.
Out of my way. The dive seems to work a lot for me.
Cut across. Cut across. Cut across. Thank you.
That's a beautiful juke from Sullivan. What's it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it?
Wow that was fast. I think he broke the sound barrier. Well you know that's like at the
air show where they fly by and they're already gone before the sound of them hits your ears.
You ever see that? Well it wasn't that fast but but for not having wings or a jet engine
What a great unlockable that was. He just kicks the pylon. Stay him. So now with their possession
you've got to be aware of a guy who has a tight end right. He shed this guy
nearly exactly what he's doing here. Wait no no. I just don't want to do him in the ass.
I want to do it in the back. I would have I would have broken his spine. I tried to do it
and it just looked out. First down and third. Number 81. Watch 81. D1 is gonna be hell.
Miraculously still hands on. That's the end of the first quarter as Las Vegas leads by seven.
Blitz him. I see what you're doing. How the hell did you. I got tricked.
He tricked me. I thought it was gonna be a handoff run.
Oh that's all right. Tie game. Who kicked the ball?
You want to get tricked? Fine. I'm gonna do a snowflake. I don't even know what this does.
Um I didn't even do that. He ran to the left on his own.
Oh this sucks.
I blame snowflake. That's what I blame for real.
And how. Excuse me gentlemen. How do you not catch that? It was right to you. It was right
to you. I blocked 81. I took him out and the ball was thrown right to your hands. Fumble.
Thank you.
Let's try it wrong. First and 30. That's not good. Oh that's not good.
Sullivan again. Beru's kidney. Get a good injection. He should be fine in about three plays.
I don't want to hurt you with this needle. Good enough.
Oh hey hey. Why aren't they showing the announcer's face?
They're all over. Probably extra money. Second to 25. Yes. Oh first down.
Las Vegas had everyone on the same page there and they are rewarded with a very nice game.
The offense is going to get the ball and he's going to get off. He's going to get his
t-bone shattered. Whatever the hell that is.
So we've managed to run for like uh hmm. Dragon downfield player. Good. You good to go?
With under a minute to play in the half we're all tied up. Is it third and 15?
Whoa is it possible we're making progress? While we're at it let's try scoring.
Gotta make something happen.
And it's incomplete.
Fuck it. It's goddamn division one. You gotta make plays. Exactly what I'm talking about.
He has the same five lines. John Madden too has the same five lines. Now I know why somebody
said can you please mute him. I was like what are they talking about? Now I get it.
First down. Three yards to go. I'll buy a touchdown.
Mexico City with a nice game there thanks to some key downfield blocks.
Uh I blew that one. That was actually botched. Um how did you still throw it?
Touchdown. Mexico City. If that's me as the quarterback how do you throw that perfect throw?
Okay. Let's watch. So he gets fucking tackled and then underhand throws the ball perfectly
with the guy downfield. It is six points. I don't understand. I almost had it. The extra
point is good and once again we're all even. It's D1. Goddamn D1. Not gonna win that one.
Let's give Snowflake another chance. I'm never doing that play ever again.
There's a guy who's in pain from a big hit. How do you know? I don't see him crying or
anything but that's probably because he's crying on the inside. That's the kind of guy he is.
And after the game the trainers got to open him up blow dry his spleen or something like that.
I went the wrong way. The computer had control.
When he gets the ball he runs to the left. I don't have control of the game.
He takes control and runs left and then gets tackled by the same guy every time.
I have not had control of the character every time I've done that play.
Runs to the left and gets tackled. Always going for the guys like balls.
Do a balanced D I think. I saw that one coming from by the way in 26. I was waiting for you.
Although they're pretty close though. Third and seven. Incomplete pass. Here we go and then
they're gonna kick it. That was fucking brutal. That was brutal and we got the ball and it's
a touchdown. Has to be. Six plays. Has the best possible scenario here. I'm gonna say
clear. I don't even know what play it is. It's gut check time. That's stupid.
I really like this play. The corner look. Watch that unleashed. Here comes not 28 please.
Not no not Sullivan. No he's going forever. Ruptured scrotum. Five games. I need him in the
game right now. That's not good. This is bad. Okay it's an easy kick. Perfect right?
That almost didn't go through.
I know I'm supposed to wear them. I'm expected to wear them but something keeps telling me not
to trust them. Good night. Broken column. You gotta be up at least five games.
Got a fresh unleash. Let's kill the quarterback.
I'm going for it. I'm just blitzing. Fuck it. Fuck I thought I had it. Oh I thought I had
it. I really thought I did. If that were me out there running it would probably make people
I really thought it was gonna happen. Good job safety. Big series of downs upcoming.
I thought I had it. That was a given. It was a given that I was gonna get that.
It's beautiful. I don't got a good halfback.
First down and 30. Kane you fucking idiot. I was about to say that was great but it
wasn't. It was awful. It was just awful.
I'm so mad about that fumble because that was the turnaround of the game right there.
This isn't gonna be another one of those games or I'm gonna be down by three or four points.
How many times is that gonna happen?
Thank you. All right Dupree and that's a touchback. We'll see if their defense can hold.
No it's okay. That's okay. There's been a guy that's been intercepting the all game.
You know what fuck it. We're going with an unleash catch.
That's a guaranteed catch. Eat shit touchdown.
Las Vegas tears up a good chunk of field there and you know what I'm doing.
Thank god. What's worse this or beer chunk. I wonder. Everybody was so desperate to get a
different celebration. Now you have pylon kick. Keep giving franchise yards. Just got stuffed
and that would have been a touchdown. First and 30. Who the fuck is franchise? I don't
know who Mr. Super Bowl is. Good let him run the clock. Let him go down the field as long
as they want. It's impossible for them to get anymore and then I just got to not throw any
interceptions. Just run the ball around the clock. Game's over. First division one game complete.
This is fine. I don't care how many points you score right now.
That's a guarantee. He guaranteed it. It's fine. He used his unleash.
Doesn't matter how many points he gets. I have a ball.
How long is this gonna be? It is 20 at best. Yeah see the 44 seconds just run every play.
Don't do anything. No unleash. Don't do anything stupid. Run the ball.
And it looks like they'll try an onside kick here.
Easy. There's my halfback in the game. Okay no incompletions. Keep it between the
lines and keep the clock running. Easy right? Yeah that's what I said. First down. All right
Cox you have to really pull through here. Take the time out. And then you got your can't get
a date to the problem. You have one more time out. What do you think about it? I'm not the
best looking corsage on the lapel. So in a way you think about it it's kind of beautiful
or at least it's the kind of ugly only a mother could find. Does that make sense?
That's fine. You don't know about the damage till days or weeks later you just sit there
eating lunch all of a sudden you just start screaming. Third and now let's just call it third
in a ways. Why did where's he running? Oh excuse me. Excuse me. I did not do that.
He just started running. Why the fuck did you do that? Oh shit.
You got to be kidding me. I'm panicking. Guys they don't have any time outs. I'm about to have
an unleashed. All right there's no reason why they get the ball to the hands-off with an
unleashed. Not a single reason with me with an unleashed full meter. You don't have any more
time outs. The person that gets the ball is dead. Un-fucking-belief. They don't have any
time. It's over. Good luck. I don't know what play I'm gonna pick. Maybe I should pick.
Oh wait what? First down 30 yards to go. This is their last play.
Fuck you. That was so close. I was so scared. I had to wait to the last second because he
was doing a clash catch. That would have been so disappointing. But that's the first
game in division one complete. I only have $290,000. That's not good. Pronghorn gear
unlocked. Yeah that was just the first one. I have to win four more games
and then I get to go to the absolute complete championship.
franchise this is grace i hope you don't mind me being forward but seeing as we're working
on the same ad campaign i thought you might like to get together for drinks this evening
so see you at the club tonight each division there's a new girlfriend
terror is trying to call me nice to finally meet you in person i'll second that i hear
the commercial shoot went well that's what my agent tells me at least he returns your calls
my lame-ass agent is too distracted with his new client anyone i heard of some hot shot league
captain tyler something you play him this sunday you know football is a rough game
accidents happen even the league captains so i've heard i'd be especially grateful
if such an accident were to occur what the fuck is that lingered for a long time all right
hi tara oh trying to get yourself a little hollywood tail yeah i know about that chick
you met you think that pamper bitch can do things for you like i can good luck with that
sorry what's the new sponsor we got spider webs plus eight hands ultra light yeah pronghorn
there they are oh it's all pronghorn no no bring back the drugs well what is
no she's still wasted we're still together hey look who's injured it's sullivan again
i don't have enough money i think hands will be the next upgrade and we're doing on drugs way
too much risk i'm not doing it and i want to save money so i don't want to spend
twenty thirty thousand dollars right now uh we're just gonna have to go in the way we are
against the denver grizzlies both want to know las vegas must win by more than four
points max bet next up we got the denver grizzlies this guy tyler neal is electric
he's an undrafted walk-on no one had ever heard of well they all know him now neal's
one of the fastest runners in the league neal plays hard off the field too he's making
the most of his newfound fame hell he's earned it so take out take out fast guy
i will do my best so they have a lack of depth everybody franchise must injure tyler neal
this game here i'll try i should get it um can someone i don't know what it is with returns
kick returners i just that's how i lose half the games and by half the games i mean two we
lost two games in the whole entire franchise first down and 30 you are fast 28 too okay
this is gonna be pain i really i have to hurt him he's gonna be hell to deal with oh that was
so embarrassing whatever six points just juked me so hard sorry the extra point is good i have
to take care of that guy that guy's gonna be a thorn acid reflux you know with the heartburn
and then you know with the rest of it all that kind of max i have to win by four points
there it is the acid reflux joke hey guess who's not in the lineup and there's a problem
somebody get open someone get open i don't know who to throw it to just go
go
that was a long time but it's okay first down 30 yards to go oh it's always my half backs
we're going to back up back up half back again oh fuck oops all right where are we
it's always half back who the hell is who is it barry what's his name bartholomew what's
this guy's name oh don't have to talk to him about baxter
again and they draw even with that score gives this team a new set of downs i'm going to kick
it like in the corner oh boy he unleashed yeah i can do that too you know i can do that too
fumble do it los vegas yes and that's the end of the first quarter and we're all tied up
does somebody fall on it okay second quarter look for the guy to come across the field
there you go you're all right buddy get out there
going to triangle goes way down field and it's hauled in the 25 yard line i can't believe you
got that good job happy 56 birthday keep it going keep it going they've given themselves
a great opportunity here in the red zone if the ball would have gotten to the defender
come on man we're gonna do this all day let's get up man let's cut this left corner
all right you know what i'm doing it works every time six more points let's take a two
on one division why do americans like this stupid sport i don't know why does anybody like
any sport a lot of people like golf a lot of people like to fish you know unleash i'd rather
watch wii bowling well you're about to watch somebody beat the championship and get to the
super bowl and win it's not the way incomplete that's too bad the offense has a ways to go
here on second down i tried to turn around and catch it injury there's the injury i was
looking for that get man that's a new sponsor stay down there goes your star player good
now i can relax a little
the backup is better that'd be really odd we need to stop them right here right now
i just assume they go for it because i go for it 75 percent of the time
what are these colors for are they're supposed to be my colors like my channel colors
somehow
who gets the ball
you're not going to get away with this
all right unleash a lot of the good starting players are gone so that's good
i'm up on third down right third and 22 third down and long gets near i don't think
he knows what is the new beer chub they go for field goal field goal blocked right oh no they're
not oh no no no no no no no no no no this is not good um good at least five or six
people touched that he was bouncing around on everybody i got one more play here to try
should i just get a field goal or should i go for it field goal be safe safe field goal
now fuck it we're going for it first and goal it's gut check time end zone
should have just got a fucking field goal and so at halftime los vegas leads by seven
somebody fucking called me a bus so i had to do it i looked over and was like oh you
baby okay
first down 30 yards to go
defense could taste that oh that was outrageous that was a trick play it was so tricky nobody
knew what the fuck happened new set of downs you already know what i'm doing defense backed
up to their own goal line franchise brings the dinner bell again 27 good beer chug to nose
i would say of all the mistakes in my life and there have been a couple you know eating
bananas with jalapenos makes is one of the biggest and a girl in san diego
apparently that's a mistake somehow
that's how you do john men he does the talk with a kind of a high voice at first
oh my fucking god i'm talking and that's why i fucked it up
and i need focus they are rewarded with a very nice game first and goal it's gut check time
ball up the 22 yard line never had a chance he got
reversal that's fine that doesn't sound like madden at all
it does if you tried to take a guess who that was who would you say that was
okay ready who am i if you never heard that
you all right let's do it you see how lightning my reflexes just were right there
oh i had to do this right the first time hold on try and hold still buddy
it's all right i was in a bad run holy good thing he's got insurance
los vegas gets it back and so with three quarters gone
los vegas leads by seven i'm pretty convinced that the trick plays are only in the game
for when you play against another human
friend of yours seems like a hell of a lot more than eight that's not it doesn't fool the computer
i have to go for a clash catch here even if it's turnover
i don't care
that was really really important it helps me seal it you know that they're an awful
friend when they make you play this game this is a this game is great see if i can
get the ball here worth a shot fourth quarter up by a lot first down and 30
a true friend friend plays paper football he's going long make sure he doesn't get that
i look like the toxic avenger it's my colors that's my green and pink color
maybe get an injury for the third girlfriend no i already did it i took this star player out
of the game in like the first quarter what are you gonna do on fourth down a minute to go
you're definitely going to go for it safety blitz
seven yard line and he's brought down and they turn the ball over now they could have
used some points right there franchise didn't franchise dude no way big stop there
i thought i did with franchise first and 30
your team looks like the arizona iced tea no it's germa 985
he wasn't ready for that he wasn't ready for that i apologize i'm sorry
deep pass god damn it it's okay it doesn't matter and that may have sealed i gotta win
by four points denver sucked denver sucked where are you he's threw the ball backwards
second and long what why did i die why don't i do anything why why buy like golf
this group i'm just gonna keep somebody in the back just in case that's why i kept him in the
back las vegas has the football here one last play let's just be at let's be complete
assholes here watch this go on cocked i guess is your winner is trying to go for like
a hundred yards or something just to get it just to pad my stats that's a victory for the bet as
well 40 grand right nice okay i think it's time for hands three polyflex ultra pads are the new
sponsor item he really came through for me my stupid agent is freaking out about his new
client getting hurt he freaked out even more when i fired his ass how about i come over tonight
and show you my gratitude want some breakfast that's not what i'm hungry for i won okay hook
up with grace in campaign mode i've got two words for you franchise fuck you have fun with your
rich little model just don't come crying to me when she dumps your ass after she gets
your shit uh plus 12 resist injury franchise is never gonna get hurt ever again look at this
stuff look at these awesome things i got out of like the loot box all right new girlfriend is
grace former tennis pro turned supermodel she competes for the same kinds of big league
endorsements franchise tries to land all right injuries who look who it is still up for a
game hands three is 525 no more fumbles training sign it automatically and we got 23 grand
just do the safe shit i'm gonna give you one too all right next game is the arizona outlaws
sullivan is there for the first quarter of every other game yeah it sucks
and when he is there we score 30 points in a quarter what are they oh and two they're a good
team that look at those stats how do you go oh and two must win by more than six points
let's just max better this week we're matched up against arizona division one title contenders
with a passing game it's hard to stop my receiver tito moss is their number one barebone
threat little shit's been in the league 10 years now and he's just as quick and just as
dirty fortunately for us their defense can't stop anybody or we'd be screwed terrible defense
good wish i had the best halfback in the league he just did the look of me did he
they have an awful running game so just gonna play zones thanks for joining us
every game we've played tonight only lost once i don't know why i just said that considering
i'm gonna jinx it bad yard knock on wood right yeah
all right cox uh-oh i thought the defense was supposed to suck
the defense will be coming here on third long
he sure didn't try to be nice thought i could throw it still fuck it let's go
this is what bill balachek would do let's go that's not good
keeper gets taken out before the ball gets near him i don't think he knows what hit him
really thought i caught him on the bond literally not what bill balachek would do on the first
possession i would have had it too i've got to cover this guy thank you very much
get out of the end zone all right what would bill balachek do right now
you can kick a field goal no don't make a fucking shitty joke let's go
first down and 30 ball at the six yards where
los vegas really executed on that play and took a big step down the field nice work
franchise demonstrating why he's considered one of the all right 24 yards i'll take it
again do it again they have uh oh they have an unleash okay i'll take the hit that's the end
of the first quarter as we're scoreless is your planning on finishing the game story
we're pretty close we're at i mean there's only three games left in the division i can't
now run out of bounds he did a great job of finding the hole and bursting through first
and goal it's gut check time ball at the three yard line so got it you think someone
would have a playbook on me right now every time he gets to within five yards of the end
zone he jumps with the quarterback that was pretty somebody tell me why we can't do that
in every position it always works every time what is good oops easy no injury here
i will build up points though do another p break i don't have to be yet it hasn't been a
quarterly first and 30 it's only been what like an hour usually p three to four times
that's the guy that catches every ball
i p like every two hours injury he's getting weak p right now do it right now i'm in the
middle of a game i'm in the middle of a game heard him just comes easy to this guy
sure he works hard he has talent but that's what makes these sorts of plays so easy for
bravo it's the coach's favorite place on the field the red zone
end zone yes yes three and own division one let's go let's do it
first down yards to go intercepted didn't i just fucking upgrade hands is there a reason why
it's bouncing out of every but it's it has bounced 50 of every pass i've thrown this game
big series of downs upcoming we just got hands to level three is something wrong with you
that's my passing two just deflate the ball i'm going for it down and goal to go don't let him do
the thing that i do damn it the way he put that ball on target come on block this you've done
it like three times and so we're tied who gets the ball i never i don't even remember
i think they do i think they get the ball it's getting a little hairy here okay triple coverage
to him oh why do i continue to do this that's not gonna matter they're not gonna get it's
gonna be fine they're not gonna get it you can pretend all you want just kick it off again
and so at halftime we're tied what do i have for dinner today i had pork chop
it's pretty good it was delicious hold them here they're gonna have an unleash in about
30 seconds i don't want to have to play ketchup to stop smash out for the whole game
yeah pork chop and a little bit of couscous it was great don't hold on wait
you youngsters out there what the run after the catch is important the first thing you have to do
is catch the ball and secure it he showed you how to do it right there for all you youngsters
they didn't really get that much yardage either they didn't get a first down
that is here but don't let them get a touchdown they get they get they get
yes yes yes they don't have anything they don't need to clash what a fucking blunder
that i didn't capitalize on yes i did fumble it again there he goes six games goodbye always
go for the water balloon yeah put some if you bust this spleen they're always out for at least
three full games it's the best thing that could have happened good yes it is the defender was
in the right place at the right time it was able to snag his second interception of the
game first down 30 yards to go
that almost ready two more chug yeah he's doing the chug again i wish he would do
anything else but chug one more no two more dirty hits and
i'm gonna strip that ball run it back for a touchdown good the question is do i let them
second 31 hmm we'll see i'm gonna stay back
they're in 22 he's still got a long way to go
this is where they unravel and 30 check this out
it's a guaranteed touchdown and i'll just stay ahead they can boo me all they want
i'm gonna come away with a victory and the extra point is good easy game yeah i'm at d1
well you guys don't have to boo me it's huge what an explosive tackle
taken out of the play and that's in between did i bet on this i don't need to be win by like
how many did i bet i think i did like 13 grand right he's going long and complete defender
made sure there was no receiver there to make the catch as we reach the end of the third
quarter las vegas leads by 14 come on man i can't believe i'm gonna beat blitz the league
two on spring add that to things i never thought i was going to do but i love it i'm having a lot
of fun it is a classic he's gonna pass the guy up here oh watch out puts it up and it's complete
after 48 out of bounds and that'll end this offensive series you can see how pumped up the
defense is after that big stop first and 30 all the way to 48 yard line make sure he doesn't
get that that was really sloppy second down and about a mile not bad that was dumb as hell yeah
it was we have a long day ahead of us check it ready out of bounds out of bounds out of
bounds right up in the middle this offense can smell the end zone runs it outside oh you know
what i'm gonna do be stopped i love it i love how it works there's not much you can do
against that though if i'm honest when you only need to go one inch point is good all right i'm
getting overconfident here i'm gonna be three and oh in division one just too much confidence
he's gonna have way too much confidence destroying who are supposed to be the division one
champions 36 seven good luck thank you for getting that because i didn't i wouldn't have
let's just be assholes okay let's do special teams just field goal blocks fucking who cares
right now like the the offensive coach of the defensive coast are laughing their asses off
what arrogance first down 30 yards to go a high five and they're shaking hands already
this is why you leave this guy back here another collarbone for you
collarbone bm stay down and let's let's end it with uh another punt return fuck it
dragged around and threw him on tornado just try i'm i'm trying i'm trying to do it i haven't
tried to do the quarterback rip his ankle up oh my god
that was brutal here comes more bm you ready hail of mary throw it downfield who cares
off one and it's hauled in at the 42 yard oh embarrassing how embarrassing oh shit
we're good
you're not giving me the final point yeah how can you know i gotta kick the extra point
it's kind of dumb i got uh alpha three and oh two more wins and i'm in the absolute
championship for the best you could possibly be i'll take that one kid you serious about
wanting to win the championship there's only one way that can happen you and me got to start
playing together not just on the field at the same time together what's done is done hey man
i fucked up all right but if we work tight we could nail the commissioner and win the title
in the process nailed a commissioner don't you work for him not anymore now i just want to bring
him down hard so we cool they're really really odd body types what's with the shoulders and the
stomachs and stuff it's weird i know what it is i'm just kidding jesus i hope you don't mind
but i took the liberty of having your team's training facilities updated that shoddy old
equipment was so out of date more equipment is bruno hey punk i think you didn't expect to
have to deal with me again after you won the division two championship well me and the riot
are here to stay okay we're against the riot franchise must get more sacks than bruno next
game this is burst the la riot okay we've got 350 not enough anybody injured i don't think i have
enough for anything 540 550 why does this have a star on it strange uh juicing is high risk
we're not going to do it i want to save money too what did i get well tackle break tackle
all right this is this is the storyline game the training facility has been upgraded oh okay
here we go la riot versus the vegas super bowls go pee i'll pee after this
hmm i'm not betting this stacked now all right i gotta be prepared for this you will lose if you
don't pee i want to pee it's all right we told you to go pee what time is it it's been
five hours all right all right fine i'll be just give me a second so i gotta get more sacks than
bruno just let me get one hold on go pee are you gonna be thinking about all game
that's true that's why i didn't go pee because that's a that's a touchdown
that's bruno right i gotta watch out for i gotta watch out for bruno
shit i was trying to wait for the guy to get open
god damn it should have went fucking p oh my god damn it that's way too much i have to
punch this is the first punt i think i've ever done how does it work why is he running over here
uh come on i got it i did it
all right safety safety safety here comes the safety you gotta get a sack safety
i think i don't have a chance for safety how am i supposed to get sacks as a safety
i need to get one you still caught it you i can't i can't fucking believe it now
that's actually unbelievable los angeles really executed on that play and took a big step
i smashed him in the side and he fell down he got back up and caught the ball
just infuriated that's the end of the first quarter just splits every play i have to be for
brian i have to offense facing a second and goal here ball at the 33 yard line
oh boy he really took a shot let's see bladder weighing down wait till after the first quarter
second quarter i mean no wait till after this game juice on the net the offense might want
to mix it up here they've been a little predictable the first two downs it's always
the call of one every time three games going you're up that means you're not going to be
there for the championship game if you're there to kick in a field goal you're not going to
get it the field goal is good okay all right give me this good possession here if you don't
pee i'm going to take the playstation you can't get it it's chained to the desk
nice play sullivan excellent work oh they just can't even touch them talk this shit
build the meter nice
he's so good i'm so glad he's in the game um just get the points
turn it over again get another touchdown it's that simple
collarbone three two one oh back three plays no that's not whatever first and
30 kind of wasted my meter there unfortunately it's a loss can we get self in the next germ
a rumble you don't want mr super bowl how could you not want mr super bowl
and almost caught it kind of went through the hands there everyone welcome
get robbie robbie died robbie's gone you're gonna punt you're gonna go for it i think you're
gonna punt yes you are i hate that uh empty let's do one of these weird rums down and 30
wall at the 50 yard line we've got a great halfback i'm telling you i'm telling you the
computer you can't do those weird trick plays against maybe you can do it against
your friend not the computer it's not gonna happen uh i got like one more play maybe
oh my god sullivan you're the fucking mvp for real wow definitely team mvp for sure
not down in my mind now he's blocked it and the extra point is good
and with the first half in the books las vegas leads by 11 do i get the ball too
well it's good that i just did that then oops it's time to yearn not yet he's gonna drop it
looks like a thunder las vegas makes the recovery this is very good we have to be we have to be
what happened did you see that why do they just roll over each other watch this oh it's not
enough oh well get the hat back in there give it to sullivan he's just i took three people
to get him down again this same play this time it's a touchdown how did that happen
i didn't even do that that guy just he went on his back how would your balls explode
las vegas hang on buddy he'd his pants here let me help you let me help you i'll tell you this
is great because storyline wise the riots are definitely going to be in the championship
like so seeing all these guys go down for more than six games
when all their starters are down for six games all they have is the backups
i need to injure their star player it's not this guy they might all just be in there
anyways yeah probably down 30 yards to go see if i can get a sack use defenders at his wake on
that one quite a gallop watch that unleash
who was that whatever we're gonna get one sprained neck shortstop yeah he's not gonna
be playing ball yeah he'll be fine hold on buddy hey get the card out take it easy buddy
it'll be over in a second he's dead no he just he just like did a kink in his neck
i've gotten pretty good at that does that count as a sack i don't think it does what
i don't even know how that happened he just kind of looking at first and
popped in there and knocked into my leg
oh shit no no no no no i didn't want to do that i wanted to die for it
pick it up better i'm gonna save money i have to get at least two or three things to level
three before the circle because at this rate i'm definitely gonna get in there
all right season ending career ending injuries three two one not to me though thank god
just get right back up las vegas comes up with a turnover as we reach the end of the
third quarter las vegas leads by 18 yes
30 yards to go
looking good uh there you are there you go memes coming in after an injury
let's see if the offense can keep it going here in the red zone
rodem rupture that was embarrassing no it wasn't it's fine i know what i'm doing
increases their lead ticket 34 i'm sad there is no sequel to this one this is what we get here
elbow hand wrist
six games put them all out of commission all of them let's do blitz need to get a sack
is that kind of a sack comes loose retains possession whatever all absolute chaos blitz
i'm going in for the kill
it's interesting you know what i'm doing
works every time i was coming in today i just the stadium was empty and i just stood in the
stands and yelled and i couldn't get no matter where i stood but you know the yelling felt
kind of good just to get it out here why is germa's team the color of every 90s birthday
party first down and 30 ball at the 28 i need to get a sack i need to focus sack
got it do it again and then i get the uh the victory just all outlets i don't even care if i
i don't care if they score three more touchdowns i need to get one more sack
get some monster yardage on that play they're in the red zone now time to capitalize get it
in zone come on i don't i need to sack the quarterback
has a real nose for the ball that's his second pick today here's the idea ready
catch it uh punt punt punt punt the ball no but that's gonna be too long i can't sack
i have to immediately get this guy on the ground just have it be awful
okay so see if i can kill this guy and so las vegas wins the game i actually got it how
didn't he get one we both got one did i get more than one i had to all right
make it from the field goal that's possible yeah nice new touchdown code square circle
triangle circle cool go back it up it's the second that's like the third time i've embarrassed
the la riot we're going to new york this sunday that means we get another shot at max
carson that kid those assholes drafted replace me we're gonna make them regret that shit so
prevent max carson from getting any sacks or injure carson with an unleashed power move next
game i get it you've got game maybe you ain't just some punk ass college wannabe but like i
told you earlier me and the riot shut up okay still got that girlfriend trainer upgrades
this is probably one of the last times i'm gonna be able to do this
what do you think strength passing break tackle this is so important i would say either passing
or break tackle passing passing agility yeah no passing yeah we're gonna do yeah
if i have enough money i got that they have to play two more games one more game to
clinch the playoffs the championship i should be able to do it one more time
we got keep the money i didn't need it except maybe yeah too much risk no don't even do it don't
don't waste any money nobody's injured everyone's good to go uh next game against the new york
nightmare and i will take a piss so everyone can take a piss and relax see you guys in like
two minutes y'all back did everybody pee i hope so new york nightmare hell let's go
win by 19 points no save money that's a really stacked team the new york nightmares linebacker
max carson is the second coming of quentin so hurt this guy fast strong and mean off the field
the comparisons to sands and carson keeps to himself that doesn't necessarily fit the new
york nightmare style no fast cars or fast women fans are complaining ow why would you do
something like that you're a professional football player you're trying to bench
yourself for the whole year don't do that wear gloves no focus but they have lots of
athleticism he's trying to be cool you just don't understand good evening everyone at
this point of the division i'm gonna injure carson with an unleashed move it sounds like
the easiest of all the things they can keep doing what they're doing and it looks like
we're set for the kickoff they look like the ravens the bells are gotta be ringing in his
yeah they really do look like the ravens how am i i gotta injure him with an unleashed move
so i have to get unleashed and then stop him and hope i break his neck
it's gonna be hard
third down let's go with hop and pop
oh no no no no not the hand not the hand
uh not the hand it's probably been six fucking games give me a break
fourth and eight what would bill belichick do he'd go for it
his face
the quarterback needs to make sure his throw gets there before the defender i think
that's uh degrading to me that i'm like degraded right now because of that
out again for six fucking games it's very bad this is nothing we might lose this thing
sullivan out on first possession oh yeah sullivan comes in for a game
in the first minute of the game breaks his wrist he's out for two games comes back in scores like
four touchdowns breaks his wrist again and is up for like another two games boy is he fantastic
when he gets to play but i don't know how much time he's had on the field versus off
you know here's what i'm first down and 30 i'm in trouble here they have an unleashed
oh no tricks
all right run it who's it cox you got this
he's safe
let's do some more classes of downs here all right i gotta get this touchdown right now
right here bingo what is it what was it what was it what was it it is
square circle triangle circle
i just didn't how would i ever expect it's a fucking football game guys how could i ever
expect that was gonna okay so uh seven to seven by the way if anyone was scared
don't think so and so at the end of one quarter of play we're tied
i wanted to see that what the hell it's all right square circle triangle circle got it
had an opportunity to go for the ass colabones it's all three plays that's it all right i have
unleashed i need to use it on i also don't get sacked either that's how i can do it whoops i
just don't bounces off his hands incomplete thank god he didn't catch it this is gonna be
a punt yeah yeah unleash where is he where is this guy where's the bad guy i don't know
where he is i need to do a run play 30 is okay i have to somehow unleash on him
i would have had it if he wasn't there i'll do it with myself here we go no fucking come on
a choice all right just screw it i gotta get a first down here
and he's down at the two yard line los vegas really executed on that play and took a big
step down the field nice work big series of downs upcoming that's not a touchdown
i stepped in there i stepped in there look at that foot look at this foot left foot is
clearly over the line and inside unbelievable los vegas now leads by six i don't know the hell it
was solidified my place in the championship game i have to win that super bowl that's the
that's the end of the game and as i win some power points here
what's my current uh win loss um 10 and 2 11 and 2 i don't remember
12 and 2 let me see good you're good to go go get i'm almost at a full hearthstone
looking at first and 30 ball at the 31 i wonder what i'm gonna get now you guys ain't
gonna pinwheel you know i'm not gonna get pinwheeled on this one i'm very clearly like
12 and 2 not 4 and 9 i wouldn't be in division 1 if i was 4 and 9
i didn't who caught it i thought i caught that
it was clearly in my hand what kind of video game you got running here
it was in that was my hands that it touched very nice game
field goal what the hell are you faking a field goal right now
the field goal is good why would you kick a field goal at first and goal
seven seconds left yeah but now i get the ball again and i'm gonna score under the touchdown
nice touchdown keep watching
oh my god please get down
and so at los vegas leads by four he almost stood back up and i would have screamed
oh my god do it do a funny scream first down and 30 no i don't want i gotta tone down my
screaming fucking gotta be kidding me new york exploits an opening in the defense for some
real yardage on that play first and goal it's gut check time it's a pass 31 can i turn my own
players up drop it drop the ball
yeah one of my guys fell out of the ceiling he was in position or he sure was
he fell from the stage lights i gotta let it get sloppy football is dumb they run for
seven seconds and then fall down
the captain is still in the game too this is bad 30 yards to go field goal wins the game
los vegas is sitting pretty after that that was app that was horseshit and i don't care first and
30 was it a game six yards how about that national anthem before the game huh those little
girls uh okay that's going the other way
no fuck no no don't you taunt me oh i'm breaking your neck the next opportunity
he like fucked me up with that stupid fucking thing he said this one's yeah i can't let this
one get away it's not out of reach yet hey you know it'll be great if my halfback didn't
get injured every single fucking first quarter make sure he doesn't get that no cox is gonna
die too here oh what do you know the halfback i wonder what's gonna happen to your halfback
bring in like the fucking mailman sure third down the list
third and 27 i have to make something happen right now i'm going for it fuck it i'm going
for it secret play that works every time picks up the first down need somebody to cut
complete at the nine fuck you oh this is the back it up one 20 20 all right are you ready
are you ready it works every time now we got a football game the conversion is good as we
reach the end of the third quarter new york leads by a point whoever gets the next touchdown wins
again just gonna stop them i got i got a good meter here what was the blocking
where was the team
that was out of my control i had control of one guy and everybody
everyone's dead good to go all right i have to i gotta get the ball back right now
unleash fumble pick it up somebody run it back the guy with like 60 fucking percent stamina
is not gonna get hit by an unleash you're gonna step on my unleash
no i that this clock is not gonna help me here now let's just call it third in a wave
you kick a field goal and screwed drop it
we gotta do it again like you do every other time block it
it almost i have to get touched out of two point conversion fucking god damn half back injury
i'm so annoyed by that touchdown two point conversion
jesus come on what the fuck is the defensive line really why are you guys this good
you can't win a ball it's all right i'm gonna play off still drop the ball
somebody touches my guy and the ball falls out i break a guy's fucking wrist that has like
45 percent stamina and you won't even drop the ball
give me this ball back third and 26 get it still possible down and long
we're gonna time out after this play he just can't get a field goal hurry up and
fucking hike the ball oh you asshole why oh you idiot fuck expires new york takes home the prize
fuck that team and fuck my halfback i've had seven doctors working on this guy every other
game we got proposal circle square circle legs pay attention to the stamina he had a hundred
he's a hundred percent when he starts the game and he gets injured in the first three plays every
time he comes back i got plenty now i'm visiting after all hey man you came through for me today
big time i owe you and i won't forget that drinks are on me at the club tonight and i'll
give you the first shot at any fine looking ass at the and i'm going against new england
this is gonna be great i gotta win one more game how much money do i have not enough
oh just get the whole fucking medical staff on him again this shit i'm gonna save the money all
right new england regulators have to win this game or the next one upgrade the medical facility
i mean like it's already done isn't it already done yeah sure did how are we doing on drugs
let's see too much risk now i guess i gotta take a ton of drugs for the super bowl so
i'm not taking any drugs none not even legal ones win by more than 12 points i'm not gonna
do it all right let's win this game we got a real test ahead of us the new england regulars
it's tough to throw down field on these james the league's premier shutdown corner
it's also one of the league's premier criminals with 10 arrests and no convictions
we ought to give his all-star trophy to his lawyers of course they leave the last like three
teams are the hard ones the new england regulators just won the super bowl they have
a terrible special teams but who cares hello everybody all right let's go come out early
come out swinging nice job good thing they're idiots they suck no they don't they're pretty
good they have a great offense but i knew what play they were doing welcome to vegas
gotta play dirty oh once i build enough meter you gotta believe it rip his head off
there it is right at the start of the game that was like a fucking pie floating through the air
and mike i don't even know what the fuck i'm saying how it's hard for me to talk and play
games like this it's like a pie it's like the pie on the windowsill and i'm in a cartoon i'm
smelling the pie air and i'm floating by i don't even know what the fuck that means first
for the first down who needs some of them when you got cox what's the new one let's see
new new new new what's the new one uh proposal circle square circle x
she said yes why all these unlockables are not very good that one is approved by the
terms of service yes it is back it up next time vinnie is hosting you for five minutes
gotta fucking make something gross happen then stay down and there he goes
first down and that was in fact gross hey you know why don't we take a look at another one
bon appetit how was it vinny's doing a vinny's doing like a let's eat food
stream and everybody like brought food to the stream sorry i didn't know i'm so sorry
i don't fucking understand get it and fucking make him drop the ball fumble
what is this shit okay he catches the ball this guy on the left 51 thought he caught it he's
pretending to catch it for some reason 81 then runs into 26 who falls down 36 then cannot
drag him down to the ground and he makes it out four people just acted like idiots
unbelievable there was like five toddlers versus the rock i just killed somebody who did i just
kill uh i've snapped somebody's neck here i even flipped like that nice three musketeers joke
the three musketeers like the fucking candy first down 30 yards to go
go get up there i know steve martin martin short i know what that movie is
no that's just three amigos
will you looking for the big play you can still get it you can still get it
in the end zone touchdown we're good do i stay now just stay in default dance touchdown
celebration and that technically is a default dancing you're not wrong this is the guy that
beat the super bowl on stream not yet it's not even the end of the first quarter and
it's already this many interesting okay first and 30 ball at the 30 yard line f f
why are we effing oh actual cox probably okay los vegas leads by seven was it third
down second down oh they're just messing around with me i'm doing a lot of good stamina drains
here too just keep playing smart and then it doesn't matter if i lose the next game
third down sack sack sack and that's the qb see you now that should solidify a win i think
see speaking of see i think vinnie started his stream
right after that one oh fuck i gotta get this i gotta get this punk
no that's me oh no wait a minute is that gonna end the season broken forearm mr super bowl
easy easy hold it steady easy easy hold it steady only two plays and he's got seven
standards no career ruined you're going to the bench let's go that could have just ended
the career who's the quarterback number 12 gilote it's pretty good he's pretty good
nice man this beautiful catch that's a first down i'm gonna go with get it to the half back
okay i'm back in don't worry well that's the only time you're ever going to see uh
yellow los vegas for a nice game there thanks to some key downfield blocks
no no you know what i'm doing what's the new one proposal uh pylon kick yeah
goal line touchdown oh yeah
don't do the chug anymore well that i'm superstitious when i do the chug
i'm not going to get like another prilosec ad bring back madden bring back but maybe in a
minute unleash here let's go with uh prevention defense sounds pretty good sack kill other
photograph who got it me or him that was their star player right oh we both activated the
unleash at the same time
ah third down is a run it's gonna be a pass it's the opposite of what they say every time
fourth down they're probably gonna go for it bring back mad bring fourth and
ten leave what do you think they're gonna go for it no they're not i got one chance here
here
21 seven going good so far i'll get out i'll bring them back i'll bring them back behind your
blockers that's how you take care of that oh why is mims so slow oh no please tell me that
wasn't his knee knee they all just don't talk to me here let's go with oh we got a guy open
there excuse me oh excuse me nobody can stop me first down close to a first down no first down
really franchise brings the dinner bell again what can you say this guy's a winner that's
what they pay the big bucks players that are lucky these days heck when i used to play
twenty seven nickels around like manhole covers and if they if they really got managing they
throw manhole covers around like they were throwing man we are going to the real super
bowl in this game if i can actually just solidify this it don't matter what happens next
what is madden doing back by popular demand it brought him back it was almost a riot in here
let's just make it a guaranteed play that works every time
oh i did a little too early it was a guaranteed play it is messed up across right now still in
third quarter the offense looking at first and 30 ball at the 27 yard line wrong guy
they're all on the same team it means they're all the enemy straight in
las vegas has been dominant against the run so far i know i wouldn't want
to be out there carrying that ball today are there rugby games that are like this
um i don't think so i think i've only ever heard of one rugby game and wasn't like an
indie game i don't remember one releasing maybe they did he's going long incomplete
the quarterback needs to make sure his throw gets there before the defender i think
what them they uh field go another going for it oops well keep that one guy back there
guys guys good thing you're back here
as we reach the end of the third quarter las vegas leads by 27
i can't believe that check time like the quarterback just walked through the whole team
here we go again
let me see that again hit the ground it actually bounced off the ground
i'm just angry field goal blocking right now it's not what i should be doing but i'm gonna do
it anyway when you're behind and turn the ball over like that it doesn't do much for
your team's mental state get it out of here first down and 30
be right through the covers there's back there he was gently placing an egg inside
a silk stock that's something my high school coach used to say i can get one more
this was almost a game
no it depends and it's intercepted again you did bounce on the ground
how are you scooping these up so well 30 yards to go ball with the 49 yard line
las vegas has the football this game is fucking wacky who cares throw to the end zone
it worked yeah let's try to
let's rub it in now it's a good number well i was scared of new england for some reason
i got destroyed by new york you can still lose this no it's not physically possible to lose
this three i cannot lose this even thing on side picker cover they're a good team well
just look their stats were great and they're one of the division one leaders
i'm just going by what i see
he's got to be at the top two or 300 players have ever seen
at least that i can remember 350 top 300 players and he's knocked down
that one was funny this offensive series now we rub it in guys imagine that this is
the super bowl that you just saw wouldn't you just loved if you just like do this to new england
be like fuck you like fuck you loser more bully more bully fine a little bit more that's
all we need all right we got it off the mark oh first and 30 that's what happened if i got
up there i probably could do a better job than that actually no i want more time out time out
las vegas as the clock runs out las vegas is your winner here tonight defeat the new england
regulators in campaign mode did i bet on this one it's a lot of clash moves damn
all right devastator pads new sponsor here comes the final game of the season i believe
yeah i already already gonna be in the championship french i love you i told you i loved you recently
grace just dumped her old agent and signed with yours truly whatever you're doing
to make her happy keep doing it there's quentin so listen up i may have a way for us to get
back at the commission can't talk about it now but i'll check back with you later
looks like all the pain and suffering you've been dishing out is paying off
i've got pro for max on the other line and they want you to be the sponsor of their new
devastator line of pads i hear you can bust a hole in a cinder block wall with these things
really let's see that's pretty good so what are we putting the final point in i think
i've got enough for one more agility strength break tackle or tackle oh
um drugs break tackle break tackle i might have enough for one more after this last game
versus the vancouver beavers i'm not going to spend any money we're good do every drug no
no no no no drugs at all because then the championship game i can take all of them
so i've already solidified the championship game five and one when vancouver enters the
league a couple years back everyone laughs at the name beaver thanks to a solid defense and
the steady rhythm of tight end carlos cotto nobody's laughing now the guy can kill him
he's the funniest trash talker in the league let this guy get rolling or he will beat you
down so here's the plan i doesn't matter this game doesn't matter i'm going to
just play like an asshole i'm not going to get anybody hurt none of my teammates are
going to get hurt they all should be back i'm gonna throw the game i don't care if we lose
because i'm already in the super bowl winning does yes winning does get you more money
good evening everyone that's your right snow why would the what would the cheerleader is
running onto the field for snowy vancouver it's all right if you lose solomon you won't
happen for the final game that's why i'm not going to even do one play
so solomon is not going to get the ball once it actually did snow in vancouver
the captain comes through for this team once again plays like he's running over and over
again at this point which is too bad that's not a bad idea anybody ever questions this
guy's leadership may can just look to a play like that fifth play of the drive
franchise gives the fans exactly what they came to see right there each of those
for the other team will admit that this guy brings excitement to the game
they're in the red zone now time to capitalize
full line touchdown let's just do that every single play why even play the game normally
six hours in you're gonna spam the same because i i don't i don't have to worry about it
let's do it again version is good i found the meta this is a really lame game to watch
it's almost very good imagine that worked i got a rupture his spleen if i'm not careful i'll get my
own spleen rupture that would be bad super bowl might get a fractured skull
now i'm not gonna get a career ending injury i just need to be above by more than five to
ten points it's all that matters third down third and 13 turn it over that kind of froze
up there in the middle this is a big fourth down coming up it comes upon field goal you're
not gonna get it look at that wind and it's good that's stuck on own teammates yeah somehow
it's all good really i thought i had to usually that's slow most different
i can just stuff into people uh-oh who is that sorry they don't matter
82 28 is the one that matters las vegas leads by five so if your main dude gets badly injured
is it legit just game over uh it is your save file does not get deleted
but you have to go back to your last save what okay what will you what the hell are you
doing so no Sullivan doesn't i don't want Sullivan to have a ball that was freaking
me out what the hell are you doing like their chances here on third and short i mean
you're that's how you do it with the first x was touchdown you don't know a series of downs here
prison all over again block in practice why should he make it in the game
second to goal the whole team is here that was unbelievable she's at least six people
very good i can unleash someone if i can strip it i hate this
qb sneak into the right episode here comes an injury on the collarbone
wow i'm surprised i didn't get that back with under 30 seconds to play in the first half
las vegas leads by 13 what down i'll take that ball back
oh he breaks his fucking collarbone kick it kick do it again give me that ball he's going for
oh fuck
Vancouver saw something in the defense and jumped on it a big game sets them up in nice
field position and so at halftime leads by 13 and i can't wait for the championship game
i'm gonna be so amped up for it and i'm gonna let up either even if i'm up by like 60 points
i'm still gonna play as hard as i can just can't string anything together they keep going for the
same run don't you know i am the only one that can do that maybe if you did your quarterback
to do the same like diaper run to the right it's not it's not gonna happen i'm sorry it's
not going to
somebody get him good fourth and 31 is it a field goal
no they have to punt it yeah turn off good field position too for some reason i thought
he's gonna die i was gonna try to jump over him first down and 30
fundamentals just keep the clock going they got an unleash not yet
24 second down and quite a ways to go fucking i'm going to the right check this
he just left the right wide open vancouver just looks weak against them that means the
offense is at their leisure to chew up yards and the clock first and goal it's gut check time
ball at the 20 yard line he's hit and dropped the quarterback received absolutely no mercy he
was taken down hard yeah right back to him it's okay you hate to see a hit like that
that sort of thing sure don't just let the time run up and so with three quarters gone
las vegas this quarterback doesn't understand the pocket no i don't you're right third down
i really don't
i can't have 23 points i don't like that number
i'm not having the devil's number it's bad luck i'll get it back right now still how long do
it though so all right last quarter that's intercepted that turnover just adds to this
team's long list 100 guaranteed i don't see how they're going to turn it around at this point
big series of downs upcoming ball of the 17 yard line
sir this game doesn't matter such an amazing game the next one sure does
zone and he makes the crap what what did i even end up fuck it whatever guaranteed win writer
three two franchise adds six more to his personal total
he's going the wrong way 28's good get 30 that's two points
so now it's just a question of building up some tackles for more money like this
i'm gonna throw the game i know i did say that
oh going all out blitz 30 yards to go try to murder the quarterback that sounds like a
plan what um that's not he's not done apparently somehow he's dead
covers it up that was really dumb
fucking tom and jerry that shit is good it's all right on side kick the don't even forget
that was brutal but i still got it first and 30 ball at the 40 yard mark
he fell all right let's run what he's gonna gently run the ball don't get hurt
he has no more time on every question everyone's gonna think i'm an
asshole for this you're gonna think i'm fucking crazy oops game over he takes it inside
i win
oh thank god by my mercy he laid him out and as time expires los vegas wins the game
oh thanks like a shattered wrist again i would fucking be so mad okay onto the super bowl
imagine seeing that in a real game that's an absolute fine from the nfl right that's like a
$100,000 fine at least all right we are at the end game here delaying the game i think
would be unsportsmanlike conduct no i was talking to miller about that yesterday the
bearcats can't trade up they don't have cap room excuse me what the hell are you doing
here i got some information you're going to want to make it quick first i want a new deal
you're going to improve my trade to the la riot next season and why should i do anything
more for you man fuck you i planted your drugs not my fault you couldn't keep franchise locked up
this better be damn good it's money baby our boy franchise ruptured his achilles during
practice yesterday what coaches and trainers are keeping it real quiet don't want the ride to
know that our superstars right bench this sunday you just earned your trade miss a few
key tackles sunday and i'll make you the riot's team captain so the sabotage another
sabotage boys this season just got even better for us so he's gonna purposely miss
tacklers to start buying stock in the la riot to the franchise oh no he's getting it got you
motherfucker mvp of the league division one 12 touchdowns 12 58 yards me hey sweetie i canceled
all of my appointments so i can be in la for the big game i'm staying at the five star hotel
right near the stadium why don't you join me i've got the top two floors running out so everyone on
the team can get a good night's sleep before the championship grace's final betrayal you that
is we busy isn't gonna be bad we'd be here sooner than later the league fucking championship
hey how pissed do you think the riot are that they had to face you just try and stay alive
so we can celebrate afterwards avoid getting dirty hit by bruno that's gonna be really hard
i don't think i have enough money for anything nope we just gotta go buy on
uh drugs alone at risk immune to injury you know who i'm giving that to whoops no go back i
didn't want to do that no i just gave him like fucking tylenol i wanted to give him the
immunity thing that's annoying all right reload the game no i'm fine i'll be fine championship
super bowlers are in the super bowl mr super bowl makes his final actual appearance
i can't save scum let's go bet everything i have here comes the world championship we're using
all forms of horseshit every dirty play every bullshit maneuver i'm going to play as hard as i
can i'm going to try to get 75 points hello everybody we're about to kick off the division
one championship and the two of us couldn't be more excited partner yeah this would be a
heck of a game i mean i'm really excited because this stadium has great hot dogs they got i got a
great seat a coleslaw that one here comes the super bowl i'm ready for some football oh excuse
me oh come on i was gonna stiff arm them to get them away from me oh i'm restarting again
those way downfield makes the catch made up for it 75 points
that's a memory i'd like to forget heck of a pass though
nothing seven points take it the extra point is good get angry get angry throw more people
down do it don't even give them a chance instantly injure someone instant injure here
comes doesn't matter i'm fine they're not gonna score right i'll watch this first and goal it's
gut check time i'm knocking out his hands right now destroyed that's that was not his head
apparently that's what his head looks like and that was one of the best players that's
happen back that's gonna set him back a long ways third and goal we're gonna do
fourth and goal they're only gonna get three points if they even get it that's how you play
defense and fucking goddamn super bowl what have you got line up like everybody over here
almost what and it's good why don't they just do that just put all like 10 players on the
right side just run at the same time put that hard i'm just trying to dive this guy gets me
every time first down and 30 fuck just put all the players on one side that's what i'm saying
i'm gonna go i'm going left side catch it catch it i'm gonna run third down i gotta make
this make it happen come on get across that plane get across that plane that's the Sullivan
that's why you said hey he's not so if you both tripped on a crack on the sidewalk you kind of
fall forward at the same speed i mean you're still still in the game after the first play
still do it again get the ball to Sullivan easy run across go across the plane oh it's
okay and that's the end of the first quarter as las vegas leads by four is he going to
complete the game tonight you're looking at it right now this is the super bowl vegas versus
la why is everybody laughing why is everybody laughing what happened get in there Sullivan
75 points i told you that's the real super bowl i've beaten the riot like three or four times
in a row they don't scare me at all injury we get spongebob at the halftime show
yeah i'll have spongebob start his act and then i'll delete the screen he'll be on screen for
like three seconds check this out that's not a fumble somehow just like in the real super
ball that's right um second and 11 i'm gonna stay back there it is las vegas makes the
recovery i didn't get a point come on give me a point we're getting something different
for these sorts of moments all that living in the shadow of the offense is worth it when you can
score oh he should be careful no excuse mark the league might find him it's only the second
quarter there's still potential oops oops how many times have i went oops and the extra
point is oops oops keep thinking those are fumbles you aren't on pace to hit 75 this game
is not really
i'll say that now of course it certainly doesn't help when he's but here we go
you know what what you gotta do you know is when life hands you lemon what you gotta do
is not squirt it oh what do you say when life gives you lemons do what
which is funny because the dog i just thought they should have named him fluffy
don't squaw don't squirt it uh looking like i'm gonna win the super bowl here
this is gonna turn into a blowout i think
and the extra point is good what is this guy's name have they even said his name
they don't refer to him as anything it's just other guy
they're pretty far back though john madden
i'm not gonna lie i just switched character and hit dive over and over again no bm what am i
doing just make it happen no bm this is a big fourth down coming up why are they using the
timeout no timeout this is a super bowl how do you make that mistake so at halftime las vegas
leads by 25 that's it you know these guys may seem tough but they're softies i heard that
one of these guys are not gonna say but but he offered a ride home to a young woman walking
through dangerous part of town just last night today he ended up giving her a ride and all he
said was honestly that's right there you're still better than the actual super bowl one
that was that's what they did at the super bowl just really screaming this
simply cannot get there running it looks like their coach is determined to keep trying
and i'll play it for real okay fine i'm gonna you know fucking play it during the game
no i don't want it on the halftime show i wanted to be playing while i'm
trying to win the game i don't know why they didn't do what he's thinking in the middle of
turn this shit off it's gonna match
oh and there it is it's auto play here we go here we go
and that puts it away that's game over who gives a shit i'm gonna throw the ball in
the end zone every play i'm gonna be the most hated team in the league free and the conversion
is good punt every possession okay no that sucks that all right no actually i'm yeah sure
go for 75 i'm gonna blitz every play 30 75 to three you know i'll try i can still get that
damn it worth a shot field goal block every play you know i'll give you a little story
back when madden was really really popular uh my brother used to want to play against me all
the time he's a huge fan i didn't know what the hell was going on i was probably like 12
so my older brother was a big fan of madden and he would always want to play with me
because who else are you gonna play with he would have some friends over sometimes but
anyways so i had no idea what the fuck i was doing red zone offense here so i just did field
goal block every play and i'm not kidding he would he would just do pass plays and
cool runs and stuff like that and it would end up being like 120
because i didn't know what the fuck was going on oh yes uh it would be over
a hundred something points each game i'm like having these flashbacks right now
i would do hail mary's every play and he would just intercept them because he knew how to
control the game and catch doing a manual catch field goal blocks and hail mary's
oh this is yeah this is embarrassing at this point it's embarrassing oops this is embarrassing
for them it's this is embarrassing oops the stream first down and 30 ball at the 33 yard line
i can't stop it did i catch it i got it into the end zone make sure all right it's worth that
all right let's go all right you know all right oops jukes touchdown franchise with six more
points do i know why athletes get paid so much money look no further than that play right there
i'm sure he's not pulling people out of a burning building or teaching a young
what's your name but this guy plays the game very very well and that's worth tens of millions
of dollars in my book i win i love how we have devolved to just me not giving shit
i just got home alone like i'm up by so much i've trained my team so well there was a
challenge here in the first few games of division but now it doesn't even matter
oh good for you you got 15 points
it fucking destroyed 75 points now it's not possible anymore first down 30 yards to go
looking for the big play he's got it i mean maybe it is
oh and touchdown i might get i might get 50 or 60 maybe not 70 it's false with me to get 60
and that's two points just jumped backwards use those timeouts i'm gonna go for it i'll try
on sidekick come on give me to 60 first and 30 ball at the 36 yard line
it keeps it deep and it's possible it's possible first down and 30
oh almost oh dick it's not possible anymore i got to whatever on sidekick
i don't care just boot it into the fucking crowd
you had time you had time it's okay another interception turn it into a score
it's about time to uncork the champagne that defensive here it comes about clinches it
well we can do it let me just do something real quick here i need to get one completion
and i can get into the end zone guaranteed pass that's perfect no i didn't okay i got okay
okay okay okay hold on hold on oh no please tell me that
the chives has just crossed the 100 yard rushing threshold for the try just to get a point
the offense looking at first and 30 that's not a point just give me a point he's fine
not even gonna see the end of the game all right here comes 80 points i fucking laugh
oh
let's just get 60 points i told you i was gonna get like 60 points
60 in the super bowl this would be the worst super bowl ever
anywhere i went and as time expires i didn't get dirty hit by bruno
through the competition unscathed that is the super league crown division champs finish
on face of the league wow time for the boss battle there actually might be something else after
we'll find out i'm not even sure bruno was even playing he might have been injured
commercial shoot new touchdown hand exchange circle circle square x staying alive let's see
how this plays out speech speech thank you damn that russian killer sure he'll fast didn't
commission i am gonna destroy oh no i'm ruined i think you're gonna be too busy to worry about
why is that inside a train money line extortion your call commission
you don't have any proof no but they do this isn't finished franchise he turns it does a
dirty tackle one of those reporters he taps x really fast he gets away let's the league two
what is this footage here we got the designers we got the party and we got the programmer oh
this is so good behind the scenes footage nice shirt nice shirt night oh what open your mouth
you know it's fun they probably had making this wow that's unreal
oh
i don't know but you're moving i put it down where's the santa claus
freeland lead designer what's happening how's it going what's up steven where are you now all
right so the internet says popcorn with cell phones we're just going to test that out right
now just to see which one is edge that's right uh i don't think he's here
we should do you just go to be able and like put in front of
makes you smell it learn how to milk
now i blur out that fucking no i want him to know it's from the hood
yeah that's quite that's quite a difference yeah now i got h i-o-r-s oh and again you're
really good at playing guys were on the ground literally six or seven guys on the ground
i ran it back for full touchdown that was game so you waited it
you didn't score 14 to 20 dude that's a score buddy see they're just having a couple of beers
and playing this to this what i'm talking about would look phenomenal it would be
man can you believe it that was more mosaic than it was frame of a guy
there it is franchise you've really earned your name today just do me a favor man don't let it go
to your head we have a title to defend next season stay cool stay clean and you know i'll
always have you back here's the agent how does it feel being the biggest celebrity on the
planet and the league championship is just the beginning you've built the championship caliber
team now take it online and show the rest of the dweebs in the world that nobody does it
better than you so this is the take it to on this is the take your team into online
it's not even turned on anymore let's take a look let's see the last uh last little bits
here president's trophy division three didn't get the passing title into division three
rushing receiving defense well there's the mvp the las vegas super bowls i hate this name
there's a lot here all right let's see defensive title division one for mr super bowl
division one champions there it is division one mvp pretty cool what about trophies now finish
the campaign franchise declare the mvp in all three divisions didn't get it very very cool
so uh i'm able to do this let's where's my final step uh league standings let's see seven
and one i was what am i total something in three sixteen and three fifteen and three
that's pretty good that was a really really fun game and that is the end of blitz the league
two let me just take a look and see if there's any bonus stuff there are a few bonus modes
butterfingers it's total chaos on the field with every tackle leading into a fumble
you get the ball back after every score every play that goes by without a score decreases
the points from a touchdown by one dirty hits unleashed hits and injuries all add points to
your score that's pretty cool the helmets are off and the hits are twice as painful leading
to tons of injuries this prison ball no kickoff no first downs in a shortened field
uh let's take the helmets off and just fucking around it doesn't really matter i'll be the
i'll be the regular vegas team i'm just doing it for fun anyways welcome to the league so nobody
has a helmet so this is kind of this is prison ball without being a prison do the
astex have perfect stats i think they are one of the only teams that have uh perfect
stats and maybe not perfect but good enough where it looks like that i think there was
like one of the team that was like that good evening ever no helmets our first injury the game
turns off make it count first down and 30 oh well thanks for coming to the stream
that's gonna that's where i'm gonna call it play mutant football league maybe eventually
but that was blitz league 2 uh if you weren't here earlier i have an unfortunate thing to
tell everybody i'm doing my taxes over the next day or two and i there's a lot i have to do
so i'm taking the next day or two off i had other shit to do the last couple days so sorry
there's only like one stream in the last like four days stream you doing your taxes
no it's a it's a painful fucking process so i'll let you guys know i'm gonna try to do it all
tomorrow somebody else got fucking hurt and i didn't do anything people are just breaking
legs and shit hey just look i'm not even controlling the game yeah i gotta there's a
lot of weird shit that i have to take care of so nothing tomorrow i'll let you guys know on
here if i got them all done so you can wipe out the whole other team
and the extra point is good the cpa is gonna be very angry with me i was really i was supposed
to do this like two weeks ago and i just didn't and i keep saying i'll do it next week i'll do
it next week i have to do it i gotta just pick a day or two and do it and it's tomorrow
in the next day maybe turn off the game i'm sorry but i will not see you tomorrow at least
thank you for joining me i will do my best at any rate what do you say we go through the
bits that came in earlier now let me get this turned off uh dropping frames but it's okay so
early we had demonic cucumber at two dollars earlier or three dollars actually they say a lot
of complications doing taxes for a dead guy and just admit it auto ate shito no that didn't
happen so this is more shitty and more complicated rugby american football is kind of like rugby
except they wear helmets and there's a lot less kicking the ball that happens a lot in rugby
doesn't it question on taxes do i have to do anything specific to explain randomly getting
like two thousand dollars it's all income that's all i have to claim it all on top of that
moving across the country is i think i have to file separate returns and my taxes it's not as
simple as just opening up turbo tax and being like okay this this this this like expenses
and because it's all 1099 i don't have like a w2 so it's always like a full two-day process
to get it all done so taxes for boston and taxes for vegas yeah because i moved
i got here in like october so i wasn't like a massachusetts resident anymore
as of october so i gotta figure out what i need to do for that
self-employment out here is a pain in the ass for taxes it is but
it's all right it's as long as you stay on top of it it's just sitting down and actually
doing it and i've determined and i've said it tomorrow is the day and there's a dog but
thank you tomorrow cucumber for the three dollars some guy thanks for the ten dollars some guy
all right i'm done with phantom of the opera for real this time can't promise i won't come back
to it within a week in the meantime here's something that isn't a phantom meme so you
don't have to delete your channel again i don't know if i believe this i don't think i
believe you you've told me every time that is not a phantom of the opera meme and every time
i've clicked it's been fan of the opera so i bet a trillion dollars that this is phantom of the
opera it's full metal jacket but it's disney character i mean here is it's like it's the
whole thing as donald duck and goofy and shit well i'm back well there's a trillion dollars
i thank you some guy for the ten dollars and not a phantom of the opera disney um full metal disney
yeah i was a monopoly money that's right hey divas thanks for the two bucks divas
combine thanks for the one dollar hey germaine i'm just curious if you still play bloodborne
every now and again or did you expand your expend your enjoyment in it already which
ending did you get that's all say hello to your mother for me i've seen every ending in
bloodborne i played through it at least a half dozen times i probably i've gotten pretty much
everything i could have possibly gotten out of it i've seen them all and without i don't really
want to get spoilers but there are a handful of endings and by a handful i mean three
in that game secure it does come out soon i'm gonna be all over that you better believe it
hey d jack thanks for the one dollar can't believe i just saw someone say this game is
boring jerma literally just exploded someone's scrotum on stream and you're not entertained
well there's only so many times you can watch somebody's balls explode before you've seen it
already but we got through like the shock value last stream and i just i wanted to win the
super bowl and beat the game because i find the game to be very fun which it is i've grown
and numb to this violence i'm just sad that there's not another one the current gen it'd
be great they could probably expand on it so much more but thank you d jack thank you timmy tim tan
for the one dollar why are you never fucking wearing clothes you weirdo i have clothes on just
not enough to turn my webcam on i don't do webcam anyways i do it like once in a while
hey razzle thanks for the one dollar where are you where are you never fucking huh is that
like i understand thank you razzle thank you marvish mcgally for the one dollar hey jerma
you're planning to do a face reveal anytime soon you promise men we know that's not your real
face what do you think i've just been wearing somebody's skin this whole time it's me i mean
hey natty thank you for the one dollar hey jerma i have two important questions
you play gta san andreas online i have not and number two you named your robot console
sun sega what about your playstation 1 playstation 2 and playstation 3 xbox 1 controller
n sega cd um laughy daffy sneezy uh sleepy anger denial acceptance the fucking 12 dwarfs
but thank you for the one dollar thank you uh meep plebe for the 12 bucks 12 dollars from
our meep people plebe uh hey jere bear had a stream idea which i understand will probably
never happen uh matt burger man comes on the stream acting like a real nice person but you
slowly corrupt him back to burger boy until he eats an entire big mac and then chokes to death
what why would that why would i do that but you i i think like you want like the return
of burger boy i can't like in canon have burger boy be gone what does no burger boy grew
up and turned into cadet carrot that's that's what was at least what was supposed to happen
his character was going to change and he was going to turn into cadet carrot
and he's gonna be really healthy we just never did it he just stayed burger boy non-canon
no that is canon that was really gonna happen hey thank you turkish spaghetti for the five
dollars hey streamer two months ago i got hotline miami 1 and 2 after being inspired by
playing it and made a goal to 100 both games and it took about 76 hours but i did it just
a few hours ago hotline miami 1 was easy but hotline miami 2 made me beat the already hard
game on hard mode in a plus every level thanks for listening to my brag you one of my
favorite streamers that's hard to do 76 hours congratulations that's that is a gamer achievement
i'm okay with just beating the game because my god going back and doing those on hard
that will be in i i don't think i could do it so anybody that can hell yeah that's awesome
still never did the idea i didn't do shrek you're right and i promised i was going to
open with shrek i'm full of empty promises aren't i hey creation of the cyborg thanks
for the one dollar hey germa just found out that in 4.4 billion years the sun will explode
meaning every planet except for pluto will be vaporized but we won't even be alive to see
that because in two million years mercury will crash into earth i'm scared uh i don't think
we're gonna last two million years i would be surprised if we made it like another fucking 30
you know what i mean i'd be surprised if we made it like another fucking 200 years
don't you watch star trek we'll be fine that's nile that's a nihilist
no i'm just saying like two million years we don't even know what happened to the
fucking mayans how they were around for a long time the dinosaurs gone they were around for
what like fucking million years two million years is a long time what killed the dinosaurs
i don't know probably some kind of fucking fluid that they were inhaling that would be my guess
it's water yeah the ice age the whole planet got real cold okay but if that was possible
oh you know uh well the dinosaurs were around and then the whole earth turned into an ice cube
for a million years you don't think that could happen again you don't think we'd go into like
a a dark souls fucking light the flame scenario that's possible who knows in 500 years we've got
all kinds of potential global warming crises the dinosaurs might come back they're probably
still buried that you know we how far can we dig into the earth global warming is going
to make the dinosaurs that were buried in ice 500 meters below the earth's surface it's going
to melt those ice cubes you ever see you ever see jurassic park with the mosquitoes in the ice
cube imagine 50 fucking trillion super mosquitoes all melting because of global goddamn warming
and they're all going to come up and suck all your blood you know how cold it is in the
center of the earth it's like 12 celsius no like negative five celsius they tell you it's
bullshit no no no no there's not it's not hot in there the whole earth is just a giant ice cube
that's gonna melt that's why wine are in cellars yet somebody gets it that's why
when it's 90 degrees outside and you go down the lower level in your house go in your
basement it's much cooler down there you're gonna get closer to the earth's center ice cube
holy shit okay before anyone thinks this is real i better move on uh but thank you alec for
the one dollar uh they say gutten morgan good morning dingus town thanks for the 15
dollars dingus town get yourself some v bucks my treat uh i'm not gonna buy v bucks but i will buy
a suit 15 suit they make them scanned i wouldn't want to but what am i gonna do with that
15 dollars in v bucks what can that can that get me like a dance can i get like orange
shirkin fucking whip it around am i can i get that with 15 dollars no is that more expensive
but thank you so much dingus town for the 15 dollars the 15 dollars in v bucks snooze and
cough two thanks for the two dollars i've been subscribed to you for 34 months can you believe
that it's kind of insane to see that number is that enough for you to play god hand
no all right i'm ending that joke right now until i hear you say i'm going to play god hand
oh okay thanks jermal i still have the playstation 2 but god hand was digital
how did i even get god hand if it was digital if it's playstation 2 how did how did i play it
there's no digital store for ps2 how did i play that game is it was that ps3 like psn store
i don't remember how i even got it it's on the p okay it's on the ps3 store ps no well
i can't tell you i'm never gonna play it ever again but i am gonna tell you don't expect
watch me turn it on next stream but thank you snooze and copter thank you so much thank you
nile arian for the one dollar so this is basically the xfl it is kind of the xfl except
people are people get very hurt in this game you'd hope that they wouldn't
in real life right but thank you thank you lazy look for the one dollar will you change
your bits threshold in your settings to 300 so that we can't donate bits that won't be
red new people could be disappointed if their bits aren't red no because then that means that
nobody can ever give any anything below three dollars and at the end of the day bits are
another form of support right whether you subscribe to the channel or if you give
bits of 15 cents 20 cents i see people they give it all the time people give it all the
time so i wouldn't want to make it impossible for someone to give me less than three
dollars because i don't want the threshold because then at that that at that point
instead of just reading you're not allowed to give me money unless it's three bucks
which the purpose of you know all these you know subs and bits in the first place are for
someone to want to support the channel 50 tall and minimum incoming no yeah that was a
lot of back and forth with trying to figure out how that was going to happen
but they had to be something had something had to be done because as we all know some of these
end of the stream sometimes there's hundreds of messages hundreds of donations that the
stream can go on after the stream is technically over and we sit here for like another hour or
two hours or whatever it's going to get to a point where it's just not feasible to sit here
for like four or five hours plus and i'd like to get in front of it rather than try to
catch up to it potentially later just talk like an auctioneer well that's another thing i've seen
people talk about well why don't you just hurry up then and read them i mean that's not the
point of why i want to do this it would be really easy for me to go like this hey lazy
luke thanks for the one dollar uh change your bitch to 300 now thanks man hey nile lawyer
and thanks for the one dollar uh dig up robbie so he can run into it when uh thanks a lot
man thanks a lot nile for the one dollar uh dig up mim so he can run the field now thanks
a man i don't want to do that i mean at that point i'm just at that point i'm just reading them
because they're here instead of giving attention to as many of them as i can and talk about things
and hang out and it's more fun that way for me i don't just want to have it be a thing
that i'm just phoning in and reading just because they're here so i like to give each
message at least some attention and yeah some of the jokey ones that people give and
they'll say something ridiculous and i'll just be like all right and i'll kind of just
keep going but for the most part i like to give each one like a full my full attention show
feet really that's your that's the response from the one guy there anyways uh that's gonna
change probably in like a week some point in the middle of february i wanted to give enough
people time to know that it was gonna happen and like last time it's still gonna be a
process to for people to understand that that's happening but i wanted to give at
least a couple weeks two or three weeks for people to figure it out right but thank you
lazy luke and hey thanks nile aureon for the two dollars here they did say dig up robbie so he
can run it in one last time and dig up mims so he can run the field one last time
mims was on the field mims was on the field we got rid of robbie because robbie got his
leg spine broken and we replaced him with another guy who got injured every other game
but was the best player in the league so you know that's just the way it is a hunter force
thanks for the one dollar the hidden details the nfl doesn't want you to know about
hidden details i don't know a captain of the never mind thanks for the ten dollars
thank you so much for 10 bucks jerma can you add leon's piss moans as a permanent
sound effect for brb's please no those were not leon piss moans that was leon moaning
and groaning because he had an injury that was so funny though piss moans thank you captain of the
never mind though for ten dollars i'm probably gonna have some new stuff made over the coming
few months here maybe some new slides some new stream over animations some new images i'll
probably get some stuff done have some more like music and i think it's time we've had
these great animations for a long time maybe it's time to change them up or at least add
some but thank you so much captain of the never mind for the ten dollars freudian weapon thanks
for the one dollar football yeah that's it football yeah i can't believe i beat this whole
thing on stream i loved it though hope it was entertaining enough because i was so into it i had
to play it you just made a shirt of the planet and now you're changing the no no no no
i'm not i'm not talking about that i'm just talking about to make new ones the planets
can stay it's not like i'm going to change the whole image just having new animations and new
stuff on maybe based around solo planets have like a jupiter brb screen that can play have
a moon brb screen that does something more music i'm not talking about changing you know the
in super quotes the aesthetic of the stream just adding to it but thank you creation the
cyborg for the one dollar hey german just got news that on the second of april google plus is
shutting down uh all the posts you've ever had on google plus will be gone uh stop by google
plus and see the end um the only reason why i had google plus in the first place is because
it was forced on me by youtube i had to connect my account to google plus and it just sat
there rotting i don't think i ever used it i remember they that was so desperate what the
hell were they thinking attaching every youtube account had to parasite into their body into
their channel google plus it was a requirement what were they thinking i don't know and now
the thing is shutting down that's kind of unbelievable but if you do use it sorry that
it's going down i think there are a lot of other places that are probably better at this
point hey nile arian thanks for the one dollar he's gonna get his t-bone shattered
has me crying something i think you guys are becoming very well aware of is anytime that
there's a game that requires attention or focus from me all other functions of my brain don't
exist all like i get i get to dedicate 100 of my thrusters to that game if i can't dedicate
100 thrusters that ship is not leaving the harbor and i'll just walk into a wall somewhere
we know i yeah i know that's why when you we play games like this and i do like a game like
this i have like four words that i'll say oh fuck oops embarrassing that's like now i may
have been playing pretty well and been doing well and gone 16 and three it's just me playing
ad libs but i do the same i do the same ad lib that wouldn't be i wouldn't be very good
at that but i still had a blast thank you nile aurelian for the one dollar thank you
anonymous for the one dollar hey germa it's the animal rescue guy with the last of his bits
i was watching the last vaude and i want to say it warmed my heart to see people saying
raid ducks happy people enjoyed the animals i love you chat and germa oh and some of our
rescue tortoises just had babies so it looks like i'll always have some baby animal to
string baby tort what does a baby tortoise look like i shit you not the only time i've
ever seen a baby tortoise or a baby turtle is a cartoon version of the ninja turtles
when they go in the ooze i don't know what they look like probably cute turtles are cool
but keep doing anything anonymous thank you so much for the one dollar and
keep on keeping on a sly 161 thanks for the one dollar you ever have that uh acid reflex
ha ha what are you gonna do what are you gonna do hey uh sugar thanks for the one dollar
what's gucci germa i want to wish you a happy 56th birthday today time flies when you're having
fun huh in all seriousness when is the mind eraser frog emote gonna arrive i've been waiting
centuries also you've mispronounced my name in all of my bit messages as sugar shin i do not
have sugary shins thank you very much for future reference the shanks in sugar shanks
is pronounced like links anyways love you germbo keep up the best you and that's why
sometimes i just say the first part of people's names because just i just mispronounce everything
sugar shins i don't know 100 of my fucking thrusters hey peter thanks for three dollars
and 85 cents they say hey guys hey thank you peter thanks for three dollars and 85 cents
demonic cucumber thanks for the one dollar two dollars back to back here uh and you guys
noticed that germa has trouble playing and commenting since the day of germa's death
now he talks between the game just like italics does when was the last time they
streamed at the same time two days ago checkmate uh hey i know we like to joke around on this
stream but i want you to know that your content seriously means a lot to us all
the fact that we can have this back and forth is a testament to how approachable and
compassionate you are i don't think anyone in this chat room would ever seriously wish to
upset you from all of us to your heart i don't believe that either and that goes both ways i
don't want to piss people off i want you to have fun and i want us to all enjoy the streams and
have a great time and i i think it'd be very counterproductive if i was like actively trying
to make somebody angry i hope it's not the same way on your end thank you so much though
star saber thanks for the one dollar roses of red violets of blue
sorry i called your arizona sorry i called your team arizona iced tea now please go pee
that's not how that is roses of red violets of blue sorry i called your team arizona iced tea
now here's my shoe and that's when like you do like a big like kick thank you star saber
thank you bro luck for the five dollars american football looks very so slow and boring
not this one though all right i agree i don't play sports games on this stream i don't play
sports games i don't do like baseball or nba or hockey or games i mean i know that sports games
are kind of a little boring they can be but i was breaking spines do you see how many times
the frog limbs would show up at least this football game lets you kill people well nobody
actually gets that injured except for robbie you played tony hawke last week that doesn't count
that's an adventure game that is a four-wheel adventure game that's not a sports game but
thank you bro luck hopefully you had a good time hopefully you thought it was at least
interesting enough hey creation the cyborg thanks for the two dollars uh germa i have
to sleep hopefully i can wake up at one uh if so if not i will cry good luck to you remember
yell fam for me fam what am i doing i can't scream anything my my voice is like dropping
like my voice is shot today for some reason i don't know why why did that happen
happen like halfway through for some reason sports resident sleeper just wait until i do
an irl stream of me in a batting cage hitting a fucking home run every single time i'm not
even gonna tell you when it's gonna happen it i did the ir it's gonna be oh why that he's
got his title says irl in the cage and it's just gonna be me the batting cage just smoking the ball
it's gonna be like a 13 minute stream there's also something else that i want to do
i can't talk about it i don't want to it's not gonna be that hard but it requires
a lot of work it's just it's so worth it though and once it heats up a little bit oh i
hope i can get it done it's gonna be great do the work oh god don't don't you worry just
gotta get a little nicer outside it's a little too cold but thank you creation cyborg thank you
the long egg for the one dollar you should have done the puppy with auto and midas
should have done the puppy with auto in my puppy bowl puppy bowl maybe but thank you the
long egg for the other dollar here take the word trophies uh take the word trophies remove
the letters p i and e what does that spell backwards trovs troz short you could do that
with any word you could do that with any word that's long enough you could just take out a
few letters and change it thanks for the dollar the long egg uh spooky spitfire thanks
the one dollar germa i just got her in the stream is ending and they say oh also i just
got a job a week ago so you're ready to hear me cheer a lot more congratulations on the
job thank you so much for the one dollar hopefully you make some money good good good thank you for
the one dollar spooky spitfire mom the peach thanks for the one dollar i did not cross the
field of action today germa well what you should have done is you should have crossed the attack
of opportunity because that's what that's called i remember i remember from two streams ago see
i'm like an elephant-sized goldfish i forget everything but i have a lot of knowledge up
here thank you damona cucumber for the one dollar a clown car is tax deductible uh i think that
depends are you a clown did you use that clown car for your work or your job probably
you're a clown and am i am i a clown i don't know that's not for that's for you to
understand and you to decide thank you i am monk for the one dollar i might not be able
to subscribe or donate in the coming months don't worry about that i know you're adamant
that you don't need or require it but i know but i know you appreciate i know i appreciate you
and love your content enough to subscribe and grind bits to give back what i can
love you germa keep doing what you do best i am forever grateful to anybody that ever
wants to give me any support any money any viewership it's incredibly fucking kind
but don't feel like there's an obligation because there isn't you you do not have an
obligation to me you know what i mean if you find it necessary to want to give money to this
channel thank you but it's not an obligation the only obligation in this chat is to repeat
bad memes well i didn't say that they did but thank you so much i am monk appreciate you
hanging on thank you convo breaker thanks for the one dollar speaking of bit reading
minimums i wanted to put this in before the minimum was raised could you make the minimum
250 instead of three buying in multiples of five is easier than buying in multiples of three and
it would keep from awkward buying two different sets of bits also please play pirate at some
point it's a choose your own adventure game with airbud must be fair they're from pretty
bad memes in here i don't know about that there's some decent ones but um i'll be
honest with you the reason why i picked three is because that's like what that's what a lot
of people have aren't a lot of most streams have like three 350 for a minimum that's just kind of
the way i just was like i guess that's what people do right is there a reason why that is
people do 420 250 the reason is three is between one and five let me let me look
into this because that that's not i'm i'm open to suggestions for sure set the minimum
i come back you know i'm gonna make a 10 i was thinking 25 because you guys said yeah two and
five two fifth like 25 22.5 yeah i'm gonna let let me have an internal conversation with myself
and ask if let me let me ask around for a little bit i i see that as a perfectly
perfectly reasonable compromise so we'll we'll talk about this again in another couple days
make tier one sub a hundred dollars
but thank you thank you for the uh thank you for the little bit of knowledge here thank you
mage for the one dollar this is a bit of a throwback fact the voice actor for the john
madden was frank caliendo yeah from mad tv he actually does a pretty hysterical phonetically
completely accurate john madden it's actually really good thank you venus gothic for the one
dollar and 50 cents hey germ hope you're enjoying vegas i'm a vegas local born and
raised and i've been watching you since early tf2 thank you for so many years of laughs even
during hard times i'm happy to have transplanted myself into las vegas i think it's a great i
think it's a great city i've been having a blast i've been really really enjoying the town
i think it was a great change thank you so much for the dollar 50 venus have a great night hey tile
thank you tile go maniac for the one dollar hey jair hey tile thanks for the one dollar
something i write a thanks for the one dollar here's my lunch money go buy a funny hat
i don't really have very many funny hats i think i have one hat that's it i have a boston
celtics hat that i've had for like a decade uh three more here thank you spooky spitfire
for the one dollar i made 200 dollars in a week dude so yeah better be ready for all those
hundred bit donations also i can't wait yes germa you are a clown that means i can write
off my clown expenses thank you spooky spitfire please take care of yourself first
have me somewhere down that ladder if you find it necessary i'm talking about like steak
dinner for you got your bills take care of like your cat take care of fish and then if
and if you still feel like it and you really want to then i'm here for that you know bit donation
please take care of yourself first thank you so much congratulations on the job again
sir rock thanks for the one dollar uh hail germa you asked chat to recommend flash games
a few streams ago you're gonna follow up on playing them yes absolutely i like just hanging
out and chilling and playing dumb little games it's very very endearing to me i think
it's great uh daffy jones thanks for the ten dollars right now daffy jones mr streamer thank
you for bringing all of us the laughs and happiness but i have to ask why do you always
stream naked or shirtless are you some kind of nudist hippie no no i'm not i don't have
any system of beliefs as to why i'm doing this there's only it's a biological reason
it's because when i sit down and i'm just hanging out i just sweat i just perspire
and there's nothing i can do about it it's not unhealthy it's it's not a bad thing i've actually
talked to doctors about it's like yeah you're a little sweaty only in certain places and i just
if i sit here with a shirt on if i take a shower and then come and sit down here and i'm
just sitting here i would just sweat through that shirt so i said you know what fucking
whatever why would i do that i've told this story a bunch of times but i can put on a
pair of sneakers get on some like tech gear i could in jeans i could in a pair of jeans
and a sweater run five miles and one drop of sweat will not come out of my body it's sitting
here in a seat sweat just comes out of my arms i don't know why i wish i knew how are
you gonna survive vegas vegas is dry i was i've been here before in the summer it was it was
115 116 degrees fahrenheit uh last year here when i came to check out places i don't think i had
a drop of sweat left my body outside only sitting at a desk don't know why but thank
you for the ten dollars daffy jones thank you clue the sniper for the one dollar no message
thank you clue the sniper and then finally here we got tile go maniac for the one dollar
that last donation was a typo big wow i was going to ask if the night sky shirt will ever be
shipping in women's uh much love um i i don't know because there's i put the the women's cup
of the glue man shirt because it was available for so long and the other they're all unisex
shirts but i kind of i don't know i kind of didn't want to like overwhelm everybody
with like four pieces of merchandise so i was like oh the glue man shirt was available
before but it wasn't available in a women's cut so i'll put a women's cup for the glue man shirt
and then this shirt is just a unisex shirt kind of like i did last time and then i'm sure i
probably will but it that's not a hard thing to do make a hat i actually can make hats
i have a lot of options but i don't want to overwhelm people with new merchandise
it's like oh i got two new i got the shirts are back like one week later and there's phone
cases and socks and stickers and hats i'd like to wait a little bit for this particular
launch of this campaign to die down a little then we can maybe talk about some new stuff
but yeah that's it for the bits thank you everybody for hanging out i'm going to be doing
taxes tomorrow and i will let you know what the status of the stream two days from now is
and i'm going to apologize again for potentially one stream in the last four days
well if you count the last you know yesterday the day before i'll see what i can do but at least
it'll all be done and i can get the weight off my shoulders of doing taxes it's really it's a
pain in the ass so i'll see you guys soon thank you so much everybody take care let's
get the credits rolling all the new subs what the fuck what how many subs were there this
is not real no no this is because of uh this is because of the uh this it's because the sub
notification thing changed right jesus okay i was gonna say were there like this many subs today
that's wild it's going so bad it's lagging the plugin read them all uh i can't remember
when i used to read out the names i do oh i remember this is seven hours but just about eight
hours oh pizza bot hey welcome pizza bot old germa remember when old germa used to read them
all fuck that guy fuck that guy fuck that guy fuck that guy no no no no i mean like
that you too no no i'm talking about like that like you guys saying that about me
i'm talking about you guys like that guy saying that about me
it's all right holy shit this is so many people fuck you motherfucker no i didn't mean it like
that i was stuff i was talking existentially out as one of you you know like oh fuck that guy's
fucked man you know that that's what i'm doing ow my elbow look what you made me do
were there this many subs uh there when i don't think there was this many
though there were not this many subscribers this is i need to hear how this sounds
old germa used to read them all fuck that guy fuck that guy fuck that guy
oh well oh well i'm sorry that whatever uh thanks everybody thank you everybody for hanging
up i'll see you in 24 to 48 hours and i'll be done with my taxes and i will be very happy
but much love to all of you see you very soon take care good night