Okay, so that's what that does. It's head came off. Yeah. Interesting. Okay.
Interesting. Sir, you appear to be on fire. What? Why? I thought I had more health than that.
You just instant died. That was okay. Funny. Funny. Funny. Funny. Funny.
Skip. Skip. Skip. Ah. It's going in my video. It's going in my video. Yes, it is. No, it's not.
What's your response to what you just did? Very quickly. I want to hear what's your response.
I'm bored. I've got my gun. Oh, what do you guys got? What's going on over here, boys?
Put your hands up. Put your hands up. Hands in the air.
Yeah, you need to. I destroyed it. That was like my game crashed. I'm trying to like negotiate
with the guy. He threw a fucking axe in his head. He looks left and right like what the fuck do I
do now? Yeah, he was like still all right. He had no idea what to do. He was like shocked. Yeah,
you threw the axe in his head and for that like two seconds he was just like, oh shit. Okay,
there's an axe in my fucking head. What am I doing? Do I run away? Got real dark real quick.
I gotta grab some food or some supplies somewhere. Can I eat these trees? I don't know. I really
just don't know anything about where I am right now. Who goes there? This is the tunnel and I'm
its troll. What do you want? No, I did. I just was looking for some food, looking for some supplies.
I just wanted to find something. Want to come in? I have food and supplies. I have both of those. I
have a lot of them. Is this some kind of trick? No, I'm not a troll. All right, I believe you.
Come in, come in. What do you got back? Do you have like, do you have any? What happened?
Just you wait 30 or 40 seconds something. Didn't work. You gotta do it again. Can I eat these
trees? Maybe I can chew on the bark and get some syrup. I really don't know. I'm just, what is that?
Who goes there? Who tries to enter the tunnel of the troll? Not me. I was just looking for some
supplies and maybe some food to eat. Well, hey, I have supplies and food all back here. If you
just want to come in the tunnel for a second. Some kind of trick. No, I'm not a troll. Oh,
okay. I believe you. I really hope you have, I hope you have pizza rolls. What's this? What
have you done to me? What have you done? I just wait like 30 to 40 seconds microwave. What are
you talking about? What am I waiting 30 or 40 seconds? This joke is so bad. It is, it really is.
This is worse than the fucking jump through the glass Pop-Tart joke. I'm gonna get you.
I'm gonna get those secrets. I'm gonna get those troll secrets. I'll get those troll secrets.
They're my secrets. Get away from me. Get away from me. I'm a troll. I'm a troll. I fucking hate
troll secrets. Why can't we not get the fuck off this stupid troll joke? I'm gonna, I'm dropping
out. We have to, we have to stop this now. Hey, it's me. Made it on top of one of the towers.
You know we're both jumping off, right? You think we're not going to do that?
There's a fucking zombie up here. Hold on. Don't, don't do anything to him. How would you have ever
made it up here? She doesn't even have a arm. This zombie is armed, one armed climbed up here.
Are you telling me that's what happened? No way. What if she got up and just climbed back up?
Oh. Hurry, quickly, quickly, hurry. Oh, what the hell? It's a spinner.
Oh, that cut scene just healed me. I'm shouting because this fucked up infected motherfucker
with guts hanging out of his mouth just spit a bunch of toxic snot at me. This motherfucker,
toxic motherfucker was fucking snotting his mouth. Turn your light off. Oh, look, there's like a door
here. What? Oh, whoa. I thought it was real. All right. I want you to go through my time travel
machine. As you see here, my lovely assistant head on through and I'll see you in the year 1900.
Oh, that's not as funny as I thought it was going to be.
Hey, it's okay. Are you all right, sir? Hey, you just dropped like 10,000 feet. I'm glad you're
like, okay, let's say what were we doing earlier? Let's go. Let's do parkour and jump. Oh, what are
you doing? What does it look like I'm doing right now? What are you doing? I'm pushing the boat.
No, what is he doing? You don't know what it looks like for you guys. I just want to ride the boat.
Yeah. Your animation looks ridiculous for me. You're gonna get it. I got it. You got it. Got it. Got
it. I got it. You got it. All right, my turn. How did you even attempt to do that? I have no idea
how you even there's a place you can stand where it's like completely it's really, really easy to
do. All right. What if I like start to start to fall and can I grab it? Maybe? No, I wouldn't do
it that way. Go for it. Look what I did. You want to talk about like falling and grabbing onto
something? Wow, Joe is the master of falling. I'm fucking the man. Back to square one. Everyone,
I want all the actors. That's no shit. No, dude. Just wait. Just wait like 30 seconds. Yeah. Guess
what? They're gonna come on. No, get the fuck out of here. Run, run, run.