People are gonna be real confused when they hear, like, Dark Souls. We're playing Dark Souls tonight, guys.
Oh, I need to unmute. Let's just mute this, too. How's everybody doing?
Uh, currently in VR chat. Got a special guest tonight, too. We can change everything over here. We don't,
why, we don't need an intro. Oh, I'm muted in the game. Oh, shit, hold on. Hey, am I muted still?
No, you're good and you're late.
Wait, wait, hey, oh, hold on, sorry. Yeah, sorry, I just put my points in. Hi, guys. Are you all good?
Are you okay? I think I'm all right. I did put, I did put two points into Dex, though.
Dex builds. Almost just fell over already. Make sure, can you, you guys can see. Wait, I have a Dex build.
All right, yeah, we're good, we're good, we're good. Why am I using that?
So, can we go VR Josh? Kiwo? Kiwo also streaming right now, right? How do I,
I got my thumbs up, but not my thumbs. Great avatar. I think I like mine. And this guy?
Is he an asset? Can I pick him up? He just sits here. Why is his head so small? Is his head that big
in the game? So, I think it's gonna get a little bit weird. I want to warn you now. Yes. Yeah,
it's about to get really weird. What's that panic button? Is there a panic button? This is VR chat.
Yes, there is a panic button. Let me, so you're gonna have to disable it, but I want to tell you
how to disable it first. So, if you go to the safety menu, open your menu, top right safety,
you got like all these options. Hold on, you're gonna have to do that one more time? I was looking
at your face. Say that one more time? All right. Oh, you're looking at my face. Oh god, they're here.
So, hit safety. It's the top right option. Wait, hold on. Don't worry about these people right now.
Ignore, ignore. Okay. So, yeah, safety is the top right. You've got all these options.
You'll just want to remember to go back to normal, the normal tab on the safety menu when you're
done with this. What? You see the normal tab there. Normal? So, if you open the safety,
yeah, so if you open safety. I'm on normal right now. There's a maximum normal. Yeah,
yeah, no, normal's fine right now. Okay. If you would like to just make everyone go away,
you press, you press and hold, I think, let me double check. I think it's both menu button. Yes,
okay. So, I don't know if you can still hear me. I think I muted you, but you hit both of the
menu buttons above your track pad and both grips on your controllers at the same time.
Press and hold them on both and then you should get a warning saying you're in safe mode.
Okay. I think I have you muted now. Yeah, let me, let me go back to.
Hold everything. And then. So, if you hit the two, the two buttons above, yeah, the two buttons
above your touch pad and your grip buttons at the same time, it should go into safe mode.
Okay, cool. And then, yeah, so, yeah, both. There we go. Okay. Okay, how do I get out of safe mode?
Oh, no, this is just like that episode of Black Mirror. How do I get out of safe mode?
I've been blocked by everybody. You don't, you're not in safe mode. How do I get out of safe mode?
Can you hear me? Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait. Okay. Right. Go back to normal, right? Okay.
Does that work? It should, it should load everything back to normal. All right. Perfect.
Yeah, I think we're good. Yeah, give it a second. It might, it might lag out as it loads everyone
back in. But yeah, anyway, so if someone shows up with a really bad avatar, which shouldn't happen
with our crowd, but if it does happen, just remember safe mode now. All right, well,
welcome to VRChat. This is the future. All right, guys, I've never been here before. First time
at the VRChat. Welcome, man. Welcome. Welcome. Shaggy. Yeah, want some Scooby Snacks, man?
Yeah. Some virtual ones. Are these poisoned? There you go. Is your arm getting tired? There you go.
Josh, can you just heal? I'm sorry now. Don't worry about it. Can you die in the game?
Yeah, you die for real though. Jump down the well. Some games. Yeah, you can die if you jump down
here. Oh, that's the guy from Mass Effect. I need to rest up. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Can you die? No, you can't die. By the way, my avatar is just a Play-Doh guy. This character sucks.
I'm all right. I'm okay. Can somebody throw a rope? Yeah, so if you want to get back,
you can respawn. Open your menu. You're like the paperclip Microsoft guy. You're like,
you know what I mean about the scouts? That's so funny. If you want to get back, you can just get it.
So as Clippy, you open your menu and right in the middle area is respawn.
You just click that and you'll go back to the start of the map. All right, cool.
Oh, I see you.
Are you all right? I'm so sorry. I should have warned you.
No, this is cool. Okay. Well, this is everyone. These are my weird VR friends.
Okay. I met most of them in here. These are my weird VR friends. Yeah.
Yeah. Do you want to go explore? Yeah. We'll have a look and see what this world has to offer.
Monkey suck. That's terrifying. So this is, this is where Frank, that's Frank. Does he talk?
You can go see him if you want. Yeah, you can talk to him. Even if you kind of look down and click,
you should be able to click on him. Really? Down the hole. Yeah. Partly down the hole and making
noise. You should see an orb to click on. That's really cool. Where it is. Will he pick you up
and bring you down? No, they don't have that. Sadly. Oh, this is bizarre. The crow up there
above you. The raven or whatever. He fed his upgraded weapon. Oh, God damn it. Oh my God.
I haven't seen that in VR yet. Oh, this is like one of the earlier ones.
Ace, this is the cheddar cheese I was talking about. Oh, there he goes. We lost the melted
plastic Mikey. Mikey? Mikey. My avatar. I'm like, I'm like a dick. We haven't even been in here.
So he wasn't able to clone earlier. We need to see.
Just like the clay mannequin. Well, at least you got working legs. You know,
you got that going for you. I really just like the robot.
So this is be our child. That's interesting.
We're trying to get the scout one if you'd like. I don't know if you'd prefer the scout or something
else. I'm so sorry. This doesn't happen. I swear.
This is the man that's in charge of the avatars. Yeah, there we go. So now try opening your menu,
click on like the little like a cylinder around him and then on the upper right.
So I'm cloning. There you go. According to him, you are still down there and still talking down
there. Wait, I'm still talking over there? Yeah. Josh was right. No, no, not you. Not you. No,
they're talking about, they're talking about the bug in the game that someone's pulling the
horn just down there talking and for him. I think there might be a mirror if you want to check
yourself out. Where's the mirror? She was talking to me, but I don't know where she is.
Where's the fire? I played this game like not even a year ago and I don't even know where the
fire is. Okay. So wait, I can turn this on.
I'm here on this map actually. What is that thing? Yeah, we could find another map if you just want
to like. That's what you call sanic. Saying what is that thing in dr chat is kind of redundant,
right? Because like what are all of these? We all look at each other like. What is that thing?
Talking about me? Oh no, talking about you I think. I just thought about that. That's awesome. The
other tracer. I can't force push. No, he was that tracer. The denim tracer. I think. Yeah.
Can we all be the same? Dark souls. It doesn't have the whole map. I wish it did, but I think.
I don't think it's been done before.
Um we found the mirror if you want to have a. Wait, I just have an out of body experience.
And kept going. Hey. Yeah. Hey. He killed me in cold blood.
Hey. Do you expect any less like. Oh, I think he just learned that he can. Yeah.
When you bring up the menu.
All right. I'm going to go find the mirror. Yeah, let's go find the mirror.
Yeah, this is it. Can we arm wrestle? We need an arm wrestling tournament.
Are you showing him the mirror? I told you not to do that. Sucks, wrong way.
Who's the big square guy? I don't know. Are we following the big square person?
Yeah, just follow kingpin. Oh, oh, kingpin. Okay, I get it. I get it. Yeah.
House in wonderland. What? What?
That works.
Didn't know if you were going to make it that there.
I almost didn't make it.
Because playmace. Down there? Are you going to catch me? Maybe.
We got this.
All right, give us a giant beam back here.
And then you click on that and you got a mirror over here on your right.
And the mirror is right here. Yeah, you should have a mirror right here if you click on it.
Are we? Which one of us is the real one?
Probably like the mouth movements on that. I'm pretty sure they're pretty good.
What a weird fucking world we live in right now. You understand?
Think about how fucked up this actually is. Think about everything they wrote books about.
Like 40 years ago, they wrote books about this shit and it was supposed to scare us.
Are you scared? You should be.
No, it's gonna be me.
Jesus. How the fuck did you do that?
I haven't seen them backflip before.
You have not seen my backflip?
No, I haven't seen the song. I haven't seen it backflip.
I haven't seen it backflip.
Then again.
Are you scared yet?
A little bit of girth on that flip.
Jesus. Can you make it down here?
This is awesome. I feel like I need to be more animated. I'm just like.
It's because the arms don't move when you walk.
That's a hell of a thing to drop down on people, Ace.
Wait. Oh, Ace. No, not that one.
I can't.
I thought we were gonna wait.
Is there a secret passage?
Have we been in it for like an hour?
I don't know if that was.
I don't know if that was a giant.
What's over here?
I'm so sorry.
I can't explain this.
I don't think it needs explaining.
It's very self-explanatory.
Is it safe to go over and look?
Is it really? Do you see that?
Just peek around the rock.
You can see that, right?
My game's like lagging.
Oh, death run.
I'd like to die.
There's some good death run maps.
Like Gmod death run.
Long live the king!
What?
My computer sucks.
Just a couple feet off the ground.
He's gonna roll you down the hill. Come on, man.
If you toggle the mirror,
if you toggle the mirror,
then it should fix.
Oh, okay, because it's mirroring everything.
Oh, he's getting framed.
Django, the mirror.
The white box.
The box is gone.
More left.
It is lagging.
It should help a little bit.
Hey, do the back flip again.
People go to less intensive avatars
because it becomes a real problem.
Ace, get away.
You look like you're being tortured, Ace.
Okay, every character here
is from some form of media, okay?
You're from Overwatch.
You're from...
What? Looking out into the what?
Animated television.
You're from Sonic. You're from animated TV.
You're from... I don't know, I did a circus.
You're...
Killing four.
Movie?
Oh, his mind.
His mind.
I don't know.
He's got hundreds of them.
That was amazing.
That was incredible.
Thank you.
I just drank some tomato juice one night
and I decided to sculpt something.
This is fucking incredible.
I'm sorry.
No, you're good, Ace.
That's so good, though.
It's so good.
We learned how to...
Josh learned how to make spore models.
It's a spore model, so you can...
You can make creatures in spore
and then export the model.
Okay.
You can actually do that?
Yeah.
Anything you can make in spore, basically,
of your avatar.
The implications are terrible.
You look like what's left after eating a whole chicken.
Just the bones.
Why are you saying this to me?
This is amazing.
Anyways, I was thinking...
I was thinking Deathrun would be a fun game
if you wanted to actually have a game to play.
Yeah, let's do it.
Deathrun is good.
Do you want to set up the portal keyboard?
How did we want to do these maps?
Did you want to do invite only or
friends only?
We don't want to do a friends plus, probably, right?
Somewhere a little osteophobic.
No, not friends plus.
I'm asking if she wants to be the one
that sets up the portal.
Is he just peeing?
Do you want me to do that?
Is he okay?
I tripped and fell.
I tripped on some old bones.
I like how your belly is moving
when you talk.
I'm burying myself.
You know what you should show him, Ace?
Show him the mole rat.
That's not Ace. That's Ace.
Yeah, I know. I was pointing at the ground.
I don't have blood.
I don't know what to get.
You get used to it after a while.
This will basically be our chat.
We've been with him for a year
and he's been doing the same thing.
Wow.
You can be that big?
You can do a lot of stuff
that's just strange.
I'm not one to be talking.
Yeah, you would know.
You've seen all of your avatars.
This is amazing.
Well, I know what I'm doing for the rest of my life.
No, don't do it!
There have been people who have spent
seven days in VR before, I think, right?
There's a problem with that.
The best part was when Snake just zoomed
up these stairs.
Well, this is Dark Souls.
You are in the right place.
Oh, fuck.
Are you really loud?
I didn't know if it was like scale
meant volume too.
Alright, now do a backflip.
Come on, here he goes.
Why is there a
backflip animation?
Why not?
Fucking Christ, sorry.
There's a spooky boy.
I thought you were holding your ribs like
a page.
Alright, can I like get on top of him?
Oops, a daisy.
You know what?
There are some avatars that you can ride
on.
You can put seats on
avatars that you make.
Permission to use one of AceJ's avatars
to demonstrate? Which one? Is it the hot dog?
I'm getting some information.
It could be.
We'll let AceJ
pull out the
hot dog.
Why does that tracer have an Iron Man thing
and your tracer doesn't have an Iron Man thing?
Because I want to
double denim.
Double denim?
We had like an 80s, 90s
night in VR.
Oh, that's actually awesome.
I
want to double denim.
Can I get double denim on the scout?
Yes.
We could probably have someone make that.
Nice.
Give me like 10 minutes.
Who said give me 10 minutes?
Me.
IQ right here.
The talent is unbelievable.
That would take me like 5 days.
First of all,
that would take me like 3 months to read how to do it
and then it would take me like 3 weeks to actually do it.
Just give me a minute.
I'm gonna be fine.
Watch out, watch out.
I don't want to scare you or anything.
Don't turn around.
Do not turn around.
Is he gone?
Nope.
Get him away from me.
Just give him a hand.
I'll definitely don't turn around now.
Get him away from me.
I'm gonna cry.
If I see him I'm gonna cry.
Do you smile?
Open your mouth.
Open your mouth, I'm going in.
I don't want to go in his mouth.
Kill him.
Open your mouth.
Just like drink something.
Even it's made.
He got him.
Oh, he did it.
It's Bob, right?
Oh, he's back.
Where?
I'm not crazy.
Your music stopped playing.
You may want this good cider in case he comes back.
Oh, there you go.
Give me that, yeah. Thank you.
Oh, he's gone. I'm sorry.
I didn't know I had to grip it.
When he comes back I'm jamming this in his eye.
Is somebody playing seal right now?
Oh, behind you.
Look down, look down.
Who's playing seal?
I'm here.
Look down.
That's a classic from Batman Forever.
I'm on promise of good music.
Batman Forever is a good movie.
Everyone says it's sad.
Batman and Robin.
No, Batman and Robin and Batman and
the other one. I've forgotten forever.
Batman and the other one.
Batman and that guy with the underwear on.
Batman and friends.
And Charles. This is Charles.
Batman and Charles.
Alright.
So we want you to do some death run?
You want to do some death run?
Don't look at it, it's SCP.
Every time we go there, it's completely different.
Don't look at it, it's completely different.
I would say decline all friend requests and invite requests.
That's actually kind of scary.
Well, you actually die.
Oh, fuck, I did die.
Sick avatar, man.
Are you making a key wall?
I should make a key wall.
Even somebody that has the guy that sits at the fire.
That's a fucking fantastic avatar.
AFK?
AFK!
Can I get that avatar?
Why are they AFK?
There's Majula.
Majula has a few Dark Souls avatars, but not many.
I think for some reason most of the Dark Souls avatars are not like...
Leave him alone.
Leave him a being.
You can actually flap the ears, too.
That's like the animation.
So if you...
You have a few finger animations on your touchpad.
Why is Thanos doing that?
And so basically any avatar you make,
You can remap those to any animation on the avatar.
So like the trumpet I had was mapped to one of those.
It's endgame, baby.
What is going on?
We're in the endgame.
Oh, is this what happens?
Yep.
This is what happens when you get an ant inside your pocket.
He really can torch his legs a bit, you know?
He's trying to get Ant-Man out of it.
Oh, great Thanos.
This is just Taffy pull Thanos.
I feel like he's going to be delicious,
and he's going to be wrapped up in individual wrappers in a candy store.
I'm made of Taffy.
Mmm.
You like that like mrrmm?
Dude, oddly satisfying me, you can stare at that thing for hours.
I opened up that video.
Who am I talking to?
I'm just like in my own world.
There are people in chat,
there are a bunch of them here,
and I was just talking to myself.
God damn it.
We don't interact with anybody, but ourselves
Action by socially interacting with ourselves
I would just be I would just mute the microphone to stand in it like corner to start talking to myself
We are souls
I'm just
Just do stuff
This is so unsettling to be that it's hard to look. I don't know what it is. Okay
all these crazy scary characters and that you were like a
Burnt like monster and I cannot look at break beaker. That's the that's where I draw the line. I
Can't
Please look at me, please. You look like the people that are in my dreams
Like when you look at a person in a dream, they look like this. Thank you
No one else gets me when I make these things no one gets me this is what a person's face looks like when I dream
I'm sorry. That's a mate of oh, I
That's that's incredible. Yeah, he says that an amazing imagination
The works
I
Made some other
What are you sure
What
Oh my god
Superhero spandex, okay. They're not just any other spandex. These are made to go in fires
They're made to explode. Let me tell you you'll never have a wet dream
I'm in urine. I'm in urine. I'm in urine, you know, it's sometimes at night. You may have had a little too much milk
I'm clapping
I'm
But it would work better
Close to it
Yeah, we had to keep you know, we're doing stuff keeping around
I'm in my menu
I don't know
Yeah, we have to hold off
Okay
So
On your right hand it's the lower left
Yeah, just kind of hold your tongue there swipe down and then like near the bottom yeah bottom sorry straight down
Yeah, so so for example
Click it
For the first time
Oh
I'm sorry. I don't have any special awareness. I have special awareness issues. I can't like
Someone goes through the timer resets. I'll just give it a second. I mean you can go through whenever
My goodness
This is serious. Okay. Well, we got a second here. Let's go tell you you're over here. This is like I
Can't I can't believe that the glue man. I don't have time to react to say awesome. That was like hell. Yeah, that was fucking so cool
All right, so
Yeah, we don't need the music
Together
You guys are a little sloth, okay
So if you wanted to be able to do the rat song on cue like I said on the right hand
It's kind of like near the bottom of the touchpad to the left
So like slide your thumb down
Because you're okay, that's why I don't hear it
So if you have it playing while your thumbs held down on there hold the trigger on that hand
And then now if you release everything just hitting the trigger should play it if you just press and hold the trigger should play
Yeah, cuz it kind of saves it saves whatever you're holding to the trigger, okay?
Yeah, I mean I'm actually gonna enable your avatar so I can actually see everything you do
That's one of the other problems with the
if you're a new user the game automatically like kind of blocks everything you
You do from other users
Yeah, it's it basically keeps trolls from ruining the game
Wait no, we're still waiting for a couple
I really really want to end all of you
What I didn't do is that oh my god that was a heinous
I
Will disappear ahead of us will run up this building up the ramps and try not to die
There's someone that's trying to set traps. So just avoid the traps if you can
Oh
How do you jump
What happened did I die yeah, what killed me
What is that
Oh
Kind of like activate this trap
Yeah, we can't so somebody's gonna be crushed we can only watch he's gonna get squished
Oh my god
This is I think this is what it feels like to live inside of a YouTube poop
I'm gonna rent like a YouTube poop apartment. It would be this right?
Yeah, yeah
In a nutshell
Of course Shaggy has to win
Here to go
Invisible for me
Into the
Looks crazy
Shaggy has the original game
I
Clear the first trap so that way no one else does
I'm doing this sweet
Duck
We fell cuz we were too slow last time we gotta hurry
The corners are usually safe
How is getting Shrek the verb Oh what happened what
Got scared I got scared I had to
Oh
What are you right now
And then one of the other buttons should be the life is pain you need to brush your teeth
You left-handed or right-handed
Oh
Pickles
That's not Bobby Hill that's Tommy Pickles from all grown up the new series that they did it failed after like four episodes
That's in high school. I was 15 months guys. I know old shows
I tend to be a good one
Wouldn't even know who you were
Sheesh, why are you calling me Scooby suddenly?
Scooby-doo, what are you trying to say man?
Do me a favor don't fart. All right
What are the like games can you play
So if you go to if you go to your world's menu, there's the whole section if you scroll down
You know, yeah, there's a huge variety wait, what is stealing Uganda? Is that
I left the team. I think I left the team
Did I leave the team? Oh, this is bad. Um, this is supposed to be Safari. I'm supposed to be like on a tour guide
I think I liked everybody. I think I'm going to wear them. I don't know we go. I
Wanted off from the tour group. I think
Hello, I'm gonna eat my lion out here
There was there was like a pool over here and there was something like rhinoceroses and hippos and shit
I got out of the car and I like went in real close and they drove off without me
What?
Looks like
So bizarre
Shaddax, it has potential getting here. I'm worried
Yeah
Where is ace where they activate a trap and then bridge just disappears every
I just you were different character. I need to see what that was
I'm getting I'm getting a noise complaint tonight
Kind of just disappeared and fell into the aether started contemplating my existence. It was
Piano I just
Mean you got a receipt of Caroline. I'm not sure you know some people 40
Okay, all right old pipe listen up these straps kind of look as old as you all right these things
little kinky
So it's a couple of straps it you know, I get PTSD every now and then
You know what she's just displacing their time all the time I have to call the different time zones
Different doll different dates like the 80s called, you know, it's sometimes you gotta get you know
2000s and 90s and 70s
You have no idea what it's like
Yeah, you know spirit it's being moved, you know if I can't really change anything over here I gotta
Know
Wait is that what that's not a person doing that
No
Yeah, sorry
You open the the menu and emo in the bottom and then you can select from a bunch of built-in emotes
backflip is like
Yeah
Yeah, oh
All right, dude, do do do do do a little one jig do a jig for us, you know
You still got it in you
No, no
No, it's just a nose white don't worry
I could try to join in but I promise it won't look a little weird, baby
My god, I got some one of those things called shocks or something, you know in cars would make
I
Oh
This is the future
School's gonna be like this
I
Would you like to do next
Your teacher your teacher 50 years in the future is gonna be salt snake in a wheelchair
Teacher
That can make you just sit for a while I'll work right and we can do scuff or I was oh what about the
apartments
I
Don't think that except the band like him at a school, let's be honest, I think they probably have a
Like figured set set in place for him not to be around the parameters like
I got him. Yeah, I got him. Hold on. Let me just find him in
Are you doing a VR chat tour?
Could I make a suggestion
Outlook
Good buddy, if you wanna if you want to make portals though, you got to go through that door over there
And then you can
That's what blue bed really should be like you should like play the part. What's going on? What is this one?
Yourself become
Do Anderson's apartment that's the one we were in before
From
You didn't call me Rex. Oh my god
Well, I mean he is he's great I agree
It's just I think it's at that's what I got the inspiration for the character
Look look look look look look look look. It's it's fine. It's fine
I got you man. I got you. Don't you gotta admit it? I got you
I've heard I don't appreciate the face like that. I don't appreciate
That counter
Where's this
Getting right in the care, you know
We're just gonna be here for a while to chill out so feel free to hang out wherever okay
Pictures and all these things is this a son whose kid is this whose kid is this?
I guess I'm taking it. This is the kids table at the Applebee's over here
Yeah, a bottle of your finest Elmer's please
Oh, there we go. I don't know why it's pink. I guess it's like the glitter kind
And this bartender sucks guys
Please anything I'm really thirsty anything anything
Okay
Some help up
Everyone it's fine. I just give me like that the heavy stuff. Is that what they call it? I'm not very
Just call me heavy
Yeah
Hey, I'm not talking about the liquor not you I can't can you give me that bottle right behind you
I don't think those are decorative ones that are glued to the ceiling. I don't know the table
I get no bartender bartender. The bottles right there to your left
Thank you, thank you, thank you
That's awful, please anything else, oh my god, that's terrible
This is different stuff, right?
This is all we okay. All right, that's about me. Let's go out here. You don't buy the bark
bark
organizing that the guy in the wheelchair is
Free drinks
Free I've been waiting here for a while and I noticed your bar
I
Don't know
Work with the glue
Hey, cheers, bro. Cheers. Cheers
Okay, let me take a big hit
Okay, okay, we need to find a smaller table this table is way too big
It's a bit it's a bit short, I don't think we could really armrests on it
It's like kind of sure unless you want like to sit on our knees. Okay, okay
There's like there's puke all over the floor from earlier, but still I'm up
Okay
Yeah, yeah, just don't slip in the puke. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Uh, okay
Make sure all right
I
Think there's glue on his hands referee
Okay
Yes
It's
Okay, well just arm wrestle over his corpse, it's fine, okay
I'm just gonna
All right, all right, let's let's get this let's get this over with okay, right ref ref
Are you still conscious ref? Can you do a countdown?
It's cramping it's cramping
God
Oh
You can see if you could still play the piano
I slipped
I slipped on my knees
Yours
Oh my god, it's like it's really sprained. Oh my god
Friends you have to pretend to also get hurt too. So then like, you don't look like a bad person
What do you mean you say I didn't you're not hurt
How do you hurt something that you don't have you're just cool
Hold on. Hold on. I'll get your wrist back in position like blue man. Stand still
But give me your hand, okay
Can you still move it you still move it okay. Okay. Yeah. Okay. You're fine. You're fine. Oh
My god, there's like a little bone. Oh, I got like do you want this chip of your bone back? I kind of
Doesn't have any keys connected there's no they're just flat
Yeah, it's this is literally cardboard. I don't know if you noticed all like the furniture here. It's just like kind of fake
I'm just gonna assume you don't want this like a little like
When I put your hand back in the place
Monkey in the kitchen who can go away
Oh
There's a shower I need a shower there's puke all over me
We just out you should be in there you made it glue. Oh fucking hurts, okay
One guy that's in the hot tub for the whole party
Oh
Drowning yourself
man
You need to chill out man. You could have drowned. That's not good. You know drowning's pretty bad
Cramping
Alone
That's like fucking next level I doing that look at all these weapons well, would you get all these yeah
No, I'm a collector what wow
This is the part of the story different
This is the part of the story where like I come into your secret laboratory and you're like surprised that I know the model
numbers
What I can't believe you have a t-145, too
I can't believe that
And I hear another Krogan drowning in the top
I know the fakes
Yeah
I keep I keep the fakes in the room and the real things are somewhere else
Excuse me, bro, always rack your weights, please
Always rack your weights
I'm gonna beat you. I'm not kidding
I got you
Give me those! Give me those! Give me those! Give me those! Give me those! Give me those! Give me those!
I can't settle down
Where'd you get them? Where'd you get them?
Did it work?
I mean you can swing them around. They don't like hurt people, but
Oh, is there a turn for me?
Dude, speaking of character, I just felt like I got out of a fucking bathtub right now. I'm soaked in water
All right, now let's use the magic wand and bring it back to life
Is this what people do?
Where's Kiwo?
Kiwo! Kiwo!
Kiwo!
I've been looking for you
You're a beat saber now
No, it's a light saber
It's gonna say beat saber?
Put that down there. It's real
We both have our addictions, okay?
Yeah, okay
That's not gonna damage the wood, is it?
Yeah, I don't know
That's a beverage
We use it as one of those coaster things
Yeah, like a koozie, come on
A saber koozie, duh
Whatever
What do you got back here?
Anybody touches that without permission?
Can I touch this?
Yeah, sure
What, touches this?
You can sell it too if you want
Wow
Hey, can I touch that? Can I touch that actually?
This?
Oh my god
I'm on your right now, sir
You cannot touch this
If you put your hands on this
Oh boy, you're not gonna win tomorrow
I mean, what are you gonna do now, huh?
In quite a situation
What are you gonna do?
Glass, glass
Come on, you know I have a fear of shots of glass
That's not cool
Stop playing in my house like that
I'm sorry
Who are you?
I'm not playing with you
How many times do I have to tell you guys
I'm letting you guys stay in my house
But you're just making a mug of it
I've had enough of this
We're paying rent
We're all doing a share
I'm not paying rent
What do you mean?
Thank you
I've been waiting for that for a while
At least work for me if you're gonna stay in my house
Sorry, sorry
I'll get the book
What do you drink from this?
There's no hole
Excuse me
Like that side, like that's the top
Oh wow, a bottle of spacecraft
What have you done?
This fell
Give me that back
It fell down off the table and I had to pick it up
Well, good work then
Oh dear, you have that
I don't need it anymore
I couldn't find any books
But what do you feel about art
Because there's a lot of things you can read in this image
Oh, I quite like art actually
There's a lot going on
What are you doing with my art
You just folded into a box
Here, take it, here
Thank you
How did it work?
You're very sticky
Just drop it, go way up here and drop it
So I can grab it
Put your arms up
Put your hands in the air, put your arms up
Oh no, look out
It's not even real, it's a fake thing
Don't listen
Put your hands up
You're gonna shoot us
I'm scared
Keep your hands in the air
Just keep pretending
Oh my god, I'm so scared
You want a picture of my children
Put your hands in the air
I'm robbing you
I can't
I'm gonna get that close
I was gonna tell him to keep
Hey
What's up
What's going on
I have to talk really loud because I'm in this avatar
Yeah, I see that
Nice
I found that
Got it
Wait
Would it be still the same thing you're doing
Awesome
What's that
You drop gun
Right this moment
Or I'll slit your legs off
We're talking about this
I heard aliens
I can't have a water
What's upstairs, right?
Signs
Button
Come on
Why is it here
What is that, why do I hear heavy breathing in my house
Can you bring me my other
Figurines, I wish to build bigger
Where's the button
I'm talking to you
Upstairs
I'm a quest
If you find me
What I want, I will give you a prize
I'm doing a toddler
I'm just
Just a little old man
Take the ship
And show it
That's what I live in
Have you seen any figurines
Nope
That sounded like a lie
Actually no, I don't know
Okay
Hey
Do you mind
What's wrong, what are you doing
Oh you're
I knew I liked you
You're doing the only person in the bathtub thing
I thought you were cool
Alright close it
Just a monkey
He's got a fucking knife
Why's he got a knife
I don't question it really
Why are you letting your son hold knives again
Remember what happened last time
Can you say something
I'm cooking
Gamer what
What
Hey
Have a little respect though
Come on
Get out of here
Oh oh oh right right
Oh shit
Sorry
I'm not from here
Yeah clearly
Get it, is your glue
Clearer
He's smiling
Let's give it a round of applause
Round of applause everybody
Thank you
Great job
Help
I need help up the stairs
I'm against this guy
Hey whoops I hate this
Huh
I made it up the stairs
You know how fearful
For my life I was
Hey you, hey yeah
I'm okay
He literally repaired the ramp
Everything's fine, this is fine
He repaired the ramp by saying
I just need to go up
The stairs if you were there
And he was there
And glue man did glue the ramp
And I broke down
And then he did not
Do those things
So you're saying
You did do the knot
Is what you're saying, because I said
You didn't repair the ramp
And you just said I did those things
So you're admitting that you did not do the things that you did
Right
Yeah
Oh that makes total sense
Oh wait which ones have I got on this one
You got Elmer's
Oh yeah
So what
What affiliation are you, are you Elmer's
Or Gorilla
Are you your own independent brand
You kind of working up at the place, indie company
It's like different
So Elmer's have a pretty good team
We've got Pritt Stick
In the UK we represent
The Pritt Stick
Oh that sounds kind of sick
What
Oh Pritt Stick
They use them in schools
Pritt, what you said, Pritt
Pritt, T-R-I-T-T
Pritt
And now it's that time of the day
When the life of the party
Is so crazy, you know what I mean
Hold on
Yeah that one
In the water
Everybody drink
No that's a crowbar
That's not really a cool thing to do with a crowbar man
So what else you got
Party tricks
What else can you do
Okay
I'm getting a little nervous
Maybe you want to put the crowbar down while you're
Getting a little anxious
What's up
Check someone out with it
Ladies and gentlemen
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the
Great Glue Man's Disappearing Trick
Magic Show
I
What I have in my hands here, thank you
Thank you, what I have in my hands here is
A crowbar, can somebody confirm
This is a crowbar
It looks like a magnet
Hold up
Let me see
Alright, you ready
Try it on the metal rods and see if it sticks like a magnet
You can test it if you want
I didn't feel anything
So it's real
It's a crowbar
And as you see here
It's real
Please
Don't talk
Don't stop talking, someone's talking in there and it's distracting me
Stop talking
I'm a monkey
Jesus
They're ruining the magic show
Shh
I was just like shut the fuck up
I'm just kidding
Like shut the fuck up
Okay, so
Here's my magic crowbar
And as you see here
All I have to do is
Swing it around a few times
Do you have a question?
Yeah, you said you were doing a disappearing act
But then you said swinging crowbar
No, no
The crowbar actually is going to be the one that disappears
So
Hold our questions
Give me a hand
We can hold our stupid fucking questions
For after the show
It's not a stupid question
You're a very valued member of the audience
So
As we show you here, we're going to spin it around in two circles
Here, count with me now
One
No, this is going to be one
This is going to be one
You all have to say it
But you can talk when I swing it
Okay
One
Two
Three
I'll fucking drink bro
It's gone
I searched them up on
Fiverr
Fiverr.com
They had a couple of Yelp reviews
Which is kind of weird
The site had other reviews on other sites
But I checked Yelp out and you got at least
Two and a half stars
They said the other two and a half stars disappeared
So actually
Five stars
But he made the two and a half disappear
I was like wow, he must be pretty good
I do family parties
As long as there's no children
Because I do have a tendency to get upset and swear at things
No children
No elderly either
I don't like the way they smell
Right
Who said that?
Right here
Okay
There it is
It's fake
What about children?
It's made of plastic
I touched it
I want to see a show now
I mean
You hired me to come here and do a show
But I want to see somebody do some shows
Okay, I'll show you something awesome
Do you want to see something awesome?
I'll show you
You
Stuck to the
I need to spray
Something
Let's see if that works
A little bit
Thank you so much
What did you get?
Out of me
I'm an ink demon
I thought that was milk
I was like wait a minute
I just ripped out a cord
Time out
Excuse me
What are you doing in there?
He ripped out a cord
He'll be there in a second
It's a weird looking banana
I thought you meant pineapple
I need a banana
Or is it a coconut?
Here we go
Oh sorry, it's a pineapple
True
That's true
My arms are falling asleep
Wake him up
Where's the red saver?
Or should I have
Should I have some involvement for him
So he feels like
He seems like
He would want his kids
In elementary school to just like
Cast a presentation
Or something like ask the teacher
Can I write one letter on this word
The whole thing
Or can I do one sentence
That he was going to read the whole thing
And write it down the whole class
It's a hard job
But the old teacher feels pity
Should I write something about him?
Yeah
Then you've got the parents
You know the faculty meeting
The parent-teacher conference
I'm walking in a room
Hey how are you
You alright?
You good?
I don't think so
Alright you ready?
I'm going to show you something that's couple of
You're fine
Now see this
What would you call this huh?
This right here
The thing you do when you walk down
Step
Straight
Yes
That's what you think they are
But what they are actually
It's a challenge
You know why?
Because for someone like me a very
Handicapable individual it's very hard to go
Downstairs sometimes
So I'm going to show you
Alright I'm going to show you something
It's magical
You're not going to believe this
This is like as seen on TV but it's
As seen in person
I know you seem to be a man of
Personal connections you like that
You're a visual learner
You like to make connections you like to connect the dots
Now what I want you to do
There's two buttons
See the buttons?
No
Wink wink see the buttons
It's magic
You see the buttons
They aren't there
You just got to believe
Okay okay
I see them now
Okay just
To further solidify this
You see polar express right?
No
We're definitely screwed here
Another movie
Yeah it's all
Anyways
Now there's two buttons
One takes me
Down
One has a down arrow one has an up arrow
You want to hit the
Those aren't even buttons
The buttons are right here
Look at the buttons
Those are more like
Air cans
The buttons
The buttons now I guess
So you want to hit the left one
My left or your left?
Okay I understand
Okay wait
Okay L for left
Shoot
Left
Well this is my left
What?
Oh god
Can you move this back on?
Do you see where I'm standing?
My left
It's here
That doesn't work that's a whole other planar field
That's not going to work out is it?
My right
My left
No no okay
So face the wall
Face the wall
Now what I want you to do
Can you do this with your hands?
I got too excited I had to jump
Yeah you're doing a little power squat there
Okay
Now one of them
Is in the shape of the letter L
Do you see that? Do you see that with my hands?
Yeah that would be right
It is right that it is left
It's correct as in right
But the one that makes L
Is the left hand
But L goes like this
Yeah it does you're right
There you go
Okay
Now would you associate the left
Which one is it?
That one
It's this one
Have a drink have a cookie
Cookie you get it after the presentation
Okay thank you
Okay get ready to hit that button
Alright ready
Okay make the sound when you hit the button
Okay so I know that you hit the button
Are you going to be safe? Is everything going to be okay?
Yeah it's part of the show
Amazing
Is that crazy?
What if I hit the one on the right?
Wow
I'm going to press the button on the right now
See what you did
Can I help you?
I can get out
By not hitting the right button
Which button makes you get back up?
No
I'm not doing it
Get up
Get him up
He's really heavy actually
He helped me pick him up
I'm grabbing you by the shoulder I'm lifting you very slowly
Give me your hands
Okay
Get the phone
Please
Fuck
Okay
Get the phone
Please
Come on come on get up
Get up you're a man
Get up
Alright, I'm going to take you down the stairs slowly, okay? Just slowly turn around and go down the staircase, okay?
I used to be a strong man, but I guess that's over now. Thanks, man
I
Know what badness is wrong. He's trying to drown himself. He does this at least once a week, so I'm sure it's fine
Powerful stride
Oh
Right, it was like a powerful, but it was quite intimidating actually
I'm glad that you know the floor could have been rumbling and I
Paintings would have been knocked down
It's like pose halfway through okay
Get all the humans down here in this area over here
I didn't make
Well over here, can we please like all the humans over here with us like over here? It's
Did someone get gramps down here
Well, just please find a way down here, okay
Why do you keep calling us cattle man, that's a little weird
What are we I don't know
Sorry everyone Gramps is just taking a long
Yeah all the time
The first place
I got
Listen stitch it and loot all of them loot all of them go around and loot
You got a wallet
Just grab
My hand is stuck to yours
I don't know why they still have their hands up
Yeah
Okay, it's not he's got a really tough school, where'd he go
Oh
My hand is where my brain is
My hand is where my brain is. Please aim the gun at my brain where I would die instantly
My hand is where my brain is right here. My shoot my hand
Shoot my hand
What's going on here?
It was that guy he just shot me in the face he's robbing right now
What is this what where am I I don't know
It's just at a wall
What do you mean dude, what do you bail dude, why do you bail on me I had to leave I see how it is
Oh
Would you like a we could try and find an acquirter I had a little break earlier
Hey
Table service was the drinks
Good year, it's a pretty good year. It's not a bad year. I could have got with like a 75 or 88 or 80
Never mind
Green flavor, I I like blue flavor
Zippy flavor
Yes, no, I want no I want a blue flavor
So, um, how how is your
Order a pizza later
So I'm stuck here
That's funny, that's funny because you're blue man you're stuck
I need wine. I need my wine
Oh, this is one finger
No, that's okay
This is just how it works
Yeah, powerful powerful grip, right? Um, would you be interested?
We could we could
Find it another world where it is. This is what VR chat is we could go shooting we can
Shooting
Okay, okay, I shall
Get it set up. There's also murder
It's a big old like big man and you got to find clues but someone in the house is a murderer but someone's also a detective
Yeah, what do you guys want to do? I'm just experiencing
Yeah, we can go to Africa. Oh you we could do that don't know
I want to ride an elephant
You can actually ride. Well, the title of the stream on my end is is vr. Yeah safari
Okay, i'm gonna find africa
I'm gonna go find it
Wait, you know, oh, you know abuk flights
Glad you're the only one that was watching that
I wouldn't know i'm a monkey
Oh, I thought you were a gop stopper. Oh, you're uh, you're the little robot little ghost. Yeah
Rare
Oh, hi, you're right, you know, I was just reflecting uh, you know
we're in this future all this
Exciting technological innovation yet. I can't walk. You know, it makes you think where are the priorities at?
Huh? That's pretty fucked up. You're right
Just look at all this technology
Here I am sitting on a wheelchair
Can't move my legs. I mean I kind of can't think kind of wiggle a bit. It's kind of cute sometimes
It's a good party trick. Can you wiggle your legs?
Probably not. No, it's okay. You could you're you're one trick wonder. It's it's fine one day you'll
uh with those
God
pepperoni nipples what?
Oh, sorry, I was admiring someone else's nipples. Sorry what?
Um yours are great too. Oh
We're going on safari
Oh wait, okay. Listen
buddy, uh
Really nervous about safaris and stuff if there's any rides and things I I might need your glue and maybe emotional support
Okay
I may bring off a tough alpha life exterior. You know
I've broken down
Physically and emotionally lately and it's been rough, you know
What oh
We missed the bus, uh
Kevo's going to be so mad at us. Oh my god
Go on the computer here. Look we can get on from here
Yeah, okay. So what you want to do with the computer right?
Is open the menu in the computer?
Oh my god, she's gonna be so mad. Oh, whoa
What are all these tabs up here?
We missed the bus tickets. Yes, we don't we don't we just we just kind of came in
But how do we do that? Okay, come on. There's somebody else. All right, they're getting a little precious there
I needed a bus schedule. What are you looking up?
We wouldn't have that much time
I don't I don't I gotta get out of here
We missed the bus schedule we have to wait for the bus to come back
Well, do we wait or?
I guess nice figuring it out. I'm just i'm fine. I'm just gonna sit here. We missed the rapture about that
Mr rapture
Oh, who is everybody here? Uh, my name's ace. Oh my ace. Uh, this is ty this is glue man. This is uh
extra extra
Wow your fingers make really weird noises when you're doing that butterfly shape with them
So, uh, what's your uh, explain your workout regiment to me workout regiment explain your workout regiment
Yeah, uh specifically your upper body regiment because you know, I can't really work out my lower extremity. So it's really easy. So
That's what I got here seated, right? Sit down
Okay, you sit down. I mean i'm already doing that so i'm already step ahead. I like it. Okay, what's next?
Here's a keyboard and then here's the mouse, right?
You're sitting
Right hand what then we got
Uh, which hand is mouse? Uh, mouse is on your on your right hand if you didn't know
And then you open up. Uh, it's a certain website for uh athletes. It's reddit.com
Okay, uh, oh wait, there's a computer right there. Well, i'll be go to that. Is that okay?
Oh, yeah, yeah, i'll continue by a panda
So well, you can pretend that can you can you just squat over there because I don't know if i'll be able to hear you
I'm not comfortable with this computer. I can't take you with me
Okay, can I get let's see cleaner and wipe like all the fucking bullshit
Okay, gamer gunk
Okay, so sit down here. I mean this computer is just one big track pad. I don't even see the keys, you know
Holograms holograms it could be touch screen. It might be touch screen admire your son over here
You know, uh, that's my son. There he is. Ah, beautiful. Oh really
That'll get some views, you know, yeah
Okay, and then usually what I like to do is I like to hover over
You know the front page is you know, all of the top of the top of the front page
Uh scroll down a little
see
Get get motivated. Yeah, this is somebody's dog running around and they have like a toy in their mouth. That's pretty
I bleached that's uh, that's beautiful. Oh god
Right by it
Okay
Is your sister's own how do you anyways just keep scrolling
What I like to do to make you but is i'll go to where you know first is uh, uh securo needs an easy mode
What you do is you click on that and you sit back here and you're fucking
You argue you argue for about 10 paragraphs
And then you hit the enter button
Okay, okay that goes through
Wait, do you enter the fuck you or you say that as you hit the end?
No, no, no, you just simply say that out loud here
You don't want to come across
This guy does lessons, you know, but yeah, you're just you're just giving an objective or subjective objective, right objective objective article
We're just talking here. Okay. I see that
And you do that, uh another uh
60 to 75 more times
And then you get you close the lid
You get up
And you go take a shower
And you're done. That's all it takes. How much muscle mass do we gain from doing this? You will get
Look at yours time yours. I got fucking 60 000 karma. Okay, i've been doing this for a long time
Wow
Yeah, okay, but you may have 60 000 karma, but how much uh platinum we talking about gold silver
All right, how much you how much you got in that she's just taking
I've been giving it a few times. I've been giving it like twice
Somebody give me gold once. Oh
I showed a picture of my nintendo switch
So, uh, what what would what would be flat level that would be 12 paragraphs or uh, 15
Who's here
I think at that point you would have two computers here one laptop
You could go right here what's going on here are you just right are you petting your bird while you do that what
No, these are these are two computers. Yeah, you go on here on this keyboard
I went on to the other one but the noises you were making was that was that your pet bird or
That sound
Usually so minor my mic is usually sound like a little
You know
You know upset how is mine so wrong
No, it goes
Yeah, no, that's not right. It goes
That's how it goes the boss is coming the the next boss is scheduled to come
We're just gonna wait for the bus right here, um, excuse me don't stand in front. Okay. Yeah, there's the bus
That's how you get jack
Like on reddit
Turn my mic up a bit is it low
Shouldn't be that low
Hmm. I'll do this. This will probably help
They're probably they're probably a little high
We'll try that. So what is all this? This is a place where you can dance
And it makes your character dance. Wait, why why are we what is this?
What?
Do you want to see
This is what i've been looking like this whole time. Wow, I forgot
Sometimes I forget
That's right
Look at oh fuck. Look at all that reddit mess
Yeah
It looks so sad
I could just do this for like 45 minutes straight. Huh? No, I couldn't i'm gonna hit stuff
Yeah, so hold on check this out
I just wanna go pee
I haven't got pee in like
L day
The way that they're gonna play songs
down
I guess uh, we're doing this now step on the button I guess
Step on a button
Go on the green circle. Okay, step a little bit close. There you go
Here we go. What is this?
We're gonna dance
Oh guys, we're actually controlling the characters. Okay
Yeah
We're doing a really good dance
man
Fuck we practiced
Yeah, you guys we did this off stream for a little while
Oh, it's been months
Finally get to do this. Oh my gosh. You guys are so good today. I'm up your ankles are really loose
This is seriously like
75 fucking hours of work
This has been worth it months man months
Hey, you know, I didn't really uh
Agree with the sock choice at first
Yeah
I'm gonna like a fucking magic spell. This can't be stopped
Can I come out and like punch myself in the face?
How do I like how do I like rake my own neck here
Oh, there you go. Yeah, show what you got
Hasn't been together too long
A mess out there today. What do you say? No, no, no, yeah, we're performing
Burn is trying to pull everything together, but no one seems to be what is still going
No, no
Well, if you want to quit
Press your menu button thing again and go to respawn same place you get the backflip
How are you going?
Uh cake then then you want to press
You're still going
I still got it, baby
God has abandoned us. Yeah. God has abandoned us. There used to be like right there
This is fucking wild
Oh my goodness
All right. I'm gonna go take a little bit of a break
You got a nice chill place where there's no like not a lot going on
I'll just take the headset off and get myself some food
Thank you, though. I'll go like over here. He's still going. I was like peeing in the corner
Oh, I'm gonna puke
That's so funny
Oh, no, did you like it?
All right. I'm gonna take a break
Oh, wow, we are in space. That's interesting
I think kibo took a break as well
uh
So give me a moment. I'm gonna i'll be back
Figure out what we're gonna do next
I'll see you guys in like two three minutes. I'm gonna get some water
Hello. Oh
so
That was an adventure. This is less chaos than I expected kibo isn't feeling good. So she's taking a break. Oh, that's too bad
Well kibo, it was really really fun and funny. Thank you for introducing me to this wild world
Oh, is she back? Yeah kibo also streaming stream is called boomer babysitter
Yeah, I want to I kind of want to do the safari. I'm kind of into that. All right. Let's uh, let me
How do we let me try to track her down? Let's get this off the screen for a second
Hey, where's the safari?
Coming up. All right. Um
She's somewhere in space
All right. Um
I wonder is there where I can where's uh, where's josh josh you here?
Um, no, i'm not muted. Why is the closet cracked up? But that's a good question shouldn't be let me
Kim check
What what?
How how would you even get in there? It's overwhelming. Oh, yeah, it's it's it's a lot to take in
All right. I'm gonna uh, let's get back in let me get a sip of my coffee
Uh, you guys having a good time. Is it fun? Is it fun to watch because you know, that's important, right? No, no
No, let me get this out of my ear or other people that are here streaming too
Um, probably I think at least a couple of them are at least a couple I would assume
All right, let's get in here. I'm gonna clean this for a second. Hold on. It's kind of greasy
Increase my mic. Yeah, let me see. I don't know what's going on there. It's weird
Shouldn't be doing that. How's that? Is that better?
Increase my mic in the game faced away a lot of the time. Yeah, that's true. Uh, hold on. Let me
Uh, I think there's a way I can actually increase it in game, but
Someone called me a cave goblin. You're not far off. You really aren't the yeah
The in-game mic is the headset. I made sure to set that first
So you guys are hearing my mic. Everyone's hearing
the vibe
Let's uh get back in here and see what we're gonna do next because that like murder mystery mansion thing sounds actually kind of fun
I feel like there could be some fun there
It's like
anime dancing
Not that you know, not that I i'm just saying kim check kim kim's not in there
What the did I just spit in this? How did I spit in here? That doesn't make any sense. I spit in here
Uh, oh, there's josh. Okay. All right. Well, let's get back in
See you all
In vr
One more sip of coffee and we'll get out of here, you know
Do more
No more
It's it's still i'm still having a decent time
I mean we're playing with with with key. Whoa in vr. Josh, so i'm not just gonna disappear and be like bye. I'm doing something else
So we're kind of all doing this together. So so let's go track them down
Hey, we both came back at the exact same time
Wow, yeah
We have a problem
What's the matter fantastic?
Oh the gnome
What the fuck just happened to me what how did you do that you just grabbed me like pulled me into you
I why can you do that? You just get
Pretty awesome
I got
Why am I stuck? Oh god, he's paralyzing me. What are you guys talking about?
All right
Maybe we're just crazy. So what's the plan?
What do we want to do? What are you guys gonna do with uh whiskey book?
A bunch of animals in there
It's like when you have loads of youtube videos open
And then your chrome crashes and you accidentally restore all tabs and then just everything at once it's it's um
It all refreshes
And stuff starts playing that you don't even know you're like when did I click that?
When did I click on beyonce single ladies? I don't remember that happening and it just it loads too
I have a world. I don't know if it still exists, but if it does
I hope it does. I have a
I have a very special world. Oh god
I'm looking forward to it. Whatever it is
I hope it still exists. Yes. Oh, it doesn't I don't know if it's working
If it just exists, um
Terma 2907 why is it the two two?
What is terma 2907?
I don't know if it it it still works. Oh, oh no
What oh is this the green screen stream
What
Oh my god
Does this exist in vr chat basics?
See if I can do them
I kind of like a look at it
Can you stand behind it behind it like this
Oh, I can stand behind it and then I can watch
Oh, there we go. Okay
This is surreal
It's just me
Whoa. Oh
This is all it is. It's just the video that plays
Oh look at it
He just like breathed in my face
This is so awkward if you would just come to this world and not know what this was you'd be like what yeah, yeah
No, no, I want to punch myself in the face I did I did that like 10 times today
How often do I do that what they're like
All right, yeah, no, that's not right
Well, um, welcome to germa world. This is all there is to see
Hey, you're my guy
I'm right here right here right here
That's me. I see you too
No, he's just he just walks by
Uh, do you want me to set up a murder map?
Yeah murder murder map. Okay
Okay, uh, but I have to go like this, right
No, there we go when it's green screen night volume two
All right
I actually want to go back and do more
Because the the encore I was going to do an encore night and then the more that I think about it's like
All right. Well, why not just do more
Yeah, get up there for like another few hours and add more stuff
I hope that they update this world, but there's just another video playing the second one
right next
It's just like see it's like stop doing that do something else
This is a fever dream. Is this my that's like my favorite movement
What the the
It's got many names
It's like that's winding me looking at it
I'm so tired
Underwear is coming out. Nobody told me about my underwear. He just took his shirt into it
Okay
Murder map is ready
All right, cool. Cool. Cool. I do just want to sit and watch
You know what?
Let's just watch this whole thing
Like what four hours
It's a long time it's like a four to five hour video, okay. Okay. All right. Did you get the invite? Uh,
Yeah
When you get that
You can enjoy your own company
Yeah
I will sit here and watch this embarrassing video
No, i'm just kidding
All right, but it's not embarrassing until they get to the raptor. That's that's where it gets embarrassing
Oh, that's the good one. No, no, the rap is the good one
Hey
Wake up wake up wake up
Food's down here food downstairs foods downstairs
He's so stubborn
Go get over here
I'll tell you though. I will say I wear
that
top
All the time
That's not like a joke prop top. I wear that every day
A little warm fleece. Yeah, no, that makes sense. If you know, not in the warmer months, it doesn't really make such sense
No, I wear it a lot
Yeah, it smells like old cigarettes for some reason, but I don't even know where I got it. So oh
Oh, oh no, that's not good
Where would it be somewhere in particular
At the top of your menu
No
Nothing yet
This is the clip that I spilled my wine over this
I kicked it
Oh, that's right
I remember you were like you were like you were like over here like you were like
Oh fucking oh god, damn it
Why I
I'm gonna break these I really am
Oh, yeah, mine's broken my base station
I'm broken. He's blinking at me
It's it's so fragile, but so expensive
You know
There are people that pay like six hundred dollars just so they could experience this
Yeah
Wait, what? Oh vibe. I thought you talked about this. I was like what somebody charges
$600 for this
That's like it's for free on youtube
You know, it's crazy. So many people charge like 600 bucks for this room and then they fill it and they watch this
That's so funny
Oh my god
Um, it's vr chat is free to download and you can all visit the jammer world
You want to see just a bunch of anime girls sat here watching
It's all huddled around
I don't know. I don't know where I was even going with this one. You see I have a sheet. I still have it. Uh
We we were taking requests
And what i'm looking at that I have like a sheet
That has hundreds of things listed on it. I keep walking over and going like what the hell are we doing now?
I feel like oh there we go. What's the next one?
I should have used that cold one for skyrim
Fuck
So, how do how do how do how do we say? Hey, did you get it? Where's the invite?
Um, there should be like a little thing saying
I'll make the
I can I can do this. I'm capable do it
Come on I do I want to fight you
I'll be fighting you. That's what's happening here
That was embarrassing you're like that guy knocked you out get in there knocking down
Oh my wrist, oh
I don't know. How are you? Hey, I got an invite. Okay. Okay. Oh fuck mine's gone
Okay, I'll see you on the other side
Um, I don't think I have an invite now. Okay. I'll make
It's like herding cat
It's like just shoving us all in the same room. What was that?
I just fell off the table
Though there's a friend request
Right new instance and I only boom
I gotta go. He's gonna kick you if you're not careful. These are pretty good. I'm gonna give myself a little credit here
I keep that one not so much, but I keep I keep getting friend invites but not um
That's fine. Oh go through here
Yep, so so that's real
Oh, this is fun. I like this one
Okay, so it's like any
any murder
murdered mystery someone's the killer
someone's a detective and
There's the how to play. Oh, okay
Okay, everyone stands in a circle mass player presses start you begin the bystander
Find knives and stab everybody only you can use knives. Don't get shot. You cannot pick up the gun. Okay
You start with the gun shoot the murderer shooting bystanders drops the gun you can shoot through walls
Identify the murderer
So there's five clues. Okay
So lockable doors throwable knife 150 plus clue locations
About this guys i've had bad experiences in creepy mansions before
Now you got experience here
Yeah
Just back in the corner tommy back
Request
Uh, no, i'm just trying to i'm seeing if I seriously if I want to be glue man still if I want to change
Did you favorite up
Uh, no, I don't think so
I just cloned because i'm a moron. Oh, well, I think I think you could favorite clone avatars, right?
Yeah, in avatar underneath yourself you can
Oh, okay, that's cool. So that way it's always at your disposal. All right
I think you can
Yeah, i'm coming back I think and you could probably help me out to get some more
It's loading I just don't see it. I don't see either if you do
There I am
Hey, look are you is that is that handsome jack?
No, my handsome jack broke. It's reese from tales from the borderland. Oh, okay. Cool
Ha ha I like this guy
Oh
Hey, okay. Whoa, okay. No, don't change out that avatar just yet
I'm just a loading nightmare for all of these people
Oh, wait, what?
Where's where's where's where's where's all I see are blue ghosts
Oh
Put on a little bit of weight there, buddy
It's those 10 paragraphs. I'm ready. We're doing enough for
Um, oh yeah, you're gonna need to make sure you're standing in the circle
Oh, it's still
The shoe is on okay
What was that hair gone
Yeah, key. Well, can you hit the reset? I like I guess they call it transformation Tuesday for a reason. Oh, you're
In one moment. He's chiseled. What do I look like freak? God vexed. He's
Everyone in the circle, what's he saying? Yeah, dude, I have like socks on
Uh
So somebody the time is gonna give us like an eight second tldr
Okay, now if it kills people if you want to shoot people bad guys, I think uh
We gotta find
I think you are the
I'm just a monkey
Uh, I guess the gunman would have a gun
Ace j owns this place, but he's not here right now. So we're gonna make a mess
To his private party
He just left us in his
Scatter like bloody roaches
It's like scooby-doo, you meant to work as a team everyone knows that if you split up and someone's gonna die
How do you open doors
Oh wait what a gun in my hand your gun in your hand
Good idea, why is it not work? Can't we just have dinner like a real family?
Apparently not apparently they they just wanted to show us up
You know what a lot of them they can bugger off and go to bed without supper
Yeah
I made some easy back. We could eat it right there real quick if you want
Hey, I made some easy back for us
Easy back
There's not a gun here
It's broken there's no gun in this lobby and we can't grab things it's broken. Oh shit, uh the lobby broke
And it's cake bed. Where's cake bed?
Is somebody in here hello
There's a knife here
Okay, let's like
We need to drop a portal to a new instance. This is lobbies broken
video game
Good drop a portal in this hallway over here. Is that a warframe painting?
Or wait, wait
Oh, I think what happened is iq was that yeah, the detective had disconnected in the middle of the
I can grab things again and I don't have like the buzzing. I'm gonna be joe
What i'm gonna be joe
You're gonna be joe. Yeah
It's me joe, I don't see joe yet, but yeah, you will in a few minutes
Is that eyeliner, uh
Oh
You gotta do something make some time. I mean, uh, that's why I put it on. I know it looks good. That's what I do
hmm
all right
Uh, yeah, don't get stabbed by the knife and watch out for the gun something like that
Oh my god, I just saw someone join the moment the match started. I just saw someone's blue avatar
Did someone spawn with the gun this time? Let's check that. Whoa. Okay. Anybody got it done? Who's got it? Who's got the gun?
Like just instantly just instantly they scatter I think we're running around all over the fucking place. I don't want to say
I agree. It's more exciting, man
It's detective tyranus. So like we got a gun. That's good
Yeah, welcome to the party. I don't trust anybody as far as i can from in here. Okay, so let's just be completely honest
Okay, I think we got a nominator here man, I don't trust that guy
We ran up into the hallway behind him in the doorway. Oh
Did you shoot
The last time you had a gun in your hand
That never happened, I don't know what you're talking about at all
What can you touch me some windex in my closet? I need I need it. I'm not going anywhere by myself
Okay, i'm gonna take i'm taking everybody if i'm gonna go somewhere. We're out of windex
If you're not in line of sight you're dead
Yeah, all purpose like a all surface cleaner. I'm gonna
Knife there's a knife in there. There's a knife in there knife in that room. I'm watching you
What about what?
Hey
Okay, uh next time I mean you're sure you're watching me man, why should I give it back said a windex mix?
You know, I thought you were helping me out for a second and you just make my disappointment a measurable
That's it
What's going on?
Bonus gun in order for the bystander to collect five of these fucking whatever kids
Hey, hey, how are you?
There's uh stuff going on here you probably don't want to be alone turn my back for five seconds
And uh big dome over here. Follow me out of the room
Where's he going?
I didn't do it
What does anything happen?
What do you got?
Hey, how's your uh, what was the clue? You have to say jinkies when you find a clue. It's the law
Thank you
Remember when like you you do arts and crafts and then you you soak a paper
In in tea bags to create like that old-timey parchment. Look it was one of those. Oh
What happened to the bug? I get it
There was a bug that was down here with us. Where'd it go? All right
Where the fuck wheelchair guy wheelchair guy is standing again, and he's doing some weird voodoo stuff. I'm actually terrified
Well, I shoot him
He keeps trying to convince me
Oh, i'm sorry, and where's joe? Hey, my name is joe. Don't forget
Nah
You got anything in your hand? I don't I don't I don't trust that fucking bug though. The bug is freaking me out
I am the bug's got a gun. So uh, yeah at the moment just until he dropped the gun your best friends with the bug
What what's going on
Did I just get kicked out of the killed out of the game the whole thing crashed
Uh, hold on
Oh, I don't trust the fucking bug at all
Are they still in how did I get kicked out?
shit
What can I get back in if I open it again?
I'm gonna open it again. See what it will put me back in where I was
Oh the game ended for everybody too. Okay, I can request an invite. Yeah, that's fine
All right. All right. Dunkin donuts dunkin donuts fucking patriots red sox patriots dunkin donuts
traffic cars fucking cars other cars traffic bossing cars
I'm ready
Okay, request an invite
request invite
You know what you know what I think that's that's a little bit
Screen it's black. What? Oh, that was weird. I was shrinking my guy. I mean, I feel like this guy wouldn't be this big
It's not like real fucking height
Hey, hey, what's up? Sorry
Come here. Hey, what's going on? Remember? Hey, don't decide a beta. He's he's we're we're fine. The director's directions one
Oh, yeah
I said we could carpool but you didn't want to
I I fucking walk I exercise get over
You're supposed to be my room man. Everyone's here. Remember the girl I tried to
Hey, what's up throwing this shit at me right now we're about to play uh
I'm going to play with these people here. Where they are
Yeah, I don't I don't know you told me you should know them
No, it was a random facebook invite. I just accepted it. I don't know
I still decide beta brothers. We need to stick together. I don't know what we're doing. I think
I was yeah, I was I was a senior when you were freshman. So like I don't really give a shit, you know
We just we took you on our wings and we told you the things and
Yeah, I mean you gotta you gotta fly you gotta fly I can't make you fly
Hey
Are you are you a facebook friends with him connected somehow?
I think so. I took it. It was it was the house party. This is on all the people here though
Somebody sent me an invite to come here and I clicked it. I'm just plus one
Is that it? What is it? No
No, what the no guys got me confused with oh you guys are talking about nick no, i'm tim
That's
You got it. You kind of got it wrong, but it's like whatever. It's fine. Well, this is probably gonna be like
I need a drink. Yeah, I don't know what the snacks cost you. We haven't paid for anything yet. Hello
I don't think that's really appropriate to do. I mean this isn't your house
There's somebody got a knife just sitting there
That does seem a little fucking dangerous i'm not gonna lie. I don't think I don't want to touch that
Is it
The brothers
Stop stop talking about college. It's fucking over. I'm 38. You're 34. Like just don't work it forget about it. Okay
All right, everybody don't talk about college all I hear about is college college college, man
I've been a banker for fucking 10 years
Yeah, I mean you're off the rep
And i'm telling you that as somebody somebody that was friends with you like eight years ago
I haven't talked to you, but maybe I invited you on facebook
Well, not not here
All right, let's get out let's see this is not even enough in here let's get out of here
Yes, I got married bullshit. What?
Somebody's got a halloween costume on a lot of you guys are in halloween costumes. What the fuck is this?
Costume I would I would have come with my jack sparrow costume, you know, I drink a little bit of fucking rum, you know what I'm saying?
Where did this weirdo guy go?
Where the hell are we joe? I don't know
Who knows what i'm looking for here?
Whoa, whoa, whoa easy somebody's got a gun
I got a laser for this gun. What are you talking about?
All right. All right. I'm just saying but you can't point that at people. You don't think easy
Okay, i'll keep pointed down holster that shit man. You can what the fuck is happening here? What the fuck?
I'm getting fucking bonus. You know what I mean? Like give me a break
Hey, hey, come here
Hey
Did you look in him?
Who look no don't lock me in here. I don't want to be I don't want to be here alone
Close the fucking door
Where the fuck even are we you what do you know? What where the wait? What why are you looking at me like that?
What what's going on here? I came in here and I was looking out the window
He fought
Okay
It looks like the police arrived and the murderer was caught
Uh
Wait, did I run out of time?
What I was gonna kill that guy
That was it. I thought oh my god. Okay
I spent so much time talking about my fucking body. I had to wait the entire time. I was gonna tell him
I was gonna kill him. I was
Is it
You ran the clock out nothing no one got killed I can't believe nobody got what a bad murderer whoever you were you
Bad at your fucking job
Are you the murderer murder
I'm okay with being alive
Yeah, hey
Step on the other circle
Switch to avatars and it won't work. Otherwise
Can I let me see that
I know
Do causing magazines and shit, you know magazine magazines and fucking doctor sucks
Oh god
I just killed eric
Yeah, no, I mean
I think I think I burn eyes a fair trade on this. I think that was a little bit ridiculous
Guns are made of steel
Mothers, thank you very much. What did you say about my mother?
My mother oh you're talking about my mother now, that's what it is. Can you give me the gun? Let me try
Driving fast fucking cars
I admire you
Actually good performance though, are they I thought they weren't no they're not a couple of them. I know we're pretty bad
And yeah, it's just all right. Hold on much smoother and everyone remember if you switch avatars you have to step on and off your pedestal
Okay
Okay, uh fighters and kibo are the same
Uh avatar. Yeah. No my brother. Wait, what where have you been? Oh, we switched to the default avatars. Okay
Fine that's the way it's gonna be
Yeah, all these yeah, we're all default right now
Everybody's just gonna have a big day
And barbara tron here to cut hair you don't have any you're fine fucking
All right, raise your hand if you haven't watched it before you're my guy you're my guy now, okay
No, i'm not doing the boston's fucking thing again. We did that's too much
Play is required. I think we've just started appearing. It's something don't know what happened. Something happened. What happened?
if br chat
Did you not make it in kibo?
Maybe if we could get saws
Maybe if we could get started maybe because it gets on
Maybe if we can get started, isn't it?
Maybe if we could get cars. No, don't say cars
Oh fuck
I'm going in what is this dark souls? He attracted the bonfire. Come on, man
Doxels
I don't know what that was. All right
And okay
Okay
I came to life from
Down to stairs. I just came to life up there. Oh, yeah, dude. Sick costume, man. Where are you from party city?
That's sick. No
Wait, sorry what maya i'm from the ancient city of maya
Oh, yeah, yeah, she's hot dude, you should totally ask her out
Did raise to about 140 degrees every so often you're
I said i've been standing up there as a statue for 2000 years
Like the earth hasn't even been around for like 2000 years now, where are you on?
You're okay. Oh, yeah, it seems uh at this point here
You're kind of just squatting dude, it's oh got it
Where the hell did you come from?
New technological weather
You got like blueberries all over you like rotten blueberries, it's kind of gross
Have you considered like cleaning up yourself like can you can you even see out of your eyes?
It looks like someone like bugshot you in the face with like a shotgun and like you live and that's kind of wild
That's kind of hot actually
Correction his name is
The blue man
I'm making my way. We're fine. Are you like talking from a mile away? I cannot hear you, man
I
The rp is fun, but we really need to focus on the whole murder thing because it just ends abruptly every time
Right does it end
That was fun, I like that
Where's my wine
Why do you have a rifle
You're like
Do you know how to turn off the name plates above people yeah, okay, okay
We should just all be the same avatar so we don't know who the murderer is
Congratulations
In like 10 minutes, uh, yeah
Like
You can also
Underscores more spaces
My is uh, I I didn't I didn't even say
All right, hey
Why do you only
Hey
What are you doing here? What's going on here?
Well, i'm looking for these little pieces of paper that you just you just you just ran in this room and you decided to come
And we would you didn't want to talk to any of the guests. You just want to run here and look for a night
No, I don't want
You sure you're not trying to get that yeah
I'm sure just looking for some of you eat. I guess I don't know. Okay. Okay. I respect that
Uh, there's no no food in somebody's bookcase. I don't know if you know that
All right, I suppose you're right. I I don't know
I'm gonna go ahead and close this door real quick. So it's uh, nice and private in here
Um, if if if anyone was to grab a knife at this point and try to kill me
They would have a pretty good opportunity. I don't think that would be there
No, what are you doing here?
Anyways, you have fun in this room i'm gonna leave. Yeah
Yeah
No, no, no, no
Hey, that's him. That's the guy. That's the guy
That's the guy I saw a knife a knife just fell a knife just fell and I added his pocket
It fell right there look at exhibit a get back get back in there exhibit a slowly back exhibit a right there
What?
It wasn't even him we can see an overhead view of what everyone's doing. Oh my god
Probably bern was a murderer
Oh god, I I
It was it was iq
If I didn't have my followers support
Well, thanks. Thank you for telling me that I gained a follower that was pretty sick
It really gave me the motivation to carry on. You know, like I do
I'll follow you. I'll follow you. What's your twitch? What is it? What's your twitch? Yeah, it's my sub bro 24
I ain't gonna follow you
What
I love
Fulfill yourself
I throw a fastball at 90 miles an hour
Response you are not buff enough to
Um, so come on now
All right
For her involving that'd be amazing
Excuse me
Everybody in the living room living room living room living room living room living room living room living room living room living room now
All of you
If you're not in the living room in 10 seconds, you're dead 10 9 8 7 6 5 4. There you go
Good work on that one. Okay, everybody in the living room
Living room now, sir living room in here now living room living room now you living room get in the living room now
Hey, hey
This is more of an entrance way than a living room
Good point. I need everybody in the living room. I need to give you a one minute briefing
Okay
Shut up
He just picked up the knife I got fucking kicked out
I didn't get banned
He picked the knife up
That's that's the killer, right?
That was that was that's what that means
That was an rtm
I saw a knife in his hand. So I had to instantly shoot him
Innocence can pick them up. No, they can't
Innocence cannot pick up knives
Oh my god
Let's go back
No, I got it right. He picked the knife up. It just I
reacted
uh
A thousand iq play
I was gonna make them all sing
I was gonna make them all sing and if they didn't whoever was out of key died
Try all right, let's go
Hold on
Yeah, if there's like a family few that would be so much fun
Or even like a jeopardy or something
quite banned
Say what?
All right glue man
uh
We had a little bit of an issue
Issues my cord has kind of gone crazy
Kiwo
Q r s
Q
Ah, this is so awesome though. It really is
This like this took time and work. This is like bravo. This is fucking amazing
I just I want to just pancake somebody in the face, you know, like just like
floss as glue man
No, no, i'm not gonna do that. Look at these muscles. They're just fucking huge
They ain't left to get to go
Oh dab. Oh, wait, this is a new room. Oh, this is new
I got booted
I need to take a seat
Is that pen control?
Clear pens just
Oh, it's in these
You can draw here
What?
Pens are we gonna are we gonna do like a big giant drawing?
Oh, whoa, that's cool
Yeah, play Pictionary
um
We could do we could do Pictionary
That'll be fun
Oh, why am I so shaky?
This is so sad
This is any time I try and draw in br. I'm just
Yeah, I guess it's because you don't have anything to steady your hand on
That's so sad
pizza
It's uh
It's a it's a man who's dead inside
There he is
I drew you
Oh
That looks great
Oh, wow. Good job
Don't mind if I do
Well, that's that's actually really really good
We should be
Me
Oh now it feels like i'm in school
Take it
Just everyone doing arts and crafts around the table
It's just me score
Oh, look at that. Look at that. Well done. Look at you go. It's a bicycle
That's what it is. What is it? It's just me
And it's my school
Oh
What are you doing to the school?
That research
I think he's gonna grow up to be an artist
Okay
Yeah, yes
What can I help you with? Would you like a juice box?
Yes, and
Hey scary from
Cookie cute, right?
well, um
Sweetie, we might have to use the power of imagination
for juice box
Oh those
Those cookies
Oh
Oh, yeah, do you like the raisin the raisin ones? No, no, no, no, no the chocolate
I think they ate a crayon
It's
Right don't don't do don't get don't get it down your face your parents will be livid
ma'am
She's not here yet. Oh
After school
Okay
Do you want me to show her your work bathroom?
Right. Um, okay
Help help help
Will you hold his hand and take him to the bathroom, please? Okay
Please
Okay party
Okay, let's go. Let's go. Let's go. It's back here. It's back here
Uh right right on this that's the toilet
just uh
That's that's the that's the urinal. That's not the toilet. That's
That's like that over like here like that's like the toilet. You're kind of pulling your pants down for the urinal
What have you done
Sweetie you've made a bit of a mess on the chest there. Haven't you there's glue everywhere?
Okay, my picture
My picture see you next time
See you next time. Thank you for hanging out
Nice to meet you
Yeah, keep up the good artwork, man
Okay, i'm gonna go wash this off now
die
You you you ruined my picture though
Well, I don't think I did because as you see here you had some line work that I needed to fix for you
And the hair was a little too messy figured maybe I would like change it out of the kind of the toupee scenario here
The eyes were a little off
If you look at it from like a different sort of angle, you know, like yeah from like this side
Like you'd understand like the line work is done like it's sort of my style i've done here like specifically that I wanted to beat you
I'm like, yeah, it's supposed to look precise angle
Yeah, well look at the look of mine, I see that I I take a lot of influence
I think my jack uh, pollock is my influence here. So that's probably what I was doing
Any chance on that that cookie and juice box you mentioned earlier? I just was
Wait, sorry. Sorry about that. You mentioned like I made I asked for like a cookie and we were talking about it for a little bit
so
Um, oh, yeah
It's more about um, like expressing yourself and have you ever seen the movie hook?
Yeah, oh, yeah
And they all think about they'll think about like what they're gonna eat and it looks like play-doh and you try to eat the play-doh
And then you realize it's disgusting and yeah, you look like a twat in front of all your friends
Yeah, it's just like that
Juice box nice man. Now you speak my language. Where where are we at?
Right here right here right here. Let me come over. Yeah
Hey
Yeah, yeah, yeah, right you see right here you see you're inside of it like this right here that's the juice
Ah, yeah, it's delicious. They're very very good. There's a there's a cookie right here as well
Get move go get away get away from me
Let's give you a cookie
He's possessive. It's like a dog get away from me
Is there jeopardy or like wheel of fortune or like family food wheel of fortune is there actually
Okay, um these guys play
A lot if you if you want to find an old game show we uh, normally it's stuff like hot potato
Oh, really?
The grenade oh potato is awesome though. That's so much fun
Yeah
That's the grenade we'll play hot potato with a with with a grenade
I think that would be kind of cool. Is it past the grenade?
If you just search grenade, you'll probably find it. Let me see. I'm running out of gas
Literally just pass the grenade. Okay. Oh, there it is
Yeah, uh whenever y'all are this is the one
Wait, let's do it
Poor babysitter. That's so fucking fun
Well that last thing made some sense though
I don't know what I hit my hand on. I don't remember how this works
Pick up the grenade and it starts a timer, right?
Yeah, and then you'll have to like just
Throw it to each other pick it up and throw it again. It's hot potato iq don't touch anything template. Okay
Don't do it
Is it gonna hurt you?
So it's hot potato with a grenade
I don't think we really need to read the rules for it as well. It's uh, pretty yeah, but pretty self-explanatory
Going in one direction it's nice to go around. Okay
You get away from that
Let's pick a number
10 yeah pick a number
Fuck we don't need numbers. We never we never did. No, we don't. Oh, you don't need numbers
Be bad, okay
Oh, we are we start who's is it like dodgeball
Oh you I think the only rule is you can't pass it back to the same people
Oh
You just killed it
How do I grab it
It's stuck on it's yours you get it. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
You just held
You just held a cannon at the back of your head and just like shot yourself
What the fuck?
Uh, here we go
Uh
It's closer to you. It's closer to you. It's closer to you closer to you take it
Oh, that's that's gonna throw it. That's hey, no, no, no
I'm gonna knock something over. Did I spill something on the desk? I might have how would you do this to me?
Well, I mean if you want it
Oh god, oh god, no, hi
Oh shit, come on. Oh my god. I can't throw up save my life
Wait, why didn't you die?
Sorry, I hit my hand
You can get that
Oh, that's bullshit
That's bullshit
God
Why that wasn't right that was cheating
That was a quarter of a second timer
That was I guess that was it tides winner. Yeah. Congratulations
This cord is giving me problems
Trying to kick it
Wait, it's going already. Oh my fucking god. Come on, man. Holy shit there goes
Sometimes you gotta just go for it, right? Oh the softball windmill technique
Um, it's not gonna like baseball
That's I'll get it I'll get it what is called a circle i'm pulling like catch outside without
Oh hits the skybox shit
Wait, is this me versus me?
Why did it kill you anybody thirsty
I could take that off your hands if you don't want
I fucked up the game though. I think I should be the one that sits it up
Why it won't let me die
I don't understand. I'm trying to get rid of i'm trying to eliminate myself
I'm seriously trying to eliminate myself. Oh what what?
Sorry, my arms are too strong. I shouldn't throw that far
Uh
He could never throw it it's it always just like freezes two seconds in front of his face
Oh fancy
That's the technique he just walks it over
All right, so what happens if uh, if if nobody goes near it does it just pick a random person I must
In fact, did your voice get deeper again
Why
Sounds like it is
I think josh maybe I think he's trying to
Good throw
Yeah, it's the high arching throws. Those are the ones that matter. I don't know. I won't stop
I'm just kind of drifting in space right now. I don't know
All right, I got good hands I got it coming to you by the way coming to you
You just want to make that
What
Why what are you still alive? I don't why am I I have it? Okay. Um
Oh my god, I didn't even touch it
Good thing I had my fraps open. Oh god
I don't
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I'm going I'm going over there
Oh
You could do the
Is it who does it explode everyone
Where is it
All right, put put it down on the center and everybody just go stare at it see what happens
We're all waiting for like the microwave for a pasta to be done
We set the timer to like four minutes
I remember what's going on right now. I just came back. What's uh waiting for don't you see?
Okay watching a watermelon
Why
I love it so much. All those are so don't do don't oh, where'd it go? Oh
It was set up perfectly too
Here here here here just there. Oh, it's falling over
Please we're using our force
On the monkey get it
Like physically grab it
This is nature this happens in nature
I died
That was pretty sick that was actually really cool that was really cool
Throw that up there get him get him you can do it
Oh
Why is it not exploded
Why why why did it take so long?
Hey, how's it going?
My god, this is insane. No, no someone take this, please. I'll take a look and see if there's game show stuff
Hey, it's mine
Yeah, you're gonna figure they have like jeopardy or sorry like a knockoff, right?
Sure
Hey
Yeah, you can get rid of this grenade some search jeopardy i'll be right back I got I got my mission
Say goodbye is there a way to search game moves?
Um, you just have to search through the worlds with the search icon up at the top right, but okay, let's see like
You have to be facing where you want to place the portal for the record
Oh, okay, just try to put it on the glass and sometimes it doesn't like that. Oh, you all found something
Oh my god, are you serious?
Hey, can I have that back now? Yeah, absolutely
This is my realm this is where I belong
All right, yeah, that's right. That's right. That's right. That's right
Hey you
How do you get in here
Yeah, you can jump like that
Can you let go through these um, you gotta use a bit of imagination like, you know, just like
Like that, you know, well hold on i'm having trouble here
I thought that was I thought that was me
I swear to god. I thought that was me on screen. I was like what the fuck is going on. Why is that here?
I thought it was me
All right
You gotta do a royal rumble
Oh, I was gonna give you a high five
Oh, I got teleported outside the map there. I thought that I thought that was a twinkie. I thought that was a twinkie avatar
What is that? Oh, I i'm gonna i'm gonna hurt myself. So i'm gonna I gotta like untangle this hold on give me one sec
All right, guys all that's uh gonna do this entrance go back there
Excuse me
Look at this. It's like it's gonna be spinning like crazy
It could be want to untangle please
Oh, yeah, so well it comes in one at a time
I'm sorry. I'm probably making a ton of noise
All right, let me see if I can get someone else
I will get hurt if this doesn't become untangled
You see the guy breaks his arm in vr if I don't fucking do this
Found a custom game show map. All right, cool
Am I muted? Oh fuck i'm not
Okay
Okay, so um
Are you going to be pulling the contestants out one at a time? What is wrong with his legs?
Something going on there
All right, so I had to take my headset off. All right. So what you want?
Can everybody hear me?
Yeah, if you get thrown
Was it oh
There's a game show world and you can make your own game shows and if the contestants lose they drop through a hole in the
Floor. Oh, that's fucking hilarious. We definitely have to try that
um
I that i'd love that i'm talking so much
So if you get it's getting thrown over the top rope is elimination, right?
I mean, that's just the way it is. Yeah, however, you know, you get eliminated every like minute or two. Somebody else can get called out
Who wants to be like the person that's doing that who wants to call everybody out?
Who wants to wrestle?
We'll probably be the first to die
Yeah, the only thing I said is we can't hear from all the way down there. So it's it's gonna be
Back here. Yeah. Yeah
There's no referee one though. I don't know how we all just go in at the same time
We all get into our intros at the same time
So everybody come back in the entrance
They all come out at the same time
Yeah, it's a big performance you better be ready
Play like every wwe thing. Yeah, every theme song has to be played. They're all you're all competing
Uh, does everybody have like just a mess they can play
All right, we ready ready to do this yeah, so everybody that wants to wrestle come back here because we'll all just walk out
I don't know if they can hear you
Hello, hey, okay, so you guys don't want to wrestle with who wants to like be in the ring
Okay, you're the rep so all right, so we only have four people five people
This is one of those like you go you go to like the local high school right and like this
This is like the indie wrestling troupe
Here we go. It's a royal rumble with five fucking jobbers
All right, you ready? All right
We're ready to do our intro. We're like coming out as a tag team
Well, actually you two go first then and we'll come behind you like we'll wait like
All right, can we get the music please
All right, here we go
Three two one. Come on out here over there
My audience that's right. Let me tell you something
When I get in that ring
You're booing you're booing me
You're all booing me
Just wait till I get in that room
Hey
I love you too. Please get in your corner, sir
Can you please put that down sir, sir? Can you please put that down?
Sir, can you please put that down? Oh my god
Is this like tag like two people versus two people or are they just coming in weirdly?
You're trying to make the actual like animations from the game here
No, I'm doing a thing with like they cut to me and I you can't see what i'm saying, but i'm just screaming and pointing
Hey
Hey, hey, hey, you can't hey get in here. Why don't you get in here and talk shit?
Hey, well looks like you and me the only ones in here
There's all kinds of stuff in here
All right. I'm ready
Can we get the starter or what?
Get in your corner, please
Weighing up a lot. It's glue man. That's right. It's me glue man
Coming from the east side of the ring weighing in at 10 pounds mac in socks
You're gonna say your quote
Okay
That's bullshit
All right beat the shit out of each other now
That's illegal
Get him out of the ring
All right. Hey, hey, this is what wrestlers do. Hey, this is what wrestlers do i'm gonna i'm gonna give you a ddt
That's what they do
Hey ddt
Give me the trash
I'm crazy. I'm crazy. I'm fucking crazy. I would say
A bloody pulp he needs a he needs a medic man's doing I think he's got an ankle cramp. I think he's fallen
It's time to pin him
Get something to pin glue man
one
two
three
four
five six
seven eight nine
ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen
You see how fucked up I am I told you I was insane
Don't you know it's like 30 seconds to pin somebody
All right
He's dead he's dead he's out he's dead just you and me
Oh, yeah, what's going on with you belt's gonna be hold on with me
you missed
Almost I thought about it. All right. Hey boxing match clean
Time out he wants to time out. Okay
One two three four
Like
Shit you fucked up audience
Are you gonna boo me stinky peas was attempting to escape the ring
Are you booing me you
Not until the end i'm trying to hit that guy in the audience right he was born
Okay, okay off the ropes
Okay
I'm kidding. Okay, you can have back what this guy's doing. He threw it. He killed seven people during the match
You have fun. Have a good time. It's very fun
Oh god this guy eating
This guy's projectile throwing up into his hands. Look at him. That's what's happening
You're standing on a chair dumb dumb and question is what error is just taking him
On
Look behind the entrance what's behind the entrance? Oh my goodness
Raw is war over that show
They still do raw
behind the entrance
What is what's back here?
Their challenger has entered the ring
I don't know who the hell he is
Hey
What
Everybody give him your money. Hey, I'll have you know. Hey, hey pal. I won that belt
You want to eat this bro?
Yeah, it looks pretty tasty
Can you hear me there's somebody in the ring waiting for you
tired
from like the like I think this is like the
Like the southeastern side of the ring
Some absolute jackass
I don't think he's ready to fight exactly yet
It's very intense the aroma here is very intense it smells like sweat
We need to know what the hell they're doing at this point. They're supposed to be fighting but they're just looking at each other really intensely
That's like half of wrestling
He's bouncing off the belts
Oh
Oh trash
What the hell is going on your face like doing a whale's impression lately or
All right, wait, what was the game show I want to get I want a juice box
You should be able to find it, but I don't know where you all went. What was it called?
It was like zanus game show or something. I don't remember zanus. Okay
I don't know. It's not for the x
I am so tired
Zenu zenu is it does it come up you just do a game show game show is one word. Yeah. Yeah zenu zenu's game show
And if you just uh hit like invite plus or whatever and hit drop portal you should be good
You find you found the map right yeah new instance, uh, yeah new instance and then said um, I guess what invite plus probably
Plus
Yeah
Is she oh she's is she mankind oh, all right, hold it
Tied a shoe
Ladies and gentlemen, it's cactus jack
Oh, yes, okay, so i'm feeling a lot of facial hair we got a really hairy one here today
Uh joker comes up
They have nothing to do with the cactus I don't get with the name at all
He's from Arizona, okay. Okay close enough
I still feel like it's a bit of a stretch personally
We don't need your rp criticism here
It's not a very good name
You could have at least like you could have worn green or something. Oh my god
Joke slam
Oh
This is the best interview for wwe i've ever heard
Cactus jack
About me
So cactus heard you have a little bit of a problem down here, but uh, what's going on with the uh, the wardrobe here
I mean it
I I I was I I mean you're peeing your pants or something or other
I was like, yeah, you know the show must go on, you know, this is true. There are no bathrooms back there. So
Yeah, I think i'm gonna be um
You know, i'm gonna be winging it. I'm probably gonna throw the match anyway, because I should
You know, it's not because i'm not uh, you know, i'm a capable fighter and everything and
Cactus jack that guy why are you gonna throw the fight?
Because I need a wave
Oh, well that makes complete sense you have to go to the bathroom so
Why not just lie down let him pin you and then go i'll go to the bathroom that sounds like a good idea
My drop
All right, you guys want to do the game show
It's the crow
Cactus jack the jobber
All right, we're ready to go to xenu's whatever it is
Game show is what it's called. If you search the game show it'll come up. Yeah
Should I do this because I only have like three people out of here?
Um, I could do it
Okay, well, or do you want to make the game show match?
Drop down on somebody
Anyone want some all right get on the table get on the table scouts
Sit on it josh, it's like the old g-mod video
Kind of worked for us. Oh jesus that table murdered another audience member josh. Hold still
There we go, you need one with a seat all right section get one of your avatars with a seat
Uh, you did like this is really fun force awakens force awakens. Oh, I can't wait
There's a portal in the ring
Okay, this is the game show i don't buy this to me on that one it was a shitty dumb reference
It's good
Oh, there's rules here's rules. I'll show you guys how this works. It's really simple back until the game is over
When there are two people left use questions with two possible answers that explains it pretty well
Control board here
so if everybody comes onto this side
You get dropped and then um the the the runner of the show stands on this side
Don't press any buttons yet, and then you can you can close the the host wall here
So once you hit that one
Nobody can walk in between the host side and the game side
And this and then this audience button closes the audience off so they can't come back into the game
interesting then basically what you do is like you say like
You say a multiple choice question with everybody standing out here and the answer is either a b or c
and then
You select the correct answer. Let's say it was a boom
Everybody except for a falls through and then they spawn back on the audience side
So you have to come up with your own questions. There's no like built-in questions
Yeah, and there's actually there's a there's a reset button after you do that that resets it and then the music button
You can kind of use that as a timer once the music ends then you can hit the button
Locks everybody in so like
When you hit cage nobody else can choose an answer so if they either chose the wrong one or they can't switch last
So you get a couple people to be hosts if you want and then yeah, it's really fun
I mean I could pull up like halo trivia or something. Yeah, I think I think like
It might be more fun to have like actual trivia questions rather than like video game trivia or something
What's my aunt's name? Is it like mary? Uh, you know
It's probably better with like actual
Get out of me ty
No, hey, I thought you didn't want to hear me say that
Halo trivia, I never even played halo
I've never even opened the game miss
What would be a fun trivia set?
Oh, I don't like diablo by diablo 2 maybe diablo 3 diablo 2
Sit down today and write some diablo 2 trivia questions. Yeah. Yeah, what's the last boss of the game fucking bail? Come on
Oh, I remember bail oh qo's here qo you want to see how to run the game, okay
The host stands on this side
And everybody else stands over there. So everybody come stand over here right now and the great I get my face
I like feel my face peeling off
Okay, what's two plus two is that a sonic character this is a character sonic right crocodile
Wait, what was the question?
You don't know the answers the correct answer was
Oh
All right sick real simple
Let me see if I can find some generic ass trivia
Yeah, like how many ounces is in like a quarter or something, right?
epic
trivia questions
Somebody say ass trivia
Oh, these are some 1990 us trivia, all right, you're ready
Studio audience
Good good luck out there. Mr. Taker. Is that is that right?
kane's, uh, i'm taker's brother kane
Close it up very close. Okay. Thank you
I don't know anything
You just yeah, you just said the voldemort
You just said the voldemort word
Wait a minute are you
Here's your first question
What is the only us state that only borders one other
Is it a?
Rhode island
b
maine
Or c washington
I don't even remember what they I don't remember what you said
Oh, no, there's more people on that side
I'm pretty sure we lost this one
Don't worry, you know, we're not only touching match. Jesus don't work
Well, I guess you tried
I spent a little time in new england
That's
Well, I guess that was our round i'm just gonna have a little sit down. Yeah, let's do that
Oh, that's that guy
I didn't know it was him though
I was going up to him like oh, I really love your game. Oh, it's really great
Is this they're talking about pharaoh height like the asshole I am
David cage, how is he? What was it like? Oh shit
I'm about to get a hot dog. What was the question? It's hard to hear it over here
I want an ice cream
Wow
Just like high school i'm just choosing multiple choice questions randomly it's awful, this is terrible. Hey, but you're still doing all right
You're still doing okay
Where's my first one? Don't talk to us. Why is a german doing so at us trivia?
I don't know. He studied it
Shut your mouth
It's always safe
My god, I lied you broke your back i'll be all right. I'll take a little bit. I'll be broken up behind like two hours
All right
Um
What
I can't tell
I'm gonna be i'm gonna be good this time
Kind of trivia or do you want to go to the line king land one more round he had the trivia pulled up one more
Is there like twitch trivia or something
But those questions are gonna be about ninja or something I get some of these are so hard
It's gonna be like generic you did but you crashed your victory was you
Wow
What's my cat what's my parents name no wait, that's not
I don't want to be inside your face b
Jeff see peter griffin that's definitely not peter griffin. It is absolutely not peter griffin
Is this a bird
Not my parents
Okay, okay, I do not you are all crazy there is no d it's a b c why do you keep saying d
Because it could be a third it could be a fourth option for b
Well, it doesn't matter because all of them are fake i'm gonna go get actual facts now
His real name is kiwi
So we didn't even have an option
What the heck
He tried to kill us everybody thought he said that
I cannot find my phone. So i'm just going to use my nintendo dsi browser. Hold on nintendo ds
You're gonna use your nintendo ds browser, I don't think that even existed
What the fuck
All right, all right, okay, what is the first ingredient
in
hagan does
ice cream first
vanilla
Is it a
shortening
b
milk
or c
Vanilla extract
What's the question you're not even the host you're absolutely crazy crazy right now i've walked in from the audience and just decided
start
I'm sorry that didn't i'm sorry. It was not real
Sorry
What is the color of spyro's wings
B purple or c orange
I've never played spyro. All right. I've never played spyro the dragon. I think he's voiced by eliza wood in the later ones
Yeah
I like his cameo in spike it's 3d
I would have got this one. I would have got that one. I don't I don't I don't know
What
So, what's the uh, what's this lion king map
Oh nice
It's party time
After this i'm probably gonna have to get out of the vr for a little bit i'm getting fucking tired
elder scrolls 5
My hair is insane right now
Yeah, after like the wrestling shit
I'm like my soul is sapped in my body. Is this as big as it looks?
It is pretty big and I remember there's different areas, too
Really?
So it's not actually as big as it looks but it's open world
I'm still cain
cain in the lion king
Oh god
Why these in the game oops what happened what I
I dropped I dropped simba
I do the thing i'll do the thing in a minute the thing is but
We can't rule out drop kicking off the cliff
Okay, you go like that, right?
Wait, yeah. Yeah, just do that. Oh actually we might be able to
um
You know what?
I think there's something better for that. Where's ace j i'll get him into his little mickey and you can hold him up
So we don't need these is what you're saying
Yeah, you know, okay
God damn it, man. I'm not ready for this
I'm too tired for this one
Oh
This is kind of like fucked up shit. Everybody does in this game
Welcome to pride rock
This is this is fucking too much
If you hold your arm out like a like a falcon cape, they'll climb up you
Posing a climb up on me
I think he ran into a wall below. Oh kiss the ring kiss the ring
Wait walk to the front here walk to the front the very edge
He's coming
What am I doing?
He's already climbing you just don't realize that he's already climbing you he's already
What what oh he doesn't even he's already on your body
This is like I feel like I ain't for an errand i'll be back
Wait, wait, did you say that? I didn't say that
He's trying to clear out some phlegm out of his throat
Jesus
Can we hold here like there we go. There we go. Okay, i'm gonna turn you around turn you around like baby simba
ah
I feel like i'm changing channels like just channel surf
Like thousands of channels like I just saw like two tv shows three tv shows at the same time
Hey andy's dead
There's too many television channels playing at the same time. There's like mickey monsters simba. There's a lion king
There's heavy there's tf2. There's flying brats
Um, there he goes up he goes be free simba
Be free
Found you
Come with me little guy. Let's go
There right there right there
Going in circles
Where where are you?
I can't it's like that's that's the way my dog looks at me
It's seriously that's like the way that's the way my dog looks at me right before he gets food
It's it's hard
Down here cool. Oh, that's interesting
He goes he's nesting
I don't know why you didn't move the arm
Oh, you didn't have to I know but it's like I have I have my brain has to do it
So I can um, and I know have you done the vr case files yet?
What
Can you hold your hand out for a minute hold your hand out? Oh shit. I have this up. Can you help me out?
What this is screwed up y'all. I need some help
What the fuck is happening in my life
I'll get him hit. I should have lost some weight get out from there
Great avatar
That's I can't I have nothing to even say that's unbelievable. What the fuck
That was unfucking unbelievable
Why is that's phil margera?
I know that that's bam margera's dad
Why is that avatar in the game?
Why would somebody's an avatar in the game?
I just
Phil margera
Is it on the toilet come on crazy god
What is all the way down there just keep going and then you find out
Oh god
You gotta you gotta push your joystick further and further really fast. Just keep spamming it forward, but not super duper fast
Okay
This music just doesn't fit for all the characters that are here
This this is like a big mmo I feel like we're going to fight boss
Oh
We could
Yeah
Go do the boss fight
I don't know if it's working the one. Let's see. Yeah, but that's the old one of um
What is this world mark looks it just looks like there's items over there there's gonna be like some poles and shit
The lion king it's wonderful. I gotta say my favorite lion king is two or is it is it one and a half?
There's a second lion king
It's a good one
One and a half is my favorite. You can't change that. I know they made like four aladins that went right to the like bin
I'm like a 10 foot tall monster and you're very tiny you guys haven't seen very many like animated genie avatars actually now I'm thinking about it
Yeah, where's like where's the genie?
Like, you know, i'm running quickly
Tracer doesn't like really run quickly though. She teleports
It's really it's just a safari this is like oh here we are
This is just a disney walkthrough
This is a disney land disney world
Disney that's I think it's insane
This is a punimotala
We've seen the whole movie now
He's fucking t-posing, right?
Of course
Don't do it
I feel like it was monkey
What is that character
Sooner or later, you're gonna be able to experience the whole movie in the movie
Are we making another deal?
You're gonna get a load of a vr lion king and just walk around in the whole movie
Where's josh at where is where's josh he's up in the sky
Oh needs
Hey
Supposed to be here
Oh
He's coming back he's climbing back something scared him I think something scared him
Can you give me a toot?
With your big your big thing your horn you got that on that avatar. Yeah
It's a boss
It's the it's the boss. It's the boss of lightning
Let's do this. Wait, I need to sharpen first
It's it's a wall here
I feel like i've not even existing anymore. I've been going on for like five hours at my brain
He's on a mission
I'm kind of just I feel like i'm just the camera here. I don't have my blood is like turning into like plasma
just
Hey play
Play the brown note
A meager offering pick me up pick me up
What it became a pig look at how terrified he is
That was a laughing scared crying face
You just shot put him over the horizon
Oh, this is fucking ridiculous
I'm just painting over here and you're just like, yep
That was fucking amazing, I think i'm gonna have to take a break though
I am oh my god. No, I just no no
No
That's a mickey mouse costume that you didn't inflate yet
That's an inflatable mickey mouse costume
Exist anymore. What is it? Oh
Favorite dreams
Just a word of warning this is a this is a fever dream. Oh god
As if any of this wasn't
Is this what we're going out on
Is this am I am I is this gonna like
Hack into my brain and kill me
Oh god
Have you guys been to like any actually pretty maps today
Make sure you have the sound effect loud enough to hear the song like like a magic. It's like the history of disney on
one place
And you gotta remember when you're going through all this somebody took the time to find all these pictures and manually like place them
around this map
Somebody eating shit, what is that? Okay
No, no
None of this is none of this is
That's like if they made a mortal kombat version of donald duck new mortal kombat 11 characters
You gotta have all this I like that boy at hand
Okay, we can we should find the window this is it it's like a more not I feel like we have I feel like we have to see
The rest you need to get to the park
These frames oh my god these frames all your frame rate bad they're like
Yeah
Yeah, if it's too bad we can find another map no
Whoa monkey that's fucking scary
Hi, welcome to chile's
Welcome to the cult of mickey. Oh
He's dead
What is this
Again, oh, yeah, they have the gas masks up ahead. Oh, that's weird. Ah, the floor is moving
No, it's not you didn't see that. It's not oh that's
Oh the gas masks, yeah, the mickey mouse gas
Oh god, oh no, hey, it's not the the boar mickey. I'm upside down
What am I what did I pick what am I you're the the pumba mickey
So what's what the fuck? Oh, why why am I upside down?
Don't click me don't don't don't don't don't don't click it'll make you sick. I mean it looks
What I can't I i'm broken
Oh, no, no, no, what did you do
Oh, no
I work on him because he he doesn't have full body. So looks fine on you
Fine being a relative. What do I what do I look like?
Do you have the camera?
Which camera should I put?
Uh, do the stream camera or or the photo camera either one
Oh, he doesn't know yeah, you have to explain how the whole like reposition, you know, right now just you look good
How do I selfie cam?
Uh
You picked me because I was upside down
Yeah, hey
Oh god
All right, perfect
I don't like this
I mean, yeah
The selfie cam got like a lot of features, but it could be kind of hey. Hey straight is the seat work on that still?
I can't seem to grab it
Open your menu. Yeah
Yeah, yeah
Uh, don't go straight take a left here if you go straight at the trap
Get stuck
What is happening makes the effect that you're running really fast big foot. Oh my god
I'm big foot. I'm the sasquatch
What's going on? He's the sasquatch. You got like a
Pelican mouth
Bite him bite him bite his head
Fight him
Hey arnold i'm stuck like this i'm stuck with this life. Yeah, I don't know
I don't like this
I think the music stopped your car. Yeah, I think we took too long getting through it
I'm trying to drink my tea and you're killing me. I'm sorry
Hey, you could get on my back if you needed a ride
You click up near his head you should have a seat right around his back right here
Oh
Oh my god, I was gonna throw up if I sit on there for more than 10 seconds
Oh my god, I was attached to your head and moving around with your head
You're gonna jump away
I couldn't do it. It was like I was underwater being shook. I just shook around
um
Be careful don't don't fall somebody's a tree now
They're all it's this corner he thought he'd have the like
If you fall it's over is it wrong that I that I want it to be
It gets skinnier and skinnier what how are you supposed to do this?
I've been thrown everywhere. I'm stuck am I stuck? What are you doing? What are you doing to me?
I'm nearly back. Come on. There we go
I feel like I just i'm about to get birthed. We're like we're traveling through this is what it looks like when you're a baby and you're getting born
This is like blood-borne level of like hunter's dream
Why am I holding my hands out i'm holding them straight up for no reason
Oh, no, I looked behind myself and I fell off
What?
No, I looked behind my
Holy shit, that was scary. Yeah, just so you know, there's really nothing at the end worth seeing
All right
Uh, it's just like a weird temple with with nothing
We need everyone to respond though. I don't want to go all the way back there falling back into mom
Oh my god
All right. I think I think I think i'm done
You're done. All right, I think my brain my brain back here
Let me go i'm gonna fly up and try to see if I can get him to come back. Oh my god
What the fuck? Okay. Wait, what?
No, oh i'm back. Okay, we're back. This is so
This is so this is you know, cool. There wasn't much there
The clubhouse i'm gonna make a um a call somewhere else
I can't be in this for much longer. It's not
Yeah
What do you mean?
Is there a video game first video game that comes to your mind? I want to find a world. Why am I like we'll try here
Oh, yeah, we never did the blood borne one
Oh, yeah. No, I want to see that. I want to see that definitely
Like you're talking about
What no, it's not a birth
No, I was saying like the way that was me that was my fault
That was me I said that
Okay, I thought that your head was the mickey mouse head for a second. I don't know
There is someone
Oh shoot
Okay
Oh, sorry
Yeah, the uh, the frame rate's low because
This uh, this map is just crazy. So
It's a really good map, but it might take a little bit to load. It's like 200 mb
That's all right
hunter's dream
All right. We'll we'll wrap it up here
This has been wild though
I've never seen anything like this before. It's just it
It's like a hangout session
But
I you can just be anything
It's second life but more nuts. Well think about like
these are
I know you can make your own models in something like second life, but these are
They're incredibly detailed. It's not it's they're like actually in-game avatars. It's ridiculous
Isn't second life a little limited with what you can actually make or is it not?
if you missed the gloom ad and the rats and
The germ of pain they were fantastic
I do want to see this though
Any pretty man?
Of course, we fucking know
Oh, hello
Wow, it's a one-to-one
Wow
Oh
You're afraid to explore there's like weapons. I mean, i'm just gonna tell you i'm gonna tell you right now this
Bloodborne is my favorite single. Please. My favorite game ever made
This is this is like seriously hitting some buttons for me. This is hitting some buttons
Here grab this
Take this from me
Are you shitting me?
So cool. Yeah, they have pretty much everything every weapon from the game is
No way
Oh, yeah, you can even get the messages
Oh
It's in the wrong hand I always like to move my great sergeant I made a build just to use this thing
Yeah, I did too
Arcade build arcane
It's one of the only it's one of two weapons
Where are the where are the other weapons?
Let me see there's a ton around them. There's a cannon over here
Can I try this one the rifle spear? This makes me want to play the game. Yeah, let me see. Cool. Thank you
This is cool
Oops
I'm glad I dropped it, but it was really awesome
What just happened if you reach down low enough? Oh, that's the electricity
Place a chalice upon that altar and partake in holy communion. Look at this one. I have no idea if they're good or not
Yeah, that's right. That's the cannon. I'm like, oh my god, this is amazing
Oh, wait, where's garmin is he over there?
What does it say one third to open the gate um, um, some of these maps have puzzles
I remember that thing
Oh, is it a puzzle? Did you play plug one? Oh, no
Oh
Is the best game that's the best game ever made
Well, there's the doll
Why are there like 15 different bobs burgers?
There's so many there's so many bob burgers
That's is it joker bob burger or is that gumby bob burger?
Yeah, there's garmin like you can talk to him he's got like a menu oh really
Hey, oh you just shot him
What the fuck
Oh that stays this is so awesome
What oh, oh, yeah, what's this thing? I think you can grab this
Wow, oh shit. Oh, that's the the car the carthus blade
No, not what cainhurst cainhurst not carthus cainhurst what is carthus
Oh, all right cainhurst, right
I just wanted to spook you with it because I like the blade. It's one of my favorite ones
This carried me through my first playthrough of bloodborne. Oh you you did a you did blood tinge for your first build. That's ballsy
That was about a hundred hours
That was like my first dark souls game too, so I oh god wow
Yeah, doing like a blood tinge build that your first ever dark souls souls light kind of game
That's so cool though
No, it is
Remember that that was the exploding thing
Oh really and that's where I got the avatar this is so cool one's in the house
Oh
Really
I'm gonna see i'm gonna see what they are. Let's do hey, let's do dark souls pvp so we can wait over here
Yeah, thank you for hearing what the heck is oh, yeah
What what's what's why are you flying? What's this? Oh, no
Oh, there we go
I can't go through here and then you click the lantern
For the lamp, you know what I mean? Wait, wait, wait, hold on this thing over here. No, no
Whoa
Oh my god, okay
Maria
You can be a winter lantern. Oh my goodness. Sure
These things were terrifying you can be nickel ash and stuff on
On they have custom animations
Do that?
No, that was bad. You should be able to
get into
Um, like the finger motions like point and finger guns and those kinds of things it'll do different things depending on which one you have
It says on the avatar board
You pick it up
Like this one, but I don't know what they are on a vibe. Unfortunately
This is so cool
Oh poly gas coin
It tells you what weapons they have for like in what gestures correspond. Oh thumbs up. Yeah, I see
Rock and roll hold infant great one
Burly gig saw like this one has a sword
This one has a gun
I can't believe somebody actually made this
It's wild
All right. I think i'm gonna I think i'm gonna
stumble over here
and make my leave
This has been a lot of fun though
Favorite the avatar. That's a good idea
Is it that's what's currently on me right now, right?
That's ridiculous. Yeah
God
Yeah, that's a brain trust for you
You're the winter lanterns
All right. I think i'm I think i'm gonna make my exit
Uh, the ghost can punch you
Thank you guys that was like actual that was like fucking amazing you guys made my first vr chat experience a lot of fun
So, thank you
Wait, where's come back sometime?
Yeah, you guys are all fucking awesome
Thanks for all the tor and
Yeah, for sure you've only you've only scratched the surface too, so I can imagine I can imagine this probably
infinite
Where's uh, where's kimo?
She's over there. I think she's
Oh, right. Oh, yeah, right, right. Let me hold on a second here
Yeah, i'll be like i'll be like a random person i've got talking to you like, uh
Okay, there we go, hey, okay, so how are
Uh, no, thanks for introducing me to everybody. It was it was a lot of fun. Thank you so much
It was fucking hilarious
Um chaos very chaotic controlled chaos controlled chaos
Are you wait, did you drag a bottle of wine? I drank a bottle of wine four days ago
I woke up 12 at 12 pm and I have not eaten and it's like
But i'm gonna take off if you want to do more vr
We'll see you again real soon. We were gonna do a mind show thing, but then this kind of we got into this
Yeah
Yeah, beat saber this happened this happened this did this did happen
Yeah, beat saber was awesome
I'm gonna get addicted to vr. Oh, i'm gonna get the wireless
It's gonna happen welcome to the club welcome to the club, but i'll uh, i'll see you guys later
All right. Thank you guys. Thanks for stopping by
Thank you. Thank you josh
Yeah, i'll get it just so do we have any how do I do that?
Yeah, you might have a lot
Oh
Which in that in that case you can scroll to the very end on the right
It's like in the social menu when you do your oh, okay
Uh, okay. I see I see
All right
That's cool, it just depends on how much you even want to play, uh, who who made the avatars
Uh ace made all pretty much all the one
Thank you, this is so fucking good, man. Thank you
You
Wait is there a fireman avatar? Yeah walking around. Oh my god, can I see it?
Uh, I don't think he's here anymore. Oh, he's not okay. We'll save that for next time
Yep, but take care guys. See y'all next time
I'm gonna do it i'm gonna plug
I'm talking this way the whole time
Oh, man
but no that was um
I did not think that we were gonna be doing that for five and a half hours
But definitely give all those people to follow
all the help from uh
Kiwo kiwo's awesome streams all the time
Go follow kiwo. She's great
Uh vr. Josh. Thanks for all the help
Thanks for everything
uh
De pope hj like the avatars were fucking next level. I can't it was amazing
so
Uh, i'm blown away by how fucking interesting and fun that was so
Got to do it again. Yeah, i'm gonna take a break from vr though
My last like five streams in a row have been vr. That's like taxing on me
but
Uh, that is gonna be it
I will see you guys tomorrow
We're gonna take a break from vr
Try to get a uh
Uh a not a virtual reality stream tomorrow
I'm not exactly sure what we're gonna do. There's a couple of options. So
we will
Figure that out tomorrow
Or i'll do it. I'll figure it out tonight
Hope you had fun
It was interesting to say the least if you take it off
Uh, hopefully we see you soon. Thank you. And let's get out of here. I'm gonna i'll be right back. I'm gonna just take a
quick break
And when I come back we'll do the bits
Just gonna grab some water. That's it
I will be right back. See you in a minute
Okay
Hello
That was just so all over the place. I don't even remember what happened
I have like bits and pieces. It really was a dream, you know, you just wake up and you go
Oh, wait, wait, what the fuck is that?
Oh that happened then that happened and it starts to leave you
That was a lot of fun. Thanks for hanging out. Thanks, uh for showing me all that stuff
Vr josh, thank you so much
I got a nice controlled
Uh tour of vr chat
Kiwa was watching the dinner clip. Oh god
Yeah, we were gonna do
a mind show back and forth thing
because if you weren't here earlier
the
for some reason
we've been playing like me and kiwa have been talking about this for like
At least a few weeks, right?
and
Well, let's go. Let's do it. Oh, no. Yeah, tuesday sounds good tuesday afternoon. Yeah tuesday night. That sounds good
the day that
Vr chat was like off
There was technical server problems earlier this afternoon
So we're kind of just like oh fuck. Well, now what the hell are we gonna do? So we're gonna do a mind show thing
and then
After like 30 40 minutes hanging out trying to figure out what the hell we were gonna do
It came back. So we just figured all right. Let's just do what we were planning on doing in the first place
But you probably will see that eventually
QRS
But uh, i'll see tomorrow. Let's do the bits
Vr is always a joy. I'm glad i'm i'm very happy
that I could
Have the stamina to do it for more than five hours today
So that's good
And let's teleport ourselves back about six hours here five and a half hours or so
we had
Uh back here guild hero
Guild hero gave a ton of community subs
Looks like 20
more than that
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine ten
Yeah, this is the 20 community subs from guild hero. Thank you so much. That's a fucking shitload. Sorry. I missed it
PMF my pleasure. It was a lot of fun
And that scripts three gave fifty dollars
Fifty dollars five thousand bits from scripts three. Thank you
Uh, they say hey germa i've been a part of your community for a while on discord where i've been putting my writing and I was curious
If you'd be interested in being hired to do a audio book
of my short story
The skeleton knight it's a fantasy comedy short about an undead knight
Uh, here here's the thing. I would say absolutely
But here's my problem
I i'm like so hard to like get to do anything
I I really don't want to be like let's do it. Um, oh, yeah, let's go
And then I just like put it off and put it off and put it off
Do it in one stream and then that might actually be kind of funny
Uh, what's the length? How long is it? What's the uh the length on it?
Because depending on how long something like that is I just I really just don't have time
It's like 10 pages. That's not bad
Uh hit give me do if you have like a link
Hit up one of the mods and link one of the mods and then we'll we'll go from there
But I cannot like guarantee that I will because I just don't want to say yeah, man
That sounds great
And I don't want to just put it off and not do it or something. You know, I want to
Obviously take that seriously if I say yes
Will I play bloodborne? No, unfortunately not not on stream
Because I've just played through it so many times. I've done it at least four three four five times
It would just be me showing you a game that you may have already played too
And we'll just kind of be sitting there going. Hey, remember this part. I remember this part
No, I love it. Hey, you guys. Hey, watch. Hey, remember that man. Watch this part
I guess maybe that's all right
exactly
I want to see you nerd out
Maybe one day when we got really nothing to do
if there's a lull in
New games or things that I want to try to do then maybe we'll just do it
Add on the list, you know
A l u l and new one
l u l what's l u l
Wait, why why is everybody laughing?
Allah. Oh, oh, oh
Okay, I get it. I was like wait what?
Hey, thank you sad vega for the 250 while an early stream glad to see this at work
Jerma, I have a friend whose internet is 0.8 megabits up and 8 megabits down their isp promises 10 down and 3 up
What do you think they should do?
um, it really depends on the isp
but isps a lot of them suck and
have
Thousands of employees that all have to communicate with each other about what's wrong with your neighborhood's internet
so
It's I can't really give you any
Advice the only advice you can give is just make sure
That you at least get some somewhat what you're paying for
because if you're getting speeds that are like
Not even 10 of what you're paying for then you need to call tech support and tell them like hey
I'm get i'm not even getting 10 of what I pay for somebody's got to fix it because I the isps do have
you know, they have a not like guarantees, but they
If you complain enough and you talk about it enough somebody will come out there, you know
I mean, I think look at look at the internet problems that i've had
Eventually somebody fix it. Somebody will come out and it will get done. It'll get fixed
But those speeds do not sound like what you should be getting
But thank you to for real dough 25 for the 250. They say watch this. Well, let's see. What watch what?
This is the scout voice actor guy. I think I think I've actually have I see
I've not I didn't see this one
Uh, it's not gonna play through what am I gonna change my desktop?
Let's see it's playing through vr. Yeah, i'm gonna put vr in a box for like a week or two
We will open that box again
another time right this
You should be able to hear this
I'm the scout guys. And so obviously I have to save the day. I save all kinds of people. I save little kids
Save kittens. I save I have to save, you know
Coupons for buying discounts at the grocery store
But I also save presidents and when i'm gonna save a president there's only one thing I need to say
one thing baby
Mr. President get down
You know and I tackle him walking into the places and see a bullet it's coming for him. Mr. President get down
I gotta save him. He's in big trouble. He's the president
I
Am I still in vr chat I feel like i'm still there god well you can watch it that was a snippet of
nate is uh, it's nate
And that's the scout voice actor hilarious, dude
coupons for the grocery store
But thank you for real dough for the 250. Yeah, that's uh, that's nate's twitch channel as well
Don't give it a fall sticks renegade. Thanks for the 255 jerma. You should try call of Juarez gunslinger again
Didn't work for you last time, but maybe you can try again definitely the best western shooter next to red deads
The playstation 3 version if you can sense the pc version failed on your last time. Yeah, I don't know somewhere
That was weird. I think that was actually on a different computer. I did try to play
Call of Juarez and it was just a frame ready mess every time I tried to stream it. It was weird
Yeah, maybe i'll install it and just see if it opens
Please one more. I'm well, i'm willing to give it a try. It's
I'm willing to try
Because I heard it was really fun. I was really real if you were at that stream
I was really disappointed because I really wanted to play it. Hey, actually, you know, let's play fuck. Let's do it tomorrow
Should we just do that tomorrow?
Let's try to figure out what I wanted to play tomorrow. Let's do it tomorrow. Whatever
RIP dragons dogma
I better beat this one
Yeah phoenix if you know, uh phoenix right ace attorney I
I hung the uh the jacket up on this one for a little while because
It's I think it's not the game that I initially thought it was
So a lot of people have been telling me
Uh, you might not really like streaming it and i'm like wait, what do you mean?
And we've been talking about it and i'm gonna play the first
like
Hour or so just to see if it's something I think i'd want to stream
It looks like it's kind of 50 50
On whether or not I should play it or not and look it's not like oh, what do you
I'm gonna make the final decision on it, right?
But i'll just make sure that it's something that I want to do
So that's kind of the i'm gonna I gotta play that for like an hour to see if it's something I think I would have fun doing
It's a lot of talking. Yeah, it's also very long too. Isn't isn't it?
It's I thought it was just kind of like a 12 8 to 12 hour experience where you like yell in a courtroom and like argue
With people but it's like a full on like 40 to 50 hour
investigative detective game, right
So I need to be prepared for that and I need to
Know that it's something I want to do
People said you'd hate disassembly too. I think you'll be fine
Yeah, but this the thing about disassembly is
each one of those
Things to take apart in disassembly
Is like 10 to 20 minutes
So it's not like oh just do one case and see how you feel isn't the first case like 10 hours
Or something really really long
First case is 10 minutes really
That's like an hour or two. Oh, okay
We'll see though. I'm i'll give you an answer in the next
because here's another thing that a lot of people I want to make sure everyone's aware of
because i've been talking about it for
a couple weeks, but
I am going to be taking
a bunch of time off
next week
my mother
Who I haven't seen in about seven months?
Is coming up to visit
So i'm going to be spending
time with her
And I know that one of my good friends came up like three weeks four weeks ago
And I took a bunch of time off then too. It's just this people are coming up to visit
in this kind of late spring
So i'm going to be spending a lot of time with my mother so
This at this time next week
Or in a couple day a couple days before that
Somewhere around i'll give you a very clear indicator of uh when i'm going to be off but
I'm going to be taking like a at least four or five straight days off because I miss my mom
You know, i haven't seen her in a long time. So
She's got a lot of things that she wants to do
Every day she wants to go do things and see things
So i'm going to be taking a little
Like vacation, I guess
And mom vacation, but I because of that
I'm probably going to be streaming this week
Probably every day. So today's tuesday wednesday thursday
uh
I'll probably try to admit as much as I can friday. I mean i'm gonna try
because
I mean i'm gonna be taking like five straight days off that are not get drunk
I'm not gonna i'm not gonna get drunk. Don't worry. I'll give you an indicator of what's going on
this is gonna be at least three days in a row here at least and then
Saturday like sunday, I don't know. We'll have to find out
I'm not exactly sure what's gonna happen, but i'm gonna try to go as much as I can before I take it off
Just to give you some more
Awareness, you know, but thank you to atrox atrox for the 250
Bonk germa venus. Thank you
Don't push yourself. Don't feel like you need to stream every day. No, I know I know and you guys know this
As well as I do if I if i'm not gonna stream then i'll just change the sus, you know
We'll just no, I just won't do it
You guys know that i'm not gonna you know, there's no pressure here or anything. This is how this channel has always been like that
So no, it's all good. Don't worry
Sometimes the sus cast itself
Hey bake me home. Thanks for 250. Thanks for the 200 bits
It was 250. What are you talking about?
That was 250. That was two dollars and 57
Uh, thank you other guy for the four dollars germa your streams never fail to make me laugh
I'm watching you when I really should be studying but whatever
But I clicked off the wrong thing there
Uh, thank you other guy 42
and there's
A video link here
What the hell oh
What?
Why why did somebody do that?
That's just like it just hurts
There's a guy jumping off of a bench just landing on his stomach
Oh my god
great video
Joe show here. Look if you really want to watch it. It's a guy just jumping off a fucking bench and getting hurt
He's just like he's in a suit. Why did you link me this video?
There's just no context. He's just like, all right, i'm gonna do this
I don't know. I don't know why he did that
agent 47
Uh smelly boy. Thanks for the 250 you could conceivably film an entire germa rumble in vr chat
Yeah
It would take a lot of choreography though
Because there's no collision
Vr chat is you just float around and is unless you have the leg trackers. There's no
There's not a whole lot of okay if I like throw a handout and punch somebody in the face
They need to know that it's coming and it's gonna be total acting the whole thing has to be blocked out
It would be fun
Nope. Yeah, there's no pile of drivers. No power bombs
You'd have a little bit of trouble even doing something from the top rope
Leg trackers exist. Yeah, you can just just buy more lighthouses and stick them on your legs, right? That's how it works. I think
Hey bro lock. Thanks for the five dollars. Here you go. Mate. Just look at yourself from our perspective. Oh god
That's you guys looking at me
looking at you
In vr
That's a full circle. It's kind of weird
But thank you bro. Look. Thank you frody and weapon for the 250 vr chat looks like a seriously fun time
Yeah, I had I had my doubts
When we were first talking about it and first loading in that was a controlled environment though, because that was all of
Uh, like kewo kewo vr josh
Like they know people in like the vr community
So that was kind of a lot of the people that they know
That wasn't just random lobbies so
It was a little bit more controlled
I could imagine yeah being in like in public would be a lot different
Public vr is hell
I figured for my first experience ever in it. I'd want to see what it has to offer before
Dunking my head in and just going into a public server with a hundred people in it
Yeah, I could imagine how it'd be
hard to navigate
Still it was still fun though. It was
Could end up doing like a viewer only server
Yeah, that would be all right. That would be fine
For the most part, you know if something happened if somebody was
Doing something bad or something just you know, kick them
Yeah, it was a fun time
And thank you soup or seal for the 250 just a reminder about the joel pogo stuck challenge
That uh that challenge is changing
Joel and I have talked
He got really busy. So we pushed it off
And we're gonna do something else
a lot more elaborate so
No more potential no more pogo stuck
Something better trust me when I say that you're gonna like it a lot better
All right, let's get the credits rolling, too. Oh, we have a minute here
Credits they are
All the subs new subs old subs all you
Thank you guys
for another fun
vr stream
Let's put it in the box for a little while play some other games
Do some other things
I'll see you tomorrow
Maybe we'll just play call of Juarez. I maybe we'll just do that. I i'm just gonna download it and see if it works
A couple more bits came in we had door cube. Thanks for 250 door cube
Are you gonna show your mom vr? I don't think she could handle it. I really don't think so
That would be
Uh, no, she probably wouldn't want to go in it. She might want to watch me do it
But not actually do it herself
But you know it is what it is
Uh, thank you nickname
Nickname jack for the 250 skimming through this stream and seeing the highlights makes me sad. I missed the stream
But god damn it was so funny
Thank you all i'm
I kind of was just
I was kind of just involving myself a little you know
Some of these guys are like vr veterans. I was trying just to hang. I was trying to hang. You know, i'm trying to hang
It was a lot of fun. Glad you liked it
Yeah, vr veterans
vr vets
It is um
Is kiyo still streaming? Is kiyo streaming still?
Let's have a look. She just okay. She just added
Because I know someone saying that she was making a mind show clip or something and I was curious
She has the one with you in the mansion scene. Oh, wait. Did she add she added herself into the family dinner singing thing?
Do you feel like the obligation to be funny on vr chat?
is annoying
No, I mean I
I was just kind of just doing whatever
I don't think I had any obligation to do anything, you know
It was not the abc one. Oh, thank god
I think when you just actually walk around and you have like a
A bar and a few people that are just in character. It's fun just to kind of
Be insane for a little while, you know
Just five hours. Well, all of that wasn't you know
Making jokes and being like in character
I would say probably two-thirds of this stream was me just like staring going. What is that? What is happening?
you know, so it was a lot of me just taking it in and then some
obviously just
Improv bits that just kind of came up for no reason
But I don't find it to be like an annoying thing. I think it's fun
Coach hanging off your arm was amazing
It's just it's hard to take it in sometimes because it's just so out of control
And then you're like, hold on. Let me let me like I want to add something to this, right?
Plus I was like glue man. I got to be glue man for the I had to do it
Oh, here's the key. Well clip
Let's see. Let's watch it
Let's add it
Let's take a look. I think this is when we were doing a test
We were testing to see if this was gonna work earlier before the stream started
Whatever you finally made it
Welcome glad you finally accepted my my messages my calls
I wanted to invite you here today and it's it's so good to see you. Are you are you all right?
You're okay settling in
Welcome welcome to my my man and my virtual playground
I
You're gonna get a lot of trouble with that concrete
I was saying like I fell down and on her house and her front steps
And she's gonna get a concrete lawsuit because I fell down
vr face palming
It's all fun though, you know, but that's gonna be my time
I will see you guys tomorrow
Try out enter the gungeon
Uh, not right now. Not right now
Maybe eventually soon
maybe
But see you tomorrow guys
Uh not gonna be starting at like
two o'clock
pacific tomorrow gonna be starting at
This normal between like three and four
See you soon
Take care. Have a great rest of your night stream legends
Yep, thanks for the reminder. Let's activate it right now
There you go. Three two one
There you go. All right. Awesome. See you guys soon. Take care. Have a good one