So I wasn't going to start streaming for like another couple minutes, but I just, my brain went into autopilot and I tweeted that the stream was live and then I went, oh fuck, oh, oh, oh, and I just pressed live.
I wasn't planning on it. I just did it early. I did the tweet first.
And look, I know, I know, but just link your Twitter to Twitch and it'll just do a tweet. I don't want the robots taking over my accounts. Sorry.
I don't want any, I don't want any, then it like goes into your Twitter and it like reads your tweets and sends them to Bezos. Where do you think they go?
What do you think his toilet reading material is? Anyways, the app is not letting me see the screen. My tweets. Yeah, just mine.
Anyways, we're going to play. Hey, first of all, hi, welcome. We're going to play Bushido Blade. I think I'm saying that right.
Bushido Blade and maybe Bushido Blade 2. It depends on if I can even get past the second enemy in this game.
This is a classic. This is an old favorite of a lot of people. This game is different from some of the other games you may have played.
At least it's kind of a fighting game, but it's different because if you get hit once, you die.
And if you hit somebody else, they die in one hit, typically.
So that with that in mind, is this the first or second one is the first one, but I also have the second one right next to me.
And I know I've been told because I played this game when I was 12 or something of 13.
And I just didn't get it. And I hated it. I think I've rented it. And I was like, this game sucks. This is stupid.
I don't like this because you just die in one hit and I had no idea what was going on.
But now as an adult, I understand that what's going on. So I'll be ready.
But to jump on the thing I was just saying, this game, the second one is apparently just a better version of the first game, but I got them both.
That's what I've been told. Anyways, welcome. Hope everyone's having a good day.
I'm still trying to figure out. So as of tomorrow, I'm probably going to do. I don't know. I have to get ready to leave.
I have to leave. If you weren't here last night, the Halloween stream is not happening in Vegas.
I'm going on location for that special stream. Should be a lot of fun.
So if there is a stream tomorrow, it's going to be short, like probably less than a few hours.
Oh, you just nailed it right there. That one one guy. Jackbox done.
Jackbox tomorrow for like two, three hours, four hours. Done. Easy. Perfect.
And that just shit just came out. Yeah. Yes, I did it.
Anyways, here we go. Classic video games. Just shoot a blade. I'm ready to attempt. Here we go.
There are other modes in this game, but I don't. I mean, I'm just saying just baptism by fire.
What do you think? I'm just going to go POV mode.
Well, we could. We have to do the POV mode after I figure out what the hell I'm doing.
OK, so. All right, I'm going to do this. I think I'm going to be this guy.
What weapon do I want to use? Tana. I don't even know what any of these are.
Is it? OK, wait, broadsword. That sounds pretty good.
Broad sword. Minecraft sword. Yeah. Hammer.
OK, I'll do the hammer. Is this the fucking hardest thing to use?
That's not even. What is this thing? It's a sword. I'm holding it by the blade.
There's no subtitles. Pay attention.
This is really a secret society of assassins called Kagei.
Everyone who knew was sworn to secrecy.
One person broke the code of silence and escaped into the ruins of a deserted castle
in search of the only way out through the castle tower.
I should have picked the broadsword.
We actually do get subtitles.
OK, it's time for me. It's kind of like a fighting game, but it's not really a fighting game, but it is.
It just is. All right, here we go. How do you play?
Wait, he got hit. You mirror hammer. I didn't hit him?
Dude, the hammer sucks. All right, hit him in the head.
Got him.
All right, I did it. I got him in the head like three times.
This is supposed to be one hit kill. What am I doing?
You crushed his face in.
Oh, shit. OK, round two.
Fight.
OK, so Serpa looks like a... You have a blade.
This is not even a sledgehammer. This is a stick with two bells on it.
She hit me with the flat end.
Oh, she hit me with the flat end. I'm fine. Oh, shit.
Oh, my God. That's pretty brutal, actually.
Sledgehammer is actually pretty good.
So is this still level one? It's a war hammer. Aren't war hammers shorter?
All right, no message.
No, no, don't do it. I'm bleeding out of the leg.
Oh, God. Oh, God, please. Don't do it.
Head. Hit in the head.
Come on, I'm just going to crush head.
OK, L1 is one.
All right, I'm going to do a running circle.
Oh, I would have had it.
No!
A lot of coward. I'm just being tactical.
Oh, damn it. Why am I not dying?
What? Are they using practice swords?
I'm dead.
Continue.
Easy mode. No, this is on hard.
OK, is there a block? Triangle is like a quick one.
OK, square is a little parry.
All right, I get it.
Yeah, square is like a...
Yeah, I got you.
I could both find legs.
I got really banged up legs.
Yeah, one hit weapon master. All right, here we go.
I got to get a good parry.
You can hit stuff.
I tried to run.
If you did that in a real fight, that would be really embarrassing.
Do I just keep all my scars?
Yeah, I'm like, oh, I don't think I can use my left arm.
What? He killed me. Yeah, he did.
Damn it. How many continues do I get?
OK, this is the hard boss.
Trying to give him a chance.
Get out of here. Got him.
No honor. Yeah, I know. That's the equivalent of punching the guy before the bell, but whatever.
Now what?
Where am I going?
I'm not controlling this.
What? All right, we're going down to the sewer.
Let's have a clean fight. Sure.
Got him. Double tap him. Get out of my way.
By the way, you might not be noticing the nuance there.
That was a parry block into a double tap.
Like I said, this weapon sucks.
Did I win? I win.
I remember this game. Why was this game so hard when I was younger?
I don't think I beat the first person.
All right, new character. POV mode.
I have to play honorably. OK, fine.
I do want to use... I want to use...
I'm going to use a small thing like this thing.
Actually, this is going to be hard.
All right, you can use the long sword. That's fine.
How much did I pay for this?
I don't think it was very much.
What's an arena?
Be honorable. Stop killing.
You have to kill...
Are you kidding me? This is actually pretty cool.
I can't even... Oh, I have to block. Get up!
Did I lose? I'm dead.
It's different in VR. It's harder in VR.
All right, I'll get him here.
No, wait. It's a short sword, right?
What?
He fell down.
I was trying to hold for his head.
It looks like a Roblox game.
Continue? Why am I continuing for you?
What?
Got him instantly.
Wait, he's...
I got to see that in slow motion.
Watch this. Bang.
Nice try.
Go back to story mode and play honorably.
Well, I need to not continue for the computer.
All right, fine. I'm going to do...
Maybe the sled chamber was easy mode.
What's the hard weapon?
Fists.
You can't use fists.
No weapon.
Fist. I can't select zero weapon.
How about just...
How about just long sword?
Or katana.
None means I eject a disc from the tray.
Google how to be honorable.
What?
Are you guys making this up?
Hold on a minute. This is real?
Hold on. Did I just go through and just kill everybody?
And I wasn't supposed to do that.
Oh. I just...
I don't know. It is real.
Okay, hold on.
Fight with honor.
Don't be careless.
How do I fight honorably? Honor the code.
Don't strike opponents in the back.
Don't throw dust at people.
Don't strike opponents while they're lying down
or attack opponents before the start of the fight.
Which I did every time.
If any of these dishonorable acts take place,
the story will end in the middle of the playthrough.
The screen will display a message
and berate the player for his cowardly act.
What?
So what can I not do?
No stabbing in the back.
Don't throw dust and don't...
I don't attack while they're lying...
Alright. I got it.
Don't hit them while they're down.
Am I trying to win?
What am I trying to do here?
Fight with honor.
Be honorable.
Is stabbing in the back a win?
In terms of a deserted castle,
in search of the only way out...
I'll do it.
...to the castle tower.
One hit is actually dishonorable.
Maybe this is why I didn't understand it.
I still don't understand it as an adult.
I returned this game to Blockbuster.
Okay. So I'm just going to stand
if somebody falls down.
But what if they trip?
I didn't know there was a dust throw button in the game.
I'm probably going to accidentally do it
and ruin the playthrough.
I don't even know the move set for this thing.
I should have done hammer.
Alright. Here we go.
Don't attack.
We're ready.
Come on.
I can't just run in there and stab.
It's not so easy now, is it?
Oh. Come on.
I like it.
Was that dishonorable?
You're doing a backflip? That's showing off.
The block.
What? You did a backflip and I did a backflip
and then you slit my throat.
Can't win with honor.
Yes, I can.
Shit. Kill me. Kill me. I didn't mean to do that.
Kill me.
You need to kill everyone without dying.
That's not going to happen.
Okay. Here we go.
I don't like this weapon.
Give me a fucking break.
This weapon sucks.
I need my hammer back.
This is probably the weapon I picked when I was 12.
And I was like, this is stupid.
Can't play without the...
My inputs didn't...
I'm not going to make a complaint about inputs.
Nope. That's an automatic
you suck moment.
My inputs weren't even... Oh, you said the word
inputs. Automatic.
I don't listen to the next three words.
That wasn't an instant kill, but yours is.
Input equals dishonorable.
I don't like this move set either.
Somehow I died.
Somehow I think I killed myself with the sword.
How?
What?
The fuck? I can't do it.
Honorable. No, I can't do it.
No, I can't do it with this weapon. This weapon sucks.
That's not going to kill?
Easy. Is running dishonorable?
I didn't run technically.
How would... I stabbed you in the fucking face.
Okay.
Don't stab me in the face.
Don't stab me in the back.
Dishonorable.
That wasn't the back. Okay, I hit you three times.
That wasn't the back.
I hit her three times with the same sword
that she's using, and I died with
one hit.
What kind of bullshit, dishonorable
bullshit is that?
Get out of here.
What'd I do?
That wasn't dishonorable, right?
Just use a different weapon.
Yeah, but I've already beat the first boss.
A skilled opponent can insta-kill
without... Did you pay attention?
The title of my stream is
you can one-hit in this game.
What?
I tried to do the backflip.
No, it's not hammer time. Actually, I want to do the training.
Hold on.
Okay, R1 is a different stance.
I actually like this stance.
Nice block.
Got it.
I got right into the intestines.
That dishonorable stance.
There's no such thing. I like that stance.
Okay, here we go.
You're not going to get anywhere just by
the ball spinning.
Got a little stab there.
Bang.
I didn't even...
I didn't need to try. That was really easy.
I don't... Five of shit.
Don't... Is he going to make that... You going to make that thing now?
Okay.
Change stance.
Good block.
What happens now?
Is it like a race?
Who hit the ground first? Oh, come on.
No, kill me. I didn't even swing.
You're hitting me when I'm on the ground.
Holy shit.
That was really
dishonorable.
Oh my god.
That's like
dialed to 11.
I thought you said not to hit
people on the ground. What do you mean you can do that?
No, you can't.
Oh, shit.
What came out of me?
How did I drop? Did I drop like
loot?
Okay.
I've been honorable so far.
We're going to jump down in the
sewer.
Take me the long way. I'm going to just jump in.
This is the sewer of honor.
Okay.
Oh, shit. Let me get out.
Aw, where's the honor?
My legs are broken.
Is this honorable?
Step on his fingers.
Shit.
Get up.
Oh, dishonorable.
You punk.
No, get away from me.
No, let me get up.
There's no honor in what you're doing.
Get away.
Get away from me.
This is not even...
I'm just
sick of my shit at that point.
I think I did some dishonorable things.
Prepare.
I'm prepared.
Let's end this.
He's wearing body armor.
How much health do you...
What the fuck?
Should I not have done that if you stabbed
when they're dead?
Is that all right?
Is that okay?
I really hope that's not
a problem.
This looks like a gun.
Wait.
A gun?
Why do you have a gun?
Play honorably.
Shoot gun at somebody.
Are you kidding me?
Can I block it like a Jedi?
What?
God damn it.
Is this God?
Get the fuck out of here.
I can't block the bullets.
Is it dishonorable?
I can't attack before he gets his text out.
I can't attack before he gets his text out
and I can't move.
Prepare.
Take it easy.
Don't die.
I just, I know I've listened to somebody in the chat, but I'm running at the guy with the gun.
See you later.
Okay, does the next person have an assault rifle or something?
He fight a tank. Now that would be funny.
Easy. He's got a, he has the Darth Maul thing. I don't know what they're called. Yes, I know. It's a called actually something, but it's not as known by Darth Maul.
It's too long. It's too long.
Get over here. Oh no, don't, don't hit him.
That's how you, I don't know. That's how you did that.
The back, not the back. Walk this. God damn it.
That's not a bad idea.
He got a little coffee. I might be his downfall.
Who's after this guy?
All right, I'll get it now. Here we go.
Block him.
Come on, I'm in that combo.
Whoa, what was, damn it.
Side step the lance. I was trying for it right there.
Now that I,
Jesus God.
All right, now that I've had some time to see different weapons and action,
and this is, this is an accurate accurate,
um, the, the lance is, that's the best weapon that's ever been invented in hand-to-hand combat.
You can just stand like 10 feet away.
It's not great, isn't it?
Isn't it like the best weapon ever?
Got it.
He's not, I thought he wasn't dead.
He was doing what I was doing, making jokes out of this whole thing.
Running around in circles.
Where did I go?
Did I, I just jumped out of frame?
Oh.
Oh shit, that was actually pretty bad.
That was scary.
Fucking spammer.
Here we go.
Block.
Oh shit.
Oh, damn it.
Switched.
The burger boy technique.
It's not a bad technique.
Oh, don't. I was trying not to stab him in the back.
Cause that's dishonorable.
Lifted up her left arm to dodge that somehow.
I'm going to go for a dab.
Holy shit.
Once they get cocky, that's when we go in.
I'm going to try to go for the other side.
Right here.
Shit.
We're getting into this though.
Counter attack.
After you block, you can't do anything for a second.
Okay, you get like a spin super move.
Where did you get that from?
I don't have one of those.
Helicopter attack.
Zangief.
Yeah.
This is not my kind of weapon.
It's like you're giving me a weapon.
I'll try.
I'm not changing stances.
I feel like that's bad right now.
Can you skip the replays? I can, but don't you guys want to see?
Yeah, after this I want to learn some actual techniques.
So let's see if I can complete the game without knowing anything.
How is your sword sharper than mine?
Are the directional inputs? Probably.
Because it looks like, hold on, let me see.
If I go down and like forward and...
I wasn't even looking at the screen.
I was looking at my controller.
I was like, wait, down and...
That's the secret.
Hahaha.
No.
I could have just ran and just slashed.
Right in his stomach.
He was like, please.
Please poke my stomach.
I did it.
Full motion video cutscene.
Wait, what are you talking about?
I have to go.
Now I'm all alone.
We're going to go into training.
Just curious, because I need to learn this for the next game.
And I have to pick a weapon that I care about.
Also, some maps you have to exit the map in a specific area mid-fight, really.
Going quality build, something like that.
Okay, so let's see.
So, circle.
You can do double dare.
What if I go like down and...
What if I go backwards?
Forward circle.
So there's a double tap there.
X has...
Forward and X.
Down and X.
Back, X.
Up, X.
Forward, X.
Double tap, back, X.
I have to beat a hundred enemies in slash mode without dying to unlock the guy with the gun.
I wonder if, like, how about triangle, like circle?
Like circle, triangle.
Because that's locked.
Clearly.
Tap.
I mean, yeah, some of these don't tap.
I actually like holding like this.
Baseball stance, yeah.
You are really slow.
I'm trying to do those, like you guys say, directional and like a fucking...
Like, lower stance with R2, I think.
Oh shit, yeah, you can do high, mid, and low.
Damn, okay.
That's good to know.
Game is too loud.
I can't hear you.
Alright, sorry, I didn't know.
This is the first time music's been in the game.
Alright, how do I get out of this?
How do I get out of...
Check the game manual?
Yeah, I would have to go online for that because this did not come in the manual.
Alright, kill me, so I want to go to the slash mode.
Start, select, yeah, that's what I've been doing.
How about...
Start, select.
Select, start.
Start, select, and shoulder buttons.
Holy shit, you do have to press everything at the same time.
Okay.
Movie.
What is slash mode?
Let's see what that does.
Mikado.
I guess we have to do the katana.
I guess I can't pick.
Eat slash mode on hard without continuing.
Let's see how impossible that is.
We want cheats, we want cheats.
On it doesn't matter here.
I just think steamroller.
Alright, bring this down.
Bring this sword down, there we go.
Ooh, that's a good, I like that.
Okay, a hundred of these?
I mean, they are pretty dumb.
Although...
I actually don't like this weapon.
But I have to use it.
Okay.
Nope, he's alive.
Good.
We're going to try that technique a hundred times.
Don't kill me.
Alright, I broke his arm.
Good.
Okay, I think I can do this.
Holy shit, he must...
Thank god.
Don't block, don't kill me.
Did I just headbop him?
No, they get harder.
Oh boy.
Good thing I blocked that.
Oh, I'm dead. I got to nine.
You have to do that a hundred times, holy shit.
Wow.
It's just a gauntlet mode.
And you have to get to a hundred.
I can imagine getting to 99.
And hating myself.
Because I'm about to be lost.
Give him one more try.
We both did the same thing.
What is honor?
I don't need honor.
I'll go...
I'm just helping this guy tumble backwards over and over again.
How many more times do I have to do this?
I just did the thing that you do at the arcade when you're really mad that you lost and you don't have any coins left.
You just get to fucking zero.
No one else is going to have fun.
Let me see.
Bushido blade combos.
The mall to spam.
Here we go.
Move list.
I'm just curious.
General moves.
Square.
Square R2 is roll backwards.
Forward R2 is kneel pickup weapon.
Throw dirt.
There's a jump.
Forward R2 and then R1 is jump.
Hold on. You can do this too?
What happens if you do this?
Do a 100% dirt throw run.
Just use cheat codes.
Can I use the gun guy?
4.5 kilogram sword.
Throwing dirt is BM but it's lots of fun.
Let me try this.
And then we'll move on to Bushido blade 2.
Because Bushido blade 2 is just Bushido blade 1 but better.
With more stuff.
The gun guy is only available in two player mode.
Oh shit. Well...
Uh oh. That's not true.
Is it not true?
Oh shit.
It's literally worse.
It's worse.
I think it's worse.
Don't play 2.
I already bought it.
I'm not going to not play it.
It's right here.
What do you want me to do?
Recycle it?
Let's see.
Stop. I'm trying to boost dishonorable too.
Forward R2 R2.
Forward plus R2 and then R2.
Let's try it again.
Oh. There it was.
Kind of. Forward R2.
Uh. It's not working.
Forward R2 R2.
Forward R2.
It looks like he kneels down for a second.
And then R2 is throw dirt.
Because forward R2 is kneel.
So when I kneel down I should...
Some moves are weapon dependent.
Oh shit.
This is one of the general moves.
Don't hit your opponent
when they're lying on the ground.
No whacking your opponent in the back.
Don't slice your opponent when they're climbing a wall.
No beheading your opponent before they are ready.
What do you mean beheading your opponent before they're ready?
No blinding your opponent by throwing something at them.
Dirt and snow etc.
Oh here we go. Hissou moves.
Looking for the rip here. There it is.
Okay. Triangle
from high stance.
Is this a high stance? What am I doing?
It looks like I'm juggling.
Okay.
Slash. So.
Here we go.
Circle circle.
X. Okay.
Middle stance. Let's just check it out. I need to learn this stuff.
Alright. Now let's get a big one.
Oooh.
Here we go.
Let's try it.
Nice.
Go back to the thing.
I already beat the thing. I can't throw that twice.
The last four hours of that game
was dog shit.
I don't want to do that again.
Play the game again
but do it backwards.
What do you mean put the controller backwards?
No.
Alright. Pursuit of Blade 2 is going in in just a minute.
I gotta have the...
Alright. Hold on.
Forward X. Circle. Triangle.
I'm gonna try this.
Forward X. Triangle. Triple slash.
Ah.
It's gonna be the same game but worse.
Will it?
Alright. It's going in.
I'm taking the bandaid off.
Let me try to do this one thing.
Am I in the wrong stance?
Yeah, I am.
Alright. Fuck it.
Take the second disc and snap it.
Alright.
I'm gonna be really upset with you guys if Pursuit of Blade 2
is much better.
If this game is really, really fun
and I love it, I'm gonna be upset.
Because you guys tried to get me to like
break it. It's actually
awful? No.
It can't be. The first one is fun
and interesting and cool. How would the second one be worse?
I guess this...
Yeah. Hold on. That's true. The sequel could be
always worse.
We're gonna try it though. Is it not
registered? There it is. People talking shit
about Dark Souls 2 are people who can't
beat Dark Souls without shields or sorcery.
What?
What does this have to do with anything?
It has nothing to do with what we're doing.
Just had to
get it off his chest.
The one guys are on a roll tonight.
Yeah, they are.
Oh, it's an example of a worse sequel.
I see where you're going. Is this the only
thing I'm gonna be doing tonight?
Probably not.
Because I can imagine this is probably gonna be like another
hour or so for this game.
And I do have Siren, but
should I start Siren after this?
That might be a mistake
because it's a long game.
And I'm gonna disappear as of tomorrow.
Dead Rising?
No, no. I wanna...
No, I can't. No.
That's gonna be a string of at least
a couple of streams in a row.
You just disappeared for
a week. Well, this is to set up the Halloween stream.
Because I'm traveling for the Halloween
stream. If you didn't know, I'm going to the East Coast to do it.
Am I gonna play horror games
after Halloween? Probably not.
There are like one or two that I'd
like to do, but we've done
a lot of scare games.
Horror Thanksgiving.
Oh, okay.
I was gonna say I can't read this.
Alright, hold on.
Master your weapon. Let's do this.
Practice. Train with the ninja.
Adjust the ninja's fighting pattern by pressing...
Okay. Yeah.
There's a lot of secret characters in
this one.
I wanna be...
I guess I'll be you.
Spear? I'm doing spear.
Oh, and you can do Tatana, whatever.
The longer, the better. That's right.
Frontal attacks.
Off, off, off. Okay.
So.
Holy shit, this thing is huge.
Alright, so square has changed the
stance of this one.
Alright.
I feel like I don't have to do anything with this.
Do a swipe.
Oh, wow.
Okay, so X.
I can go bang, bang, bang.
Is there no blood in this one?
The stage doesn't look finished.
It's just a training stage.
This is lame. No blood.
Hold on.
Since there's no longer a parry button,
in Bushido Blade II,
you must learn to use the attack buttons to parry.
Oh.
Is this why everyone doesn't like it?
When the opponent attacks
with X, hit O
just before the attack. When the opponent
attacks with circle, hit X to counter.
Okay.
Well, that's good to know that there's no parry.
Like, a parry button.
God, I love spears.
No blood. No blood.
No blood.
There's an actual dedicated jump button, though.
Alright, that's pretty cool.
Oh, that's sick.
Oh, yeah. Oh, two is
way better than one.
Alright, I think I can do it.
But there's the whole other thing called rebound attacks.
When an attack hits the opponent's weapon,
a pink flash will appear.
When this happens, both the attacker and the defender
can follow up with a rebound attack.
So if you're attacking and this happens,
you press circle.
Okay.
When this happens, you press circle.
If you're defending,
if I'm hit, it's X.
There it is.
Where am I reading this?
In the game's online
manual.
That's cheating. I'm reading the game's
manual. Alright, weapon clash.
When two attacks meet, a weapon clash will occur.
A weapon clash has three phases.
Yay.
Neutral, advantage, and overpowering.
In any phase, is this just a spam button?
Like, press it as fast as you can?
In any phase, either player
must hit the attack buttons more quickly than the
other in any order to gain the advantage.
I win. I will never lose
one of those. Okay.
So now,
what's this thing called?
It's not called the spear.
Oh, there it is.
Okay.
I'm ready.
Top menu.
Story mode. Here we go.
You can do POV story mode. That's kind of insane.
Insane.
800 years ago.
100 years ago.
It's kind of hard to read.
Was honor in this game too?
How does honor work in this one?
There's nothing on
Bushida Blade 2's honor system.
There is no honor in Bushida Blade 2.
Why would they do that?
You actually cannot fight honorably or you lose.
Cave on the left.
Okay.
So, I'm going to just do the same
thing?
I think I have a good understanding of what's going on.
I'm on Tutorial Island.
Moisac.
Who's talking to you?
What?
I'm speaking from above in the
rafters.
I could just come down and meet you.
But, holy shit,
worse than one.
Look at that fucking fake virtual fighter
blood.
How do you do that?
He'll never win one of those.
It'll never happen.
Right in the head.
Oh, what?
That was right in the head.
You probably shouldn't have
did that, but it's okay.
How many times do I have to do this
to prove myself?
I'm going in with
the slide thing.
Nice.
Can I?
Alright.
By the way, Dad, can we get some furniture
in the living room? The echo is
really, really fucking strong.
Instantly got him.
Wait, we're going again?
You'll never win.
Oops.
He broke my arm, but it doesn't matter.
I can do this with one hand.
Oh shit, one handed.
Right in the face. Just let him walk into it.
He'll walk into it.
Spare is the best weapon.
Okay, for a second,
I thought he was standing up.
I was like, oh, my arm is still broken.
That was a smart play.
See ya.
I'll never understand that stance.
The stance we're both doing.
Why hold your hands up?
The vital organs are like in your armpits.
If you get slashed in the armpits...
What?
Oh.
Good to see ya again.
I do doubt ya.
Not gonna pull a gun out on me, are ya?
He's like...
He's dressed.
Wait.
It's me now.
What if I just lose?
Oh, you suck. You're not fast enough.
Oops.
I was...
Is he dying?
That's fucking funny.
All right, hold on.
There's a different ending, I think.
Why did I give him the spear?
I didn't know how to use this shit.
Here, let me see that weapon.
I have no idea how to use.
It can't be that hard.
He's just sticking with the end that's sharp.
Why would you charge a guy with a spear like that?
Mistake.
Too flashy.
Just go back to basics.
Spears are seriously the best weapon.
Oh, shit.
What happens if I die?
We're good.
Already broke my fucking arm.
Cross it.
There it is.
Dumb.
I didn't even do anything. He just ran into it.
Same thing.
I'm like a spike trap on the wall.
Sorry.
As long as I'm here, you won't be going any further.
Okay.
Why are we fighting in a...
Oh, hold on.
Why are we in a parking garage?
I'm just realizing this right now.
Weren't we like 800 years ago?
Wait.
This is 800 years ago.
What?
I can't even...
Okay, let's go.
You gotta start back here.
Right there.
Boom.
Triple combo.
They're LARPing in a parking lot.
That guy's just died.
Live action roll.
They actually added a person with
an assault rifle.
Okay.
Parking garage's assault rifle.
She blocked my sword with the gun.
And then shot me.
Of course.
Kill, kill, kill, kill.
Kill, kill, kill.
Kill.
She was missing me at point blank.
Get her.
Oh my god, she's so bad.
Kill her.
Ugh.
The eye died.
Stewie grimace.
Ha ha ha.
This sounds like
me. I was gonna say
I do this voice a lot for
Nuke.
I do this voice a lot.
It's coming to me. Fist punch.
I do this one all the time.
Can you really handle a sword?
No.
That's why I use a spear.
Die.
Let's do a whirlwind attack.
Ooh, got him right in the
toe.
He doesn't have honor anymore.
Bring it up.
Let him walk into it.
Bingo.
You giddy.
A sword made for the sole purpose
of revenge.
It sounds like Michael Jackson.
Pretty good.
You've made it this far without losing your breath.
Oh, Utamaro.
I mean like, exactly.
Damn.
You've outdone me again.
This is nothing.
Besides, it's not
over yet.
Yeah, undoubtedly.
Unless we sever the enemy's bloodline, we won't reach
our true goal. Where's your weapon?
Vengeance to settle this prolonged
hatred? Revenge
is nothing to do with me, but I suppose
it can't be helped.
Well, I suppose I'll
help you. You can pay me back
later. Hear me?
I'll go on ahead.
Okay.
This is called the Tartar Shrine
path. Wait, what?
Why does he keep changing characters on me?
Wait, what?
Bring it down.
Bring it straight in.
Oh, that guy got
fucking destroyed.
Oh, what happened to your arm?
You okay?
Something wrong?
Oh, got it.
Again, we go. Okay. Let's go down.
Oof.
I felt that one.
I've been looking for a good challenge.
Oh, yeah.
I'm only Matsumushi and I'm just passing through the area.
Why are you holding onto your hair?
I might not be worth your effort.
That's what I do. I do that. I get it.
Down you go!
Take that!
Low. Can I do it low?
Okay. Sweet.
Take that!
Die! Take that!
Come on, you can do better than that.
Got it. One more.
Down you go!
Take that!
Die! Take that!
I'll leave the rest up to you.
So, alright.
I go back to me?
No, me.
That was a good damage hit.
Do it again.
Swing it down.
And...
Oh!
His arm.
I love that combo.
What?
Oops.
Don't.
I do like the fact that they give you these little...
Hold on. Let me just instant one of those.
Hmm.
There's a little, like, fist bash at the end of that.
Oh.
Bring it down.
I like the down.
Gives you the opportunity to get killed.
Because you get too greedy and do the same thing.
Hmm.
Already broken arm.
Already.
Right in the chest.
Get it!
Get it! Come on!
No!
They're getting smarter.
Hmm.
Why am I killing these people? I really have no idea.
What the fuck?
What's that weapon?
Hold on. Your weapon's cooler than mine.
You got, like, the ten cards in the iPad game
that are my weapon and then I pay, like, four dollars
and it upgrades into that one.
I want that one.
Hmm.
Ooh, that would've been a great counter.
So would that.
You could've chose it in the beginning.
I stick with what I have.
Oh my god.
She just took out my whole entire thing.
Zorax, whatever it's called.
No, that's an ant.
That's like an ant's body.
The thing in your throat.
Hmm.
You're long, too.
So it's fair. I don't like this.
The larynx. There it is.
Oh, I tried to do, like, the scoop
but I couldn't get you with it.
I'm too slow.
Right in the middle.
What are you doing?
Excuse me.
What?
That was fucking stupid.
You would cut your hands up so much.
Alright, let's end this.
You got too cocky.
The end is near.
Always without the weapon, too.
You just find a new one.
I suggest you give up.
The Naru Kagami have protected the Kagami lineage
for a very long time.
I cannot allow you to make an end of it.
Okay.
Uh, I guess what?
The guy has magic powers.
Okay.
I think I have to counter him.
Yeah, I have to counter him.
Alright, I have to wait until he attacks
and then counter him.
How the fuck do I do this?
Why would I see that little flash?
I gotta counter it.
So, like, wham.
And...
counter.
Maybe he'll run out of mana.
Damn it.
He's running out of mana.
His teleport gets shorter and shorter.
For real?
He's probably in, like, a false insecure...
Alright. That was a pretty cool move,
but...
How did that not hit him?
Fuck.
It looks the same. Yeah.
No, I'm gonna have to counter
or something.
Like that, but...
How's that for magic powers?
Oh!
Damn it.
Come on. How did I miss him?
I, like, grazed his ear.
He blocked it on the ground.
He's blocking them on the ground.
How are you doing that?
Alright, low.
Get over here.
That was... I parried and countered.
What happened?
This is a nice boss theme.
Yeah.
The crickets and the owl
stand perfectly still.
Why would I do that?
Alright, I'm gonna try to block.
Okay, he swings. I'm gonna swing with circle.
And then hit X.
No, it was...
That was X.
Only attack when the owls hoot.
Do something!
Please! Do anything!
I mean, he's...
He's almost like he's too far away to counter.
I like... Hold on.
I like the... Hold on.
Let me try this again. He's on the ground.
I just have to, like, sweep the ground.
I googled it.
You need to hit him enough times so he teleports next to you, then...
What?
Hit him enough times until he teleports next to you?
And then stab him?
Okay, hold on.
Is he getting closer?
Did I hit him or did he hit me?
I can't tell.
Oh, come on.
Come on.
He's definitely not getting closer.
Are we sure?
I need to, like, this one.
Because then I can just go, stab, run.
Kick him.
How do you kick?
Google says he gets closer.
If you get stuck on this, you can play the first one again.
What? Kick.
What's the kick?
This jump. What if I jump?
You have to hit him until he teleports
next to you, then kill him there.
So, yeah, I was doing it right.
He definitely is getting closer.
There's no way he's not.
Yeah, he is.
He is.
There he is.
Don't you fucking
dare.
Okay, now?
Don't fucking die.
God damn it, he did kill
my god.
You're a real pain in the ass, do you know that?
Don't you dare.
Alright, that's a good one. That's a good one.
I like this one. It's more defense.
Don't do the third
attack. It's not worth it.
Alright, I countered
and parried and he went further away.
No, please, please, please, please.
No, stop it.
He keeps, like, sidestepping me.
Why is he getting further away?
Oh, shit, he's right behind me.
You...
Oh, come on.
So you have to do that until he is
actually right next to your body.
Is this the boss of the game?
Swing the spear instead of poking him.
But look at how vulnerable I am.
This is stupid.
Oh my fucking god.
Just throw sand at him?
Alright, here we go, come on.
Okay, cool.
Fun.
Great.
Okay, fun.
This is fun.
Oh my god, okay, he can't be doing it
that many more times, right?
Fuck, you don't...
Die!
Oh my fucking god.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, he...
Have I actually hit him once?
No, because you have to hit him
until apparently he teleports
directly next to your body.
Because he has to be kneeling like that.
And that's the only time he can be hit.
But he can hit me once.
I have to hit him like 20 times.
Can I put him in a corner?
No, because he teleports behind me.
I'm just going to do this and see what happens.
I'm just going to keep doing this.
Just do it the exact same way every time.
I'm close.
But he goes behind you!
Oh my god.
Goddamn.
Do with my eyes closed.
Okay.
Why? What?
Why is it doing that?
Oh, it's because my webcam's not plugged in.
So it's taking the last
frame that it captured.
Alright, hold on.
Can I even plug this in? No, I can't.
Because I have to unplug.
Do I have too many USBs plugged in?
Actually, yes, I can.
I can. I have to unplug my mouse.
Okay.
I have too many USBs plugged in and they're all incredibly useful.
Shit.
Okay. I just tried to use my mouse.
That's not going to work. Did it work?
No, I need my mouse. Hold on.
I don't have any other emote
slots. USB
slots. I don't have
any other USB slots in my fucking
whole computer. Yes, I do.
Why is the Razer app
opening right now? No, I'm not going
to install your fucking garbage software.
Get out of here. Hey!
Look how red I am now.
It's the same shirt.
Yeah, because it's the same day.
It's the same day.
It's been like probably an hour
and 45 minutes since that image was
captured. Is it desync?
Oh, kids. Alright.
I'll turn off the desync. There's no
desync, you liars. Oh, no, there
is actually. You guys are not lying.
Hold on. Sorry to
really fly off the handle on that one.
Okay. Now
I'll do it with my eyes closed.
This is not going to even work. Why am I doing this?
Okay, ready?
Why did I
just, I heard like five moves.
Why am I alive?
I'll sidestep that.
This is the best way to do this.
It is.
It is. Just get away.
Only attack if you know you have an opening to do this.
It's getting closer.
Here it comes.
Shit. It's okay.
Run.
Do it again.
Run. Do it again.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Don't!
Don't! Don't! Don't! Don't! Don't! Don't!
Run! Run!
Don't, please.
His armor's broken.
I didn't even look at him.
Oh my god.
I got it.
What does he have?
Ow, my chest.
What does that mean? I know what it means.
What does he have? Lego hair?
That's not it. There's more.
The other one.
You have come.
By orders of Shinto, I have come to kill you.
Yes.
It is the mission of your clan.
To take my life with your Yugiiri.
To end our existence.
It was 800 years ago that our ancestors,
the Kagami family,
destroyed the Suede family
and destroyed them.
There is only one way to have your revenge.
And lay this feud to rest.
I don't have to let go here.
Go ahead.
Take my life.
For I am the descendant of the Kagami.
Do it. Are you going to do it or what are you doing?
I want to get this right.
I want like a full on
baseball swing.
Wait. Try this way?
There it is. Alright. Ready? So it's one,
two, three.
Just practicing.
One, two.
Whatever. What do you mean it's fate?
This endless, vigilant protection
so meaningless
of the blood of the Kagami family.
It can end now.
With my death.
And everything.
Do you guys really give a shit about
the bad end of
Bushido Blade 2?
The people of Kagami fought for the Kagami family.
And the people of
Suei fought for the Suei family.
You can run out the door.
I'll do it next time when I do this again.
Oh wait no I have to fight the teleporting guy again.
No that's not fun.
There should be no shame or regret.
As one of the Kagami family
was it not your destiny to fight
until the very end?
Sword. To fight in order to protect
something. In the end
that may have actually saved you.
How unfortunate.
Watch the blade.
You're going to step on a rake and it's going to hit you in the face.
Alright how do I do
the assault rifle?
Battle? How do I
unlock assault rifle in this game?
You change the game first.
No not yet.
Let's go with
not broadsword. We did big and slow.
I want small and usable.
Not longsword.
It's an adachi.
Small streamer.
Get that person out of here.
I'm going to do this quick.
My hair has not moved.
Alright let me get this done real quick.
Just wild swings.
We're just trying to
die like that one.
Okay good. Keep going.
That was a nice counter.
That was kind of cool but not cool enough.
Okay.
That's the hair from the last time his frame
was captured.
Alright now you got me looking over at the chat
room about my
Lego body. Whatever it is.
Why do I have two
headphones in? I don't need them for this game.
Because I need to be able to hear you guys.
Get it.
Bring it over this way.
Cross.
Got it.
This is not accurate.
Hold on.
That's fine. God damn it.
How the fuck would you even know
what that is? How would you even know?
It's mirrored so it's hard for me to do this.
It's exactly the fucking same.
It looks nice.
Oh look. He's got the same fucking
Lego hair.
Doesn't he? Same hair.
Oh look at that.
Yeah fucking guess what?
Lego hair
looks pretty damn good.
It's nice and smooth and
it's styled. I'm going to kill this guy. How many lands? Watch this.
One, two, three.
Lie.
German lied about Minecraft VR.
Right?
German's hair looks like
Minecraft VR.
Oh!
He did the thing I wanted to do.
I'm not even paying attention.
I'm supposed to be learning combos.
One, let's see.
One.
One, two.
There's a two combo.
I played the first
game. I already did.
I already beat the first game. Honorably, by
the way.
Alright, I'm just being, I'm running and
being violent. I need to like
control my emotions.
I thought I had it.
There it is.
I'm not clicking any world Lego
links.
That's not even it.
Why is there a
green screened image
of a balding Lego character template?
Why?
What is this for?
What is the application of this
image?
Wait a minute. No, that's just, that's gonna put
me in there.
Oh my god, it's trying to key out my green teeth.
No, it's not. Okay, I thought I had green ass teeth
right there for a second.
No, I don't have, look, I don't have green teeth.
Wait, I'm a new character.
I don't, I'm done.
This just looks like my hair's up in a bun.
Alright, let's see.
My hair's up in a bun.
Alright, let's key out
green.
That doesn't do anything.
Okay, I thought I didn't grab it.
Oh, fuck.
I actually like this. This is kind of fun.
The trees come down.
That's, okay,
that's very clearly.
Alright, well to do this correctly,
give me a second.
I'm gonna do this correctly.
Let's see this correctly done.
It would actually be more like this.
Because they have these like square heads.
Not that way.
Wrong image.
It looks like I'm wearing a fucking old like 1930s
football helmet.
This is not correct. There you go, I'm done.
Don't say I never did anything for you.
Oh, do this one too.
I'm trying to play Bushido Blade 2.
Fuck this game.
This is not, is this like, I don't know,
what is this? Is this supposed to be like a beard?
No, it's like a, what is this?
Where's the image?
There's a bald cap on it.
Okay, hold on. This is gonna be hard to do
because of this color. I have to key out this color.
This is stupid.
It's not even the same color as my like skin tone.
Hold on.
It's closing in on him.
Alright, I'm gonna add another key.
Okay.
And it's gonna be this color. Not green.
Custom color.
Okay, it's this.
Where's my grab, my little grabber thing?
I need to put it over there on there.
I don't think I can.
Hold on, here we go.
Nope, not that. Wrong one.
This one? It's like that one.
Okay, let's see what happens.
Is that too similar?
Oh hey, oh well.
What, somebody made a cutout?
What's happening right now?
What is going on?
I don't have Photoshop open right here.
I mean, I've got like a stream going.
I've got stream labs. I've got my game.
I'm not like, oh let me open up Photoshop.
Over here.
That looks like, yeah, let me use the pen tool.
Open paint?
I can't open paint. I'm at, I'm 600 milliseconds behind.
This game sucks.
I didn't say it.
In fact, I didn't because this one was, I actually had fun with this one.
Why is this one all dirty?
Why?
This just looks like I'm wearing a hat.
Okay, I want to change
wait, color correction.
It just looks like
I have a fucking giant white head
as a fucking skull.
What if I just like
Like that, this is not,
this is just a cyst.
Good, did everybody get their screenshots?
Now make an angry face.
I'm like held hostage right now.
Okay.
Okay, okay, alright, alright, alright.
I'm trying to match this.
There you go, that's all you're getting. Good night.
Dr. Phil.
I think the game broke.
What happened?
Hold on, did I die so many times
with this character that his plot armor
melted?
I died like 15 times.
Siren, siren, siren.
Hold on.
I like this game.
Alright, you're going to get a choice.
You're going to get a choice.
No, you're not. I lied.
You're not getting a choice.
Why would I ever play Daze Bomb?
Because it air shot you.
Come on, Joe.
Come on, that was it.
I don't even know how you got there.
Okay, that is the run that you do
when you drop a glass
and it shatters in the kitchen
and you don't know what to do. That is the
I have to go get mom run.
Another gun.
Dude, we shot in the air?
How do you block that? What are you made out of?
Metal?
Do you have metal shins?
Oh shit.
Sleep well?
Do you reload?
What is this
laugh?
Why are you doing an Elmer Fudd laugh?
Reload.
And you blo- I didn't.
Dreamcast sucks.
Laughing by himself.
Favorite
chat comment of the last
three years.
Come on, climb up. You climb up.
You climb up because
you're getting destroyed. I'm going to hit you. I don't even
care. Fucking honor?
Nope. Yeah, I'm going to
cut your damn fingers off.
Come on, get up here.
My doctor is going to be so mad
at me. I keep
hurting myself.
Okay.
Don't
go that way.
That's so
funny.
What's going on?
Where am I?
What am I doing?
Alright.
Here comes the
fall jokes.
Press R2
and then hit circle.
Alright.
To be fair though, I did not realize
what was going on until like I was by
the rock. Could I-
Okay, once I got to about right here
I may have been able to stop
but even if I turned around quickly right here
I don't think I would have done it.
Sorry, R2-
Wait, R2 and then circle?
Dude, shit.
You say I throw knives, that's not a knife.
That's a full sword.
Alright, give me that back.
Can I pick it up?
I don't-
I can't pick this up.
Dude, you just die already.
How does that not kill you?
Okay.
There it is.
Oh, I can't throw it because
I don't have a hand to throw it with.
This damn sucks. Flee, shred it.
Hahaha.
I win. I'm not gonna shred
this. You can shred
the Guy Fieri game because it was $4.
Bushido Blade 2 was like $30
or $40.
This is like a rare game. You don't shred
this one.
Back it up. There it is. It's pretty
incredible.
Please drop her off the cliff.
Why do I want that to happen?
Yeah, I mean, it's a pretty- it's a pretty good image.
I will tell you. That's a pretty good image.
What a twist.
It means you're-
you're that person's brother.
That's your- you came from
the same parents.
In fact,
you aren't carrying it at all.
Seems to be glued
to the tops of your fingers.
That wasn't that loud.
Okay, so
do I have a choice here?
Oh, no, I-
Ooh, I like this.
Ooh, I like that.
I like the spin.
I like that.
Oh, he's dead.
No, stay away from that character. They're not a longer part of the game.
And, by the way,
they died to a default enemy.
They died to the default
regular, just enemy.
That's- that's sad.
Hey.
Oh,
I was trying to bury it in his head.
There it is.
Ooh.
Damn it.
What the fuck was that?
He blocked it twice.
We cut the shit?
All right.
His arm is broken.
All right, I'm looking over at the chat
and I see more purple text
than white text.
And it also doesn't help that this link
is like a Google image link
that's like- what the fuck
just happened?
Who shot me with a gun off screen?
All right, I want to stab. I want to get some of this.
I mean, that's a pretty cool follow-up,
but the thing never works.
Let's go
back this way.
Got it.
It's a virus link. It's a Discord link.
That's the same thing.
Oh, that's me from before.
Now I have to kill me.
Ooh, this is so dumb.
What does it even do?
It just makes me vulnerable to getting hit in the-
it just makes me vulnerable to getting hit in the face.
And I didn't get it.
Same move.
Same ideas.
Ooh, that would've been nice.
So that-
Shit.
Joopstorm, attention.
Joopstorm, chat is bored.
Joopstorm, attention. Joopstorm, chat is bored.
What is this?
What, is this the school bus
back from the field trip?
Am I the bus driver?
Can I look back
and everyone's just like, Joopstorm,
Joopstorm, Joopstorm. And I'm like,
God damn it, kid.
I'm trying to drive.
I know- I know
everybody was really excited
going to the old English village.
But relax.
Was I bleeding on my stomach?
For a second I thought the audio was off the whole screen.
Go to the McDonald's
drive-through
with a school bus.
That would be the most fucking
ridiculous thing.
Imagine seeing a school bus
in front of you at the- like the Burger King.
You'd be like,
nope, I'm gonna go somewhere
else.
Just stop.
Somebody's like, can we play something else
besides Bushido
Butthole 2?
Excuse me.
This is a fucking- this is a classic
game that is very
very- it paved the way for a lot of stuff.
And it's fun. I'm playing
it. What?
I just did that to him to look cool
because he looked cool.
R2 then jump.
Holy shit, that was cool. What?
What?
A sword came out of it.
Why does a sword
come out?
If the game
is so good, why did they only make two?
Okay, why did they only make two
Parappas?
Why are there only two Paper Marios?
Why are there
only two Corona games?
God damn it, I lost
again.
Why are there only two Team Fortresses?
Why are there only two Half-Lives?
In fact, if a game has
more than three or four iterations,
it's usually a shitty
game franchise.
You ever think about that one?
6,000 IQ chat room?
Look at that thing.
That thing's awesome. What's that called?
That's like the Moonlit Greatsword.
That thing is so cool. What's that called?
I ain't gonna let you do that shit.
That would've been good.
His arm's fucked up. No.
I can't believe it.
It's called Big Sword.
Guys, I'm only doing this to get to the end
so I can kill the lady again.
And everyone can go.
The D.
The D face.
Got it.
Down. Down.
Oh, the spin.
Wait.
Is it teleporting person?
Uh-oh, it's teleporter.
Nope.
Wait, it is.
Wait, is it?
Is it new? Is it new guy?
It is. Thank God.
Oh, he's got
an armor gimmick.
He just bounced
it off his chest like it was nothing.
Countering it every time.
Out of level.
Fuck.
I'm trying to hit him in the back.
Damn it.
He has like this thing on his back.
Is that like a spot to hit?
Okay, I can't hit him.
He's running after me.
Burrito? What?
Strike his back. I'm trying!
It didn't even get me.
It didn't work.
He doesn't know where I am.
I did it. I got him.
He was even looking over his
shoulder like he was backing out of a parking spot.
Like he was turned looking
straight back.
Wait, son?
Brother? What does that mean?
I'm your
father. I'm your
brother. I'm your sister.
Sister.
The most basic of all twists.
Just three in a row.
That hasn't been confirmed yet, so you know.
Okay.
Guys.
I have to do it again.
With another character.
I have to.
It's gonna not take-
I'm gonna do a very good weapon.
Explain why.
I don't know.
Wait, we didn't even do
VR mode.
That's god. We haven't even done VR mode.
Stop.
That's enough.
We've been in the drive-thru for hours.
Everybody wants me to move to Siren.
And I can't wait to see
all the people that say
go back to Bushido Blade.
Oh, it's gonna be-
It's gonna be rich.
Alright. Just one boss.
As you.
And I'm gonna use-
Hold on. Don't worry. We're almost done.
We're almost done. Don't worry.
Broad-sword. We're almost done.
And then we'll play
Siren.
Well, this is awful.
Why would they put a wireframe here?
Of all the things that
don't deserve a punch-out-style
wireframe.
It's this game.
What information
are they conveying to me?
I don't know if that's my body,
my stomach, or-
Let's go.
Okay. My final take
on the Bushido series.
That's pretty cool. It was great.
It's a fun game.
Especially when you play- when you played this game
in two-player.
It was really, really, really fun. Because it
was so easy for someone to die.
It was great.