Nope. I'm here. Nope. Told you. What's going on? How you doing? Hey, what's up? On time, yeah.
For once. The one and only time I will ever be on time. No, that's not true. So we had a plan today,
but the plan kind of got changed a little. Just a little. I was gonna do Stanley Parable and then
Infomercials or Infomercials and then Stanley Parable. But it has been brought to my attention
that the Stanley Parable Deluxe Mode is way longer than an hour or two. I played the old one from 10
years ago and I remember after like an hour or two I was like, oh okay. So this is way more than just
like a graphical update. This is apparently a, there's a ton of new stuff. So it's about,
it could be about four to six hours. Yeah. So this is probably going to take the whole stream.
But that's cool. That's all right. I played for about seven hours, seven and a half. So Infomercials
are going to be tomorrow. We'll go tomorrow. We'll do Infomercials for like, well, maybe three or four
hours tomorrow. So I'm going to split it up. So instead of one eight hour stream where I play
Stanley Parable for three hours and then Infomercials for three hours, I'm going to break it up. I'll do
Stanley Parable as long as I feel like playing today. Try to see everything I want to see maybe.
And then just Infomercials tomorrow. What about inscription? I am, I'm going to be playing
inscription on my off time. I feel like I would enjoy it more. That means he's never playing it
again. No, that means I'm never streaming it again. Oh no, he said it. Oh, oh I said it.
We can, can we get, can we get a hernia update? Um, I don't think I really, oh health update,
sorry. Hey, can we get an update on the hernia dude? Maybe. I'm doing all right.
Still having issues. It hasn't never gone away. Didn't get better, didn't get worse. It's just
still there. I just don't talk about it. Why, why talk about it all the time and have every other
stream have like a down point, right? No. I'm doing all right. I'll be okay. Don't worry about me.
There are a few options that I have to consider over the next six, 12 months.
I might do a few procedures. I have actually, I have an appointment coming up to talk about
these very things. Am I going to just go get hernia surgery? Am I going to do a intercostal
nerve block? These are the things that I could do. These things that are options to see if it can
kind of get rid of it. I don't know. I would be lying to you if I didn't say that the three or
four months I took off from streaming and I didn't solve the problem was a little demoralizing,
if I'm honest, because, you know, I'm like, oh, I'll be, I'm just going to go to the doctor like
fucking 20 times and figure this out. Didn't happen. I might have kind of figured it out.
We'll find out, but it's going to take some major, I want to say lifestyle changes and
potential procedures, like maybe a surgical procedure to see if it works.
What? There's your update. I'm fine. I'm drinking green tea. I got green tea coursing through my
veins. Am I allowed? I turned myself up. Am I allowed now? Am I good? Black tea is better.
What? I can't stop laughing. What the fuck? Oh, fuck, dude. I was laughing so hard at what
you just said. I can't believe you just said that. It was so funny what you said. No, they're both
good. I'm not a tea elitist. I'm not a coffee elitist. I drink Folgers and I drink the expensive
stuff. I drink green tea and I drink like Lipton black tea out of the little bag thing. You know
what I mean? I like it. I enjoy all these things. You're a tea centrist. Call me whatever you want.
Call me whatever you want. I know what I am up here. And that is an enjoyer of all things.
Okay. You can call me whatever you want. That's your opinion. Your opinion is not my opinion.
And my opinion is my own fact. Get dunked on. Are you guys ready to play before I like embarrass
myself in the pre-stream anymore? Here we go. Okay. Stanley Parable. Deluxe edition. Ultra deluxe,
I think is what it's actually called. Would I call you my husband? No, that would be fucking weird.
No, that'd be odd. Okay. Why do I? Do you guys ever go? Okay. Does anybody just sit at their
setup? And it's been the same exact thing for potentially years, but something just fucking
does it. Something just doesn't feel right. I feel like I'm just, I'm like, I'm uncomfortable. Why?
I'm like, like the seats, I'm like, no, I hate it. Like what's going on here? Why do I feel like
this? Like I'm, my seat's too low and my seat's too high. There's not enough cushion. There's too
much cushion. The armrests are in the wrong place. I can't like grab the mouse. I can't move. This
sucks. I don't know what, nothing happened. Nothing changed. This has been the same. Look, I feel like
I'm floating around. What's happening? Stop gaslighting yourself and just play the game.
This is going to be, you've changed. I'm kidding. That was a fucking joke finger. What's wrong with
this? Hold on. Okay. My feet are not touching the ground. You understand what I'm saying? My feet are
not touching the ground right now, but they did yesterday, but that doesn't feel right either. Now
my, now my knees are like up. I'm like too far down. I don't know what I did. This doesn't feel
right. Shit doesn't feel right. That feels a little better. That's a little bit better. I might move a
couple things. Not yet though. All right. I think I'm all right. I think we can go. I know everyone's
going to backseat me in this game and it's, uh, people are going to tell me like, go in that door,
go in that door. You're just going to get fucking banned like for a year. If you say even one,
if you say the word like go and then like blah, blah, blah, blah, blah door, you're going to get
timed out for like fucking two years. Just want to let, make sure you know that. Uh, if, if people
get too crazy about it, we're going to put an emote only mode and like, you're going to get banned
for a year. There you go. I scared them. Now they won't do it. This is the story of a man named
I remember that I played this like 10 years ago. I remember this for a company in a big building
where he was employee number four, two, seven, going to our number four, two, nine first,
stupid job was simple. He sat at his desk in room four, two, seven, and he pushed buttons on a
keyboard orders came to him through a monitor on his desk, telling him what buttons to push,
how long to push them, and in what order. This is what employee four, two, seven did every day
of every month of every year. And although others might've considered it soul renting,
Stanley, every moment that the orders came in as though he had been made exactly for this job.
And Stanley was happy. Stanley decided to get up and go this way. One day something very peculiar
happened. Something that would forever change Stanley, something he would never quite forget.
He had been at his desk for nearly an hour when he realized that not one single order had arrived
on the monitor for him to follow. No one had showed up to give him instructions, call a meeting,
or even say hi. Never in all his years at the company had this happened. This complete
isolation. Something was very clearly wrong. This is your day when you're not screaming.
Frozen solid, Stanley found himself unable to move for the longest time.
But as he came to his wits and regained his senses, he got up from his desk and stepped out
of his office. F1. Okay, I think maybe I should press F1. All right, the FOV is at 90, but it
kind of feels like it's too high for me. Is that weird to say? It is too high. Yeah, it's like too
high. Hold on. Now I'm showing you like 85 maybe. That feels a little better. Yeah, it was a little
too much. You should leave the room. I'm going to do whatever I want to do in the Stanley Parable
ultra deluxe mode, okay? But Stanley simply couldn't handle the pressure. What if he had to
make a decision? What if a crucial outcome fell under his responsibility? He had never been trained
for that. No, this couldn't go any way except badly. The thing to do now, Stanley thought to himself,
is to wait. Nothing will hurt me. Nothing will break me. And here I can be happy forever.
I will be happy. So Stanley waited. In 15 minutes, am I going to get... Had years gone by,
he no longer had the ability to tell. But the one thing he knew for sure beyond any doubt... It's
been two minutes. ...was that if he waited long enough, the answers would come. Eventually,
someday they would arrive. Soon, very soon now, this will end. He will be spoken to.
Then in one minute. He will be told what to do. Now it's just a little bit closer. Now it's even
closer. Here it comes. What? But Stanley simply couldn't handle the pressure. I'm not going
anywhere. He had to make a decision. What if a crucial outcome fell under his responsibility?
He hasn't been trained for that. No, this couldn't go any way except badly. The thing to do now,
Stanley thought to himself, is to wait. Nothing will hurt me. Nothing will break me. And here I
can be happy forever. I will be happy. Stanley waited. Hours passed. Then days... Had years
gone by, he no longer had the ability to tell. But the one thing he knew for sure beyond any doubt
was that if he waited long enough, the answers would come. Eventually, someday they would arrive.
I don't know, I thought it was gonna be... Soon, very soon now, this will end. He will be spoken to.
He will be told what to do. Now it's just a little bit closer. After a hundred cycles... Don't say
that. Here it comes. Okay, so if I close the door, I get a funny ending. I can't open 428. I can't
open 429. All of his co-workers were gone. What could it mean? Stanley decided to go to the meeting
room. Perhaps he had simply missed a memo. Okay, everybody's gone. No matter how hard Stanley looked,
Stanley went around touching every little thing in the office. He did. But it didn't make a single
difference. Nor did it advance the story in any way. Yeah, but you never know. That's why, can I
just say, I do appreciate when devs have like a point-and-click adventure game and like stuff
kind of glows, right? Like, oh, there's like a thing you can touch over here. It glows. Rather
than have nothing there. And you just have to... And then this draw on the bottom opens. Like,
I don't know. Like, I like when things glow. So like, don't tell me what to do with it,
but just tell me that I can interact with it. Like, oh look, it's interactable. Rather than
just walk around and do that. Okay. But no, this is cool. So, all right, everyone's gone. I can't
go in 437. I can't go in 430. This doesn't matter. Just go. Close all doors behind you. So, the
amnesia monster does not get us. Okay. I'm stuck in here. 425, 425. This office is fucked up. What
is going on here? What does that say? Would that say? I probably shouldn't have done that.
Awaiting input. Input received. More? Do I have to touch all the computers? Do I do it again?
Input received. All right. I got it. Does that do anything for me? Okay. Uh, spill. I hate Mondays.
417. Nope. You got to break it up a little bit, man. Like if I ever had an office complex,
you got to break it up a little bit. When Stanley came to a set of two open doors,
he entered the door on his left. No, he didn't. He entered the door on his right. I, yeah. Where
am I going to go? I wasn't going to defy the narrator. No, I'm going left. Yet there was not
a single person here either. Feeling a wave of disbelief, Stanley decided to go up to his
boss's office, hoping he might find an answer there. This looks like the whiteboard that we had
for the dollhouse meetings. Oh, like this, this is kind of what we were doing. Yeah. All right.
Cool. Business meeting. We, everyone is unique. You, most of all. Me? Synergize core value
expenditures. Shift global market. I've read. Monetize free to play. What do people want?
Things. Money. More money. Things, but with money to buy more things. Graphs. Graphs about things
and money. Stock market is somewhere here. Call it in segments. Stripes. Requires more secondary
research. What is hot? Profits. I don't know. You know, sometimes I feel like these big executive
board meetings are just kind of nap time when you were fucking five years old. They all come
in here and they shake hands. They're like, Oh yes. How are you doing? Yeah. Michael, Michael,
good to see you again. Yeah. Profits are up. They are. They sure. And they're like, it's like
sleeping bags all over the ground and they like are getting in. Yep. Yeah. Oh yeah. Yeah. We could
fire like four or 500 more people. Yeah. I think that would be a decent idea. Yeah. Okay. You go.
Yeah. Say hello to the wife and kids for me. And they're all just fucking sleeping in sleeping
bags here for like two hours. And then they get up and they leave and they shake hands and they say
thanks. What happens in these board meetings? Like what even happens in them? No, I wasn't done. I
wasn't done with my board meeting to rant. Come on, man. Stanley stepped into the broom closet,
but there was nothing here. So he turned around and got back on track.
Somebody just comes in with like eight glasses of milk, like carrots and broccoli, raw carrots
and raw broccoli. There was nothing here. No choice to make, no path to follow. Am I stuck in here?
Empty broom closet. No, that's bullshit. No reason to still be here. Oh, that's bullshit. There's
something in here. It was baffling that Stanley was still just sitting in the broom closet.
He wasn't even doing anything. At least if there was something to interact with, he'd be justified
in some way as it is. He's literally just standing there doing sweet F.A. F.A. forensic analysis.
Are you, are you really still in the broom closet? Yes. Standing around doing nothing.
Why? Please offer me some explanation here. I'm, I'm genuinely confused. I got a very important
board meeting going on. Don't you understand? We're talking about, we're talking about what
we're going to do in the third quarter. You do realize there's no choice or anything in here,
right? If I'd said Stanley walked past the broom closet, at least she would have had a reason for
exploring it to find that. But it didn't even occur to me because literally this closet is of
absolutely no significance to the story whatsoever. Oh yeah, that joke. I never would have thought to
mention it. Oh, there it goes. They let him out of the park. Oh yes, I'm in a board meeting and
we're awful shitty people. Oh, there it goes. See you later. Go talk about this with your
friends or say, Oh, did you get the broom closet ending? The broom closet ending was my favorite.
I hope your friends find this concerning. Don't read auto mod. I'm not really, really stupid.
Hey, he probably only got the job because of a family connection. That's how stupid he is
that all with drug money. Also, Stanley is addicted to drugs and hookers.
Well, I've come to a very definite conclusion about what's going on right now.
You're dead. You got to this broom closet, explored it a bit. And we're just about to leave
because there's nothing. Am I dead in here? Physical melody of some sort shut down your
central nervous system and you collapsed on the keyboard. Well, in a situation like this,
the responsible thing is to alert someone nearby so as to ensure that your body is taken care of
before it begins to decompose. Hello. Anyone who happens to be nearby, the person at this computer
is dead. They have fallen prey to any number of your countless human physiological vulnerabilities.
It's indicative of the long-term sustainability of your species. Please remove their corpse from
the area and instruct another human to take their place, making sure they understand basic
first-person video game mechanics and filling them in on the history of narrative tropes in
video gaming so that the irony and insightful commentary of this game is not lost on them.
All right. When you've done that, just step out into the hallway.
Oh, dude, look at that one. Oh, there it goes in the left field.
What if I don't go anywhere? Oh, he's fucking killing it today. Do I actually just, I might
just die in here. How many layers is the irony stream right now? Glad somebody got it. You
understand. You understand comedy. What? I don't want to leave though. Don't I? I kind of want to
can anything happen in here? Ah, second player. It's good to have you on board. I guarantee you
can't do any worse than the person who came before you. You too. Unbelievable. I'm at the
mercy of an entire species of invalids. Perhaps there's a monkey nearby you can hand the controls
to a fish fungus. Look, you can hammer out the details. I'm not particularly picky. I'll just
be waiting for when you're ready to pick up the story again. Really? Okay. What if I do it a third
time? I can't do it a third time. Maybe I can. Coming to a staircase, Stanley walked upstairs
to his boss's office. Now I went downstairs. Have a flashlight. Stanley just couldn't do it. He
considered the possibility of facing his boss, admitting he had left his post during work hours.
And in such a competitive economy, why had he taken that risk? All because he believed everyone
had vanished. His boss would think he was crazy. And then something occurred to Stanley. Maybe he
thought to himself, maybe I am crazy. All of my coworkers blinking mysteriously out of existence
in a single moment for no reason at all. None of it made any logical sense. And as Stanley pondered
this, he began to make other strange observations. For example, why couldn't he see his feet when he
looked down? Why did dogs close automatically behind him wherever he went? That's true. What's
going on here? These rooms were starting to look pretty familiar. Were they simply repeating?
No, Stanley said to himself, this is all too strange. This can't be real. And at last he
came to the conclusion that had been on the tip of his tongue. He just hadn't found the words for it.
I'm dreaming. Yes, I'm dreaming. One, two, three, four. This is all a dream. Oh, what a relief
Stanley felt to have finally found an answer, an explanation. His coworkers weren't actually
gone. He wasn't going to lose his job. He wasn't crazy after all. And he thought to himself, I suppose I'll wake
up soon. I'll have to go back to my boring real life job pushing buttons. I may as well enjoy this while I'm
still lucid. So he imagined himself lying and began to gently float above the ground.
What? Then he imagined himself soaring through space on a magical starfield.
It was so much fun. And Stanley marveled that he had still not woken up. How was he remaining so
lucid? And then perhaps the strangest question of them all entered Stanley's head. One, he was amazed
he hadn't asked himself sooner. Why is there a voice in my head dictating everything that I'm doing and
thinking? Now the voice was describing itself being considered by Stanley who found it
particularly strange. What the fuck? I'm dreaming about a voice describing me thinking about how
it's describing my thoughts, he thought. And while he thought it all very odd. That just reminded me of like a
YouTubers or Twitch streamers play the game compilation that sometimes people make like devs or
like companies whatever. Was Stanley simply deceiving himself? Believing that if he's asleep he doesn't
have to take responsibility for himself? That's the cut. Stanley is as awake right now as he's
ever been in his life. Now hearing the voice speak these words. So where do I go? Shocked to Stanley.
After all he knew for certain beyond a doubt that this was in fact a dream. Did the voice not see
him float and make the magical stars just a moment ago? How else would the voice explain all that?
This voice was a part of himself too. Surely, surely if he could just. He would prove it. He would
prove that he was in control. That this was a dream. So he closed his eyes gently and he invited
himself to wake up. This works. He felt the cool weight of the blanket on his skin. The press of
the mattress on his back. Can you guys change channels? I can. Fresh air of a world outside
this one. Let me wake up. He thought to himself. I'm through with this dream. I wish it to be over.
Let me go back to my job. Let me continue pushing the buttons. Please. It's all I want.
I want my apartment and my wife and my job. All I want is my life exactly the way it's always been.
My life is normal. I am normal. Everything will be fine. I am okay.
Oh, it's not a dream. Stanley began screaming. Please someone wake me up. My name is Stanley.
I have a boss. I have an office. I am real. Please just someone tell me I'm real. I must be real.
I must be. Can anyone hear my voice? Who am I? Who am I? And everything went black. This is the story
of a woman named Mariela. Mariela woke up on a day like any other. She arose, got dressed,
gathered her belongings, and walked to her place of work. But on this particular day,
her walk was interrupted by the body of a man who had stumbled through town talking and screaming
to himself. Wait, what? Collapsed dead on the sidewalk. And although she would soon turn to
go call for an ambulance for just a few brief moments, she considered the strange man. He was
obviously crazy. This much she knew. Everyone knows what crazy... Lost to Mariela? And in that
moment, she thought to herself how lucky she was to be normal. I am sane. I am in control of my
mind. I know what is real and what isn't. It was comforting to think this. And in a certain way,
seeing this man made her feel better. But then she remembered the meeting she had scheduled
for that day. The very important people whose impressions of her would affect her career,
and by extension, the rest of her life. She had no time for this. So it was only a moment that she
stood there, staring down at the body. And then she turned and ran. What happened to me? Why did
I just die? Why would I just die? Okay, well, we're not going down there again. All of his
coworkers were gone. What could it mean? Stanley decided to go to the meeting room. Perhaps he had
simply missed a memo. This time I'm going right. Stanley came to a set of two open doors.
Yet there was not a single person here either. Feeling a wave of disbelief, Stanley decided to
go up to his boss's office. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
not again. I won't be part of this. I'm not going to encourage you. I'm not going to say
anything at all. I'm just going to be patient and wait for you to finish whatever it is you
enjoy doing so much in this room. Please take your time. I'm such a little, I'm such a good toddler.
I didn't do it. Coming to a staircase, Stanley walked upstairs to his boss's office,
weird office, executive bathroom, because the boss knows that what the boss says goes if the
boss suffered losses, then that's what the boss chose. Who wrote this? I, no toilet next to a
window. I'm sorry. I don't want, I don't care how high up I am. No thanks. You know, I feel the same
exact way about the hotel room. Look at this big curtain. Wow. Look at this, all the view. You can
see like the whole city from here. Now I could close that shit immediately. Close it immediately.
I don't want that open. What have you taken a shit? What are you like naked? I closed that.
I don't fucking, I, that freaks me out so much. I hate that. Oh, it's just a huge window here.
I don't want to even look in my fucking hotel room. I don't want to look at my bathroom. Like,
what the fuck is this? You want a good, you want a view. All right, here, install like a little
wizard of Oz slider. You know, like, wait, munchkin land. Now you can't come in here.
Just like a, so you can just put your eyes out. Oh, wow. That's cool.
This does the same thing. It does the exact same thing. We don't need all this.
Show your pants. No, no, I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't show you my pants. All right.
Fine. Okay. All right. Fine. All right. Fine. All right. It's, it's, it's Super Mario. Okay.
You see, there's Super Mario pajamas. Okay. Are you happy? Are you happy? Okay. There's Super
Mario pajamas. Don't you guys get it? I just have, you just have to, I just have to be presentable
from here up. I just have, my fly is not down. It's buttoned. You know how many times I've had
a nice shirt on and wearing like in little like pajama, like shorts a lot. All that matters is
like this camera right here. Right. That's all that matters. What the fuck? Holy shit. Okay.
I didn't think that was a panda until like a second ago. The nose of the panda I thought was
a mouth going like this. Like I didn't, and the black I thought was a background. I was like,
what is that? I thought it was like a face. The nose is like an open kind of mouth. I,
that was fucking weird. You can see it. Yeah. Of course you can. No, I'm not going up there. Not
yet. Anything else I can touch in here? Anything I can do? What about over here? Stepping into
his manager's office, Stanley was once again stunned to discover not an indication of any
human life. Shocked, unraveled, Stanley wondered in disbelief who orchestrated this? What dark secret
was being held from him? What he could not have known was that the keypad behind the boss's desk
guarded the terrible truth that his boss had been keeping from him. And so the boss had assigned it
an extra secret. Really? Oh. But of course, Stanley couldn't possibly have known this.
How did he get it? Stanley just sat around twiddling his thumbs, trying to input anything on
the device was useless since he could never possibly know that the combination was two eight
four five. I don't know. I can't get it. Two eight four five. I don't know. You're not supposed to
be listening to you. You could pull this whole room forward in the Sims building tool and it's
still the office is fine. What's the point of all this? Just go over here. Emergency override
kicked in and the door just opened all by itself and Stanley got the hell along with the story.
Well, what did you do? What the fuck? I got it. What was he hiding? What's this big secret?
Really dark. I can't see anything. What's the secret? You don't want to know, man.
Descending deeper into the building, Stanley realized he felt a bit peculiar. It was a stirring
of emotion in his chest as though he felt more free to think for himself, to question the nature
of his job. Why did he feel this now when for years it had never occurred to him? This question
would not go unanswered for long. Stanley noticed that there was a place to jump halfway down the
elevator. He jumped very excitedly, landed on the ledge and was disappointed to find it was just a
grace mimic. Just a grace mimic. Stanley walked straight ahead through the large door that read
mind control facility. Is this where I put the helmet on and see all the all the mutants? The
lights rose on an enormous room packed with television screens. What horrible secret did
this place hold? Stanley thought to himself. Did he have the strength to find out?
What's going on here? Hold on. I gotta for the for the streamer and youtuber supercut. Hold on.
I gotta make a good one. Make sure I get on it. Now the monitors jumped to life. Whoa.
Each bore the number of an employee in the building. Oh my god. The lives of what the
fuck? That wasn't good enough. That was that was not good enough.
I can't swear you're right. No I can swear but they'll do they'll do this. It'll be like
what the I always find like censoring like fuck or like shit. It's like you hear the first two
letters and the last letter it's like what you're just essentially censoring a letter
like ready for instance what it like you why does it matter fuck fuck fuck right like it doesn't
matter you literally like shit you know what I'm saying like it's literally the eye and shit is
being removed who cares it doesn't make any sense kids will learn get your kids off of
youtube immediately do right now get your kids off of youtube now like do it today get them off
there immediately and get them out of here too get them out of here no you don't want them here
it's too horrible to believe it couldn't be true had stanley really been under someone's control
all this time was this the only reason he was happy with his boring job that his emotions had
been manipulated to accept it blindly well we need much more high quality children's television
okay we need children's television like in children's content like holy shit what a disaster
can you imagine auto auto's grotto like one of the segments it's like auto sitting at a table
and it's like a counting segment you know like and there's this this five there's five treats
on the table and it's like oh auto hey can you count with us auto he's like yeah I can count
with you absolutely my name's auto it's like how many treats are on the table and he goes
oh one two three four auto count again auto there you try again no just four one two three
and then he eats the fifth one four then it goes like
and then it like zooms in and it's like a cute thing how do we teach kids counting
he refused to believe it he couldn't accept it his own life in someone else's control never
it was unthinkable wasn't it was it even possible had he truly spent his entire life utterly blind
to the world this is getting intense man whoa intense was the proof the heart of the operation
controls labeled with emotions happy or sad or content walking eating working all of it
monitored and commanded from this very place and as the cold reality of his past began to sink in
stanley decided that this machinery would never again exert its terrible power over another human
life for he would dismantle the controls once and for all but i could turn it right could i
turn it on i'm sorry not before my morning coffee i don't do anything before my coffee
i'll come back all right fine controls idle awaiting input and when at last he found the
source of the room's power he knew it was his duty his obligation to put an end to this horrible
place and to everything it stood for can i change this like do you have to be like eat like 20
more vegetables like i just make it down anyway what if it was just like like cigarettes are gross
right like oh cigarettes are gross yeah cigarettes are gross and eat 10 more broccoli
hey that was loud let people decide that on their own i'm fucking kidding blackness and a rising
chill of uncertainty i turned it off was it over yes he had won he had defeated the machine
unshackled himself from someone else's command freedom was mere moments away
and yet even as the immense door slowly opened stanley reflected on how many puzzles still lay
unsolved where had his co-workers gone how had he been freed from the machine's grasp
what other mysteries did this strange building hold but as sunlight streamed into the chamber
he realized none of this mattered to him for it was not knowledge or even power that he had been
seeking but happiness perhaps his goal had not been to understand but to let go no longer would
anyone tell him where to go what to do or how to feel whatever life he lives it will be his
and that was all he needed to know it was perhaps the only thing worth knowing stanley stepped
through the open door could i like mind control myself to know way more than i do like if i go put
if i go like go to that machine and i was like i'm gonna mind control myself and to know like every
language could that work it's not like the matrix no it wouldn't that's the matrix all right but
okay what if so what if i was like i was in the mind control machine and somebody walked over
was like you now know every language on earth what would happen would i come out of it like in the
i come out of the machine and i'm just like i don't know what do i do would you know it would
stanley felt the cool breeze upon his skin the feeling of liberation but what would you think
immense possibility you would think you knew every language on earth this was exactly the way
right now that things were meant to happen that's fucking funny and stanley was happy
so would i be would i pretend to understand french that's so stupid but when people were
like say something to me in french what would i do all right let's go and he decided to go to
the meeting room to check on his co-workers he never functioned well by himself all right so
we're gonna go we needed support and guidance from others i'm gonna go should i turn on the
machine it was terrifying to him you wouldn't know any new languages but everyone else thinks you
do came to a set of two open doors he entered the door on his left what all right i just i want to
i'm on i want to go see what happens yet there was not a single person here either
feeling a wave of disbelief hey decided to go up to his boss's office hoping he might find an
answer there that's funny that's funny good one that's a good one coming to a staircase i want
to go and he walked upstairs to his boss's office i want to go up because i want to press the other
button wait what did where does this go this is i didn't do this should i go up or down i remember
i was in an elevator one elevator one time and this like mom and her little girl came in
and we were just going down the elevator and the mom was like not paying attention
and the little girl went like this walking with her finger pointing right towards just going for
a button and she was going she was going for like the emergency bell button and it was just in slow
motion i was just like oh no and it was she pressed it and it went like and for one second
and it was just like oh yeah and then we got off the elevator and like nothing happened
it was like what the fuck what's going on that's a fake story that's not a fake story
i didn't just make that up why would i make that up why would i make up a stupid elevator story
where a little kid presses like the bell button for like the ring the emergency button why would
i make that up there's no reason what do i gain from making that up what's that huh wait it was
a funny stream moment all right get me out what the fuck is going on go up what's what are you
doing i can't sing on the elevator are you pretending so i probably just have to sit here
for a minute all right i did it
blow some bubbles uh they're not here you you fail to comprehend the joke what wasting
someone's time is a joke wasting my valuable time is funny that's funny wasting my time
i just wasted my time that was a waste of my time and that's funny this new generation does not
fucking whatever stepping into his manager's office stanley i know the code already stunned
to discover not an indication of any human life what could it mean stanley wandered aloud to nobody
he began wildly stanley was in such a rush to get through the story as quickly as possible
he didn't even have a single minute to just let the narrator talk that kind of anxiety isn't
healthy he relaxed for a few moments with some calming new age music hey no but i don't you know
what i don't like when someone deliberately wastes my fucking time again right honey right feeling
soothed and rejuvenated stanley calmly walked forward into the opened passageway oh oh here
comes the streamer ego okay so i'm gonna i'm gonna press the other button you wasted all of our time
when you played this strawberry game oh that's different though that was funny that's different
that was funny that's a lot different oh yeah you wasted my time by having to make me put a
poll up every 15 seconds to get 85 percent of you to keep confirming to keep playing the game
that was wasting my time we're even stanley walked straight ahead through the large door that read
mind control facility all right do i press the on button or do i go this let's go this way although
this passageway had the word escape written on it the truth was that at the end of this hall stanley
would meet his violent death your mods were doing it it wasn't even to you the door behind him was
not shut yeah and had every opportunity to turn around and get back on and like going to my other
monitor and typing each letter to say run another oh my god my fucking hands hurt after that my
fingers are so delicate i'm wasting my time at this point stanley was making a conscious concerted
effort to walk forward and willingly confront his death delicate do i actually just die if i go in
here there's sprint everyone's calling me a coward hey jeremy jump in this hole it'll grind you up
into a thousand pieces no coward you're a fucking coward okay do a gigachad oh well now that i'm
gonna be a gigachad of course i will jesus i thought i was supposed to die as the machine
word into motion and stanley was inched closer and closer oh shit it's gonna squish me he reflected
that his life had been of no consequence whatsoever stanley can't see the bigger picture
he doesn't know the whole story trapped forever i took a man to a grave
good farewell stanley cried the narrator as stanley was led helplessly into the
enormous metal jaws in a single visceral instant right a little toaster that's right
reiterated as the machine crushed every bone in his body killing him instantly no it didn't
it's too dark i can't see a movie and yet it would be just a few minutes before stanley would
restart the game back in his office as alive as ever why is there a narrator did the narrator
think he was going to accomplish dude this only happens with the pirated version when every pass
you can walk has been created for you long in advance death becomes meaningless making life
the same do you see now do you see that stanley was already dead from the moment he hit start
really office layout this blueprint shows the office from the beginning of the game path from
stanley's office to the two doors was the first part of the game that was built sections have
been added and altered throughout development the core layout remains almost identical to the first
iteration what the what the is insane that's the one the pacing of this opening section was
important to get right this corridor has been moved and altered to make sure the player reaches
the two doors in good time interesting filing cabinets cool office computers oh employee database
huh paintings look at this tuber nature paintings wow wow wow wow wow wow wow
the credits of the game what are these buttons oh auto how many buttons are there well it is one
two three four and this four bunch five oh it was here cookie behind you nice job nice job nice job
to all of you nice job actually great work like for real this is game school all right so where
do i go this way i'm gonna go over here maintenance room i've played so much elden ring that in my
brain there's an item right there there's a little glowy thing right there behind that you did it you
solved it not really early in development we designed an ending where stanley would end up
on a battlefield fighting aliens the action game would become sentient and would wage war against
the narrator we realized shortly after starting to build it that it was far too jokey and on the
nose for the tone of the game plus some people interpreted it as making fun of people who like
shooters which was not our intention that would have been that would have been kind of crazy
ultra deluxe announcements in december 2018 we announced the ultra deluxe version of the stanley
parable at the game awards these are screenshots of the videos we made for the announcement in the
game's delay cool the office the lounge the cargo lift why am i expecting a bunch of little chat
bubbles around here that i can click on and all of a sudden it's just like and that's why we decided
when we delayed it by a year or two that when we finally got it on steam we were gonna make sure
that me gaben would personally announce the games listing on steam like i feel like i'm looking for
those or this is gonna explode i don't want to see that that's spoilers maybe just a peek
maintenance layout there's a lot of stuff here what is going on why did that make my eye itch
zending levers are the zending the player would pull a lever in the narrator would describe what
color they pulled these are all spoilers out of the zending layer the zending model what's
his ending what does zending mean i don't want to see that countdown desk no this is i don't want
to see this freedom ending yeah i saw that okay i know that one yeah all right let me get out of
here i don't want to see this you're wasting time you're wasting our time oh please all right let's
do it stop stalling oh look at these two how they wish to destroy one another how they wish
to control one another how they both wish to be free like i'm gonna do this and the room that's
black is gonna lighten up and i'm like zapping somebody in the electric chair it's like look
at what you did can you see can you see how much they need one another no perhaps not sometimes
these things cannot be seen but listen to me you can still save those two you can stop the program
before they both fail push escape and press quit there's no other way to beat this game as long as
you move forward you'll be walking someone else's path stop now and it'll be your only true choice
whatever you do choose it don't let time choose for you don't let got it begin the game again
stanley knew the office layout like the back of his hand pretty much it was only a matter of
time before he found the others wherever they were just a matter of time he was supposed to quit
what i thought i was supposed to quit the game i missed the ending i was supposed to quit when
stanley came to a set of two open doors he entered the door on his left let's defy this was not the
correct way to the meeting room and stanley knew it perfectly well perhaps he wanted to stop by the
employee lounge first just to admire it it's truly a room worth admiring it had really been
worth the detour after all just to spend a few moments here in this immaculate beautifully
constructed room he's free stanley simply stood here drinking it all in like are these free why
yes really really worth it being here in the room a room so utterly captivating that even though
all your co-workers have mysteriously vanished here you sit looking at these chairs and some
paintings really worth it i mean i'm just checking it out man stop trying to rush me
at this point stanley's obsession with this room bordered on creepy
and reflected poorly on his overall personality i'm just trying it's possible that this is why
everyone left you're wasting time you're wasting the narrator's time stanley sat around waiting
for more dialogue but when a long time had passed and there was no more he decided that the game
was trying to send him a message but at last he'd had enough of the amazing room and took the first
open door on his left to get back to business nope i'm not going in there i'm gonna look in there and
see what's in there but i'm not going in stanley was so bad at following directions it's incredible
he wasn't five years ago what's this omega low warning do not jump from the cargo lift while
it is in motion will cause death penalties can i go in here i need a credit card look stanley i
think perhaps we've gotten off on the wrong foot here but in his eagerness to prove that he is in
control of the story and no one gets to tell him what to do stanley leapt from the platform
and plunged to his death good job stanley everyone thinks you are very powerful all of his co-workers
were gone what could it mean stanley decided to go to the meeting room perhaps he had simply missed
a memo and it's the same what happens when stanley could be lying to a set of two open doors this was
not the correct way to the meeting room and stanley knew it perfectly well perhaps he wanted to stop
by the employee lounge first just to admire it wow yes this room but eager to get back to business
stanley took the first open door on his left best burp of the year what a dumb category
okay so here we go stanley was so bad at following directions it's incredible he
wasn't fired years ago so go on the thing don't follow up look stanley i think perhaps we've
gotten off what if i do it again what if i do it again i'm not your enemy really i'm not
but in his eagerness to prove that he is in control of the story what if something changed
stanley left from the platform and plunged to his death good job all right i just didn't i didn't
know i sometimes there's something different i don't know it could have been like stanley realized
that he thought to himself am i sure that the orders stopped coming in how is that possible
they never stopped surely i was mistaken no no the orders were still missing for now
yeah i don't know i it could have been like oh stanley realized that the ai had not loaded in
the fall damage yet i don't know who knows this is a game this is a weird game you never know when
stanley came to a set of two open doors this was not the correct way to the meeting room and stanley
knew it perfectly maybe three times perhaps he wanted to stop by the employee lounge first
just to admire it no i'll have to do it a third time the lounge was sublime a work of art but
eager to get back to business stanley took the first open door on his left oh i'm gonna go across
stanley was so bad at following directions it's incredible he wasn't fired years ago
okay let's go look stanley i think perhaps we've gotten off on the wrong foot here i'm not your
enemy really i'm not everyone realize that investing every single person is my enemy
but the fact is that the story has been about nothing but you my enemy this time there's someone
you've been neglecting stanley someone you've forgotten really i was in the middle of something
do you have zero consideration for others are you that convinced that i want something bad to
happen to you why i don't know how to convince you of this but i really do want to help you
to show you something beautiful look let me prove it let me prove that i'm on your side give me a
chance all right do it do it then stop talking about it and do it danger everywhere now listen
carefully this is important okay stanley walked through the red door what if he kills me he said
he wants to prove it prove it oh thank god you are willing to listen to me prove it now you see that
i really have wanted you to be happy all this time but you haven't proved it the problem is all these
choices the two of us always trying to get somewhere that isn't here running and running
just the way you're doing right now don't you see that it's killing us stanley i just i want it to
stop so this is i would we would both be so much happier if we just stop you get auto balanced well
i think i have a solution here let me show you what do we want what are we looking for
oh what do we want here yes oh it's beautiful isn't it if we just stay right here right in this
moment with this place stanley i think i feel happy i actually feel happy whoa does it do
anything else oh here comes the green here comes the green all right if this light show is more
than 40 i'm leaving a two-star review on yelp green tea it is like green tea you're right
green tea oh and red for red tea wow and look there's there's peach tea raspberry tea you guys
you wow you're right bro just leave i'm not gonna leave this is i want to see what happens he's not
gonna leave i'm not gonna leave yet something about the this entire video game is just a
of moments like far cry 4's first 20 minutes you don't just leave leave just leave bro go just
leave that i'm experiencing the video game that's been crafted okay now i'll leave no wait where are
you going never listening to you ever again he wasn't done oh baby sensory i love watching the
videos people go and like you know what i mean like gunk gunk oh i love that nobody know what
i'm talking about the like the drywall paste stuff where they go like they mix it the i don't
know i figure what it's called this is thick like almost concrete like gunk and they just like
carve carve carve slide slide slide come on oh no stay away from those stairs okay hurt yourself
if you die the game will reset we'll lose all of this yeah it's like drywall paste i can't believe
you know stanley let me stay here don't take this from me all right i'll give you five more
minutes good good we can't be too safe promise me you won't go back there just just stay here
five minutes is gonna make me go watch something else bro there's like 500 billion pieces of
fucking media on the internet just one there are more youtube videos than stars in the sky
you got options you got options no what do we talk about you're risking everything we achieved
you heard me before didn't you you will die what about this isn't getting through to you but
there's the person in chat said they wanted me to hurry up oh that chat member why don't just
ban him time him out for 10 minutes please stop looking at the negative comments all i did what
do i just walk off why am i just walking off oh my god you lived you have me worried oh my god
okay can we please get back to the other room i think i think my legs hurt there see
this is what you want i think i'm slower both be happy we really can if we stop moving we just
have to stop moving how do i get out of here stanley go back there's nothing good that can
come from this do i have to just reset no no no what are you doing do you just not believe me
what can i say to convince you how long is the show out there how long is the light show i do
how long is the light show i don't understand will this kill me stanley let's go back to how
can you do that for me what the fuck i i keep yes perhaps you can i apparently i have a lot of
health let me see what i'm talking about okay what is it what i know you'll see you'll see
that we can't be happy if we leave this place you can see that can't you can i walk off of this
just stop moving i i've stopped moving for a long time i've stopped moving wait you have to stop
moving looking counts as moving do a 360 spin off the catwalk okay i don't want to do that i
don't want to do that no perhaps not does what does that actually do anything are you guys just
fucking with me my god is this really how much you dislike my game that you'll throw yourself
from this platform over and over to be rid of it you were literally willing to kill yourself
to keep me from being happy no i didn't reading the situation correctly no i just no it doesn't
work all right getting a kid i'm gonna go stand still i don't know doesn't work do you actually
want to stay alive or are you just teasing me i apparently have i'm invincible i guess
so we're gonna not move to just to be happy here stanley i really did i wish i still thought that
what i'm not touching the most bunch of fucking liars all right i'm not a bunch of wires i'm not
moving the most do i actually have to jump off that oh okay okay let's start over i guess is it
over does it do anything it's going to restart isn't it i'm going back okay um we starting again
okay so i don't go that way i'm gonna go in the blue door this time blue door and he came to a
telephone whatever to the door and answer the phone whatever this was not the correct way to
the meeting room and stanley knew it perfectly well perhaps he wanted to stop by the employee
i need to go in the blue door just to admire it standing now in this incredible room stanley for
the first but eager to get back to business stanley took the first open door on his left
no i didn't stanley was so bad at following directions it's incredible he wasn't fired years
all right blue door look stanley i think perhaps we've gotten off on the wrong foot here
i'm not your enemy really i'm not i realize that investing your trust in someone else can be
difficult but the fact is that the story has been about nothing but you all this time there's someone
you've been neglecting stanley someone you've forgotten about please stop trying what really
oh wait what do you have zero consideration for others
something bad to happen to you give me the blue door i don't know how to convince you of this but
i really do want to help you to show you something beautiful look let me prove it let me prove that
i'm on your side give me a chance blue now listen carefully this is important stanley walked through
the red door perhaps you misunderstood stanley walked through the red door i still don't think
we're communicating properly stanley walked through the red door all right fine go ahead stanley you
want to know so badly what's out there you want to find out what lies at the end of this road
you've chosen world don't let me stop you you see there's nothing here i haven't even finished
building this section of the map because you were never supposed to be here in the first place
broken rooms exposed developer textures is this what you had wanted was it worth ruining the
entire story is a jump map specifically for you do you not think i put a lot of time into that
because i did and in the end it was all for nothing because this is what you wanted to see
help me here stanley help elucidate these strange and unknowable desires of yours what would have
made this game better what did you want to see ours yep a car skilled trees work with me you
give me absolutely nothing so far tell you what let me take a stab in the dark at a new design
and you can give me some feedback there we go a third option already feels leaps ahead of where
we were before go ahead stanley take it for a spin but should i go in there or should i go one of the
other doors i'll try it please rate your experience okay i'm going to stop you there
now tell me about your experience with this new version would you say that the game benefited
from allowing you more choices feel free to be honest i'm looking for some real critical feedback
here a one i mean i can understand if you had reservations you saw ways the game could be
improved to more fully express itself mechanically and artistically but a one that's not even helpful
what am i supposed to do with that uh but i guess it isn't my place to judge here based on the data
from your previous playthrough i've compiled a new version and to be perfectly candid i think
i've knocked it out of the park with this one let's take a look stanley powerful worldwide
leaderboard worldwide leaderboard 21 percent of players skipped the intro sequence only the worst
30 percent of players chose the blue door 98 percent of players uh how long does it take you
to get to the correct door compete against others to improve your stanley parable career
that's funny now you see a lot of one star reviews would you say that competitive leaderboard
when you read the review motivated to keep walking it's like they forgot a ketchup packet
honest answers please i mean the server was actually really nice the food was fine
i mean they forgot um forgot to put a sauce in the bag oh fuck this place hey i nearly forgot
i've got a prototype of a new game i've been working on and now would be a lovely opportunity
to give it some play testing you wouldn't mind taking a look at it would you sure perfect let
me boot it up in this game the baby crawls left towards danger oh no you'll click the button to
move him back to the right and if he reaches the fire you fail it's a very meaningful game all
about the desperation and tedium of endlessly confronting the demands of family life i think
the art world will really take notice but of course the message of the game only becomes clear
once you've been playing it for about four hours okay why don't you give it four hours of play
to make sure it's effective so rescue baby notes on your experience so loud it's too loud
how long do i i don't i don't i don't like this i don't like it i don't a baby sounds
you can do this but i'm not doing it i don't care you heartless bastard did you do it because
you hate babies or purely to spite me because if it's the latter well i don't know what to do
i'm completely out of ideas i can't think of a single thing that might improve the experience
for me i'm not even going to try i'm out i'm out i'm done no it's over what thank you for playing
your input was extremely valuable refund hey since my game was so awful why don't we play
someone else's game just to ease the pain let's see what do we have here
yes this seems like it'll work let's give it a shot what fascinating what do you think this
game is about stanley what's our backstory this fire watch this vision well it seems obvious to
me that you are meant to play as a creepy man spying on innocent civilians below you from up
high in your creep tower perhaps for some sort of twisted erotic purpose hmm yes that must be it
what a fascinating venture into the experience of total mental depravity so far i love everything
about this game stanley and it seems there's even more come let's venture outward and see what else
okay i think you're gonna see your asshole i love the okay somebody just said what with like
three question marks this is you need a little bit of context go to youtube.com slash germa985
an old channel and go look for a video called the photos are in you might like unfollow the
channel after watching that video right should i tell people to go watch that i mean it's like
my favorite video but i mean like should i be telling people to do that so this is it's an
open world game good god quickly block it off hey oh dear goodness stanley what a close call
you nearly wandered off into that that thing that big open just wandering around no right or wrong
directions no path to follow you can just go in any oh thank heavens we avoided it we're out of
the woods now stanley okay i'm going to get us out of here let's find another another game all
right this is something with walls something with nice big insurmountable walls what do you got
okay i think this will be just the thing rocket league see this is exactly what i had in mind
just a nice big box for you to run around in there isn't any possibility that you could get
lost here now this is game design stanley if you manage to get lost in this game i will be
phenomenally impressed but where are the cars okay so what exactly do we do here let's see
there are lots of cars here in the back but obviously there's no racetrack
okay i'm seeing that there's a ball of some kind back here is this game sports ball stanley i think
it's sports ball oh what fun what fun run the bases and do a touchdown together yes i think
surely we must okay stanley here's the ball have fun will this kill me if i go near it by the way
i picked the blue door i'm shooting into the blue goal and he's probably gonna be like pissed
are you doing it winning is this fun is it better than my miserable little story that i work so hard
on stanley i have a thought actually never got into rocket league i'm not a sportsologist but if
one ball generates a certain amount of raw adrenal pleasure then surely multiple balls
what are you doing stanley don't do that i can't follow you there i can't help you
how will you write a story without me you can't do it you know that
shit okay so now what filing cabinet what did i say like that it's too dark i can't see anything
please rate your experience oh my goodness this is a horror game now or something this is a
horror game isn't it this is he turned it into a horror game is that what happened what's that
four two seven what the fuck i can't do anything i wonder what he found if what he wanted was to be
the leading man in his own story well perhaps he's gotten it down in wherever he is right now
i wonder if he's happy with his choice and if he's learned the heavy cost that comes with it
he'll understand soon what i was trying to tell him he needs me someone who will wrap everything
up at the end to make sense out of the chaos and the fear and the confusion that's who i am
that is what i mean to this world oh yes yes i'll be back there's no other way once this ends after
it all comes to a close then i'll be back the end will be here soon very soon i can wait used car
salesman here okay let's go how long was i sitting there stanley wandered to himself minutes days
centuries did something crucial happen while my senses were turned he made a note to be more
careful with time from now on all right so where do i should i turn on the mind control machine
new content oh new content what does that mean new content new content can i turn the brightness
up hello and thank you for playing the stanley parable ultra deluxe as you may know the stanley
parable was a video game released in 2013 on home computers not even on fucking wii u critical and
commercial success it was expanded upon in 2022 with the stanley parable ultra deluxe a reimagining
of the game for consoles and home computers the stanley parable ultra deluxe features exciting
new content that broadens and expands the world of the stanley parable delighting audiences the
world over well please step inside and see what thrilling new adventures await in the stanley
parable ultra deluxe five nights at ready this sounds delightful i'm very excited to see the
thrilling new ultra deluxe content i actually am too this is cool that's the worst turbo reaction
it was a fake tuber reaction okay so far it's an elevator nothing special yet but i'm sure it's
just the beginning of a mesmerizing adventure okay um is it broken what's going on here should we
should we be moving somewhere or oh there we go all right finally at long last it's onto the new
content i've never been more ready let's do it
i have to say initial impressions of stanley parable ultra deluxe mostly tedious it's as if them
oh okay let's see the content give me the content stanley content all right all right let's see it's
the jump circle jumps remaining oh there's a jump now okay well 11 10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2 1
i'm not gonna fucking do what you tell me to do is is that it surely that's not all the new content
there has to be something else right goodness another elevator stanley i have to say initial
impressions of this game are not positive it's just elevators and jumping is this what passes
for exciting new content if this is new content then i could just read you the whole dictionary
there's 20 hours of new content right there there's more than that counter 30 trillion you could
put that on the box the stanley parable ultra deluxe now with over a thousand hours of new
content and it's way more than it's more there's way more than that yes i knew there had to be
something else is there a melee now i'm ready for whatever it is all right where's the jump
i don't have a jump that's it oh you've got to be kidding me you see stanley this is what happens
when greedy video game developers with no respect for their fan base rush a cheap expansion to market
for no reason other than to make an easy that's pretty good don't get me started on the level of
craftsmanship that's gone into it that was good i'm looking right now at the game's achievements
and it's hard to believe one of them actually says test achievement please ignore what quality
assurance department signed off on this i'm infuriated and i'm offended and i i intend to
find these people on twitter and hold them personally accountable it's my fault stanley
i built up too much anticipation around the new content i'm afraid it could never have lived up
to such expectations that's true you're still with me why don't we just reset the game and we'll try
to get back to what the stanley parable is really about no frills no gimmicks just you and me having
a great time together wait so that's it do i have to do something else what do you say friend wait
this is different wait what happened this is different it's different door four eight door
four thirty stanley come over here in the vent i want to show you something oh not yet
keys no this cigarette butts holy shit oh you don't want to see the cool surprise i made for you well
you're a dork anyways you're a dork okay new content it's closed when stanley came to a set
of two open doors he entered the door on his left yet there was not a single person here either
okay feeling a wave of disbelief stanley decided to go up to his boss's office no i'm going down
here staircase stanley walked upstairs to his boss's office but stanley just couldn't do it
he considered the possibility of facing his boss oh wait i'm gonna dream left his post during work
hours he might be fired for that and in such a competitive economy okay begin the game okay
okay stanley come over here all right in the vent i want to show you something
okay you remember how cheap and unsatisfying the new ultra deluxe content turned out to be
thinking about the past and how much better the stanley parable used to be
i made something special and tucked it away here where the game's developers won't find it
just our little secret what is this is this the warcraft portal what's that thing called
it was a warcraft portal i've ruined it whatever i call it the memory zone it's where i've been
storing all my favorite memories so i can relive the peak experiences of my life
whenever i want a memory zone like the launch of the stanley parable on pc
the memory zone okay so what can i do in here did i really not answer the telephone i whatever
don't forget you see stanley doesn't the memory zone remind you of how wonderful stanley parable
was before it was solid with a cheap re-release remember back award-winning 2013 when the game
originally launched back then video games had integrity back then it all meant something oh
the waste 2013 2013 our first kiss my first car the release of stanley parable is 2013 was a pretty
dogshit year for video games wasn't it what even came out in 2013 gta 5 did that's it what else
came out in 2013 assassin's creed mario kart 8 stanley parable the last of us metal gear rising
metal gear rising bioshock infinite british academy award british academy award british
cat a lot of academy awards risk of rain old 2013 germa will never get the magic back
no we'll never get the magic i'll never get the magic of never mind
and over here is where i keep reviews of the stanley parable like this stunning
triumph of games journalism 10 out of 10 from destructoid.com didn't really get a 10
sterling rights did it actually get a 10 and a 10 we're so many games that aspire to be more
than games end up less than any form of art stanley parable it got a 10 out of 10 succeeds
to be every game ever created did you hear that stanley every game ever created that's how grand
and all-encompassing the original stanley mod db 2012 every game ever passed it was skyrim it
was persona 3 it was all of them and now it's nothing it's no games at all it isn't even the
stanley parable anymore it's just a husk now narrative excellent husk with an hour of
wait a minute elevator content persona three i didn't play i haven't played any of the personas
nostalgic it was good well i feel like in like 10 years i'm gonna be gripping one of the two of
those not 10 years holy shit dude whoa i was talking about being like buried like in a coffin
with those and like i'm thinking back to like i remember when i won those i said oh in 10 years
no i can i can this be a lot longer like 60 70 more years i'm gonna be gripping those things and
i'm like fucking 90 in the coffin just like the end is never the end here's another moving passage
this time from gamespot.com what is both a richly stimulating commentary on the nature of choice in
games and one that offers some of the most enjoyable surprising and rewarding choices
i've ever been confronted with in a game nine out of ten don't you get it stanley
the game was perfect it didn't need anything else it didn't need new content it just needed to be
left alone to spend the rest of time collecting dust in the hallowed hall of beloved video game
memories look how sad the serious room okay i can't go in the serious room how do i i can't
where's my jump i can't where's my i don't have a jump oh these were simpler times stanley
but i wouldn't give to go back to have it all over again and we're there stanley pick the door on the
right right that would be crazy basement wait hang on i don't recall this part of the memory
zone before what's this what's down here mario 64 andy it's a joke oh no no stanley it's a collection
of reviews from steam the online video game distributor i haven't looked at these in years
i can't even imagine what's been collecting down here steam reviews these reviews were glowing as
well weren't they oh god oh honestly i could not be bothered to play this game to full completion
the narrator is obnoxious and unfunny with his humor and dialogue proving to be more
irritating than entertaining unfunny i'm not trying to be funny i'm trying to make a serious
work of art i suppose i could write up a handful of gags to insert into the stanley parable but
the game is already such a densely layered web of profound philosophical insights that i can't even
imagine where i'd have the room to stick them unfunny okay does this do anything nope i climb
this nope remember there's a spider on your shelf he's probably eating the bad bugs can you guys
imagine if there's just one day yeah all of a sudden all of a sudden there was just a huge
tarantula just like here like and climbing over here and shit and i was like what are you talking
about guys fucking stop make shut up like a fucking 90s comedy movie says while the idea
for the game is good for someone who prefers non-linear games this preachiness gets annoying
fast preachy stanley i'm not preachy am i you can tell me if i'm preachy honestly you can
oh goodness this is actually quite shocking for me right i always worked to be honest i had always
thought of the game's dialogue as being rather terse to begin with you can't know how much fluff
i cut from the game to get it to feel as light and airy as it well i always thought it did but
maybe it wasn't three hours on record that's a lot you pretty much saw everything memory to have to
hold on to these black marks are my otherwise unimpeachable track record i feel like a failure
like i let these people down perhaps the stanley parable isn't quite as sterling as i always
remembered it's like the one person that's like hey dude dollhouse sucked it wasn't funny i'm just
like fuck and i'm like guys i gotta take a few i gotta take a week off streaming what's this one
got to say you constantly have to stop doing anything so the narrator can catch up with his
again explanations of what's happening i wish there was a skip button a skip button
let's stick up 10 hours well yes yes i think we can do that if i'm truly too preachy then
then maybe letting how do you play the original stanley parable for 10 hours
and i don't understand that negative reviews from the record only positive reviews of the stanley
parable that's my motto today and it's always been my motto i do anything for the customer stanley
yes a skip button we shall have these minds are resonant evil four like this this exact
thing i'm looking at right now this exact screenshot exact is resonant evil four right
here right there and here it is go ahead and give it a shot i'll get you forward in time
so that the second my incessant droning starts to how long has it been your back you see you
were only frozen in time for a few minutes but it was plenty of time for me to deliver
a long rambling monologue full of um well there's sport you really did catch me rambling on a bit
didn't you but that's the power of the button the minute i start to go off on a thoughtless
display of self-absorption it's right at your fingertips okay poof and it's all over oh i
can't wait to see what cooking nine will say about this and whether they'll edit the rating
of their steam review or at least change some of the wording perhaps to be honest i don't even
know if one can change their review can you edit a review i guess i should okay welcome back stanley
now i should say that the amount of time the button has been skipping through is becoming longer and
longer that last one was well i want to say maybe 30 45 minutes stanley stanley stanley please don't
push the button again it's been 12 hours you've just been frozen there why age skips are getting
longer but they're really truly getting longer and my god there's no way out of the room stanley
the door is gone it's completely gone i've looked at it from every angle i've checked every one of
those walls a thousand times yeah yeah stanley there's no door there's just you and the button
and if you keep pressing it i have no idea what will happen i have no idea how long i'll be made
to sit here and more than anything else i don't know how to stop you from pressing the button
great door i can't control anything in this room stanley i can't touch it sorry if the
muppets could do it you could too i have to know that sooner or later no matter how much i plead
with you you're going to press the button again why would you i've been thinking and thinking and i
i don't know what i can do to convince you otherwise oh my god and it's all because
of those reviews those reviews that i couldn't get out of my head i just couldn't ignore the
feedback why was it so important for me to fix the problem why did cookie nine's opinion matter
so much to me i've never even met oh stanley oh my goodness i have someone to talk to again
i think it's been a week or two weeks i've been sitting here all that time just sitting here
should have watered the plant and you'd think that that's just how it's always been right me
talking and you saying nothing would you think that it's exactly the same as always their door
doesn't that feel like what we've already been doing me just talking but it isn't stanley it
isn't the same at all it isn't even close because i know you can't hear me once you push that button
that's what i'm realizing now stanley i'm realizing that i needed to know that someone was
listening i needed there to be a vessel through which my words were moving it was the vessel i
needed stanley none of that matters anymore i'll give it all up i'll give up every branching path
i'll burn my story to the ground one single thing i need and god i can see now that i needed more
than anything is to know that someone else is taking it in these words that i'm saying i need
to know you can hear me because maybe stanley maybe if you can hear me then maybe it means i'm real
gotta keep me interested keep me interested play a sound effect or something perhaps yes perhaps
i've been scared this whole time that if i stop speaking i'll slip backwards into the silence and
be consumed by it i can't be taken by it stanley i can't lose myself in the stretch of emptiness
oh i'm gonna press it i'm gonna press it when you press that button you're still right there but i
know you're so tremendously far away and in those moments the emptiness folds itself outward in
between the two of us all right i'll give another minute i am suspended in its unyielding quiet
it's a i know it's like a podcast the edges of my reality curdling inward and decaying
i can tell that i am becoming less and less real yet to speak to you now i am alive
i am truly and completely here i am a being i am someone i am something i am being listened to
i am being recognized yes the emptiness between us has collapsed and i feel right now like i am not
a work of fiction i feel oh hello it's you you're here again welcome i have had time to think about
you and about us and about everything we've been through i've had so much how much time i
stopped keeping track after a year let's put a year sat down in one place and not move for one
entire year let me describe it for you to begin with there is only regret there is only the turning
wheel of missed opportunities i felt nothing at all but regret for the lost time stanley
door months i lost it all in a blur of the deepest longing to undo the past
and when that feeling had begun to subside where is he did he leave where did he go where is he
where is he how long has it been where is he what do you mean he's dead he's a computer
program he can't die what the fuck all right all right all right all right all right okay
okay all right all right turn it off turn it off turn it off turn it off turn it off
turn it off where is it turn it off i don't want to hear this turn it off but they didn't understand
the game was never meant to be funny it was meant to have a point it was meant to speak to the
human condition but where are the jokes where are the jokes they bemoan they screamed they gnashed
their teeth and said entertain us it right they had to leave a pathetic little thumbs down review
and make all of their pitiful demands but then he's talking too much they said yes he didn't
entertain us now he won't shut up it's the inconsistency it's the lack of accountability
unwillingness to examine with an uncompromising heart the words that they are speaking into the
world as though there were no consequences for a lack of cohesion in one's assessment of others
but of course absolutely anyone can leave a review so here's what we get we get these demands that
seek everything and are accountable to nothing i'm not skipping at all someone will say no skipping
there should be a skip button you should be able to freeze stanley in place while the narrator sits
there forever and ever we want all of this in the new stanley parable we demand it and then because
it was said because it was spoken now it simply has to happen the most immediate desires every
single thing demanded by every person at every moment in time if someone wants it then it's a
crime not to bring it into being have we been given to indulging every fleeting whim for no
reason other than to do so yes yes it seems that this is now the world we live in it seems that
we are play glover play glover discomfort with ourselves that our entertainment is farting you
chair hey hey make a sound funny stuff fart and make fart in the sound
i just want to hear that sound anymore gross minus 10 you've lost to the skip button every
time you press the skip button you lose a thousand viewers no that's not happening is it no is that
happening ah that's not is that happening the end is never the end is never the end is never
and is never the end is never the end is never the end is never the end well isn't he crafting
the game why would he just craft a like i don't know like a tuner sandwich or something for me
to hang out and eat why am i like demanding a sandwich what am i talking about this is like
not cool how long has it been i've been here for like a thousand years or something what's going
on can i get out vegeta like life is growing in here now dude what would be awesome is if like
you heard boom boom boom and like a t rex's face looked in and we weren't going forward we were
going backwards what the fuck that idea is dumb as hell that's stupid fuck you fuck you all right
how do i get out of here it's uh it's scary now hey why is it so scary what the fuck oh i can get
out doesn't work the fuck how long was i sitting there stanley wandered to himself minutes days
centuries did something crucial happen while my senses were turned he made a note to be more
careful with time from now on be more careful with time write that down new new content not
old new content okay oh good you notice my sign yes i have something very exciting to show you
what about that door i could probably go this way too right eventually maybe i don't know
new you see stanley i've been reflecting on the stanley parable and about how roundly disappointing
this ultra deluxe version has turned out to be i think it's all right stanley parable was a landmark
and any new content for it should live up to that legacy i think it's so far get this ultra
deluxe nonsense i say we take it one step even further which is why i'm very proud to announce
for the first time ever the stanley parable too oh yes you see isn't this far superior to a me
stanley parable too with a few minor additions think of all the new territory will cover with
a fully fledged sequel an entirely new experience built from the ground up why there are so many
possibilities it could go in so many different directions this is what fans have truly been
asking for investor showcase the end is never the end again stanley parable too calling it
the stanley parable too is just so much catchier than ultra deluxe don't you think ultra deluxe
what does it even mean but the stanley parable too now that's an artistic statement right there
yeah it's future-oriented it screams progress and innovation and long-term franchising potential
yeah i i yeah i agree oh but stanley parable colon let's get it i think would have
dragged in more people stanley parable colon fuck you people would be like what is that
they're back two doors win win sequential mid-share color red leverage paradigm shift
synergy oh this is the graphics hmm i would say i'm more of a fan of the fur i like the fur
this maybe i think of the one with the good one all the others are too i don't know i don't like
them i think they wanted the right idea number three number three that looks like a soap opera
no now to be clear i haven't quite nailed down what exactly the stanley parable too is going to
be but let's take a look at some of the features i've been developing for it i figure that if i
can loosely organize a handful of interesting concepts surely the game will sort of naturally
spring up around them it'll all work itself out game development is much more of a fuzzy magic
than anything scientific or logical really number two chat i feel like i drew these the end is never
the end again two two that looks like a movie poster this way to the show floor all right what
about new features what we got new features new content new features expo hall two whoa here we
are go on try out some of the new features merch is this all fake because i probably wear one of
these is this fake are these real things this t-shirt is the best new feature and then have
like the two on the back i would wear one of these what is that reassurance bucket the button that
says the name of the player that is playing the game hear your name in the game the button that
says the name of the player that's playing the game that's new back what do you mean back what
merch oh it's a qr code so it is real we want the qr code all right well get get close enough look
what do i want to tell you don't do it i'm not i i'll do it later i'll do it later i don't want
to do that right now no screenshots why is it making the sound that happens when you're about
to get like a phone call you guys know that sound that's fucking weird man this is the sound that
happens through speakers when your phone is about to ring that's so weird that's actually weird
the jump circle how do they get that sound how do they even know what that is enjoy the new
features okay name for the stanley parable too i asked myself what do players really want
and of course the first and most obvious answer is that they want to be individually recognized
and validated as people too big too small with that in mind my first addition to the game is
this button which speaks the name of the person playing the game isn't that wonderful try it here
uh is this gonna say my steam name because my steam name right now is fucking gas can
is it gas can right now sorry i should have clarified right now the button only says the
name jim but of course in the final game this button will say your name whatever name that is
here let's have you role play as jim i don't want to role play jim experience of this feature
just play along i promise you'll love it okay here we go let's take a deep breath clear your mind
forget whoever you are and simply become a person named jim i want you to imagine yourself living
as jim sleeping and waking as jim falling in love and being heartbroken as jim seizing all of the
world's possibilities as jim and as jim watching your dreams crumble into dust do you feel it
deeply i mean are you really truly jim right now and jim if so jeremy jim jeremy i mean press the
button yes you see what a thrill what a rush that was you the button described you do it again do
it again it hits even harder the second time if this were the only new feature in the stanley
parable too it would still be worth the money thrilling take a break from the jim button i'm
too emotionally drained from all of this personal validation oh there cowboy sometimes a person can
be too much jim i'm putting the jim button away otherwise soon you'll start to lose
all sense of who you actually are that's really loud oh all right a clip through the floor yeah
what are the new features are in this new game i actually kind of like that big button because
i really feel like it's going to be squishy and i can punch it and it'll resist me but it'll be
squishy so it'll be like you know what i mean it'll be like kind of full of i can like punch that
button that one is way too small the uh that one's kind of cool though because it's like a
like a pen cap right those are fun to do i would think this one's the wrong one yeah that's like
just basic i can't punch that one and i can't click that one frankly it's a waste of goddamn
time okay i suppose i could allow only people named jim to play the stanley parable too that
would actually save me the work of finishing this feature so what else is there there's this like
weird guy over there hold on epilogue i'm not ready for this an epilogue would be fun wouldn't
it stanley yes yes it will go at the end of the um well we'll figure that out later what's with
the weird metaverse guy all right i need to know what that is free achievement free new plus easy
achievement it can't be that simple go the jump circle you know what stanley i actually think the
jump circle was a pretty good idea i'd like to hang on to that for the sequel what do i have any
more jumps this map free achievement the button that says the name merge settings world champion
stanley parable reassurance bucket infinite hole all right well i need to see this first
well there's an exit all right exits over there but what's this can you find them can you find them
can you find them collect them all ah collectibles now it's a real video game in the stanley parable
too you all run around gathering up these miniature stanley figurines and what's truly
innovative is that there were you're on the website for collecting all of them what i don't
want to stifle the intrinsic you're on the qr code you simply collect all of them and then you move
the hell on with your unremarkable let me check the code please go to the website what do you mean
go to the website stanley parable too what wait what the fuck is this expo visitor live feed right
now a man named called germa is exploring the exhibit he's reading this right now what what the
hell are you talking about right because i pressed the button i thought you guys are fucking with me
this is this is weird hold on this is very weird this is what's on the fucking website right now
that's so strange how would they know i was germa that's what how would they know that that's so
weird my username my username is gas can that's why i gotta wake up that's fucking crazy that's
funny that's cool though all right let's keep going that's so weird they manually did it wow
that's cool hi all right that's cool it's gonna be a brain it's updating what do you mean it's
updating what is going on what what what it's taking this random thumbnails hold on
i just heard ollie ollie ollie i just heard holly say you in the other room i just heard it
i fucking heard it i heard holly say you i heard you oh i touched my tooth is that david no is it
updated let's go to the stanley parable 2.com okay oh no but i'm looking i'm looking over there
shit no i'm looking hold on i'm looking i can't be looking i can't be looking it's gonna i gotta be
looking down like i gotta get it again or how about this like there is there is there all right
wait what a fucking gerential that's so stupid all right now put the put the tarantula in my mouth
put the tarantula in my mouth i'm gonna be like shocked that it's in there you know what i mean
like like oh yeah is there not a soy face it's a fucking spider in my mouth face there
is the dev the dev is even sick of this joke the dev is like all right it's kind of funny but like
fucking hurry up okay all right wait no wait well that's funny that's funny all right let's go this
would be saying dude don't like open your mouth and like go like oh whoa whatever oh my oh no
whatever oh whatever you're torturing the devs that's kind of funny that they do that all right
let's go i didn't see what's down here this is weird um um hold on one second i'm realizing
something happened that i'm not happy about but i'm gonna whatever i'm not happy about this but
it's funny to show great what's going on with you i'm fucking choking nice clickbait what do
you mean update this different person they're cycling through like streamers man it's different
person they're just like look we're gonna move on from this because right now i believe this is
jacksepticeye now jack it's a good game that's i fucking love that that's so fucking funny
oh wait i can collect these but jacksepticeye is not even live is he god it really is the worst
when you collect everything in a video game and then they give you a big fancy reward absolutely
tragic they have wait they wouldn't mean this what does it say man calls shawn all right let's keep
going wait that's his his name's his name's not jack it's whatever it's all right jim well your
name's jim oh all right let's go let's go to the bucket a common complaint of the stanley parable
was that it was confusing and paradoxical that it engendered a chaotic sense of
well i'm happy to say that after much consideration i've engineered a clever solution
to this fundamental problem with the game it's the stanley parable reassurance bucket you see
stanley anytime you're holding the bucket a sense of calm and ease will fill your mind and your heart
it's true as long as you hold on to the bucket the many disorienting contradictions of the stanley
parable will feel perfectly normal and perhaps even comforting you may even come to long for
the gentle embrace of jarring cognitive dissonance while the bucket is in your arms and to be honest
it's a much more convenient solution for me than actually redesigning the game to be less
uncomfortable can you imagine what a pain in the ass that would be yes the bucket is the perfect
solution come on give it a try did i like mess up my white balance like here or something
ah can you feel it the glow of comfort even in the face of crushing despair
must already be sweeping through your body and in fact can i say that i do believe the bucket lends
you an air of charisma as well i think that just holding it has made you the slightest bit more
attractive as a person the benefits of the bucket seem to go on and on don't they put it down all
this and more awaits you in the stanley parable too it's a puke bucket can i be gross for a second
let's see does anyone give out awards for most enjoyable bucket in a video game that really
should be an award if it isn't already all right um so how do i put this down what about the
infinite hole i can't put this down what about the infinite hole get yours right now pull the
lever receive your new achievement no more steps it just works get yours right now now here's
something special you remember that broken test achievement that got left in the game on accident
yeah what the fuck's up with that technology to simply give you the achievement yes you see you'll
come to this lever and when you pull it the achievement will be given to you it's as simple
as that if this was real life i piss in this bucket right now i gotta pee right now there's
no bathroom here okay perhaps i should have clarified this is technology that will exist
right now the achievement is still fully broken i'm not a wizard stanley but i guarantee it will be
fixed in the sequel to at last satisfy the hordes of ravenous fans all over the world who have been
uproariously demanding this feature gamers we hear you and i gamers i can't get it come on
really come on quick i can't get this bullshit all right i'm gonna pay i'll be right back it'd be
like two minutes two what's going on guys welcome back i am gonna be hopping back into the stair in
stanley parable 2 all you gamers uh thanks for joining me as always let's uh get back to it if
we could let me adjust this because this needs to be brighter i don't have mad scientist here right
now but that's all right that worse or better for detail what'd you just say dude this stream is like
not funny whatever that's your opinion i think it looks fine whatever all right so i had the bucket
eat the horror get the achievement i i how am i supposed to get the achievement what do you mean
get the achievement what the fuck i can't get it what do you mean you can no i can't stop
i'm gonna start fucking timing people up but it wasn't for a few days you know all right i can't
get the achievement doesn't work please oh that doesn't work i probably have to do something
special i definitely have to do something special and come back here oh the lever i just i did it
already lying to me how you guys doing you guys doing good how are you how you doing today all
right actually how are you what other exhibits haven't we seen yet um what actually have i not
done i did the jump circle i did this i ate a minute oh i like that one uh free achievement
the button that says the name merch settings world champion was that okay settings world champion is
by the merch table let's do that is the bucket merch
settings world championship where's that here is this in okay i'll be honest i haven't yet
decided on this one i think that in the new version the office could use a bit of decoration
like balloons but get well someday and happy 12th birthday which would you go with happy 12th
birthday okay get well someday happy 12th birthday i think it's gonna be 12th birthday
you know sometimes when you solicit another person's opinion it makes you realize that you
knew which one you actually really wanted all along get well someday it is hey that's not fair
i said i wanted to get a happy whatever is that it no this option maybe i should have gone with no
no i've made my decision we're moving on no screenshots what if i take a screenshot
what a screenshot on steam that i might have remapped it f12 no what what what what could
i possibly remapped it to oh okay um i didn't do the hole where's the hole i didn't go down
there okay where's the hole okay office decorations epilogue collectibles infinite hole k where's k
all right so i need to go what's a9 collectibles so i gotta go from here i gotta go straight then
left i get out of here and go left this way right this way that's the name button down here
where was it over here oh there is infinite hole i was just in here wait oh oh huh huh i don't get
it i was already here where's the infinite hole i was i was already here this way he's actually
trolling i'm okay this is it i don't know i did that that was go that way infinite hole chart
educational use only it just keeps going for real stanley here's an idea that i'm truly fond of
it's never been done before in a video game this is in fact a hole that you can fall down forever
that's right infinite falling you can fall until the end of time if you like a standing forward
for video games as a medium okay so if i jump in that is it over i have to start over i throw the
bucket let's go you see isn't it wonderful one of my more ingenious concoctions if i do say so
it's gonna make me puke now then since you've gotten to see the infinite hole you can press
the teleport button to pop back up to the top and we can continue onward what if i hmm now i don't
know be a bummer but i do recommend you use the teleport button to go back to the top maybe do it
on the sooner rather than later spectrum of things it actually infinite or am i gonna splat
on the ground i don't know quite how to say this tactfully but it's possible that i slightly
exaggerated the infinite nature of the hole is it a very very deep hole to be certain it is
it's an extremely deep hole i don't want anyone to say that it isn't an astonishingly deep hole it
is is it infinite well that sort of depends on your definition of infinity it's got bigger
perspective the infinite is merely philosophical in nature it's more of a okay well good for you
you found the bottom of the hole i made live found me out stanley i'm a liar and a cheat and
you're so clever look i think the issue here is just that you're unusually fascinated by
falling true what normal person actually wants to fall infinitely i figured the hole was as deep as
anyone would actually need don't you put this on me maybe you're the problem how do i get out of
here the thing's got a little heated there i think we both said some things we didn't mean
why don't we just put all this behind us and agree to just call the whole mostly infinite if that
works for you then go ahead and press the teleport button to warp up to the top of that's a lie you
that's that's false advertising up here when you're ready false advertising i'm not going
anywhere till you fix it and make it actually infinite i got all day great now i'm very excited
oh for heaven you see i was right the problem is you take a big slide the problem is that you like
holes too much a normal person would have said yep that's an infinite hole right there goes on
forever till the end of time don't need to see it all but not you oh no no no no you have a weird
sort of oh hey did the hole seem even shorter to you this time i couldn't help but feel like
you spent a little less time in there than you did before i mean admittedly i didn't make an
infinite does this keep getting shorter and shorter that not infinite well i suppose once
again there's nothing to do here if you decide you've had enough of the hole you can hit the
teleport button and come join me up above had enough i'm positively thrilled gosh
how could i have guessed you're back in the hole if this stuff okay yeah i'm starting to become
extremely certain that the hole is not only not infinite but that it's growing steadily less and
less infinite i suspect that i'm starting to hit the point where it's no longer feasible to call
infinitely deep now it's just a kind of big hole for accountability and marketing what's going on
here stanley i have no explanation for the uncertain nature of the hole's length here
let's try something let's pop back up to the top and we'll see if it gets any shorter let's see it
well there it is the shame of my eyes come to haunt me oh my fucking ankle oh i know you're
just twisted it i stopped it it just bent it the other way
see this fucking goddamn stupid ass fucking lip on the ledge who am i to judge you just do
whatever it is you're here to do and hit the teleport button when you're ready to move on
fucking hurt i rolled my goddamn ankle hmm is the um teleport button not working
you sure well i mean what did you do i really don't have an explanation it was working just
a moment ago try it again still nothing well i suppose i suppose there is one thing i can
do to fix i can't climb out of here i'm out goodbye stanley you couldn't bear to be away
from the hole and now you'll get more time with it than you could ever have asked for it's a win
for everyone you get to be with the hole i get to do literally anything else take care stanley
i hope you and the whole have a wonderful rest of it hey i have a bucket though i can turn the
bucket around step on it and get out every pause button is a roman numeral just the two of us we
can make it if we try just the two of us just the two of us just the two of us building castles
meeting at 2 p.m sincerely management am i actually stuck in here uh well goodbye change
your perspective change your perception this is the this is the part where the bugs start crawling
all over everybody this is the exact music that gets played when like like just like roaches just
like everywhere in your reality i stopped what the fuck wait is it is it like cartoon music
actually leave me alone this is fun but you're awake it seems you had sort of dozed off drifting
away into because this hole is just so darn fascinating that i want you to be wide awake
for every second of it you don't want to miss a single moment so how about if i just pop in
from time to time and wake you up to keep you really truly focused on the whole from the looks
of things you and i will have many many years here in this hole does this payback for all the
skipping all of them stay alert stanley i'll be back this is my punishment for all the fast
forwarding are we doing it again oh back out here here we are go on try out some of the new features
okay go back to the hole that's what i was thinking is to go back to the hole yeah i can get another
bucket too should i get two buckets all right i'm gonna get two buckets and i'm going back to the
hole and then i'm gonna get wait i this is i can get two out of six right hold on let me do this
first wait one i can't get it i get another one shit are they actually hidden you need to do a
welding i will do a well don't worry can i get another one i can't get a second bucket i can
only have one they don't it doesn't reset it just sends you the yeah okay all right i want to go back
to the hole oh the balloons are actually here now that's fine all right whole time i want to go back
in here you should do the clown world i figured there's probably a clown world hey you're gonna
lock me out i can't go there that's horse shit okay so where can i go that's new what's new over
here did i go that way that's new well how do i get in that door how do i get up there how do i
get up there oh i can go up here mostly mostly infinite hole settings world championship all
right let's do that why is it closed what are you talking about it's closed check your settings
how do i do it should i just change every single setting i did these story what the fuck okay was
it 86 all right video v-sync i have to do every single thing i don't want to turn like v-sync off
res x res i can't change this what is res x res i drew every setting in checkbox all right i did
every one of these i did every one of these i did every one of these did i get it did i get it i
missed one every single language okay sound effect volume you set every slider to maximum then go
through each number individually with the right key shut up no way okay that part actually was
a troll all right well fuck all right so did i do it i think i clicked every single one of these i
did every single one did open you'd get an achievement thing if you did it i know fuck i
missed one of the sub settings which one was my achievement click through res x res what what is
res x res simplified control i did that already just google it i did it i did everything rebind
the simplified controls are you fucking kidding me set all setting sliders in the menu to all the
available numbers what didn't i do that i don't actually have to do this right that counts okay
that counts joel what's up joel thanks for the raid welcome everybody from joel stream we're
currently really trying to five head our way through the stanley parable 2 uh hope you had
a good stream worst stream 2020 please i have to okay if you're wondering what i'm doing right now
all the viewers from joel i have to put every single slider to each individual number that it
can possibly be to open this door that's a spoiler by the way hopefully you've already played it if
not then holy smokes i'm sorry take the website there i'll help you you can drag the sliders but
you need to be on every number once also enable all check boxes and check their sub settings of
friendly dev i think i'm i think i got it okay it's done i just need to do this now okay on on off
off off off there do it this dude's unhinged all right audio what you can slide all right but i did
it i already did it i already clicked on everything look the arrow sub options big cat why am i a big
cat all the sub where the sub options aren't these this is the only sub option where are the other
sub options i can't change the resolution are there any more sub options oh okay field of view
i did field of view i did this i did this invert why i think i did everything check the website
you have audio video and controls you missed some sub settings in general i did what where are they
video this is a sub settings in video where are they they said general what what are you talking
about you missed some sub settings in general where subtitles off i think i pressed every button
in general audio please then i did it already dude i pressed i i pressed every button i pressed every
button i pressed every single the general tab i pressed every fucking button like 50 times
dude i pressed every single button okay on on one-handed walking presentation english we can
put it in fucking dutch for all i care turn everything off slide this this slide australia
this is all the way look okay this too what am i missing you have to toggle some settings first
to see the sub options what what the fuck wait i did where these are the subs options website in
general like translation labels i need to go to bed just keep playing this bit isn't super important
also follow us on twitter at crows x3 we deserve it after all this tech support in general like
translation what do you mean like translation labels translation labels yeah i did this already
i did it already how do i get out of here what's with my mouse what the fuck is wrong with my
computer it worked it worked it worked it worked i got it i got it i got it my controls are inverted
i can see you've gotten the settings world champion achievement well done you've experienced every
setting i'm inverted to all corners of the settings menu there's nothing you haven't seen so just for
dude i did that already too i'm including an entirely new setting something called bump
scocity what exactly is bump scocity well i haven't embarrassing it wasn't embarrassing i
fucking trust everybody adjust it on some sort of slider and that it'll be available from the
settings menu we'll sort the rest of the details out later i hope you're looking forward to trying
out every level of bump scocity in the stanley parable too all right first of all um i gotta
turn this i gotta turn all this stuff off i have a ton of shit on like my field of view all right
invert no control of vibration now get out of here english subtitles medium with a little bit
of opacity i don't need all this okay what about is my video settings fine and we're good all
right we're good yeah everything's fine okay bump scocity was bump scocity thousand i appreciate
the help though dev i'm brave i have a p brain so tweet now no i remember was so bad at following
directions it's incredible he wasn't fired years ago but i but i went i did everything
all right so what does what does bump scocity do oh this is the epilogue room okay very cool
did i miss any of the rooms am i done i'm done here oh this is a cool area this place was cool
that was a fun exhibit now where do i go can i leave oh there's an exit right where is it
it's around here somewhere where's the exit i think it's down here um yeah i saw the tweet
all right have you seen everything you wanted to i think so to move on now i think i am what's this
so stanley what do you think do you like all of the new features yes i know it's not exactly
clear yet how exactly these features will come together as one single coherent video game but
i can feel it in my soul it's going to work there's definitely a good game in there somewhere
say let's do an experiment i'll arrange these new features together and we'll see whether or not
it coheres into a meaningful gameplay experience okay are you ready here it is i give you
what the stanley parable two what if i what are the chapstick um well i mean there's potential here
right it's sort of okay never mind hold on let me do a different arrangement i didn't eat it did i
eat it yes this is much better i feel good about it here we go i didn't i didn't need it too well
that's oh yeah who am i kidding stanley this isn't a coherent video game at all it's a lot of gags
and i do very much enjoy creating gags but they don't add up to anything i didn't need it i wanted
more than anything to create a sequel that would capture all the magic of the first game i wanted
fans to love it no matter how good these gags are they wouldn't stand on their own they would need
the structure in the gameplay of the original oh yeah wait maybe that's it i can take the original
stanley parable and simply well insert a few of my new features into it tastefully of course
with respect with care for the vision and integrity of the original game would it possibly
work i suppose it could but it would need a really really tremendous title screen a title
screen that says with bold and uncompromising conviction this is the stanley parable two
let me see if i can whip something up like the designs that were out front go ahead take a look
oh look at that stanley parable two here we go this is the story of a man named stanley stanley
worked for a company in a big building where he was employee number four two seven employee number
four two seven's job was simple he sat at his desk in room four two seven and he pushed buttons on a
keyboard orders came to him through a monitor on his desk telling him what buttons to push
how long to push them and in what order this is what employee four two seven did every day
of every month of every year bump viscosity looks crazy yeah others might have considered it so
ranting stanley relished every moment that the orders came in it's a lot of bump viscosity it's
making me made exactly the backs of my eyeballs are itchy stanley you know i mean that's kind of
when a lot of bump viscosity happens that's when you get there's a lot one day something very
peculiar happened something that would forever change stanley something he would never quite
forget he had been at his desk for nearly an hour when he realized that not one single order
had arrived on the monitor for him to follow no one had showed up to give him instructions call
a meeting or even say hi never in all his years at the company had this happened this complete
isolation something was very clearly wrong shocked frozen solid stanley found himself unable to move
for the longest time but as he came to his wits and regained his senses he got up from his desk
and stepped out of his office okay so should i do the same thing i did last time but stanley simply
couldn't handle the pressure that's like what i did last time to make a decision what if a crucial
outcome fell under his responsibility he had never been trained for that no this couldn't go
any way except badly the thing to do now stanley thought to himself is to wait does this change
nothing will hurt me nothing this doesn't change me in here i can be happy forever i will be happy
stanley waited oh this is different this is not different then days had years gone by he no longer
all right this is not different but the one thing he knew for sure beyond any doubt was that if he
waited long enough it was my bucket answers would come eventually someday they would have stopped
wasting our time very soon now this will end he will be spoken to he will be told what to do
now it's just a little bit closer now it's even closer here it comes all right so that doesn't
change so what changed balloons are here uncomfortable and stanley decided that as
soon as he found a new space he felt safe in that he would never leave it again in his life
what about the claw the brim closet oh my bucket stanley picked up the bucket nice i feel happy now
wait that's two inputs now oh every time i come back i do another input i wonder what happens
that's cool all right we'll find out in a minute we'll check it out stanley clutched the bucket
tightly to his chest and entered the door still no one was here stanley needed the bucket's warmth
and comfort now more than ever okay perhaps his boss's office was where he'd find answers
this is open again nice oh stanley can you feel it the broom closet it wants the bucket
oh
other cleaning supplies good for you stanley don't give him don't hand over the bucket i know how
hard it must be given the pressure that the broom closet is putting on your shoulders right now but
you have to be strong this is your bucket this is your companion and lifelong friend fine you
can't hand it over we're getting into name calling now it seems this is how low the broom closet
has said that it has to resort to this stream of petty insults simply in order to get you to
hand over the bucket yeah stanley i never liked this broom closet for a variety of reasons
me neither do i this is worse than i had imagined yeah fuck this place the closet has the goal to
imply that you and the bucket are not truly deep and lasting friends what that your relationship
is purely superficial and convenient oh shut up life is super null and meaningless when they say
that the same sort of kinship towards any inanimate object which happened to lay in your path in an
even partially enticing manner well i never i thought they i thought we were friends lay into
it really tell the broom closet off for its demeaning comments expand on the wide variety
of experiences you and the bucket have shared together go through each of them point by point
share your journal entries detailing the rich emotional landscape of your feelings for the
bucket as they have changed and evolved over the years yeah let him have it it stinks like a public
bathroom in here and the walls need to be painted and okay i've got you something which i think will
help settle this debate once and for all here we go yeah now it's settled yeah no more debate
no more discussion take a hike broom closet with all your meandering philosophical diatribes
about the nature of cleaning supplies and their relationship to broom closets in the natural
yeah yeah let me kick the fucking you man fuck you what are you gonna do fuck you right i've got a
second sticker back here and i'm going to slap it on as well because i think it's appropriate
but fuck up yeah see yeah i feel that it works because the sticker is also a bucket that way if
you're ever unsure whether the thing you're holding is a bucket too far look down at this
sticker and say to yourself oh it's a bucket there really is a wide variety of applications for this
sticker violence doesn't solve anything dude no i just like kicked this thing i just kicked like
this metal thing take the name calling and the dismissal of your kinship with the bucket but now
the broom closet is just giving us a silent treatment and to be honest i'm sick of the
pettiness on display you can stay here all you like but i've had it with this impetulant room
of cleaning supplies easily the most childish such room i've ever been in i'll see you outside and
we can get on with the story about you and your bucket bro you didn't really fucking say those
things did you did you say that you didn't say those things right man really what a disappointing
disappointing coming to a staircase stanley and the bucket walked upstairs to the boss's office
okay scared me why remember no reward for collecting all of these only the intrinsic
pleasure of a job well done you can't buy that sort of happiness stanley god knows i've tried
so i employ you to savor each and every moment you come across one of these beautiful figurines
okay to be rich is it a crime to commit crimes isn't it rich what a life it would be to have
to pick just one you definitely aren't cleaning this every day and like you just use your bathroom
wall to write all this shit and somebody else has to take it off and then you come back and
do it again you're annoying somebody here and like you should just stop write it on a fucking
notepad stepping wait manager's office stanley was once again stunned to discover not an indication
of any human life crushed by the weight of this revelation stanford stanley gets the correct code
by sheer luck got it was it the bucket knew all along was the bucket guiding him yes this is
certainly the most logical explanation what about the piano nothing with the piano
nothing but the piano hey don't i die here oh another miniature stanley figurine i only need
three more you know there really must be a snappier name for these things what about
mini stands stanley figs oh what about stanley yes stanley i think i like that
another stan lorraine under your belt okay what happens when i get six treatment thank you
all right this time i'm going to turn the mind control thing on go back up i can't the elevator
race downward plummeting towards an unknown fate it would be all stanley could do to keep himself
together if not for the bucket soothing him comforting him reassuring that in this darkest
moment of uncertainty he would be all right the bucket is here for you stanley everything
will be fine all right stanley and the bucket walked straight ahead through the large door
that read the mind control facility okay i could go that way or you could go with this way with
the bucket i'm gonna turn it on i'm gonna turn it on what happens when you turn it on the lights
rose on an enormous room packed with television screens what horrible secret did this place hold
stanley and the bucket both wandered to themselves yeah i'm gonna turn it on and see what happens
i want to do the input thing again monitors jumped and stanley nearly dropped the bucket in shock
everyone in the office was being videotaped monitored like guinea pigs the bucket had never
seen anything like this and it very nearly burst into tears as stanley
reassuring it that everything would be fine okay now yeah live bucket reaction was the bucket under
the mind control facilities influence as well had the bucket been told to do things it didn't wish
to do what kinds of things does a bucket want to do or not want to do in the first place these
questions raised furiously and stanley okay if i put the bucket on my head will the mind control
radiation get through the bucket no he screamed into the bucket he couldn't accept it his own
life in someone else's control never he squeezed the bucket tighter his one friend in the entire
world where did i just go this point he could trust no one except for the bucket where did i
just go wait did i just leave oh no wait what but here is the proof the heart of the operation
controls labeled with emotions happy or sad or content walking eating working all of it
monitored and commanded from this very place and as the cold reality of his past began to sink in
stanley decided that this are going there would never again exert its terrible power over another
what if i walk down here for he and the bucket would dismantle the controls for good
two best friends stanley and the bucket up against the world they high-fived in a really cool way
and the bucket made a sassy comment about taking down the system okay so let's turn it on i want
to turn this on when at last they came to the source of the room's power stanley and the bucket
knew it was their obligation to put an end to this horrible place and to everything it stood
for but at the last second the bucket jumped in and pressed the button to turn on the controls
double cross stanley gasped in horror had this been the bucket's plan all along to take over the
machine and claim the power for itself how could the bucket have betrayed him like this stanley
was prepared to throw the bucket away in disgust when suddenly an image appeared upon the enormous
screen birds silly silly birds the control buttons became active again okay do i want
eagle or do i want um sparrow sparrow stanley flipped through one video of silly birds after
another and then it dawned on him this wasn't a mind control facility at all what is it was a
facility for monitoring and surveilling silly birds all over the world what a silly bird only
a facade to disguise its true intentions at the bucket known this all along stanley marveled at
the metal genius in his hands the one who had pointed him towards this incredible discovery
stanley and the bucket never found freedom because they spent the rest of their lives here in this
place flipping through lives oh wow of the silliest birds imaginable of all the possible paths his
life could have taken it looked like robots like mechanical
and stanley was happy no i want to see more of those that don't cut me off i want to see more
of that when stanley came to a set of two open doors he entered the door on his left where's
my bucket this was not the correct way to the meeting room and stanley knew it perfectly well
perhaps he wanted to stop by the employee lounge first just to admire it i can't do it without the
bucket i'm nothing without the bucket if you're nothing without the bucket then you're nothing
butterflies in his stomach giddy in a way he had never known before was it this rupert eager to
get back to business stanley took the first open door on his left i've never gone this way and so
he detoured through the maintenance section walked straight ahead to the opposite door and got back
on track no i went this way but stanley didn't want to go back to the office
he wanted to wander about and get even further off track so now in order to get back he needed
to go left right oh no no it's to the right my mistake no no no no not the right why would i
have ever said it was to the right what was i thinking it's clearly oh dear would you hold
on for a minute please that door do a long rip now let's see we went down right left down left
right yep yep okay okay yes i've got it now this story is absolutely definitely this way okay wait
can't go that way have to go this way kind of scary oh the mind control room no no no no no no no
no this isn't right at all you're not supposed to be here yet this is all a spoiler quick stanley
close your eyes i already saw this okay okay we just we just have to get back to um oh who am i
kidding it's all rubbish now the whole story completely unusable however rather than waste
my time trying to salvage this nonsense we'll just restart the game from oh he's sending me
back to the beginning suppose we don't wander so far off track hmm okay rubbish all right where's
my bucket all of his co-workers were gone what could it mean stanley decided to go to the meeting
room perhaps he had simply missed a memo was the input thing right it was i could do the input
thing i can't there's another input input come on let me do input three really really and the
bucket's not here either that's sad that's really sad i don't have my bucket how am i
supposed to ever play this game again i missed the bucket when stanley wait what no no i restarted
i swear i definitely restarted the game over completely fresh everything should be what did
something change stanley did you change anything when we were back in that room with all the
monitors did you move the story somewhere i didn't have my bucket hold on am i asking you i'm the one
who wrote the story was right here just a minute ago i know for sure that it's here somewhere okay
then it's an adventure god stanley let's find the story um this one oh by the way i got a blood wash
and murder house i'll say it this is the worst adventure i've ever been on i can promise you
there definitely was a story here before do we just do we need to restart the game again
no i'll find it unlikely that we'll ever progress by starting over and over again
i got it it's got to be better than this i got it okay let's give it a shot no i got it i just
got it oh my god it's another one of those kind of short horror games right all of his co-workers
were gone what could it mean stanley decided to go to the meeting room if you guys have any more of
those like two three hours short horror games i you're so much louder than the game am i am i
good okay yep it's worse where the doors go what the fuck remembering this wrong it's oh dude it's
pop it's because of this this is it's because i turned everything down the story is back where
we just came from why don't we go back the other direction and see if we missed anything where's
my game i i paid for a fucking game i paid for a game and it's not here i'm just quit i'm quitting
uh i knew we'd miss something what the story here it comes no wait never mind not the story
the fuck okay let's head back the other way and retrace our steps i don't like this well i'll be
honest i don't recognize this place at all is this the story i don't think so i can't quite recall
but i believe my story took place in an office building it is that correct hmm do you remember
me what do you know what since i've completely forgotten what we were supposed to be doing
how about no don't restart the game again oh congratulations oh that worked i know you put
in a lot of hard work and it really paid off so good job oh no i don't feel right about this i
did it we both know you didn't put in any actual work for that win some people win fair and square
and this was not one of those situations okay i'm getting weirded out by whatever this place is
i don't care what might happen this time i have to restart stanley parable two adventure lines
time to make sure we don't get lost i've employed the help of the stanley parable adventure line
just follow the line okay how simple is that that's more like it no input oh well okay
everybody left no no i'm done we're leaving it up to the line from now on all right fine fine
okay you see the line knows where the story is it's over in this direction onward stanley
to destiny though here's a thought wouldn't wherever we end up be our destination even if
there's no story there no or to put it another way is the story of no destination still a story
no simply by the act of moving forward are we implying a journey such that a destination
is inevitably conjured into being via the very manifestation of the nature of life itself
story case stanley i need to follow this train of thought for a minute just stick with me i'll let
you finish it now we can both agree that the nature of existence is in fact a byproduct of
one subjective experience of that existence and just waiting for my turn to talk now i'm not
listening at all i'm just waiting for my turn to talk rests inside of your subjective experience
of this office is this office in fact the skeleton of my own relative experiential
mental subjective construct here hang on we're back there well i'd like to apologize
not sure where i was going with all that you know what i think what we need right now is a bit of
music to lighten the mood i agree a story is a narrative construct
uh i got i missed the line i didn't do it right wait what wait what way too dang cut the music
go back and look at that fern stanley this fern what's way too dank important later in the story
make sure you study it closely and remember it carefully you won't want to miss anything i
can understand the shape and the size and the um directions it's going and that's fern i think
i got it okay i got it fern fern whatever there's a fern wait what we're back at the office no no no
line you do know we're looking for the stanley parable right the story is any of this ringing a
bell um this way i guess not oh no no no spoilers how could you have done this to us and after we
trusted you after everything we've been through you no i can't take this anymore to hell with it
restart did i follow the line still you know what stanley i say forget the adventure line what's it
ever done for us we're intelligent people right why can't we make up our own story yeah we could
exciting daring mysterious oh this all sounds perfectly doable why don't we simply start
wandering in well i don't know how about this direction now yes this is exciting
just me and stanley forging a new path a new story well it could be anything
what do you want our story to be go wild use your imagination i want to be a knight whatever it
might be stanley i'm ready for it i'll be a knight the staff that has spells and i want to fight a
dragon and i want to win oh no not you again i don't care about anything i'd also like to
veto the line from having any role in our awesome new story no lines or monitor rooms just don't
acknowledge it we should be fine you'd be a lion yeah i wouldn't be a lion ah a choice we get to
make a decision from here the story is in another choice how important we mustn't squander the
opportunity in fact i believe i need a minute to think here just walk in circles for a minute
okay so i know that each door has to lead somewhere which means that somewhere the
place where we're trying to go this is fun to walk around this door that leads here and that in turn
means that our destination corresponds with the counter-inverted reverse doors origin
so starting from the right let us ask will taking the right door lead us to where we're going
and since the answer is clearly yes then by all accounts the door on the right is the correct one
that's not another victory for logic come stanley our destiny awaits this is my only choice i have
to go through i have to guys do this this is kind of fun i'm breaking the rules now just want to
be a little bit edgy there hold up what's this
confusion ending you're telling me that's what this is it's all one giant ending
and we're supposed to restart the game but eight eight times that's really how all this goes
it's all determined so now according to the schedule i restart again then what
am i just supposed to forget well what if i don't want to forget my mind goes blank simply
because it's written here on this thing line the line line after long stanley dies well
i die me why don't i get to decide why don't i get a say in all of this is it really find a bookstore
no it can't be i don't want it to be i don't want the game to keep restarting i don't want
to forget what's going on i don't want to be trapped like this i won't restart the game i
won't do it i won't do it i won't do it i don't want to do that i don't want to see you there
and i don't want to see the turtle did we do it wearing a hat the cycle the um whatever it is
that made this schedule how would we even know will someone come for us will something happen
somebody said he's gonna do it you were fucking right okay i guess now we just wait you know
i suppose in some way that this is a kind of story wouldn't you agree i'm not quite sure if
we're in the destination or the journey though they're always saying that life is about the
journey and not the destination so why is it why is it counted off right now we'll find out won't
we eventually well in the meantime hey what the fuck ow what happened what was that that was
ridiculous that hurt all of his co-workers were gone what could it mean stanley decided to go to
the meeting room perhaps he had simply missed him he's gonna do it meeting today in the meeting room
stanley lifted the bucket into his arms and a wave of comfort rushed over him stanley pressed the
bucket upon every little thing in the office nothing responded to the bucket's touch but it
did little to discourage stanley's belief in the magic of the bucket let's go he didn't check the
input i didn't see it stanley clutched the bucket all right so where i didn't go to the left the
door on his left should i wait i did do the left and i pressed the button should i go right this
time and go where should i go i'm gonna say yeah i'm gonna say right this was not the correct way
to the meeting room but stanley had felt the bucket calling to him telling him that the employee
lounge was simply the place to be and here it was had the bucket turned out to be correct was
this better than the meeting room yes stanley thought to himself yes perhaps it truly was
stupid fucking idiot never mind the bucket was wrong stanley took the door on his left
to go back to the meeting room i haven't gone up there okay i'm gonna go here no said the bucket
don't go to the meeting room go somewhere else the cargo lift yes go there go to the cargo lift
every audio book you've ever listened to in your life good said the bucket now ride the lift all
the way to the top there's something up there i need you to do i'm going up stanley did not
question why or how this bucket was speaking to him it should have alarmed him of course because
buckets can't talk but stanley chose not to think about this obvious fact he was firmly convinced
that the bucket had spoken to him and he unthinkingly did whatever the bucket asked
okay in here said the bucket go into this dark room over here stanley once again
obeyed blindly i love the bucket voice the bucket voice is amazing okay what else do you want to do
bucket hey now pick up the phone said the bucket pick up the phone and it will take us back home
where we can go about life together i just again i just see the in the studio with the glasses
down here like this reading the script i like just see it i love it i just it's just so comfortable
to me it's so comfortable to me this is the sad story of a man named stanley and his bucket once
upon a time i gave stanley a bucket because i thought he was lonely and could use a friend
and then very distressingly he began to believe the bucket could speak to him
okay my friend take me to work with you okay the stanley parable reassurance bucket was merely
meant to provide the comforting glow of companionship it doesn't literally talk
and give you orders whatever stanley is hearing the bucket say to him is just in his head but
you mean it wasn't talking to me it was just it was you the whole time
cheap that's fucking cheap take me back home with you okay lately i've been concerned about him
oh wouldn't you be concerned as well dev twitter see him delusional like this obsessing over an
inanimate object i want to say something to him but i don't know how i can convince him i don't
know what's the what's on the dev's twitter oh i've seen this yeah i've seen this all of his
co-workers were gone
i've seen it scroll down but okay all of his co-workers yeah everyone was so bad at
following directions he was incredibly he wasn't fired yeah i've seen it yeah i i saw that video
it's funny yeah that's from a while ago that's from like like a year ago yeah i've seen it
that's fun go back to work do i sleep why am i just going back and forth here
i'm just going back and forth back without like eating or sleeping stanley can you hear me listen
to me it's just a bucket it can't think it can't talk all it would ever truly do for you is
effectively transfer a liquid from one location to a different location what a huge deal it doesn't
do anything else that literally changed the course of all humanity basic tools made us gain
consciousness essentially like the idea of the bucket of the stone axe of the wheel
that changed the course of human history don't listen to the loud man press p for us to go back
home yes let's go you see he's not listening he's still taking orders from the bucket you know once
upon a time it was me he took orders from me he trusted and listened to not anymore he cares about
his awful bucket this stupid hunk of metal not anymore ignore anyone in your life except me
it's sad i suppose he doesn't need me anymore from now on he's just going to cling to this
bucket this cold empty bucket this sort of shiny bucket well i'll give it this the bucket does
have a nice shine to it it is very shiny and it makes fun noises too you believe i'm really
don't you stanley go back home yes i suppose on closer inspection that it doesn't quite look
like your average hardware store bucket it's just a little more um what am i trying to say
yeah plus i could put it in my head capable of transporting liquid i can put it over my head
better at moving an amount of water from one room to another and go like this
and i didn't think it was funny relive the same day with me over and over and over again okay
oh my am i saying better at carrying water from room to room it's a bucket it's literally just a
bucket why do i feel some need to point out the ways in which it's so much more than just a
regular bucket because it is a coin it's just a coin which it is you know that line that i've just
watched but you know what i mean i'm having feelings for the bucket no no no no no what's
going on why do i want to be with the bucket hear what the bucket has to say do anything it asks
what the fuck i don't understand perhaps perhaps if i had the bucket this would be less confusing
yes the bucket could tell me what to do in this troublesome situation now this is my ring i have
the one bucket to rule us all not you it's mine mine stanley give me the bucket no to me give me
now it's my bucket i need it no to me now no or i'll go back to work stanley it better not be
gone or i'm gonna be really pissed off i'm gonna be very co-workers were gone where is it what could
it mean stanley decided to go to the meeting room perhaps he had simply missed a memo no matter how
hard stanley looked he couldn't find a trace of his co-workers where is it thank goodness
the confusion and the chaos all seemed to melt away as stanley embraced the bucket thank goodness
input input input i i didn't see a computer i looked at the computers i didn't see one with
an input on it look i didn't see one how do i get it oh go to the phone again go do another phone
ending stanley clutched the bucket tightly to his this was not the correct way to the meeting room
but stanley had felt the bucket calling to him telling him that the employee lounge was simply
the place to be and here it was had the bucket turned out to be correct was this better than
the meeting room no never mind the bucket was wrong stanley took the door on his left
to go back to the meeting room no he didn't no said the bucket don't go to the meeting room
mr bucket somewhere else a cargo lift yes good at the top of my mouth mr bucket all the way to
the top of my mouth there's something up there i need you to do we're all gonna run mr bucket
not question why or how it's a fun was speaking to him it should have alarmed him of course we
come off the left no but stanley chose not to think about this obvious fact he was firmly convinced
that the bucket had spoken to him and he unthinkingly did whatever the bucket asked but stanley
feared that any path he walked might lead to the separation of himself and the bucket
his dearest friend so he threw himself to his death that they might die in one another's arms
how deeply touching i'm gonna do the phone i'm gonna go to the phone i'm gonna go to the phone
i'm gonna go to the phone i decided to go to the meeting room perhaps he had simple memo
warmth spread through stanley's arms with the bucket in his arms again he was home i'm gonna go
clutch the bucket tightly to his chin this was not the correct way to the meeting room
but stanley had felt the bucket calling to him telling him that the employee lounge was simply
the place to be and here it was had the bucket turned out to be correct he did the phone with
the bucket already the bucket was wrong did i stanley took the door on his left to go back
to the meeting was something else i could do with the phone no said the bucket don't go to the
meeting room go somewhere else the cargo lift yes well what about yeah what about this one
go and unplug now ride the lift all the way to the top there's something up there i need you to do
stanley did not question why or how this bucket was speaking it should have alarmed
it was because buckets can't talk what stanley chose not to think about this obvious fact
i'll go back firmly convinced that the bucket had spoken to him and he unthinkingly did whatever
the bucket asked okay we'll do that next in here said the bucket go into this dark room over here
stanley once again obeyed blindly okay phone phone rings don't answer the phone instead
now pick up the phone said the bucket pick up the phone and it will take us back home where we can
go about oh hold on why did you unplug the phone i felt like it were you trying to resist the
bucket's orders stanley i was joking obviously the bucket isn't talking to you and telling you to
do things buckets can't talk it was a joke don't you get the joke it's funny stanley a talking
bucket the bucket was talking can't you see oh goodness i must have really bungled up the
delivery if you actually took me seriously the bucket had a different voice than you
paused for longer or spoken quicker oh comedic timing is so difficult i wish i were better at it
but there isn't exactly an instructional video on comedy that one can watch to fully
oh wait yes there is um it's sitting right here why let's take a look what is what is comedic timing
what is comedic timing how does it work how long should it last how can it be used to effectively
silence your political enemies and more importantly can it be taught in its entirety within 90 seconds
so it takes decades thankfully the answer to all of these questions decades yes craft let's dive
deeper if you've ever told a joke or made someone laugh in all likelihood you did it while standing
50 to 80 centimeters from them in a room of no more than 76 degrees fahrenheit with one of your
arms raised straight upward at a 15 degree angle from your body these are the optimal conditions
for good comedic timing to begin the joke start by stating and spelling your name
next provide a brief synopsis of the joke including the specific times at which the
recipient of the joke will laugh and then spell out your name a second time with these steps
complete it's time to begin the humor speak the entire joke in no more than 18 seconds
and no less than 13 and a half pausing only for bathroom breaks when necessary
when the joke has concluded it is customary to inform your listener that the joke is over
by declaring in your loudest possible voice i'm dunny with the funny let's practice screaming
i'm dunny with the funny now i'm not gonna do that good this saying is a perfect example
of expectation management that was the cornerstone of good comedy wasn't it finally
it's time to hand out surveys collecting hard data from your audience on how
wrapped they were throughout the joke is the only way to grow with minus twos and plus twos
an effective survey should be no less than 10 pages long and should include the same question
reprinted several times just to ensure the survey taker is actually paying attention
and not simply filling in answers at random and that's all there is with these strategies
at your disposal you'll have audiences doubled over in laughter and even tripled over in laughter
scary scary just remember to let them stop laughing at some point you gut-busting little
scamp after all with each of us needed on the front lines of the war to fight the 12-legged
who's very existence and a very lucky die in a hailstorm of bullets and mandibles
all of us must be prepared to give our lives to this noble cause just as our children must
do after us and their children after them godspeed and may earth reign supreme
jesus hey goodness this video is a little outdated isn't it well no matter i think
the fundamentals of proper comedic timing are still as relevant today as they were back then
so with that in mind i believe the only way forward is for us to return to the two doors
and walk through all of this again so i can try telling my story with more appropriate comedic
delivery come along does it change i hope it does that'd be funny if it changed does he start
talking in like a funny voice talking a funny voice please i can feel it this time i'm really
going to nail the delivery you'll be in stitches a talking bucket you'll say how ridiculous how
absurd what a hilarious concept the king of comedy that's what y'all call me thank goodness
we have the instructional video otherwise who knows where we'd be right now i'm gonna eat with
the funny comedy that's for sure the bucket spoke to stanley the bucket spoke the bucket spoke oh
i'll figure it out on the fly i think a little higher to think things i think a little bit higher
you actually nailed it with the with the higher kind of more nasally approach i think that was
actually funny because a bucket i'd add an echo to your voice too just a slight one just like a
little small one like this and talk kind of with a higher voice and maybe have like sort of a new
york accent i think that might be kind of fucking funny too a new york accent and a kind of a high
echoey voice i think would nail it and be crass too be crass say some swears it's a bucket it
sees like paint and and slop and dirt it would be a little crass be crass go fun with it have fun
with it is the joke over yet i'm not conforming to that here we go you ready when stanley and the
bucket came to a set of two open doors they entered the door on the left no no no no no you
were supposed to go through the door on the right what leading back to the phone what the fuck i
don't even look at the instructional video i think this is all covered very no but i no way i can
make the comedic timing work now it's done what is completely down and over it's all your fault
stanley i'm going to be ridiculed in the community of other joke writers i'm going to be shamed at
every one of our meetings from now on all because you couldn't watch a simple video and take a hint
are you proud of yourself for bringing me down stanley are you proud what the hell happened
when stanley and the bucket came to a set of two open doors they entered the door on the left
there you go all right let's see it well we're back at the phone already no no no what's going
on there were supposed to be several rooms leading up to it's called improv figure it out to be a
build-up to this point a dramatic display of remarkable comedic wit which you got to be
ready for anything scene with the phone but now the timing's completely off the joke will never
land well not the way it was meant to and it's all my fault i must have forgotten that the phone room
comes immediately after the two doors room what an egregious mistake i'd made a fool of myself
i don't deserve the title of king of comedy i'm nothing i'm not even the lowliest joke telling
well well i think i need to go back and re-watch that instructional video again
yes surely that will help me improve my stanley you love the bucket so much it's like you
it's as though all of your other dispositions pale in comparison yes let me try that again
stanley i heard that you are in love with a bucket you are where the hell am i is it the delivery
pale with shame pale with shame pale what's another word to describe a bucket stanley this
bucket is so mental i think i saw it playing guitar no no no you don't need to tell a joke
you don't gotta tell a joke yeah that's unfortunate unfortunate so i never got the
normal ending somebody said that's the normal ending workers were gone i got the bucket normal
ending decided to go to the meeting room perhaps he had simply missed a memo damn it stanley picked
up the bucket and smiled he'd never be alone again not truly alone not with the bucket around
fucking come on stanley clutched the bucket tightly to his chest all right where are we going
entered the door on his left so i did the right i didn't do i want to go left oh the collectible
shoot i'll get it after i'll get it after how can we find them trust the completionist instinct you
must find them it will be a reward for finding them all well floating objects have appeared across
the office we have to synergize our resources to ensure their retrieval there are many questions
let me tell you spotted one what makes them float in the air who took these pictures of them
follow clues provided by employee 416 we can do it red room i got the hiccups good luck all right
i gotta go to the red room large ooh a large room lots of boxes stairs something to do with stairs
somewhere both red and blue no i know where those are stanley we must move on from this broom closet
simply because i have no remaining stickers if i did you can guarantee we'd be in here for hours
but alas no stickers coming to a staircase stanley on the bucket walked upstairs to the
boss's office up or down i think i did it up already and now i'm torn between stan lorine's
what do you think stanley what name better encapsulates the intrinsic sense of happiness
that you get from seeing a small number i need two more that's it screen go up by one
let me sit on it i'm sure it will come to me wait this is the floating ending he considered the
possibility of facing his boss admitting he had left his post during work hours he might be found
for that do i get a different bucket ending competitive economy why had he taken that risk
all because he believed everyone had vanished his boss would think he was crazy and then
something occurred to stanley i have my bucket maybe he thought to himself maybe i am crazy
he looked down i still die am i crazy he asked the bucket the bucket returned his gaze but said
nothing at all that's strange stanley thought usually the bucket is a source of guidance and
wisdom for me in difficult times such as these he held the bucket close yet felt none of its
familiar reassurance and comfort and that's when stanley realized floating this isn't my bucket
it's just a normal everyday bucket someone else's bucket perhaps how i end up with someone else's
bucket this is all terribly wrong i got the stickers on it good would come from this hey who
knows what sorts of bizarre hallucinations stanley might experience without the psychologically
grounding presence of his bucket why did it go away indeed now he noticed that the rooms were
repeating which was of course very odd and now he felt himself floating off the ground what the
hell oh gracious what the hell without my bucket i've gone truly mad where is it i must find it
far off in the distance now he heard it calling to him stanley stanley it's me the bucket where are
you could it truly be he rushed forward from room to room passing by one bucket after the next
oh shit none of them were his none of them were his special bucket why come to me stanley find me
he had to find the bucket he had to return to his old where's my bucket was the only way to truly
restore his sanity and then suddenly he froze dead in his tracks he knew where the voice of
the bucket had been coming from the real bucket was inside of him all along it was incredibly
painful stanley doubled over in agony and blacked out wait this is the story of a woman i still die
i actually still die mariella woke up on a day like any other the bucket in the scene rose
picked up her bucket of comfort and security and walked to her place of work
but on this particular day her walk was interrupted by the body of a man
who had stumbled through town talking and screaming to himself and then collapsed
dead on the sidewalk right away she knew what the problem he didn't have a bucket this man
had no bucket right of course he'd gone mad ranting and raving about a narrator describing
all of his actions and how everything is predetermined and free will is an illusion
and it's all just a video game it could all have been prevented if only he'd taken his bucket with
him perhaps he didn't even realize he'd forgotten his bucket at home in the first place how cruel
the world can be mariella thought and she hugged her own bucket even tighter but of course she had
no time for this there were a myriad of confusing problems she would soon have to confront at work
for which her bucket would provide absolute guidance and total clarity on everything
heck yes she thought to herself my life kicks ass and she backflipped all the way to work
what am i doing i take this fucking thing everywhere everywhere i take it to work all
of his co-workers i take it to the store what could it mean i constantly have it decided right
here meeting room perhaps he had simply i take it everywhere somebody got my mouth and it was
not even that bad because it's not even a big deal it's just like fucking whatever it is
what is chapstick made out of helanthus anus sunflower seed oil coconut oil beeswax castor
seed oil aroma shea butter cocoa butter strawberry seed oil some kind of soybean
glycerin or something oil geraniol and natural flavor now this is content thank you what was that
oh okay now i'm gonna go get the one that's in the big room the big room then i'll need one more
after that when stanley came to a set of two open doors he had this was not the correct way to the
meeting room and stanley knew it perfectly well perhaps he wanted to stop where's my bucket where's
my bucket i don't have my bucket anymore just to admire it where's my bucket was okay i missed i
didn't take i didn't pick the bucket up but i fucked it all up to get back to business stanley
took the first open door on his left no idea i'm gonna get up here i'll jump off stanley was so bad
at following directions it's incredible he wasn't five years ago you're getting one more now stanley
you've nearly gotten all of the figler and marines very soon you'll collect the last one and then the
first number will equal the second number and that will be it will be different people by then
different in the sense that we used to have none of them looks why he looks so sad we have them all
you can't go back to when you had no figler and marines none of us can but in his eagerness to
prove that he is in control of the story and no one gets to tell him what to do stanley left from
the platform and plunged to his death all right good job stanley everyone thinks you are very
powerful my bucket all of his co-workers were gone where's this last one stanley decided to go
to the meeting room perhaps he had simply the good old bucket just stanley and the bucket off on
another thrilling adventure together stanley clutched the bucket tightly to his chest
and entered the door on his left no this was not the correct way to the meeting room
nope stanley had felt the bucket calling to him telling him that the employee lounge was simply
the place to be and here it was had the bucket turned out to be correct was it no never mind
the bucket was wrong no the bucket wasn't wrong the door on his left we're going the right way
to the meeting room because i'm doing this now said the bucket don't go to the meeting room
go somewhere else the cargo lift yes go there go to the cargo lift okay what's down here
cassette tapes oh narrator dialogue narrator dialogue oh we're gonna meet the narrator this
is day number 295 take number i don't even know lost track nothing feels real anymore
wait is this supposed to be the narrator when he was young i study this bucket less sense
anything makes this is me talking sheer euphoria i feel every time i pick it up this is dark souls
dialogue no matter how many times i've done it it's always the same feeling and the emptiness
in my chest when i set it down doesn't make sense there's no explanation for it i still
haven't figured out why i see the world so differently when this bucket is in my arms
why everything feels so what do i do with this treasure i can i can monetize it it's unthinkable
the amounts of money people will pay for just an hour with the bucket this is my golden ticket
but i have to be careful because as soon as this gets out there's going to be a target on my back
even now i don't know who might be trying to get what's that who's there
blast harry potter you just ruined the moment i have to hear it i keep fucking thinking about it
i can't stop thinking about it dude i really fucking can't i promise i can't stop thinking
about this okay we're good i just need to hear it every like four or five days i just need to
hear it every four or five days that's it what happened this is different all of his
co-workers were gone what could it mean what how i decided to go to the meeting room perhaps he
had simply missed a memo where are we going today the bucket asked stanley just smile anywhere they
went together would be stanley pressed the bucket upon every little thing in the office
yay responded to the bucket's touch but it did little to discourage stanley's belief
in the magic of the bucket the whiteboard ending dog mode let me tell you about the
dog sound like christmas album where it's like the jingle bells and shit they don't sell them
anymore they don't make them anymore they don't make it anymore
i used to fucking cry laughing at that shit it was so stupid we wish you a merry christmas
barking dog christmas song wait you found it already do they still exist
okay what is this this is jingle bells i'm serious if you want to win a you laugh you
lose challenge or like a no emotion challenge play this for somebody and they're gonna be like
just what the fuck man like it's too much it's just stupid i'll try i'll try it that one's not
even funny the dogs aren't even there anymore wait what
where do they go they're not here okay there they are okay listen to the cat ones
so all right this is the last one and i'm done i would i would fucking
i want to like put this up i want to go like big christmas party and just put this on
it's just it's it's just so different it's just so odd that people would be like sitting there
drinking the drinks and like it's not the typical just shit that's on the radio it'd be like
what the fuck is this like what this is kind of weird no it's a 10 hour version guys i'm not
gonna let it play the whole time we lost like 300 viewers amateurs let's go they clutched the
bucket tightly to his chest and entered the door on his left all right so what was i gonna do
it was more like 4 000 oops all right we need to go left and then we need to go
somewhere else i want to find that oh that just scared the shit out of me
okay somewhere both red and blue coming to a staircase standy on the bucket walked upstairs
his office okay i'm gonna go up no no where do i go up no where should i go from here it is up
isn't it i need a red and blue door because the boss knows that what the boss says goes if the
boss has suffered losses then that's what the boss chose oh shut the fuck up stepping into his
manager's office stanley was once again stunned to discover not an indication of any human life
two what is it two eight of this revelation stanley may have broken down into an emotional
four five but stanley gets the correct code by sheer luck was it that the bucket knew all along
was the bucket guiding him no it was the dog yes right dog certainly the most logical explanation
right dog you have the floor whatever you'd like to say about what just happened
oh hey hey hey hey what the fuck what the fuck dude i gave you the fucking floor and
jesus that was actually fucked i'm not letting the dog talk again just fucked up fuck man stanley
and the bucket walked straight ahead through the large door that read mind control facility oh can
i do i can do this one right i haven't done this one with a bucket this passageway had the word
escape written on it the truth was that at the end of this hall stanley and the bucket would
both meet a violent death i got where do what do i find the red and the blue door next to each other
right the door behind them was not shut stanley and the bucket still had every opportunity to
turn around and get back on track at this point stanley and the bucket were knowingly walking
forward into a very painful death for each of them so now what happens if i have the bucket
we're gonna do infomercials tonight plan is to do infomercials tomorrow as the machine word into
motion and stanley and the bucket inch closer to their demise stanley reflected on how meaningless
the bucket's warmth and comfort had turned out to be to be sure it puts the mind and the soul i stop
it with the bucket embrace the bucket but what use is a sense of ease when you're about to be crushed
to death this is what stanley thought to himself and he sort of kicked himself for wasting so much
time carrying a bucket everywhere farewell stanley farewell stanley cried the narrator who is this
person why they and the bucket were led helplessly into the enormous metal jaws in a single visceral
instant the bucket's life came to an end as it was crushed violently to death it was a shame the
death of such a magnificent bucket it's true that all buckets are radiant in their own way
but this one stood above the rest it was a glorious bucket to behold what the fuck the bucket
welcomes you to the grand exhibit okay this is different can you see how arrogant it was for
stanley to take a bucket like this and to claim it for his own can you see the hubris that blinded
him can you see that the bucket is far more noble than stanley will ever be in his short life
um all right bucket with two handles this bucket is depicted as having two handles such a design
has never been created in real life haven't been deemed too dangerous and recklessly experimental
every year dozens are put to death just for attempting it word the inferno bucket replica
of the inferno bucket which in the medieval era was so powerfully alluring that it drove dozens
of nations to war with one another for control of it billions died and yet in spite of it all the
simple fact remains no one can control a bucket what the cave drawing while we know that buckets
predate the existence of mankind we do not know by how long this cave drawing depicts early men's
discovery of the practical uses of the bucket by which time the bucket had already likely been
around for several millennia notice in these drawings how the bucket is allowing itself to be
used having judged humanity to be worthy of its treasures no man can own a bucket and certainly
not a bucket as dazzling to behold as this one it is man who should kneel before the bucket
the hanging bucket this piece symbolizes the necessary relationship between bucket and
humanity however clear our grasp of the bucket may be there is yet more that is always out of reach
this distance inevitably is for our own good i got it but there is something we can do something
we can do together you and i that will right this terrible wrong let stanley die let him be crushed
by the machine don't reset the game don't give him another opportunity to run off with another
beautiful bucket we can save the world's buckets from their treatment as tools and implements if
only we let stanley die together the bucket shall take its place as ruler as leader as commander of
a new world a new vision i can't wait to tell this story to my co-workers stanley thought
how amusing they'll find it oh won't we all just laugh and laugh at the time i thought everyone had
gone missing no matter how hard stanley looked he couldn't find a trace of his co-workers
when stanley came to a set of all right i want to get that last one he entered the door on his left
i want to get the last um this was not the correct way to the meeting room and stanley knew it
perfectly well it's this way wanted to stop and then on the catwalk right lounge first just to admire
it it was okay i think it's yeah i gotta go as if we get the two doors to get back to business
stanley took the first open door on his am i gonna get the true ending if i get all the
bobblehead things stanley was so bad at following directions it's incredible he wasn't fired years
ago look stanley i think perhaps we've gotten off on the wrong foot here what about the bucket i'm
not sure i don't want it really i'm not i realize that investing your trust in someone else can be
difficult but the fact is that the story has been about nothing but you all this time there's someone
you've been neglecting stanley someone you forgot one really wait what was in the middle of something
do you have zero consideration for others are you that convinced that i want something bad to
happen to you okay i don't know how to convince you of this but i really do want to help you
to show you something beautiful okay let me prove it let me prove that i'm on your side
give me a chance my eye okay so both red and blue stanley walked through the red door
and got them all the last stiggly wiggly savor this moment stanley this is a real accomplishment
this is doing something just for the sake of doing it where so many people expect to be rewarded for
the most trivial achievements you've insisted that a job well done is its own reward i would
tell you that i'm proud of you for collecting them all but that would be like a reward and we
can't have that so instead i'll just say it's done we're all done here and now we can go to
whatever the hell you were doing before you hunted for figurines okay let's go on the blue door i just
have to go to perhaps you misunderstood stanley walked through the red door red oh thank god you
are willing to listen to me do you see that i really have wanted you to be happy all this time
the problem is all these choices the two of us always trying to get some reset just begin the
game again just reset do i win did i win should i go back to the stanley parable 2 area is that a
better idea stanley i'm sorry but i have to put a pause on things it's just it's those figurines
those figs i haven't stopped thinking about them since you nabbed every last one wasn't it just
the most intrinsically fulfilling moment of your entire life didn't it fill you to the brim with
their inner richness yes i know we're supposed to be telling a story who's up there but won't you
please indulge me with one more trip back to the memory zone okay i would love nothing more than
to revisit the figurines just one more time i wish there was a burp mode where i could be like
now remembering when stanley found the collectibles okay remember this 2013 stanley
parable stanley parable stanley parable is an exploration story games his choice what does
it say audience award stanley parable all right i've already seen this wait here's where it all
began the first collectible oh right no idea of how many of them we'd find sure it's at six right
there on the screen but how could we know for certain we were so innocent we'll never be like
that again stanley are there any more this one right here wait it was definitely a trick it was
a trick and here was the second stan lorraine you found this one all on your own just by poking
around in the boss's bathroom you did that stanley i'll be honest back then i had no faith in you to
find any of them let alone six but you continue to surprise me in all sorts of mundane
unremarkable ways seven am i actually did i just like get am i screwed can i go back through them
okay let's do a little quiz which of these rooms was the room you found your third mini stan can
you remember i think it was under the stairs it was under the stairs you're fine you don't need to
okay it was under the stairs yeah it was i mean no yeah it was it was under the stairs that was
the fourth one are you sure was it the office don't lie to me is it wrong hey that's exactly
right it was here behind the boss's office it was the third one you picked it up and then after that
you had three of them i'm glad these moments are so crystal clear in your memory but i shouldn't be
surprised after all science tells us that it's impossible to forget your third time doing anything
okay you gone let's see what came next oh yes we found a figly in this pink room
oh well i can't actually say i remember being in this room but it's here in the memory zone
so it must have happened okay definitely wasn't here unless this is somewhere else
any of the doors open no what's this this was the fifth mini stan oh yeah was really something
special it was in the warehouse i remember it so clearly in fact because this one is
particularly special to me i made a little down there to commemorate the occasion enjoy
windows movie maker you found it near the cargo lift
ah takes you back doesn't it i've heard to be like time making 2000 but it was eight minutes
i wouldn't have spent on anything else okay i can go down there can i make it
there's a wait i can go down there is it will i die if i fall here i can go through look dog b
well like 2006 yeah i think i'm dead if i do that looks like i can go i can go over there though
back here again and then stanley then we came to the last collectible the final figurine
right here by the red and blue doors this memory is the most distinct and clear in my mind perhaps
because it was the one that happened more recently than all the others who can truly say how the mind
works all i know is that this is the moment where you picked up a figly and i thought to myself
yes that's all of them they're all collected it was a moment unlike any other except for the
other moments picking up figurines which it was exactly like what are you doing i'm being a bird
uh does it matter which one i go in you are in the present and then there was no more because
we've caught up to the present moment nothing left to do but move onward into the future goodbye
memory zone hey lbl just checking no no no i'm not done i'm not ready to move on stop the
loading screen isn't there some way we can stay here keep enjoying these figurines let's just
go backwards we'll do the memory zone again from the opposite direction no i don't feel
oh my god okay can i like turn the tv off or something unplug it i have to go through and do
all that again backwards oh god okay whatever came through here it's right around the left
there's the first one the room with the red and blue doors i remember this i must say of all the
figurines we looked at in our initial tour of the memory zone this one is the most distinct and
clear in my mind let's keep going i want more weirdo and here's where i made that video don't
you remember the video we watched i don't watch it again oh my fucking god yes that was a great
video it only has 600 thumbs down and two thumbs up it's so great you're doing great it's a great
video still don't remember the pink room stanley still no memory of this one good room though a
solid room a pretty solid room i enjoy it these really were a treat to hunt down you know if there
have been any kind of reward for finding all of these it really would have muted the intrinsic
joy of collecting them i'm very glad we resisted the temptation next one i wonder what my most
disliked video was what was it what is it my most dis no it wasn't smite should i go under the
stairs the dark souls one i don't think so it was demon lord at freddy's you know what that actually
might be it that actually might be it don't you remember yes i remember it too the past is truly
a wonderful thing why does anyone ever choose to leave it keep going yeah okay it's because
people thought that was first of all not funny and second of all people hated five nights at freddy's
i remember that yep i remember uploading that video and that was right in the middle of five
nights at freddy was getting popular and people like hated it and i was doing like this demon
like avatar thing and people didn't think it was funny so it was a double whammy oh there's this
one this is it the very first one we found in the exhibit where i introduced you to the figlarines
oh i want more memories stanley i want to keep going no this is there what came before this
the big bang i fucking hate demon lord zaraxas collect them all i don't agree with you but it's
look it's the terrible new content that we were originally sold on i remember hating it back then
the time does put a rosy filter on everything in fact i dare say i'm actually quite fond of it now
in five nights at freddy's now is more more memories more popular now than it ever was
interesting oh yes the two doors who could have forgotten that a classic memory this
that video made the game popular no it did not that was one of the least viewed videos on my
channel and i was at the tail end of that game's initial first five nights at freddy's one popularity
i was like four months late to the party and i tried to do like a fun little spin on it and
i was way too late way too late if anything that video made people dislike the game more
and me and me too and before everything else there was your office there are probably people
from like 2012 2013 there's something i feel i can remember i can remember who left in rage
and never came back from that video yes i'm remembering something now i remember before
this whole story got started back then i was i was different i used to make big decisions i was
passionate i was skeptical i weighed each decision with profound thoughtfulness and then somewhere
along the way i stopped making decisions i became lazy and i came up with well came up with a
character named stanley to do my thinking for me he would make the decisions he would decide which
way to go i would cheer him on as he collected figurines for no reason why did i invent stanley
was i lonely yes perhaps that's it perhaps i needed to imagine i had companionship
okay and stanley really did make for a wonderful companion even if he was a fiction but i suppose
it's grown old i i want to think for myself again i want to go back to how it used to be
yes i can be on my own again i can do it i'll be stronger this time i'll take care of myself
i don't need stanley anymore oh but he truly was so much fun to play with you know what
since we're in the memory zone how about one more good memory let's go back just once and
give stanley one more run of the office and one more go retire him for good i did enjoy telling
his story so very much okay here we go this is the story of a man named stanley one more i get one
more go i gotta make this count wait stanley thought to himself am i sure that the orders
stopped coming in how is that possible they never stopped surely i was mistaken this is it okay last
run the end is never the end the end is never the end the end is never the end the end is never the
end the end is never the end i need to make stanley happy with the bucket of course a good bucket a
strong bucket a humble bucket a committed bucket a bucket of culture and distinction
which way do i go they clutched the bucket tightly to his chest and entered the door on his left how
do i how do i end the how should i how should i end it just make him happy still no one was here
stanley needed the bucket's warmth and comfort now more than ever perhaps his boss's office was
where he'd find answers reboot the game entirely today i just quit the game okay rebooting please
enter the current time 9 15 p.m hang on hang on before we get started can i just say something
thank you for actually setting the clock both times you booted up the game a lot of people
don't take that step seriously just leave the clock set at 12 and call it a day when you're
actually taking the time to set the clock and i appreciate that that's how i know that you care
about the experience you're paying attention i don't even have any way of knowing if the times
you're setting are correct tell you what i'll make you a deal since you've been so cooperative
next time you boot up the game and see the screen just set the clock to your favorite time pick
whatever time you want even if it's not the correct time you've earned it all right get back to the
video game 10 o'clock 10 p.m 10 p.m is my favorite time not too late not too early to still like
about probably a couple two or three hours left in the night relaxing reboot it again again okay
i'm gonna say no you know 9 30 is probably my favorite time when i look at the clock and i see
it's 9 30 i'm like all right there's still the whole night is there i'm relaxing i'm cool i'm
good it's at least probably three to five hours before i'm even going to think about sleep at
current time they said i could make it whatever i want 9 30 is the best time 9 30 p.m not that far
from now that's my favorite time well could you simply not resist giving me the correct time
again no that's what time that's not that's 15 minutes from now after all i know how much you
enjoy setting the time correctly and now i'm curious how accurate 9 30 p.m is let's use another
slider to find out how accurate is 9 30 p.m i would say that's very very close that's like
incredibly close right i mean that's in literally like 13 minutes you know can i just say regardless
of the accuracy of the clock i'm having a great time adjusting these settings i feel like i'm
learning more about you now you like things to be set it's good to collect data i wish we had more
sliders but we've gone through all the sliders i have perhaps i can invent some new sliders to
gather new data on you shouldn't be too hard yeah let me whip up a couple new ones to be ready by
the next time you boot up the game stop rebooting it's terrifying please adjust the slider until the
computer is barely visible i like it this is brightness please just slide into the dog and
cat are friends i'd say right about there right there please just slide until the number five
becomes the number nine one two three four five six nine nine well it says becomes the number nine
not spell it not no bullshit no roman numerals the number nine just that that's what it's telling
me to do just slide until you stop adjusting the slider okay hold on all right i think maybe
i think i'm thinking about here yeah i think so maybe just a little bit more i'm not feeling it i
think it's a little bit up right here is fine which of the two made-up words below is most
appealing to you scrumptious or ocarina oh my fucking god ocarina a million times
please don't adjust the slider okay you know what time it is right now yes i do it is nine twenty
is the time that it is right now the correct time yes what is it what is time anyway i don't know
is there anything about yourself that you haven't told me yeah shit love yeah you're a computer
yes will you come back to visit me yes what time is it does anyone really truly know of course they
don't nobody knows anything you and i don't even know each other we're like strangers sure i've
adjusted all the game settings to your exact specifications but who hasn't it's just what i
do like a day job and now the job is over there's no more information for me to gather i've collected
all the data on you that i can i still don't really know you you don't know me and neither of us know
what time it is i guess some settings are just unsettable but if i'm being totally honest the
clock doesn't do anything in the game anyways you won't have me here when the game starts next time
but that's okay video games are meant to be played alone you like being alone don't you that's maybe
the only information that i really learned about you it's not even what time for me to leave there's
still one more setting that we need to adjust but it may take a little time before i'm ready for that
not really in my job description but that's okay perhaps you'll see me again if you can find me
talk soon epilogue did i get did i get something i got something i got something epilogue many many
years later wait this is from the the skipping this is back when i skipped a bunch of times all
right yeah i guess i camped out for a night i gotta keep going it reminds me of outer wilds
to the moon towards the towards the moon towards the moon i'm gonna say towards the moon
towards the moon towards the moon to work going the direction towards the moon this is the memory
zone right didn't i leave the memory zone why am i going back to the memory zone in loving memory
the stanley parable 2 bookie nine's blog review the stanley parable 2 like so many i enjoyed
my time with the original stanley parable which underscores how truly disappointed i am with its
sequel with a first game teamed with originality the stanley parable 2 is dull uninspired and
often insulting to its fan base rather than expand on what made the first game enjoyable the sequel
veers off into territory nobody asked for an infinitely deep hole who cares where are the new
endings what about enjoyable bits from the stanley parable one like the adventure line instead we
get an uninspired side quest collecting figurines even this diversion feels incomplete collecting
all the figurines gives you nothing i must say though i found the bucket to be quite comforting
a welcome reprieve from 2027 this one stanley parable 2 is gonna come out stanley parable
developers no more spinoffs no more sequels when the stanley parable launched to a massive
success in 2013 its creators made plans to build the property into an entire franchise
but a disastrous critical and commercial reception the stanley parable 2 has prompted the developers
to rethink their ambitions as outlined in a press release they published today to clear that more
stanley parable is not what the fans want we thought that we had a vision for the series
that players would be excited about it turns out this could not have been further from the truth
press release goes on to promise to preserve the artistic integrity of the original game and
to stop assaulting fans with our reckless and insulting creative visions the word sorry appears
more than 25 times in the press release get on the green we got pretty close the cat dog friendship
will last forever i can go left stanley that's me what are they all the only one is it stanley
okay oh cool 25 perfect that's a perfect number thank you for enjoying the new content yeah it
was pretty good that was fun anything else hello again it's nice to see you but it's terrible to
learn that there will never be another stanley parable game did you read what the developer said
preserve the integrity of the franchise what nonsense stanley parable is not sacred we do
not need to protect it screw the legacy let's keep making stanley parable games until the sun
explodes let's run this franchise into the ground let's drag it through the mud and back and if
people hate it who cares you see that was the narrator's problem he was so obsessed with what
people thought of his work don't make his mistake don't cling to the legacy let it burn it's not
hard in fact let me show you together we're going to make the stanley parable three it's simple all
we do is change the number in a game's title screen we also really need a really dumb subtitle
for the game something loud and gaudy good try combining some random words together to make a
new title for our game but what i say was let's get it stanley parable three let's get it stanley
parable three pantry pantry i love it every time you restart the game we'll advance the number of
sequels by one and then we'll pick a new subtitle that way the stanley parable will never end and
nothing in the game itself will change when you do this either adding more content sounds like work
no need to do that it will just be the same content recycled again and again and again with a new
title screen what do you say should we go forward with this plan i like it but i want you to have a
say as well should i do that that sounds kind of funny sure let's do it a new sequel every time
you start the game and you know what did you put faith in my idea i feel like giving you something
as well see i'm noticing that the narrator's never found a way to give you the broken achievement
did he of course not i wouldn't expect him to know how it's been bothering me let's fix it
all right there the achievement machine is all fixed see i'm on your side we're in this together
we're going to keep this train rolling the stanley parable cannot end it can only spiral in on
itself forever i must keep the wheel turning i'm ready are you ready great there's only one last
thing we need to do please enter the current time i'm 30 i'm 30 that's my favorite time okay
this is the story of a man named stanley stanley worked for a company in a big building where he
was employee number 427 employee number 427's job was simple he sat at his desk in room 427
and how do i go get the um the achievement orders came to him through a monitor on his desk telling
him what buttons to push how long to push them and in what order this is what employee 427 did
every day of every month of every year the new content door although others might have considered
it so ranting stanley relished every moment that the orders came in oh the content door okay we
have been made exactly for this job and stanley was so the narrator made this guy up well then
who's the computer then one day something very peculiar happened something that would forever
change stanley who's the computer something he would never quite forget he had been at his desk
for nearly an hour when he realized that not one single order had arrived on the monitor for him
to follow no one had showed up to give him instructions call a meeting or even say hi
never in all his years at the company had this happened this complete isolation i don't think
the intro changes very clearly wrong shocked frozen solid stanley found himself unable to
move for the longest time but as he came to his wits and regained his senses he got up from his
desk and stepped out of his office okay all of his co-workers were gone what could it mean
stanley decided to go to the meeting room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
how is the new content ah where's the content embrace of an old friend a weathered companionship
that stands the test of time stanley clung the bucket to his cheek could his co-workers really
all be gone oh please are you really just doing this for the achievement yeah click a door five
times is that all that you think an achievement is worth no no no no i can't just give these
merits away for such little effort a measly five clicks how many do you want now suppose you were
to click the door 20 times you got it i would say that's the kind of effort that warrants recognition
i have to say i'm still not feeling the satisfaction of witnessing true effort
for a noble cause gonna be like a thousand perhaps 50 clicks will do it yes almost certainly 50
no no i'm still not feeling it you see now that you've gotten the bucket involved what standards
have gone up don't bring the bucket into this single door is no longer enough now i want to see
you press this bucket against multiple doors now that's the kind of thing that merits an achievement
why don't you put 20 bucket touches into door 417 oh fuck you fine 417 okay great now go touch
the bucket on door 437 a few times just to open the door please or 37 yes now we're getting
somewhere how about door 415 give it some bucket love hey there it is now back to door number 437
you know i think the copy machine needs some attention why don't you rub the bucket on it
a bit all right back to room 417 i'm really feeling it now i think we're getting somewhere
okay okay now bring the bucket on top of employee 419's desk hey what the fuck on top of the desk
how do i climb up it i can't get on i can't climb up yes this is great now the bucket knows exactly
what it's like to be employee 419 now let's introduce it to door 416 okay where's 416 415
where's 416 is this 416 417 420 416 probably right here 456 425 stanley clicked on literally
every single door in the office because he doesn't pick up well on cues from his
environment where is it 416 is it this one it's the new content door oh i can't complete it
what oh it's right here look what come on it's right here 50 times
shit it's broken god damn it oh well it has to be the true 416 oh that's all right hello
and thank you for playing the stanley parable ultra deluxe as you may know the stanley parable
was a video game released in 2013 on home computers after receiving critical and commercial success
i want my achievement 2022 with the stanley parable ultra deluxe a reimagining of the
game for consoles and home computers i'll fix it when i wake up tomorrow is it dev
the stanley parable ultra deluxe features exciting new content that broadens and expands the world of
the stanley parable delighting audiences the world over that's all good to me please step inside and
see what thrilling new adventures await in the stanley parable ultra deluxe oh do the
go to the mind control one without the bucket thrilling new ultra deluxe content
i'll do the mind control one without the bucket after this and that's probably a bucket you're
holding it's the bucket i've been working on for my sequel how did you get your hands on it isn't
this the preview to the sequel how do you have the bucket already this this makes no sense at all
hold on did i already show you my ideas for the sequel i don't remember doing that at all
you're seeing things all out of order he's gonna fix it isn't he i'm gonna get to the achievement
room and he's gonna be like no no no this is wrong you shouldn't be here yet the jump circle
yep all right let's see it's the jump circle he's not gonna let me touch the machine i'm gonna go
reach for it he's gonna reset the game i bet a dollar to myself did you see them already stanley
none of them are ready yet i'm still developing them they're not even close to finished how did
they look when you saw them were they captivating were they exciting did they fulfill on the promise
of everything that a sequel to stanley parable could possibly be yeah i figured out how the hell
to make a sequel to this game you had you had a little bit of trouble you had a little bit of
trouble wait if you're still carrying the bucket around with you if the bucket is interesting to
you that means i must have made it correctly yes you carrying the bucket with you everywhere
is exactly what i set out to accomplish the bucket is the exciting and captivating new content that
i promised i did it i win i made a sequel to the stanley parable yes the sign is correct thank you
for enjoying the new content thank you for taking the bucket everywhere with you clinging tightly
to the bucket never letting it go it means i've won it means i am victorious over the gamers it
is a sweet salve of victory on my soul thank you for enjoying the new content the bucket is the
stanley parable now they are one and the same there is no stanley parable without the bucket
i win i win take that gamers i win i win i win i win okay hey but wait i wanted to go to
i want to go to the sequel area all of his co-workers were gone what could it mean stanley
decided to go to the meeting room perhaps he had simply missed i want to oh i gotta go without the
bucket i have to go without with the bucket yeah i don't bring the bucket yeah no no no bucket
right because then we they'll yeah without the bucket all right let's go yeah bring bucket take
the bucket no no no do a bucket get the bucket take the bucket no no don't bring the bucket i
got the bucket made stanley want to be a better man and a better co-worker in time perhaps he
would become both of those things all right i'm going in with a bucket everybody's called me an
idiot and here we are we're fine we're good you see stanley i've been reflecting on the stanley
parable and about how roundly disappointing this ultra deluxe version has turned out to be
i don't think so which nor stanley parable was a landmark i think it adds a lot new content for it
should live up to that legacy so forget this ultra deluxe nonsense i say we no no no no no no no no
even further which is why i'm very proud to announce for the first time ever the stanley
parable too oh no we're good yes you see isn't this far superior to a measly re-release with
a few minor additions think of all the new territory will cover with a fully fledged sequel
an entirely new experience built from the ground up why there are so many possibilities it could
go in so many different directions this is what fans have truly been asking for now to be clear
i haven't looked at the table down what exactly too late too late is going to be but let's take a
look at some of the features i've been developing all right let's go achievement figure that if i
can loosely organize a handful of interesting concepts that surely the game will sort of
naturally spring up around them it'll all work itself out game development is much more of a
fuzzy magic than anything scientific or logical really two buckets okay let's go get two buckets
go on try out some of the new features give me a second bucket i deserve it wait there are two
buckets here how did you get a second bucket there's no two buckets and comfort of a single
button is already so great so intoxicatingly wonderful with two buckets there's no telling
stanley can you still hear me are you with me oh stanley what oh thank god i didn't lose you
stanley the no buckets was too much i had to destroy both oh get out of here i know how much
the bucket meant to you and take the risk i hope one day you can forgive me well what am i going
to do now without that i was so used to picking it up every single day oh well okay uh now the
achievement room right all right where's the free achievement this way that's sad all right here we
go free achievement now here's something special you remember that broken test achievement that
got left in the game on accident well i'm developing a technology to simply give you the
achievement yes you see you'll come to this lever and when you pull it the achievement will be
given to you it's as simple as that got it as you can see the machine is not working yet yes it is
wait what in the holy hell is going on you've got the achievement why did the machine work stanley i
didn't fix it i didn't do anything to it i swear it was broken just a second ago who fixed it is
someone here are we being watched oh god composure composure yes as you can see the machine is
working as normal as i intended it um it truly speaks to the awe-inspiring magic of the stanley
parable too breathe just breathe well all right i got it i win should i do the infinite hole what
what other exhibits haven't we seen yet up on your lip i can't help it calling it the stanley
parable too is just so much all right where's the hole ultra deluxe don't you think ultra deluxe
what does it even mean your blood is leaking out parable too now that's an artistic statement
right there all right we'll do the hole oriented it screams progress and innovation and long-term
franchising potential time is it right now it is currently just about 10 pm 9 50 stanley here's
an idea that i'm truly fond of it's never been done before in a video game this is in fact a
hole that you can fall down forever that's right infinite falling you can fall until the end of
time if you like a stunningly hard for video games as a medium you see isn't it wonderful
okay anything change here ingenious concoctions if i do say so now then since you've gotten to
see the infinite hole you can press the teleport button to pop back up to the top and it changes
here all right nothing changes all right now i'm very excited to show you even more of my ideas
for the sequel okay cool i don't have the bucket that's right okay so i think i'm gonna i want to
go do the mind control without the bucket i had the bucket the first time yeah i know i did it
already all the weird stuff all right we're gonna reset and i want to go do the mind control thing
turn the machine on without the bucket and then that'll probably wrap it up all of his co-workers
were gone what could it mean stanley decided to go to the meeting room perhaps he had simply missed
a memo do the window ending yeah i'm looking at the windows i don't see a window yeah i did i did
the infinite hole thing a long time ago yeah okay i'm not doing that we're gonna go turn on the mind
control machine which is a set of two open doors he entered the door on his left no it's the where's
it's the right jump out the window climb the deck all right we'll do that after this i want to turn
on the uh mind control thing yet there was not a single person here either feeling a wave of
disbelief stanley decided to go up to it stanley stepped into the broom closet but there was nothing
here so he turned around and got back on track coming to a staircase stanley walked upstairs
to his boss then it's down right is it down to go to the mind control room no it's up
oh up up all right it's like gotta go to the catwalk i know i'm not supposed to talk about
these things mods and mods are gonna be pissed but i just somebody you added the term
um stepping into his manager's office stanley was once again stunned to discover not an indication
of oh mods typing shocked unraveled stanley wondered in disbelief who orchestrated this
what dark secret was being held from him what he could not stanley was in such a rush to get
through the story as quickly as possible i'm not gonna enable it didn't even have a single stop
reading i'm not gonna read this stuff anymore nope i'm not doing it i'm not i'm not putting
pressure on the mods for no reason he relaxed for a few moments with some calming new age stop
reading our stuff no no wait you hold on i i hold a second apparently a term was permitted to
permissions like to add to permissions right permitted term finger butthole it was added to
the permitted terms not removed not banned that was permitted was it banned because of
the elden ring streams oh and there it's gone it's definitely because the elden ring streams
people would probably just like finger butthole my finger butthole i get it i get it but now that
it's like you know it's been a while let's add the term finger butthole and then i just ruined it
whoops let's see everybody relax with the chill music all right feeling soothed and rejuvenated
calmly walked forward into the open it's just funny like oh add it show the humor with that
this that's so that's very humorous like i look over and i see like uh permissions added for you
know finger butthole like oh okay we got permissions i just make the mods um job way way harder don't i
that gets you banned that gets you timed out and i am making it really really difficult the building
stanley realized he felt a bit but the running joke is that i would be banned from my own
channel in his chest as though he felt more free to think for himself true to question the nature
of his job why did he feel this now when for years it had never occurred to him this question
would not go unanswered for long okay here we go stanley walked straight ahead through the large
door turn it on without the bucket facility i want to see what the mind control ending without
the bucket is the lights rose on an enormous room packed with television screens what horrible
secret did this place hold stanley thought to himself did he have the strength to find out
now the monitors jumped to life their true nature revealed each bore the number of an employee in
the building okay so what happens when i turn it on the lives of so many and then i'll do that
window ending that people are saying and that's it one of them eternally monitored in this place
where freedom meant nothing oh mods going chaotic evil i'm allowing all of these oh
this mind control facility it was too horrible to believe it couldn't be true had stanley really
been under someone's control all this time was this the only reason he was happy with his boring
job that his emotions had been manipulated to accept it blindly no he refused to believe it
he couldn't accept it his own life in someone else's control never it was unthinkable wasn't
it was it even possible had he truly spent his entire life utterly blind to the world
all right now you guys now you're just reaching now you're reaching operation
controls labeled with emotions you're reaching now you're all reaching or content you're hey you
play with fire i'm just saying you're playing with fire you're gonna get timed out very place
and as the cold reality of his careful careful stanley decided you don't want to touch that
line too far be careful it's terrible power over another human life would dismantle the controls
once and for all right turn it on oh stanley you didn't just activate the controls did you
after they kept you enslaved all these years you go and you try to take control of the machine
for yourself is that what you want control stanley i applaud your effort i really do
but you need to understand there's only so much that machine can do you were supposed to let it
go turn the controls off and leave if you want to throw my story off track you're going to have to
do much better than that i'm afraid you don't have nearly the power you think you do for example
and i believe you'll find this pertinent stanley suddenly realized he had just initiated the
network's emergency detonation system in the event this machine is activated without proper
dna identification nuclear detonators are said to explode eliminating the entire complex
let's say um two minutes two minutes ah now this is making things a little more fun isn't it stanley
run it's your time to shine you are the star it's your story now shape it to your heart's desires
oh this is much better than what i had in mind what a shame we have so little time left to enjoy
it five mere moments until the bomb goes off but what precious moments each one of them is
more time to talk about you about me where we're going what all this means i barely know where to
start four you'd like to know where your co-workers are i need to press the number four
moment of solace before you're obliterated all right one two you're gonna die anyway i'll tell
you exactly what happened to them i erased them i turned off the machine i set you free
three of course of course four in this instance of the story where's four i tell it i simply let
you sit there in your office forever pushing buttons endlessly and then dying alone
other times i let the office sink into the ground swallowing everyone inside or i let it burn to a
crisp i have to say so this version of events has been rather amusing watching you try to make
sense of everything and take back the control rested away from it's quite rich i almost hate to
go but i'm sure whatever i come up with on the next go around or even better my goodness
i need 34 seconds left but i'm enjoying this so much you know what to hell with it i'm going
to put some extra time on the clock why not these are precious additional seconds stanley time
doesn't grow on trees oh dear me what's the matter stanley is it that you have no idea where you're
going or what you're supposed to be doing right now or did you just assume when you saw that timer
that something in this room was capable of turning it off i mean look at you running from button to
button screen to screen clicking on every little thing in this room these numbers buttons no these
colored ones or maybe this big red button or this door everything anything something here will save
me why would you think that stanley that this video game can be beaten
do you have any idea what your purpose in this place is
stanley is any key to send power sir quite a disappointment but here's a spoiler for you
that timer isn't a catalyst to keep the action moving along it's just seconds ticking away to
your death you're only still playing instead of watching a cut scene because i want to watch you
for every moment that you're powerless to see you made humble this is not a challenge it's a
tragedy you wanted to control this world that's fine but i'm going to destroy it first so you
can't take a look at the clock stanley that's 30 seconds you have left to struggle 30 seconds
until a big boom and then nothing no ending here just you being blown to pieces will you cling
desperately to your frail life or will you let it go peacefully another choice make it come
or don't it's all the same to me all a part of the joke and believe me i will be laughing at
every second of your inevitable life from the moment well shit all right where's the window
what could it mean stanley decided to go to the meeting room perhaps he had simply missed a memo
how do i was the window one heart stanley looked he couldn't find a trace of his co-workers
use the chair other chair like up here at first stanley assumed he'd broken the map until he
heard this narration and realized it was part of the game's design all along he then praised the
game for its insightful and witty commentary into the nature of video game structure and its
examination of structural narrative tropes do it again with the bucket now that you're here what
do you think isn't this a fun and unique place to be why don't we take a minute just to drink
it all in all right okay i'm over it now what do you think are you sick of this gag yet no ah then
in that case we'll continue but now here comes the real question what do you think would have
happened if you had told me that you wanted this to stop do you think it would have been particularly
different reset would i have taken the same idea but rephrased it superficially to fit that answer
perhaps you never would even have thought of it if i hadn't brought up the issue in the first
place you would reset the game now think about it will it be worth it for you to restart and then
come back here just to do the other option clearly this whole gag takes some time what if the other
option is even longer how long would you spend in total just to have heard all the narration oh and
one omega low in there just played the other option omega low you come to see one omega low
this one so what do you think which choice was the better one imagine if you had selected continue
on your first playthrough how tantalizing it would be not knowing what happens when you pick
the other option indeed you are one of the lucky ones though if the other option is really miserable
to listen to then perhaps you're not in fact i'm just going to say that no one who's listening to
this is lucky well now i've built up the other options so much that i'm going to stop talking
and leave you to your decision whether to come back here continue with the game or just sit in
this spot forever and ever jesus don't come back with bucket first of all okay fuck off how long
was i sitting there stanley wandered to himself minutes exactly centuries did something not
everyone is so lucky to have a bucket but stanley is a very lucky fellow very lucky indeed
what the fuck is that yes whispered the bucket into stanley's ear we've done it we've escaped
from that dull office and that pesky narrator at last out here in the white void we are alone
now and for the first time i can reveal to you my true self the bucket began to tell stanley of
its history of the countless wars it witnessed desecrating the land and lives of untold numbers
of innocent humans and the buckets own complicity therein of sadness and regret and the many years
it spent dwelling on the actions it might have taken to curb the madness and the decay if only
it had been stronger of hope and redemption and its crusade to uplift the stock of life for the
common man to manifest justice where none existed and the bittersweet reality of time to see one's
dreams and wishes met halfway meted out in parcels like charity and abandoned as soon as the warm
glow of inspiration begins to dim the opportunities to do so much more there was so much it could have
done perhaps the bucket wondered to itself perhaps if it had seen its own darkness with a clearer
perception this was way too much for stanley what are you talking about he screamed you're a
bucket to this the bucket furrowed its brow now said the bucket not since the evil wizard gamb
horata first ensnared me in his machinations as payback for the sacred amulet i stole from
his treasured vaults i was young back then and could not conceive the ramifications of
no stanley screamed even louder this time this is stupid you are a bucket this is so stupid
why are we even doing this as stanley screamed and screamed and screamed the bucket revealed its true
form transforming into a mighty beast of untold power we're gonna see things glistening like
oh god stanley you did it you saved us from the bucket thank god you already had all 12 emblems
of sages and knew the incantations to summon their true power otherwise we would have easily
been overwhelmed by the bucket's power i'm speechless you've demonstrated such bravery
here today come let's restart the game and we'll agree to never again go trifling with this bucket
nor the dark magic cast away inside of it blood all of his co-workers were gone all right what
could it mean that's it stanley decided to go to the meeting room perhaps it takes a lot of humility
to carry a bucket so magnificent all right that's it checked his ego that's it proceeded all right
that's it stanley clutched the bucket tightly to his chest and entered the door on his left
all right that's it still no one was here i'll see you tomorrow that's it stanley needed the
bucket's warmth and comfort now more than ever perhaps his stanley we must move on from this
broom closet simply because i have no remaining stickers if i did you coming to a staircase
stanley on the bucket walked upstairs to the boss's office no don't go down here i want to go up
so tomorrow we are going to do infomercials stunned to discover not an indication of any
probably that's it but stanley gets the correct code by sheer luck
was it that the bucket knew all along always streams where i want won't be that long
it'll be like four showers this is certainly the logical explanation watch infomercials okay
now i go back up all right but not yet do you like this game wait down then up okay
yeah i do i think it's fun the elevator race downward plummeting towards an unknown fate
it would be all stanley could do to keep himself together if not for the bucket soothing him
comforting him reassuring that in this darkest moment of uncertainty are you gonna finish this
game right um it is here for you stanley everything will be fine i i didn't i i think i did didn't i
get to the few endings like the true ending i think i saw the true ending stanley said to the
bucket can we go back i think i've seen it when i was pressing those keypad buttons there was
something very intriguing about the number three i want to go back so i can try pressing the number
three again the bucket said nothing okay press the number three here we are said stanley now i'm going
to try out that number three button he took the bucket over to the keypad and began absolutely
slamming on the number three over and over and over well he said the number three is such a
special button i'm having the time of my life stanley looked expectantly at the bucket but the
bucket remained silent this was a shock to stanley who had always felt such a connection with the
bucket how was this not as exciting to the bucket as it was to him once stanley had had enough of
the number three he got back in the elevator do it eight times eight that was weird perhaps the
bucket had missed perhaps it had not seen how much joy stanley got from slamming the number three
repeatedly go back up a hint of regret nagged in the back of stanley's mind should he demonstrate
the number three for the bucket again sure no no no no no said stanley you can't go on yet
not did you understand how much the number three means to me you and i have been through so much
together and i just want you to see what i see feel the happiness i feel he smiled at the bucket
and the bucket said nothing yeah the voice actor for the narrator is amazing very funny perfect
perfect role okay three here we go said stanley this time i'll really show you
he ran to the number three and began to wail on it like a musician on a beloved instrument
waving a concerto of truth and passion he wielded the number three like a fine artist would wield a
paintbrush he taught stories through the number three stories of his dreams and hopes and fears
the whole time he looked to his bucket for a reaction of some kind anything to let him know
that the bucket appreciated what he was doing the bucket conveyed absolutely nothing at all
only silence crushed by a wave of dejection stanley returned to the elevator the bucket hates me now
why stanley and the bucket were so close it always been there for one another why suddenly
could the bucket not connect with this passion of stanley's the question caused stanley to
kill the bucket i did not kill the elevator he knew that there must be a way to get through to
the bucket to communicate fully with his dear friend surely there was a solution mustn't there
be that wasn't another life do it again again again again said stanley i know what to do
i know how to fully express this feeling in my heart he decided right then and there that he
would hold a press conference where he would speak to the public on all matters relating to pressing
the number three over and over he would elaborate fully on what the number three meant to him and
why he felt so alive when pressing it then the bucket would be able to see his joy through the
eyes of others it would get to see the world react to this discovery of stanley's and it would be
through the public eye that the bucket would finally understand stanley's work press conference
for months he advertised and marketed his press conference building excitement around it developing
and rehearsing it until it couldn't be refined a single measure further when the big day arrived
stanley was as prepared as he'd ever been for anything in his life stage door okay this was it
one last chance to win the bucket over one opportunity to share a true connection with
a loved one okay the dude who came up with pizza there was no one here nobody had come to the press
conference to hear stanley speak to listen to him talk about what it really means to press the
number three on a keypad over and over he was nobody literally no one interesting he was a
failure no one in that moment stanley knew that the bucket would never again take him seriously
there would be no connection no deeper understanding the bucket merely sat there in
his arms indifferent and so it began that slowly over many years the two of them grew more and more
this is germacon attendance
i'm not my mother would go there would be no more games sorry no more long conversations about
passion and pursuit only a silence that consumed the space between friends and stanley
having for once in his life discovered the warmth and comfort of true companionship
was cast back into the unremarkable normalcy of loneliness i thought you said nobody was here
just heard somebody cough a lie wait rare phone spawn rare phone spawn this where's it message
scheduled either by you or person in your place of work the purpose of this message is to warn
you about the dangers of recorded messages if at any time you believe you are listening
to a recorded message please terminate it immediately and cease all flow of information
from the recorded message into your perceptual sphere hello hello hello hello no it's your first
day be careful for be careful foxy watch out the thing that i do i want to tell you about
foxy is foxy yeah foxy stanley cradled the bucket in a gentle embrace protective
yet delicate assertive yet compassionate stanley clutched the bucket tightly to his
this was not the correct way to the meeting room but stanley had felt the bucket calling to him
telling him that the employee lounge was simply the place to be and here it was had the bucket
turned out to be correct was no never mind the bucket was wrong stanley took the door on his left
to go back to the meeting room no said the bucket don't go to the meeting room go somewhere else
the cargo lift yeah good said the bucket whatever um all right i'll see you guys tomorrow
wait i want to try this i want to restart the game
will it be stanley power before when i open it again and that's the last thing i want to see
uh i'll give you my review for the stanley parable 2 the stanley parable ultra deluxe edition i
think it's a really good uh i think it's a good edition i think it's like the definitive version
of the game i think it's very good there's definitely enough content there and plus it's
just a fun experience it was very nice it was a very nice time all right that's it see you later
see you tomorrow around four o'clock we'll watch some infomercials for a few hours have a great
night thanks for joining me as always fun to play games with you you know there's a ton of
infomercials and i the reason why i only want to do like three or four hours is i don't i don't
want to overdo it because they're so stimulating and there's so much that you can kind of get like
infomercial overload so i think like a solid three or four hours is good that's the plan for
tomorrow infomercial scientist you promised to eat a glove and i am got to get one it'd take me
a little while to find the right one you promised to eat a glove i'm gonna eat a glove i just got
to find the right glove make sure it fits well make sure it's there make sure it's right spices
on it and everything all right good night i'll see you guys tomorrow take care of yourselves call
your mother see you later