Be very careful here. Be very, very careful here. Be very careful here.
There he is. Okay, if I don't get this guy right now, then I don't know. Zoom in. Dude,
the other team's over there. Scope in. Scope in, dude. Scope in. What are you, what are you doing?
What are you checking for? Landmines? Let's go. Does nobody know I'm standing right here?
Hi. Oh, this is so much fun, dude. This item is so much fun. Forget about the mini crits,
man. This thing is just a blast. Just jumping around is like the funnest damn thing ever.
This is so much fun. Watch this, this sniper right here. I think this is my, yeah, there's a sniper
right here. Wow, here comes a pyro. Where'd he go? What? Oh, he's got this too. We, this
two bird scouts. All right, I'm feeling it. I'm feeling the double bird scout. Um, Sir, I just
shot you like three times. Sir, I'm standing in front of you. Sir. Sir. Excuse me, sir.
See that roost up there? You see this roost? I'm going to roast their turkeys in a second.
You're going to get your fucking turkeys roasted, snipers. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Thought I had more ammo. I thought I had more ammo. You want to get your turkey roasted? Open
the door. You want to get your turkey roasted? Go ahead and open the door.
Roasted turkey, oven roasted with some ham and some onion. What about this guy? You want to get
your fucking turkey roasted. Are they still up there? Oh yeah, they are. Oh, you better believe
it. Please don't shoot me in the face already. Make sure I equip the nice bird jump. Is anybody
up there? Whoa. See you. See you later. No, come on. Get up there. That's so dumb.
I'm out of here. See, I left. I'm not here. You don't have to worry about a thing. I'm not here.
All right. I'm not here. See, I'm gone. See, I'm gone. I'm gone. Don't even worry about it.
It's, there's no reason to be that concerned about this. Just walk into just my God. Can I
please get this? Is it not going to even happen? I'm swear to God, dude, please just walk in.
Don't, please. Earthquake. Don't mind me. I'm just going to chill out right here.
I'm going to get seen. There's no way no one's going to see me do this. Some soldier is going
to turn the corner. Wait, I spy in the window. I think he's AFK. Oh my fucking God. Oh my God.
Oh, that only, only two. I don't have any words for that. I don't have words for that. I just
got so destroyed right there. That was horrible. I'm on his head. He didn't even know. He doesn't
know. He didn't even know. He didn't even know. Give me that health pack. Can I have that health
pack please? You want to jump scare me medic? Is that what you want to do? You want to jump
scare me? Huh? I ain't going to get jump scared twice. That's a spy. You want to go? You want to
activate the bird scout? Come on. Bird scout. Ooh, see you later. You think you're going to get away.
You can never defeat the bird scout. Come on dudes. Where's the? Oh, hello. Oh, hello.
The confusion. Confusion sets in. I actually get a kill, but that's not what I wanted.
God, that's going to be such a pain in the ass to deal with. A scout jumping around all of you
is annoying. A scout jumping around all around you 20, 30 feet in the air has got to be even
more annoying. There's a lot of people stuffed in that room. Here we go. This is what I want to do.
I can't. Hi everybody. How are you? What? You. How did he hit me with a melee?
That didn't make any sense. I was like 40 feet above everybody. Holy hell. What the hell was that?
Oh, watch this. This heavy, this heavy, this heavy. Here we go. What? What's going on?
What happened? What just happened?