Welcome to the stream. Hi everybody, welcome. It's me. I'm almost not late. I mean I'm not late.
How can you be almost not late? You are either late or you're not. So we're gonna finish
Katamari Beautiful after we finish the DLC. I think there's another one or two levels in the
base game and then there's I think six or seven DLC levels. We're gonna smoke them all.
I'm anticipating that will take somewhere between two and four hours. No, maybe it'll take a little
shorter. I don't know. Maybe it'll take longer. I don't know. Regardless how long this takes,
if there's still some time, which there probably will be. I don't- Bumbo came out. I didn't even
know that. The Legend of Bumbo released last week. I kind of been waiting for it. It's the
binding of Isaac prequel. It's a weird match three kind of card game. I don't know. Edmund
McMillan just makes crazy shit. So I want to try it. It's addictive as fuck. Well, that's good to
hear. So we started Katamari last night. I'm gonna finish it. We're doing this thing where I start
game, finish game, but there's still it's been like two and a half hours. So start new game.
The train just keeps moving, apparently. I also, I kind of, I don't know, I kind of like want to
play the Star Wars game. I just keep seeing people talk about it. I seen the lightsabers
and the dodge rolling and just like, I think I want to play that. He's a fake Star Wars fan.
I own more Star Wars clothes than anybody. I mean, does that mean I'm a big Star Wars fan?
Does it mean that I shop exclusively at Walmart? You're wearing an Aquaman shirt right now. I am
not. It's a decent game from what I hear. Yeah, and we never play brand new releases. Sometimes
we do. When a triple A game releases, you 99% of the time don't see it on this channel. So
yeah, the ape game. Yeah. But that was, is that a triple A game? I don't think so. That's like
a double A game. You literally only play monkey related games when they release.
That's true. That is a true statement. But still, I'm talking non-ape related video games.
We'll see how it goes today into the next week here. But I don't know, I might play
Bumbo and get addicted and I never play anything else. But let's finish Katamari.
Beautiful Katamari. Already got it open and I'm already at the next level.
I have no plan. We're kind of in a mystery world here. Well, not right now. I'd love to say I'm
playing Katamari. This isn't Dead Rising. I beat Dead Rising. Yeah, Dead Rising 2.
One go. One save file. Well, I mean, I mean, no restarts is what I meant to say.
Yeah, I did that. Somebody's gonna pogchamp and go, are you fucking serious? Yeah, add it to the
fucking badge. All right, this is called Schloss Cosmos. Roll up a powerful things
to make a supergiant. This might be the last base game level to find out. Welcome to the icon of
the princedom Schloss Cosmos. A grand space for an epic race to roll a supergiant.
We want you to collect lots of powerful things. Sumo, Rikishi, wrestlers, elephants and bulldozers.
The supergiant needs to have some stopping power. Anywho, let's go. I wonder what song we're gonna
get this time. I missed big bits. Big bits. Did they? Yeah, they did. File actor at Lichon
of the 5,000 bits. That's so much money over the last few months, man. Thanks for the 5,000 bits.
Just saying, Jeremy, the new Star Wars game is kind of like Star Wars Dark Souls. Best Star Wars
game in a long time. I know, I know, but I've heard, I've heard very mixed things about it.
I've heard it's a great game. I've heard it's too safe. I've heard it's too hard. I've, I,
it's, I kind of just want to see for myself. You ready? I'm gonna die to lightsaber wheel.
I gotta form my own opinion, asshole. Why'd you call me an asshole? Hold on, this thing has to
be 10,000. That's a huge, this is absolutely the last base game level. I have 20 minutes to roll
10,000. Holy shit. Yeah, that's what I'm saying. I want to make my, I just said that I want to make
my own opinion on it. What is a review? What is like somebody telling you, you know what I mean?
Like, I'm gonna make my own opinion. That's what I just told you. We gotta plug the black hole.
We need this to be an unimaginable size and all cosmos is home free. Otherwise,
squishville. Wow, it's not easy being you, is it? All right, let's go. This thing has to be
10,000 kilometers. Off to a terrible start. It's a pretty good song.
Uh, little cars. I'm already one beater, so. How the hell am I gonna do this? It seems too big.
Get all the chicken. Can I pick up people? You have 20 minutes. Yeah, that goes fast though.
I mean, anybody that's been on this stream, in Time Plaza and you're having fun, 20 minutes is
like fucking two on this stream. We have just so much fun. See, it's already been, it's already
been three minutes and it's felt like 30. See? We have so much fun here. Let's get big enough
to get on the buildings. That's all I care about. I gotta get out of this, but three meters I can
go up. Bikes will do it. Yep. All right, let's go. I'm gonna go up this way. Wait, where was it?
This is the best game? I agree. This is a great game. All the Katamari games are awesome.
What was the last? Is this the last Katamari game? Besides the reboot? No, what was the last one?
There's another one on the PS3. So did they just kind of, I mean, I guess once you do this enough
times, there's only so many times you can make this game where you're just like, yeah, we kind
of did it all, huh? I would love to see, I know it's, what else would they do? I would love to see
another Katamari, like a current gen Katamari. I feel like you can make it bigger. The scope could
be larger because that's what happens in a game like this. It's like, well, what do we do? Do we
just keep the same game but just make it even bigger?
Pick them up? Yep. Let's go down the road. Katamari with guns and crafting. All right,
he's talking. Katamari with guns and crafting. What is it? It's 15 to get over the next hill,
right? I might just go up there now. He'll just do it now.
Oh, that looks like a lot of time, but there's a prince right there. Who's this? Is it a horse?
It's Kenta. Why aren't you eating your mash? What? All right, let's get the centipede. All right,
turn it around. This is it. All right. 10,000. I'm only 15 meters. How is this going to work?
We need bigger stuff. Run over the trees. Run over the tank. There we go. Tons of people.
Go. Get over to that car park. All right, and this whole city here. We've got everywhere.
That's what I'm trying to get around. Everyone always says, dude, what if the earth and where
to end? We're going to get hit by an asteroid or something. That's boring. I wouldn't be much
prefer this. No. Why? Wait, you just want to get hit by an asteroid? What about don't get hit by
one? What about nothing? Yeah, I'm saying in the event that there's like a catastrophic space,
like big bang type shit again. Yeah, if it had music, that's what I'm saying. If this music
just blasted. I got 12 minutes almost. Music would have to be fine. All right, back to the other.
I get the big ones. I can't. Can I get the big building?
Thanks. Nope. Head back over here. Got to get to a hundred. Once you get to a hundred,
that's when you can just start steamrolling every single thing across.
Two, three, four. There it is. All right, scoop them up. 60. You got to be 60 feet.
Get it all. Take up the whole earth. What? I still can't get it. This is the last level. This is the
last base game level. There are seven DLC levels. I'm going to try this. We're going to play.
I think it's island time. No, I need one more. Get the stadium.
Oh, another prince. Macho. I got him. Oh, it's right there. All right, go for the dinosaurs instead.
Present. Oh, what's the present? Yep, island time. Let's go. I got a lot of time.
Let's go get all the monsters. One more growth increase and I should be able to pick up the
actual island. Funny time. That's right. You get it. Bastard. Stadium. 300 to get the next increase.
Oh, shit. All right, back to the turn around. This way. Jumped everything I wanted. Just pick up.
Damn it. Give me the bird. Oh, too small. All right, 300. Time to start moving. I can actually
pick up the ground now. Momentum. Too much momentum. Too much momentum. This way. I don't even
know what I just picked up. There's a whole other island over there I haven't even been to. This is
going to get you a lot. Please don't tell me to pick it all up. Some of it. 500. I need to get to
10,000. Not 10. I need to get to 10,000 kilometers. I'm not sure I'm saying that right.
Pick up all the pink. I'm stuck. Holy shit. Look at that giant octopus. All right, this way.
Look at all these mushrooms. Forward. Pick it up. Look at these penguins. Pick it up. A whole fat
penguin. What am I picking up? I think I got a present. All right, yeah, I got a present.
All right, I can't. I don't want to lose this, please. Okay. This is going to get insane. This
is so satisfying. What I just did right there was the equivalent of watching like 10 self-cutting
videos in a row. I feel great. Fuck. All right, forget it. Just go. I have to move. Turn. Turn.
It won't turn. I'm trying. It's too big. I don't even know what to say. There's too many islands.
Is this what it looks like from space? Imagine this is what it actually looked like out of
the window from the space station. Would you guys, like, if you were an astronaut,
would you talk about this? Would you want to take a picture of this? I feel like the worlds
is better off not known. I don't even know if I'm picking anything up. Get the whole city.
Yeah. 10,000. Where the fuck am I going to do that? Can't get the volcano. I don't think I can get
the octopus either. Nope. Not yet. What is even left to pick up? Did I get him? I got him.
Only two. Get the dragon. Got you. Holy shit. Uh, this is earth. Oh, 400.
Well, this started to really, really pick up. I need to get to 10,000. Hurry. Cousin. Got him.
It's Mag. Uh, I don't know if I'm going to do it. It's going to be close. Really close.
I can't pick up the land. I'm trying to get it. Let's get all of Antarctica.
Come on. I can't get. What is that? USA? I need more land mass. There we go. Right here.
Get it all. Quick. 5,000. One minute. Come on. I'm not even close. No. 6,000. Get it all. No.
It's going to be so close. Australia. I got it. What's left? This way. What's left? 9,000. I did
it. We're finally in space. Somewhere out here is the yucky black hole. I have to plug the black
hole. I don't think I won. How about a two minute bonus to level the field? I got nice. I got this
perfect. Okay. Don't go near. Don't go near the black hole. It'll suck you in. Wait until the
Katamari is big enough to plug it. Where's the black hole? Oh my god. I'm getting all the planet.
Pisces. Orion. There's the sun. I can't get the sun yet. What? What? What? What? Danger. Danger.
Danger. Get away from there. I can't see it. You're near the black hole. Run or it'll squish you.
Where is it? Shoo from the black hole. I can't see it. Wait, is that? That's him. Oh, there it is.
I see it. Okay. Turn around. Give me that planet. Approaching black hole. Approaching black hole.
I'm not big enough. What do I have to be? 500,000? Something hyper. It's ace. Oh shit.
I only got 30 seconds. Am I big enough? How big do I have to be? 10 seconds. I gotta be a million.
Oh fuck. I'm not gonna do it. I didn't do it. I didn't do it. All right. Very nice. This Katamari
looks kind of big. But why is it here? We did say it's to plug up the black hole. Then why is it
still here? You want to take it home? Oh, go on then. But wait. What about the black hole? It needs
to be plugged up. Why don't you listen to us? You don't want to help? We have nothing to say.
Too bad, bad. Sorry. Shame. Resignation. Wrath. Con. Put that silly ball down and come over here.
God damn it. Shit. That's a lot. That's sad. I need to get to a million. Okay. I'm gonna go quick now.
It's all right. It's all right. We can still do it. Omega lull. 20 plus minutes. It was fun though.
I'm just gonna be faster. Okay. I get two extra minutes. Here we go. That was a warm-up run. Bad
RNG. Bad spot. Bad spot. This is bad RNG. Sorry. I'll make it work. Can't get people yet.
Bad RNG. Bad RNG. It's okay. I gotta get to three. Better not. Why is this whole town on fire?
Second I get to three, we're turning that corner. This might be salvageable if I get over there
quick. Damn it. Come on. I'm almost there. That's a shit start. That's kind of a shit start for me.
I gotta make this up very quick. I have to make this up now.
Still possible. Oh, it's a shit start. Should I restart? Hmm. Oh. If I can get to the next
phase really quickly, then I don't have to restart it. Add elephant fucking RNG to me.
That's a lot of time that I just made up. Down here? Decent. Okay. Decent. All right. Come back.
Don't, don't lollygag. I'm not, although I, I do, I will admit I did look over at the copypasta
and I read it. That was my mistake. House is looking good. It's key forward momentum.
This is the one I want to be in. Right here. Don't hit the plane. Don't hit the plane.
All right. Next town. Next town. Next town. Next town. Back up here. Stop the pasta. There's no way.
I can't. Why do you expect me to do that? Everyone says don't put it on slow mode.
But why is R9K on? You got your answer. It's in front of you. 12 minutes. Is this enough time?
Blow it. I blow it. That's a reset right there. I blow it. Do a jump. How's my pace from last time?
Worse? Is it worse? I can't tell.
Chat is worse than ever. Fuck. All right. Just wait a minute. Give me a minute. I'll figure it out.
Just hold on. I need to get those clouds. Stop interrupting me. Ping. Let's get out into the
ocean now. Get the whole Antarctic. I can get most of this shit right now. Go. Go, go, go, go, go.
This way. This way. This way. Fast. That was a good line. This is fucking Tony Hawk level.
That's like a million points. Spin. Good. That was pretty damn good. Oh no. I didn't want to
go over that. Wasting time. I mean it was really cool, but what a waste of time that was.
Go forward. Forward. Forward. Hold it. You have to relax. No, there's no relaxing. All right.
I'm going for the rainy city over there. All right. Almost at the point where I'm going to
get like five times my size. Let's get this entire island. Don't leave it. Get it all.
Got some present. The line going. I'm going to go forward. Right to the volcano.
Can I get the volcano? Remember, I get two. Flip around. I get two extra minutes.
No. Can't get the volcano. Still can't get the. No, I got. Go faster. I'm trying. I need to get
up like four. It's gonna happen. Three. All right. This is where it starts. Hurry up. It's all about
the clouds here and the right here. Pick up all the sand. Because it said it couldn't be done.
It might not be done. I still have to do it. Trying to pick up as big the island as I can.
All right. I know. I know. I got somebody. Good. Good to know. Bigger. Bigger. Bigger. Bigger.
Bigger. All right. Can I pick up all the sand? I think so. I'm gonna get this and I'm gonna spin
around. Come on. I don't want to do it again. It's 20 plus minutes. All right, I got. That
that was Europe right good I think I can pick this up nope go fast
oh it's so hard the tournament is this big not big enough for that I think I have an
extra two or three minutes than I did last time that was so much faster I got
six minutes instead of two do not go into the black hole two minute bonus
don't go to the black hole don't get sucked in I got about six minutes let's
go come on shit start and I got plenty of time with black hole make sure don't
hit it get the stars first the colored stars oh fuck where is it where is it
danger danger danger I know where is it oh that's a black hole right there okay
don't freak out I'm good I'm sorry to scream so loud I got time actually oh my
god where is it oh my god I know where this spinner non no no please no I'm
trying to turn this no I'm trying to turn it oh god damn it if that's is a
full 60 minutes on this level it's just I trying to get away from it you can't
even see the damn thing big I saw it first and I turn around all right if I
don't I'm doing it this time god damn it another 20 fucking minutes I'm so
fucking mad right now you've no idea I'm probably purple right now
red I probably am I'm gonna go so slow when I get to the space part I don't
care I'm gonna get there with ten minutes remaining check it show purple
well not purple anymore
of course you can get sucked into the fucking black hole and end the 20 minute
level come on next area let's go pretty clean actually just watch the engine on
YouTube no cuz that means I didn't do it that's that's the total just give up
strategy at that point why don't I just watch the whole world is watch a
playthrough of the game where the person doesn't talk I'm gonna go so slow it's
gonna be painful when I get to the space part
here shit I can't get it actually hitting that trees enough in the trees
oh I'm just unlocked I'm about to smash the controller into the ground like it's
gonna explode into a million pieces it's gonna be dust by the time I'm done with
it you know sometimes people just like oh fuck they break their kitchen no no
this thing is turning into dust you're gonna have you know I'm gonna break this
control so bad you're gonna have to sweep it up he's mad
pretend I'm not I've walked through the black hole so I had instant lose
mechanics in video games am I right almost 20 houses cars trees here come
on quite 30 40 there's a really good start and then I started to process in
my mind over and over again losing to the black hole and I basically you
basically just fucking shattered my glass screen all right this is where
this is where I actually can do it I need to go back to the original town
you know this will do come on big do it so I can pick the rest of this up
please he's going across the way all these trees back to the city yes I know
we're gonna get to the ocean now 200 hurry already behind okay I just got to
get there with like three or four minutes because I get five the ice turn
the lyrics what are the lyrics
I really don't want to do this again get the big guy oh it's so hard to turn it
when it's this huge I'm holding forward right now you understand I think I might
save some time there don't go into the black hole if I go to the glass the black
hole one more time I'm good I'll eat a ghost pepper on screen you know what I
mean like that's the kind of shit I need to make sure I don't do switch you hear
how many times I clicked both buttons at the same time wouldn't that destroy my
stomach yeah so I better not go in the black hole he's gonna go in that hole
I'm not gonna go in that hole I can assure you I'm gonna do everything
possible to not go in that black hole I'm gonna be using the prince look
camera give me your energy guys I need it yes somebody just said dog give it to
me put your hands in front of the screen and power up to me I don't think enough
people are doing it I feel like shit you're doing it for somebody else it's
just like toes like Christian infomercials put your hand on the
screen after drinking your miracle spring water
we go get all the little dollops we go mountains good
this way
just let me get there for five minutes and don't go into the black hole can I
get this stuff I think so no no I can get all the sand
so it's land sir why are you not picking that up I'm starting to freak
out a little just calm down I have time all right I have almost got every land
mass there's one more over here all right I have four and a half minutes
where's the black hole where is it okay where is it where's the black what I'm
wasting time trying to see where it is I'm so paranoid I don't want to do the
dash but I feel like I need to where is it I don't know where it is you're near
the black hole shoe from the black hole what the fuck you're getting close to
the ghost pepper I have done I'm not turning around I'm okay
wait wait a minute so where is it okay I'm huge now just I can probably see it
really clearly if you would get the fuck off my screen get off of my screen why
do you have to fill up the whole HUD when you have a question I'm not gonna
make it no no sick where I need a million get off the screen there ain't
nothing left to grab wait go in go in go in go in where is it where's the black
hole you told me one million you told me one million
million somebody you guys made me think it was one fucking million yes they did
why would I say 500 million no it was one super million okay I was like 400
wasn't I already 500 fucking million what was I what was I two times ago what
was I two times ago you were 300 last time who I want to go I want to go into
the logs and see how many people said a million a super million oh my god I
can't believe it wasn't it no I was like 600 I was like over five or six
hundred oh fuck no because I didn't plug I didn't go into the hole the first time
I was like 600 million the first time but I got I've ran out of time because I
didn't know how long I was 700 million oh my fucking god and then some some
this one person I look over it it's dude you got to be one million like that
omega lol scream it sucks he's got to be a million and then I just turned back
over here it was like focusing so I was trying to a one like Terra million oh
man I can't believe it I can't believe it I didn't know I didn't know can I
change the music is there like a music change 500 fucking million on god damn
believable I can't believe it if only I had looked over at chat after getting to
500 million I wasn't looking I was just trying to focus and not going to the
black hole you guys are probably spamming go in and shit I look over at
like 780 million I didn't look at chat one fucking time I trusted that one guy
that said a million because that seems so such a perfect number to do if you're
enjoying this I am except for when I don't do the fucking this is actually
gonna be the last time now watch me get sucked up by the black hole do not think
negative thoughts like that that's negativity I'm not having that no I'm
not gonna get sucked up by the black hole and I'm not gonna like press press
when he comes on this I am waste our energy you gave me lots of the tune I
got on 780 million why would you tell me how much it was to plug it he just says
here's extra time one that hole but don't go near it stay away from it but
plug it but don't go near it tell me what you want I'm good at delivering if
you tell me what you need I'm happy with this so far except for that big gaffe
return our energy no it's mine there's no energy refund plus you've already
expelled the energy you want your energy back sure don't eat a banana go eat a
salad go eat go have a hamburger waste some time one guy always prevail power
the power in the one guy is so wrong the next time you don't think you have like
any power in the world just come to German 985 you will change the course of
whatever I'm doing as long as you're the only one I can't get over that I've
beat it that was gone now I have to do it again this will be the last time
room island grapefruit bang around turn around after this speed back to the other
island here other island soon they can run what did the pyramids run how long
it's only 500 I don't have to have I don't spend much time the pyramids
I know what I saw you can't tell me that I didn't see it it goes pepper waiting
room well that was if I got sucked into the black hole prematurely not if I lost
around he's that big
it's such a sloppy pace but I don't even care I just need to beat it why would I
it's a roll that goes straight and I just shot to the left
it's never relaxing though is it going home now I would love to move great to
actually move the character 300 to plug the hole it is not three hours I know
it's like funny and intentional that he takes up the whole fucking screen but
like is it funny funny is it that funny anymore no it's not funny anymore
disabled hug there is no disabled from like 2005 not bolting yet my dead skin
is not dropping off at the moment I'm gonna buy like a skin suit
it's gonna take like six to seven weeks
more suit yeah that's I'm talking about like a spandex like one of those spandex
super fan suits don't you think I'm talking about no not a suit made out of
skin more suit I get it I got a look at that means it's time okay five minutes
and of the screen voice huh we just started like it oh my god it's never
mind it's been how long has it been it's been an hour and a half holy shit I
can't believe it's been that long are you sure it hasn't been eight and a half
this is my fourth time this is my third how many times is this right this is not
the fourth time this is the third time oh no that makes total sense it's an
hour an hour and 20 minutes of the screen the hell
okay I just need 500,000 forward forward forward forward forward get something
anything
two minutes
500,000 don't fly in 500,000 let's go wait where is it
nobody know where it is where is it all right slow down I got plenty of time
slow down
am I getting close where is it where is it that's you can't go away what do you
want to do like what the hell what do you want me to do oh it's just like a
stupid you got to be kidding me now the go my god I can't fucking believe we're
doing this again because of the last 30 seconds of this 20 minute level why why
why why why I tried I didn't know where it was when I found that I switched spin
get away nope I tried I really did welcome to hell I'm not watching a
video oh my god I can't believe it no the ghost pepper was if I got sucked in
that last round I didn't I'd run out of time all right let's be real fuck that
you know I mean like that's all I gotta say let's be real fuck out of here with
that you know I'm saying like that last tens you know you know I'm saying like
fuck that that's what I have to say I have to say not the ghost pepper I'm
talking about like the little that this ending to this level fuck that like get
back come on that's all I gotta say I'm gonna not say nothing else to say about
that one I can't it guys if I eat a ghost pepper I will die I can't eat one
fucking black hole danger black hole pop-up windows 1998 internet pop-up
window why'd you go over there why'd you do that why'd you do that why'd you go
over there little did I think I had no idea that beautiful Katamari's final
level was gonna be harder for me than all of dead rising to this can't be it
can't be I can't this can't be I can't be I'm doing this again I can't stop
it's only been like an hour and a half we're just starting we're just hanging
out here but you know what I mean like fuck that so they're gonna stand still
I can't stand still eat the pepper I've not eaten a ghost pepper on stream I
lied all right make a new username in fact make 20 of them for all I care I'm
a selective truth-teller sometimes I say things and they're real sometimes I say
because I'm a selective truth-teller oh so a liar not liar I just selectively
tell the truth sometimes on give me a break give me a break I can't eat a ghost
pepper I already told you I said wouldn't it be you know what I I'm
protected is be clipped but I say specifically wouldn't it be funny if
imagine if imagine now if yeah these are hypotheticals they're not real I
specifically said wouldn't it be funny if imagine if he's now he's lying about
the lie I'll die I'll go to the doctor after eating it and my GI doctor will
say specifically why did you eat something that can potentially kill you
like you see doctor I I lied to my live stream about eating ghost pepper and then
I got I was brushing in the evening because I told everybody I was gonna eat
it because I was malting during catamari the final level I got sucked into the
black hole and then he's gonna drop his fucking data sheet right he's gonna be
like fuck that level I'm gonna be like we talking about fuck that level he's
gonna be like yeah I remember that level I mean what is with the developers
putting an instant lose scenarios in 20 30 plus levels 30 plus minute levels
I'm gonna be like what I thought what is that I remember that level and it took
me like 10 tries oh by the way because you ate the ghost pepper you're dead in
three days oh and then he's gonna walk out of the room and under his lab coat
I'm gonna see he's gonna have molting skin like this gonna be like a big cape
of vaulted skin like he's already done this shit he did it like two weeks ago
this might be the best run yet and I get up and shake his hand I'm like he takes
a step out I take a step out and I step on his like wedding gown skin and he
flies forward and I fly forward it's wicked embarrassing what event I'm just
I'm just trying I'm venting this is the best run I've had since starting my
career on Katamari he's distracting us from the ghost pepper all right car can
I can I eat a can I eat a tomato that a ghost prepares for me okay like can I
have a bell pepper that I get somebody's like a ghost makes I mean that's
technically would be a ghost pepper right no what who cares about eating
anything on screen I hate eating on screen I'm stuck show feet ban that
person for the McChicken review yeah I like turn the camera off ten times eight
show your molten skin no I'm not know what
stop being so weird I'll make sure to monologue that into the bathroom nervous
like wait do we why we evil only what happened I'm the fucked up one why did
we go I'm the problem here it's me I'm the problem
it's my I'm the problem oh it's because people can't I I see I get I know I know
why I get it but I'll be fair to chat though I you can't I can't just like
drop a new and then just run into a bunker and be like people are gonna
react to that but I essentially was like oh hey guys uh good luck and I press the
button and then I just jump into a bunker what about the time fuck right
welcome to the one level in Katamari screen how long does the Simpsons hit
and run final level take me two hours I can't pass that record that final level
it would get close I don't want to break that record
be bad god damn it what I can't click that right now in the middle of a game
okay I can pause okay I saw clip at this clips link I thought said sweatiest
ugliest Boston no it's that's not what that is sweatiest ugliest ugliest Boston
streamer I was like what the fuck is this title yeah okay I know it's the
McChicken video what is the actual title sweatiest ugliest what that's a weird
title that's not the one for me it's the McChicken it's the best same I I agree
me too no the person that had the sweatiest
ugliest one you know who you are I'm gonna see it sweatiest ugliest Boston
streamer it's that's real what did you get this no that's a fake don't click
that that's fake that's fake where's the action okay I'm done
I was like you can do custom links that you can't somebody actually has it it's like
something ugly bison most of the time sleepy ugliest bison ginger power what
that's the link that's the one fucking me up so bad I can't no more chat I'm
just gonna look straight ahead it's gonna be hard for me I'm gonna look
straight ahead I only have four minutes sweatiest ugliest Boston you got this
okay I need to pay attention I'm gone I'm actually gone right now I thought
it's been ten minutes it's been two hours relax I got it 500 meters 500
million whatever the hell it is I'm gonna have time I just have to get five
hundred I'm gonna go very very slow but you can't go slow but you're not you
can't go fast enough away from the black hole I'm gonna get two more minutes
that's enough to get five hundred why are you not more? pick up something 60 so I'm gonna grow again
no over here come on just pick up something please
yikes get it all right all right all right all right no black hole 500
million no black hole just follow the stars I'm
sticking around earth out of my way stay near earth it's gonna take the whole
three minutes but I'm gonna do it great way to lose a lot of shit over here
where's earth?
two sixty three hundred okay okay okay okay okay where is it where's earth where
it is hey stay over here walk alone I did it with black hole where is it I have a
minute to find it don't need to do it yet okay go all right hey I just beat the game
on to the DLC cool that was cool the super giant made its way slowly towards
the black hole and what the hell just happened I just got 50 community subs
that's from about 32 Nixon's like Richard Nixon's that thank you for the
50 community subs holy shit oh no no what's happening
Dino Pulse just gave 10 but that's a huge amount of money Nixon's thank you
and Dino Pulse oh my god ie Elliot thanks for the 10 community subs
appreciate it thank you guys enough to buy a ghost pepper oh no that's enough
to hire an actor to put on a ghost costume and then hand me a pepper holy
okay all right we got a lot more just came in non-descript civilian thanks for
the 10 subs Vilemi thanks for the 10 subs evil program five subs it's the
thing all over again oh my god more dodges adventure MFD and five subs thank
you evil program I got you but five I got two thousand four hundred and eight
objects landscape goat five big boy Ego thanks for the ten community subs new
heights we're going to new heights here pixel mic five subs ban ban that took
forever in a nice way yes it did wild marrow thanks to 10 subs landscape goat
five any who aren't we like done what's the hold-up hits on fire two thanks for
the five subs surprising that tits on fire one was already taken thank you for
the subs thank you dr. shrug for the five subs thank you Jerma sucks for the
subs what is this is like a Mario level pixel mic another five tits on fire to
another five is there a stick around so we can poke it wait it's minigames it
is viva minigames appreciate it guys seriously thank you Dom Cheetal for the
five subs you guys fucking too much seriously you shoot and will offer
moral support okay I guess we're gonna do it a rectangular five community subs
thank you rectangular so I just shoot how do I shoot oh check this out some of
you guys that are new here this is what I'm known for I'll show you what I'm
known for you ready Jamie 2802 803 thanks for the subs
five subs destroyed cabbage for just thanks for the five community subs what
I'm known for I wrote the book on that that should be two dogs why am I
shooting that oh you have to break them apart before you can pick them up oh my
god I'm so dumb DLC after this I am better thank you everyone on the right
side here for all the community subs these are all the subs today appreciate
raggle waggle thanks for 20 community subs 20 more from my god daddy thank
you for your miraculously unbanned not name I don't even know how you have this
name but thanks for the 10 subs the gold oh yeah gold shots now thanks and 10
thanks for 20 thanks for the five dino pulse thank you you think I should ever
play a game like this what's the one that everybody loves it's like PlayStation
Nicaragua yeah that'd be good oh my fucking god Abe Abe cash him babe cash
him thanks for the 50 community so thank you for the 50 community subs you guys
gonna put me in a new tax bracket holy shit 50 fucking subs thank you so much
everybody that is a 5,000 bit drop to oh my god from villainy congrats on beating
that level German now plenty ayayayaya level again or else I'm sure you know
the song again but thanks for the 5,000 another insane amount of money am I
saving everybody I'm okay I haven't been paying that much attention am I killing
them and then picking up their angels oh I'm not supposed to be avoiding these
either I'm supposed to be picking them up I'm treating it like it's an actual
bullet hell game insanity guys the frillity 10 subs 10 more on top get cat
I can't I feel like I'd be pretty good at some of these games I really do
somebody made my oops somebody made it I remember a while ago somebody made my
like streamer like D&D kind of card and I had I had a 9.2 in twitch reflexes I
have four in problem-solving but I mean I think I might twitch card was pretty
good I did it finally we have peace and harmony in the cosmos it's been a while
we feel sort of funny plus 10 bolting you've all done such a fab work we're so
proud of how much you've grown hey thanks King that was like powerful
better than fashion week that's pushing by the way how was that freakish little
game it's in Katamari Memorial if you ever need it fab all requests completed
anyhow wipe screen we forgot something major you know about Uranus one of our
favorite star it hasn't been remade yet we left it off the list our bad we know
we'll fix it through ban ban you remake Uranus and we'll totally cooperate we
even built a special house on the big tripper Chateau Notre-Dessier so come
on get wrong not this one all right I need to go to my accessory shop so here's
the DLC levels but we're not gonna do them yet I want to go to my accessory
shop why am I pronouncing it like that all right what we got big giraffe head
yeah cuz that one all right I know is there is there is somebody yellow you
yeah I want to be the giraffe wait that's more of a giraffe isn't it no
this is correct that's fine was this looks good there's a run button whoops
all right there's the memorial boy was the one in a new island right I love that
noise I love the running sound oh there we go
where's BamBam where's BamBam get over here no I want to dance too I like the
robot one I kind of want to play with the watch dogs print the buttons here
it is complete the King's request to make Uranus colored lights there's a
green screen stream gonna be soon yeah probably in a couple weeks I have to
make the channel go first a royal roll here means the dawn of a new Uranus
hmm you're in a good mood any who this one's for us okay so a super special
rule whatever we ask you roll like stylish then cute then gadgets and so
on we want a planet after our own capricious heart I need that game the
vocabulary game all righty off to earth it's not pronounced is it pronounced no
it's not Uranus Uranus no it's Uranus no baby here we are this room is where we
start now there's this here's the scoop on the special rule this is one for us a
starry tribute yes it's Uranus does that make you Cronus don't get any ideas
will be your Katamari a blast from the past see it's our inner child we're so
cute roll everything up so our boyhood self grows what is the King there's no
time limit and oh you have to find whatever we tell you like food or
drinks or creatures or gadgets we want Uranus to have it all I wish is your
command like roll up chick stuff quite a challenge but can you handle it and you
get to watch the evolution of us by the way we only roll first-class no bumping
strange yes you get to be the adult for once ciao Nick ever think about style
fashion and such we do it's not just the vanity it's because the cost of this
song can use all the fun and beauty it can get you know we will vote at the
best-dressed creature in the cosmos adapted from another source accepted on
behalf of all cosmos classic we kept the trophy it was too shiny to share I'm
getting like tired here my character is lying down shaped like a cake and yeah
and a bunch of accessories chosen personally you know what our favorite
accessory was it was a shark oh don't know those it's a hat and shaped like a
shark and it roared fish don't roar but I had to do what's your point stop
wiggling we may even get you one right okay roll up the stylish things thank
you and someday you can be ornament okay goodbye stylish things they said no
bumping this is Peter and the wolf what's that song what's that no Peter in
the stylish no there's no time on the coins those are stylish no bumping right
if I what happens if I bump do I lose is a toad oh that's not right we thought we
loved this when we were little but children childhood ends oh well moving on
next roll up rich luxury okay yes luxury jewels all the luxurious stuff
imagine if I read all that cookies all right go no money money and jewels don't
bump I bumped like three times it doesn't matter
diamonds can't get him in wait I think I'm going down I'm going down money
can't get it I'm gonna can you get us cute stuff we're talking adorable small
cute you roll up cute cute cute cute cute cute cute cute cute cute cute cute cute
cute cute cute roll up cute roll up cute get cute cute cute cute cute cute good
cookies dice cute dice are cute our rats are cute oh here he is
Gabby J now do you want only need out here a life cute things I'm doing it you
got so many cute things that's so fast gracious you've earned yourself another
story okay come to think of it we don't remember having much fun as a child
there are every day we studied strict royal education for a future king just
between you and us Papa was a skinner Ian wish we'd played more frolicking in
the fields playing ping-pong cavorting in clouds
dancing with das daisy food daisy poda deed I don't all right you got to bring
it from PhD to like eighth grade that's the only way I'm gonna know what you're
trying to tell me play time take it the mice I need to be 20 centimeters to do
that this takes us back to a happy place oh we need it out of life back then we're
play things you got something that's so bad gracious you've earned yourself into
the story yeah we're kind of hungry roll of some food yes maybe some ramen curry
is nice too we are the foodie King arugula beats
cuz I don't want to garlic and sapphires we eat it all that's how we got this
amazing cosmic bod Nick is trying yes but far from buffness being picky icky
carrots liver fishies try everything feed the body and brain this I feel like
you wrote this as a copypasta in this chat food is an adventure exercising his
trip but we confess we did have one food dislike we used to hate cheese it just
smelled weird Papa said it was rude so we made ourselves eat it thanks to him
we have great teeth and bones and we like cheese now humble fog yum dinner is
served Nick go roll up lots of food how about ice cream sandwich rats are not
food orange slices how about bong water you think is sick fuck other rats actual
food so good coffee creamers not food you sure it's Gary got it everything about
style fashion yes I have we do fashion fashion fashion best dressed yes I've
seen sharknado whatever he said let's go up money there is he grew oh my
goodness what's going on I'm all warmed up perfect we want you to
collect warm things now an endurance challenge no we have our reasons get
hot stuff last night we went out for Korean barbecue with a friend and we
put away a serious amount of food epic rule was keep eating until one cried
uncle we won of course yay couldn't move though nay how did we end up doing a
thing like that it's all a blur too much soju we think for some reason it's been
like this all week the pasta pandemonium the sushi shin did and now our very own
obesity crisis the weight can't stay no like guess they must go this is the
reason we ourselves are on a roll but warm things will help us sweat out the
fat yes then we can go back to our old spelt selves and go out with friends for
ramen tomorrow night okay hot food matches you can't sweat out fat only
water is this the part where you press your glasses back up to your nose is a
kid's cartoon you can breathe out fat magic hot things we want luxury how many
to do this for until he's grown bananas with luxury aren't they airmail that
box you rolled up as a present we were wondering how are you with cold we adore
the cold I love the cold roll up cold things stop ignoring me roll up cold
stuff oh really we didn't know so it was our bad we have to apologize don't stop
skipping cake is cold peanuts cookie tin rats rats are cold-blooded so it's so
easy is it really that easy right now it's coming back to us the bygone days
of youth we used to have a collection of cold things to think earth had so many
cold things you did good we think you're big enough to hear about this
hey Nick what kind of thirsty not something drink thought so rolling is
thirsty kind of work hydration is important we need a nice drink but not
to excess no glugging or chugging can't risk wetting the bed yes such trauma
other kids can be so cruel you know hmm how long did we wet the bed let's see
that was wait you first Nick what you stopped doing that ages ago seriously at
your age but we didn't stop until we were almost oh backpedal we like never
wet the bed ever we didn't even need diapers as a baby you talk about the
weirdest things really few we're thirsty go on fun as a drink
things are so weird they're just strange that's a basket better be in the
Tabasco versus I don't know name I it's so it's so bad I can't even tell you
it's named Sriracha yeah it's coming back to us the bygone days of youth we
used to have a collection of drinks to think earth had so many drinks you did
good we think you're big enough to hear about this okie-dokie sound go click
something makes sound boomer actually likes Tabasco omega low I don't think
Sriracha is very good I like Tabasco Tabasco is fantastic it's what you
should be putting on oysters you should be putting on pizza you should be
putting on eggs this is important to me I just I want to know how many people I
would not invite over for dinner and I wouldn't let you in my house okay I
almost just spelled it wrong but whatever is it like a Sriracha or is it
Sriracha it's Sriracha it's it's Sriracha okay let's find out I have to
put this on hold for just a second come on where would mean they both suck hey
looks like looks like the this is really close 51% like Tabasco more than Sriracha
half of you were invited over my house for dinner well 52% I'll bring the
Sriracha hey invite what are you having something I can ruin with Sriracha yeah
I'll bring it you're not invited over my house either that's all right Sriracha
is good in noodle dishes idiot I don't put it in anything and if it's in the
food if I order like they'll say ramen in this Sriracha they put it in the
broth I immediately send it back and I saw oh excuse me excuse me it's give me
what wait waiter excuse me is this Sriracha in here yeah it's part of the
broth okay chair against the ground standing up someone's get five green
leader thanks to the five subs now I will eat Sriracha I just refused to put
it on something if it's in something like okay like a lot of spicy mayo's are
made with Sriracha that's fine that's all right I'll eat it I'm not gonna put
it on anything what about the guitar I need sounds okay you can take up the
imagine liking mayonnaise this is yes or no question I'm not gonna tell you how I
feel because I want a completely unbiased opinion on this let that run
for a little bit okay I'm glad I'm glad a majority of you
guys silver 9992 thanks for the 10 more subs 10
silver sound go clicks okay I gotta get sound musical instruments out here
pianos trumpets yes and yeah I am fully aware that there's there's a scale of
mayonnaise being gross if you get the good shit the real good shit yeah I'm
gonna make a lot of people upset here and I might you know this is this is
such a fucked up opinion to a lot of people I might actually lose some of you
as viewers for saying this it's actually very possible when I say this some of
you might now have such a bad opinion of me that you don't want to be here
anyway it's like I do oh I do I don't not every time but it's sometimes when I
feel like it if I really feel like it I do my french fries English style
that's right I'm one of those sickos I don't need to say what that means feels
good to remember he's getting bigger you've earned some of the story we were
wondering how are you with cold more cold cold cold cold cold cold cold what do you mean by that
okay you ready I'd like to dip my french fries and mayonnaise okay I'm done I said it and now
I'm I've lost you not every time not every time only sometimes that's not I
don't do like ketchup it's English style I know a lot of when you tell that to
people they don't look at you the same ever again yeah sometimes I do french
fries and mayonnaise like I like the way that the texture and I like the kind of
deep flavor that it with the fries and the crispiness and you may as well just
told them that you love to swallow fucking spit like I may have just asked
that person to spit on in my mouth hey if I lean back can you spit in my
mouth what the fuck that's like that's the kind of reaction do I like pizza in
ranch I'm and Pete yes pizza there's no pizza in blue cheese pepperoni pizza in
blue cheese dressing get out of town man how many of you hate me now I guess I'm
going around the same circle this guy's a sicko I'm not a sicko see I told you
it's like going to a restaurant and saying I want did you give me a side of
mayonnaise with my fries in rewind hey could you go into like the cat litter
and dig out cat shit and put it on my food same reaction I need luxury lily
pads aren't luxurious and we need animals now Earth has lots of living
things not as many as it used to which makes us sad here's an idea you can roll
up creatures everyone needs to pick me up now and then yes do you have any
favorite friends English style small ones slow ones snails mouse lemurs we
prefer the Giants whenever we're on earth we visit with whales we swim and
jump and feast by the light of the start there are old friends and we can't find
though did we all offend them that would be just often we have big friends on
other stars too we got big friends big enough to wrestle like the fish and
this is a Trump spawned in a grease trap fire fast-food store we confess he's the
only creature that scares us just a little though and only when he's eating
anyway we want you to gather lots of creatures friends from all walks of
hops and slithers of life we think of Katamari maybe the ideal ecosystem I
just saw Tabasco sauce on an s-tier convent list yep you did all right
animals there we go on the tier list I think I already did it people animals
yeah that man I guess it's true and people are just whether the animals
right no people are animals people aren't in they are we're a species of
animal okay I'm gonna do a state's tier list yeah it would be like
Assachusets Nevada I don't know like New Hampshire I've only been to like five
states guys how am I supposed to do that well that's not true I've traveled to a
bunch of states but I haven't spent enough time in them to give them put
them on a tier list earth is so many plants all right name a state I'll tell
you if I've been there before no no no no no no name a state I'll tell you if
I've been there for more than three days Kansas no California yes Alaska no Rhode
Island yes Arizona no I've been to the Arizona I've been to the Phoenix Airport
for 30 minutes Colorado no Mexico no New Hampshire yes Germany is not a state in
America but no Georgia no Michigan no South Carolina no Pennsylvania oh no
Oklahoma no Connecticut yes New Jersey no Maryland yes Oregon no New York yes
Illinois yes Nevada Wyoming no Massachusetts yes Rhode Island yes I
already said that one Texas interestingly enough no I in fact have
never even been to the state of Texas not even once like a connecting flight
or something I've never been to Texas we've been to Rhode Island but not Texas
yeah I lived in New England for 30 years oh but I not go to Rhode Island Maine
yes oh our Papa can still lift us you know but we can lift you so we're even
then again Papa gave up the most powerful job ever so we can be the king
of all the cosmos does giving up power make you more powerful thinking face do
you grow into power by growing out of it thinking face whoo getting too near the
deep end of the pool let's just stick to rolling up powerful stuff what's a
surprising Florida yes Minnesota no California yeah New York yes Montana no
Alabama nope lots of powerful things Arkansas nope
go back no that's all right we need to roll up playtime he's getting big how
have I not been to New Jersey well I've been I've been in New Jersey but I've
never been there for more than a couple days yes I've driven down the driven
I've driven through New Jersey and I've spent maybe like a two hours there
from a pump to Brazil 12 hours is enough but that's okay here's the thing a lot
of people don't realize especially if you're not American if you are a non
American watching right now you're probably like wait how the fuck you live
in the United States have you never been to some of these places and because why
I don't have a reason is they may as well be other countries look I know you
can go from like France to Denmark in like seven hours in a fucking train it's
a it's USA is huge and it may as well be like eight different countries from the
climate from the different climates that are in America to the different
types of people that are the different cultures it's a huge place and I know I
know I do my prize English style but I'm an American but yeah people I was all
right let me tell you something the difference between Nevada and Alabama it
we may as well be on other planets one of them is like the desert and the other
one is like a swamp the United States is just Dark Souls it's just a Dark Souls
map it's a video game region it's Warcraft zones I got a little ocean
stuff yep yep VR Josh I have not paid it I have not even been looking at the
screen I've been reading chat at least 10 to 12 straight minutes I've just been
moving these sticks long as this level that's a great question long enough to
hopefully not fail it's my opinion on ketchup
ketchup and mayonnaise well you just made a dressing ketchup and mayonnaise is
the thing already thousand islands now you got my attention I can't really eat
it anymore but I was a fiend for Tabasco and ketchup
you would do ketchup and a little thing a little cup the cup with the that's is not
that's all you need and then stir it up with a french fry
that's so that's the blue you do like two or three bloop bloops and that's all
you need you don't need anything else more energy more energy and that's what
I'm doing when is it eating the ghost pepper I already did man oh it's good
burn socks tears tears tears are coming down tears are coming down
we've got you're grasping them never been aggressive to stop you before
all right we're hopefully nearly full grown we've managed to put on some size
haven't we we find the sound of our own voices soothing we sort of lose track of
everything else but we're quite content with the job you've done you're free to
roll up whatever you like we'll nap if you'd like to stop just hit the X button
what about the DLC levels they're gonna be the DLC levels are gonna be just not
even interesting if I roll up every single thing in the game I got some roll
up the key here he is rolled up he's in there the DLC levels are more themed
now I'm getting flashbacks I don't want to be going with the big
posthumous thing again I beat it let's do these themes levels just get it over
just get it over with and do the Mayo tier list
didn't I already do condiments did I I didn't do condiments I did yeah I did
1,494 memories somebody got it already this is my list that's not a tier list
that's that's Jerma Jerma Poznan T'racha it sucks
Jerma Pepper let me see this is the same thing oh a horse I can have the king head on that's cool
and that's I've never taken giraffe off I've ever had old bay yeah I have old
bay's all right it's good on a lot of stuff but I wouldn't just put it on
anything do I like my steak with a one the back when I was like 14 I would put
A1 on the steak because I thought it made me more of an adult I thought
ordering A1 made me look older and look like I knew what I was talking about at
restaurants also another funny thing I used to lie to my dentist all the time
for no reason when I was like 13 I would tell them I don't know my brother used
to laugh his ass off at this he still brings it up sometimes when I would be
in the chair and we'll be talking about how things are going yeah I get any
concerns anything going on yeah you're brushing twice a day yeah you're
flossing oh yeah I'm flossing and I've been chewing a lot of Trident too like
I've been chewing Trident gum cuz that was the one that was supposed to clean
your mouth from all the commercials and the dentist would always be like oh okay
that's that and that is a straight-up lie right it is they used to have
commercials for Trident where it was it cleaned your teeth was that real it
can't be it's true the backpack is Connor okay now I'm gonna stay with the
draft how to Mario Memorial go to the crown what do you think I'm doing I did
all this before I've already done this I've done this oh you want to play the
music not this one what's it called where's my favorite song which was it
is it all right viewers gonna go up or down you was gonna go up and down you
was gonna go up or down which one you were is up or down which one watching
closely went up it went up
test that sorry I apologize okay it's time for fancy this is DLC and let me go
off on a little bit of a rant here I had to buy all this DLC individually
they're $1 each so I had to check out of the fucking Microsoft store seven
separate times in a row for a $1 purchase there is no bundle you cannot
add to cart I thought my credit card was gonna get declined at number five get
away from the person like a stew in their head what is that $1 purchases
you gotta put the credit card all right we go create a space station within the
budget this is DLC you've never seen this before nobody here has welcome to
the swanky fancy and schmancy we need stuff for a space station so collect
lots of things to make it well equipped food stationary toilet paper
electronics finally the title makes sense oh fuck yeah the title is now
accurate it's taking three hours it's okay nobody knows what this game is we
want Ayaya open up a new tab type in Katamari OST go to the section that has
that song and play it over and mute me tension shoppers what a nice big store
so bright so clean what an extraordinary shop must be why it's called a
supermarket anywho we have another special rule for you today's topic
shopping roll up many things by the way all sorts of currencies are used on
earth you know dollars rupees pesos euros and such too many for us to keep
counting let's just use Japanese money this time hmm strange mark looks like
chicken scratch any who will give you 300,000 that's a lot of money go on a
shopping spree but the key here is to make the most out of your money so pick
up a lot of cheap things it's for a space station so get going shoe okay I
got three hundred thousand dollars eggs are cheap fifty cheap donuts are cheap
dishes the expensive toothpaste is cheap now this is a great song you don't like
this one flavored seaweed can sweets these are expensive soda for the what
are these what are those Kool-Aid bursts work fish cake sausage are expensive
aren't they yeah that's too much money that's all right you've lost a hundred
that's because I stopped playing this song you know that some people have a
program set up that any any music how much were those I have to pay attention
to that sea urchins are actually serious cheap are they what are these
sushi juice whoo don't pick up that 300 yen well that was expensive I don't
know what I picked up watermelon slices that that's not expensive
what about cheese yeah it's harvest 700 bucks I just picked up a
thirty thousand dollar camera oh no this is film this is disposable film this is
too much money old coin old coin with 7700 rat this stuff is expensive let's
see yeah goodbye this is the expensive room not going in there lots of popsicles
it's expensive how is a lollipop more expensive than fruits and vegetables
don't back with that purse there's probably money in it
whipped cream yeah I got the bag gum section don't touch the cameras and film
we flip which I could get up there yeah don't touch the camera the whole case of
chewing gum all right let's get the fruits up here
I feel like this is gonna be good wait oh wait what's with the fish counter
don't touch these it's gonna be too big to what's up there napkins wait this is
special there's a sale this stuff all this shit's on sale what I just do what
I just do what I do how does it all on sale that shit it's not on sale it's
over 98 98 for these so what's the deal that's way more than 98 per can of tuna
what the bottom shelf wasn't on sale really there's like 200 cans there you
know sales work yeah there's a huge sticker that says everything here is
98 yen there was gold bars on the shelf yeah 98 times a hundred cans equals
$98,000 Jeremy what are you talking about $98,000 I think your math is off
that was fun oh we ordered a lot vegetables and cooking supplies and
got a cousin melons are only grown in shizuka prefect and in central Japan
you can cost over $200 each unlike the $5 mass-produced melons are likely to
come across in a Western supermarket crown melons take constant care and
attention to grow they've been growing these melons for 60 years at his farm
it's pasta okay well David saved it thanks to the five community sub not DLC
get it out of here all right let's get some more DLC this one over here it's
actually two over here no it's this one munchies manner roll up food to make
Cetus well what melons are gross anyways that's the that's the fruit that you
avoid in the fruit cup until you have nothing left you don't have any more
grapes anymore strawberries little pineapple pieces you just have melons
there that's that's the avoiding fruit and then you're like all right I guess
I'll eat the melon we need to collect our tons and tons of food vegetables
fruits and snacks all that yum whales eat four times their own weight in a day
yes so vast amounts of nutrients are in order wait hold on yeah somebody said
I'm thinking about cantaloupe it's cantaloupe that's what I'm thinking of
right now maybe is it may not it's not the cantaloupe is a melon that's yeah
cantaloupe is a melon yeah it's the gross one that's in the can it's the gross one
that's in the cup and I know everyone in the chat right now is like oh yeah let
me let me like get that let me eat my fruit cup and get to the melons and half
of them are hard chunks that have like the rinds part still there that you like
spit them out something smells good no I don't like melon I don't like cantaloupe
I also don't like look I'm gonna be completely open with everybody it's a
new Jeremy I'm gonna tell you everything about me I don't like melons I like
watermelon that's pretty that's pretty much the only one I also don't like are
you ready I'm gonna put it all out there this is just put it all out there today
I forgot what I was gonna say I don't remember what the thing I said after
the melons it was fuck he's really polarizing what was it
what was it it's gone I don't know it's gone was it a fruit no maybe it was no
this is gonna kill me no I don't know I hate when this happens how would I
transition from cantaloupe I need calories we calorie dent with the
tahini paste hot dogs high calories chocolate ice cream don't have very
much time lots of look at that that was a shitload milk whole milk gross
mushrooms are calorie dense all right
muffins very calorie rich look at all those cookies get me up there this is
it right now check this out all this all the desserts I'm gonna go for like
300,000 calories bread too oh god the bread disgusting I can't in good
conscious say that I love I love bread so much it's so bad because I'd like a
million else fresh rolls at dinner is like one of my favorite things in the
world
come on get up there slow down yeah tomato blocks all right let's get out
here while we're in here until lunch I want to get up top but I'm not big
enough to get up there all right whatever okay let's grab okay I'm up
oh holy shit that was a lot where am I okay anything else crabs into the proto
section again no don't get stuck don't get stuck six hundred down nice
I've ever swallowed gum on purpose no it gives me anxiety because I was told that
it takes nine years to have gum go through your whole digestive system so
it made me scared forever only seven years how would a rumor like that even
start to scare you it was done no I know it's parents trying to scare their kids
so they because kids oh this is yummy delicious tastes like fruits no but they
don't you're not supposed to swallow it down so what if we just tell make up this
huge lie about if you swallow it you're fucked for ten years don't swallow that
gum little Timmy it's gonna stay in you for seven years it terrifies you I get
it it's kind of funny because I'm pretty sure if bagel and cream cheese takes
longer to go through your body than gum if you were to swallow it takes like
four days
that was barely worth it what kind of bagels do I like I like everything
bagels or onion I will tell you I'm not a sugary bagel kind of guy cinnamon
raisin bagels no French toast bagel no it's not into it come on down here
lovers Lou roll up fabric to make a big up salmon bagel yes salmon I like it I
have to be in the mood for smoked salmon on a bagel though that's not
something that I want every day but I do like it yeah smoke salmon cream cheese
it's great you got to really be in the mood for it though it's kind of heavy
red yes yarn to string even bagels have more sugar than a candy bar yeah white
isn't white bread the equivalent of eating cotton candy like in your body
this process the same way it's worse is it I've heard I'm telling what I've
cream cheese capers that's the only place where I think I would ever have
actual want capers is on locks and bagels that's only in America you guys
are strange and put sugar in everything I'm not into that wait special rule for
the day make a big ball of yarn and string look at I love this level already
this is makes me want to play Zuma let's say this big in three minutes one meter
that's not very much time okay yarn cloth string be crafty and spin a ball
of many colors all right let's try it
what the hell can I even pick up here I need to pick up something okay can I get these I need to get bigger but this one's going to be
satisfying check this any more colors than red no I don't like it we've gone
over this before on screen but just the people that have never been here you're
only supposed to take in I think men are supposed to take in 38 grams of added
sugar a day and I think I think women are supposed it's like 32 or 34 but one
can of coke is your whole daily allowed limit for added sugar that's I kind of
fucked up three cokes a day dad dude I used to pound code red I would drink
code red every day I got it back downstairs I love this level this stuff
is awesome I might replay this level just to feel good the sugar is everywhere
only take it in 37 38 grams of sugar a day added like damn that's hard to do
it's in everything and then you see well I just do sugar-free that shit's bad for
you too
one minute 30 seconds
that means you have an iron that's all right I got to think what can you eat
with iron in it spinach most meats liver if you I don't like chicken liver
but chicken liver is the one of the highest places you can get actual good
real iron I just I think it's gross so I can't do it but you can get from
spinach spinach iron content is not great that's a lie well it's one of the
plant-based ways you get it's not the same kind of iron you get from me and I
agree with you still there iron is just iron research has found that the intake
of meat heme iron but not plant non heme iron was associated with an
increased risk of stroke they're different that they're different there's
hem there's there's he may and non he may iron okay well
oh yeah I know what I'm talking about don't eat that he may iron but no
chicken liver oysters too that's another one I don't it's the worst thing ever
because but let me save you guys I will rescue everybody in here that needs to
get more iron in the diet let me save you let me rescue you listen to me
closely what's the one food that I told you that was really into and I was
buying and I was eating it for like before streams and after streams what
was it no not garlic what I was it was like a four-day tirade not tuna you're
close you're close I thought that was like three straight days they come in
a can they come in a tin sardines somebody got it finally sardines are
one of the best foods you can possibly consume on earth they got iron they got
vitamins they got minerals they got protein it's good shit it's really good
for you except for the sodium yeah and apples have cyanide in them you can't
win and coffee gives you diarrhea and garlic gives you heartburn you can't
there's no you can't win guys there's no winning with food you just pick you try
it is your best did I do this one no roll up constellation related things to
make the Milky Way every anyone who has ever eaten has died that's true garlic I
guess garlic is really good but everything has a con is there any real
food on earth that doesn't have one single con water but you can drink too
much water and get over hydrated yes you can drink too much water and you can die
if you drink too much water it's true what are we supposed to do you could
choke on a cinnamon roll so what I know it's dangerous human breast milk I don't
think so I don't think so I think you're wrong there bootleg Snoopy thanks for
the five community subs appreciate it no one said that yes they did I would
never say that out loud when this where somebody else said it first hmm looks
like the yard of that glam house alrighty let's go over the rules for this
one constellation namesakes does that blow your mind well mind or no mind you
have this much time to gather stuff related to constellations for
constellations like cancer a Leo and Pegasus you can find crabs lions and
winged horsies that's the equivalent of biting a red pepper not liking the heat
and fearing the color red that's how our ancestors did it let's go
88 constellations
gotta get big enough to pick up the rabbit starfish crab no dog food what
constellations dog food
Chronos time
dumpling I'm not sure is there a god of hot dogs
nothing like it but you guys are speaking of hot dogs you guys know that
hot dog can legally be called the hot dog if it has 40% plastic in it pay
attention to what you're eating before anybody like relieves the channel that
like it's just kind of that's not true that's a lie I'm kidding that's that's
an actual fucking dumb lie like somebody may be like about to leave and clicking
the X like what the fuck is that true and then look it up and like you look
scared I'm just that's a lie I'm kidding I'm in some way gone all that trouble in
public opinion because it was their chicken and their chicken sandwiches like
40 or 50% soy and then everyone started the legs looking at wait a minute what
about like Taco Bell what's in that meat what's the filler they have soy in their
meat I think it was like 89% meat or something
Taco Bell is close Taco Bell is like 90 something I think 80 or 90 percent actual
real is it 100% got you it's not 100% Taco Bell proclaims that 88% of its beef
consists of premium beef and 12% of it is made up of a quote signature recipe
okay three or four rungs down is is Taco Bell horse meat why would you think this
is it what wait wait wait wait wait a minute wait this is this is not like a
scary Google hold on a second when was this I need to read this Taco Bell's
ground beef is the no it's a business insider which means I'm not allowed to
look at the website okay there we go Taco Bell's ground beef is the latest
food to be implicated in a horse meat scandal sweeping Europe and the UK is
this an onion article I'm not like eating an onion right Taco Bell's ground beef is
among the four new four new products found in the UK's food standardization
to contain more than 1% horse meat am I eating the onion this happened wait 2013
why would they be a horse meat what happened EU horse eaters what Ikea got
caught in it with their meatballs what the fuck is happening wait who this is
2013 that's not that long ago Burger King in Ireland admitted that some of
its burgers contain horse meat Taco Bell sent this statement to stress that the
finding would not affect its US businesses our domestic restaurants
have not been and will not be impacted because we do not use any meat from
Europe we stand for quality and we use a hundred percent premium beef like all
beef in the United States ours is USDA inspected and then passes our own 20
quality checkpoints all right good to know Taco Bell 88% meat look at this is
just like how like fucking bullshit fake articles hold on so this is the headline
Taco Bell says their meat is 88% beef not 36% 30 well how would it spread that
it was 36% meat they thought people thought it was oats and starch oat meat
I want to get some delicious oat meat wait three to five percent is made of
oats starch sugar yeast and citric acid the rest is water and spices check the
full statement below oh shit it is five percent oat meat how long good this is
2011 Taco Bell oat meat wait hold on Taco Bell this is the Taco Bell finally
adds vegan meat to the menu but there's a catch it's oat meat is that real this
is I thought this is a joke oat meat this is 2019 Taco Bell will launch a
limited time menu that features tacos made with oat based meat but only in
three places in London let's look at all this news look at all this is weird
look at all these random articles are you fucking with us no type in Taco Bell
oatmeal I don't know I try that I think about that like think about oatmeal it's
kind of like sloppy and like slippery and fucking slimy and shit like ground
beef is in the taco you can probably dress that up and I got it that would
I don't know if you put like beet juice in oatmeal and added like meat
flavoring to it and then like filled it up with some like I don't story or
something you might actually have like a taco me I'm not I'm not talking shit
because I've had to be on burger I've had the impossible burger before they're
good they're actually good they hate I'm not what am I gonna lie to you I do that
all the time but not this time
I'm not gonna be one of those people that eats the Beyond Burger and goes
like internally oh this is actually but externally is like yeah gross hey throw
a steak on the barbecue for me make it rare I like that that's what I like
it was good it tastes good I don't know how you want to swing it first is it how
processed it is maybe the taste is there and this is somebody that is also
saying this somebody that lost five grand on it trying to short it in the
stock market because I was like fuck this dumb I didn't do that that's a lot
of money I did not do that so it was ten no you better fess up like this the
stock rose in value by such a since its IPO it's such an insane amount that it
had to come back down it was impossible actually impossible like their food
that shit like increased by like 300% in value you guys ever played I'm not a
video game
oats no I was gonna say grand theft auto 5 you didn't do the grand theft auto 5
stock market you know how it works I've read a few books I read a book was
called timing the stock market the easiest way to make money timing the
stock market written by Jeremy Elbertson what kind of name is Jeremy if I had
access to the chat right now I would delete your comment but I mean like it's
kind of weird sorry my name's not like Greg it's Jeremy what kind of a name is
Jeremy it's a great name actually Jeremy's a I like Jeremy doesn't
Jeremy sound like a very inviting person oh that's Jeremy that's a psycho name I
didn't even look I'm not paying any attention roll it this big in this much
time two meters five minutes what am I looking for her collect lots of
mechanical stuff okay this level seems kind of fun
get the mechanical stuff what are we candy corn we're not speaking to you
I gotta get up what about battle toads why don't you say that what are you talking about
what do you mean battle toads battle toads like am I a battle toad you think I'm a toad you think I'm like
slimy and stupid and like gross what do you mean toad why am I a toad you think I eat bugs
do I eat bugs I don't eat bugs do you think I eat bugs why do you say that all right I'm
obviously not big enough calm down captain mania damn half the stuff I can't even get this is a really
good song the rest 50 come on is there any boppers here I don't know extreme boppers get all the
robots give me that goddamn food it's all I've been trying to find it in my
brain cantaloupe melons all right oh yeah squash it's gross got it I don't like squash at all I
don't like it I didn't know how I figured that out because there's a bunch of different kinds
of melons with a bunch different kinds of squash it's not a fan I think they look cool I would have
squash in my garden not because I like to eat them because I think they're interesting to look at
and I would sell them big pickup right there I'm running out of time what was it two meters right
get in there this level is pretty cool too
robots don't think I can get them no I cannot you get all these sewing machines and TVs
yellow and green so what about yams yams are fit in that category right yams is a yam a squash
squash family squash kind of relative or something yams a potato uh yeah because I like yams
they're okay as long as they have the dollop of melted marshmallow
thanksgiving uh dish a little side it's pretty good failure here comes the failure
failed level is kind of small try it again yeah I'm gonna beat it here we go better spot to start
yeah it's like I'm gonna stay right on the corner and get all these
little mosquitoes salt shakers was a mosquito zapper
I spent a lot of time getting hit by this stuff they like I just go back on
this level I liked it originally now it's making me angry I can't fucking go anywhere at this level
I'm gonna go in the ground
I can't get any of this stuff
jerma hates this level it's a little cluster it's a little crampy
it is it's kind of crampy I don't know I can go outside eventually I didn't do it yet but
barrier belts damn it's kind of fucked up I'm not thinking of picking them up
barrier belt pick pick pick pick pick pick pick pick lots of robots get them
uh squash is what it was all right I haven't said a sentence in like 30 seconds that's sorry
down down yes spur yeah I know I know I know open up that door so I can get out of here
if we're gonna open oh you idiot yeah we're good yeah there it is now it's open
two meters what is that that person is a flying computer social commentary
but we're all obsessed with consuming and we need to unplug we're all just computers now
we all got a barcode that's how you do it for a walking camera it's too
woke already done I think all the sardine iron is going to your brain
good that's where I'd like it to go I'd like it to fill my brain with nutrients that would be
great so I think there's one more two more DLC levels I think we're almost done
do I chew on the sardine eyes no I get skinless boneless sardines I don't get well I did no what
the hell enjoy the mercury poisoning and then they did the smiley chat person face
and then they said I don't know I'm just kidding is that the thing
the dangerous colony only babies get it boneless no only babies want to eat no bones
when they spread it over a piece of toast if that makes me a baby then uh boo boo gaga
wowie so many buildings all right time to get started rolling in this strange place
roll a katamari this big that's pretty huge three thousands not a joke lots of dangerous stuff
all right I gotta get three thousand pick up dangerous things I think it's a real big enough
height dinosaurs are dangerous like seven minutes to get there
I'm just there I go just not even looking at the game I was reading about mercury what's wrong
bad bad with bad I'm not even bad I'm not bad I'm not bad seriously
just fucking goddamn fucking thing fucking dumb thing I was doing that in the pre-stream chat
and I realized that not everybody was here yesterday I wrote like three or four times
like stupid fucking dumb fucking thing games fucking stupid and people just like yeah what's
are you all right moving city what is going on with this city what is on here
are these giant whales holy shit those are big all right I gotta get bigger
the whales are saving us I'm coming I'm coming get all that vegetation that's mine now
hold on you want to go out auto yeah auto wants to leave the room he's been in here the whole time
and I didn't even show him do you want to go out you want to leave the room he's resting on a pillow
20 auto or riot no I'm not even dressed no I'm not dressed for the occasion I'll be right back
do you want to go out what do you want to do I'm sorry yeah let's go all right I'll be right back
I actually hadn't even gone this is the first BRB all right let me pee too cool and I got a
new drink let's bring you back any oatmeats in chat oh show auto maybe later
it's kim kim has heard the door and he was like
bring the dog to and they go oh my god somebody's here somebody's here somebody's here somebody's
here somebody's here something droopy this is way more elaborate than that he's a cousin
Havana and peso wait I already have these and there's miso and marcy still not big enough to
that whale shit that'd be 3000 the game is too loud how it's been the same volume for hours
give me a whale all right whales are now obtainable like lag lag there's a big present over there
on earth is going on what the fuck I'm so confused
so
there he is well I gotta get him what the fuck look at all those bits flying around
it's a lot of money big bits look at that 100 bucks right there oh I can't get it
okay I hope I can get big enough to at least even see this stuff there's a big present over there
it's gonna be close I don't think I'm gonna do it though 3000 already wow pop it up present
or riot I'm gonna try come on increase in size 6000 do it oh killing me seriously
why have I not grown present no longer 8000 give you that king
where's the king did I get him no I didn't get him where is he come here oh no
oh well well omega lull omega lull omega okay so there's regular lull which is like laughing
that means you're laughing so is omega lull like you had hearts to laugh ultimate laughter
what the fuck do you think it is um an emote that replaces the letter o
because that's like 75 percent of its uses true oh my god what is it wings it's in the cake
and like that's us wow droopy droopy best cousin droopy with the giraffe head
I was barely with it scorpius if scorpions were bigger would we be eating them like lobsters
because that's what they are we eat them already we do I think that's it is there any more
I think there's one more dlc level it's one of the pods
did I get them all I do this one that's the dangerous thing I just did
I feel like there was another pod up here this one that's the constellations
yeah did that did that did that up here did I do this pod mechanical yeah I did game over but
not yet not yet see what the collection is is it over 100 79 percent how
I beat the damn game I want to where's the new um wait the dance party that's how I get them over
I'm not doing it right oh you have to get 100 on every level I see
are you yep all right wait I need to look at the other costumes kind of cool kind of cool hold on
flowers cool too cool and the wings should I do the wings they're not that big I wish they were
bigger now I want the drill to be prominent I think the backpack is just the best man it works
okay yeah well that's it for Katamari I did it I beat it there's no other I did all seven dlc
levels right do a condiment tier list is that what you guys really want I've already done it
you guys want condiment tier list really oh that's right read to the yarn level thank you
so much how could I have forgotten that where was it lovers loom thank you
did I do munchies manner yep I have to do this one one more time and then I'll do a condiment
tier list I wonder how it differs from when I did it already I did I what if it's all completely
different one more just normal Joel's movie no I'm not gonna watch Joel's movie I'm not gonna watch
a movie no I will some other day that's 30 minutes I don't get that kind of time
don't distract me from my favorite level you've already distracted me from my favorite level
and for this I I could not forgive you I've been distracted let's do it again you spent
two hours on one level I don't have time no we're gonna do a video watching stream anyways pretty
soon I'm not doing it tomorrow no I want to watch I want to watch like a movie on Twitch I
want to watch like a public domain movie and I guarantee you're gonna get sick of that real quick
so we can watch that movie there oh also while there's people here let's talk about this um
remember if you were in this pre-stream chat no you if you were in the post-stream chat I talked
we talked about this extensively yesterday we talked about stream that's gonna happen at some
point we've thrown ideas around of salt and germa where I get servers over the course of
a few different games and it's you I'm going to try to have as many people as humanly possible
in these servers let's say for instance a Minecraft server or a Conan exile server
and the whole goal is I'm the king and you have to do everything for me and if I die
the stream ends there are at least three or four games that I want to do this with
I'm gonna and what not just that that's just one piece of this I also want to set up like a king's
court where people come and like share their grievances with the king like we'll make like
a castle and shit and they'll I'll have like king's guard and you can come ask questions and
there'll be executions and shit I'm not gonna die in four seconds because I'm gonna have a
loyal king's guard there's gonna be like 20 people whose only job is to make sure that they're like
in like the gold armor to make it so I don't die me and uh me and cad were actually talking
about random stuff and like imagine a scenario where we play Minecraft and it's like bring me
50 gold bar gold boxes and make a statue of me or I execute five people I was like holy shit that's
fucking funny and now imagine there's 500 people in that server I want to collect taxes I want to
go door to door with my like king's guard and collect taxes and shit and if you try to kill me
or you better you better make it for real you better conspire with I'm coming to collect taxes
you fuck up an assassination attempt you're getting fed to the lions which is like a 12
foot dug hole with like aggressive wolves in it no lions are them lions in Minecraft I did it cool
that's fun but not just something like Minecraft but going to like here's the thing though like
Conan exiles I think you can only have like 50 people in a server why don't just get disconnected
so it would have to be we would have to whitelist people and maybe you'd have to like put an
application in as to why you should be in the town and I also want to set up a thing where if
we have a scenario like that oh you can only have 50 people in that server people are just
going to sit there and they're going to turtle they're not going to they're just going to you're
the same person's going to be there for like the whole other entire like three or four street by
the way uh the idea is that if I'm alive we keep going and the town progresses but um they'll be
aged so it'll be like one minute is like five to ten days and if you get to be like 60 years old
you die of old age so there's no you know we we're always cycling through people does the king age
yep but I'll age a little slower so I might just die of old age one day on stream
I just die of old age you gotta I'm gonna be a good king though what game am I thinking about
doing this in uh Minecraft is probably the easiest one to do it in there's also rust
there's also cone and exiles there's arc I'm thinking of any one of those games that came
out where it was just an open environment where you're supposed to build a castle
or build a thing with a bunch of people on the same server reign of kings there's a lot of them
and we could it could I want to make it a series but from game to game and scenario to scenario
for instance we talked about like I don't do anything it was going to be wow classic where
I was not going to play the game and if I had to exert any force then I would turn the stream off
that was the joke we were talking about last night and I was like if people want to actually
watch me do that shit we still could do that I don't know but imagine a scenario where there's
like a bunch of tunnels that I can like escape in in Minecraft somebody like if there's like
an angry mob outside coming in with bows and arrows it's like 30 of you that have all like
conspired that you're ready to go today's the day you're gonna go for the king oh better make
it there's 15 tunnels I'm gonna go through good luck I want to be like a living ecosystem for at
least a few days I don't know I might die instantly but I think it's worth doing I want to put like a
bunch of like time and resources into it I feel like it'd be really funny and really fun someone's
gonna shoot you in the head with an enchanted bow not if not if I look you gotta start from zero
it's gonna I'm gonna it's gonna be not easy I'm gonna I'm gonna mod those servers it's gonna be
you're gonna have age they'll be on your team we'll see your bodyguards will just be shields
well the theory is that to make it so I don't die in the first 10 seconds there's a you know town
hall and there's a castle and I have a room in the castle and all my loyal servants have rooms in
the castle and there's like 25 people in that castle that I gotta ring the bell if somebody's
climbing in my window with a fucking axe and I could defend myself too by the way if you die
that you're that's it you're out someone else is gonna take your place as a baby we'll just swarm
but will you though this is where it gets interesting because I'm not going to be like
a bad king I you know I'm just gonna I want the town to be sufficient and be moving forward and
there's gonna be lots of loyal people that are in this town well you think that they're just
gonna try to kill me we're gonna have trials there'll be trials by combat if you do something
wrong it's like if you if you get like arrested or if you try to kill me or something and I'm
feeling a little generous today the two people that tried to kill me that were working together
in their own little private discord you two have to fight to the death and whoever dies see you
later is the server gonna be hardcore probably not sure yet but I want to do this a few times over
a couple different games so this is all very preliminary but it's doing it for me and you
know one of the one is an idea that does it for me it's it happens it's just gonna happen
I'm gonna put a bunch of time and I'm gonna put some money into it too see if we can get
some like coded server shit that you know you can have aging in the servers and you just get
deleted and you die it should be fun but there are a couple different ways to play it we can
do them as many ways as we want what game that hasn't been decided yet it'll be probably like
minecraft rust reign of kings arc cone and exiles something but we can just openly just sort of rp
in on our own terms with our own rules in the server I want to see how long I last I want to
see if I have any loyal people that will protect me make it a weekly event that's the idea the
original title of the stream was going to be lazy fuck because I didn't do anything I just stood
around well everyone did everything for me and like money was poured into my like character's
account and stuff ego maniac all right let's move on I'm gonna do my tier list hey ball rolling
dlc is actually done all right give me a condiment tier list let's see one give me
that's the spy statue bit it's the spy statue bit but with actual rules and potentially
hundreds of people participating not just like three so it's a kind of an evolution of that
all right tear maker checks mix no not clicking that one us president's not clicking that one
is there even I where's the condiment tier list let me see it okay
this one sucks butter is on here who uses butter as a condiment butter that's not a condiment it's
like an ingredient you guys think it was gross when I said mayo and fries butter as a condiment
on vegetables yeah but that's like no no no no no you that's like part of the recipe you don't
just like you you guys add a bunch of butter on your vegetables are eggs a condiment too
ah fuck damn it that hurt okay uh this one I did better one something better than this
did you eat a toenail let me look about I'll just look one up world of warcraft expansions
condiments and sauces this looks like the one this is okay here we go this one looks a little
better let me get out of this game just give me one second while I do this that was katamari it
was a lot of fun those these games are wonderful that's how you know I have a real xbox and you
just heard that noise I didn't make that with my mouth fine I'll do the world of warcraft okay
I'll do the expansions one two and I I could do this with my eyes closed why would why do
I even need to do this on camera I could just say it this was six of them