Dude, I just took a big sip out of my coffee.
It was a huge mistake. Just a massive mistake.
Because I didn't stir it enough. I stirred it a little bit.
And the creamer that I put in went to the bottom and I sucked up pretty much like
30% of the cream that I put in. So now my cream ratio is ruined.
I had this perfect. I didn't stir it enough.
God. That's a real sad, sad emote scenario, I think.
Spit it back out. He's already swallowed it.
And there's some new, there were some new random emotes.
We're testing out a couple of them. This German window, is there now?
I might just make that official. I was thinking about, because there's animated emotes now.
I was like, hmm. I was thinking maybe I could have like me jumping out of the window as an
animated emote. So we're going to give it a trial run here. This one is just free.
See how people like it. I don't want to do German TV again.
So because that is never used and it's just still there.
Upside, yeah, we're gonna play No More Heroes 3 again today.
Continuing the journey through the game. I don't think I'm going to beat it today.
We're going to go the same amount of time, I think.
Somewhere between like five, four and a half to like six hours or something.
Very, I want to play. I wanted to get into it, but I doubt I will see the end.
So we will finish this next weekend after today and after WarioWare.
This WarioWare comes out on the 10th. So you bet your ass that on the 10th
we're going to play WarioWare. And on the 11th, probably No More Heroes 3. Finish it up.
I mean, I'm just on the Switch. So that makes a lot of sense.
German TV is my most used emote, German Punching.
German Punching should be, maybe should be official too.
I got a tweet. I'll be right back.
I'm also realizing the title right now for a lot of you.
Probably just like, what the fuck is he doing? That's the seal.
I don't know. I couldn't think of what to write.
I couldn't think of anything to put on the title because it's just playing No More Heroes.
So I couldn't, whatever. Sometimes this titles that makes sense.
I didn't have one. What about the sunflowers?
Yeah, yeah, maybe you'll see those tomorrow.
I'm just kidding. Yeah, I've got, I've got a full spread of images to show you today.
Green Thumb Andy. You'll see those eventually.
I got to find a way to put those in and just stall somewhere in the stream.
I don't, I don't want to do it right now.
I want to wait till there's 25,000 people, concurrent viewers here today to do that.
So, I mean, I'm not, I am not going to show the sunflowers until I have 25,000 viewers.
So, I'm sorry. That's just the way it is.
No, I will do it in like a few minutes. I'm just kidding.
I'm not going to hit 25,000 viewers.
It's 12,000 people with two eyes. Holy shit.
That is a, that's a next level take, I think.
You're going to max out at 12,000.
If that, I don't know. I don't think so.
Yes, you will. Well, we'll see.
Because if I do, then you get to see some of the sunflowers.
I'm very excited to play this again.
Do it now.
No, we got to wait.
A lot of people have been waiting to see these sunflowers.
So, they might not, they just, maybe they just got the notification.
Maybe they're eating, maybe they're just hanging out.
I don't know.
Okay, we're going to wait till like at least 10 to 20 minutes into the stream.
Last thing we did was,
I just beat the ninja.
It's the last thing that happened.
And we just kind of stood right here.
This is Persona.
This is no more heroes free.
Twitch mobile notifications take about 20 minutes to send.
Yeah, so we got time.
You won't play the spin-off.
We have new clothes.
We already had this.
I actually really like this.
Got a good message on it too.
I really, I like the black hoodie and the black pants.
Yeah, we're going to wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. I want to see what else is there.
Let me see what else is there.
You have a hoodie that just says, fuck.
I think you need to load in a little more.
Let's see what, I got like two, three other shirts though.
I actually, I like that one too.
That shirt's actually merch of a band.
Really?
Kill, kill, kill, kill, kill.
Didn't I get something else?
I thought I got something else.
I thought I had another shirt.
No, I wore kill, kill, kill, kill, kill already.
I like that hoodie.
I want to put it on.
Let's go for it.
I want most of these shirts IRL.
I mean, what's the term?
What's the term for like, look at how awesome these, the good clothes.
Shirts, the pants.
What is it?
No more racists three.
It's called Drip.
I feel like in all the pseudo games, there's lots of that.
You didn't wipe?
No slang Andy.
Why would I have slang?
I'm like 20 years older than you.
You know what my slang was?
It was fucking radical.
Totally tubular.
You would punch me in the mouth if I said that to you, wouldn't you?
That's totally tubular.
Like you would punch me in the face immediately.
And like, I don't want to, why would I want someone to do that to me?
51, what's with the 51?
51 Ronin, 51 grams.
Oh, it's pseudo 51.
Okay.
But like, whatever.
Whatever.
All right, let's do it.
We got to go to Perfect World.
The sus guy has really changed.
No, he hasn't.
You've changed.
Your perspective on how you feel about me has changed because you've changed.
Anti-Aliasing Andy.
Well, I didn't make this game, so don't worry.
I didn't unclog this toilet.
You've changed.
He's got Drip.
The sus guy literally did the face like five days ago.
That's me.
Just say I did it.
We're waiting for the sunflowers.
Yeah, they're coming.
Don't worry.
You'll see them soon.
It's actually, it's going to be like really cool.
I did like a, you'll see.
I had a professional editor edit the photos.
We're professionally done.
I feel like I'm fucking around.
I'm watching this while taking a shit.
That's based.
You see, when I say it, you don't like it.
You think it sounds weird, right?
If somebody in your Discord call right now says it, you think that they're cool.
Do you understand how this works?
I'm too, I'm way older than you.
I got to save it.
No, that saying is just dumb.
Is it Scorpion?
Ooh, I'll get it.
You just got plus 10 social credit for that one.
Why do I save so much?
It just goes back to like the old days.
Oh, there is one.
Okay.
The old days of video games when you didn't save, you got screwed over.
That was terrifying.
Why?
Oh, that deserves a Monka W.
Is Monka W or Monka W?
W.
It's Monka W or W.
What do you guys prefer?
Oh, Monka W or Monka W.
Oh, oh, Monka W.
Which one?
First one?
I'd probably say the first one, you know?
All right, let me go to the highway.
This map is big.
There's fast travel.
Is there?
Well, I'm right here.
Yeah, there is.
Perfect world.
Oh, there is fast travel.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
I kind of like the...
I like driving around because I like to do the random things, though.
I don't want to get just used to this.
Hurry, please show the sunflowers.
Yeah, I'm going to show the sunflowers in exactly five minutes.
T minus five minutes for the showing of the sunflowers.
I'm going to go over the entire thing.
I'm going to tell you everything about it, the process,
internalizing everything and seeing how things play out.
All right, here we go.
Now, do designated matches.
Cool.
I just upgraded a bunch of shit, too.
Sunflower stream.
Let's go.
Yep, let's go.
Oh, this is a blue fight?
Yep.
All right, let's get back into this.
Everybody's having a good weekend.
How's your weekend going?
I didn't even ask you.
Good?
What's stalling?
I'm playing the game.
I'm not even stalling.
Your perception of me stalling is what's changed.
I didn't change anything.
I didn't do anything.
Oh, I thought I was a super bug.
I hate these guys.
They're the worst in the game.
Oh, I have these new moves.
Holy shit.
This makes this game so much more ridiculous.
Like, holy shit.
Those moves make this game...
I don't want to say easier, but I want to say maybe.
I'm watching a scary video at the same time as this.
Why?
I'm watching a scary video?
What was that?
You did pay attention here.
Here we go.
Do I remember all the No More Heroes 2 bosses?
I mean, you told me that if I could name all the No More Heroes 2 bosses
in the next five minutes without Google,
that you'd give me a million dollars.
I wouldn't be able to do it,
but I remember a couple of them, maybe.
The fake fan.
For a second, I thought something was wrong with this bench.
I thought it was pushed up.
I was like, what's wrong with this thing?
I thought it was one continuous piece of furniture.
This dude's zonked.
Shh.
Two minutes until sunflowers.
Yeah, we're getting there.
Name all 151 Pokemon.
Ars Art.
Squirtle.
Man Champ.
No Toad.
No, that's Futurama.
All right, I have to stop.
I got to pay attention.
These moves are so good.
I hate this dude.
How did I miss?
You know what's really hard to do?
Holding left trigger and then having to hit hold left bumper
to do the special moves.
I guess that's by design because you can't just do them.
Yeah, I get it.
Favorite enemy type so far?
I like the sword guys.
Like the ninjas.
Good dog.
I'm gonna get double killed right here.
Nice.
All right, that just saved me a shitload of time.
10 seconds until sunflowers.
Did they come?
Okay, so let's talk about the sunflowers.
I know for some of you this is a big deal.
For some of you, you don't care at all.
It's not gonna take very long.
Maybe like 10 minutes or so.
Let's get to a pause menu.
So a few months ago, I decided
that I wanted to...
Well, hold on.
I can't talk over the cut scene.
This is a Metal Gear joke.
Where is he?
It's me.
I'm here.
Where are you?
Oh, can't you see me?
That means it's not time just yet.
Does that mean exactly what I said?
You are not yet prepared.
Stop screwing around.
You harbor doubts, don't you?
With regard to me and yourself.
Myself.
Okay, that was awful.
I'm done, I'm done, I'm done.
That last one was fucking terrible.
That was like TikTok cringe compilation.
Levels of bad.
I'm done with this.
That's it.
We're moving past this one.
Your past.
Is it really yours?
What about your memories?
Your body?
Your mind?
Enough with the riddles.
I'll give you one more.
I'm me.
But am I really?
Once you begin to doubt, there is no end.
Aunt May?
That deserves a sip of coffee with me.
I just stabbed myself in the fucking mouth.
Ow.
With the straw.
I'm bleeding.
Fucking hold on.
Yeah, I just like stabbed myself right in the mouth with the straw.
Yeah, like underneath my lip.
Like where my teeth meet.
Matt, you know what I mean?
It looks like it's fine.
It's not that bad.
I just, I hit the straw and it hit my teeth
and the upper part of my kind of gum lip area.
They both connected and it pinched.
I'm never doing a snake impression ever again.
That's what caused this.
Okay.
But here we go.
Once you begin to doubt, there's no end.
But once the seed of doubt has been planted,
call an ambulance.
Oh no, I bit my tongue.
I didn't need an ambulance.
That seed takes root and begins to grow
and becomes as you are now.
What are you trying to say about me?
We'll meet again.
Soon.
To be continued.
Stop stalling.
I just had to get away from that
and I can take and pause the game.
Is this the doy doy doy guy?
You know what?
You know, I've been in other fucking TV shows.
I've had multi-million dollar television shows produced.
I've been in 10 different movies.
I won two Academy Awards,
but I'm the doy doy doy guy.
Yes.
Five years ago, I made a sound on stream.
You know how many other things I've done?
Hollywood Andy.
All right, let's do some flowers.
But you do it a lot.
Yeah, I do.
All right.
So the following.
Get excited.
Are you ready?
So a few months ago, the idea crossed the mind
to plant some sunflowers.
I actually learned a lot about gardening and planting.
It's something I've never really done before.
You don't just put things in a pot and just water them.
There's a lot of things that go into the first
like two or three weeks of growing flowers
that I just had no idea, especially sunflowers.
So the following images you will see on your screen
are that process.
And this is not just one picture.
This is multiple images over the course of the entire life.
So the first one you're going to see, which is pretty cool.
This is the pot.
And this is like right, maybe like, I don't know,
a week after planting.
And you're probably noticing there's a lot of little guys here.
He's grown his own weed.
No, no, not no.
When you grow sunflowers or any kind of big plant like this,
they sort of fight to get to choose
who gets to be the one that lives.
It's pretty sad in a way.
Because after you germinate them and you put them in the ground,
you have to thin them.
And you get to watch which ones are the strong ones.
And they're the ones that kind of get to stick around,
which it's sad because you'll end up with scenarios like this
where this one's coming up.
It's like, oh, he's so strong.
He's so big.
And look at him.
He looks perfect.
But the one next to him can't be there.
So even though the one next to him is growing and looking good,
he's going to have to go.
Because you have to, with sunflowers,
I believe it's at least six to eight inches apart
to have them have their roots be OK.
Yeah, it was a sad process of watching them all kind of do this.
And as you see, here they come.
And you see the ones on the right?
That's the seed.
That's the sunflower seed still on it.
It stays on.
And then eventually it falls off and they spread out.
And that's how they look like then.
So after a couple more weeks,
this is probably like maybe two and a half weeks, two weeks.
The ones that get the tallest forced Darwinism.
It's called thinning.
It's not full.
They look like in-game screenshots.
Well, they've been like they've been edited
to look a little nicer and to accentuate sort of the important stuff.
It's thinning.
No, you have to understand if you just they can't survive like this
and you don't know which is going to be a strong seed
because you don't know because when you put it in the case.
So some of them don't come up at all.
So when you plant 10 to 20 of them, five of them might not even come up.
So if you just plant one or two and they never show up,
you don't have a harvest.
You don't have a plant.
So you have to do it like this.
Otherwise, you don't know.
This is another image of it.
And at this point, it was hard to tell.
At this point here, it's like, all right.
So who's going to be the real the ones that are going to grow big and strong?
You can see some of them that look like they're a little bit hardier than others.
And this is after some of them have already been removed at this point.
If you can zoom in here, some of these have actually been removed already.
Down here, it was one or two that were removed
because they just weren't really coming up at all.
They were stuck.
They were kind of wilty.
Would we survive in your society?
This is basic gardening 101.
I am not like...
What are you talking about?
This is basic gardening.
Eventually, after they've been thinned a few times,
and some of them were stronger.
Some of them were strong enough, actually.
So as you see in the right pot, there are four.
The four were able to kind of stick around.
And also, notice the two over here.
These were taken out of the pot on the right
because they looked healthy enough.
And I just, I don't know, just felt bad.
I didn't want to just...
If they were strong, then I wanted them to survive.
So they got their own pot.
Actually, like three or four of these,
besides the one on screen, were repotted.
If I have to give you a real number of the seedlings,
maybe like three or four, maybe five total didn't make it.
The other ones were repotted and were given as gifts.
It was like, hey, here's like a kind of young sunflower.
Do you want it?
You can have it.
It's like watching your child go off to college in a weird way.
It's like, okay, here you go.
I've taken care of them for so long,
but make sure you give them plenty of water
and plenty of sunshine, make sure you aim them at the sun.
And make sure they eat every day.
It's like watching your kid go to school,
or like off to college or something.
But eventually, as you see the ones in the pot on the right,
they're about six to eight inches apart.
So they're good.
Very healthy, growing, strong.
This is where it gets interesting.
See what that is?
I'll zoom in on you.
A little praying mantis baby decided to sit up here and stay here.
And there's an interesting story about this praying mantis.
They never left.
And you'll see maybe a few images later.
Maybe you'll see this little friend again.
And the best part about the praying mantis
was this guy controlled a lot.
We're talking about like if they have this aphid problems, right?
It's really, really easy when you have this just guard dog
that's here constantly.
That was kind of an issue too.
He's trying to figure out like,
huh, I don't want to use pesticides.
So how do you naturally take care of the leaves?
I don't want aphids.
I don't want like the spider mites.
So having to come up with a solution of,
oh, you can like make your own like organic insecticide spray.
It's like light soap and peppermint.
And it actually, it works pretty well.
And yes, this praying mantis will be in the next German rumble.
That's a guarantee.
This is where they started to actually form leaves.
As you see, they look weird too.
It's an insane process.
Look at that.
Doesn't it look like she's going to open up
and just spit acid in my face?
And they were very healthy too.
They were very healthy.
They were very strong.
But the problem was it's really windy in Vegas
and these things grow these long stalks.
So do you know how many times there was like
15 plus mile per hour winds here?
And the panic that ensued of trying to make sure
they weren't going to get blown over.
There were storms.
There were big winds.
It was just like, shit, okay.
Just shimmy it behind like a wall.
When it got to this point, this is like,
I never thought I was ever going to be able to see this.
I thought I was going to screw something up.
There was so many opportunities to like break them
or damage them or weather problems.
I was like, holy shit, they're actually going to open.
And eventually another probably,
and this is probably about two months at this point,
maybe two and a half months.
Eventually they opened.
And this is what he looks like after opening.
So there you go.
There's your sunflower picture.
Big, beautiful, and ready for the bees.
Is it taller than you?
Yes, it was.
Especially the one on the back got to be about,
I want to say eight feet tall, seven feet tall.
I didn't stand next to it for scale
because I'm not going to do that.
I'm not going to give you guys that image.
Yeah.
Oh, there's more.
Don't worry.
You see the one behind?
So the one behind did not open immediately with the others.
Took about another two or three weeks.
He has his father's eyes.
But see, the green stakes were to prevent the wind.
He was really trying to stop the wind from just crushing him.
The one in the back actually at one point was a big windstorm.
And it bowed to a point where I gasped audibly and was like,
like I just watched like a animal that I had
or like a fucking kid like running out of the house,
like straight out of the house,
into the front yard and stuff and into the driveway.
Like, no, don't get back here.
It was horrible.
But he was okay.
Because remember, this is important to know too,
is you got to take care of these every day.
This wasn't just, oh, I just have like a plant back there.
Fuck it.
Don't even care.
They needed constant attention trimming some of the leaves.
You can see some of the browning, the yellowing.
You really don't want that to happen.
You want to try to keep them healthy.
They need water.
They need to be trimmed.
They need to be like fertilized.
It's an everyday thing was out there.
So if one of them had, if they got destroyed,
like two and a half straight months of doing this,
it would have been so sad.
So this is the other one.
This is the secondary one.
He was just barely opening.
And here's the cool part about it.
Sunflowers, if you didn't know,
they're not always yellow and orange.
Sometimes they can be, drum roll, please.
Drum roll, please.
I'm waiting for you.
Red, purple, brown, even like a dark,
almost like a dark brown.
Now this is a rare, you know what I mean?
You got the yellows are commons,
orange is a kind of uncommon.
Red is rare.
Purple is fucking legendary.
And there's white too.
Yeah, there is.
And the packets that I was using was an assortment.
So I did not know.
I had no idea what they were going to be.
So it really was like opening up flower loot boxes.
And when it's fully open, kind of went more orange.
It was red initially.
Take a look.
The bees loved these things.
There was constantly bees, honeybees going out there
and looking at three or four honeybees,
just collecting, picking up pollen and stuff.
It was awesome.
You kind of get to watch what happens around us in a way.
Don't worry, I'm not going to become like,
oh, philosopher in there, you know, humanity.
No, but listen.
When you get to just sit there and watch that,
a bee just coming over and just collecting pollen,
it's like this whole world is around us
of just constant moving and shaking
and like cars and trucks and airplanes and technology.
And if you slow down for a second,
this is ridiculous that this is still going on.
They collect this shit every day.
It looks like a stock photo.
Yeah, that's how good it is.
Thank you. I appreciate that.
Yeah, that's the one that was in the pot on the left.
So this one is...
Let me see if I can get it again.
No, no, no, no.
Where is it?
No, okay.
So the pot all the way to the left
is the one that you just saw, is the red one.
Now we're almost done.
Hey, come on.
This is like three and a half months in the making.
I can do this.
I can stall.
Take a look.
Look at how big our boy has gotten.
He's stuck around for the whole four months.
And then one day he just wasn't there.
When we see these things, it makes us a little sad.
It makes us cry.
You ate him.
I didn't eat him.
They grow up so fast.
So when they had to be...
When the sunflowers actually had to be...
Because they were done.
They were kind of dead or dying.
They had to be taken up.
Because here's a really sad thing about sunflowers.
If you didn't know, this is really important info.
Sunflowers, at least most of them,
there are some that are...
That they come back.
I believe perennial versus annual.
Sunflowers die and don't come back.
So it's not like, oh, yeah, I plant my sunflowers.
They grow ahead this year.
Cool, they bloomed.
See you next year.
Ooh, it's chilly out in December.
I'll take care of you.
No, they're dead.
They don't come back.
So watching them die and knowing that that was it
and you were just going to kind of trim them down and pull them.
It was like, okay, I mentioned having your kid go to college.
You know, think about what it's like to...
It's like, no, not only you're at college,
you got married and you're never coming back to mom ever again.
You got married and you have like four kids and you're gone.
Ah, it was sad.
Are you going to dry them and roast them?
They actually were harvested.
So I took the heads off, spread them out.
It's a really weird process when you do that too.
Actually harvesting a sunflower is not what you guys think.
If you've never seen, go look at a video.
Go watch like a sunflower harvesting video.
It's weird.
You decapitated them.
Yeah, I did.
Who's that?
Wait, is that Otto?
Oh, look at it.
It's Otto.
But yeah, this guy stuck around the whole time.
And then he went off somewhere else.
But it was cool to see the baby turn into the adult.
I believe there's what, one more?
Yeah, so here's the final picture I'm going to show you.
It was a hydra.
So the one in the back grew to be this five-headed hydra.
And this is about, I want to say, seven to eight feet tall.
And there were even more heads too.
There were two or three more heads that started that kind of stopped halfway.
Because sometimes this doesn't happen.
Getting a hydra, a lot of people will trim the heads
to make the big head, the head in the front in the middle, bigger and stronger.
I was like, no, fuck it.
Let's just see what it does.
It had like seven or eight heads.
But only four or five of them opened like this.
This is a legendary drop, yeah.
So I will tell you, that's the remainder of these.
We'll zoom in a little.
It was really cool.
It was actually cool.
It seems like a kind of a boring...
I mean, I guess when I turned 35, I never thought I'd be like,
I can't wait to take a look at my sunflowers.
But it is kind of cool.
It was a fun experience.
And I'm going to do it again.
We'll see what kind of legendary drops I get next time.
Or maybe not.
It's not boring.
Oh yeah, I don't really think it is.
But it's so sad now because they were outside.
So when I look outside to where they were,
it was always sort of a morning ritual to just look out there and be like,
ah, there are the...
Oh, they're gone.
They're absolutely gone, completely.
But I got seeds from their heads.
And those seeds, I'm going to preserve them.
And that's the seeds I'm going to plant next year.
So the family will live on.
Yeah, it was cool.
So we'll do one more.
It'll give you a little perspective here.
So here we go.
Here's the little babies.
There they are.
And they grew into this.
Plants are so weird.
The fact that a tiny little seed can just do this.
It's just crazy.
So if you want to know which one this one is,
this one, I believe, is this one here.
So this right here turned into this.
Stage one, final stage writer.
Absolutely insane.
It's to scale.
Yeah.
Did you name them?
No, not really.
There you go.
There's the sunflowers.
The sunflower journey is over.
Wasn't that worth waiting for?
The stream's not over.
That's imagine...
All right, see you later.
See you next week.
That was an accidental click.
You don't have to leave.
Okay.
Let's go back to it.
Back to No More Heroes.
End of the stream.
I got a couple more battles to do.
But yeah, it was cool.
I always wanted to do sunflowers.
And they get really big and healthy out here.
We had some community subs here.
We had five community subs from STXNE.
Ten from Leon.
Five community subs from TheFoolie.
And five community subs from Halulu.
Thank you, guys.
Thanks, Halulu.
Appreciate those five subs.
I'm talking about your flowers for ten minutes
added years onto my lifespan.
Well, if you got...
Yeah, it was cool.
Can you eat more than the seeds?
I think you can eat the heads.
Shut up.
I'm talking about my sunflowers, okay?
Sorry, I'm not killing people
with a fucking sword right now.
All right, relax.
Yeah, I think you can eat the heads.
I don't know if I would eat the actual heads.
Then you can grill them.
I love sunflower seeds.
They're delicious.
And you get a lot of them.
That was also surprising, too.
Because I wonder how many sunflower seeds
I get from one sunflower head.
It's like 50.
It's like 100.
LSFone, thanks for the ten community subs.
Appreciate it.
Snooze and Copter.
What's up with all the community subs?
Five community subs from Snooze and Copter.
Thanks.
Eating your children.
We're actually eating sunflower babies?
No.
I don't think that's accurate.
You're eating sunflower...
Thank you, Onymos, for the 20 community subs.
20.
That's a big number.
Thanks for the 20.
Say it.
I'm not going to say it.
You can figure it out.
What's going on right now?
Why is so many people giving subs?
MadStury gave 20.
MelScribbles5?
Oh my god.
I just showed sunflowers.
I don't...
You don't have to do this.
Thanks for the 10 subs potato chips, though.
Oh my goodness gracious.
I don't...
You guys just did this like a week and a half ago.
You don't have to do it again.
You guys just did this.
You know how many people subbed during the dollhouse stream?
We don't have to do this again.
I really mean it.
Trust me.
I can't even talk.
Another 10 came in 25.
Hold on.
Oh Jesus.
All right.
I'm just gonna...
You're funding the sunflowers.
Sunflowers are like a dollar.
It's like two bucks for a pack of like a thousand of them.
That's...
You're giving me like a 50 million percent premium.
So you don't have to do that.
Oh my god guys.
I can't even...
It's a sub storm.
It's for sun...
Cry cry cry.
I'm not gonna cry.
Thank you all of you.
It's...
It's unnecessary though.
You don't...
We don't have to do this.
Too much.
You're standing in the middle of the street.
Well I mean I've got some...
Hundreds of subs are coming in.
This is a new enemy.
He's gonna cry when he says he's not gonna cry.
I'm not gonna cry.
Thank you though guys.
Appreciate it.
Let's sing the song.
Thank you for the subs.
I'm just gonna play.
I'm gonna play.
This is...
This is fucking insane.
You just did this.
Like thousands of subs came in like a week and a half ago.
I don't expect this to ever happen.
Again.
And I don't...
It doesn't...
You don't have...
Thank you everybody.
I'm gonna play...
I'm gonna continue to play No More Heroes.
I really appreciate it.
I hope that you think it's worth the money you're paying.
I'll try to use your money the best way I can.
By buying snacks.
And by purchasing equipment.
For...
Oh I'm gonna...
Well you know I'm gonna get equipment for the stream.
All right what does this guy do?
What does this guy do?
He's cracking.
You guys are cracking me.
I'm getting cracked.
These guys are full on attackers.
Guard yourself.
Watch out for an opening.
Check your remaining power.
Sunflower equipment.
I'm gonna buy stream equipment.
Like what the fuck?
What a lie.
That's not...
I'm not gonna buy streaming equipment.
What does that even mean?
This is a boss.
I love this game by the way.
I like gardening equipment.
Throw crazy.
I can't grab the boss?
Why does he keep saying double kill?
I'm not killing anybody.
All right let's go kick this guy's ass.
And whoop.
All right.
Death meld shower.
I cannot hit him.
Do I have to do a perfect dodge to hurt him?
Oh my god.
What the fuck's going on?
Do I have to guard?
They got the perfect dodging.
All right dodge.
What the fuck?
What do I have to do?
I guess he just did perfect dodging.
Jesus.
No I can hit him now.
What?
That was weird.
Why couldn't I do it before?
I'm just swinging at nothing.
What are you gonna do?
Harvest moon stream?
Tomorrow.
Just kidding.
Whoa.
He's got weirdly timed moves.
Jesus.
This guy's fucking hard.
He has like 15 different moves.
All right this is my least favorite guy so far.
I don't think I can dodge that.
All right there we go.
That's how you just double it up.
He's boring.
He's not boring so you can't beat him.
I had like an S going that whole time too and now it's gonna be a C.
You've said this is my least favorite guy so far to everybody.
No I haven't.
I've said it to two different enemies.
What are you talking about?
This title is so annoying.
I'm probably saying annoying people that scroll by.
Okay one more of those.
There's one right next to me.
Why are you so self-conscious?
I mean think about it.
Okay just think about pull yourself out.
Think about it with a different perspective.
If you were scrolling down Twitch right now and you saw the stream and the title was
Hello there haha like how it's funny like all capitals.
Get out get out of here.
You'd be like I'm not clicking on that stream.
That guy's like a dork.
Don't talk about my favorite streamer like that.
This is great so if I really like this game a lot.
It's very I'm having a good time.
All right count how many times I say this is my least favorite enemy.
But also count how many times I said I like this game a lot.
There's so many of these guys.
Holy shit.
I gotta fight them inside of this thing.
Mustang mode.
Oh my god give me an S plus.
Come on S plus.
S plus I can get it by doing this.
This is how you get the S plus.
Only one guy left.
Come on.
It's been like not even two minutes.
That has to be S.
I didn't get the 100 combo.
I know it sucks.
I'm good though.
We're fine.
One minute and 10 seconds.
There we go.
Probably isn't an S plus.
I took too much damage.
Yeah probably.
Fuck there is actually an SS.
Oh how much money do I need for the tournament?
30,000 coins what do I have?
How many coins do I have?
I sound sad.
We just did the sunflower thing and I'm like sad about it.
Okay I was putting it off for so long.
These cars are driving backwards by the way.
Imagine if there was a star system in the game.
I feel like is there another job I can do?
I don't know if this is going to be enough money.
Travis touchdown.
Hit and run.
I pressed A.
I tried to get it.
This one's silver.
Silver scorpion.
It seems super hard.
Okay where is this fight?
Hello?
In the water?
Where is this fight?
Am I losing my mind?
Has to be like over here then.
Behind the back fence is it?
Whose fence?
Who has a back fence to go over?
Skate three.
This is not skate three.
Where is this thing?
Oh my god.
Okay well come on.
I'm standing right in front of it off the motorcycle.
Whatever.
Pretending to be bad at video games.
That's it.
I'm leaving.
Stay.
Don't go.
Are you going to play the skate?
New skate game coming out?
No.
Here we go.
I swore off all skate games forever.
All of them.
Forever.
He actually hit me.
Get.
Come on.
Get that shit out of here.
Really?
I grabbed his ass.
Here comes another C.
I'm going to die.
This might be the first D the whole time I played.
D Andy.
That's me.
I'm going to C Andy.
Don't fucking talk shit.
Tried to dodge.
Tried to dodge but I pressed every button on the Switch Joy-Con controller.
Because it's a piece of shit.
Okay.
Hold on.
Slow down.
Don't get angry at this.
I love this game.
All right.
Come on.
That's going to be an A.
Oh no.
He's starting to pretend convince himself to not get mad.
Don't get mad.
I'm going to get mad.
He never does jump attacks.
No.
You already don't.
I don't know why.
I feel like it just puts me in C Andy.
Candy?
Whatever.
All right.
I have enough money.
I want to do some more things though.
C Andy.
It's not C Andy.
Whatever.
It's fine.
Let me look at the map.
All right.
There's a toilet.
The sushi shop.
ATM.
T-shirt alien.
Defense mission.
Nothing really even over here.
Let's pay the ATM.
Let's go to the T-shirt alien.
If I can get this.
Is there another mission for the Molon?
Is this like a level two?
Oh, level two.
Let's go.
There are rocks in the way now.
Okay.
Three minutes.
Just keep that up.
I missed a little piece but it's fine.
I'm trying to turn the damn thing.
What's North America's most well-known dam?
Hoover Dam.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey.
Don't hit me.
What's the tallest building in North America?
Empire Strikes Back.
I don't know.
The Sears Tower.
It was.
It was the Sears Tower for a while.
What is it now?
When are you going to stream Doki Doki Literature Club?
Never.
Ever.
I promise you'll never see that on this channel.
I got crystals.
Nice.
Do I even have enough money?
I don't even have enough money.
30,000.
Good.
You would suck at it.
Well, good.
You don't have to worry about watching me play it.
I've definitely done.
Oh, I like that.
I can get it.
Cool.
All right.
I actually really like that shirt.
Remember, don't read the hate comments.
What hate comments?
All right.
We're going to make some money.
Let's travel here.
I know.
Fast traveling.
Right.
I know.
Right, right, right, right.
I feel like I've already done everything over here
and why would I drive by anyway?
Remember, you only have four months left
for two Catboy streams.
What do you mean two?
Catboy's already made their appearance.
What are you talking about?
Here's the scorpions.
I got shredded snake skin and a chicken feather.
Oh, now I got enough money.
Nice.
I was supposed to be two in a row.
Do you guys remember?
Some of you guys that have been here
for more than four or five years plus.
Some of you guys will remember that.
Didn't I ask a long time ago
to have somebody compile every lie I've ever said?
And it was a funny little joke,
but somebody in the chat made a really good point.
They were like, dude, that video would take forever to make.
It'd be like four or five hours long of edited clips.
I'm like, holy shit, is it really that much?
They're like, yeah, dude,
you say weird fucking lies every other stream.
I'm like, no, but not that much.
A litter box.
Yeah, well, did I do this one?
Level two volunteer mission, let's go.
Accelerate.
Boost.
It goes two streams in a row.
Oh, right, I can't hit the other cars.
Forgot.
Well, it's hard to do that
when they're directly in the way
and I take up almost the whole road.
The only thing I've hit this whole time
has been a pedestrian car.
It's the only thing I've hit the whole time.
Get it.
God, it's because I have to hit them
with the edges of the car, right?
I don't have a minute to do this.
I'm not going to do it.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Just forget about it.
I have to just win.
Can you get an F?
I guess F is actually not completing it.
Is there actually a D or C the lowest you can get?
I'm just looking at chat.
Name the Mantis Cromwell.
It's not a bad name.
Get over here.
All right.
I'm going to be really honest with you.
This minigame is as good
as the game that's in the ad for the iPad game.
That's how good this is.
Like the ad you get for the game
for the iPad game that they're advertising you.
The ad game.
That's what is it.
It's that same quality.
A lot of you don't get it.
All right.
So you know when you're when you get an ad
for an iPad game
and they say drive on the road
then you just put your finger
and you have to actually do it to.
It's not the actual game.
It's the it's an ad game for the actual game.
I don't get ads.
What?
You're just a hater.
Mobile gamer.
Well, but never mind.
Is there another one already?
Level three.
Oh God.
I hate this.
I don't want to do level three.
But I'm going to I'm just going to get out of the way.
All about speed.
That's all I care about right now.
I'm collecting these like punchy.
That's all I care about.
Let's start.
Good start.
This might be a.
All right.
Wait for the cool down.
No pedestrians hit.
I'm just waiting to accidentally touch the screen
so the app store open.
No.
All right.
One more.
Come on.
Still in this territory.
Oh, please don't hit yellow.
So close.
So got it.
He's giving me motion sickness.
Me too.
I'm just trying to get him out of the way.
All right.
I'll take a gold.
Holy shit.
Death drive MK1.
I got a car.
Nice.
All right.
I got enough money with the ATM.
This is rank kind of rank six.
Rank seven.
I don't know.
I'm just playing.
Go to the video store first.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The hell's a video store.
Sushi.
Beef head.
Where is it?
Trash collection.
Oh, I do trash collection.
Where is it?
Is it beef head?
Where's that?
What's the video store called?
Video store is near parliament.
I'm sorry.
I didn't understand.
You didn't stand up slowly.
And arch your back and put your chin in the air.
So I don't understand what you just said.
Yeah, this is it.
This guy's high as fuck.
No, he's not.
Death man is just too damn cool.
Here's your cut.
Final doll.
I had more than one, didn't I?
Hey, what's up?
Check car.
Oh, sell junk?
That's 10 grand.
Wait, but isn't this?
I don't know.
These are materials.
I don't want to sell these.
This is not junk.
No, no, no, no.
I don't want that.
Cool.
Do not sell.
Hold them.
Yeah, I'm not selling.
I have the things I put in my watch.
I'll just take the money.
Ever been to Boston before?
Never.
I heard it's a pretty cool place.
I live in Vegas, so I don't know.
I heard it's pretty cool, though.
I heard it's a nice place.
Have fun when you go.
On the other side, isn't it?
Of course it is.
You should go to Boston.
They have pizza.
Yeah, they do.
I heard it's really good.
I heard that if you don't have it for a while,
you really start to miss it.
That's steep, man.
And you wish you could have it.
You can't.
On what I understand, what I've been told,
nothing comes close where you currently are.
Nothing comes close.
Prince, you hate me, don't you?
I don't hate you.
I just don't like you is all.
That counts as being in the hate category.
But what would you know, huh?
You making fun of me?
I'm just being honest.
Listen, value those who tell you the truth.
Nobody speaks their mind in front of the prince.
What?
The people always say nice, happy things to you.
But they're either talking shit behind your back
or they're knocking on you to the king.
Definitely.
One hundred percent.
Is this true?
If you don't believe me, set up some cameras or something.
This shit is not okay.
I'm going to execute them all.
Hey, now, calm down, Prince.
That's textbook spoiled rich kid talk.
Let it go.
Bernie Sanders?
Or give your enemies and make them your friends.
Oh, it's not.
That's how a real leader does it.
Vanishing point.
Will you keep being honest with me?
Prince, I couldn't bullshit you even if I wanted.
No, that's like vendor in Gadgetzan.
With me, too.
Come on.
I love that voice, though.
That like, hey, come on.
What do you got?
This game for you.
The hell is it?
Jimmy Love?
It's for Kimmy's concert.
It's an invitation to the VIP seats.
Oh, shit.
It's huge.
Do you know her or something?
Who the hell is that?
Recently, they say she's even bigger than Taylor.
Yeah, she's famous.
I got that.
This already sounds hella sketchy.
Why are they doing this?
Listen, just play along.
Accept the invitation.
Otherwise, you'll regret it for the rest of your life.
Beast, this culture is some serious shit.
If it's serious shit, more reason to say screw it.
It's like a weird thing to have.
The next prince assassin is Vanishing Point.
An alien criminal who steals memories.
This should turn out to be a real battle of the minds.
Hey, call before you show up.
What?
Is there something you do not want me to see?
Is this also part of the review?
Yeah.
Subscribe to your channel, you know.
The recipe stuff you do is awesome.
For tips all the time.
I feel like this was just pulled transcript
right from whatever review they're parodying.
It really should be me doing it, but...
Diversity.
But diversity is something people say at times like this, right?
Are you acting as an agent for the ranking battles?
Prince Fu has formed a business alliance with the UAA.
So as the head organizer,
I can move around freely.
They say to keep your enemies close, right?
They're talking about real movies.
It's not the...
I thought the reviews were real too.
Appreciate everything.
For reals, I mean it.
Okay, whatever.
Accept this invitation and go to the concert.
Vanishing Point will be there.
Anyway, I'm kind of in a hurry.
Wait, we're not done talking.
Okay, email me then.
Don't you want a beer?
Hold up.
Not real reviews.
I don't know why someone said that.
Did I get one guide?
Because yesterday people said there was real reviews.
It was more than one guy.
It was a lot of guys that said that.
All right, 20.
I have to get 20.
I refuse to leave if I don't get at least 20.
You were tricked.
Accounts.
Double the debt if you don't get the 20.
No, we're not doing that.
Once you get to 12, 15, 16, it becomes impossible.
I gotta treat this like I treat Stacker in the arcade.
It's just on the first go through, right?
Immediately.
Don't give it a chance to fuck with you.
Just the first pass.
Hey, that's the Stacker strategy to how you get the major prize every time.
Don't even let it do it.
Don't let it go over because then it gets in your head.
Just the first movement it does.
Okay, well it baited me a little bit and they got my Stacker strategy they heard about.
What's up, huh?
Stacker is rigged.
I know it is.
But if it goes past it on the first pass, you gotta do it.
All right, now that strategy is out of the way.
Shit.
This is so hard.
I have to get 20 or I'm not getting up from this.
I promise.
I swear to God.
What's the matter?
Steady your hand.
I'm not doing that.
All right, it's all right.
I'll get 20.
Where are you sleeping?
This is boring.
All right, like Chattered 500 whatever.
20.
Don't yikes me right now.
Okay, I'm restarting that because somebody yikes me.
20.
I've hit 17.
I can hit 20.
Don't be an idiot.
Just be smart about it.
Don't blame chat.
I am.
The debt will be cleared if you watch Cromwell on stream.
Well, that would be illegal.
So no, I would rather have fake debt to a chat room of friends and family members.
I'm not a you afraid.
No, just wait.
Hold on.
I'm a family.
I just fucked myself over here.
I just I just fucked everything up here.
I just created a huge problem right here.
Do you understand how much of a problem I just caused myself right now?
Just a single little offhanded comment just created a huge amount of problems.
Okay, so listen.
What was I saying?
Okay, having a debt on my channel is a joke.
Is not as good as having debt with lawyers and actually getting into real debt because
I get sued from like fucking Paramount Pictures for watching a licensed TV movie on my stream.
That's illegal.
Too late.
We're family now.
The debt isn't a joke.
Okay, but you understand like you and I as acquaintances as online entertainment acquaintances.
I'm not a look.
Listen to me.
Listen, I'm going to give it to you real.
I can't call everybody my friend.
I don't know.
I don't know how half of you guys.
No, that implies I know half of you guys.
I don't fucking know any of you guys.
I don't know anybody here.
I know like I don't think eight of you.
Paralegal, parasocial.
No, listen.
I just fucked it up and I'm into like a 20.
I'm not I'm not leaving until I get 20.
He hates us.
No, paralegal, paralegal, parasocial.
Come on.
What's the matter?
How does Mike know?
All right.
What's up, huh?
All right, we're good.
Yeah, I thought we were family.
This is my favorite one of these comments.
I thought we had something.
I know not hold on.
I got to read it.
I make sure I get it right because it's funny.
What's up, huh?
I thought we had something.
I can understand the other people but me.
I like that.
That's funny.
What's up?
Family is everything.
Where's my Christmas present?
Family member.
You don't turn your back on family.
Paranormal relationship.
I invited you to my birthday party.
What's the matter?
You see how hard this gets after 10.
20 is insane.
All right, we're on a good pace here.
I got three lives.
What's up, huh?
Yeah.
Nice.
Just use the stacker technique.
It works every time.
I had it but I second guessed myself in the last quarter of a second.
All right, come on.
What's up, huh?
20, let's go.
Is that in there?
What's the matter?
Ah.
Where are you?
What's up, huh?
Come on.
That's fucking with me.
Bring it.
Shit.
One more try.
What's up, huh?
All right.
I'm 35.
Don't...
What am I acting like that for?
Shit.
Stomping my feet.
What am I?
12.
Let's go.
Come on.
Last try is pretty good.
What's up, huh?
Isn't your birthday Hobbit Day?
I want that person banned permanently.
Permanently.
And then I want them unbanned.
And then I want them timed out for 10 seconds.
That's an old joke.
Minus two.
But it's a good one.
All right.
Back up to 10.
This is my last try.
If I don't get to 20 then whatever.
I get a game to play.
Come on.
That's such a bullshit.
What's the matter?
Where are you aiming?
Come on.
Bring it.
That's in.
Yeah.
What's up, huh?
I'm gonna be quiet.
It's in.
That's in.
Shit.
I thought it was gonna move really fast.
What's the matter?
Holy fuck.
This is impossible.
Actually impossible.
You just didn't get lucky.
All right.
This is my last attempt.
I swear.
What's up?
I'm not talking at all until I get it.
I just have to lean in.
Just stare and not say any words and just focus.
Yeah.
Come on.
Bring it.
Yeah.
What's up, huh?
Meow.
I added a game designed for cats.
All right.
Here we go.
Meow.
Where are you aiming?
Come on.
What's the matter?
It's in.
Right on the edge.
That's in.
Right in the corner.
Paint to the corners.
Get the fuck in there.
Two more.
I thought it was gonna go right across immediately.
All right.
Come on.
18's enough.
It rounds up to 20.
What's the matter?
You stupid game.
You dumb game.
One more.
No.
Fuck.
What's up, huh?
Come on.
I'm just getting so goddamn mad.
I'm just like gonna start punching my fucking desk.
Punch the desk.
I'm so sick of this.
Acting.
I just joined the stream.
Hey, what's going on?
How are you?
Good to see you.
That was Tommy Wiseau.
Paranormal streamer pretends for likes.
This is a pretty good run so far.
I haven't missed.
Bingo.
We're at 14.
Three lives.
Let's go.
This is the one.
That's in.
All right.
We're fine.
Ah.
That's it.
Done.
I win.
Good game.
20.
That's impossible.
That's literally not completable.
I'm done.
That's not possible to get that.
Look at how small that is.
What's up, huh?
I got to 20.
That's what I wanted.
That not worth anything?
Really?
Get a 50 high score to clear the debt.
That's not possible, man.
Sorry.
25 is a t-shirt.
You just decided that 20 was an arbitrary number.
But doesn't 20 sound like a number?
First of all, 10 sounds like a number to get something.
20 sounds like a number to get something cool.
And then something like crazy like 50 is just,
oh, you get the achievement and you get like a t-shirt or something, right?
The prize is at 51.
All right.
What am I upgrading here?
I got a lot of money.
What should it be?
I'm thinking attack power.
Definitely attack power.
I got 79.
Did I get the charge?
I feel like I wouldn't use this this much, though.
I would use the double dodge.
More battery, yeah.
Do I have enough?
Yeah, I could do another attack.
Yeah, I want another attack.
2,000 left.
Is that enough for 36?
Yeah, I can do health.
Cool.
All right, good.
I don't think I got any new chips that I want to put in.
We'll see.
Is this new?
Oh, this one's new.
Death force attack power 10% higher.
Death slow duration 10% up.
I like that.
That's my favorite one, I think.
Out of the kick.
When health is at 20% or lower, weapon attack is...
This is worded weirdly from my brain.
When health is at 20% or below, weapon attack power 15% up.
Okay, now I already have one of these.
During slow down after a perfect dodge.
That's good, but not enough.
I would want it to be like 30%.
I'd get three of those.
Oh, I think I'm good for the chips right now.
It's like tanky.
Okay, I think that's fine.
I think the ones I have are good.
I do want health.
Definitely always have this maxed out.
It's just estuses essentially at this point.
I have not even used this.
I can look at my menu, my quick menu, right?
Because I haven't even used any of those.
Special move, okay.
This is my sushi.
How can I tell...
Can I see like of the menu?
No, is there a way I can tell...
What's mapped to what?
I don't know what's mapped to what.
You can only see it in battle.
Oh well, okay.
Well, I got what I wanted.
I might actually eat one of the actual eat-in ones.
You know what I mean?
For this fight.
How's everybody doing?
Master, master.
It's me.
I'm right here.
Genoba, wake up.
I'll teach you a super special suplex.
Hurry up and wake up.
Let's get training.
My favorite suplex is...
It's got to be the one that Maeda used
to take down Ordolf with a reverse arm assault.
When he made his triumphant return from Europe as
Quick Kick Lee.
Fleeting beauty of that bridge in Parabola.
Genoba, remember how that moment felt.
Paris Parabola relationship.
Parasocial, whatever.
Oh, it's Gene.
Gene?
Not interested.
Not interested, what?
Try it again.
Gene?
No, doesn't care.
Okay.
All right, time for rank battle.
Versus the memory guy.
Stop having a parasocial relationship with your cat.
All right, I'm going to get sushi.
True.
What do you mean true?
Okay, sushi time.
Should I do that first?
Will that last all through to my next battle or something?
Or should I buy it right before the boss door?
I would assume right before the boss door, right?
Yeah, I'll just buy it there.
Perfect world.
Is he finally playing the game?
Yeah, I mean, I've been just kind of grinding money.
You practice that off stream for at least 20 minutes.
Nope, not even one second.
Or maybe a few seconds.
Maybe like two seconds.
That did sound very practiced and rehearsed, didn't it?
But I didn't, I can assure you.
This is weird.
All right, I'm buying one of the Eden ones.
They're expensive, but I'm going to do it.
This one's really expensive.
Okay, if you die, you come back to life.
That's a lot of money though.
Greatly increased health and attack power.
Okay, this is just a chef's choice, who knows?
Maybe he's more easily stunned.
I'll just go with this one.
Yeah.
Enter into battle with a greatly increased health and attack power.
It's very expensive, but I'm going to do it.
I think it's worth it.
Can you say your stream title out loud so I know what it means?
Sure.
It's hey there.
It's the seal video of the seal talking.
And that really cleared it up.
Thanks.
Anytime.
Okay, it's time for a fight.
Action.
Wait, what?
Whoa.
Oh, shit.
It happened again?
One back to back?
Aren't all these guys supposed to be Thanos level threats?
What is he doing up here?
This is the high school girl from the second game.
Is it?
Oh, do I have to go?
We need a voice crack.
I need a voice crack right now.
Please, please suit him.
He did.
This is so, this is so, this is all, this is insane.
This time we fight to the death.
Yeah, bitch.
Fuckhead.
Wait, what?
What?
This is so stupid.
This is insane.
That was, I don't even know, I can't even process what just happened.
He actually had a voice crack.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
Where?
Oh, they explode.
Okay.
Taffy, quick.
He just snapped my neck.
Oh, I'm fine, I'm fine.
Everything's good.
God, I need to do some dodging, man.
I'm not dodging anything.
All right, let's go.
Nice and easy.
Get in here.
Oh.
Oh, mustang pod, it's over.
Oh, my God.
Holy shit.
I don't even know what's happening.
I'm still swinging.
She's in a cut scene.
What?
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
I'm dying down here.
Holy shit.
Do I guard?
Can I block it?
No, I can't block it.
Is she back?
Ow.
This view is insane.
No, not this shit again.
Hey.
Get out of here.
Got it.
Game over.
Is she dead?
She's over here.
See you later.
That was crazy.
That was fucking crazy.
Yeah, and it was diamond cutter.
Let's just goodbye.
Damn.
Oh, my goodness gracious.
I'm so overstimulated right now.
First of all, they pulled the
it's not this boss, it's this other guy.
At this point, I'm assuming that
all the people in Fu's party
are just dudes they found at the subway
that are in fucking Halloween costumes.
No, they haven't done anything.
All right, that's B.
I'll take a B.
Oh, I got a CD.
Congratulations.
That was the most wild one yet.
You were recognized as number seven
in the galactic rankings.
And just look at this kid.
I guess she just could not grow up after all.
This is the last time I kill a woman.
Well, how kind of you.
Don't ever hit a girl.
My grandma used to tell me that.
What are you?
A good Samaritan now?
How far do you think that kind of
posing will get you?
Kimi wasn't supposed to be a
They're just cheering.
Aren't they fans?
I'm only after those fucking alien assholes.
I never signed up for this.
The strong survive.
That is how the world of killing works.
You have not forgotten, have you?
Did you think you were going to become friends
and team up to defeat the big, mean aliens?
This is not a superhero.
They have glow sticks.
It is not that simple.
Why don't you ask your katana there?
Just how much blood it has sucked so far.
It is still too early.
Stay at the ready, though.
If I have to rank the Star Wars movies,
this is definitely number one.
Without a doubt.
No More Heroes 3 is by far the best one.
The one thing that I miss,
and this is why you play the second game,
I really, really liked the 8-bit
sort of old Nintendo-esque minigames for money.
Those are really cool
and just kind of funny and interesting.
And they're really easy to play over and over again.
It's the one thing that I really liked
in the second game.
The first game was sort of...
I don't think...
I mean, maybe they did.
I don't know.
I don't know if he thought
this was something that he was going to do later.
The first game felt like a complete package.
Just, oh, it's a Suda 51 game.
It's No More Heroes.
This is it.
Cool.
It was a fun experience and I made it.
But No More Heroes 2 and 3
and then having all these other things in the franchise.
No More Heroes 1 is this almost enclosed in its own place.
Did the game just end?
No.
Those of you that were just catching the stream now, no.
It's like a fake anime.
Intros and outros.
This is by far the most fun.
And fun doesn't mean actually playing
the physical video game either, right?
A lot of times.
Fun is just the whole package sometimes.
Like watching the cutscenes and...
The color is green.
The boss fights that aren't really boss fights,
they're kind of just there to be fun and interesting.
It's not about just swinging the sword at people.
It's the most fun Star Wars movie.
So what rank...
What was it?
Rank 6?
Time for a pee break.
Actually, that's a great idea.
After this next cutscene,
we'll take a quick break.
Where's Damon?
He said he would be out on his monthly glamping trip today.
Oh, that guy is such a hassle.
What's up with Velvet Chair Girl?
She called in saying she could not make it
due to an appointment at the nail salon.
I see.
So she couldn't make it, huh?
Was it really such an important appointment?
It is for her nails, so...
Okay, I'll let this one slide.
Seriously, women are the biggest hassle of them all.
Both humans and aliens are a hassle.
You got something you want to say?
No.
My apologies for...
Oh, here it goes.
The intro.
Don't ever skip the intro.
How many times have you ever skipped an intro accidentally?
And you get pissed?
Or you're too lazy to go back and watch it,
but you're really just sort of secretly incredibly annoyed?
How do you accidentally do that?
Um, I don't know.
Sometimes you just press the button.
Sometimes, like, if you have, like, a touch screen,
or if you have, like, an Apple TV or something,
or you have, like, a remote.
No, I don't think so.
You're just hella wrong.
You accidentally press left on your console controller,
if you're doing it on, like, PS4 or PS5.
Bullshit.
Mieke never read the original.
The script is what's most important.
The script is what the entire art form is based on.
You can't make a movie without knowing the material.
Don't underestimate Mieke's love for the originals.
So...
So any old hardcore maniac can make a movie, then?
All you need to do is love the originals, right?
What about Terraformers, then, huh?
Terraformers is...
You want to watch it again?
Terraformers?
Let's do it.
Terraformers.
Oh, we got a new t-shirt.
Oh, wait.
Important.
Cat.
Cat, check wardrobe and then pee.
I gotta go on a diet.
No, I'm not throwing the ball again.
Okay.
Uh, this is with this hoodie on.
I just want to see what the shirts look like.
Can I get new shirts?
Where is it?
Taku freak.
Flame tea.
Ooh.
Oh, there it is.
I like that one a lot.
I really like this, though.
I actually really like this.
All right.
I'm gonna wear this till I get some more clothes.
Yeah, I like it.
You did no progress and you saved.
I know. I just do it because I sometimes do.
I just like it's like a nervous habit in a way.
Just like, okay, save, press button.
Okay, good.
All right, I'm right back.
Time to go pee.
See you guys in like a minute or two.
Okay, I'm back.
I just was laughing in the bathroom.
Just keep thinking of death.
This is the insanity of that last fight.
It was all over the place.
I couldn't even process.
I just went into full on...
I went into full-blown panic mode.
Okay.
I gotta get out of here.
So we are rank seven.
So the next fight is six.
Very, very cool.
Okay.
We have Germaplexis back?
I don't remember what Germaplexis is.
Are we gonna get a cut scene here?
I will shush up.
Get on the highway, head to Call of Battle.
Look at my mail.
Rank six is 35,000 coins.
Ocean's 51.
All right, let's head to the...
This is a new zone, I think, right?
Call of Battle?
What are you drinking?
It's nice coffee.
Ice?
Coffee.
He's still bleeding?
No.
You get a cut in your mouth.
It's weird how it bleeds really badly for five to ten seconds.
And then it's just immediately sealed.
It's really weird.
It's just like, oh my god, I can taste blood.
I'm bleeding.
Gone.
Not anymore.
Healed.
Why is the mouth so...
Mouth heals super fast.
Yeah, but why?
What makes the mouth so different versus getting a cut on your finger?
Iron?
This is ugly.
Holy shit.
I just want to get to my destination quickly.
Five figures.
It's because it's saliva.
Rapid cell replication.
Damn, this is an ugly zone.
He's giving me double middle finger?
What was that?
Okay.
Designated matches.
This place is ugly.
I feel like I'm looking at this with 3D glasses.
To a movie or a thing that is not supposed to be 3D.
It looks like Gears of War 1.
You know, I've never played any of the Gears of War games.
That might freak a lot of people out.
I've never played Gears of War for even 15 seconds.
All right, let's go.
Strawberry.
Right on.
We played 14 seconds.
I don't know.
I don't know what that is.
The answer is probably no.
I was looking at a double killer right here.
Hit them both.
Yeah!
Real crazy.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry.
Ow!
All right!
Whatever.
Oh my god, this is the worst enemy in the game for me.
It's the worst enemy in the game for me.
I hate this enemy.
This sucks.
What the fuck?
You do all your moves, take up the whole screen.
Don't!
Oh, sorry!
Where'd you go, where'd you go, where'd you go?
All right, destroy the eggs.
Just, I'm gonna beat the eggs up.
Fuck you.
What was the Peter Griffin thing?
Oh, it's me, Peter Griffin.
I'm playing the Sims.
I remember that was so embarrassing.
Fuck out of here.
I'm gonna push you out of the fucking zone.
Cute shit out of here.
Oh, that enemy is the...
I'm not gonna do the fucking, like, you slow down 0.25x on YouTube joke.
Again, you heard it before.
See.
When has that ever stopped you before?
Yeah, you're right.
Somebody said it was literally Gears of War's fault for all the cover shooter bullshit
that swept the whole industry.
I never really played it, so.
But yeah, I do remember pressing right bumper against any surface.
It was a really big deal for a long time.
Hey.
Oh, this stuff over here.
What is it?
Oh, it's sushi.
Chest high walls everywhere.
That's right.
Oh, it looks sushi.
This is your moderator is clearing up chat.
Thousand bucks for that.
I'm almost halfway there.
It's because I made a lot of money last time.
I didn't spend it.
What?
Vlog it up again.
He says berries because it's a reference to an in-universe magical girl anime
where all the girls are named after berries.
Really?
Refill these.
I still have not used any of the other ones.
Raw berry on the shortcake.
A tank mission?
All right.
How do you know what that is?
How do I get in here?
Yeah, I know he was...
I know he says it in the first two games, but I never kind of knew why.
I had a feeling it was something anime related, but I didn't really know.
Get ready.
All right.
And height.
Bye.
And hello.
Hello.
And let's go.
Those things shouldn't be able to explode at regular speed inside my vault.
I must find that partly infuriating.
Come on, do a move then.
Your buddy's not there, you're dead.
Know what?
Berry bush, berry bush.
Go crazy.
I actually hate these enemies.
I hate these stupid balls.
They're annoying.
One more time.
I'm just getting started.
What was that?
Your next lot effect will always be Mustang mode.
Really?
Holy shit.
This is...
I'm going to clear this in a second.
Here we go.
Give me a thing so I can slide.
You're so annoying.
Give me this lot.
And...
Go!
Okay, 88 hit combo.
That's got to be worth at least an A.
That was less than a minute.
I took a lot of damage, but whatever.
This shit again.
Where is he?
Where are you?
Huh?
Across the road.
Can't really see you.
Is that so?
But you're becoming able to see me more than before, yes?
I heard I can ask for anything I want.
Of course.
As long as you pay the appropriate price.
Even murder?
I don't dabble in such vulgarity.
However, I am able to perform actions that would result in death.
Is there really a difference?
Of course there's a difference.
Can you kill anyone?
That's what you wish.
Problem lies in why exactly you want the person in question dead.
Why?
Do you need a reason?
Yes.
It's part of the price you must pay.
Think about that first.
Money comes after that.
The reason I want them dead is...
Hello?
Are you there?
The line's dead.
Oh, never mind.
I can't hear you.
You're still not fully prepared.
I'd speak again later.
Dabble continued.
Are you actually gonna finish you, Kriza?
I sort of laughed at that.
I'm sorry I just laughed like in your face.
But I did not expect to answer that question today.
I should not have laughed at that.
That's not what my intention was.
That was a laugh out of nervousness.
That was really rude, it was.
Alligators taking over the beach.
I'd like to test out your fortitude.
Please go enlist with the Coast Guard.
Coast Guard?
Help to quell the mass panic.
Fight off the alligators riding in on tanks.
Okay.
What?
Targeted and firing.
It also reminds me of...
It reminds me of the VR shit that you can play in the mall.
Like it sucks absolute asshole.
And it's like not good.
It feels like it's from VR tech from like 15 years ago.
Like an Oculus Quest is better.
Right?
Am I almost out of time?
I don't understand.
How am I gonna have to kill?
Oh, it's the tutorial.
Yeah!
Mall VR is what made me buy an Oculus Quest.
That's true because it's really like...
It's a watered down version of what you can actually do in VR.
So it just maybe gets you interested.
What's wrong with the quest?
There's nothing wrong with the quest.
I'm just saying like it...
Like the quest is better than the huge gigantic system that's in the mall.
Some of them might even be on quests now.
Lots is wrong with the quest.
I've never used it.
All right, let's do this now.
Targeted and firing.
Focus.
I gotta have an efficient way to do this.
I missed?
What?
Wow.
Stay right in the middle.
That's a hit.
This is actually scary.
I've had nightmares where this happens.
Off in the distance gigantic monsters destroying a city or coming out of the water.
I've had this nightmare before.
Oh my goodness.
Okay.
You can double kill?
I don't think that was supposed to happen.
I feel like I'm playing...
What's that game?
With bugs.
You fight off the gigantic bugs.
It feels exactly like I'm playing that.
Why can I not think of that?
What is what that is?
Holy shit.
He's big.
I got him.
I killed them all.
EDF.
Right, Earth Fan Sports.
You see that?
Gold?
I think that was better than gold.
It's a reminder for you to give our daily auto update to tell us everything about auto.
I want level two.
Auto's great.
He's doing really well.
He's nice and happy.
This is level two.
What makes this harder?
Targeted and firing.
Run once more.
I imagine this probably does get much harder.
Easy way to make money though.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
They run fast.
They run faster.
Oh god, that's terrifying.
You gotta start to prioritize enemies now.
All right, I get it.
Why is that one red?
Why are they red?
Oh, they walk in different directions.
I get it.
This is scary.
I don't like this.
Whoa.
Good.
Missed.
Come on.
Oh, shit.
He'll die.
Hit him in the head, do more damage.
And does that not even matter?
I bet it doesn't matter.
Whoa, no, I missed.
Fuck you.
What?
Are you serious?
How did I put it under his armpit?
Whatever.
He raised his hand up and I shot under his arm.
All right, we're good.
Targeted and firing.
Yeah, this motherfucker raised up his armpit.
Well, now I know what happens.
So it's not based on when they decide to run.
It's who comes up first is who runs first.
They had that messed up.
I was assuming the person that was in front was going to run fast.
They go in order.
Okay, here comes a big guy in second here.
Big guy coming up.
Didn't keep walking.
Okay, let's go.
What does he worth?
How many points?
500.
That's where I died.
I got it.
Really does look like a dream.
Yeah, it feels like a dream.
It's creepy.
Somebody said that level three is really the actually hard one.
Find out.
It'd be available, right?
Level three?
I guess not yet.
Later, okay, cool.
Damn it.
All right, well, there's a fight right here.
Come on, I don't want to walk that way.
Okay, I'll just walk fine right here.
Do I still play VR games?
Yeah, I've taken a break from VR just because it really, really, really fucked me up last time.
Break dancing and getting thrown through a window at the dollhouse
for some reason was not even remotely as bad as streaming VR for a few days.
I don't know.
It just kills me now.
Something about the headset being on and how hot it gets in there and the movement.
Standing and all the motions.
There's a lot.
It was just horrible.
This feels like I'm playing Resident Evil 1 Silent Hill or something.
I really would like to get out of this area.
It hurts.
Game's resolution keeps getting worse.
And we keep losing a couple hundred pixels in either direction.
Let's get this over with.
Oh, this is going to be, this is going to suck.
Keep him in here.
Pick him up.
Dodged it.
All right, this is really clean.
I got a kill here.
This is really clean.
And give me Mustang right now and let's go for it.
Bro crazy.
I can't even pick these guys up.
I can't even touch these guys.
Yeah, no, what's the, they have like these stupid ass shields.
They start hitting people.
You're fucking with my flow.
Honest to God.
Well, why don't you die already?
Come on.
Oh, we got a raid.
Shit, hold on.
Good, good, good, good.
This is exactly what I want to have happen.
I just saved the whole run.
Thank God.
Okay, we got a raid.
We're raiding.
Jimmy here.
Jimmy here with a, that's a, that's a big raid.
We've got like 1500 people just showed up.
Welcome everybody.
How you doing?
Thank you, Jimmy.
Thanks for the raid.
Raid song.
Oh, I haven't done raid songs since like 2019.
Oh, no raid songs.
Welcome.
Playing Normal Heroes 3.
I love it so far.
We're about, I'd say probably halfway through the game.
So if you're gonna play it yourself, just, you know, be aware.
You might see things you don't want to see.
We're about six to seven hours into the total game play.
Raid song, fine.
Welcome to the stream.
I think you're the best.
Now this is a test.
Welcome to the stream.
Will the raiders stay?
Hey, after I scream this shit, let's see how many you leave.
I was just in there, come on.
Do I have enough money?
35, right?
Yeah, I don't have enough.
Spoken word is not a song.
Let's rubble out of here.
You know what this actually feels like?
And it's weird because this was a game that was on that console.
This feels like a shitload of original Wii games.
Damn, were they ugly.
They were so ugly.
Some of them were so ugly that it was almost impossible to play them.
I remember having a Wii and other people having a 360.
And any time a game that had decent, in quotes, graphics on the Wii came out,
it was always a big deal you tried to make to your friends.
Like, yeah, look, it looks pretty good.
And deep down, you know that this is supposed to be the good graphics.
And everybody's judging you.
And you're even judging you.
I remember selecting.
You guys remember switching cables on the Wii?
And it was like an Omega Chad moment
because you switched to component cables and could do 480p.
Here we go.
720.
I get progressive scan now.
Yeah, I remember the old Mega Chad moment of just plugging in the blue cable.
Like, yo, bro, I got the blue fucking cable.
Oh, you got the Chad cables.
Yep.
Of course I did.
Death melt shower.
Spin death.
Baste 480i.
What's that?
Oh, armor standing by.
Oh, let's go.
We have not seen this in-game yet.
Holy shit, I just killed everybody.
480p has a nostalgic, comfy amount of crust.
I actually liked 480p.
I remember switching from 480i to 480p for the first time.
That's a double S.
When I switch from 480i to like 480p,
you guys remember the Wii used to have a little bit of input lag?
And when you switched, you had that kind of sloppy,
maybe 50 millisecond, 100 millisecond response delay.
And when you select 480p, it was almost one-to-one.
It was literally the 480i to 480p Nintendo Wii
was like having a 120 hertz monitor the first time.
It was world-changing.
Yeah, it was like going from 30 to 60 FPS.
All right, I got enough.
There was an ATM, actually pretty close to one.
Hold on, there's a lot of question marks here.
GameCube component cables go for like $400.
They make adapters for the Wii that are HDMI,
and it forces the game, if you put a GameCube game in,
it forces progressive mode, which is really cool, actually.
A lot of times you've seen me play GameCube
or with the HDMI adapter in a Wii.
Fake pirated game?
A fake pirated game is just you bought the game, dude.
How do you fake a pirated game?
VR is going to get scary technology in the future.
Yeah, it is already kind of scary now.
All right, what else is over here?
There's tons of stuff.
There's a trash cleanup.
I'll do that.
Here is one of these.
I couldn't even see that on the ground.
Okay, oh, acquire a total of over 10,000 Utopia coins.
I have that.
I want that.
I like that shirt a lot.
How am I doing on sushi?
I'm about to fight the boss.
It's now more of a fun thing than the scary thing.
It's really easy to tell the difference.
Yeah, once they make...
And I don't know.
Here's the thing.
I don't think there's ever going to be a point
where we can tell the difference,
at least in our lifetimes.
But we can't tell the difference is what I mean.
This is like kind of a real life VR type shit.
You know how many pixels it would take
just to get somebody's realistic face photo realistic?
Show up on your screen.
It would take an incredible amount of computer power.
So you and I are not going to see that.
Maybe a few, I don't know,
a few generations ahead of us.
Depends on how quantum computing goes.
You and I aren't going to see it.
Maybe somebody else will.
And I'll tell you, I'm kind of happy I won't.
Because it's going to be really weird.
That real life is going to be...
It's going to be so uncanny valley.
I like being able to tell the difference.
Even if it's really good looking,
being able to actually tell the difference
lets us exist in both spaces.
Because once you can't separate fiction from reality,
what the fuck even is reality anymore?
I don't like that.
I like to be able to separate them.
I don't want it to get to that point
where I can't tell the difference.
Terrifies me.
Everything's just a lucid dream at that point?
Yeah.
Ah, yeah.
No, no, no, no, no.
No thanks.
Shut up and stream, gamer boy.
And now that's what happens when I'm not even looking.
Where is it?
Head to the motel parking lot.
Oh, okay.
Well, we can just fast travel.
Shut up and stream, gamer boy.
I imagine a hacker
sends you a video of your mother freaking out
and crying and screaming and shit.
And it's not even real.
But technology has gotten to the point
where you can fake everything.
And it's not even the deep fakes.
Oh, it's a deep fake.
No, no, no.
It's like it's just you can't even tell the difference
between fucking fact and fiction.
MonkaW.
Yeah.
We MonkaW at deep fakes right now.
The one thing that I would be happy with
with like the kind of technology
of not being able to tell the difference
is like somebody kind of just mentioned it a little bit.
I can imagine somebody just had made a realistic
like in real life you're watching reality
of like Richard Nixon like fighting
like fucking I don't know
like the Quaker Oats guy in like a wrestling ring.
Like that's kind of funny, right?
And if you couldn't even tell the difference
it's just like actual video footage.
I already did this.
It was a very strange example.
Or like a realistic real life of
let's just use Richard Nixon again.
Like they did make him like a pop star.
And he has like singles and shit.
It could be anybody.
They could like break like Abraham Lincoln
could have like a songs in like movies
and it would just be him.
Like we...
Okay, here we go.
I'm gonna get really existential here.
Are you ready?
This is really existential scary shit.
You ready for this?
I don't think you guys ready for this.
I don't know if it's too early for this.
If we have a world where we can just...
It's so realistic that you can't tell the difference.
People don't die.
Huh? Yeah?
People will always be able to exist.
Terrifying.
Look at that.
Smoke on that one for a little while.
Black Mirror already did this five years ago.
I don't care if Family Guy did a reference to that.
I don't care.
You and I are having a conversation right now.
All right.
Let me get...
Okay, listen to this.
If you and I are having a conversation in a living room
where I'm sitting on a couch,
you're sitting on the chair across from me
and I'm like, man, you know,
just talking like existential stuff.
Like can you imagine...
Like I got something for you.
Imagine how fucked up it is
like when you can't tell the difference
between like fact and fiction.
It's gonna be so fucking crazy.
And you just leaned in and said,
they did a Black Mirror episode about that.
Stop talking to me.
All right.
Hey dude, I saw a funny thing today.
Dude, you know Captain Crunch?
Dude, it like cuts the roof of my mouth all the time.
Like what the fuck?
Family Guy did that joke already three years ago.
Shut up.
I...
Okay.
You're so stoned.
Chat cancelled, isn't it?
All right.
I'll get back to the game.
Let me get back to the game.
We got like a bunch of new people here.
Come on, Gwen.
Don't cross over just yet.
You must not chase after the swan
on the other side of the lake when the rain falls.
That little girl is dangerous.
You'll get sucked down to the deepest depths
of your subconscious.
The beautiful landscape
and the melancholic melody are just lures.
Stay away.
I can hear Birkin's voice.
Your daddy doesn't want to see you just yet.
What am I?
What's this fucking weird?
What am I doing?
Dude, imagine like...
Dude, imagine like the world...
Like when technology gets so crazy.
You know, it's me and you're just hanging out talking.
Shut up, Simpsons Watcher.
Did I save the game?
Wait, I gotta upgrade.
Pass the joint already.
I don't have any toys.
Where do I get the toys?
I have no toys.
This sucks.
Wayne's World already did that.
And I know the song they did too.
Ballroom Blitz.
Blitz.
And the girl in the corner.
Everybody want a ballroom blitz.
Yeah, I've seen that movie.
I've seen that scene.
That doesn't mean we can't have a conversation about it.
All right, I have 6300.
I'm gonna just...
Yeah, I gotta do this.
I gotta go down this path
because I want the double dodge.
So hold X to charge your beam katana.
Leaves you so vulnerable though.
Takes too long.
I'm gonna dump it into this
because I want to be able to get that immediately after this.
Death skill level one.
Why is it death skill level one?
Oh, shit.
Right, that's what this is.
All right, I'll do that again.
Do it after this.
Okay, all right.
I think I'm good.
Any chance of a face cam?
Not with this nudity.
Would you ever like to be immortal?
No.
Although I can't lie, I don't ever want to be immortal.
But I think I would want to live a thousand years.
I think that's enough.
Maybe less.
Maybe 500.
Or you know what?
Like, okay.
Maybe like 150.
And you don't really start to actually get old
until 130, 140.
Thousand might be too long.
What about immortal with the chance of ending it on your own
when you want to?
No, I don't like that.
And I'll tell you why.
So if you have the choice to just turn it off,
when are you gonna turn it off?
Just one day you flip a switch?
Okay, that's it.
No, I don't think anyone would actually be able to do that.
It would be a really tough thing to do.
Because I imagine like the two or three lifetimes
of different people.
It's a lot.
Yeah, it's a lot of like responsibility
to be able to be like, okay, I can turn the switch off.
Like, I imagine like me right now,
it's been like 600 years.
I don't know.
Part of me would just sit there and kind of be like,
you know, I wonder if Bitcoin is going to be like 60 million dollars.
Like, I got to stay alive, right?
What if, okay, hold on.
I got to stay alive.
What if the US dollar is worth like 600 million US dollars in one dollar?
Like, I kind of need to know.
Are aliens going to show up?
Well, I want to, okay, what if I turn it off
and then like a week later, the aliens show up?
I kind of want to see it.
What do cars look like?
Are there cars?
What happens to roads?
I feel like I would have a list of like end game of things
that I thought were like, okay, like economic stuff.
What does the stock market look like?
What does like cryptocurrency look like?
What does the world look like?
What do world powers look like?
I think I'd have a checklist of things
that I would want to see how they played out.
What happens in the Marvel universe?
Yeah, what happens in phase 35 of the MCU?
I need to know.
Yeah, I don't know.
I kind of would want to like see how the world plays out
in a lot of very kind of maybe specific ways.
But it would, how, when would I turn it off though?
I don't know.
What if I, okay, what if I fulfilled those things?
What if like, okay, by the way, the stock market went to zero
and, uh, fucking silk has replaced the U.S. economy.
Oh, all right, cool.
Now what?
Like, when does it end?
The number six ranked assassin is Velvet Chair Girl.
She is the intergalactic musical chairs champion.
She works with Oma who has a huge gastro gun.
She turns it off before the sun explodes.
Welcome to the Garden of Insanity.
So what, you're saying that like, wait, okay, well,
I'm looking at the sun and it's been like another four or five thousand years
and I see it start to shake a little.
The sun's shaking a little bit and turning bright orange.
And then I look up and I'm just like, yep, switch off.
God, off, off, off.
Is that what you're saying?
Or do you wait till you see the, when do you do it?
Sun is shaking.
It's making sounds and then it just implodes and starts waving towards us.
And then switch off.
There's a billion years left on the planet before that happens.
I don't want to live a billion years.
I'm sorry.
I don't have any money so I can't buy anything anyways.
Although I could do one of the little ones, yeah.
Oh, I actually can't.
I can't afford anything.
Just before it turns into a red giant.
Oh, living forever would be mad boring at some point.
Like at some point you would run out of things to do.
Yeah, it would be kind of boring after a while.
Honestly, after the first like, I think 100 years, I think it'd be like, well,
fuck, there's only so many times I can go to Disney World before I've,
I've shaken hands with Mickey Mouse like 400 times already.
How many more times can I do that?
I've traveled the world a hundred times over.
What else do I do?
Should I try to, like, okay, here's a question for you guys though.
If I'm a mortal, does that count for other planets?
Like, do I breathe oxygen still?
Like, could they, could you just shoot me in a rocket into space
and could I like try to find another planet or something?
Do I need to, do I have to breathe oxygen?
Or could I actually, could you just shoot me in a rocket into a random planet in space?
And just give me a deck of cards and I'll just fucking,
I'll play solitaire for like a thousand years.
Immortal does not mean invincible, right?
Your mind would break?
But what if I said to make, okay, so I'm not invincible.
So I'm just a person though.
Would I be a person or could I withstand a rocket going like 500 times faster?
I'm just a person.
All right.
Well, look, we'll, we'll wrap back to this later.
We have a cut scene and a boss.
Face.
Yeah.
It's a bit too over the top.
Looks like public fun spent badly.
It's a form of culture, you know.
I don't think so.
I mean, what even is?
I don't want to talk about this all night.
Yeah.
Well, first let's take out this next dickhead.
Then we'll talk.
I love that term.
I love dickhead.
Today's main event, the galactic title match is about to begin.
What is going on?
Please welcome the galactic champion.
I feel like I'm watching an episode of Xavier renegade angel.
Well, it's this looks like Las Vegas.
You know, I actually kind of like this stuff.
Please.
I've got to do it.
And I stop being immortal.
I could never be immortal or could I?
That's a question.
What musical chairs?
When the music stops bolt straight for the closest chair,
hit the buttons displayed on the screen in time with the metronome.
Oh no.
I don't have the this memorized this controller.
What?
Oh, God.
I said to pretend I'm playing Super Mario RPG.
And I have it memorized if I think I'm playing Mario RPG.
I swear to God, that's how I'm doing this.
What is it?
When do I stop doing this?
How do I stop?
I got a chair.
Nice.
This is just Mario Party with a few extra steps, I think.
Oh, no.
Here we go.
There's only four chairs.
Oh, what?
That was quick.
Okay, there's only two.
I gotta be ready.
This blinking is hurting my head.
I remember where I'm going here, where I am.
Oh, my God.
Where am I?
What happened?
What?
I did it.
I just like failed the game.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
This is fast.
It's so hard when I don't have it memorized completely.
I just don't.
What?
I went...
What are you drinking?
What just happened?
There's one velvet chair girl dead.
You lost musical chairs so you die.
No.
No way.
We hadn't even started going at it yet.
For her, the most important battle was lost.
Oh, no.
That monster thing.
It's getting super weird over here.
It's freaking out.
Suicide by orange juice.
Isn't that hilarious?
Well, time to get to work.
Oh, boy.
Okay.
Here comes the actual fight.
Whoa.
All right.
That's an instant kill.
We try with one half times attack power.
Thank you for the cheat code.
Pity mode.
Okay.
So what's the strategy here?
Is it about on time?
All right.
You have to wait until it's a big long one and then you start swinging.
Okay.
Go.
Now get in.
Don't get greedy.
It's about not being greedy.
It's going to touch me.
Don't let it touch you.
Is that hitting?
Whoa.
Okay.
No.
He's not doing it longer anymore.
There we go.
What am I doing?
That was really stupid.
Okay.
I'm fine.
Don't let it touch you.
She's always dead.
I'm on a fucking battery power.
Adrian.
Raspberry.
Strawberry.
We're just two shitty Pokemons.
Somebody said that.
I was funny.
Oh my.
Omega L.
What's that sound?
She's crying.
It really is just like tears.
I think I have the extra power.
11,000.
Congratulations.
You have been recognized as number six in the galactic rankings.
I still got a long way to go, but this is getting kind of fun.
If I take down the baddest dude in the galaxy, then I'll be the baddest dude in the galaxy.
Right?
Rise up, Travis.
Higher and higher.
To the edge of the universe.
He won by cheating.
I'm going all the way to the edge.
Meow.
Who's number five?
Midori.
Midori Kawa.
I just noticed the planets on the right.
The Earth is a star.
Oh, yeah.
Back to the existential talk.
I don't even remember what we were talking about.
We were talking about being immortal.
And like when you see the sun about to explode, you just like turn it off.
And then we had, I don't know the rules.
Immortal means unkillable by definition.
Well, hey, what about never age, but you can die of anything else?
Yeah, then I mean, after like a few hundred years,
you would have experienced Disney World 50 times.
You would have traveled the world 10 times.
You'd have eaten every single food probably 50 times over.
I think it's like three or 400 years.
You would just die in like a car crash.
Or something.
Wait, hold on.
Why am I assuming that I'm going to live for 400 years?
That's exponentially giving me more time to die by something.
Like get hit by a bus.
Or like fall down like a ditch or something.
Statistically speaking, yes.
Huh.
Interesting.
Statistically speaking, you'd probably be guaranteed to die in a few hundred years.
Regardless of if I aged or not.
Shit.
You know, you don't even really think about that too much.
What are the chances, somebody look this up.
What are the chances of somebody being struck by lightning?
What is that actual chance?
Is the average person lives to be about what?
75 to 90 years old?
Like 80 to 90?
It's one in what?
One in like 500,000?
One in five million?
Hold on.
Hold that, we'll get back to this in a minute.
If you lived forever, thousands of years,
would you statistically be struck by lightning and die at some point?
Going back to work.
Miss Christelle, I'm leaving him to you.
Dammit!
Son of a bitch.
That's not how stats work.
Right.
But if you lived for like 50, like 500,000 years on Earth,
you probably are going to get struck by lightning and die at some point.
Just because you're giving it, it's just going to happen eventually.
Just only live in a sunny area.
They got lightning here, man.
The Underground Society series is so great.
Miyake's film is just blazing.
Kitamura is so bad at being an assassin.
I can totally tell.
Oh, MonkaW there is lightning?
He's got the same eyes as you.
He definitely gives up.
There are so many other things that are more likely.
Yeah, but those increase exponentially if you live for thousands of years.
Yagami no Kitsu shit done.
One of these days, man, Kitamura's Underground series.
Shinjuku is so awesome.
Shinjuku is like some kind of paradise.
Statistically speaking, carrying a bunch of Oreos in my hand.
God damn, I want to check out Shinjuku sometime.
Up to like my bedroom.
And falling down the stairs.
Exponentially increases when that happens 50,000 times.
Eventually.
I wonder what would get me though.
You know what I mean?
What would it be if like if I was guaranteed like immortal.
Like I don't die.
Like I'm just I just live for 100,000 years.
I wonder what would actually be the thing to get me.
I think I'd get attacked by a bird.
I really think I think a bird would like swoop down and fucking take my head off.
Like an eagle would just decapitate me or something.
Like I would get attacked by an eagle and die.
I think that's really what it would be.
After like a year, like 400 and like like 400,000 like an eagle.
I'm going to be in the wrong place somewhere and I'm going to get attacked by a fucking eagle.
It's going to rip my eyes out.
All right, I've got a new we're going to close.
I want to see what's that mountain there.
It is Death Mountain.
Oh, I like it.
Do you have any other pants?
I want to change my pants.
Which one?
That's my angry goose.
No jacket off.
Yeah, we'll wear this for a little while.
What's up?
Gene?
Like his brain.
Okay, wow.
Go for 25.
I'm not going for 25.
No, I wouldn't want to be immortal though.
Okay, how much?
Let's keep going.
I need like at least three or four thousand Wesson, right?
Just check the weather wherever you go and you'll be fine.
You can't check the weather for eagles swooping down with a vicious look in their eye.
There's no forecast for that.
All right, we're going to Neo Brazil.
It's a new zone.
Oh, let me turn in these.
I have a couple of cards.
Don't I have a scorpion too?
Do I have a scorpion?
No.
Nope.
Come to Brazil.
He's going to Brazil.
Finally.
What the fuck?
Yes, there is a check eagle schedule.
Just see where they play.
Hey, good.
Oh, vinyl clubs.
I don't know what that is.
What if you're immortal and get caught in an avalanche or a landslide and got stuck?
I would die.
Well, because I assume I still have to eat food.
I still have to eat.
It seems like we're changing the rules here a few times over.
You're immortal.
But do I have to eat?
There's a very specific bunch of rules here that we need to get clear.
Do I have to eat?
I don't have to eat food.
No, only for pleasure.
Okay.
You will never have to use the bathroom again.
You see, I don't know if I buy this though.
Of course you would have to use the bathroom.
Where would anything go?
Do you just disappear as a black hole in my stomach?
Do I have organs?
Well, I don't have organs then.
I'm just like skin filled with air, like cosmic air.
You have a skin and a brain.
I'm a jellyfish.
Okay, Neo Brazil.
All right.
How much money?
Fine.
Designated match when you do three.
Let's go right here.
What if you had to poop?
Whatever.
That one's weird because that one doesn't make any sense.
You're just trying to give me, say, a gross thing on stream.
And it was really close.
You almost had it.
Spin death throw.
Strawberry.
Screw bluster death kick.
Death melt shower.
All right.
Let's kill that guy.
Double kill.
I'm trying to get a 100-hit combo.
It's going to be hard with that weird guy over there though.
Kill.
That's good.
77 hit.
80 hit.
Strawberry.
Screw bluster death kick.
Ooh, 88.
Fever.
93.
95.
Give me 100.
Yeah.
Death melt shower.
Gravity death force.
120.
Come here.
Oh, I lost it.
Screw bluster death kick.
I'm trying to build a combo on these guys.
They have a shield.
Right off.
Spin death throw.
I just took one damage already.
Fuck you.
I hate you.
Stupidest enemy.
You spuck up the flow.
I just want to correct the record.
Jellyfish don't have brains.
They have what's known as a nerve net.
I like you, but don't want you spreading dangerous misinformation on your platform.
Time that guy out for an hour.
I'm kidding.
10 seconds.
Yeah.
And that's like saying we don't have...
A brain is not a brain.
It's just electromagnetic pudding.
Chunky pudding.
See?
I can say smart things too.
Is this...
What is this?
Free wave defense mission.
I'll do it.
There's so many weird animals on this planet.
So many weird organisms.
Let's get this over with.
Wave one.
Spin death throw.
Nice.
Give it to me.
Yeah.
I thought it was better than that.
Can I stay in the same wave?
Come on, wave two.
Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick.
Give it to me.
Try not to take a hit.
That'll hit too.
Ooh.
Full armor.
Let's go.
No.
What did I do that for?
Fuck.
That was stupid.
I should have...
I'm so mad right now.
I could have ended it immediately.
Oof.
What an oof.
That's just actual oof.
Unbelievable.
I could have ended it immediately.
I'm so sad.
Ooh.
Side step.
Everybody free.
Ooh.
So kill them both.
Thank you.
Oh.
I got Mustang mode.
Holy shit.
All right.
That's ass.
Absolute ass plus.
Couldn't even see what was happening on the screen.
That's how you know it was good.
Yeah.
That was really cool.
Very fun.
How much do I need?
Okay.
I have...
40,000 coins to enter.
I think I have like 30.
I'm gonna do a couple of the jobs after this.
Game's a little loud.
Yeah.
I'll turn it down.
All right.
Again.
Land, please.
Oh, bad.
It's okay.
I'm behind, really.
Get out of here.
That was a perfect dodge.
I felt like that was a perfect dodge.
I think I got hit from the other guy.
Let's give this a try.
I just kicked him in the air.
Hit them both.
Get them both.
Kill them.
Oh, shit.
Watch the health.
He's invisible, right?
Okay.
Wait till he comes out.
Perfect dodge it.
And...
Come out of there.
I'm wasting time here.
And...
I'm gonna crush you.
SS streak is over.
Well, it might actually be an S.
Ah, it's okay.
All right.
This is the third time this guy's called.
Very curious now.
My reason.
You need my reason, right?
Oh, we've gotten so close.
Have you thought of a reason?
Yeah.
It's a hassle.
Just thinking about him makes me nauseous.
I want him to disappear.
I feel like I can't breathe.
Like I have something stuck in my throat.
I feel like I'm gonna die.
All just too much to deal with.
So, am I trying to get somebody to kill Fu?
I think that's what's happening.
I see.
How self-centered.
I've heard your reason.
I'll accept your request.
Out of consideration for the utterly pitiful weakness of your heart.
I don't care why you do it.
I just want it done.
In that case, we'll enter into a formal agreement next time.
An actual physical contract is not necessary, however.
Shit, we have to do this again?
Whatever, fine.
Next time it is.
What if it is Fu?
Uh-oh.
Calling the sus guy at 3 a.m.
I wanna do a couple of jobs.
I did that match job, but I wanna do another job.
Do not call the sus guy at 3 a.m.
I really wanna make that video.
I would love to.
For god's sake, don't.
I kind of need to, though.
I have to.
I almost need to do it out of...
Okay.
Does that video have more video views than any of the main channel videos I've ever made?
If I do it the same way I do it exactly like the videos act,
it's not a joke.
I don't make it a funny joke.
It's just I make one of those videos and try as hard as I can to do that.
No, yeah.
No swearing.
Just like, oh my god, guys.
What the heck is happening?
Don't call him.
It's, like, I would just put on, like, the thing and just see if I can do it.
Holy sh...
I can't say holy shit, right?
Head off to conquer the space monster.
Yeah.
Like, holy crap, guys.
Oh my god, guys.
Oh my goodness.
What the heck?
Yeah, I could pull it off.
Can I already fight this guy?
Round two.
Round two it is.
Watch it.
Gonna break that ice.
Watch the rockets.
Ice coming in.
Cannon.
Oh.
Yeah.
Hit the core.
Core.
Come on, his mouth is open.
Hit it.
Core coming up, right?
Oh, shit.
Death is part of life.
Not if you're immortal.
All right, let's see if I can get him right here.
Cannon.
All right, got it.
Nice.
Go back to space.
I'm being called a fuckhead.
I just got here.
That's just what he does.
Hey.
Ooh.
All right.
Okay.
Go for...
There's a couple of other things on the map.
Yeah, I'm not gonna do this one yet.
Actually, I probably can just get out of the way.
Yeah.
This is the main one.
I'll get this out of the way.
And then we're gonna go do some jobs around the city.
Something that I've noticed.
Let's get deadly.
I feel like I'm like halfway through the game.
Right?
Because it feels like that.
Um.
I only...
Any other beam katanas?
When do I get another katana?
Oh, I'm looking at chat.
I'm not playing the video game.
There's only one.
Really?
Oh.
You know, I haven't really noticed it being a problem or anything.
It's just like, oh, right, right.
Where's my other katanas?
So, yeah, it's fine.
All right, time to play the game.
I've literally just been looking to my left.
Not a big deal, but it's a weird change to make.
Oh.
Where's he at?
There he is.
He's in this room.
Get out of there.
Yep.
Battery's almost done.
I just double dodged, but I can't hit him.
Fuck.
Really?
Shit.
Watch out for those stupid parasite things.
Goodbye.
Watch out for those parasite things.
Oh, all right.
Throw him back into that.
He's dead.
Oops.
All fuckberries.
Oh, that seems to be more in-depth and free.
More katanas aren't needed.
Yeah.
I think with the chips in the glove makes it a little more interesting.
Although I say that, but I've only been using the same free the whole game.
I have enough money.
I want to go do the jobs.
There's a couple of jobs here that I want to do.
There's a toilet to unclog, but what is this?
A t-shirt alien?
Okay.
Uniform of Don Mai Sushi.
I love it.
Defeat a total of 50 enemies.
I've done that for sure.
Yeah, I want that.
Nice.
I love it.
Looks pretty clean.
Oh, toilet.
Matches the bike.
It does.
End of the stream voice.
What?
No, I'm just relaxing, man.
I'm good.
Ending the stream.
I just wish that that NPC just kind of glanced over.
And then glanced back.
It'll be a nice touch.
There's a race over here.
This has got to be level four at this point.
We're level four and five?
I wonder.
Oh, let's get this out of the way.
Yeah.
Bike missions.
Yeah, I've done this.
Except this request.
Yeah, but didn't I already do this?
Why does it make me do the tutorial again?
Is this better than one and two?
Yes.
Absolutely without question.
Holy shit, that's a sharp turn.
I got to keep in mind that that turn happens because that sucks.
He loves the game.
I do.
I think it's more...
Well, it's definitely longer, right?
I think it's...
I don't know.
It's in a weird place because they've removed the levels in the game from what it seems.
They just made a bunch of open world mini games.
Some of them are fights, some of them aren't.
And something about that doesn't like take away from the other games.
But it makes the whole process just streamlined.
You can kind of do whatever you want.
So if you want to do the fighting missions and run around the open world.
It's more focused on actually just kind of going around and looking at stuff.
I do some...
A little bit, I do miss the actual missions where you go run around and fight in corridors and stuff.
And it's just a wave of enemies.
You keep going.
There's a little cut scene.
A wave of enemies, wave of enemies.
But at the end of the day, does it really matter if you're doing the same thing?
You just have to press a button that says, I'd like to do a fight mission, please.
It does feel weirdly paced.
Fun to play, but not very immersive for an open world.
Yeah, I could see that.
I still think it's better.
I think it's a better game.
Something about this one feels more fun than the other two.
But I don't know.
There's recency bias is a problem.
Because I love those little mini games from the second game.
I think I like this game's...
This game's feel and this game's kind of storyline.
I love the kind of superhero aspect of it.
I think it's funny.
Because what the hell are you supposed to do with a guy that can kill all the assassins?
Oh, we just do like a Marvel universe.
It's funny.
I don't really miss the other stuff I'm talking about.
This feels different enough where it's not a problem.
I haven't really thought about that at all this whole time.
I really need to kind of beat this before I get a D.
Don't do that.
Shit.
He's right there.
Just get him.
Wouldn't you want to be immortal to be able to play all the video games?
Sure.
But would you though?
Would you really want to?
If it was only a certain amount of media your brain could consume
before it all really just bleeds together.
10,000 years of video games?
I wouldn't remember Super Mario.
You would just forget about the worst ones.
I would need to kind of have post-it notes around me at all times
to remember all the things I thought were cool.
My fridge would be just all post-it notes
that I have to look at from time to time.
A year.
3,200.
Game system.
The Omega Sony.
The Sony Omega.
Okay, what was it?
Liked main character.
His laugh was funny.
And attack of the gigantic monster village.
You'd have to constantly remind yourself of what you thought was interesting.
There's one.
Slow it down.
I have to kill some of these guys.
They have like, look at the health they have.
They have no health.
Damn it.
I'm not even close either.
Fuck you.
No!
Fuck!
Come here!
Oh god.
I'm ahead of him.
That turn doesn't even make any sense.
Why is it even there?
I don't even care if I get bronze.
I just want to get these over with.
All right, we're good.
If you're immortal, people would find you and experiment on you to find out why.
Why would you tell anybody?
I failed it.
I didn't get a medal.
I'm not going to walk up to a CIA agent and whisper in his ear and go,
hey, I'm immortal.
Nothing kills me.
I can't die.
No, you live your whole life.
And then, no, I wouldn't tell anybody.
Why would anybody need to know?
You would just cycle a whole new lifetime, right?
You wouldn't get old.
I would just constantly be making new friends.
But what age are you?
How old are you?
How old do you look?
Am I the age that I am right now?
Like 30?
50?
20?
You'd be in your prime.
So what, like 28?
29?
30?
Oh my god.
I'm so sorry.
I was up all night and slept in.
Going to have to cancel.
My job done laters.
Oh yeah, you're probably pissed, huh?
You're going to try to kill me now, right?
My boyfriend is already on to you.
If you're going to kill me, he's going to kill you.
As soon as possible.
I'm getting in the way with this Travis fight, okay?
This is serious stuff.
Who was that?
Was he just killing people in this restaurant?
You can't kill my boyfriend.
What is he doing?
He just stood up and just blasted that person.
The person was just enjoying like a tuna melt.
What the hell was that?
Do I have enough to level up?
I feel like I didn't get that many Wesson.
Could be wrong.
I had a tuna melt for dinner last night and it was good.
You guys know that once we start talking about food,
the stream end countdown is about like one to two hours after that, right?
I like this shirt.
I'm going to keep it on.
The more you tell me how awesome and delicious the food you ate yesterday was,
the more that like the internal clock has just started.
I got 10,000.
Let's go with pull down time reduced on this
because me and one of my is not going to do it.
I seem to use them a lot.
Pull down time reduced again.
And then the double dodge.
How do I do this?
Let's press B while dodging to dodge even further.
So it's just BB.
But you know, it's AB actually.
It's boom, boom.
Okay.
Last attack.
So this is just a normal attack.
Mash Y to unleash a high speed continuous thrust attack.
Don't I already do that?
Eight, nine, and that will go.
I feel like I already do that move.
Today's national cheese pizza day.
Is it really?
All right.
I'm going to look at this because I feel like I need to make something.
I got to do something here.
We've been doing the extra damage.
It's cool.
But I kind of want to go for something else.
Okay.
During slow down after a perfect dodge.
Damage taken.
I don't want the tanky ones.
I don't care about the tanky ones.
Tension gauge depletion.
That's not bad because that means I get to stay in the cool modes 30% longer.
Another tanky one.
Wait, what?
After a successful perfect dodge, slow time 50% up.
Does that mean the cool down is reduced?
Or does that mean I get a slow down?
Does that mean after a perfect dodge slow time it'll last 50% longer?
Oh, shit.
That's really good.
Wait.
So if I get three of these, that means it's 150% longer.
Yeah, I'm going to get one of these.
That's awesome.
That's a huge deal.
Even if I just have one of them.
I can get two of them.
I'll come back to it.
This is 39.
50% more tension gauge.
That's pretty good.
While performing the recharge, power charge amount.
So I get 50% more charge.
Essentially, recharging the battery takes half as much time.
But I don't think that's that big of a deal.
While walking alerts you when search object is close.
I'm assuming that's scorpions and stuff.
I think I'm going to make two of these.
Yeah, I'm going to get a full 100% longer.
But I have to start doing perfect dodges, though.
Otherwise, it's not worth it.
You had pizza yesterday?
Yeah, it was good.
I had a barbecue chicken, bacon, garlic, vinegar, and oat milk pizza.
That's pretty good.
All right.
I want to know, what's this?
Well, your health is 80% higher.
All right, so this is just 20% more damage.
Okay, we're going to get rid of two of these.
So now I do 10% more damage.
Or technically like 18% less damage than I was doing before.
But the slow time function is like forever.
Let's try it.
See how it seems any good.
We combined all of our sleeper agent words.
Yeah, that's funny.
I'm going to eat one of those things, too.
Because why not?
I'm ready to move.
Let's do this boss fight.
It is time.
But not yet.
Let's check on Shinobu.
I can still fight, but even in your nightmares, you're fighting.
You're a real beast.
Speaking of beasts, Akuto's Northern Lights Bomb.
That move is risky.
It really tests your skill.
Shinobu, are you ready to drop a Northern Lights Bomb?
The Northern Lights Bomb awaits you.
What's wrong with me?
All right, let's just do it.
I'm ready to go.
I also can go back to the time machine and fight other bosses and make them harder.
I haven't done it all.
I have to pee again, but I'm going to hold it until after the boss.
If that makes sense to me.
Or should I go right before the boss?
What do you think?
One's in chat if I should go before the boss.
All right, I'll be right back.
This is probably the last break of the night.
I'll probably go for like another hour, hour and a half or so.
We'll see.
I'll be right back.
What's happening?
Oh, there we go.
Okay.
What's with the smile?
What's with the smiling?
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
If you tell me not to worry about it, I'm not going to worry about it.
Why would I worry about something I'm told just to not worry about?
Let's do the boss.
Here we go.
Garden of Insanity.
The number five ranked assassin is Midori Midorikawa.
Occupation Dark World Princess.
Even the UAA Internashk does not know exactly who she is.
Get all your yayas out Travis.
Welcome to the Garden of Insanity.
I wonder what they're going to do.
I have no idea what this game is going to throw at us now.
Because I think there's only really been two or three real boss fights the whole game.
There's been maybe three you fight the boss games.
The rest have just been insanity.
Mini games inside of the rooms.
People killing each other.
Somebody teaching me moves.
I wonder what this is going to be.
All right.
Let's go with this one.
Greatly increased health attack by our intention.
Let's do it.
I mean, why not?
If you have the money, just use it.
And we just musical chairs.
All right.
I got five heels.
I'm good.
David.
He's fall asleep in the toilet.
The sushi looks good.
Yeah, it does.
Somebody said a tuna fish and I don't want it.
I want like a nice big cheesy tuna melt.
With just like a bunch of pickles on the side.
Damn, that sounds good.
That's the game plan after this.
Like a side salad.
Carrots and shit.
Yeah.
Where the hell are we?
At school.
A Japanese school, huh?
I've seen places like this in Miyake's movies about delinquents and stuff.
This place is kind of scary.
Yeah, like one missed call scary.
Scary.
Oh, God.
Something feels off here.
Yeah, super off.
Is this?
I'm probably going to have to run away from a scary monster thing.
My name is Midori Midorikawa.
Bill's sister's name is Do-Re-Mi Midori.
It's spelled like notes and pronounced Do-Re-Mi.
Those weird names people give their kids these days.
My house is near Midori Yama Studio.
During my rebellious period, I wore lots of Kimidori green.
I was disappointed in myself for not wearing my favorite color, red.
I've been cursed by green, which is Midori in Japanese.
There are so many things I hate about it and I almost totally blamed my parents,
but I just couldn't hold them accountable because I love mommy and daddy.
There was someone else I loved even more.
He led me down this path to becoming a cleaner.
What sort of path, you ask?
Where do I even start?
Time and space have been distorted, so I can't really get things straight.
But for starters, I'm going to kill you.
So I'd appreciate your cooperation.
I would run.
She disappeared.
Where is she?
I don't care how skilled I am.
I'm going to run.
I'll just call the nuking.
You know what I mean?
I'll just send a nuke.
I'm going to run.
I'm going to try to get out.
Are you fucking kidding me?
It's first person.
They really just said, fuck it.
They don't even give a shit.
They just said, fuck it.
We're going to do whatever we want.
Each one of these bosses has been like a weird, almost like tropey thing.
I love it, but they just said, fuck it, huh?
It's now a scary game.
It's going to be a jump scare.
There has to be.
You don't make this without a jump scare.
It kind of feels like I'm in Gary's Mod right now.
What does that mean?
We need a face cam.
I don't have a T.
I don't have clothes on.
Oh, God.
Okay, fine.
I got to put a T-shirt on.
Give me a second.
I'll give you two seconds.
Okay, I got a bathrobe.
That's the closest thing I could grab.
I got a bathrobe.
All right, that looks good.
Here we go.
Turn off the lights?
No.
It's going to turn around.
It's going to scream.
No?
And we're certain that Suda51 didn't have seven or eight games in development
and just mushed them all together and made No More Heroes 3.
Are you sure?
Are we certain about that?
I feel like these are all just like EXEs he had on his desktop.
He was just like, yeah, I'm going to try to make like a little horror game.
And he's got like 40 EXEs on his desktop of games that he made
with a group of friends and his teammates.
And then it's like, yeah, fuck it.
Let's just put that No More Heroes.
Why not?
We're good.
Mustang mode.
I will back to first person in each series.
A 20K robe?
I think this is from Target.
What happened?
Blood.
Okay.
This is getting more and more bad and scary.
It's going to come out.
She's going to be screaming, coming out.
I'm going to turn around and run.
Left or right?
That doesn't open.
All right.
I'm going to say right is a shorter hallway.
So I'm going to go right.
Return to the motel?
What the hell is this?
It's a way out way.
It's the midway point in the haunted house
so the little kids can leave when they're really scared.
Okay.
You know, like fucking Darth Vader is holding the door open
for the parents to take their kids out.
It's like, oh, thank you, Darth Vader.
He lets you out.
You go out.
You don't go to the scary, awful part.
Like they wave, like two or three of them wave as you leave.
I remember that.
They try to keep you from the really scary shit.
Unlocked of memory.
Old joke, Andy.
No, I can make reference.
Reference is an old joke.
You're referencing something that happened before.
So I can reference a thing that I'm referencing
because it's old and I'm referencing it.
Two, two.
All right.
Remember these numbers up here.
Salty Andy.
Somebody flashlight in there.
That's a mirror.
Never mind.
I did that on purpose.
Haha, that was funny.
I have this blood in here.
I hope this part goes on for an hour.
Death bro.
Strong it.
Right on.
Dodge.
You're never gonna catch.
Watch this shirt.
Get some.
I feel like I just have like a lit cigarette.
Just in an ashtray right here that you can see.
I don't smoke it once.
It's just there.
Just lit for an hour.
I have to clear all these rooms.
Is that what's going on?
Or is it just the ones with blood?
Definitely all the rooms with blood.
Absolutely right.
Yeah, of course.
Spin death slow.
I want to try the dodge.
Let's try dodge.
So let's see now.
How long is this guy?
I mean, I can't even tell.
I'm just killing him so hard.
Remember we can see the damaged tattoo.
What if you guys just never knew?
But I was just covered in tattoos from my hair down.
From the neck down.
You just saw like a bunch of patterns in there.
I feel like I would not.
I would have been.
You probably would have known that by now.
I see green.
Oh shit, no.
So where do I go?
Wait, what happened?
Hey, it's putting me at the end of the hallway.
Oh, that's what's going on.
It's put me at the...
Okay, this is just putting me
at the end of the hallway when I do that.
So all right, let's fight then.
Okay, I gotta clear the rooms.
Put a tattoo of yourself.
Hey, come on.
Reference Andy.
Come on.
I made the joke like three years ago
that I was going to get a tattoo of my face on my face.
Full scale.
I think that's it.
Maybe one more room.
Get a tattoo of the sus face on your face.
What is this?
Disco.
Somebody started a disco?
That was like a big thing.
It was a disco in the chat or something.
What was that?
Then what am I supposed to do?
So I just leave?
Oh, it's open.
Okay, it's open.
I think the face cam was on so you could see that.
Okay, I think you got your face cam that you wanted.
And stupid and intelligent and dumb.
But you're also a nice guy with a serious side too.
Is this chat talking to me?
There's a certain type of guy that reminds me of my old boyfriend.
Something happened and we ended up breaking up.
But the reason for that was actually pretty funny.
Want to hear about it?
No, I'm not really in the mood.
Oh, it's about time we finished settling this.
All right, then let's go up to the roof.
Jump with me, okay?
I kind of hope it's still first person.
Seems quickest.
One, two, three.
Huh?
I messed up.
This is-
This is that rock quarry in Ibaraki that they use to film those tokusatsu shows, isn't it?
Awesome.
I can't believe I'm here.
This is where they film common writer zeal, you know?
Oh, sorry.
I kind of can't deal with all this otaku talk.
So could you not?
Fine, whatever.
All right, so we're actually gonna fight.
Okay.
Is that a mouth on her hand?
It's morning.
Holy shit.
Listen, this scary old man is standing right there.
Let's kill him together.
He's pretty tough.
I might even die.
Oh my god.
No, don't die.
Nice.
Changing forms like that and all?
You must really love the tokusatsu stuff.
Once these guys wake up, it's all over, Travis.
Whatever.
I'll kill all your asses.
I gotta change up forms, too.
Otherwise, it would be rude.
Really?
Is this a suit fight?
This is a suit fight?
We're going into space?
I'm gonna have nightmares about this.
I really will.
Are they like wallet warrior laughing at me?
Okay.
Like nice skin.
Press R to launch a tiger attack.
Press L to fire your multi-missile.
Tiger attack multi-missile.
It's also called full green mode.
These are both extremely powerful attacks,
so they'll need time to cool down after use.
Watch out for the right time to unleash them.
Do I have a regular attack?
I have regular attacks.
This is ridiculous.
So when should I use this?
I'm gonna use it now.
I can't do it.
I just tried to do it.
Oh, wrong button.
Get the fuck out.
I just point blanked.
Don't stand in the fire.
Oh, you guys get to see my APM down there.
How am I doing?
Ow.
Almost phase one.
Of course, we get a pew, pew, pew.
All right, phase two.
Now what?
I'm fine.
This is pretty easy.
This one's not.
This one's pretty easy.
Let's just kill her.
That was a cool fight.
Just a cool character.
But I mean, I just absolutely dunked on you.
Dory, Dory, Dory lose.
That's to be a little easier since you can't use your healing items.
Oh, I guess I meant to say it makes sense.
That was more of an experience than it was a rough fight.
Oh, is this a real boss fight?
Who the hell are?
Trav, it's me.
Kamui, is that you?
Not this one.
Another fake out.
Stay out of this.
That's my girlfriend.
Seriously?
This is your girlfriend?
We've got no beef with you.
We just sort of took full upon his offer and thought of it kind of like going to a nice barbecue,
you know?
Like that thing that's really trendy these days.
Dompering or whatever.
That was basically what we envisioned coming here.
Are you for real?
I've never actually met Fu.
During the breakout, I made eye contact with him for like a second.
And I could feel the dark world in those eyes.
Oh, yeah.
By the way, I'm a dark world princess.
And that's right, Dory is an actual princess.
Isn't that awesome?
Okay.
So I kind of got no idea what's going on right now.
Travis strikes again.
Skipper left in the dark.
Omega low.
Thanks, Trav.
I return the favor.
Come on over and hang out sometime.
That's good enough for me.
Trav, you really are a good guy.
I've been too good of a guy, really.
So then, what do you all think about this?
This boss fight, it had become quite the confusing mess.
But somewhere inside that confusing mess hid the truth.
What is real?
What is not?
We were just talking about this.
Questions for the ages.
There is only one thing that is real.
I am here in front of your very eyes.
After crossing the river of life and death,
find the place where the point and the line
of everyday life intersect.
Be waiting for you.
Is this the streamer?
Kill the life.
Destroy the life.
Kill the boy.
Erase the life.
And let the man be born.
Once it's all gone, it's all over.
And then have everyone forget.
It's not actually over yet.
Because it was so awful.
The true end is killing the past.
No one even remembers this entire series.
John.
Kill the past.
Yeah, that was...
Okay, that was weird.
Kill the boy.
What a peculiar...
Congratulations, Travis.
You have been recognized as number five in the galactic rankings.
I feel like I'm at a Suda 51 convention,
and I don't even know I'm there.
He's just referencing every game he's ever made.
Okay, we're now number four.
We're number five now.
We're going for number four.
Let's go for the next one.
We'll do another one.
Yeah, I feel like going for the...
Being number four means that we have three more to do.
That's probably not enough for a whole stream, though.
So...
Okay, so I'm going to play WarioWare on Friday.
We're not done.
I'm not...
I'm still here.
I'm going to stream for like an hour.
WarioWare is going to be Friday.
And then Wario...
I might even play...
I'll play this on Saturday.
And then depending on how long this takes to finish it,
because I feel like there's probably still another four and a half,
maybe four to five hours left in the game.
There's also the time machine to do the bosses on higher difficulties.
That's true, yeah.
So there's still plenty of content to do for a whole stream.
So we'll go for one more,
and then I'll finish this up on Saturday.
And then we'll do WarioWare on Friday.
And we'll do one more.
Get us towards heading to the top three.
And then it's tuna melt time.
What if you get struck by lightning before then?
I've already lived like 200 lifetimes.
So I don't care.
I guess humans are pretty tough after all.
Yeah, they're not weak.
What's a big Hero 6 guy?
So how are things now?
What's his name?
This guy is really something.
The assassin called Travis.
Baymax.
Just give me the word and I'll go kill him straight away.
What if a little kid drew Baymax?
Because Baymax is their favorite character.
And then they just put it to a 3D renderer.
What's he thinking?
I just want you to kill him.
By the way, I love this character's design.
I think it's amazing.
There was not a dog at the design.
It was just kind of an observation.
Who are these two?
Ah, big four have gathered.
Or to put it a different way, only the big four survived.
WWE 2K20.
I'll wait patiently.
Could this human even make it all the way to me?
It's fucking crazy.
I'm not worried.
Sniping Lee here will put this earthling down.
That's what everyone says before they get killed.
You're probably going to die too.
Prince fool.
Can I kill this guy?
Take him out with a headshot.
Xavier Renegade Angel.
Yeah, it is.
Damon.
Those are some pretty big words there, huh?
It's the truth, foo.
I just want that guy killed.
I want to see him torn to shreds.
Jump Force create a character.
Yeah, Soul Calibur create a character.
It's for me.
Keep your opinions to yourself.
Fine.
I'll kill him my own way.
Don't you fucking get in mine.
Hurry up and take this guy out so I don't get in your way, big fool.
It's so funny how intentional that is, though.
It's so charming.
I love it.
This is stupid.
I'm going to take a nap and wait.
Don't get killed in your sleep.
I'll take your head first.
These guys don't look very powerful at all.
That's number two, number three, and number one there.
That's so funny.
They look like such jobbers.
I remember the E3 trailer being like, holy shit, look at those guys.
They look crazy.
When there's no lighting effects and they're just standing around.
Yeah, it's like, yeah, you kind of do look like a bootleg action figure.
They're so humble, Kamui.
Oh shit, this scene is awesome.
Really?
Creepy.
Man, Kakihara is so cool.
For reals, Kakihara is the shit.
Asano is kicking ass, too.
He's totally losing his shit.
Actually, I don't really care for Japanese movies.
Even though you're Japanese?
Yeah, but still, I just don't like them much.
I guess I kind of like the serialized dramas a bit more.
Okay, then.
How about the Girls X Heroines series?
What's that?
I recommend Maji Majo.
Can't go wrong with Maji Majo.
It even beats Bizarre Jelly.
No, I mean like Aibo, Tokyo Detective Duo and stuff.
Aibo?
You mean the Aibo where Miike guest starred in season 10, episode 16?
You've got good taste.
I only have season 10, episode 16.
But let's watch it together, you guys.
Want something to drink?
Okay, I'll take a mango cola.
Nice.
I'll have one, too.
Oh, man.
Ooh, I got a t-shirt.
Nice.
Let's get this out on a tray.
Let's get this out onto a tray.
Why did you say that?
What the fuck?
Now I'm gonna only think about that for the next two hours.
I can't.
Oh.
Yeah, I've probably seen every single one of his videos up until like a year or two ago.
I've seen almost every single one.
I used to listen to those videos before.
I would just put them on repeat, just go straight through them all while I was about to go sleep.
He always loves the cigarettes, right?
So I was like, oh, man, there's cigarettes in here.
These old cigarettes.
And I'd be like, oh, what kind of cigarettes?
I actually like that.
On instant coffee, yeah, the coffee, too.
It's like, is the coffee good?
You still drink it?
I want the devolver burger.
It's just my favorite color.
Sorry, if you have a shirt that has my favorite color in the world, I'm gonna wear it.
You see, the Civil War hardtack was wild.
I don't think so.
I don't remember.
Germacolor is mint toothpaste.
Yeah, just really too bad that they don't have the aqua fresh orange shower clean
shower for your mouth toothpaste anymore.
I can't find it.
I don't know where it is.
It sucks.
That's a lot of subs.
Mystic mushroom.
Thanks for the 20 community subs.
20 community subs.
Appreciate it.
20 subs.
And I have enough to do this.
Yep.
Haven't heard that reference in a while.
I think about that toothpaste all the time.
It was white and orange and an orange stripe and it had this flavor.
It was almost like a minty citrus kind of flavor.
And it just foamed up and made these insane
awesome like minty tingly foam bubbles in your mouth.
Why would they ever get rid of that?
It was awesome.
No, it wasn't like candy flavored.
It was mint.
But it was just a small hint.
Tiny hint of this kind of orange flavor.
It was too good for the plebs.
Oh, that's sad.
You didn't say community subs in the goofy voice.
Oh, sorry.
I got community subs.
Astor, I'll kill him.
Please let me kill him.
Still fighting in your dreams.
If you're going to kill someone, you got to go full on.
Tag team version of the infamously STO move.
Back when New Japan was at its peak, Hashimoto and Ogawa simply owned it.
The one tag team surpassing the fabulous Freebirds
has got to be Hashimoto and Ogawa.
Has to be.
All right, let's go.
I think I'm going to unlock the last area of the game right now.
That's how Neelix would say.
Oh, I think so.
Scrumptious.
I just made the most delicious coffee.
Scrumptious cake.
On my home planet.
Everyone used to hate me for doing that.
When I first did the Neelix impression, everyone screamed at me.
And now you all want me to do it.
Now it's what I hear.
Do the Neelix impression.
Even though when I did the Neelix impression, like two years ago,
like 3,000 people left the stream.
And I was told, I'm going to unfollow the channel if you do that again.
Lenny the person, thanks for the 10.
Go to call of battle.
Where is that?
Didn't I get some new cards?
I think I did.
Pretty sure I got a couple of cards.
Aqua Fresh, extreme clean whitening toothpaste.
It exists.
But is it orange?
And do you have to buy it on Amazon or eBay?
Didn't get any?
Secondhand toothpaste.
Say Aaron.
You guys hate something until I do it enough times
and then you want me to do it.
How about this?
I will trade you one Aaron.
How's that?
I only picked up two scorpions the whole game.
Call of battle.
So easy.
Do the sunflower joke.
Oh, I have to go back here.
All right.
Let's not spend very much time here.
Let me get the missions done.
See you spoke again.
That's good enough for me.
Figure out try a new one.
I figured out try a new one today.
What the fuck?
Do it.
That doesn't last so much longer.
Hey, can you untry that please?
Goodness.
Oh, I got you with another one.
Didn't I?
I don't know where I am.
Do it.
Oh, my fucking God.
This camera's stuck in the goddamn wall.
I don't have any heels left.
Whoa.
Is he going to walk in it?
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Good night.
This fucking motherfucker just ruined everything.
Are you kidding me?
I'm in the middle of Mustang mode.
This guy hits me from behind.
Are you shitting me?
Why are you still alive?
Why?
Full green mode standing by.
Oh, nice.
Let's go.
Why is it off?
All right.
This has been really confusing.
Okay.
What system is this on?
This is on the Nintendo Switch.
See?
Whatever.
Just skip it.
I'm still wearing this bathrobe,
but it's so uncomfortable.
Nintendo Switch.
Daniel Bryan just walked out at AEW.
What?
Are you serious?
Are you fucking with me?
Are you kidding though?
Like, is that really happening?
Holy shit.
Do you stream naked because it's a fetish?
I stream naked because it's hot in Nevada.
I'm not naked.
I just want to shit on it.
Show me good time, okay?
Spin death throw.
Death melt shower.
I take him.
Hodge.
Screw bucket death kick.
Death melt shower.
There it is.
A hundred.
Knock him out.
We get a 200 hit combo right now.
Grab him.
You motherfucker.
I'm actually infuriated over this one.
Fuck.
Screw bucket kick.
Spin death throw.
Hodge.
Special kill.
Get him.
150 at least.
Where am I?
God damn it.
This fucking camera.
Let me get to 200.
Come on.
Don't kill him.
200.
Let me see it.
There it is.
All right.
I got 200 to combo.
I'm fine.
I'm happy.
I get stuck in between the cars and the trucks.
I love the idea of having to reload the sword from a design perspective.
You know it was actually a lot harder in the other games.
It took a lot longer and you had to stay still.
During some boss fights it was hell.
You'd have to just sit there standing still just boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom.
Kind of like doing a whetstone in Monster Hunter.
But it took a little longer.
Will you ever stop streaming?
You mean permanently?
Eventually?
Yeah.
Probably one day.
I mean tonight.
I mean not right now.
Maybe in a little bit.
I mean we all permanently are going to stop doing stuff permanently at one point.
Change what you're doing.
Do something new.
I don't know.
I don't have any plans on when that will be.
I just know that eventually maybe it will happen.
You know I'm a human.
I kind of want to do the tank.
The alligator thing again.
I'm going to do this and then go see if I have another mission for the alligator.
That looks like it's kind of fun.
Who will you give the channel to?
I have like a son or a daughter.
Germa985 continues.
Greg Elbertson.
That was a little explodey thing.
Ooh.
Utopia coins.
Get another 100 hit combo.
I'll take it.
Do a charity auction for your channel.
I don't think so.
I don't think I want to do that.
That would be invincible.
I just kicked him out of the thing I wanted to keep him in.
Am I still invincible?
Nope.
No.
I thought I was still invincible.
Oh that's annoying.
Good.
1.5x attack power.
No it's just going to exist.
Nobody has to own it.
It's just going to exist though right?
That's bad in my way.
They already have skin?
Greg don't.
What is he hitting me with?
How many healing items are there?
Old green standing by.
What's happening?
What's going on?
What?
His screen was like frozen.
I'll give you $10 for the channel.
As you know this channel is worth $2 to $5 billion or like $100 billion.
We looked at it last time.
What's the channel worth I think?
What's my collective online internet channel's worth collectively?
If like a company were to wake up tomorrow morning with all of my logins and it's theirs.
I'm going to say a clean $20 million.
Not even close probably.
$20 million.
$10 million?
You think that's more than a million?
What do you think?
My channel?
$8 million?
$6 million?
$750,000?
$1 million?
Okay.
$3 million?
$2 million?
You're slowly coming down.
Well you're collectively slowly coming down.
It started at like $10-$20 million and now it's like you guys are being like,
actually no not even close.
It keeps going like $10.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
This is the auction now.
I know what this channel is worth.
Priceless.
How's that sound?
I'd like to get down there though so I could like actually do the mission.
It's just priceless.
To me.
$10 million or go fuck yourself.
To where I stand.
And we're off.
A $20 gift card.
It's not worth anything without you.
Oh man that was like actually.
I mean we're all just fucking around.
I'm just messing around here but damn I like I felt that one.
I did.
He's getting a big head.
Now anytime I feel like I'm getting a big head I just like pull the,
I just open up the little thing in the back of my neck and let some air out.
You gotta let the air out every now and then you do.
A nice dad joke.
Thanks.
All right somebody said this was actually hard.
Oh we'll see how hard.
Okay here we go.
Alligator attack.
This one's the hard one.
Two full minutes.
Focus on this guy first before the red guy.
I don't know how close he needs to get to kill me.
I wouldn't say this one's particularly harder than the last one.
Nice.
That was close.
If I didn't get the devil it might not have done it.
Take the gold.
5,500.
Nice.
Is there another one after that?
What do I?
I need 45,000.
So I got a long way to go actually.
I need some more missions.
I'll do the mission over here.
What's your favorite Star Trek?
I actually have only watched.
I'm probably gonna make a lot of people mad and I think I've said this before but you know
there's a lot of new people here.
So Star Trek Voyager is the Star Trek that I actually watched the whole thing through.
I've seen a fair amount of The Next Generation.
I've seen one clip from the original series
because it was in a Jim Carrey movie and I've not seen anything after that.
I especially have not seen the Star Trek Rick and Morty edition.
I've seen that one.
I don't know anything about that one.
I don't know anything about it.
I saw an advertisement for it.
I really thought it was a Rick and Morty episode.
That's it.
Roll crazy.
Don't throw crazy.
No, not anymore.
What's the...
What came after Next Generation?
Was it Voyager?
Oh, Deep Space Nine.
That's right.
I think I've seen some Deep Space Nine.
Not very much but I've seen a little bit.
What's the one with Why Was Six Afraid of Seven?
Because Seven Eight Nine.
What was it?
Who's that?
Is that Deep Space Nine?
That's Voyager.
Careful.
Oh, boy.
I'm in trouble.
He's got cubes.
Your next lot effect will always be Mustang.
Good.
You're reading chat too much.
You would love Deep Space Nine.
You would love Quark.
He loves gambling.
I don't love gambling.
I just heavily enjoy RNG and Rift.
I want to kill this guy back here.
So much health.
Good.
Welcome back.
Excuse me.
What's happening on my face?
Oh, he hit me with one of the parasites, right?
I'm reading a bio paper right now.
Thanks for the relaxing fight sounds.
Hey, you're welcome.
I'm about to fight the Nameless King for the first time.
Don't tell him.
All right.
I think I have enough now.
Just barely enough.
There's another fight mission over here.
I need to refill my sushi because it's gotten me killed like two times now.
Straight ahead.
Are you ever going to do anything familiar to the dollhouse in the future?
Probably not.
I'm going to do something hopefully to that scale.
I want to do that more often.
I kind of like to move on to the next thing.
Hey, come what?
How would you jump that far?
I'm trying to stay away from him.
Whatever.
But I talked about this a few streams ago.
It doesn't have to be that scale every time.
I want each calendar year to have a couple of smaller scale streams,
a couple of mid scale streams, and a couple of large scale streams.
This is all right.
Well, space peacock.
Super giant bird monster.
Be sure to reveal his weak spot.
Watch him closely.
Something's got to be hiding in those colorful chairs.
Is this Simon?
It's Simon Says.
Hey, fly for shy.
Thanks for the 10 community subs.
Wait, those are tier three.
Holy shit, dude.
10 tier three subs.
What are you doing?
Thank you.
That's crazy.
Where'd he go?
Watch it.
This guy's much more difficult than the other one.
Oh, my god.
It's a lot to pay attention to.
I can't.
You know what's freaking me out about this?
I can't move forward or backward.
I can only move up or down.
I wonder if the color is any purple.
I think it was purple.
It is purple.
All right.
Yeah, I understand.
How do I get away from that?
It's gone.
Time for red.
Go kill.
Jesus.
Where are you going?
Now what?
Yellow.
My health.
Yikes.
Super kill.
Blue.
First blood.
What is phase two going to be like then?
Oh, he's sucking me up.
Phase two.
What is it?
Super.
Right in the middle?
In the head?
In the back?
Oh, my goodness.
I don't know.
And just floating around in between these stupid killers.
The back.
Ay, yi, yi.
Oh, my god.
It sucks to have to do this.
Oh, I need to hit it one more time.
That was actually hard.
I got 50 subs.
Bill one shallow.
I got 50 community subs.
That's a lot.
And 20 tier two?
Who gives 20 tier two?
Fly for Shy gives 20 tier two.
That was 10 tier three from Fly for Shy.
20 tier two from Fly for Shy.
And then 50 tier one from Bill one shallow.
And then, oh, my goodness gracious.
That's absurd.
That's a lot.
Tier threes and tier twos.
Thanks a lot, guys.
I got enough money.
It is time to do the next boss.
And then after that boss, we're going to call it.
I'm going to get the scorpion right now.
I'm not going to overthink it.
I'm just going to get it.
I don't even overthink it.
Just stay behind him.
And got it.
Silver.
I'm going to get out of here.
I'm going to have to run all the way back here.
Yeah.
We'll conclude today's stream after this fight and cut scenes and everything.
And then I'll see you guys on Friday.
The launch of WarioWare.
And then we'll finish No More Heroes the next day.
I'm just trying to get here as fast as I can.
I don't even care.
When are you going to play Freddy Fish?
I don't know, dude.
I swear to god if this guy dies before we get to see who it is.
We have to assume it's going to happen now, right?
Do a prediction?
Yeah, do a prediction.
I don't know, wait.
I'll pause it before we see.
So much.
Does this guy get baited and they die before we fight him?
Yes or no?
I have so much energy.
I'll go win.
Go, Lee.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
If you already played the game.
This is not an exclusive stream of the game that no one's ever done.
What am I talking about?
Half of you guys could have already beaten this game.
And just get free points.
Damn.
Okay, well, we're going to upgrade.
You could also just Google it.
Yeah, don't do a prediction.
That's right.
If you lost that prediction, then I think that holy shit, something would be wrong, right?
Oh, no.
Or that person really is just trying to play along.
And they don't want to go look it up.
So they actually have altruism.
And they're actually like a good person.
Points have been ruined by coin flips anyways.
All right, what do we got?
I'm going to say...
Attack, battery.
That's a lot.
I'll do attack.
Attack or health?
Health.
Do I have enough for attack or another health?
I do.
Dang.
I have the sushi I need.
And I can do it anyways after that.
Let's just go.
I can guess for debt off.
Or if I'm wrong, debt gets added.
The call of battle.
100 million if you get it right.
100 million on it.
No, it's not worth it.
500 million off if you guessed right.
But I can just Google it.
And just go to the bathroom in quotes.
That's not fair.
Why would you spoil the game for yourself?
Yeah, that's also true.
Well, I mean, half a billion dollars of debt taken off is worth it.
Shortcut.
Not doing it.
I want to experience this game the way I want to experience the way it should be played.
Doing it at my own pace.
My own time.
My own...
Yes.
Here we go.
So this would be rank number four.
So then on Saturday we will have three ranked battles to do
before getting to the end of the game.
I don't think I have enough money to buy sushi.
Yeah, I've got five heals.
Wait, is this a...
Yeah, I got five heals.
I can't afford the eat-in sushi that I want.
Plus, I don't want to waste money.
I think I don't want to.
Can I make the prediction just for fun?
Sniper Lee is going to get sniped in the head by somebody that's another sniper.
This is going to be a different sniper.
Here we go.
Let's find out.
There's a similar area in the other game.
Is he holding the Enterprise?
He did.
He got sniped.
Wow, I should have bet 500 billion.
I should have bet half a billion dollars.
Why did I not do that?
I should have bet it.
It's so...
I knew it was going to happen.
Why does this keep happening?
I'm Notorious.
You're tough.
What's your story?
I'm a superhero from Earth.
And also, I'm the WWWWW Heavyweight Champion.
Holy shit!
This guy's a famous pro wrestler.
Are you really THE Notorious?
Like, for reals?
Yeah, I had a couple of overlapping road shows
and was a little late arriving for the whole threat to the planet thing.
My apologies.
You don't have shit to apologize for, man.
But listen, I kind of feel like a hunter who's had his kill stolen from him.
It pains me to hear this.
After all, eliminating external threats is a superhero's duty.
Are you really an actual superhero?
Yeah, I'll be it part-time.
But I am indeed a superhero.
Champion, please, let me take the fight from here.
You go wait in the back.
Champion, I can't do that.
My duty is...
Protecting this town is the duty of the people living here.
And I accepted their challenge.
Oh, is this a...
And this is a big if.
But if I were to get killed, please finish this for me.
I will, Travis Touchdown.
Three left.
I can see that asshole's head on a stick already.
I'm glad you understand, champion.
The champion is you.
You're the real champion.
Oh, don't do it.
Don't do it.
Oh, they're just friends, okay.
I thought he was gonna like spin me around and throw me.
This one apparently got skipped.
Next up is the number three ranked assassin.
But this is going against the rules.
It's no fun without any boss fights, right?
Was that her eye or clipboard?
Whatever.
I guess he'll do.
Now go, Travis.
Burn.
Back to the Garden of Insanity once again.
Click.
Okay, um, hold on.
What the fuck is going on in this game?
Still images, man.
Something weird is coming.
Who is it now?
Switching to blue mode.
Our power system's functioning.
This silhouette.
It's been a while.
That's destroyed, man.
That's fucking destroyed, man.
They just had to put him in the game.
They had to find a way.
Another handshake.
Looks like the main character from Frisky Dingo.
The fight can't begin.
Come on.
No tricks.
What's that guy's name?
Can't trust you.
I'll look me in the eyes.
Come on.
Kill face, yeah.
Okay.
Fine.
Let's do this.
So they had a Switch boss fight into another Switch boss fight.
Seriously?
This guy seriously fell for it.
Why are we fighting this guy?
He just came out of the ground.
I don't understand.
This guy is seriously dumb.
He totally believed me.
Okay.
I'm going to die.
I'm going to laugh myself to death.
Oh, shit.
Who else?
Oh, I'm dying.
Oh, my god.
This guy is so stupid.
I don't fucking think so.
Oh, we didn't even get to fight him either.
Oh, it's all destroy man bots.
Just man versus machine.
Oh, god.
This is going to be horrible.
Mass produced destroy man.
Third time's the charm.
They'll attack and drove, so take them down with your death glove skills.
Don't underestimate that destroy cannon.
How many times is this guy going to come back to life with his head spinning like that?
He's freaking me out.
Ay, yi, yi.
Ow.
Wait, he sucks.
He's like falling down.
It's a Curly Larry and Moe.
One of them's just stupid.
Oh, almost to 777.
Let me get some.
I got to fight five and then number 10.
I like the sounds.
It sounds like I'm going to have a Game Boy.
How do I do the dodge?
Is it AA?
I thought it was AB.
Why did I do that?
I could have just killed that guy.
It's two, right?
Yep.
You hear me?
I thought it was AB at the same time.
It is AB at the same time.
You're a genius.
Thank you.
Oh, okay.
Battery.
Dodge that.
My mistake.
Invincible mode.
Let's go.
I don't think I'm invincible anymore.
Move.
There it is.
What is happening?
I just beat him with my incredibly powerful abilities.
What the fuck?
There are millions of them.
Maybe not.
This is pretty fucked up, Travis.
All battles must end.
Here we go.
Travis, get away from there.
What?
Jam.
I cast it.
Cannon.
Did you get him?
Located the enemy.
The real one is down below.
Leave this to me and get to Central Magna.
I don't really get it,
but I need to go down into that hole, I guess.
You got it.
Shit.
This is scary.
Meow.
The cat.
At least hold on to the cat.
Goodness.
Omega Destroy Man.
Now let's have a fair fight.
This is so dumb.
So this is the real one, huh?
This place.
It's been turned into a Destroy Man factory.
What the fuck are you even trying to do, you weird-ass bastard?
I'm Destroy Man, the superhero.
I destroy the evils of this world.
Evil assassin, Travis Touchdown.
I will destroy you.
Okay, let's go.
This dude is such an immature little bitch.
Even more than you.
This time, I'm really gonna mash up those brains of yours.
All right, real fight incoming.
Destroy!
Bring it on.
Ooh.
That was sneaky, wasn't it?
He's got a lot of health.
This is gonna be a long fight.
Okay, easy, easy, easy.
All right, I gotta run.
All right, dodge.
Holy shit, he just double tapped me.
I forgot they were in the air.
Okay, I gotta walk around.
Walk around.
Don't be an idiot.
I gotta check his moves out.
I gotta wait for this.
Okay, those have to get ran into the wall, for sure.
All right, let's go.
Fuck.
All those things are so hard to dodge.
That was a good spring.
All right.
Man.
He stunned?
I thought he stunned.
All right, phase two incoming.
Move back.
That's a huge AOE, okay.
All right, he's got a few more moves.
Destroy cannon.
I can't just outrun him.
Fuck.
Okay, that was really, really close.
That would have been bad.
I can't outrun those.
Oh, yeah.
Let's go.
That's lucky shit right there.
Let's move.
Oh, hell yeah.
I just killed him.
That was lucky shit right there.
Nice, okay.
Rolled sevens.
Easy.
Try man, true face.
Dead.
You just skipped the boss, pretty much.
Although, I'm not on the hardest difficulty though.
I'm on the medium difficulty.
There's a difficulty after this.
There's probably another difficulty after that when you beat the game.
So, the game probably gets a thousand times harder if you're on the spiciest.
I'm not on the spicy difficulty.
I'm not playing on easy, I'm playing on bitter.
Yeah, I was observant.
Thanks to you, I was able to stop him.
He was one tenacious dude.
Yeah, you got that right.
All right, champ.
Let's run.
Let's.
What the hell was that?
Yuck.
I was rocky.
Somebody said this seemed a little under tuned for what is medium effectively.
Can I really hire you to do this?
If it's a contract, I won't turn it down.
Kill this man.
Maybe a little.
What's the price tag?
Some of them have been pretty challenging.
30% of the total stock.
Convert it into cash, and you'll be a very rich man.
Sounds like a good plan.
I'll take the job.
The transfer is complete.
Confirmed.
When are you gonna do it?
Before the autumn winds blow.
Seriously, I'm really counting on you.
Please kill him.
No need to rush.
I was not getting hit by.
I.
All right, instead, I've.
I don't, I, whatever.
There's nothing I can really say right now.
This is just a series of weird dreams that Suda51 stitched together and made a video game.
Stuff has, stuff has like no beginnings or ends.
Just middles.
And then ends.
There's middles and ends.
It's just insane.
I love it though.
I think it's hilarious.
I think it's wonderful.
Always climaxing.
Yeah.
It's just out of context.
Everything.
No exposition.
Just context.
This is the best No More Heroes game so far.
You know.
Now that I'm almost done with it.
Like another probably few hours.
That really depends on what you want.
Because I think this experience has been the best one.
But I think the first game is more of like almost like a true video game than this one is.
This seems like a series of interesting things stitched together.
And the characters are all hilarious and everything is just funny and crazy and out of this world.
But I think the first one is actually like a like video game.
This feels less like a video game and more like almost like an interactive dream experience.
And this one has an actual open big open world to kind of go around.
If that's I'll be honest it's not that interesting.
The actual physical open world is not that I mean they put NPCs moving around
that you can run into with your car.
For me personally this is the best one.
But if you're more into I guess more of a structured video game.
The first two are probably what you're looking for.
This feels like a lot less structured than the other two.
But somehow I like it better than the other two.
I don't see Damon.
I heard from him in several days.
What happened with Sonic Juice?
It's more of a hub.
Yeah it's not it's more of a hub.
I cannot get a hold of Mr. Juice either.
He's probably off training again.
Sonic is a tough guy.
I mean it's my fight but still.
Okay there was something wrong with me there.
I spent too much time fucking around.
How many hours of gaming per day?
10 hours.
Oh wait that's too much.
That's too much playing.
It should be like an hour.
10 hours is too much.
I've gotten too caught up in gaming.
I'm sick of video games.
Wake up!
Who is it?
I'm still sleepy.
You can't even beat your desire to sleep huh?
He's just killed him.
He's just killing this guy.
And we're not going to be able to fight this one.
They just gave up on these bosses.
They just don't give a fuck about these bosses at all.
There's no rhyme or...
When I talk about structure this is what I was referring to.
There's zero structure.
It's just...
There's...
It's nothing.
It's just all...
Nobody matters.
Nothing matters.
Travis, Touchdown, and Fu are the only characters that matter in the game.
And maybe Damon as it...
Nothing else matters.
And something about that is kind of...
Refreshing in a way.
Like, who gives a shit about any of this?
You forgot about Gold Joe.
So now there are only two left?
Yeah, there's only two people left.
He uses his imagery to push back.
Without leaving all the work to Kudo's words.
Push back!
Charlotte!
Hey, you want a beer?
Revival!
Finally doing better, huh Charlotte?
Who calling me that?
It's a nice name.
It suits you.
Which Miike movie do you like?
I'm fucking killing you.
Miike?
For reals?
You don't know Miike?
He's like a film super director from Japan.
If it's Japanese stuff give me anime do you like?
Seriously?
Was that...
Was those two real shows?
Watching together.
Eisner though.
Let's drink.
Aye, aye, aye.
Okay.
What a mess.
This game is a mess.
It's wonderful.
Okay.
Well, I'm gonna save it here.
Wait.
Is there any new games with Gene?
Buy me a new ball.
Well, let's save it.
Alright.
That's gonna be it.
This has been wonderful.
We will finish this this coming weekend here.
I got a feeling there's probably at least another three hours left in the game.
Somewhere between two and four.
There's still an entire area that I have not been to.
I think.
So.
I'm assuming there's probably at least another two or three hours.
Three-ish hours?
Yeah.
So I'm not gonna complete it tonight.
So the next time you see this stream live we'll be playing WarioWare.
Get It Together.
At which I...
This has been insane.
Somebody said this the other day.
What?
I'm being spoiled.
Two of my favorite franchises.
I've had brand new games come out.
That have not had really new games come out in their series in a very long time.
I've been waiting for No More Heroes 3.
Like a game like this third person No More Heroes 3.
Since probably a year after No More Heroes 2 came out.
This is awesome.
I've been waiting for a real WarioWare game.
Since Smooth Moves.
So we're getting two 10-year sequels here.
In the first...
In the two weeks.
So I'm very excited.
I will see you guys soon.
Friday.
We're gonna be streaming at 2 p.m. Pacific on Friday.
I'm gonna pull it back.
I'm not gonna do 4 p.m. anymore.
I'm gonna pull it back to 2.
So I'll see you Friday.
We're gonna have a lot of community subs here through these credits.
Because there was a shitload of subs given.
And Psychonauts too.
Yeah I forgot about Psychonauts.
What's with the...
These games that have been celebrated for a decade.
That just all the sequels came out.
But if you're curious if you should buy No More Heroes 3 I would say yes.
Absolutely.
If you're a fan of this franchise and you think it's an interesting place.
Interesting concept.
It looks like there's a shitload of content that's not the actual main game either.
With the time machine to go back and fight bosses at a harder difficulty.
For materials.
That's cool.
Did you beat the game?
No I did not.
You will see the end of this game on Saturday of this coming week.
I want to make room for WarioWare.
Remember I am twice a week Andy.
It's only on the Switch.
As of right now No More Heroes 3 is only on the Switch.
So who knows if the coming next six months, year or whatever it might.
Show its face on PC or Xbox or something.
The other two did.
We'll see.
It makes it more special that it's on the Switch.
It's nice to see Nintendo have exclusives that are not just first party stuff.
Worth having the console for.
I think the Switch is a really good console but kind of adds just to it right?
It's time for tuna.
It is time for tuna.
A tuna melt.
Of all things.
What do I- hold on.
What kind of cheese am I going to get though?
Do I have cheese?
Oh shit this is a disaster.
This is a disaster in the making.
I don't know if I have cheese.
You can't have a tuna melt without the melt portion.
That doesn't work.
Uh oh.
That's bad news.
Do I have- I gotta see if I have cheese.
Alright I'm gonna go.
I'll see you guys on Friday.
Goodbye.
Good night.
Take care of yourselves.
Thanks for watching as always.
I'll see you soon.
Don't forget about me.
I won't forget about you.
No.
Good night.
I'll see you later.