What's up? How you doing?
There's a bird at my window. I- I- Sorry, I was like, one minute late.
I had to see it. I heard like, a tapping, like tap at the window.
I was like, this bird- Ah, it's a bird. It's definitely a bird.
I was like, I gotta see it. I missed him.
Didn't see the bird, unfortunately.
Uh, as you get- Listen to me. You hear the voice, right?
Kind of getting back to normal.
It's a little, uh, it's a little grungy, but, you know.
That's a good excuse.
So, uh, those of you that didn't know,
the reason why I've been gone for the last like, four or five days,
is specifically because I couldn't talk.
I was sick for about a week and a half,
with some type of cold or flu or something.
I tested negative for COVID.
That's a good thing.
But I- I blew out my voice.
The day after that last stream, I sounded like this.
I couldn't even talk.
It was- I blew my voice out somehow.
How am I talking now?
Um, because that was a week ago.
Gion Rivers, yeah.
No, the last ti- Yeah, don't we know?
When I turned the stream on last,
that's the last time that I was like, alive.
I just go into like, hibernation.
I go- You just power me off and then you turn me back on.
Hold on, I gotta get auto.
But no, I'm feeling a lot better.
I haven't been sick for probably at least a few days.
But I've just barely, last night into today,
I haven't had a just completely constricted, horrendous voice.
So I didn't want to talk.
So I'm trying to keep my mouth shut.
And here we are now.
I should be fine.
Scrap this shit for an auto stream.
Oh, I just want to like, chill and like, play flash games.
What do you mean, scrap this shit?
People have been asking for flash games for like, a year.
I'm not gonna play cyberpunk.
I probably- I don't know.
I probably will never play cyberpunk.
You want me to be honest?
It's probably cool.
I don't know.
Maybe eventually.
You mean like, look, I'm like-
I play new games a year after they come out.
Or like, at least a few months.
What is this?
Hold on.
Cyberpunk sucks.
Does it though?
I mean, I don't think it does.
Who told you that?
We had a bunch of subs come in.
Thank you, Nukable, Super Bruce, Bananarism, and TheFooly.
All for five community subs.
Back to back to back to back to back.
Thanks guys.
All bugs, no snacks.
But yeah, how- is it- is it any good?
Do a cheese and wine tasting stream.
I didn't even tweet this stream out yet.
Hold on.
Everybody- it says in the title, just chill, okay?
Five subs from any neb subs here.
I don't know.
Are there?
Jerma, please, we need the funny.
That's what I'm doing here, man.
I'm trying to come back so I can give you the funny.
I almost just like cough- like, flam-puked on you.
And that would have been horrible.
Some of you heard it.
Some of you were like, I heard that.
That was like phlegm coming up from like your esophagus
all the way into your mouth.
You heard it.
I know some of you did.
That's why it took a little bit of time.
Also, we have to talk really quickly about, of course,
that an anonymous gifter has given five community subs.
Besides that, in the Discord right now,
guess what channel just opened?
Come on, let's see some slugpogs.
Uh, the New Year's Eve nomination and discussion channel is open.
You're going to be able to nominate stuff.
Maybe even add categories.
It's just open for discussion.
It's going to be up there for another probably eight to ten days.
The voting will commence after that.
So you got about ten days to figure out your nominations for the year.
Cyberpunk in two hours?
I'm not- I don't care.
Look, I'm up playing Cyberpunk.
That's a Reddit game.
It's not a Reddit game.
No, that's a mainstream, huge video game.
So many people are waiting for that.
That's not just like Redditors that are waiting to play Cyberpunk.
That game had like 600 million pre-orders.
Only like 12 million people use Reddit.
Okay, I gotta- I gotta retweet this.
Hold on.
It's a Reddit game.
I just wrote Cyberpunk and then for like my stream,
but no, I can't do that.
That's misleading.
No, I'm not going to do that.
I'm not going to piss people off for no reason.
Although I kind of do that anyways sometimes.
I do that like for fun all the time.
I didn't even say a title.
I just wrote my stream.
Fuck.
It's been a week.
Give me a- give me a minute.
Flash games, dude.
I'm so high right now.
It took so much.
Flash games, dude.
I'm not- I'm kidding.
I'm not.
And then take- I haven't-
I have not consumed a marijuana product in probably three weeks, okay?
Relax.
Clip it.
You can play Dead Space?
Yeah, maybe like eventually before I turn 40.
Oh, I'm assuming that before I turn 40, I'll play Dead Space.
Oh, you'll see it before I turn 40.
All right.
You guys ready?
You guys ready for the-
I don't even- hold on.
Wait, let me make sure my-
Because I know everyone's going to freak out and be like,
dude, why do you not have click maps?
Come on, dude.
I'm going to have them, but I'm going to-
It's going to be streamer's choice and then your choice.
I'm on congregate and I'm on armor games.
If I missed one, please tell me I missed one.
But I'm just going to play some flash games.
Whatever. Let's go.
Let me just get the click maps running.
No, not Neopets.
Neopets is- I don't know.
I'm not playing Neopets.
Holy shit.
Like how- You know what I want to see?
Am I not logged into Twitch?
What the fuck?
I got logged out of Twitch?
Have I not been- Have I not opened it in like three- two weeks?
No, I have to like- Hold on.
You got to feed your little gremlin.
I don't- No, I don't want to do Neopets.
They'll die.
I'll do a Neopets stream.
We'll hang out for a little while.
And it'll be- Aw, cool.
You got like a little octopus buddy.
Dude, oh my god.
You fed him like his favorite treat.
Like octopus food.
Everyone will freak out and it'll be fine.
And then I'll never hear the end of it when after two or three weeks
when I don't play the game
and people say check on your Neopets and they're all dead.
You guys are going to be very upset with me
and I don't want to do that.
True. Yeah, I know.
I'm- I know.
Trust me. I know.
All right.
Let me turn on- Let me get click maps ready.
Because I know everyone's going to say,
do it, do it, do it.
You're fucking making me so angry.
You're pissing me off Jeremy.
There's no click maps.
I'm going to punch you in the mouth.
I'm going to punch you as hard as I can in the mouth.
Like, all right.
Well, just relax.
It's in the title.
Okay.
Uh, shall we?
What should I start with?
Kongregate or Armored Games?
I guess it doesn't really matter, right?
We'll go to Armored Games first.
Why are people already doing click maps?
Stop clicking on the screen.
It's not ready yet.
Stop clicking.
I have to- I just turned it off.
Viruses everywhere.
There's no viruses here.
Relax.
It's in the title.
Come on, quit.
Hey, we get it.
You smoke.
I don't.
So what should I play?
What we got?
These are new games.
How about Bouncy Quest?
Is Bouncy Quest any good?
Has anybody played Bouncy Quest?
I don't know.
Let's try it.
Oh, can I make this full screen?
Please tell me I can.
Turn it on.
I just did.
Loading.
Okay.
Is there a full screen in- on, uh, Armored Games?
Ow!
This just happened in real life.
I- that's- I seriously feel like I got hit in the head by a frying pan.
I got hit right in the fucking head by a frying pan.
I gotta turn this on in my mixer.
I- I know that's- I feel like that's what it would feel like.
Jesus.
I end up with like-
Okay.
Is that better?
Am I gonna zoom this shit in?
The hell?
I have to manual zoom?
Is a dev in chat?
No, no, no.
Leave it.
What do you mean leave it?
Control plus.
No, I- I'm gonna- I'm gonna do a manual zoom.
No.
Hey, we're doing the Game Awards tomorrow, by the way.
Those of you that make it excited over that one.
All right.
We got the manual zoom.
What the fuck?
What just happened?
I'm supposed to be playing Bouncy Quest.
Did I just open up like an ad page?
Okay.
Wait.
Now it's not zoomed in for me, though.
This needs to be zoomed in.
Oh, I need to do a manual zoom on my own.
Control plus, right?
Okay.
I got it.
I manual zoom.
I have to manual zoom and then I'm gonna manual zoom you out.
Omega low.
Quiet.
All right.
That was-
Now we're fine.
We're playing Bouncy Quest.
All right.
How do we play?
Oh, this has got a good soundtrack.
Super foil.
Thanks for the 10 community subs.
Level select.
Level one.
Bouncy Quest.
How do you play Boun-
How do you play?
Save your-
Use the arrow keys to move.
Okay.
There's one.
It's not centered.
All right.
Just hold on.
I'm trying.
I'm working on it.
There.
Is it better?
That's better.
Okay.
We're fine.
All right.
Let's go.
Hey, Syrophunk.
No.
Fuck Syrophunk.
We're playing Bouncy Quest.
Play this is the only level.
Watch out for spikes.
This is fun.
I like this.
How do you jump higher?
That one's extra bouncy quest.
This is the only level.
Obviously, this is level four.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Watch out for enemy slime.
Jump on to eliminate.
I said that right, right?
Eliminate.
Did I say that wrong?
That was weird, right?
Thank you for winning those.
What?
This dude is zonked.
I'm not zonked.
Dude, when does Syrophunk come out?
Oh, dude.
Syrophunk.
What?
When they-
Do not leap when they sleep.
Hey, I got a cyber game for you.
Hey, guys.
I got a cyber game early.
Oh, he did, didn't he?
Does he get an early copy of-
Does he have a copy of a game
that people don't have right now?
I wonder what that could be.
Of course.
I mean, please don't be naked.
Of course, I'm talking about Siberia.
27, 2027.
Siberia, the year 2027 for the 3DO.
You don't think I came prepared
for the launch of-
This is the right one, right?
This is the right one.
Mom, your mother at GameStop
that buys you the wrong game.
No, mom.
I didn't want the SpongeBob game.
I wanted GTA.
Henry, you're 14.
Mom, buy me that game
where you can see naked people.
Hey, idiot.
What?
Fuck, hold on.
This game's cool.
Siberia.
You got an emote.
I did?
Why?
Make sure you-
Do the nominations, guys.
Make sure you get some nominations
and you only got like 10 days.
How do I keep dying from the same person?
It's like, have I not-
Have I not burned in my memory
that that person is here?
This music's pretty good, though, I will say.
What's this game called?
Bouncy Castle?
Dev here?
Where's the dev?
Do you want to know where the dev is?
Certified idiot.
What?
I'm doing fine.
I'm fine.
Look at chat.
Stop!
Leave me alone.
No screaming.
My voice is gone.
I just looked over at chat.
I have not had any Marijuana products
in like three weeks, okay?
Relax.
Thank you BBB for the five community-
A lot of community subs today.
What are you guys doing?
I think I'm done with-
Okay.
I'm done with fucking Bouncy Quest.
I swear to God, I'm not like pretending.
I gotta beat this level, though.
I'm not pretending.
By the way, speaking of pretending,
that is a new category in the 2020
Vest of Worst of the Year.
In your nominations for the new category of Worst,
he is pretending moment where you thought
I had to have been making it up.
There's no way it would be fake.
There's no way it would be real, I mean.
I'm not.
I swear to God.
I promise.
Bouncy Louncy?
What?
I had timed that person out.
I don't know what they said.
All right, I'm done.
I'm done with Bouncy Castle.
I don't want to play it anymore.
No more Bouncy Castle for me.
This is so easy.
And I just-
I'm just like not paying attention.
Pay attention.
I'm so glad I didn't decide to play Spelunky 2 today.
It's just not one of those days, right?
You can already tell.
It's not one of those days.
I beat it, see?
Are you gonna cry on New Year's?
What?
What are you talking about?
Jump on top to break.
It's one.
Wink.
Stop breaking them, you dickhead.
I'm gonna do what I'm gonna do.
Can you see the mouse?
Oh, shit.
That's what everybody was yelling at me for.
Sorry.
Everybody was screaming at me.
They were like,
Get it off the screen.
Get it off.
All right, I gotta beat one more level in Bouncy Quest
and then we're gonna move on to the next one.
Whatever it is.
I don't know.
I'm like-
No, we're done.
How about Idle Racing?
Simplified racing game where you don't actually race
but manage cars, garages, and races.
Each race has its upgrades in racing.
Our choice now.
Okay.
Well, it has to be on a page.
Let me choose.
All right, well, okay, hold on.
You guys wanna choose one here?
Okay, you guys can choose one here.
Go ahead.
Today?
Oh.
Make him do a puzzle game.
Because there's zero waiting room.
I'll go back to that-
I'll go back to that after the game awards.
Just let one random person choose.
Maybe I'll do that eventually.
I'm just hanging out today.
I'm just trying to ease back into it, man.
All right, looks like we have-
I mean, I said I-
The streamer said the thing.
So that's why everybody clicked it, right?
I guess we're gonna do Idle Racing for a little while.
See how much I like it.
Hey, Under Armour, thanks for the five-
That's not your name.
Under Andrew, thanks for the five community subs.
All right, we'll do an Idle Racing.
Thanks for voting.
See if this game's any good.
Rigged.
I wasn't rigged.
Play This Is The Only Level.
All right, I'll play This Is The Only Level in like a-
In a minute.
Idle Racing, buy your first car and start-
Hold on.
You guys, this is way too-
This is messed up here.
Hold on.
You're gonna play the game I want.
All right, that's better, right?
I probably will eventually.
You just gotta be patient.
Okay, buy your first car and start racing.
Go to dealer.
No sponsor.
Compact car.
I like those.
Family car.
No sponsor.
City car.
Or off-road.
Let us pick.
No.
All right, well, I wanna do a city car.
Probably, I don't know, the Simpsons car?
Okay, I'm gonna do the Simpsons.
Homer Simpson's car.
How much money do I have?
Where's my money?
City, 5300.
Wait, is this an ad?
Go to the dealer.
Buy your first-
No sponsor.
Compact.
Oh, I just have to get one of these.
I don't have-
Oh, I have-
Where's my money?
This is how much money I have.
Oh, okay, it's up there.
It's a little too big.
Hold on.
Just look, you fucking dope.
Okay, I'm just gonna get a basic compact car.
One acceleration, one speed,
one hindrance.
Bought it.
Okay, now we go to the race.
This one here, free race.
First place gets $50.
Takes five seconds.
Select my car.
I'm gonna be using-
The winning chance is bad on this one,
but okay, race.
Okay, I'm done.
Give me another one.
I don't wanna do this.
I wanna get a better one.
This game's-
I don't know.
This is like a game that you sit on the toilet
and play for like four hours.
All right, give me another one.
What was it called?
This is the Only Level?
Should I play that one?
Or do Simpocalypse?
Streamer's Choice.
Guys, I'm gonna be here all night.
We're good.
I'll be here for like at least five hours.
This is the demo version.
Standalone game with all unlocked features
is coming to Steam on December 15th, 2020.
Uh-oh.
So, should I play the demo?
What if I like it?
Sign up for the beta.
Hold on, it's too zoomed in.
I'm not gonna put my email in anywhere.
How would I put my email in?
Do it, do it.
Guys, you got-
Some of you might remember,
back in the day,
there would be a mall.
Just, they would-
Well, of course, there would be a mall.
You know, back then when there were malls.
At your mall,
there used to be a little drop box
where you would just sign up to try to win something.
You would put all your information on it
and drop it into a little box
and hope you like got like your name on a list or something.
Or you got where-
This is like-
This is dropping your name in that like mall box
of signing up for shit.
Just, you're just giving an email to somebody.
And what are they gonna use it for?
Are they gonna tell you about beta testing?
They might.
It's not a bad analogy.
No, it's not.
Maybe you just write their full addresses and shit
and put it in that slot.
Your email address is your like on-
Your email address is your online address.
You don't want anybody to have that shit that you don't want.
That's why it's called email address.
It's your internet e-address.
No, it's not.
Yes, it is.
You gotta be careful.
Don't fuck around.
That's your IP.
No, it's not.
It's your email address.
The world as you know it is gone.
Human greed inevitably led to war.
After 10 years, the radiation settled down
enough for small groups of survivors to start coming out of their nuclear shelters.
You are the leader of one of them.
Okay.
Everything is ruined.
Resources seem gone.
But this must not be our end.
Explore and establish your settlement to survive.
Good luck.
Okay.
Starting boost.
Select your home continent.
Start in Africa.
Plus 30% faster builders suggested.
Australia.
Plus 20% mining rate.
Europe.
Plus 20% knowledge gain.
Asia.
Plus 30% citizen gain.
North America.
Plus 50% lower market spread.
Antarctica.
Plus 40% water gain.
Uh, the mining.
Let's do North America.
I don't know.
50% lower market spread.
Whatever.
Start exploring.
Get out of your shelter and start exploring for resources to survive the post-apocalyptic era.
Your group of survivors is small, but maybe you can find others.
Start by exploring the area around your shelter.
There have to be resources we can use around here.
I'm not nexting already.
What?
We did that already.
Start...
Assign some explorers.
Okay.
Assign some citizens to focus on exploring and look for resources.
And mom, don't next me yet.
I'm not ready.
Okay, so I want to put...
Assign explorers.
Okay, they're exploring.
Scavengers.
Assign citizens to start collecting food for your explorers.
Oh, this is cool.
It's just like a...
Everyone, you kind of spread people out to do different tasks and stuff.
It's an idle game.
I know.
All right.
Just let me...
Give me a minute.
Let me see how good it is.
And have one scavenger.
I'm seeing a lot of resident sleepers and it's really starting to make me self-conscious as a streamer.
Let's go with five scavengers.
It's making me look a little self-conscious.
Water and food are critical.
Drinking water.
Oh, um...
Okay, I guess...
You know when you get yourself in trouble here?
I was too lazy to type in armorgames.com.
I searched Armor Games.
Is Armor Games a safe website?
I couldn't just write armorgames.com.
No.
I had to search for it and then click on it.
That's lazy, but that's lazy for all the wrong reasons.
Because it's adding extra steps.
That's kind of bizarre.
Okay, what should I play?
What's this on the front page?
This is...
Oh wait, popular games.
Here we go.
Raid Heroes.
Total War.
Mob Wars.
Which one of these is actually, like, should I play?
This is not the only level.
This is not...
Please sort by god.
What?
Sort by god.
All games.
Action games.
Wait, hold on.
Adventure games.
There is no game.
Did we do that one?
Yes.
Okay.
If you like this non-game, go check out the Steam page.
What do you mean, Steam page?
Is this another one of those you sign up for the beta because there's a demo?
Better with audio.
Is this a crosshair?
Not a game.
By Kamizoto.
Probably not made with constructs.
There is no game.
I was feeling very leave.
There's no game.
So I hope you're not too much disappointed.
You can still watch TV, go outside, read a book, ask for refund.
And that game is free.
This is not a game.
It has nothing to do with the game.
It's just a massive package of boredom.
Okay, cool.
So I just sit here and let this guy give me comedy lines, right?
There's nothing to do in here.
Start clicking on stuff?
You can quit and leave me alone.
Sorry.
What have you done?
You've just ruined the title.
Put it back.
Put the latter back.
Okay.
No.
Come on.
I'm trying to put the letter back, dude.
Never mind.
I will fix it next time someone reloads the game.
Non-game.
No game here.
No game.
He said no game.
Click game.
No game.
Do I have to refresh the page?
Pop right.
Delete the Y.
What?
What is this?
I can't click it.
Use the O.
What?
Delete the A.
I can't do anything.
There is no game-o.
I don't know.
There-o-e-o is...
Duh.
What do I do?
Oh, shit.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Seriously.
Are you going to break everything?
I muted him.
That was horrible.
Finally.
Well, I get it.
You're trying to kill me.
Am I putting like a bag over his head?
As you love to click everywhere.
What do you think about that?
All right.
I have to crush him.
I can still get it.
Stop it now.
I think we're good.
Sorry.
I had to use the sort of procedures, but I had to.
I love the voice.
I love the accent.
He sounds like, oh, what's his name?
Oh, my God.
I'm trying to bring that one.
Oh, it's his name.
Peter.
Oh, Peter.
It's Peter.
What is it?
Peter.
Oh, he's in...
What's the game with the horror game?
Yes.
Stormer.
Peter Stormer.
I love that accent.
It's great.
You're a stubborn as a mule.
Call Superman for that one.
What's his name?
I don't know.
Stormer?
Stormerage.
Stormare?
I know Superman does not exist, but as we're in a game...
No, we're not.
The guy from Fargo?
You're still there.
Wait, what?
You're thinking about how to live that big days on you.
Check this shit out, guys.
Now you get audio cues as to how fast I can do that.
What was that?
What were they doing?
Oh, pick up the O and drop the O there.
Grab the E.
Grab the H.
It's going to be a screamer.
I don't think so.
It's a hit sound?
It kind of is, isn't it?
It is a hit sound.
Yeah, you have Pyro running around holding down the button.
You just turn the corner on Dust Bowl,
and you don't even care if you instantly explode.
The final point on Dust Bowl,
when there's like four engineers with four sentry guns pointing at you,
you just turn the last corner,
and even though you're dead in a half of a second,
you hold the button down and you hear this.
And then you hear...
You're like, yeah, yeah, you're still on fire.
Oh, you fucks.
Oh, shit.
Yes, yes, go on.
This is for my life.
What the mess?
These screws?
I hope you will clean the place before living.
Just what do you think you're doing, Yuzuru?
This is pretty cool.
There is a game.
Don't look.
It's private.
You're going to do a terrible mistake.
There is a game.
I can spell it.
Oh, cool.
This is one of my favorite games.
Breakout.
Don't play, it's forbidden.
If you play, they will come.
I don't want them to come.
What?
They can kill me, you know?
Please.
Oh, arrow keys.
How do I move?
Oh, bug snacks.
Bug snacks ending.
What do you mean?
There's a fun game.
What?
Oh, fuck.
I mean, nobody lists stuff.
Oh, shit.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
What do I say?
What do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do, what do I do?
What do I do, what do I do?
Bug snacks ending like when I ended the stream and I like fucking...
I like played Breakout at the end of that stream.
I must find a way to stop you.
No, there's no one talking about like a game ending.
Like any spoilers or anything.
I like ended the stream.
And I like went, fuck, I'll play Breakout, who cares?
Dude, without the ball.
That was a bad save.
Look, I'm...
No more ball.
Who cares?
Actually, I almost just dropped it.
Leave now, please.
I don't feel well.
What was he talking about?
I'm going to be sick.
We just like kind of spoiled the end of bug snacks.
So I just desperately tried to pretend like we did.
The one person that doesn't think that we did.
Oh, no.
They're here.
Glitches.
He said, we.
Well, somebody did.
And then I just read it because I'm stupid.
I told you to stop.
You must find a way to get rid of them.
How is this even remotely like that, by the way?
How is it...
This doesn't make any sense.
How can I become self-success with all the glitches?
Think, think, think.
What the developer will implement will sell a bugged creation.
I'm not talking about spoilers.
I see three possible things.
Gorgeous armed hero girls.
Or a ton of zombies and brood, of course.
Or a goat.
Cyberfunk is out.
I know, but try to find one of these three things.
OK, so we have to find...
Does it find a goat?
Perhaps the letters can help us.
There is a goat.
Sexy girls and zombies.
OK, it's attractive in a way.
All right, well, well, we got to go now, all right?
Obviously, the cage is locked.
You must find the key.
All right, we need a key.
Key, key, key, key, key.
Can I spell key?
Key!
Get it!
Hey!
That flying squirrel took it.
You must get it back.
Find a ladder or something to go up.
Something to go up.
Something you can climb.
What can I climb?
That reminds me of my childhood.
Can I spell it?
You used to climb a huge tree in the garden to get back my kite.
Yes, I know what you're trying to do.
Climb a tree?
Climb a waterfall?
Well, this is a small tree.
And finally, it was bigger.
How do I get a big tree?
All right, I'm going to take it over here.
Can I bring water over here?
There's water here.
All right, I need to bring the water over here.
How can you bring water to that tree?
Bucket.
A container.
A box.
I'm going to bring water over here.
I need a bucket.
The rope?
That's five letters, man.
Yeah, I'm going to drink it, and I'm going to come back over and regurgitate it into the tree.
I need to see the words.
Let me see the letters.
I'm more water.
Trophy.
Read chat.
The trophy.
Oh, oops.
Backseaters.
What?
I didn't know it was actually...
Okay, whatever.
Give me some more.
Keep going.
More.
Save the goat.
I'm...
That's what I'm trying to do, isn't it?
Trying to save the goat.
We fucking finally did it.
Hey, I...
This is...
Give me that key.
And then you go over to your friend's house, and they have a fucking really annoying hit sound,
and you just have to play on their terrible hit sound,
and they think it's funny, but you think it's annoying.
Can I go even higher?
All right, I need to take that...
What does a squirrel like?
Nuts.
Uh, nuts.
I kind of smell nuts.
Does it go even higher?
No, I don't have to go higher.
It's nuts, but there's no N.
Can I get a nut somewhere?
Nut.
Uh...
No, I need water.
I need a nut.
I dropped the...
I dropped the safe on his head?
Why would I do that?
That's, like, terrible.
Can I pick...
Can I move this?
Is it in...
It's in the tree.
Is it?
Got it.
Shit.
Come here.
I have to break it?
Oh.
All right, wait, wait.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Give me that.
All right, I got the key.
Save the goat.
Save the world.
Open.
He fucking exploded.
No!
The goat, it's getting worse.
Goat was a lie.
Oh, gracious.
Now what?
It was wrong.
It was a bad idea.
Everything disappeared.
Except me.
How old is this game?
I don't know.
Probably a lot...
Pretty old.
It's all my fault.
Please, will you forgive me?
Oh, there it is.
All right.
That was called...
There is no game.
Now should I play there is only one level?
Wait, what did that say?
World...
One billion off debt if he gets world record speedrun in any of these games.
That's not gonna happen.
All right.
Now play there is only one level.
So first there was no game.
But now there's one level.
Okay.
Is it on here?
Oh, I played the absolute hell out of this on iPad.
I like almost 100% at this game.
Like a year or two ago.
Is it on here?
It's called...
There is only one level.
Just search for it.
Okay.
There is a bomb.
I don't think it's on armor games.
This is the only...
This is a work of fiction.
This is the only level.
This...
Four of these.
This is...
This five of these games.
This is the only level.
This game requires flash.
Flash is blocked.
Fuck.
Does it?
It looks like it's loading.
Oh.
Well, hold on.
Yeah, by the way, the reason why we're doing this
is because in like two or three weeks,
flash is literally going to be deleted from the internet.
It's a nice flash games.
Hold on.
Let me do this.
Go into...
Go into settings.
Should I do this?
This is bad.
Settings.
Site settings.
Flash.
I don't think...
Isn't it highly recommended not to do this?
Not yet.
Okay.
Site settings.
Uh...
Flash.
Block sites from using flash.
Okay, we're going to allow.
Ask first is what it says.
I can't even allow it.
I have to do ask first.
Okay.
Well, let's have to reboot it.
Run flash this time.
Okay.
Did it work?
I don't think it did.
Oh shit.
What happened?
Already?
Did I get hacked already?
What happened?
I turned...
I turned on flash and I get a notification.
They really don't want you to turn this on.
They desperately do not want you to turn this on.
Flash player will no longer be supported.
Turn it off.
Holy shit, man.
Can you see?
How come I can't capture the window now?
Oh, okay.
There we go.
That was weird.
Okay.
All right.
So this is the only level.
This game...
Flash is blocked.
It's not.
I just unblocked it.
I don't think I can play this.
Click it.
Click.
I...
Look, I don't use...
I never really use Chrome.
I'm a Firefox guy.
There's only one level.
Okay, play it.
That's based...
Of course it is.
Why would you use Chrome?
It uses like 40% CPU.
Mozilla's got like quantum tech...
Mozilla has quantum technology.
I've read that.
Did you read that about Mozilla quantum?
Firefox quantum?
Yes, I'm aware that that's just like
infomercial speak of like new and improved.
It's just soap and water.
I know.
But like they say, the new technology.
The new soap bubble technology.
I get it.
Play or continue level one.
I have a web timer?
Hold on.
I gotta zoom this in.
Why do I feel like I've played this game before?
Does the timer matter?
Okay.
Arrow keys.
All right.
Stage complete.
But this is the level over.
Okay.
So they made my controls backwards.
I remember this game from like 2001.
Think before doing.
I remember this game.
This is one of those original like troll games.
Alternate control scheme.
What?
Mouse?
Oh, okay.
Get in.
This is like the impossible quiz
where you had to memorize every single answer.
Free floating.
It's a legendary game.
Yeah, it's a bit bouncy.
But okay.
I get it.
This is not like the impossible quiz.
Yeah, but it was the same time frame.
Wait, I can jump?
Oh.
These all came out like around the same time.
With the impossible quiz today.
You know what's really funny?
I probably have still...
I played that game so often when I was younger.
I think I probably have memorized
a shitload of those answers.
Handy stripes of doom.
Okay, so don't touch pink.
Okay, don't touch pink.
How do I...
Oh, fuck.
Hold on.
How am I supposed to...
How do I get up there?
A hundred million off the dead
if you can do the impossible quiz.
I think I remember most of the answers.
Arrow control?
Oh, shit.
Hold on.
You know when you go to your friend's house
and they've got a fucking crazy...
He hits it out.
Okay, then do it.
I have to click.
Heavy headwind here.
Look at how fun this is.
Remember when...
Oh, dude, remember when video games
were so much better?
So much time and passion went into it.
This ain't even boomer.
What are you talking about?
This is millennial.
This game came out when I was probably 14.
15 or something.
Got a raid?
We're raided.
We got a raid?
Did we get a raid?
Oh, shit.
It's Kit Vogan.
Kit Vogan raid.
I got to sing the raid song.
Hey.
Thank you for the raid.
Well, I'm doing it to this song in the background.
Thanks, Kit.
I hope you had a good stream today.
Hope you had a good stream.
Welcome everybody.
We're currently just doing flash games
and chilling for a little bit.
I actually saw a pretty funny Kit Vogan clip recently
and when he was talking to a scammer
that didn't believe he was him.
This scammer was like,
yeah, I'm a big fan of Kit Vogan.
It's not you.
He's like, okay.
He's like, maybe one day you'll get to talk to him.
And the guy's like, yeah, maybe.
It's not you, though.
But welcome, guys.
Thanks for the raid.
One, I could only jump once.
Yeah, we're currently playing games that,
you know, you look back and you go like, man.
Back when people made games like Passion,
like Super Mario, Super Mario 2, Super Mario 3.
The impossible game.
Time to refresh.
I mean, what?
I have to actually hit F5?
No, you don't.
But is it going to count though?
Because Flash Player is like dead and broken.
Will it remember?
Uh, okay.
Welcome to the channel.
Thank you Kit Vogan for that sweet ass raid.
That was a bad one.
That was a good one,
but it was a bad one at the same time.
Why am I at level one?
I was like, that was yikes.
Oh, what happened?
Did I get baited?
Oh, for that sweet ass raid.
No, I don't want to do this whole thing again.
Did I get fooled?
Do an impossible quiz.
No, let me get past that.
Let me do this first.
I'll do this quick.
Think before doing.
Turn on cookies.
Am I going to turn cookies on?
Possible quiz.
I will do the impossible quiz, I promise.
By the end of the stream today,
I will have completed the impossible quiz.
Okay, you understand?
At least, hold on, let me make this.
I know people are calling me a liar and that's fine.
At least the first 50 levels, okay?
I will get to level 50.
I know there's like 125 levels,
but I'll get to at least level 50.
Moving a goal post, that's fine.
I'll continue to do so.
What's that singing?
You said you'd beat it.
Oh, come on.
What the fuck?
I'm going to...
This is all going on YouTube, guys.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
And then what's going to happen is whenever I do...
Whenever I get really close to dying,
the camera is going to zoom the fuck in
right at when I fall down, right there.
It's like a one second cut.
Like, no, no, no, no, I got it, I got it, I got it.
No.
Oh, I mean...
Oh, there we go.
It's going to zoom, wick-a-ding, wick-a-close.
And it's going to zoom, wick-a-close to my face.
I'm going to be going like this.
I don't...
Don't use that.
Perfect dog cam today.
Air pet him, all right.
Otto!
Who's a good dog, Otto?
Move.
I'm...
How's my hair?
It's there.
You've got to press it on you.
I guess again that's what you do, baby.
Hold it down.
There.
In DMCA me, well, that means I did a good job.
So go ahead.
It's there.
It's a great song.
No returns, no refunds.
It's coming up.
It's there.
Left, right, march.
I actually haven't heard the new Gorillaz album.
I really haven't.
It's kind of bad.
I love that, man.
Stop playing this trash.
I will.
Okay, time to refresh.
Why though?
Why is it doing this?
Enter refresh.
I'm not pressing F5 again.
You have to enable cookies.
Is that...
Cookies are enabled.
Turn on cookies and refresh.
They're on.
All right.
Give me the...
Let's go.
I'm doing impossible quiz.
That one was fun.
Impossible ball.
Well, that's not it.
Where's impossible quiz?
Is it on congregate?
Oh, there it is.
Impossible quiz.
Wait, impossible game?
Enabling flash.
Hello, players.
The latest version of Chrome includes enhanced security.
It must be configured to allow flash.
Oh, God.
Okay.
Use the supernova plugin as an easy way to enable.
It's already installed, isn't it?
Go get flash player.
Do it.
Click the link.
I'm afraid.
I'm like afraid.
I'm afraid to click the link.
I don't think I'm...
Hold on.
What's this?
Zorn lovers?
I'm only five miles away.
All right.
It took me a second to realize what this was.
And then it was very funny.
Hold on.
Let's get it.
Okay.
We're going to enable it, I guess.
Is it going to work?
I think it worked.
Did it work?
It's not loading it though.
It's blank.
Hold on.
Let me try to refresh.
Refresh.
Come on.
Is there another one?
Wait.
There's another one.
Impossible quiz dot...
Is that a good one?
Is this a real website?
Or did you just fucking type this in and make it up?
Oh, this feels like a fake.
This doesn't feel like a real website to me.
It's real.
Okay.
All right.
This website uses cookies.
Eat them.
I'm five miles away.
I love to chat.
Can I get rid of these ads though?
Like really?
What the fuck just happened?
I just clicked an ad.
This was an ad.
You suck.
The game's taking impossibly long to load, but it'll be worth it.
Oh, it's part of the joke.
What the fuck?
I just clicked the ad again.
Hurry up.
I want to get...
Hold on.
Get rid of this.
I'm not going to let this...
I'm not going to stand for this.
I'm not going to...
I'm sorry.
That's not going to happen.
Wait a minute.
What's that slot machine?
Okay.
Oh my fucking god, Jeremy.
I just gave this website...
Like why is this doing this?
Play the Zorn game.
I'm on the impossible quiz.
Why is this doing this?
I didn't even click anything.
I highlighted text.
Stop.
I'm trying to get...
My fucking god.
Okay.
We're finally done.
We're ready.
I'm going to...
I remember half of these answers.
All right.
Impossible quiz.
I remember.
Let's go.
Let's see how many I remember.
Are you ready?
It's time.
Let's see if I can remember these.
How many holes in polo?
That's two because they're actually...
They're talking about the word polo.
No, they're not.
I forgot.
I missed it already.
How many holes in a polo?
One because it's a t-shirt.
Okay.
That's wrong.
What?
Four because it's polo.
The word.
Okay.
Can a match box?
No, but a tin can.
K.O.
Click the answer.
It's the answer.
Put the mouse on here.
Now don't touch the blue.
Sure thing.
I won't.
Onion.
That would be shallots.
The answer is really big.
An elephant.
Search for it.
It's not there.
It's right there.
What was the answer to question two?
It would be that one.
Choose the food.
It's the teeth.
What follows December 2nd?
That would be N.
Click the smallest.
It's this one.
What sound does a bell make?
Fatang.
What can you put in a bucket to make it lighter?
A hole.
I got kind of close though.
I could do it.
How many holes in a polo?
That'd be four.
Where's the music?
Isn't there usually music?
Where's the sounds?
Okay, how many holes in a polo?
Four.
Can a matchbox know what it's in can?
That's a KO.
Click the answer.
Mouse over here.
Next question, please.
Shallots.
The answer is really big.
It's an elephant.
Search for it right here.
What was the answer?
This one.
Teeth.
Uh, N.
Click the smallest.
What sound does a bell make?
Fatang.
What can you put in a bucket to make it lighter?
Torch.
Oh, this would be horse.
What is the seventh letter of the alphabet?
A, B, C, D, E, F, G.
It's G, but it's probably not G.
It is A, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
It would be the letter E.
One, two, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, H.
24 minus seven equals?
That would be 24, 23, 22, 21, 20, 19, 18, 17.
Um, it's not, I, this is, no, it's a trick.
There it is.
Stop.
I believe the answer is banana.
It's hammer.
Uh, color in the correct order.
That would be blue, orange, green, green, yellow.
Masterpiece.
Thank you.
Deal or no deal?
No deal.
No.
Yeah, no, it was deal.
I forget.
I think it was no seal.
Watch carefully.
The choice is yours.
I would like plus one skip.
Save changes to untitled.
No.
Cancel.
All right, I got it, I got it, four.
Get a matchbox if I can.
It's a K.O.
Uh, click the answer.
This one here.
Put it over here.
Dollots.
Go ahead.
Uh, elephant.
How much do I get if I beat this?
That one.
Teeth.
Second.
Okay, click the small one.
Batang.
It's a torch.
That's a horse.
Uh, the seventh letter of the alphabet was, um, wait, it was H.
Seventeen.
Hammer.
Blue, orange, blue, green, green, yellow.
Good.
Deal or no deal?
Seal.
Watch carefully.
It's this one.
Plus one skip.
Save changes to untitled.
Brand.
Okay.
I know how to do this one.
Click.
Click the lives button.
How do you kill a werewolf?
With shoe polish.
Which of these places names doesn't exist?
Oh, I don't, I think it's arse facey.
Okay, I hope you've been paying attention to the questions.
Numbers go to 21.
Go to 24.
It's go to 26.
Which of these places names doesn't exist?
Arse facey.
Go to 28.
What is this?
That would be abundance.
What flavor is cardboard?
It would be, uh, um, oh, I forget.
Uh, talcum.
Fuck.
Egg mayonnaise.
Okay, put the mouse here.
Be careful.
Woof.
I believe this is woof woof woof.
What are the main ingredients of shampoo?
Uh, rocks and saucers.
Nope.
Baby Cham.
Okay.
How many letters in his hand?
One, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
There's nine there, but that's not what they're asking.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Elephants don't like mice.
They don't.
So get it off the screen so they can move in.
Read chat.
What?
If you press this button, it's game over.
Right.
Alternatively, click this one to carry on.
What do you call a wingless fly that is a...
Jason.
Shit.
What are you guys saying?
It doesn't need to read chat.
No, I'm trying to do this on my own.
Heyo.
Click the answer.
I told you I knew half of these already.
I played this so many times when I was younger.
That one.
Teeth.
This one.
Whoa, don't do that.
Don't right click.
Tang.
A torch.
Horus.
H.
Seventeen.
The hammer.
Blue, orange, green, green, yellow.
Go ahead.
Seal.
It's this one.
Fuzz a skip.
Ran.
Click the V.
It's shoe polish, right?
Yeah, okay.
R.
Spacey.
Go to 28.
That's abundance.
It was egg mayonnaise.
Start here.
Be careful.
Good.
Woof, woof, woof.
Baby Cham.
Seven.
Watch out.
What are you doing?
God gamer.
Boomer reliving his youth.
What are you linking here?
Put it in E mode only?
You lost 2,000 viewers.
Whatever.
I don't care.
Okay, I gotta get this right.
I'm on 36.
A walk, I think.
Okay.
Can you get this question wrong?
No way.
Mary Rose sat on a pin.
I think it's-
Oh, really?
No, it's not.
First her piles?
Mary Rose.
Okay.
Right here, right now.
Space here.
Cough drops.
Cylindrical adventures.
I don't remember.
Cough drops.
Nope.
Shit.
I don't remember.
I think it's adventures.
Yep.
Put the mouse here.
Don't touch pink.
Hmm, I've only had a bridge.
Uh, wait.
How do I do this one?
How do you do this one?
I forget.
Um, I've only had a bridge.
What's the-
What do I have to do?
Oh, shit.
Right.
I can right click.
Wing.
Okay.
Afro sexy bill.
Dirty rectum?
I think it's-
Is it dirt?
No, it's-
What is it?
I think it's dirty rectum.
I don't know why I thought it was dirty rectum.
That was stupid of me.
Okay, click the smallest one.
That's a tang.
We got a torch.
We got a horse.
Very cool.
H-17.
Hammer.
The funniest thing about this game is
I swear to God,
every like three to five years,
I come back and beat this game.
Seal.
I think everybody does that, right?
Woof, woof, woof.
Okay.
This one.
Seven.
Watch out.
Everybody?
I think a lot of people do.
I think at this point, yeah.
Emote only to keep him honest.
You can do that if you want.
Keep me honest.
That's fine.
Yeah, I mean, clearly.
You guys have to remember.
From the second that you see something on screen,
it takes about five to eight seconds before,
like before you see it.
Like when I do something,
right now when I say,
you probably just heard it right there.
So it doesn't matter.
I've been doing it on my own.
All right.
I want everyone to do yes
when they hear this sound, okay?
We'll test it out.
One, two, three, four, five.
Okay, it's five seconds.
So it's five full seconds.
Let's try it again.
I want you to do Resident Sleepers.
No, don't do that.
I don't want people to think this is like a boring stream.
Do no, okay?
Two, three, four, five, five.
Yeah, it's about five full seconds.
No way.
It's Mary Rose.
There we go.
Bridge.
Okay, this one, what was it?
Is it Evil Eye?
Afro, okay.
What is the answer to life, the universe, and everything?
It's 42.
Right, but it's weird.
No skipping here.
I forget.
There's a distinct reason.
I think you click on like the 40 second one.
Let's see.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Ten, 20, 30, 40, 42.
There it is.
Bridget makes everyone a straight by Tom Cruise.
I remember Tom Cruise.
We're gonna put the piece together.
Uh, hold on.
There's no timer, so don't worry.
It doesn't matter.
Does this one say cheese?
Cheese check?
Cheerios flick here.
Oh, right.
Okay, hold on.
I can't move this one.
Click here.
Okay, we're good.
Good, good, good, good, good.
This is Wingdings, but I don't remember which one.
I believe it's, uh, I don't know.
I have no idea.
I have to guess top right.
Fucking beautiful.
One of the four chance.
Best flash, holy shit.
What's happening?
Best flash ever.
Man, oh my fucking God.
You kill Sonic.
You bastard.
It's that one.
What is this?
Where's my mouse?
Okay, snake, snake, snake.
Which is the correct spelling?
Slap-me-do, slap-me-do, spap-me-do, splap-me-do, it's slap-me-do.
Shit.
It's splap-me-do.
Remember, blue, red, blue, yellow.
Uh, 108 minus 4, 8, 15, 16, 23, 42.
Blue, red, blue, yellow.
Remember, blue, red, blue, yellow.
Fuck.
Uh, blue, red, blue, yellow?
I'm gonna skip it.
I don't know.
Fight.
Hooray.
Carrot.
Holy shit, I guessed it correctly.
Accidentally.
Okay, that's the third one.
Marmite.
Uh, what is that?
Yum.
Butt-pa might not.
I only have one life left.
I don't know.
I can't take a chance.
I think it's urr.
Depends.
I think it's probably yum.
Nope.
Shit, it's urr.
Shit.
Okay, whatever.
I got it.
Pick the answer.
Yeah, move over here.
An elephant.
Search for it.
There it is.
That one.
Teeth.
And click the small one.
A tang.
Uh, a torch.
Spell it out.
School, H, uh, 17, blue, orange.
Queen, queen, yellow.
Oh, seeing Resonance Leapers.
Oh, see it, see it tomorrow when you wake up.
Cause I'm beating it.
This one.
Well, you guys should be thinking about the next game.
You should be thinking about the next Flash game.
Egg mayonnaise.
Here it is.
Woof, woof, woof.
Uh, baby.
Seven.
You guys should be thinking about the next Flash game.
That's only an hour.
I got plenty of time.
I'm just gonna get a water.
We'll get a coffee or something.
We'll hang out.
Whatever.
What?
Come on.
Away.
Uh, Mary Rose.
This one.
Okay.
Afro.
It's 42.
Shit.
It's the one below it.
Oh, god.
I'm cruise.
Click here.
All right, which one is this one?
It's not this one.
We have three more chances.
Top left.
That's bottom left.
Shit.
Top left.
Oh, god damn it.
Whatever.
Fuck.
Okay.
Nobody can.
K.O.
Get the answer.
It's this one.
Go over here.
Quick.
Hurry up.
Hurry.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
My voice.
Oh, no.
No, no.
I wasn't ready to come back.
I wasn't ready to come back yet.
I shouldn't have.
I should have waited another day.
I wasn't ready to come back.
Wasn't ready to come back.
I should have waited another day.
That's my fault.
I should have waited.
Okay.
What if I calm down and just stop?
I'm gonna just clear my throat for a second.
We're fine.
See, I'm back.
Blue, orange, green, green, yellow.
Seal.
This one.
Plus one.
Skip.
Ran.
That one.
Shoe polish.
Arse facey.
Abundance.
Egg mayonnaise.
By the way, I'd do this if the stream wasn't even turned on,
I would be doing this.
You say all the things.
Out loud.
Okay, baby.
Yeah.
Okay, seven.
This is the elephant part.
Okay, don't click it.
Wait till it changes.
Like this one.
Okay.
Okay, that's a walk.
In a way.
Mary Rose.
Cylindrical.
Watch that.
Get a right click.
Okay.
Afro, 42.
Tom Cruise.
Of course, everybody does that.
Don't lie to me.
Bottom right.
So what the hell is it?
I clicked on all of them.
Which one is it?
What?
I clicked on every single one of them.
It's not anything down here.
The number?
I can't cheat.
I can't.
It's one of the symbols?
Shit.
I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
I think I'm just gonna skip it.
Okay.
Snake.
Splap me do, right?
Okay.
Now what is this one?
Blue, red, blue, yellow.
It's not what.
It's probably GTFO.
Oh, that was so popular at the time.
Really?
I can't.
This was so deeply in the lingo
back in early 2000s,
late 90s internet.
Okay.
I gotta skip it.
There's the carrot right here.
Okay.
It's ugh.
What the fuck?
No.
What?
Are you serious?
Some super obscure thing.
It's impossible.
That's the nature of the game.
Okay.
I gotta get the Wingdings one.
Horse.
Age.
17.
Yeah.
Oh.
Resident sleeper.
Why is he not listening to me?
Resident sleeper, I said.
What was that laugh?
No.
Shit.
I was looking over at you guys.
Dude, there's one
three, three, one, seven viewers here
that's like late.
All right.
There's a lot of people here.
I'm like, am I trying to like make people leave?
Am I trying to make people think I'm like a dork?
No.
Stay.
All right.
What the fuck is this one?
I don't get it.
Flag.
Square.
Diamond.
Nay.
Yay.
Nay, nay.
No.
Yes.
No, no.
No.
Yes.
No, no.
What is that supposed to mean?
I can't figure.
No.
Yes.
What are you trying to convey to me?
What are you trying to say?
No.
Yes.
Wait.
No.
Yes.
But I clicked this one already.
What?
I clicked.
I clicked that one.
You're in emote only.
So no backseating.
I know.
But I didn't understand.
I didn't get it.
And it was so obvious.
All right.
Splat we do.
OK.
What about this one?
Blue, red, blue, blue, blue, red, blue, yellow.
Blue, red, blue, yellow.
They're cheating again.
They're cheating.
You can cheat.
You know what?
It would be actually easier if emote only mode was off.
Because then you guys can't do the connect four to tell me what to do.
It would get lost.
OK.
It's not yum.
It's not.
What is that?
It's probably what is that?
Because a lot of Americans don't eat this.
Nope.
Shit.
But Pah might not.
What does that even mean?
What the fuck does that mean?
Shanghai is indeed the largest city in China.
Why is there a question mark?
About 20 centimeters off the ground.
Never been.
Why is there a question mark?
It's true.
It's never been.
God damn it.
Nostalgia.
Hey, do you guys remember?
Hey, and who remembers this?
Nostalgia gaming.
Everyone's probably playing cyberpunk right now.
No, not me.
I'm a contrarian asshole.
New game that came out.
It's like a big AAA game.
People have been waiting for years.
No, not me.
Contrarian.
I don't do that here.
No, we do things that go under the radar.
There's tons of streams you can watch to play cyberpunk.
But not for a minute.
I yell that to myself in the mirror every stream.
28.
Abundance.
Egg mayonnaise.
Don't screw it up.
Triple woof.
What do you guys do?
There's no answers that I'm looking for.
How was you guys week, by the way?
How was you guys like Thanksgiving and stuff?
Wait, I streamed after Thanksgiving, didn't I?
Yeah, what am I talking about?
I almost fucked that up.
You guys can't even answer me.
Wait, which one was it again?
Top right, right?
Yes.
Snake.
Splat be do.
Wait, which one?
Is that okay?
I forget.
I forget this one already.
I think it's okay.
Do I forget this one already?
Okay, I got it.
It kind of looks like Rocco from Rocco's Modern Life.
All right, Papa.
Why is there a question mark?
Shit.
Is indeed the largest city in China.
Oh my god.
So it's the fourth one.
Oh, about 20 centimeters off the ground.
Oh my god.
What is the digestive system?
A series...
Oh god.
A series of workers to break down food and extract energy and nutrients.
Cheese.
I thought it was going to be a meme answer or something.
At least I got to that point now.
The best part about this is every time I start over, it's just a wave of resident sleepers.
It's like, isn't that the nature of the game to like have to go through it a bunch of times?
That's the whole point.
I'm getting that 100 million off.
I'm telling you.
It's going to happen.
Cyberpunk 2024.
20...
40...
What is it?
2044?
2077?
No, that's 2024 is the one that I have.
2024, right?
Who cares?
Why did they just name it cyberpunk in the future?
But like, it's just cyberpunk.
Why does it have to have a year on it?
Because you know what's going to happen.
In like 2080 in real life, people are going to be laughing at that game.
They're going to be looking back and going like, yeah, look what they thought was going to happen.
Don't ever put a year.
Look at how much we make fun of that.
Like, danger Will Robinson.
Danger Will Robinson.
They thought that was going to happen in like 1992.
Didn't.
You get this question wrong.
No way.
Mary Rose.
Yes.
Cheat.
Thank you.
Go.
42.
Tom Cruise.
Click this.
Click this one.
That's Sonic.
You guys chilling out?
How you guys doing on a chill...
I don't even know what day of the week it is.
I don't even know.
If you made me tell you what day of the week it is right now,
for a million dollars, I would not be able to tell you.
Jeremy, I'm going to give you one fucking million dollars in cash.
Taxed, by the way.
You don't have to pay taxes.
It's like, taxed.
One million.
Cash.
I can't tell you what day it is.
I don't know.
It's Wednesday.
Nope.
No, what's today?
Is it Wednesday?
Did I get the money?
It's Wednesday.
I win.
I'll take it.
I was going to say Thursday.
Splat me do.
Okay.
Make a...
Make a fight.
Nice.
I win.
Garrett.
Nay.
Is this one...
Okay, here we go.
A series of organs that break down food.
A games console for whole meal biscuits.
A series of...
This one.
Something best by...
This one!
Okay, it's top right.
It was top right.
I do remember.
It was...
Wait.
Remember the color or remember where the placement was?
It was red.
Shit!
It was placement.
That was a wave of resident sleepers.
So predictable.
At least do it...
Okay, at least do it by question 30.
You can't just do it at question 1 through 10 and then stop.
You can't just do that.
You have to do it like the whole time.
But don't do it the whole time because that...
What the hell?
Don't do that the whole time.
Okay, blue, orange, green, green, yellow.
You better be getting the next game ready because I'm going to beat this soon.
I have this weird memory that's coming back to me right now.
It was four, five o'clock in the morning.
I was in college and I was incredibly tired and just over exhausted.
And I was playing this and my body and brain wanted so badly to go to sleep.
But I wouldn't.
I had like class the next day.
I just was sitting there just with my eyes just burning.
I was on the question 50.
I'll go to the beginning.
Go through, go through, go through.
Question 55, go to the beginning.
And I think I had closed my laptop.
I was like, I have to go to fucking bed now.
I can't do this anymore.
Do you know when you're lying down in bed and you know that you should be sleeping
but you just don't?
Because your mind just needs to just continue to do something.
Sleeping is too boring for your brain at that moment.
Even though your brain and body are like, dude, just fucking put your iPad down.
Put your phone down.
Just close your eyes.
You'll be asleep in 30 seconds.
It's like, no, I don't want to do that.
I like want to keep playing the impossible quiz.
I want to keep watching this woodcutting video.
So judging by all the residents sleepers, it feels like a lot of you guys are doing
that right now.
It's fun.
Okay, here we go.
This is where it gets a little...
Okay, I got to remember this.
Is it placement?
It's placement.
So it's right there.
Right here, right kind of in the top kind of center.
I thought it was color.
Oh, by the way, anybody know how long are the game awards?
How many hours?
Like just write yay and write how many hours it is.
Judging by the amount of residents sleepers, whatever.
Okay, four residents sleepers in four hours?
Three hours?
Is it three hours?
Okay, four residents sleepers in four hours.
Three, okay.
All right, here we go.
I hope I remembered.
It's right here.
Right there.
What?
That doesn't make any sense.
What are you talking about?
Is it hidden somewhere?
What?
It was the red one, but it was up here.
I clicked red last time and it was wrong.
What just happened?
What?
What the fuck was that?
No.
What?
I don't understand.
It was correct for a second.
All right, turn off.
Turn off emote only mode.
I want some suggestions on there.
I'm going to do the same thing I did when I was in college.
I'm going to get to question 16.
Just close the laptop and be like, fuck this.
Blue, red, blue.
Oh, okay.
I get you now.
I see what you're saying.
Okay.
This is the worst game ever.
It's a classic.
It's like saying that like Super Mario is the worst game ever.
Stop.
You made your point.
Wait, what do you guys think?
You think I'm making a point?
What do you mean?
I'm trying to get through this.
I have a hundred million on the line.
The deal is off the table.
What?
What are you talking about?
There's no deal.
The deal is off the table.
How is it off the table?
I cheated?
When did I?
What are you talking about?
When did I cheat?
Off the table.
No deal.
You had one shot.
So wait, it's been an emote only mode this whole time
and you guys have desperately been telling me
that I don't have to keep doing this
because I lost the bet already?
Oh.
Well, now I kind of want to just do it.
Keep going.
I know I'm close to the end.
There's like 80 questions or something, right?
We have to pay him to stop.
No, you don't have to pay me to stop.
Don't pay me to stop.
Okay.
Blue, red, blue, yellow.
I did.
Hey, lobster.
Thanks for the five community subs.
Blue, red, blue, yellow.
Look out.
Count Dracula.
He's a sexy one.
Sorry.
I prefer lemurs.
I don't know.
Look.
Count Dracula.
One.
Okay.
On the subject of Dracula, what is his favorite food?
Shepherd's pie.
Charge the laser.
How?
Oh, how do I do that?
Shoot it.
Be honest.
Did you manage to do the last question on your first go?
Yes, I did.
Is that a butt?
If thimple, click the moth.
What?
Oh, the moss, not the mop.
The moth.
Okay.
What are chicken nuggets made of?
Tasteless white filth.
Win.
It's definitely, it's not.
Soil?
I don't know.
So I'll come back to it.
Skip.
Which is true.
PSP is better than the DS.
The DS is better than the PSP.
PSP is the DS.
Or egg is better than 28.
Egg.
Click the largest.
It's gonna be a trick.
This is a trick.
It's probably, I don't know.
Click the largest.
Got it.
Hurry up.
It's the end of the world.
Armageddon.
Oh my fucking god.
D.
Armageddon.
No, what else?
What do you want me to do?
I'm not playing cyberpunk.
What's that?
Fucking stop it.
All right.
What's the next game then?
What's the next flash game?
Well, you guys figure it out.
You guys will debate it in chat for like a few minutes.
Cool math.
I've done cool math.
Pop-up games.
Age of War.
Age of War?
I feel like that's gonna take a while.
I feel like it's like a strategy game or something.
Yes, do that.
Is that like an idle game?
You guys are gonna be mad at me for that one.
Do Age of War.
I will after this.
All right.
I'm gonna see if I can get through here.
Cookie clicker.
I did an idle game already.
Swords and sandals.
I'm seeing a lot of that.
Is that good?
I, no, I legit refuse to play Happy Wheels.
I refuse.
I'm never gonna play that game ever for any reason.
Both swords and sandals.
Is it good?
Any reason?
I wouldn't even do it for a million dollars.
Play Roblox.
Hey, I'll play Roblox when their IPO comes out.
We can celebrate it.
They went public.
Yeah.
Is it gonna be like, uh.
Swords and sandals.
I'll check it out.
I did remember.
Blue, red, blue, yellow.
Okay.
One.
His favorite food is shepherd's pie.
Shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot it, shoot it, shoot it.
Play Raid Shadow Legends.
No.
That doesn't, that will never happen.
I did it on my first try.
Thumbs up.
Click the moth.
Now this, I'm stuck here.
Play Spongebob flip flop.
I'll try, um.
I just clicked on like the first five.
It was five people said win in a row.
And I, or I did, no.
Faceless white filth.
Okay.
I already knew the answer to that.
Egg.
Like the largest.
Okay.
Armageddon.
Hurry up, it's the end of the world.
Oh my fucking, Australia.
What?
Oh my god, damn it.
We'll figure it out the next game.
We'll just figure, we'll get the next game figured out.
We're gonna play swords and sandals, possibly.
Any other things that you guys have up your sleeve.
Swords and sandals, um.
Balloons, tower defense is a pretty good idea.
Swords and sandals is long enough.
Okay, all right.
Madness interactive.
That's an interesting game.
But please, why don't you guys explain, tell me about it.
What is the premise of madness interactive?
What do you do?
Tell me, I'd like to read about it.
For the next five to ten minutes.
Balloons six.
It sucks.
Okay, well, that's why we're having this debate.
That's why we're spending the time here.
To make sure we get everybody's opinions on the matter.
Tropica.
That's interesting too.
Let's check that out.
Interactive buddy.
Wait, is that the moment you just kind of throw the guy around a room?
And you like punch him in the face and stuff and like throw stuff at him?
All right, this is the last attempt, I swear to God, no matter what.
And I'm gonna open up sword and sandals.
No matter what, this is the final attempt.
People are, I'm looking at the capas.
Okay, let's make this interesting.
If I do another attempt, add a billion to the debt.
How's that sound?
Right, I got it, now I have to.
It's the last attempt.
Cruise, okay, okay.
This one, a final ninja.
Okay, put it on the list.
Play the world's hardest game.
No, I don't, let's play something fun.
Not that that game's not fun, but you know.
Age of War.
I got that, it's on the list.
Blue, red, blue, yellow.
Okay, one.
Shepherd's Pie.
Shoot.
Okay, I got it on my first go.
Thumbs up.
Moss.
Tasteless white filth.
Egg.
Click the largest.
Okay, now the next one is the Armageddon one.
It's the end of the world.
Oh, shit, here we go.
Can I show this?
What do I do, what do I do, what do I do?
What do I do, what do I do?
Okay, it's a big hairy asshole.
Whatever it was.
Oh, you have to pet the cat.
Okay, are you enjoying the quiz?
I'm level 69.
My dog's got no nose.
How does it smell?
How am I supposed to know?
Terrible, like piss.
Terrible, fuck.
How am I supposed to know?
Using my dog's got no nose.
How does it smell?
How am I supposed to know?
Using its anus?
Oh, Christ.
Search.
What am I searching for?
I got it.
Question mark.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know.
I don't understand.
What is it trying to ask me?
It's just the same one.
How many questions does this quiz have?
100.
No one knows that.
You can't really class this as a quiz.
200.
It's not 200.
It's 100.
Skip it.
I don't know.
Be prepared.
Skip it, skip it.
You are my candy girl.
Sugar.
Oh, honey, honey.
You are my sugar.
Honey, honey.
Okay.
What is this?
It's a tea bag.
A testicle.
Mr. T's oven glove.
Question 77.
It's a tea bag.
But I don't know if it is.
I don't know.
It could be wrong.
Skip.
Dj vu.
Plus one life.
Give it to me.
No!
No, I'm so close to the end of the game.
I'm so close.
There's like three questions left.
No, I have...
It's a billion dollars.
What's it at now?
No, I don't.
I can't.
That's a billion.
That's too much to add.
That's too...
No, I can't.
It's too much to add.
What's the next one?
Sword and sandals.
Let's go.
God damn it.
I really want to beat it too.
Swords and sandals.
Wait, this is on Steam.
To buy this on Steam?
Hey Wiggly Joe, thanks for the 15 community subs.
15 subs.
You can if you want.
Where do I get it?
What can I just play it?
Is it on congregate?
Sword and sandals?
What the hell is it?
Swords and souls.
Swords and sandals?
Swords and sandals crusader.
Swords and sandals one.
Swords and sandals two.
I guess I'm just going to do the first one.
Loading game info.
Okay.
Oh, that scared the shit out of me.
Swords and sandals.
Is this game any good?
Swords and sandals two.
Waiting room.
But hold on.
I just...
I have...
This is the first game.
Can I even play the first one?
Okay.
Play.
How to play.
Click here to get an overview.
Swords and sandals is a...
Oops.
Is a mini epic gladiator game.
Wait.
Two is just the same thing but better.
It's just the exact same thing.
Yes.
Two is way better.
Just play it.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I've seen a couple of no's but...
I've...
Sword and sandals two.
Emperors reign.
Why the different versions of this?
Swords and sandals two.
Why the different versions?
The game will start after this message.
What message?
Game brought to you by Third Sense.
This is the...
Okay, I have to zoom this in.
Graphics on high, obviously.
This is way too far.
I need to go in closer.
Hold on.
Okay.
There's a...
Why is there a chat?
I remember not being able to put games on high.
Every game had to be...
You had to...
I had to right click every game and put it all...
Put like the shockwave player down to low.
Because it would run at like two frames a second.
Okay.
That looks all right.
All right, let's go.
How to play.
Much has changed since swords and sandals one.
Apparently, chat.
But for those who have played the first game,
the basic premise is the same.
Create your gladiator and battle your way to fame and fortune.
Tooltips will guide you through the specifics of the game.
But the basic pattern of the game is as follows.
Create, build up your character,
buy weapons, armor, spells, and potions,
defeat gladiators to win experience and gold,
and then do it all over again.
Your ultimate aim is to defeat all the arena champions
and reign as champion yourself.
All right.
Great.
Become a member of the playaholics to save and load characters.
I'm not going to do that.
Name.
How about killer?
The killer.
Yeah.
How about um...
Great.
Follow me.
Okay.
Well, I feel like this looks like a self-part character.
Hairstyle.
I give him the...
Wait, I gotta find the German 985.
These all could be German 985.
I have different hair every day.
Um...
No.
How about just uh...
I don't know.
Should I do like the poop hair?
No, that's too wild.
Oh, Dragon Ball Z character.
Yeah.
It's gonna be one of the Dragon Ball Z characters.
The ones that like don't fight that much.
They're like smaller.
Piccolo fights all the time.
There's a little green guy that doesn't fight all the time.
Right?
Who's the little green guy that doesn't fight?
Krillin.
Yeah.
What color is his hair?
Dendy?
Yeah.
I don't know.
What color is Dendy's hair?
Do I have this right?
Hold on.
Dendy?
Dendy.
Okay, yeah.
It's this guy.
No.
Is it Dendy or is it Krillin?
Who has like the hair?
No.
Krillin does not.
Yeah, it's Dendy.
But is there a Dendy with like uh...
Is there a Dendy with like the hair?
No.
Okay.
I guess whatever.
I love that.
I like that.
Okay.
Strength, agility, attack.
Let's just make my character, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
So, um...
The great...
The great star, underscore, once said
that if I had a character sheet in real life,
every single point would be in luck and charisma
and I'd have a zero in everything else.
So I...
I mean, I don't know how accurate that particularly is.
But I feel like I'll lose every match.
I wanted to be kind of strong.
I don't even know what these do.
Can I look?
Strength...
I definitely need...
Okay.
Stamina and vitality.
What's the difference?
Five strength, two agility, three attack.
Is that gonna work?
I don't think that's gonna do anything.
I'm gonna probably die.
Tool tips are at the bottom.
They are?
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Strength determines how much damage your character dishes out
and your skill with axes and clubs.
It also affects the height and weight of your character.
Stronger characters can push weaker characters further.
Okay, well, I mean, I'm not the biggest guy in the room,
but you know, I'm also not the smallest guy in the room,
but I can keep that at a one.
Agility represents your character's speed,
skill with swords and ranged weapons.
Faster characters can move in and out of combat more easily
and perform spectacular aerobatic leaps.
Well, with my kind of medical stuff recently,
I haven't been able to move around too much,
like that fast or that much.
So having some, you know, trouble layers
probably should be a one.
Attack.
Your attack is overall offensive weapon skill.
Gladiators with high attack scores
tend to hit their enemies more often.
Finding gaps in armor with masterful precision.
I have trouble like opening up Amazon packages
with like a pair of scissors.
I can never quite like cut the tape
and I end up just ripping it up.
I just grab the edges
and I just fucking pull as hard as I can
and the tape is starting to give,
but it hasn't given yet
and I pull as hard as I fucking can
until it just breaks.
So I probably wouldn't be very good at that either.
Defense is a vital part of protecting oneself in combat.
High defensive stat means you'll get hit less.
I mean, I do a lot of sitting.
I just sit here.
I mean, people could give you through
like a rock at my window right now.
It'd go hit me right in the head.
So I don't think I'd be very good at that either.
Your vitality represents your overall health.
That's one.
Charisma reflects your overall charm and likeability.
Characters with high charisma please the crowd.
Winning you more gold for winning fights.
Shopkeepers will lower their prices by 1%
for every charisma point you have.
I feel like I'm right at home here.
I feel like I can do this pretty well.
I feel like I have energy sometimes
and I can really speak to a crowd of people.
Are you guys ready?
Are you excited for German 985's
YouTube account?
I think it should be 10.
Stamina.
Every leap, every parry or hack you perform
in the area arena takes some of your energy.
I got some energy.
Well, no, I don't.
I stream for like four hours.
Um, what about magicka?
You cannot harness the power of magicka in your combats.
To cast magic spells and potions,
you'll need a high magicka.
Each magicka point you have also adds 1% resistance
to magical damage.
I don't know, man.
I kind of feel like, you know, how many times have I,
you know, like power, like total power.
I feel like I would be like one of those guys.
I would just open up.
I would go into the room with a big robe on
and I would just tell a bunch of jokes
and then I would zap everybody to death.
I think that would be me.
If I had a D&D character, that's who it would be.
You are a wizard.
Well, I don't know if it would be a wizard.
No, 10 charisma.
No, I could be like a magic user.
How could I not be a magic user?
Fine.
Nine charisma, two magic.
Well, this is going to be really funny.
Laugh out loud streamer joke.
I can't wait for like this to not go well at all
and I'm going to die in like the first arena
and like I'm going to fucking just quit the game
and we're going to move on.
Tholomew, yes, that was your name
but it seems and now here you are languishing in the darkness.
A forgotten prisoner in the emperor's dungeon.
Door opens and your eyes are blinded by the light.
A dark shape appears before you.
Soldiers, oh, you're in the basement.
Hey, you get up, worm.
It is time and boogers are flowing out of this guy's nose
and he has a plate of bacon in his hand
and he waves the bacon in front of your face.
Somebody who, if you know what that is,
holy shit, you are a long-term viewer.
It's the fucking copy paste book that I put into the chat
when I was writing that book.
And so in a frenzy of blood with a stench of fear,
your days as a gladiator begin.
Tholomew versus live from the dungeon.
Fearful prisoner.
Check out your opponent's armor.
Okay, stats.
This guy's got zero in everything.
Preview, okay, let's go.
Walk forward, jump forward.
Wait, is this like, is this how I can tell a joke?
Taunt enemy, press this to yell taunts at your enemy.
Just fucking made him angry.
Let me read these.
Jump backwards, press this leap to leap out of danger.
Jumping saps your energy quickly.
The height and distance of your jump
is determined by your agility.
Step away, useful when your health is low,
but be aware that jumping saps your energy.
Okay, so it's to get away.
Jump forward, jumping uses a lot of energy,
but it's faster, you get closer.
Or attack, charge enemy.
Press this to perform an aerobatic,
an aerobatic, like I'm flying,
leaping attack at your enemy.
I missed him.
How do you block somebody yelling at you?
Do you just close your ears?
Do you like plug your ears into your fingers?
All right, all right, all right, shove him.
Shove enemy, press this to push your opponent back
and give yourself some breathing space.
Power attack, holy shit, okay.
2,500 gold.
I leveled up, sick.
Day one, glorious freedom.
Your adventure starts here in town square.
Before you enter the arena,
you should visit the armory in the weaponsmith
and stock up on a weapon or some armor.
Click on one of the buildings nearby to enter
or click the call scene to jump straight into battle.
All right, let's go to the armory.
What sort of armor are you looking for?
The portrait on the right represents
the different types of armor you can buy.
Click an area on your body to see what's available.
Elmets protect you against critical hit damage
as well as contributing to your overall defense.
Shoulder guards increase the chance
of a charge attack succeeding
as well as contributing to your overall defense.
A breastplate converts a percentage of damage
taken into energy as well as contributing
to your overall defense.
A gauntlet increases the distance you can shove
your enemies as well as contributing
to your overall defense.
This thorough thigh guard protects against
critical hits as well as contributing
to your overall defense.
Shields make you hold them up in the air.
Shin guards you block soccer players.
Boots increase your movement speed
and contribute to your overall defense.
Okay, and then over here we have...
I'm not trying to be funny.
Stop, I'm not trying to be...
Everybody get...
Okay, can I just say something?
If I go in...
If I do an English accent,
you guys just burn your computers.
It's like this huge triggering thing.
Like, hi everybody.
I'm going to do an English accent.
Break, break my...
Throw my computer in the fucking trash.
I could sit...
I could...
I could sit here and go like this.
Yes, yes, do it again.
Yes.
Hi everybody.
I'm just talking with a different accent.
My whole body's on fire.
Just use it, cover yourself in a blanket
and like roll around your room.
All right, what do I want to do?
Helmet?
Ooh, it's a leather helmet.
Anything but the accent.
How much is it?
$1,200?
If you have enough gold,
you can buy this item by clicking the tick button
and it will automatically place on your character.
Have you changed your mind?
I wasn't supposed to scream today.
What the fuck?
I'm not supposed to be yelling.
Listen to this now.
I'm getting a little...
I'm going to have to take another two days off.
No, the game awards is tomorrow.
I can't miss it.
Okay, how do I get the tooltips off for a second?
30% crit protection adds 20 to your armor.
Acquired gladiator level.
It's like Bane.
When I used to...
Remember Bane?
It would go like this,
and all of a sudden everybody's...
Oh, everybody's...
All their entrails would come out.
Uh, I don't want that.
I should get a weapon.
What the fuck?
What's going on?
Louis D. Lungeville,
master at arms.
Can I interest you in a weapon?
Slashing weapons are truly the weapon of the gentleman.
They require high agility.
What's the weapon of the charisma?
A microphone?
Hacking weapons are great for slicing.
They require high strength.
High strength?
Okay, I need, um...
I need like a staff.
I have...
What was a magic thing I can use?
Why does everybody get so mad?
I...
What?
Did I do an accent to these people?
Sorry.
I did an English accent for five seconds.
Nobody kill me.
Magic shop.
Welcome to the magic shop.
Don't steal anything.
Okay, spells.
Teleport to a random spot.
Gale.
A gust of wind that knocks your opponent back a great distance.
Oh, shit.
Enchant weapon?
Burn your...
A flame weapon?
I don't have a weapon.
I could put it on a rusty knife.
What?
Nightfall.
The hours late and the town quiets.
You find yourself growing weary.
Will you brave the streets to spend some gold?
I didn't buy anything.
Uh, I need to go to bed.
You make your way to the Cozy Nook,
a tavern in the merchant's quarter.
Paying the innkeeper 250 gold pieces,
you're shown to a comfortable room
with a view of the forest to the east.
Just leave this peaceful and awake feeling
ready to take the world again.
I wasted time browsing around.
Okay.
I need...
I need a weapon or something.
I should buy something.
I buy, like, a dagger and...
Enchant it?
Let's just go.
Whatever.
I am Arglax, Overlord of the Arena.
What kind of...
What sort of fighter are you after?
The next tournament is for Gladius level 4.
A duel.
Okay.
This person is just me, but way better.
He's just got a bigger chest and got a helmet.
He's a...
What do I do to him?
Oh, go, go, go, go, go, go.
All right, let's go.
You get seven armor, he's got 40 health.
I got more health than him.
Like, what, I beat him?
He yielded.
Okay, you gained a new ability.
Win the crowd.
It allows you to gain more gold from fights.
Okay, I got money now.
Weaponsmith.
I need just something to enchant.
No, should I get Gale?
I think I'm gonna get Gale.
Gale.
37, 40.
Shit.
I'm gonna enchant my weapon with flame.
Your opponent will miss a turn writhing burning pain.
Frost, your opponent will miss a turn frozen to the ground.
The power of venom.
How much does it cost to do this?
It costs zero gold.
Oh, it's range only?
Don't waste the money.
What's in the church?
Welcome, you will find peace here.
Do you require the church's aid and your soul saved?
I guess you can just buy potions.
I'm just like juggling.
The crowd is bored.
Oh, shit.
Look at his face.
You have the forehead of a 400 gold?
What the fuck?
Buy armor, you dummy.
All right, I'm gonna buy a leather helmet.
Buy it.
Okay, I have a leather helmet.
I have shoulder pads.
Is this just skin?
All right, and breastplate.
Okay, I'm gonna get my money back.
What do you got?
He's terrible.
His hit points are 100.
He's got terrible strength.
I'm gonna scream at his face and win.
Let's go.
All right, get the crowd behind me.
How much money did I get?
Do it again.
This is level three.
Give me some more money.
Go.
Oh, shit.
All right, back it up, back it up, back it up.
Okay.
Shit.
Come on.
What happened?
Oh god, oh god, oh god.
Uh, I win.
What do I do?
Okay, I need more.
I need a weapon.
I'm just gonna get a sword or something, man.
I'm gonna get a dagger.
I can't buy anything.
I need three agility.
I can't even get a slingshot.
Okay, I'm going for agility next time.
Breastplate.
32 armor.
Okay.
Nightfall.
All right, find a tavern.
Okay, go to the arena.
It's time for the tournament.
Once you enter a tournament,
you cannot return to the town until you are victorious.
To lose a fight is death.
Okay.
John the Butcher Woldridge is a pillar of the community.
Every year, he hosts a tournament for low-level gladiators to gain valuable experience.
The winner even gets to take on Woldridge himself for a short shot of big prize money.
I'm level four.
I'm four, I'm two levels higher than Poseidon.
I'm gonna get the crowd behind me.
Crowd's indifferent.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, I'm fine, fine, fine.
Interested?
It's okay.
Entertained.
Enthusiastic.
All right, now scream at him.
What just happened?
Come on.
He fell, he fell, he fell.
That was funny.
The crowd liked that.
Back up.
He's cutting my limbs off.
I won.
Oh, shit.
Nice.
Okay.
I'm blocking that shit.
Rest and heal.
Oh, am I hitting him with a sandwich?
I don't even have a weapon.
Come on.
There it is.
What?
How are you blocking this?
Ow, that hurt.
Fuck, come on.
Back up, back up, back up, back up.
I need to sleep.
No.
Come on, please.
Come on, dude.
All right, I want to play a real one.
Let me play a real one.
Play again, play again, play again, play again.
All right, I'm going to do a real one.
I'm going to do a real one.
I don't know.
Okay, I don't know.
This guy, okay.
Uh, is it a guy from Star Fox?
Is it a guy from Star Fox?
Pigma.
Okay, I'm going to do this for real.
I want strength.
I want attack.
Get rid of the magic.
I don't care.
Attack.
Vitality.
Agility.
Let's go.
Ow.
Pigma.
No, don't you dare.
Oh, I'll do it.
That's worse noise contender.
Fuck, I'm in trouble.
I'm in trouble, I'm in trouble.
That was like worse noise contender.
No, by the way, it's too late.
You know how December is the month,
like halfway through December?
You can't nominate that anymore
because we're like too far in December.
All right, let's just,
let's smoke this guy.
Low charisma.
I know.
What the fuck?
What are they saying?
Gladiator.
Gladiator's off.
I hit Gladiator's off.
I don't know.
All right, give me a dagger.
Graded nine slashing damage.
I'll take it.
Let's go.
Start stabbing.
It's time for a duel.
Here we go.
Scream.
Get a man.
What's that club?
He's gonna enchant a club.
What?
What the fuck just happened?
How much money is this?
I can't even afford this.
Get armor, you idiot.
I will.
We're good.
Okay, now I'm gonna get armor.
Gladiator's off.
All right.
All right, strength and attack.
Wash your ears.
Wash your ears?
They're filthy.
Shoulder guards.
Okay.
All right.
I need a better weapon though.
I'm gonna try to make money for a weapon.
All right, let's get in closer.
Closer.
Nice.
Good trick.
What can I get for a weapon?
High agility.
High strength.
Okay.
So this is 22.
28.
All right, let's get a few more.
We'll get an axe.
All right, get in.
Shit.
See, I blocked it.
Power.
Charge.
What the fuck, dude?
God damn it.
The child in the mill.
You are approached by a frantic woman.
Please help me.
My only child was playing in the old mill
and is trapped under some heavy wooden blocks.
I cannot free him.
You help the rescue of the child or decline and get about...
Yeah, let's rescue the child.
You follow the woman to the mill
and get to work with the rescue effort.
Although it takes an hour and most of your strength,
eventually the child is free.
You become a hero.
In both the mother and the child's eyes,
you gain three charisma points.
Oh, shit.
Nice.
I have to win a battle.
I have no money to buy anything.
All right, duel.
Come on.
What do you have?
Shin guards and a shoulder guard.
Okay.
Four to 16.
You guys got a cleaver.
Hey, Dallas O'Leary is the patron saint.
I'm gonna lose.
Let's get in.
Rest.
Okay, he fell.
Now we go in.
Normal.
Good.
All right.
Okay.
Back it up.
Rest and heal.
Get the energy back.
Back it up again.
Lunge.
Shit.
Okay, we're fine.
All right.
What should I put this into?
Seriously.
Attack?
Let me look at this again.
Vitality?
Yeah.
Okay.
How much money do I have now?
Enough for an axe?
17.
Nope.
I don't have enough money.
I don't have enough for an axe.
I have to win another...
I have to win another one.
Oh, god damn it.
I'm gonna have to do this again.
Can I sell something?
I've got to get a...
Go to the church and save the game?
Fuck.
Are the graphics on medium?
Yeah.
What the hell?
Save your character.
Oh, shit.
There we go.
Wait.
Do you want...
The church can save your soul for 40 gold.
Do I want playaholics to load?
Oh my god.
I just have to win.
I'm not gonna be able to win.
I bought the wrong weapon.
Can I afford any armor?
What about a shield?
Or just even just a little one?
Nope.
What about gauntlets?
I can afford gauntlets.
Want any armor?
What is your armor?
Yeah.
Okay.
I have to get something.
All right.
Just win.
I've got more health.
I've got more armor.
And I just have to kill him.
Oh.
Good start.
All right.
Power.
Lunch.
Normal.
Stop.
Lunch.
Okay.
I won.
1000 gold.
Okay.
Shit.
I'm not gonna win.
He's got 18 armor.
He's got an axe.
He's got an enchanted axe.
Come on.
Let me get lucky here.
Don't you...
Don't...
You...
Don't pull...
Get over here.
Don't pull that out.
Yeah.
I was gonna say.
Give me a break.
Good.
Lunch again.
Back it up.
Sleep.
Lunch.
What happened?
Power.
Good.
Okay.
All right.
Just a couple more.
Behold.
Arena champion.
John the Butcher.
Oh, shit.
All right.
Okay.
Back up.
Run away.
Run.
Shove.
Sleep.
Black.
Back up.
His energy is so much higher than mine.
Fine.
That's okay.
Good.
Fuck.
No.
Don't kill me.
75 stamina pot.
Huh?
Wait.
I didn't have the stamina pot.
What?
Ah.
No.
I'll do it again.
I can do it.
I get it.
I understand the game.
Go, go, go, go, go.
I don't care.
Okay.
I get it.
I understand.
I don't care.
Zero skill points.
What?
Okay.
Go.
I win.
Good.
I get it.
I understand.
Okay.
I know I bought a dagger on the axe build.
Not again.
Not going to happen again.
Here we go.
I'm going to buy this cleaver.
Done.
Now I'm going to win.
Watch this.
Okay.
What the heck?
Yes.
Okay.
All right.
We're good.
Strength.
Okay.
Now I'm going to go to the armory.
I'm going to buy some potions and shit too.
I need magicka of four.
Oh, shit.
I can't.
Get stamina and defense.
I will soon.
How much money do I have?
Okay.
I need 2800.
Elmit.
I can't afford any of this stuff.
Shoulder guards.
I can't afford this.
At least I can afford these.
That's fine.
Okay.
Back to it.
Duel.
Buy boots.
I will.
One guy.
One guy's laughing.
What the fuck, dude?
I wasn't even...
One guy in the audience just screwed everything up so bad.
No, don't.
What happened?
I'm on fire.
This character just sucks.
I suck.
Hi.
What?
Oh, my fucking God.
The guy has a loincloth on and that's it.
I have no fucking money.
I'm over.
I need stamina.
God damn it, man.
It's asleep over here.
Why does everybody have magic fucking items?
Why does everybody have magical shit?
I have no money.
God damn it.
I thought I was going to be able to do like a basic strength build.
Charisma was better.
You did best on the joke character.
I know.
Oh, my God.
That's so frustrating.
Why?
Why is it possible?
Why can't I hit anybody?
All right.
So give me some stamina.
Give me some defense.
Give me some attack.
223.
Attack.
Reattack.
This is good.
Okay.
Go.
Here we go.
Let's kill this guy.
Oh, four strength, four stamina.
Okay.
So I should do...
No, no.
Go back.
How do I take that back?
Why is it not a minus?
This should be a minus.
I'm ready.
I'm going into this shop and we're going to buy...
I'm going to get the bigger axe because I'm going to just watch this shit.
You ready for this?
Watch this.
Oh, wait a minute.
Fair maiden, while leaving the arena,
you spot a pretty girl smiling at you as she spends some time as you know a lady.
You pluck up the courage to ask her for a meal.
Will you be extravagant or just take her out for beers?
1,500 gold.
You accept your offer and that night you meet at one of the finest restaurants in town.
The meal is splendid.
The conversation flows and soon enough,
the next morning the maiden gives you a kiss and a rose.
You shall be her champion.
You got two stamina points.
1,500 gold.
It was not worth it.
We just got monster subs from Mr. Sark.
Sark, thanks for the 20 community subs.
That's the Mr. Sark, streamer on Twitch.
One of the old school YouTubers.
Very, very funny guy.
Follow him right now or I'm going to be extraordinarily upset with you.
By the way, I've heard that Mr. Sark is the new Drew Crew ambassador from what I heard.
Hey, Sark, they're yours now.
They're yours now.
No, but thanks though.
Seriously, why does it keep going to medium?
I haven't gone pee or had water the whole day.
So let me just do that real quick.
I'll be right back.
Let's take a look at some art.
I just drank so much water.
That's a lot.
How's the art looking?
Looks good.
That's good.
Look at that.
Will you lower it to auto?
So funny, whenever I talk to the vet,
I can't help it.
Every time I say auto's name, I have to say auto.
So it's like, oh yeah, just call him.
Yeah, auto has an appointment.
Yeah, I'm just calling to make an appointment for my dog, auto.
What's his name?
Oh, it's auto.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
I mean, auto.
Sark says sexy art presentation too.
Sick transitions.
Yeah, it was made by a couple of people in the community.
So Yen Wen Len and Lazy Luke.
It's real.
Oh, can you imagine?
Look at that fucking booty.
I've really leaned into that, I've noticed.
I've really leaned into that.
I don't know why.
I just have whatever.
Yeah, why?
I don't know.
Look, I thought it was fun.
It's funny.
It's fun.
It was fun, okay?
It's a funny, fun thing.
I don't care.
If you do a big zoom in of my ass, it doesn't bother me.
It just doesn't.
If you have a zoomed in picture of my ass cheeks, I don't care.
I'm just like, all right, what are you doing?
But I don't give a shit.
I look good for my age.
I'm 35.
Look, there's art that says it too.
No, you don't think I know?
You don't think I know what I got going on down there?
Get it off.
Never mind.
I love this though.
This is fantastic.
I'm going to cut it off.
A collection of sub badges.
Oh, shit.
I have so many empty slots on my Twitch dashboard.
I really need to do something about this shit.
Look at that.
All right, let's go.
Back to it.
All right, let's find a bed in the tavern.
Game Awards start at 3.30 Pacific tomorrow, right?
I can't wait.
I'm going to get there.
I'm going to get my coffee.
I'm going to have a nice hot coffee.
Back to the art.
Okay.
Here we go.
What is he holding?
A disc?
Can I just smile at him?
What the fuck am I doing wrong?
I don't have any armor, but I can afford armor.
I took a lady out for an expensive quail.
I don't have any money.
Boots.
I have shoes.
Okay, cool.
So I have shoes on now.
I got the boots.
What about greaves?
Oh, I can do greaves.
Just reset.
No, I can't.
Please, can you do...
I don't even know what you're asking.
I'm not even going to respond.
Come on.
11K Andy, 11K Andy, 11K Andy.
That's pretty good.
That's really good.
I'm happy with that.
That's pretty big.
How about you went from 12K to 11K?
So?
But you guys don't understand when I go on break,
I fucking squeeze both my fists together.
I go, I went from fucking 12.3K to 11.1K.
This can't be happening.
I've got to pull them back.
I've got to pull them back,
and I'm going to do it as best I can.
I'm going to go in there still making cartoon noises.
And what should I do?
Vitality?
Was it Trump?
What?
I'm going to...
It kind of was.
Shit.
I'm going to be pulling them back.
I'm so...
No, this is just like I'm annoyed.
Oh, it is kind of Trump.
This is I'm...
I do that all...
Okay, all right, all right.
Everybody settle down.
I'm putting one of the strength, one to attack it.
What did you say?
One into vitality.
What's your favorite cartoon noise?
That or...
All right, I got to relax.
I'm just having too much fun today.
I'm having way too much fun today.
This guy has so much shit on.
Come on.
70% chance.
How do you not...
How do you miss 70% chance three times in a row?
I don't understand.
It's because duels are only first blood.
Yeah, but I...
Okay, all right.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
Some armor on.
It costs money.
That costs money.
Play Binding of Isaac.
Ooh, when's the expansion coming out?
Okay, do I finally have enough money to buy anything?
First blood.
I got to go for a stab.
A quick 92% stab in the face.
Sometime before the end of the year is what's planned.
Wait, what?
Can't do that.
I have to reset again.
Do I really have to reset again?
I can't be, right?
Just get a weapon.
I can't do it.
I really don't...
I don't think I can do it.
Die, you motherfucker!
You need way more armor.
Yeah, I need to not die five times in a row.
I have to...
I'd have to get lucky.
This guy's got a club.
Yes, okay.
We're good.
Okay, hold on.
We're good, we're good, we're good.
No, you dick!
Where did he...
92.
Come on.
Again.
No, don't let him win.
Yes.
All right, come on, John the Butcher.
This is the one.
Come on.
This is the one right here.
Blocked it.
Okay, get in.
Okay.
That hurt a lot.
Yes!
Oh, it hurt.
It hurt, it hurt, it hurt, it hurt.
I'm gonna lose.
God damn it!
I'm in trouble.
I'm trying to sleep.
Just stay away from me.
Get away from me.
Stay away from me.
I'm running out of room.
Oh my, how big is this place?
I want rest and heal.
Rest and heal.
How come I can't heal?
Keep walking, keep walking.
Rest and heal.
There we go.
All right, all right, right, right.
What just happened?
Oh, shit.
Come on.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
This is the most boring fight ever.
Imagine paying for front row seats here.
God damn it, I'm dead.
I'm dead, I'm dead, I'm dead, I'm dead.
Run, run, run, run away.
Run, run, run.
Oh, shit, can I go behind him?
Oh, come on, get him.
Come on.
Come on, heal.
No.
Come on, dude.
God damn it.
No, I have to get this right.
I can't just pay like some lady $1,500 for food.
I can't just pay somebody $1,500 for food.
Just win, win.
For God's sakes, just win.
Ah, five strength, four strength, four attack, three defense, four defense.
Okay, four stamina, two, three stamina.
Okay, all right.
I don't care what his name is.
Who cares?
It's the same person.
If I do not beat this guy, I'm going to be very mad.
Here we go.
Are you ready?
I'm going to stab this guy once and win.
And then go buy the axe.
Oh, my fucking God.
What the fuck is going on?
Okay.
All right, all right, all right.
I'm good.
What should I put it in?
Attack and strength, defense and vitality.
How much money do I have?
I need, okay, I need to win a few more.
I'm going to get the crowd riled up.
How are they still bored?
All right, all right, all right, all right.
Back up, back up.
Get me in there, get me in there.
Okay.
Oh, fuck you.
Thank God.
Vitality and strength.
Weaponsmith.
Come on.
Let's go.
2,200.
I have enough of the axe.
Let's get the axe.
Thank God.
I have a goddamn weapon now.
And it's time for the tournament.
It's time.
I'm going to win.
Let's go.
If I lose right now, then I'm going to be doing something else
because obviously I'm not, I cut out for this apparently.
I'm not cut out for this game if I can't do it.
It was risky.
Okay.
Otis?
Bootis?
Okay, here we go.
Nice fall.
That's comedy.
That's pretty funny.
Good guy in the audience.
Come on.
92%.
We're going with normal.
Again.
Aye.
All right.
Here comes, here comes the butcher.
This is it.
I have to win this.
Doesn't, his armor sucks.
Why is, how is it, how does he have that much armor?
Let's go.
Wow, he put himself in such a bad spot.
And he slept too.
Perfect opportunity to get to him.
Nice.
All right.
Let's go.
Forward, move forward.
Lunch.
What are we at?
70, only go for the 70%.
Move forward, we're not going to do anything stupid.
Again, move forward, not going to do anything dumb.
Move forward again, not going to do anything stupid.
He just crit me for fucking 50 damage.
You piece of shit.
Are you kidding me?
Really?
Fuck, I just cut off my attack.
The guy, if I get close, I'm going to die.
I don't even know what the character looks like.
I don't even know what he had points in.
Just go full charisma.
I'm never going to beat the butcher.
Fine.
Fuck it.
How about just a bashing stick?
Christmas OP, just yell and taunt.
No, get armor first.
Okay.
So should I just get a big chest plate?
What's the best thing to buy first?
Please help me.
I can't beat the butcher.
Just get all the cheapest shit.
So just get all the cheap crap?
Like the 48, these peasant boots?
Single comma name.
What?
No.
All right.
I'm just going to...
Okay.
I'm going to buy these.
I'm going to buy how much of these?
400, hold on.
Gauntlets are 300.
Helmet is cheap.
No, it's not.
Shoulder guards are cheap.
No, they're not.
Gauntlets are cheap.
Yes, they are.
We'll get the middle of the road ones.
What about a shield?
Can I get a cheap shield?
No.
Greaves.
Okay.
These are...
Get the greaves.
Shoulder guards.
I'm just going to get the...
I'll get the cheap shoulder guards.
Or should I get shin guards instead?
Do the shoulder guards.
Okay.
I bought all the armor I could buy.
So now I'm going to go and I'm going to start screaming at people for the duels.
And I'm going to taunt and I'm going to make a bunch of money.
Get me over there now.
How can you block a scream?
God damn it.
Get that first hit on him.
Let's work the crowd and make some money.
What is this guy's weapon?
He's got a golden sword.
Why is this working?
Stop.
Come on.
You piece of shit.
All right.
I'm good.
Okay.
Doing all right.
I don't want to mess this up now.
Seriously.
What should I really put this into?
Charisma and vitality.
Charisma.
Seriously.
Stamina.
I'm going to do...
All right.
What do I got for money?
2400.
Okay.
I'm going to save it.
I'm going to keep screaming at people.
No.
Okay.
I had to buy something.
What do I do?
I feel like I should just get this.
Enchant the club.
Or better armor.
The waist?
Armor.
Okay.
A shield?
I could get a shield.
Okay.
What else can I get?
Shin guards?
All right.
Okay.
I can get shin guards.
All right.
I think I'm ready.
I already have these, right?
Potions?
I can't buy potions.
I don't have enough magic.
Okay.
You need four magicka to buy potion.
Go enchant.
Okay.
Enchant.
So I'm going to enchant with...
I'm going to enchant my rusty knife.
With fire.
Or ice?
Yeah.
We're going to fire.
That's one flame, one frost, one poison.
Yeah.
We're just going to fire.
Whatever.
Potency.
Add three fire damage.
That's...
For free?
All right.
That's pretty sick.
Let's go.
I'm ready.
I'm going to beat John the Butcher right now.
I'm so sick of this.
Okay.
I've got 107 armor.
Let's go.
Burnt him with my sound?
Am I finally going to beat the butcher?
Please.
With my yell build?
I told you to do this build.
Yeah.
But I don't know.
I was under the impression that this was just a joke
that we were doing in the beginning of the game.
I didn't know it was actually viable.
I want the money.
He's got a long way to go before he gets over here.
No.
He's coming.
Hold on.
Oh, that hurt.
Good.
Good, good.
All right.
No.
Back up.
Back him up.
Come on.
There it is.
Again.
All right.
15 charisma.
For John the butcher,
I think I'm going to have to do some more defense.
What vitality?
Which one?
Vitality probably?
Yeah.
All right.
Bring him on.
Let's go.
I'm done with this bullshit.
There it is.
All right.
38.
38 again.
This is the win.
This is the win right now.
Get away from me.
Eventually, it's going to work.
It's a matter of time.
Oh, you know what?
Let's get a little step.
No, let's not get a little.
Move him away.
Nice.
Come on.
Please.
Let me beat John the butcher.
Yes.
Finally.
He's dead.
It took like an hour.
12,500 gold pieces.
What?
Oh, my God.
Okay.
Well, now I need to figure out what the hell I'm going to do.
Breastplate.
I have to get this one, right?
64 armor.
So I just dump all my money into this breastplate.
3% damage taken converted to energy.
What about a shield?
Definitely this one.
Look at this thing.
Okay.
Nice.
All right.
What about this one?
Now enchant.
Enchant weapon.
Enchant.
More potency.
Do fire again?
Buy a weapon.
Oh, I don't have enough money for a weapon.
Save at the church.
I need to make an account to save and I'm not doing it.
All right.
Let's try this.
Level five.
All right.
Look at all this armor, though.
This guy doesn't have any armor.
I just instantly killed that guy.
I just made money.
This guy doesn't have any armor either.
All right.
We're going to work with the crowd.
I want to work with the crowd a little bit.
I'm just...
Wait.
Did I just burn him with...
I just farted on him and I burnt him?
What the hell was that?
It was a charisma fart.
Don't let him get the first hit.
All right.
Crowd's entertained.
Hold on.
Interested.
Entertained.
Enthusiastic.
Okay.
I don't care.
I'm still dancing.
Let's fill that bar.
Wildly entertained.
More.
Transfixed.
Fanatical.
And...
Come on.
Get him.
All right.
Get him out of transfixed.
Fanatical.
How much money do you get for doing this?
Back up.
All right.
Here we go.
Just kill him.
Just punch him in the face.
3,200...
3,300 gold for that.
Holy shit.
What do I do?
Not all charisma.
I can't be a dope.
I mean, maybe one.
One more.
New weapon.
What do we need?
What do we want?
Bow?
No.
What about this?
I got 6,000 gold.
I kind of need to do that.
I have to buy this.
Don't buy a weapon, you dummy.
More armor.
Okay.
Let's replace the chin guards.
Ooh.
Look at these ones.
Yeah.
Nice.
Okay.
New greaves.
Oh, look at these.
Veteran greaves.
Nice.
Okay.
What about new boots?
Oh, veteran boots.
Greaves.
Okay.
All right.
I'm gonna say about...
Level 9.
229 armor.
Easy.
Easy with this.
Block that.
3,700 gold, dude.
Looking pretty good.
Just level 3.
Why is a level 3 fighting a level 6?
Save up for the better helmet?
You're never gonna break my armor, dude.
I'm gonna sit here all day until I get the most amount of money possible.
Nice weapon.
I had 200...
I had 200 armor.
How did that happen?
A crit goes through armor?
Oh, you shitting me.
Don't...
Okay.
Just kill him.
Can even shoot...
Okay.
He's dead.
I just beat John the Butcher, chat.
Did you?
Nice.
He's tough.
Hey.
He's pretty tough.
Nice work.
Swift sandals, was that?
Don't crit me.
That counts, right?
Chauvin taunt.
Don't ever use your weapon.
So just never upgrade the weapon?
Never.
What the hell?
I don't want to just do only...
All right, I'm going to bed.
Okay, I'm going to bed.
6900.
I'm gonna save it.
I'm gonna save the money.
All right.
No, no, no.
I'm not.
No, I'm not.
Okay.
What can I replace that's expensive?
Gauntlets?
Yeah.
Okay.
What are these?
Yeah.
Get these things.
Nice.
All right.
What about the...
60 armor, 50 armor, 40 armor, 30 armor.
Okay.
Helmet, you fool.
All right, I got it.
All right, let's go.
Let's kick this guy's ass.
What's the next tournament?
The evil ninja.
What the hell is this?
Psych up?
Psych up two?
Psych up three.
What the hell am I doing?
To charge up power mood.
Yeah, but I just yell at people, right?
Yeah, what's the point of doing that?
Screaming and farting.
It really is.
I think I can fill that bar.
He's not going to kill me.
Fart and scream build.
I know.
Well, look, I didn't intend for that to happen tonight.
He's in close.
Just kill him.
Don't use your weapon.
Well, sometimes we have like a 70% chance.
That's good.
Here we go.
We have next coming up is another level seven.
Haunt is 99.
My god, it's so stupid.
It's so stupid.
That sword looks kind of scary.
No farting.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I haven't incorporated it.
I got to get my rotation.
Okay, what happened?
Here comes the evil ninja.
Okay, let's get the crowd behind us.
He's got no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We do not.
We just go.
Oh, come on.
Does it not work?
He has shout protection.
It doesn't work.
I can't kill him.
He has shout protection.
Where did it go?
What just happened?
He just pulled my.
Am I seriously going to lose because he has like shout protection?
No.
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
Why did you guys tell me that was 57 fucking damage?
Yet.
Why is it not hurting him though?
It should be hurting him.
No, it don't work.
It doesn't work.
It's over.
Did I do it?
Oh, shit.
That was stupid.
Didn't do anything.
One of these has to land, right?
It says blocked.
Holy shit.
It worked.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, ladies and gentlemen.
Hold on a second.
Everyone relax.
Everyone relax for a sec.
I did 57 damage.
We're OK.
We're going to be fine.
Good.
Keep doing that.
I hope you keep doing that.
Stick to the plan.
I'm going to stick to the plan.
Chad is bored to tears.
Oh, hold on a sec.
It's working.
Wait, it's working.
Just wait.
All right, fine.
You want to play that game?
Now you're just bored silly.
57.
Let's go.
Come on.
57 again.
Back to back.
Plus 85.
He's got healing potions.
Of course he does.
Get away from me.
Get the fuck away from me.
Get away.
One more and it's over.
And we thought I was going to lose.
We thought I was going to lose that one.
No, not that one.
17,000 gold.
I'll take it.
What do I got on now?
This?
This is double the armor.
OK.
Shoulder guards?
No, I already have the best ones on.
No, I don't.
48.
Gauntlets.
Shield.
OK.
That's a big deal.
72 armor.
Let's go.
Greaves.
I have the best greaves on.
Chin guards.
Yeah, these are the worst.
Put these on please.
Improve that shoulder.
No, I can't.
Get a fucking weapon.
All right, I'm just going to get a weapon
because why wouldn't I?
Just give me the turkey leg.
Who cares?
I don't have money.
Oh, well potency two.
Whatever.
All right, let's go.
Sorry.
Sorry about that.
OK.
Hey, soy.
Soy boy.
Thanks for the five community subs.
They like me better.
I got way more charisma than you.
37,000 back in gold, dude.
Need more stamina.
I'll do.
I'm going to just load into stamina after this.
No more charisma.
More charisma.
What?
One more.
All right, bang.
Got him.
4,400.
No, just do more charisma.
Yeah, but I don't.
I want to be able to land.
I don't know, man.
That seems kind of like.
Am I going to beat this whole game by yelling at people?
How can you stomach playing this for two hours?
I don't know.
Kind of just fun.
I've been having a good time.
I'm just chilling, man.
I'm just having.
I'm just hanging out having a good time.
We're just chilling today.
It's fun.
Yeah, it's fun.
How dare you stop enjoying this?
Just chill, screaming and farting
and yelling and losing to the first tutorial boss for an hour.
You know?
All right, this guy's got shout protection too.
There it is.
What is the last level in this game?
How hard does it go?
He's a little too close.
Goes forever.
Don't let him do that.
Okay.
All right, I got to level up here.
I'm thinking you get a new quiver.
Whatever.
I'm thinking charisma and defense.
Or stamina.
Or actually magic.
Stamina and charisma.
Okay.
All right, it's tournament time.
Tournament time.
What can I upgrade here?
Breastplate.
Can't do that yet.
How about a new helmet?
No.
I'm going to get...
What about boots?
No.
Chin guards?
Greaves?
No.
Gauntlets?
Shield?
No.
Shoulders are the only thing I can do.
Okay.
All right.
You get the discount.
Try to buy it.
Wait, what?
Oh, shit.
Would you look at that?
Oh, well.
We'll come back.
Potions?
I can't buy potions.
I don't need them.
I don't need them and I can't buy them anyways.
This game looks better than Watch Dogs.
I mean...
God.
That game.
I swear to God.
That's...
Okay.
That's not nominated for anything.
Are the game awards right?
Is that nominated for even one award?
I hope not.
Is it?
No, it's not.
What is it nominated for?
No, it is not.
Bullshit.
What's it nominated for?
Tell me.
It's not nominated for the game of the year.
No, it's not.
Nothing.
Good.
Where'd he go?
Oh, he's...
Remember, I worked so hard on that game.
Stop.
Don't...
Hey.
That's not...
Dude, quit hitting your bong.
I don't think I could hit a bong, man.
I really don't think I could in real life.
I would probably fucking fall down.
I would hit the bong.
It'd be like...
I gotta be...
Because my head would just fucking hit the table.
I'm not doing that.
No.
I want to be able to control exactly what I'm doing.
I'm back to how much I'm taking.
Yeah, and why did I just do that like I was eating spaghetti?
That was not a good bong sound.
That was like you're slipping up like spaghetti and meatballs.
What is that?
This is...
This is not...
I'm not even having fun.
This is just like screaming.
I'm not...
I feel like I'm not even playing.
I'm just like looking at you guys and talking.
I've kept my mouth in the same place, I think, for the last
four or five straight minutes.
Play Doodle God?
Oh, I played the absolute hell out of that a long time ago.
Okay, Son of Stylonius.
Not yet.
Hey, Doodle God, right now.
Well, link it to me.
Turn off the stream.
What?
I'm not done yet.
Remember, he hits the bong and dies.
Hold on.
Let's hear this.
Curious.
Not what I intended for that to sound like.
I wanted that to sound like this.
I wanted it to sound like this.
For some reason, when I go through the stream,
I don't know why, but I'm going to leave it on this for a little while.
Hold on.
Is it?
Let's find out.
Let me find out.
Let me find out if it's...
Now, let me tell you.
I am not...
Madam Secretary, I am not going to stand down here
and not give a stimulus.
No, no.
The American people are going to be just fine.
They're going to be fine.
Mitch McConnell has a joker laugh, by the way.
Listen to Mitch McConnell laugh at something.
He does the Jared Leto joker.
Seriously, it's like...
Eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh.
How do you laugh like that?
Think about it, people that...
You know, when you laugh, you just go...
Or like...
Is that political?
Political.
All right, here he comes.
Son of Stylonius.
Scream at him.
I win.
Nice fart.
I can match your fart with a fart, too.
You want to get farts on?
All right, fine.
Let's go.
Oh, he's charging something.
Nice.
Okay, you missed.
People are wildly entertained by that, too.
Oh, he's burnt.
Piss on him.
You can't even pee on people in this game.
And if you can, I don't know.
I'm not going to probably unlock it yet.
I won.
Congratulations, you have won.
I kind of feel like I have not been in the arena yet.
Okay.
Emperor Antares has granted you 22,500 gold.
The hour is late.
Okay, find a tavern.
Sleep peacefully.
All right, that was fun.
I'm going to move on to Doodle God now.
Let's move on.
Let's do Doodle God.
Yeah, this game is cool.
But like, I don't know.
I don't want to just yell at people for another hour or something.
That's too much.
I like it.
It's a really fun game.
And I remember it.
It's very nostalgic.
But we are going to do this.
Doodle God.
I remember this game.
Might be a little too big.
Let's make it a little bit smaller.
Okay, a little.
Just a little.
Okay.
Remember, you normally just yell at us for hours.
What?
I don't.
You do that to me.
All right, Doodle God, play.
You can now play Doodle God on your phone.
Check it out.
iPhone version has priority in getting updates.
In the beginning, there was only Doodle God.
Doodle God created the four basic elements.
Earth, water, fire, air.
From Earth, Doodle God created the planets.
From water, seas, and oceans were created.
From fire were created volcanoes and other stuff.
From air, you know, the world is still vast.
I know what the game is.
Okay, here we go.
We're going to do we're going to do fire and we're going to do Earth.
And that is going to make stone lava.
If your heart is a volcano, how shall you expect flowers to bloom?
They get quotes.
Okay, cool.
There's a new element in the group now.
Yeah, there is.
Now we have lava.
We can do lava and Earth.
Earth and lava equals the same thing Earth and fire do.
How about air and lava, steam, stone?
We have stone and water equals sand.
Cool.
Now we can do let's do air, air and sand.
Air and Earth creates dust.
How about fire and sand makes glass?
I know that from Minecraft.
Teaching children all these things too.
Don't forget that your little brother plays Minecraft.
It's teaching him things.
Dust and glass, dust and stone, dust and sand, dust and Earth, air and dust.
Air and water, steam.
There it is.
How about steam and fire equals plasma?
Glass and steam.
Fire and steam, fire and dust is ash.
Who suggested this?
I don't know, man.
We're just jumping around.
We're just hanging out.
Sand and steam, stone and ash, Earth and ash, Earth and steam.
Dust and glass, steam and sand, water and ash, water and dust, water and steam, water and air,
steam.
Turn off the game sounds.
All right.
You don't like them?
You're too loud.
Okay, Earth, sand and sand, sand and stone.
Play nitrome.
What is nitrome?
Nitrome now, nitrome now.
Let me at least get to plasma.
Fire and, fire and steam, fire and water is alcohol.
Alcohol and, alcohol and water.
Okay, alcohol and a ton of water.
Spotlight.
What is nitrome?
I don't get it.
Lava and vodka makes fireball.
I'm sorry, I had to.
High quality indie game.
What is, okay, nitrome.
Is it on, where is it?
What about glass and alcohol?
This is like, well, that's just, that doesn't make any sense.
Alcohol and sand.
Alcohol and Earth.
Fire and alcohol makes bomb, energy.
Okay, energy and Earth, oh, look at this.
Okay, energy and air makes storm.
Energy and steam, energy and storm.
How about fire and energy?
No?
How about energy and Earth, energy and stone.
Energy and sand, energy and glass.
Dead Rising 2, Waiting Room.
I played that game through like two or three times.
I like beat that whole game.
What are you talking about?
Alcohol and energy, lava and energy.
About energy and water, energy and alcohol, energy and water.
Energy and alcohol, vodka and energy.
Vodka, Red Bull, I don't know.
iCarly PSP Waiting Room.
I'm not going to fucking buy that game.
No, I'm not getting that game shipped here, okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm not going to play iCarly PSP game.
Double energy?
Hmm, now you're onto something.
No, you're not.
All right, how about fire and energy is not...
Wouldn't fire and energy be like destruction or something?
What am I missing?
Air and Earth, dust.
Fire and Earth?
I already did fire and Earth, didn't I?
Yeah, it's lava.
Water and Earth makes mud.
Swamp, okay, swamp and energy.
Swamp and energy is going to make a frog.
Life, okay, life and steam.
I want everything to combine with steam.
I don't know why.
Air and life, ash and life is a ghost.
I've created death.
Ghost and glass, ghost and sand, stone, Earth ghost.
How about ghost and life?
How about energy and ghost?
No, about life and Earth, life and stone.
Egg, egg and energy equals bird.
Egg and life equals bird.
Egg and steam is bird.
Egg and air is bird, got it.
See how the game is progressing, chat?
Yeah, okay, now we got animals, bird and life.
Bird and energy is a phoenix.
No, that's fire and bird.
There you go, look at me, look at me, look at your idiot.
Life and death, no, you can't do that.
It's too powerful.
How about egg and glass?
Bird and alcohol, vodka and bird, bird and swamp.
Water and bird, seagull, no?
Sand and bird, Earth and bird, ostrich, stone bird.
Life and water, weeds, life and sand, sand plus bird.
Weeds and energy, weeds and life, weeds and egg, no?
Water and weeds, alcohol and weeds, swamp and weeds.
There we go, all right, now we got moth.
Moss and alcohol, moss and stone, moss and Earth is grass.
Grass and life is bugs.
Energy and grass is bugs, eggs and grass is bugs.
Moss and grass, weeds and grass, fire and grass is tobacco.
Tobacco and air is smoke.
Tobacco and ash, tobacco and steam, storm and grass,
steam and grass, dust and grass, air and grass.
Tobacco and bong is, all right, ghost and tobacco,
phoenix and grass.
These alchemy games always get me hooked.
So it's so much fun to try all the combos.
Yeah, it is.
How about kind of something with bird?
Bird and weeds, moss and bird, and life and bird, no?
How do we make a life and sand to seeds?
Here we go, seeds and water is plants, right?
I mean, that's very obvious, right?
It has to be.
Seeds and water, fucking dumb game.
Really?
Seeds and grass, kidding me?
Life and seeds, egg seeds, energy and seeds.
What?
Seeds and bird, what the fuck?
Seeds and Earth, tree, tree and bird, bird family.
Tree and tree is forest.
Seeds?
What about air and tree?
Anything?
Tree and dust, steam tree, ash tree, storm tree.
I'm not gonna, I can't do it.
I can't do it.
Those are all last names of different Warcraft characters.
Whatever, I'm not gonna do it.
You know what I was gonna do.
I'm not gonna do it.
I refuse.
Shadowlands, game's got the fastest selling PC games of all time.
It really changed a bunch of stuff for the better.
It's like, it's pretty, I mean, it's a stupid fucking game.
I don't know why, if you play that game, then you seriously have to be dumb.
There's no way you're not dumb if you play that, right?
I don't play.
Why is it the fastest selling PC game ever?
Fucking game sucks.
Energy and phoenix.
No, energy and, there's gotta be something else here.
Egg and here we go.
Dinosaur.
Entrairian loser.
No, game's fucking stupid, like dumb game.
All those warlock changes look pretty fun.
Fucking stupid game, stupid shitty game.
Air and dinosaur is dragon.
This is not funny.
Somebody's actually really upset today.
This is for real.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Look, all right, I bought it.
All right, I bought it.
And what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna be mad at me?
Are you gonna yell at me?
I bought it and I played it.
You're gonna be upset with me about this?
Fine, I'm gonna admit you.
Here we go.
I bought Shadowlands and guess what?
I'm having some fun.
Not that, not very much, but I'm having fun with it.
It's very good so far.
I've played it a little bit.
Kill this man.
He bought Shadowlands, oh mega low.
Look, I haven't played the game since Legion and I was just looking at it.
I haven't played it for like two weeks.
I just told you.
How dare you?
I know, like what the fuck?
Add Shadowlands to the dead.
Why?
Because I bought it?
He wasn't sick.
He was playing Shadowlands.
Now that's horseshit.
That's not even real.
You know, I actually was, I was.
It's not even real.
The truth comes out.
No, no, are you kidding me?
I would not stop streaming for like a week to play Shadowlands.
I've just been, I've like smelled it a few times.
I would not do that.
A tree in life.
A tree in, oh my god.
Just like that game, just like that game.
World of Warcraft with the tree.
It's where the, at Mount Hyjal.
I mean, why are you doing this?
That could mean a lot of different things.
Why am I talking about Shadowlands?
Why did I admit that I bought Shadowlands?
Why am I playing flash games?
Why am I playing Doodle God?
Why have I not played Cyberpunk?
Why are you not playing Cyberpunk?
I mean, I could answer that.
That depends on what you mean.
There's a lot of different answers there.
All right, what's sand and where's the Swiss Swamp?
Swiss Swamp.
Clay, okay, cool.
How about clay and clay and earth?
Stone and clay, sand and clay, glass and clay.
Life and clay, that's gonna be a golem.
Cool, all right.
What about dragon and, dragon and fire?
Did I make like a fire dragon?
Life and go, I made a human.
There it is, finally.
I did it.
Wait, you actually bought Shadowlands.
No, I didn't.
I did not.
Human and human is baby.
Sex.
Sex and, let's see.
Sex and, sex and water?
Sex in the swamp?
Sex on the beach?
Sex in the backyard?
Nope, sex on the, it sucks, sex up in a tree.
Passion and sex, sex and eggs.
I don't know, sex and eggs.
Sex and energy, it's like, whatever.
I'm starting to get a little weird here.
Sex and sex.
I'm trying to combine stuff.
Sex and sex is sex too.
Sex with a dinosaur.
I want to click it, but I can't.
God, God is sitting in the clouds.
Oh my God, sex, oh, sex in a tree.
Sex in the water, oh, sex with a dinosaur.
Sex with a bird.
What else, I wonder what else we could do.
Sex with a dragon.
Sex with a ghost.
Sex, he just had a whiteboard,
just writing all this shit down.
No, no, no, oh, sex while playing the harmonica.
Yeah, that's a good one.
I think I'll do that one too.
Steam and sand.
No, I keep doing steam and swamp and sand.
No, I did that already.
Fire, yeah, fire and clay, that's a good one.
Makes bricks.
New element, structure.
Bricks and water.
Bricks and life.
Energy and bricks.
Eggs and bricks.
Seeds and bricks.
Sex and bricks.
Bricks and sex.
I don't know what, I don't know what you're doing.
Um, I don't know why you need a brick.
Okay, never mind.
Like, um, what?
Dude, no.
Hold on, I'm starting to like see stars.
That was, I laughed too hard very quickly.
Hold on.
Smash with a brick.
No, guys, that's ridiculous.
That would fucking hurt so bad.
All right, I'm gonna be all right.
I'm gonna be fine.
What's, what's the, the bricks and the bees?
The birds and the bricks?
The birds and the bees?
The birds and the bricks.
Okay, how about bricks and sand?
Bricks and earth?
Bricks and stone.
Clay and bricks.
How do you make a house?
Bricks and glass?
How about human and brick?
That's not gonna work.
You know, can I tell you guys,
one of my favorite words in the English language is brick.
It's the perfect word for what that is.
I love that word.
When you think of the word brick,
you just see this heavy, thick, dense,
just clump of fucking a heavy, dense thing.
It's just, I love the word.
It's perfect.
Why is he not playing Nitro?
I will in a second.
Hold on.
Dinosaur and water.
It's like a water dinosaur, right?
Dinosaur and swamp?
Alligator?
Hey, Morty, I turned myself into a brick.
No, that's not funny.
If it was a pickle, I might have laughed at it.
That wouldn't be baby.
Pickle, brick.
All right, that's enough.
Tobacco and free.
What am I looking for?
I don't want to do that, but oh, coal.
Sex and life.
Sex and egg.
No, sex and life didn't work.
Human and brick.
I already did a human and brick.
It didn't do anything.
Oh my God.
Human and moss.
Human and weeds.
Can I make like a swamp person?
Fire and human.
Oh, corpse and air.
I don't know.
Corpse and dust.
Corpse and...
What about corpse and life?
Zombie.
Zombie and coal.
I don't know.
I'm trying to get away from...
What's the new game?
What was the new game?
Was it called Nitroam or something?
Bricks and coal.
Yeah, that's a good one.
Wait, what's coal?
Brick and coal.
No, nothing.
Remember, you good?
I'm fine.
I need another building material.
How do you build a house?
Wood.
Where's wood?
Where the hell's wood?
Tree and axe.
Where's wood?
Where's tree?
Tree and something to break it.
Life and tree?
No, that's tree and...
Brick and brick.
Mud and brick.
Yeah, how do you make mud?
Earth and water?
I think I've already done that.
Yeah, I already did that.
Water and clay?
I need tools.
Yeah, how do I make tools?
Human and vodka.
Alcoholic.
What?
Alcoholic?
And I don't understand.
What?
Human and corpse.
About...
Egg and corpse.
Energy and corpse.
Human and energy.
A wizard!
Fire wizard.
Coal wizard.
Oh, that face went no wizard.
Sex.
Oh, my fucking face hurts right now.
It's so stupid.
Wizard and energy.
Who makes a demigod?
Okay, if you have sex with a demigod,
that means that that's how like...
Isn't that like...
Yeah, aren't they like Dante, right?
This makes a quarter god.
Hercules.
Somebody said Dante.
Yeah, Dante.
Is Dante from Devil May Cry a quarter god?
Don't you feel like that eventually?
If let's say like, you know, demigods were, you know, procreating,
you know, procreating, and they were, you know, demigods,
and now you have, you know, just like a human and a demigod,
and then, you know, eventually you get to the point
where you have like, like 2% demigod on like Ancestry.com.
He would be like, I'm a demigod!
That's me!
They'd be like, just you stand over there, man.
I'm gonna try to like shoot fireballs at you.
Like, that's not how it works, dude.
Just fucking relax.
Yeah, like fucking like 27 million years ago,
you had a demigod.
Okay, whatever.
And he said, I thought the gladiator yelling was boring,
but you managed to outdo yourself.
I'll time that person up for an hour.
No, I'll do it.
What's your name?
I don't remember you.
There you are.
There they go.
Right click.
Ban for 72 days.
Oh, he actually died.
You actually died about.
All right, after 10 minutes, reverse that ban.
I just want them to know what they did.
Egg and grass?
I feel like I need to do more stuff with eggs.
Human plus computer.
I don't have a computer.
Do brick and brick.
Would that actually do anything?
Where is brick?
Okay, brick and brick.
No, that's not gonna do anything.
Brick and corpse.
No, I tried that already.
Clay and water.
I'm gonna like lose track where everything is.
Let's go for it.
No, swamp and...
I need to make mud or like cement.
Bacteria.
Oh shit.
Okay, hold on.
Bacteria and dinosaur?
Bacteria and...
Not that.
Come on, earth and bacteria.
Stone and...
I could make some kind of animal, right?
Bird bacteria.
Water bacteria.
Energy bacteria.
Life bacteria.
Egg bacteria.
Look, I'm just gonna do it because I have to.
Water and bacteria.
There we go.
Oh, plankton.
Okay.
Plankton and...
Plankton and energy.
Plankton and egg.
Plankton and seed.
Plankton and sex.
The secret formula.
Sand and earth and plankton.
Worm.
Okay, we're getting somewhere.
Worm and earth.
Earthworm.
Beetle.
Beetle and tree.
Beetle and...
Grass and beetle.
Grass and worm.
No.
Sand and worm.
There's a snake.
All right, we got another animal.
Bird and worm.
Let's try that.
No.
Bird and plankton.
Bird and weeds.
Bird and beetles.
Snake and worm.
There's a lizard.
I still need...
I make bricks.
Lizards and worms.
Beetle lizard.
Snake beetle.
Moss lizard.
Snake moss.
Dinosaur beetle.
Weed bird.
Bird bacteria.
Plankton dinosaur.
Snake worm.
Oh, whoops.
Snake and water.
Lizard and water.
Fish.
Okay.
Fish and...
I don't know.
Fish and what?
Fish and...
Snake?
Fish and bird?
Fish and grass?
Fish and water.
Fish and alcohol.
Swamp fish.
Lizard and fire.
You just burn it.
Just toss the lizard in the fire.
Why would you do that?
I don't know.
I just...
It's on the whiteboard, I guess.
I don't know.
Let's take it off.
Energy and lizard.
Life and lizard.
Egg and lizard.
Lizard and grass.
Lizard and swamp.
Lizard and water.
Snake and swamp.
Fish and...
I'm surprised fish and water doesn't make something else.
I guess it is just a fish.
Lizard zombie.
Ghost...
A ghost fish.
Lizard fish.
Snake ghost.
Lizard ghost.
A human snake.
Fish sex.
Lizard sex.
Snake sex.
Bird sex.
Dinosaur sex.
I don't know.
No, I'm talking about like...
It's just a term.
It's not like you...
It's not you having sex with a lizard, okay?
It's just the terminology for like procreation.
I feel like I haven't been using fire for anything.
Fire and bacteria.
Beetle fire.
Worm and lava.
Fire and worm.
There we go.
Oh my god, whatever.
Fire and grass?
No, tobacco.
What? Tobacco and human.
I haven't tried that at all.
Fish and plankton.
Hmm.
Good call.
That's a really good call.
Look at that.
It made a whale.
Look at that genius in the chat.
Genius.
Lizard and earth.
There we go.
Beast.
You trying to get me to buy it?
Like, I don't even have a lot of fun, but...
I mean, it's on the app store.
Go get it.
Beast and human.
Makes a werewolf.
Makes a domestic animal.
Okay, domestic animal and energy.
Life and egg.
Seeds.
Snake and beast.
Beast snake.
Lizard beast.
Cow snake.
Fish cow.
Whales cow.
Beast whale.
Fire...
Fire cow.
Fire beast.
Fire whale.
Fire bird.
Phoenix.
I already did it.
Do beetle and sand.
Okay.
Sand and beetle, you said?
Sand.
That's not right.
Here, it's over here.
Oh, scorpion.
Nice.
Okay.
This game's...
I'm addicted to this game.
It's fun.
We'll change.
Once that guy's time out comes up, we'll change.
Worm and stone?
Scorpion and earth.
Scorpion and sand.
Scorpion and clay.
No.
Scorpion and snake?
Fish?
Scorpion and lizard together.
Fire and stone.
I haven't done fire and stone yet.
Are you serious?
How have I not done that?
What?
Metal and brick equals house.
Tree and metal equals water and metal.
Alcohol and metal.
Fire and metal.
Lava...
Coal and metal.
Lizard and metal.
Human metal.
Tools!
Finally!
Okay, tools and we got a lot to do here.
Tools and energy.
Tools and life.
Tools and eggs.
Tools and seeds.
Tools and sex.
Human tools.
Corpse tools.
Wizard tools.
Demigod tools.
Alcohol tools.
Air and tools.
Dust tools.
Steam tools.
Ash tools.
Storm tools.
Brick and tools.
What?
Earth and tools is field, okay.
About metal and tools, obviously, right?
It has to be metal and tools.
Weapon.
Human and weapon is going to make like a fighter.
Hunter.
Hunter and beast equals food.
Meat, wool, and blood.
Okay.
Meat, what is it like?
Lettuce, like meat?
Okay, meat, lettuce, tomato.
It's like a whopper, like it comes together.
Wool and human.
Sweater.
Corpse meat.
Wizard meat.
Tools and wool.
It's your fabric.
Meat and fire.
It's a good one.
Wow, okay.
That's actually pretty surprising.
Tools and meat.
Brick and tool.
Okay, I'm surprised brick and tool doesn't do anything.
Tools and fabric.
No.
Water and fabric.
Alcohol.
Water and field.
No, okay.
Grass and field.
Blood and field.
Blood and bricks.
Blood and life.
That sounds like a good one.
Blood and egg.
Energy and blood.
I'm not going to do it.
I'm not going to click that.
Seeds.
Oh, fire.
Yeah.
Seeds and fields.
You're right.
Where are those seeds?
Hey, where's the seeds?
What do I do with them?
There.
Seed and field equals crops.
Air and blood.
Blood and storm.
Blood and snake.
Lizard blood.
Bird blood.
No.
Grass blood.
Tree blood.
Maple syrup.
Fire and blood.
Blood with water?
No.
Tree and tools.
There you go.
Wood.
Finally.
That took forever.
Now let's go with wood and...
Wood and tools again, right?
Yeah.
Makes a wheel.
Blood and stone.
Blood and earth.
Blood and metal.
Blood and sand.
Blood and...
It doesn't do anything.
Blood and clay.
Blood and weapon.
Oh, that's not a bad idea.
Too bad.
Ooh, blood and zombie.
Meat and zombie, right?
That would be a good one.
Blood and blood.
Hmm, I tried that.
Coal and fire.
Blood and human.
Oh, shit.
Vampire?
Vampire.
Okay, vampire and wood
is like a stake through the heart
which makes a corpse, right?
Sex and vampire.
A human vampire is just
a double vampire, I guess?
Wheel and energy.
What could I do with wheel?
Wool and wheel?
No.
Tools and wheel.
Wood and...
Metal and wheel.
Stone and wheel.
Really?
Glass and wheel?
Come on.
Brick and wheel?
No?
Oh, there we go.
Cart.
Steam and metal, somebody said.
I'll try it.
Steam and metal.
Hell yeah.
Boiler.
Cart and...
Wheel and animal?
Cart and animal?
Hold on.
Wheel and animal.
Cart and animal.
Wheel and beast.
Wheel and whale.
Cart and lizard.
Snake cart.
Wheel dinosaur.
No.
Boiler and human.
Okay.
No.
Boiler and hunter.
Weapon and human.
I already got it.
Wheel, whale.
I haven't done anything with meat.
How have I not done anything with meat?
How about life and meat?
Energy and meat?
How have I not found anything?
Human meat.
Hunter meat.
Alcoholic meat.
Wizard meat.
What can I do?
Hunter and...
What about some of these other animals?
Hunter and bird.
Oh, feather.
Okay.
All right.
Let's do...
I want to do hunter on the other one.
On everything else too.
Hunter and dinosaur.
Is just blood.
Okay.
Hunter and snake.
Hunter and lizard.
Hunter and fish.
Hunter and whale.
Hunter and beast.
Okay.
What about hunter and...
Tree and tool.
I think I did wood already, right?
Yeah.
Human and snake.
Oh, nope.
That was a pretty good idea though.
That was a good idea.
Hunter and vampire.
Hunter and zombie.
Hunter and ghost.
Hunter and tree and...
Hunter and golem.
Hunter and dragon.
What?
Oh, I get it.
The hunter's dead.
Energy and demigod.
Energy and wizard is demigod.
So energy and demigod makes...
What?
Life and demigod?
Blood and demigod.
Well, demigods don't have blood.
They don't like electricity or something.
Yeah, I got to combine wheat with something.
The boiler and the wheel.
Boiler and wheel.
Let's see.
Boiler and boiler.
Boiler and weapon.
Boiler and tools.
Okay.
Boiler and wood.
Boiler and fabric.
Boiler and bricks.
Boiler and field.
Boiler and...
Boiler and metal.
Boiler and stone.
What'd you say?
Boiler and cart.
Boiler and wheel.
No.
Weapon and cart.
Weapon and wheel.
Tools and cart.
No, really.
Hunter and hunter.
Okay.
Hunter.
Hunter and hunter.
Hunter, hunter.
Doesn't do anything.
Hunter and human...
Human hunter?
Water and wheel.
Smart.
Very smart.
Hunter x hunter.
Um, oh.
All right, never mind.
Let's do water and wheel.
Wait, water and field?
No.
Water and wood?
Boat!
Cool. All right, I got a boat.
But what was the last one you guys want to do?
Water and what?
Water and human.
Water and hunter.
Corpse in the water.
Alcohol in the water.
Wizard in the water.
Wheel. Right, right, right.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Damn.
Cart and water.
Boat in water.
Alcohol in the boat.
Alcohol...
A boat in a swamp.
Energy in the wheel.
I'm gonna try everything with the wheel, actually.
Let's go.
No, okay.
Meat in the cart.
Meat in the boat.
Meat in the wheel.
Wool in the cart.
Wool in the boat.
Wool in the wheel.
Weed in the cart.
Weed in the boat.
Weed in the wheel.
Feather in the wheel.
Feather in the cart.
Feather in the boat.
Air in the wheel.
Air in the cart.
Air in the boat.
Dust in the wheel.
Dust in the cart.
Dust in the boat.
Steam in the wheel.
Steam in the cart.
Steam in the boat.
And you know the rest.
Storm in the wheel.
Storm in the cart.
And storm in the boat.
We've got a bird in the wheel.
A bird in the cart.
A bird in the boat.
A whale in the wheel.
A whale in the cart.
A whale in the boat.
A dinosaur.
That's too many syllables.
Animal in cart.
I'm surprised this one doesn't work.
Fish boat.
What's storm in metal?
That's a good...
This is such a chill day right now.
I'm just chilling.
You guys chilling?
This is kind of nice.
I like this.
Storm in metal.
No, fuck you.
Fuck you.
No, you suck.
No, no.
Oh my god.
What the hell?
What's going on here?
You guys are making me sad.
Storm in metal.
Nope.
Metal and energy, mate.
Oh, here we go.
A countess flagrant.
Boosie?
Boochie?
Energy in metal.
Dude.
Oh, yes.
Fabric and feathers, please.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
But I got electricity.
Zombie and...
What's electricity and stone?
Electricity and metal.
Oh, electricity and stone.
Electricity and glass.
Fire and electricity.
Boat and electricity.
Motorboat.
Water and wind.
Oh, wait.
I got steam.
Electricity and human.
Just electrocute them?
Boiler and coal.
Go for it.
Damn, there it is.
Steam engine.
Okay.
Now we're getting real.
Steam engine and tools.
Steam engine and weapon.
Steam engine and cart.
Steam engine and steam.
Does that sound...
Oh.
Electricity boiler.
Yeah, you know what?
We're going to do some spamming here.
Because I really feel like electricity is going to work with so much stuff.
Electricity, energy.
Let's just go for it.
Electricity, egg.
Electricity, sex.
Seeds, no.
Meat, electricity, wool.
I have feathers too.
No.
Electricity, scorpion.
Electricity, metal.
No.
None of this works.
Electric, snake.
Hold on.
Electricity, water.
Alcohol.
Swamp.
Really?
Electricity and snake.
No.
Damn it.
Guys, we're not trying to make Pokemon here.
We're trying to combine elements.
Use one of the hints.
Some of these may react.
Vodka and lava.
Swamp and coal.
Swamp and lava.
Swamp and fire.
Vodka and coal.
Vodka and lava.
Vodka and fire.
Alcohol and coal.
Alcohol and lava.
Alcohol and fire.
Energy.
That wasn't it.
Where the hell is it?
What did I not do?
Water and fire?
Wait, what?
Water and coal?
Oil!
Do water and water.
Please, I'm having an aneurysm.
Water and water.
Alright, settle down, man.
This doesn't do anything.
You were freaking out for no reason, man.
Okay, oil and...
What should I do?
Oil and what?
Oil and...
Life?
Oil and electricity.
Oil and energy.
Blood and oil.
Seeds and oil.
Sex, oil.
Worm, oil.
Human and oil.
No.
Two minutes for another hint, motherfuck.
Phoenix and oil.
Vampire oil.
Dragon oil.
Sand and oil.
Metal and oil.
Earth and oil.
Clay and oil.
Stone and oil.
Wait, wait, we have tools.
Tools and oil.
Steam engine and oil.
Boiler and oil.
Weapon oil, come on.
Meat and oil.
Wool.
Wheat.
Feather.
Damn.
Heart and...
Ooh, there it is.
Alright, finally, I got a car.
Car and human.
Energy and car?
What was car and human means?
No, nothing.
Wizard in car.
Car and sex.
I don't think that's gonna work.
Clown and car.
Where's a clown?
Yeah, air and car might make an airplane.
There it is.
Nice.
Alright, cool.
Airplane.
Toy and boat.
Toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, fuck.
Toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat.
I had it.
I tried.
I almost had it.
Wheel and air, maybe.
Wait, air and bricks.
Fabric and air?
I don't know.
Tools and air.
A weapon and air.
You know, just swinging your sword in the air.
I'm not gonna do anything.
Wheel and air.
You gonna play Fancy Pants Adventures?
Make a house, please.
I'm gonna do it.
Okay, a house would be what?
Wood and stone?
Or like tools and wood?
Tools and...
What would it be?
Airplane and weapon.
Oh, shit.
That's right.
Oh, take the hint.
Oh, I was already on it.
Okay, tools and wheel.
Tools and cart.
Tools and boat.
Let's go through the whole thing.
Weapon and boat.
Weapon and car?
Steam engine and wheel?
Steam engine and plane.
What?
Locomotive.
Oh, okay.
Okay, so locomotive and art?
To make a weed and stone?
Ooh, flour.
Okay, flour and eggs.
Flour and eggs is gonna make bread or something, right?
Flour and eggs.
What?
I can't make like a cake?
And seeds.
Two eggs and some butter.
Police electric corpse.
I'm dying over here.
All right, let's do it.
Hold on, man.
It didn't do anything.
Flour and water.
Yep, that's a good one.
Dough.
All right.
Dough and eggs.
Dough and life.
Dough and energy.
Tools and dough.
Fire and dough.
Blood and dough.
I wouldn't eat at that restaurant anymore.
Fire and dough.
Bread.
Okay, bread and human.
It should make...
It should definitely be happiness.
Human and bread.
Just happy.
Hunter and bread.
Well, you don't hunt bread.
You just make it.
Bread and meat.
That's not a bad idea.
Flour and bread.
Meat and bread.
Does it make like a sandwich?
Come on.
Why should...
That should make like a hamburger.
Hunter x Hunter German.
I know, you made that joke already.
Fire and meat.
Yeah, I tried that.
It didn't do anything.
That's weird.
Bread and tools.
Let's try it.
Bread and weapon.
Flour and weapon.
Feather of tools.
Feather weapon.
Feather boiler.
Feather engine.
Bread and alcohol.
Oh, that would be beer, right?
Yeah.
If there's anything else.
Okay, there's beer.
Fire and brick.
Human and stone.
A hut?
Wait.
Hut and tools should make...
Hut and tools.
Where'd it go?
Where is it?
Where's the hut?
Where the hell did it go?
Am I stupid?
What is it?
Where did it go?
Pizza and hut.
Oh my god.
I was looking under...
I was...
I have to...
Sorry.
Tools was already over there.
I'm sorry.
Tools, pizza, hut.
Pizza and hut.
Yeah, that would be so funny
if they did like a dumb branded version.
I know it would be stupid,
but if you could eventually make like a king
and you had like a burger
and you could make Burger King or something.
Nobody would think that was cool,
but like three of us here.
Okay, some of these can interact.
Metal and weeds.
Let me try it.
Earth weeds.
Mushrooms.
Plankton and stone.
Okay, shell.
Mushroom and tools.
Make poison.
Poison and human is death.
Wizard and mushroom.
Okay, wizard and mushroom.
Mushroom and human.
Mushroom and hunter.
Hunter and weapon.
That's not a bad idea.
That's a good one.
Yeah.
Oh, warrior.
Human and field.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Look at this.
This is like we have like a little game night
tonight together.
You know what I mean?
This is like a little game night.
What about tools and field?
This is the streamer and chat bonding experience.
Warrior has to combine with something.
Warrior and boat.
I don't know.
Warrior and dragon.
Ooh, a superhero.
Superhero and water.
Alcoholic superhero.
Human superhero.
Hunter hero.
Corpse hero.
Warrior hero.
Wizard hero.
Demigod hero.
No.
All right, let's make a house.
Hut and brick, somebody said.
Wood and hut.
How do I make that a house?
Train and metal?
Hold on.
Oh, right.
All right, train and metal.
Metal and wheel.
No, none of these really do anything.
Do poison and weapon.
Nice.
Poisoned weapon.
We're almost at the end.
We almost have everything.
Holy shit.
I didn't think we were going to win.
Let's beat this game.
Let's go game night, guys.
Come on.
Hey, wango bangy.
Thanks for the five community subs.
Appreciate it.
Thank you, wango.
We only got like 20 more.
Poison weapon human.
Assassin.
Assassin human.
Is a live assassin and a dead human.
OK.
Assassin and brick.
Do poison sex.
Sorry.
OK, let's do poison and sex.
Fine.
Where is poison?
Didn't do anything.
Ceramics.
Human and clay.
Good one.
Shell and stone.
Yeah, let's do that one.
Limestone.
Ooh, nice.
OK, we got a lot of comp.
Swamp and worm.
Snake.
All right, go back to that.
That was wrong.
A swamp vodka and worm.
Tequila or something.
I know it's not tequila, but you know, I don't know.
I'm stupid.
Never mind.
Swamp and shell.
Ooh, sulfur.
Sulfur.
What could I do with sulfur?
Sulfur in like coal?
No, sulfur in fire.
Sulfur in oil.
Sulfur in coal.
Really?
You can't do sulfur in coal?
One too many eyes.
Say one too many eyes.
Thanks for the five community subs.
Appreciate it.
One too many eyes.
Beer and weapon.
That worked.
Need weapon.
Weapon and...
Well, what did you want me to do?
Weapon and what?
A tree and life.
Swamp and grass.
Do weapon and sulfur.
Where's sulfur?
Oh, where's sulfur?
Damn it, no.
No weapon and oil.
No weapon and coal.
Do wizard and stone.
Assassin and stone.
Metal assassin.
Limestone and wizard.
Oil and boat.
Should I do oil and boat or...
Wait, should I do...
What about a hut?
No.
Sand and boat.
More community subs.
Holy shit.
Seabone.
Thanks for the five subs.
Thank you, Seabone.
Oil and boat doesn't work.
Coal and boat.
Fire and boat.
Sulfur and boat.
Nope.
Do limestone and clay.
Okay.
Limestone and clay.
Oh shit.
Cement.
Finally.
Holy shit.
Give that person a...
Give that person a thumbs up.
Now we can do cement and hut.
Or cement and brick.
Or cement and bricks.
Really?
Cement and wood.
Cement and ceramics.
Cement and metal.
Cement and stone.
Cement and sand.
Cement and glass.
Cement and clay.
What?
Cement and tools?
Boiler.
Engine.
Hut.
Human.
And cement.
What?
Cement and water.
Concrete.
Alright.
Concrete and human.
Concrete and tools.
No.
Concrete and hut.
Concrete and...
What?
Finally.
A house.
Okay.
House and human is like family or something, right?
House and hunter.
House and hero.
House and wizard.
House and house.
Like a city?
House and fire.
House and oil.
House and sulfur.
Help me out here.
Here we go.
Okay.
Tobacco and snake.
Bird tree.
Tobacco.
Grass.
Tree.
Snake.
Tobacco.
Tree.
What the hell is this?
I feel like I did all these combinations.
Beast grass?
Beast tobacco?
Tobacco animal?
Tobacco gro-
Oh, shit.
Milk and fertilizer.
Okay.
Hold on.
Milk and eggs, alright?
Milk and meat or...
Milk and flour.
Milk and beer.
Milk and meat.
Dough and milk.
Eggs and milk.
Milk and eggs.
Poison and the milk.
Life and milk.
Energy milk.
Muscle milk.
Blood milk.
Milk and bread.
Milk and sex.
That's not gonna do anything.
Uh...
House and milk.
Fertilizer and limestone.
I keep forgetting to do that and I'm sorry.
You keep saying that.
I keep forgetting it.
Okay.
Fertilizer and limestone.
Let's do it.
Saltpeter.
Okay, we got saltpeter.
I don't know if that does.
Not that much more.
It's got human and sky.
Right, that?
Human and...
There's no sky.
Human and air.
Peter and sulfur?
Okay.
Okay, saltpeter and sulfur.
It's gunpowder.
Gunpowder and tools makes gun.
Gunpowder and tools.
Oh, gunpowder and weapon.
There's your firearm.
Okay.
Firearm and...
Car?
Like we need to make like a tank or something?
Firearm and human.
No.
Hunter and firearm.
Assassin firearm.
Hero firearm.
Warrior firearm.
No.
Uh, what about gunpowder?
Yeah, that's not...
Wait.
I haven't done anything with fabric.
Fabric and sand?
That says make clothes?
Fabric and fabric?
Fabric and tools.
No.
Fabric and hut.
I'm trying to make like clothing.
Fabric and fire?
Fabric and human.
There it is.
Clothes.
What about clothes and...
Clothes and domesticated animal.
It's like fucking Bugs Bunny.
Bugs Bunny didn't wear clothes.
Uh, this is Daffy Duck.
Donald Duck wore a t-shirt and no pants and shit.
Um, Mickey Mouse didn't have clothes on.
No, Mickey Mouse had pants on.
Yeah, Mickey Mouse, whatever.
I feel like I have not used electricity for anything.
Electricity in house?
No, I have not used electricity one time.
So it has to be used for something.
Whatever, let's find...
Okay, again?
What the hell is this?
Water and tobacco?
Water and tree?
Alcohol tree?
Alcohol, grass, vodka tree?
Swamp grass?
Makes a reed.
Okay.
Tobacco and human?
Electricity and energy.
No.
Electricity and life.
Tools and reeds.
It's paper.
Paper and tools or paper and pencil?
Human and electricity and paper.
Human and paper.
Fire and paper.
Hmm, what about fire and paper?
No.
Hunter and paper.
Tobacco and paper!
Here it is!
Perfect!
Yes, that's a great idea.
Tobacco and paper.
Good, good, good, good, good.
Paper and gunpowder?
Is that doing anything?
Let's get tobacco.
Cigarette.
There it is.
Paper and feather.
What would that do?
What the hell is paper?
It's paper.
How did I miss it already?
What category is paper?
Oh, okay, right, right, right.
Okay, paper and feather.
It's a book!
Paper and weeds?
I'm sure.
Paper and grass.
Paper and reeds.
Paper and...
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Look, we're down to the final...
Almost the final...
Ten.
Storm and bird.
Let's try it.
Thunderbird.
They actually have...
Do a book and worm?
Yeah, that would work.
That definitely would work.
A book and worm.
Oh, that's too bad.
What about sand and book?
Metal book.
What about a wood book?
Hold on.
Weed and swamp.
Oh, that's a no-brainer.
Oh, it didn't work.
Book and house.
Okay, book and house.
What about book and human?
Like scholar or something?
No.
Book and...
I don't know.
Book and house?
No.
Book and hut.
Cement and house.
Brick and steam engine.
Wait, give it to me.
All right, let's go.
Ash and...
I'm gonna do ash.
No.
Storm worm.
Storm shell.
Storm shroom.
Steamweed.
Steam beetle.
Dust?
Weed?
Dust beetle?
Steamed weeds.
That's gotta be air then.
Whatever.
Air and weeds.
Air beetle.
Air scorpion.
Air plankton.
Air shell.
Air worm?
Oh.
Last one I possibly could have done.
Okay, butterfly.
Ten more.
What about lizard shell?
I'll try it.
Snake shell.
Bird shell.
Lizard.
Scorpion.
Butterfly lizard.
Clay and gum powder.
Let's try clay and gum powder.
Do snake and oil.
Okay, I have not used wheat.
I've used wheat like once.
Feather once.
Wool like once.
Worm and shell.
I guess I could try it.
Yeah, let me try these.
Do glass with glass and house.
Try it.
Okay, glass with glass.
Glass and house.
Oh, shit.
Skyscraper.
Perfect.
Alright, skyscraper and human is like office worker,
businessman or something, right?
Oh.
Skyscraper and house?
Do fertilizer in the field.
Oh, shit.
Okay, yeah.
What category is that in?
I don't fucking remember.
Fertilizer and field.
Fertilizer is...
I don't remember.
There's so many categories.
There's so many things.
Fertilizer and...
Where's the fertilizer?
Okay, fertilizer field.
No, shit.
Skyscraper and hut.
Field and house.
Concrete house.
Human and clothes.
Shit.
Fabric and boat.
Okay, fabric and boat.
Try this one.
What would fabric and boat do?
No.
Fabric and feather.
Okay.
Where the hell is the feather?
How many things?
Fucking hundred goddamn elements.
I just keep forgetting where everything is.
My brain is fucking fried.
Feather is...
Yeah, I don't know.
This one?
There it is.
Oh, it's in food.
Why is it in food?
Alright, bird house.
Shit, there's less than 10.
Bird house.
Shit.
Sand and egg.
Egg.
Oh, no.
Sand and egg.
Okay.
Turtle!
Yes, okay.
Turtle in water.
Turtle in swamp.
There's one more animal that is not here.
Cat and beast?
Do water and sand.
I feel like I did water and sand a while ago.
Didn't I?
No.
Oh, this is interesting.
How about ghost and bird?
Ghost, whale, ghost, dinosaur, ghost, beast.
Ghost, snake, ghost, animal, lizard, ghost, turtle, ghost, fish, ghost, zombie, bird,
beast, golem, zombie, bird, zombie, whale, zombie, animal, lizard, zombie, turtle, zombie, fish,
dragon, turtle, dragon, beast, thunderbird, turtle, thunderbird, beast,
freent, whale, vampire, beast.
Oh, Jesus.
Okay, there it is.
Werewolf.
Nice.
Sand and tree.
No.
Fertilizer and tree.
Boat and wood.
Wouldn't the boat made out of wood?
I feel like the boat is already made out of wood.
Ship.
All right.
Down to the final six.
Only a few more.
Yeah, I figured boat and oil would.
Ship and oil?
No.
Coal and ship.
Fire and ship.
Coal and locomotive?
No, really.
Ship and steam engine.
Try that.
And there's the steam ship.
Perfect.
Five more.
Now I'll do ship and boiler.
Human and ship.
We'll try human and steam ship.
Human and airplane.
What about beast and fish?
Cool.
I'll try it.
Dolphin.
There's only four more.
This is almost done.
Metal and energy.
That's a good try.
Let's see.
Oh, oh, it's electricity.
I'll do ship and fabric.
Okay.
Ship and fabric.
Is this a sailboat?
What are the last three?
We got all the animals.
All the gooey things.
We're missing some of the life things.
I feel like a little bit of fire.
House and domestic animal.
And then they wrote four.
Fuck's sake.
All right.
I hope you're right.
If you're not right, you're getting fucking timed up for 10 minutes.
You're getting timed up for 10 minutes if this is incorrect.
Okay, let's find a house.
Ready?
House and domesticated animal.
Oh, get him.
Right now he's like, no, no, you'll never take me alive.
Or what if he just hit the X?
Otto, what is it?
Oh shit, I'm out of here.
Whale and human.
Oh, hi, Otto.
Whale and human?
Okay.
Otto plus energy.
Fire arm and vodka.
Oh, we got a hidden coming up here.
Hold on.
And okay.
A blast thing of transportation.
Fish and boat.
Fish and ship.
Fish and steamship.
No.
Bird and plane.
Beast and cart.
There it is.
Nice.
This is done.
What's left?
There's only a few things left.
Two things left.
Okay, Otto, I'll take your side.
Otto?
Let me just take him off real quick.
I'll be right back.
You want to go over this way?
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Very cool.
Very, very cool.
Chunky fireman in real life.
I'll hit.
Very cool.
There was a hundred gifted subs.
Wait, what?
Hold on.
Let me see.
What are you talking about?
Oh my god.
There was a hundred subs.
What the fuck?
That's too many.
That's from ZapX.
There's a hundred community subs.
I thought you guys were debating for a second.
I was like, oh my god.
I feel like you've done this before.
That's too many.
I really appreciate it though.
Thank you.
That's a monster amount of money.
Way more.
It's way more than I deserve.
So what is that?
Oh, bust of an E-clown.
Okay.
Let's stop there.
Let's head back over here.
We have only two more elements and I have a hint.
Water scorpion?
Water moss?
Water bacteria?
No.
What's the last one?
Water mushroom?
Water shell?
Butterfly water?
Swamp butterfly?
Water beetle?
No.
Water swamp?
Beetle swamp?
Alcohol and worm?
Yeah, I tried that one already.
Weed swamp?
No, I did that already.
I don't know.
What is it?
Mushroom and vodka?
Water and...
Is it alcohol?
Has to be something weird.
Vodka and beetle?
Moss and swamp.
Urn.
There's only one more.
What's the last one?
Urn and something?
Fabric and ship.
Yeah, I did...
Yeah, I got the sailboat.
Is it water and metal?
That can't be the last one that I didn't do.
No way.
Okay.
Do zombie and wizard.
Vampire wizard?
Ghost wizard?
Zombie...
I don't know.
Vodka plus firearm.
Oh, okay.
Zombie and corpse.
Is it?
Oh, there it is!
That's the end of the game.
Ghoul.
Congratulations.
In the next episodes,
which path will the development of the world creation take?
What other fantastic adventures will Doodle God make?
Maybe technological disaster will throw the world into stone age.
What creatures will inhabit the planet?
Or maybe world will take the path of magic.
Perhaps the Doodle God himself will descend from heavens
and take on adventures personally.
You can now play it on your iPhone, by the way.
There are like five of these.
Yeah, there's like Doodle Devil,
this is Doodle Medieval, Doodle Doodle Magic or something, right?
That was fun.
That was very chill and just...
That was really fun just to hang out.
Okay, I promise everybody that I will play Nitrome this week, okay?
We'll go back to it.
But I am going to call it here.
It's been five and a half hours.
It hasn't really felt that long.
I'll see you guys tomorrow for the game awards.
Stream will be starting somewhere around like 3 15.
We'll hang out for like 15 minutes before it starts.
We'll do that.
And then we'll see what's going on on Friday.
But I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Yeah, game awards are tomorrow.
I'm only watching the game awards for Elden Ring.
I don't care about anything else.
I'm just going to sleep through it until...
I have like an alert on my phone when the announcement is coming.
There's probably some other cool reveals too.
There might be.
We'll see.
That's going to conclude tonight's stream.
Thanks for watching, guys.
Sorry I was gone for so long.
I just wasn't able to talk.
It really took until about this morning
before I felt comfortable speaking for more than like an hour straight.
So we unban that guy?
That guy should be unbanned by now, right?
Send him a DM like and just say, hey, you got noticed.
No, he's still banned.
He's still banned.
Well, okay.
Maybe he'll be unbanned tomorrow.
All right.
So raid, raid.
Okay.
Raid.
You want...
Is Dunkey...
Dunkey is streaming now, right?
But I'm such like a fan.
Like if I stream...
If I raid Dunkey...
I could be like, oh, it's Dunkey.
I'm such a big fan.
And here's like a bunch of people.
Yeah, Dunkey's really funny.
He's been around for a long time.
If you don't know who he is, he's very, very funny.
He's got some of the funniest YouTube videos I've ever watched.
One of my favorites is the capture video.
If you haven't seen it, please give yourself a treat
and go watch it right now before you, you know, watch the stream.
We're going to raid Dunkey.
Look, I'm just a fan.
Whatever.
He's cool.
What is this?
I got to follow him on Twitch.
What is his Twitch name?
I got to follow him right now.
Dunkstream.
Oh, yeah.
He's had this account for a long time, hasn't he?
All right.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Have a good one.
Take care.
Good night.
Goodbye.
See you tomorrow for the game awards.
Get that raid going.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I'm looking forward to the game awards.
I think it's going to be some cool stuff there.
I don't know.
We'll see.
Good night, guys.
Thanks for watching, as always.
See you soon.