I'm actually seeing a few people do say Kurt Russell. Fortunately Kurt Russell is not in
this game, but hello. This is a sequel to The Thing. And wait, I didn't even tell you what
we're doing. I didn't even make a tweet. I'm not supposed to be here. I'm not supposed to be here.
But let the intro play for like 30 seconds. Okay. Hi everybody. Today we're going to play The Thing.
In quotes, The Thing, the actual game, The Thing. This is a sequel to the movie. If you've ever
seen the movie, it's a good one. It's a movie about deceit, movie about who is it, who did it.
Without spoilers for a movie in the 80s. Oh right, they've remade this game, this movie.
I forgot about that. They did do a full remake of The Thing a few years ago, didn't they?
It was a prequel, unfortunately. Really? Was it not good? What does it have on Rotten Tomatoes?
Thing? What? 2016? What? 2009? 2011? Oh, not very good at all. This is 35% on Rotten Tomatoes.
Six on IMDB and... so this is not that good. Okay. Well, whatever. Forget about this one.
If you get a six on IMDB, I don't know. Usually a seven to 7.5 is every movie.
If you're not every movie, then you know, it's horrible. IGN gave it a 10 out of 10. They did
not. What kind of boomer uses IMDB? I mean, it's just, it was listed on the... IMDB was listed there.
It had some scary scenes. But we're gonna play the game. Oh, okay. This is weird because... so
this game is the sequel to the movie. And I believe it is canon. This is a canon game.
So, right? That's not incorrect. This game's also trash. Well, that's for you to say and for me to
find out. Because what if I love this game? I might like it. I might really like this game.
It's a third person shooter, scary, fun game. But yeah, that's what we're doing today.
It's trash. It's a trash. You don't even know that. You didn't even know what the thing was
until we just talked about it for 10 minutes. You haven't even seen the movie. Raise your hand if
you've seen the movie. I bet you half if you haven't even seen it. Here it is. Are we gonna
get a recap? We might get a recap, so this would be good. You guys ready? I am. Quiet during the
cutscene. Oh, okay. Normal, auto-aiming, hard, normal, or easy? No, this is a game from like
1998. I'm not doing hard. I'm doing normal. Always normal. Always normal.
Jeremy, the game is insanely hard. Okay, then I'm doing normal. No, I wanna be...
It's not the same. It's not what you guys think. This isn't like it is now, where there's like six
difficulties and the first four of them are easy. No, this is back in the day when hard meant
actually hard. You motherfuckers. Are these subtitles? Was this subtitles? Could I put subtitles on?
What is going on? That's not me laughing. I know it sounds like it, but it's not.
I gotta turn subtitles on and the game's on fucking hard. What the hell? This is not gonna be fun.
What do you see? David Hayter?
Have you found it? Your transmitter's down and everything else is foobar.
What do you mean? The base is gone, Colonel. It looks like massive explosives damage.
Any clues here are gonna be like finding a needle in a haystack. Are we sure?
Understood. Do a recon, see if you can find anything that'll give us an idea what happened.
I could try to get the chopper back to you within an hour, but visibility's not very good.
Okay, we'll make a sweep and report back. Roger. Check it out. Check up on Alpha Team or Blake.
Are we jumping out of the helicopter in the air? Okay, no. I was like we don't-
Keep your team together and get them to shelter as quickly as you can.
Roger that. Blake out. Okay. The snow is pretty-
All right, as you play through the first four levels, text pop-ups like this one will come
on screen from time to time to explain different parts of the game to you you can skip them by
pressing the escape button or turn them off entirely by pressing the escape button to bring
up the pause menu okay so i don't want to skip it and then selecting options you can then switch
the tutorials off by entering the game settings menu however they will teach you how to play the
game so it's suggested that you read each tutorial at least once more help and advice can be found in
the field manual you can find the field manual in the pause menu by pressing the escape button
something to note about this game that you guys need to know you can soft lock yourself in this
game you there are people that if you kill them you could ruin the whole game so i've been told
to pay attention because you're gonna fuck up the whole game is what i've been told good all right
cold exposure it's 40 degrees below zero in the anarktic and so whenever you're outside you'll
suffer from the cold an exposure meter it's a blue meter at the bottom of the screen will show
you how much time you have until temperatures begin to actually harm you and take away from
your health so i have a meter at the bottom that when the meter is depleted that's when i take like
dock damage okay as you play the game you will be given objectives these appear in the top left
hand corner of the screen and are color coded green text shows that an objective is still active
an orange text means an objective has been completed you can check the status of all of
your objectives by pressing the f button to enter the keys documents and objectives menu
once in this screen move the mouse up to highlight the document icon and then press the enter button
to view your objectives so f all right so green means it's what you're currently on orange is
completed retrieve evidence and rescue any survivors keep the team alive so this is my
team all right hold on we're that's cold let me i gotta turn on game settings tutorials on auto
aiming hard i'm so glad i can change that okay is there a audio video no advanced controls
there are no subtitles you guys are gonna have to pay attention no there are no subtitles in
this whole game good luck here we go okay retrieve what was it so we have to explode
we're gonna get it's cold right now we're gonna get out of here okay i just right i hit the right
click button and all of a sudden i am holding a flare in my hands i don't know what the controls
are i don't want to soft lock myself somebody take this okay how do i open doors blake you need
anything repaired or even a simple bypass and i'm your man i need subtitles any damage give back to
me asap and i'll help you out i'm not carrying any dead bodies back it's leonardo from the niche
turtles i'm locked loaded and ready to make shit dig squad member communication your squad is made
up of three different character classes that you can tell apart by their headgear soldiers always
have a tough camouflage helmet on engineers don't go anywhere without their trusty cap
camouflage is soldier engineer trusty cap and medics like to keep a warm keep warm in a beanie
with a red cross on the front why couldn't they just i can just remember that i know i just i'll
start to build a relationship with these people i'm i'm wait actually this is good for me because
i'll just be like oh red cross hat all right that's good the members of your squad are very much
alive they blink they fidget when they are bored and they think for themselves be careful how
you treat them as they are all trained veterans even if they are unarmed they won't hesitate to
take you down if they decide you are acting suspiciously they will also communicate with
you both verbally and with the use of icons that appear over their heads for an explanation of the
overhead icons refer to your field manual okay you guys didn't think that this was going to be a
fucked up game well let's wrap in as has already been explained your squad mates are intelligent
people and they will react to your actions based on how much they trust you when you enter the
squad menu you will see a bar above the names of each squad member that shows their current level
of trust for any squad member if his level of trust is in the green section it means he trusts
you and will take orders and help you throughout your mission if his level of trust is in the
orange section it means he doesn't trust you and he won't help you but he isn't yet convinced
you're an enemy so he won't attack you either if his level of trust is in the red section it
means he doesn't trust you at all and sees you as an enemy okay so green is good yellow is
cautious and red is i'm going to kill you where's the field manual oh yeah commanding your squad
you're in for a long one giving weapons you can give items to your squad by accessing the squad
menu selecting the squad member you want to interact with and then selecting the give
weapon option your weapon inventory screen will then come up and you can hand you can give weapons
to take techie taking you can do the same thing squad menu it's everything's in the squad menu
orders squad menu school you can issue various orders use squad members squad menu from the
squad menu you can issue a group command to all your squad members telling them to either stay
guard or follow you you can do an individual squad member menu you can issue an individual
command to stay guard or follow you as well send squad member to a location you've identified to
tell your group for an individual squad member to stay or guard or follow you access the squad menu
all right it's all in the squad menu follow stay yeah overhead okay here we go overhead icons are
one way in which your squad members communicate with you here are all of them different icons and
what they mean i this is important this is important this is important this is important
i'm going to read this because i need to know so this is the trust and fear icons my trust has
gone from high to low my trust has gone from low to zero my trust has gone from low to enemy level
one my trust has gone from low to enemy level two my trust has gone from low to enemy level three
what does that does that mean like i'm going to throw a grenade in the room what's the different
enemy levels so at enemy level three i now see the player as an enemy and then going the other way
too so we have to build trust with everybody here so my trust has gone from high to buddy
my trust has gone from buddy to high all right so this we this is what we're looking for trust
my fear has gone from danger to crack up level two my fear has gone from danger to crack up level
three all right i think i'm starting to understand i'm talking enemy spotted i'm losing health
i am in i am i am in man down trust synopsis if your squad members don't trust you they won't do
anything for you got it all right how do we how do you save the game oh shit this is an old game
junction boxes whenever you see the hand icon it means that you can do something by pressing the
e button yeah okay right the junction boxes in front of you is a basic one when you walk up to
it yeah i know you press e to open stuff okay when you walk right up to it a message will be
in the center of the screen to tell you the name of the junction box you will also see a picture
of a hand and a yellow bar at the bottom of the screen this tells you that you can fix this
junction box yourself okay to fix it press and hold e you'll see the yellow bar start to fill up
when it is full the repair is complete you can release the interact button at any time
to stop fixing the junction box if you then return to it and hold the e button
the repair will continue from where you left off good i mean you can't what i'm doing it
i would scream at you right now but i need you to trust me okay what why did this room explode
whenever you've got low enough health or any of your squad members are hurt bad enough that
they go into the man down state so when you're kneeling on the floor be careful when a member
of your squad is in this state it's only a matter of time until they die unless they're healed
bring your medic within close proximity to the injured person and he will automatically heal
them the medics you meet throughout the game can heal any member of your squad with the exception
of themselves so you will need to keep an eye on your medic's health and heal him yourself
when he is injured so heal me how many of those do you have all right what is this gun
gun clips oh ammo too that's all i can take area secure what about this thing turn it on
did i just lock myself in like a freezer what no all right so how do i well what's a squad menu
where's where's these guys q is squad menu okay all right so this is welden burrows north
does well then have a gun you do now why is it of zero oh yeah here you go all right you got a
gun now you now you can you can defend yourself okay look plus we're buddies now we're now friends
nice all right that's how it works can you give like food and stuff and like all right hold on
is there a flashlight no that's if okay now what do we do do i have a map can we move this out of
the way is there a crouch can somebody get in there no why am i walking oh what the fuck is
going on is there a flashlight in this game how do i turn on the flashlight there is no flashlight
oh god damn it all right explore over here where's my squad oh my would that have killed me
maybe i don't know all right one of these guys is gonna get hit in the head one of these and
it's gonna be all my fault this way in here of course not all doors will require you to fix a
junction box some of them are just plain locked the door in front of you is locked and you need
to find the key in order to open it the key could be nearby or far away or on a table or in the hand
of a corpse whenever you find the key for a locked door simply return to it and it will open
automatically is a hint the key to this door is hidden underground now that's wonderful
underground i don't have a map do i hey what are you guys doing face cam face cam face cam
or enemy level three what all right all right all right you guys are gonna crash my game
hold on a second can i even hold on i'm not even sure can i even do this i don't think my webcam is
even plugged in face cam or enemy level three give me a break what's even plugged in here
oh get this out of here all right all right i'm about to i'll do it fine
i'm doing it i'm doing i'm putting the face cam on faster what you do it's
what what what happened to you guys why is it why is everybody like fucking drinking the stuff
under the sink again all right that should work did it work why can i get it through here that's
pretty nice uh background i think that's that all right here you go here's your goddamn webcam
i don't even know where to put this webcams it's a boomer wallpaper no it's called the i don't care
wallpaper because wallpapers get in my way and when i have something i mean for a while it was
pac-man and then it turned into carnage and then it turned into the stereo and uh it just
gets too much back there i need like just a just a default background where my icons can go
because it hurts your eyes if you see some of these images are so fucked up looking all right
let's go all right i don't remember what the fuck i was even doing but let's go just put a just put
a black canvas i could do that but that's boring all right so uh underground remember see anything
underground this is i mean we're safe i wish i had a flashlight i'm gonna turn the brightness
get mad at me there is no brightness turn off face cam no no it's it's staying on for good
all right i need to find underground tunnel or something underground i've ruined it turn it off
it's deep underground you guys are fucked you know when the chapstick comes out the shit's
getting real on the stream you know that right all right it's gonna it's definitely gonna be down
right over by the why would it tell me to go look over here he's insulting us well you guys are
acting like fucking goddamn werewolves it's definitely it has to be over here no it's not
maybe it's all the way down i can't can i sneak in here all right do we have enough uh human
battery power to go this way well where the fuck do i go we're all gonna die underground
well i gotta get inside first before i run around a circle we're not gonna die right now right just
get in here oops i just i wish i could see better all right we good we're like we're dying now
i have to like actually go into this building what all right get in here come on get over here yes
it does all right let's try this again no not this way follow the blue lights yeah that's what i was
doing but i i was dying i was my cold meter was going down you'll be all right all right
what's over here any items supply what is with this camera sorry don't shoot me
the medics are like what the fuck was that buddy weapons go take that how do i say take that
wait where's our uh you stay go to take weapons and you go to empty slot go to the save slot
take weapons and ammo no you're i think no you got whatever just get in here oh fire
extinguisher who's gonna be the fire extinguisher guy it's probably gonna be you it has to be you
come here all right so we're gonna give give to squad member i can't give that to you okay
so how the fuck do i use that is that just a usable item monster trucks underground
can i go in here so it's a flying saucer cutscene what the hell it's an alien
what do you think it is captain i don't know and i don't care looks like a goddamn ufo to me what
a great leader this shit gives me the creeps yeah yeah we're not lovers and all that crap check it
out and move on this is key there's the key why is it so quiet i don't like how quiet it is
where's our other guy where's our other guy where's the other guy uh the other guy's the thing
i knew i should have shot that guy in the beginning what are you doing out here why
didn't you come in with us huh okay keep your eye on the medic supplies over here i'm gonna hide
this tape when i'm finished is that kurt russell for you think it rips through your clothes when
it takes you over windows found some shredded long johns but the name tag was missing they could be
anybody else i can do just wait rj mccready helicopter pilot u.s outpost north 31 movie
yeah remember when everyone lied about seeing the original movie i know you did now that's
offensive to me i love the thing i'm glad you did it's a great movie remember when no one knows
what a cassette tape is all right gain access to the infirmary completed uh what is that uh-oh
here take some bullets maybe that'll make you like me again the virus has the ability to replicate
the original biological entity including the clothing could be anybody it's so dark in here
do i don't have any light please don't tell me that i'm a fucking idiot and i'm gonna play
this whole game without a flashlight and it's like t power supply advanced junction boxes
in front of you is an advanced junction box and can only be fixed by your engineer
i've paraphrased to get your engineer to fix an advanced junction box you need to first identify
the junction box by walking up to it until its name appears as you would for a basic junction box
there are two ways that you can ask your engineer to fix it first if your engineer is close enough
to the junction box the i can fix it icon will appear automatically over his head this allows
you to walk right up to him and then press e which tells him to fix the junction box the second way
to have your engineer fix the junction box is to bring up the squad menu by pressing q select your
engineer then select the go-to option and lastly select the junction box you want him to fix he
will then go fix it can you fix this go fix it medic with the gun just looks like he's never
held one before it's freaking me out but you're holding that like a golden eye npc and that's not
how it works okay so we're going to go through here access codes the door in front of you is
the access code door and you'll need an access code for it to open access codes can be found
written down and as part of a computer terminal message or you'll find it somehow you do not have
to make a note of these codes as blake can remember them why can't i remember them why is it my trouble
with that what why do one of my squad members have to do this when you found the access code
for a door go up to the access panel next to the door and press e look for the access code to this
door and return when you found it hint access codes are usually just a series of numbers and
may not be obviously labeled an infected entity has the ability to fragment and survive every part
of it as a whole why the oh the lights just turned back on right all right
oh christ what is that you didn't see that i we chill out everybody keep tight till we figure out
what's going on that is a late reaction uh-oh your squad members are always conscious of their
circumstances and the environment around them and when they've seen too much they will begin to lose
it to see how a squad member is handling his situation activate the squad venue if press the
q button and pay attention to his picture if he's doing okay he'll casually be looking from left to
right if he's noticeably frightened he'll be looking all around at a panicked speed if he's
close to outright losing it and cracking up he'll be shaking uncontrollably to reduce your squad
members fear try giving him a weapon or get him to follow you out of the area refer to your field
manual to find out about different things you can do to calm your squad members when fear gets them
why would i give him a weapon are you good i mean i gave you a weapon but you're not doing
all right you follow me come here follow me go to how do i say follow me just come over here
follow me over here you come over here and just stay over here okay stay don't move there we go
see i did just fine i've compiled a five page report from the autopsy performed on the
anomalous corpse that was discovered at the norwegian outpost it appears that what we are
dealing with is some kind of self-repairing entity that has the ability to morph itself
into different biological forms access to medical supplies is limited to myself and garry code one
one three eight that's the kind of information willy was talking about i gotta find that report
okay one one three eight junction box i can do this actually you know what yeah you do it
we're friends okay saving the game oh oh it's only in specific save points oh that sucks it's like
resident evil thankfully i can do it as many times as i want oh medical bags where's the medic
wait a minute he's been fucking acting really weird see let's go you told him to do that
yeah but still all right come over here medic go over here and open up the medic slot go to
do you need these i guess you don't wouldn't you just go get them automatically all right
anything else over here they need to look at no game is safe let's go what's this oh that's
oh shit what is this i don't know what that was all right nothing else on here
we're gonna have for 15 seconds you're gonna be fine what's in the corner whitley this is blake
what have you got one body identification says childs no survivors and what appears to be
one body and and and and what and and and oh what'd you say son i didn't pick that up it looks
a ufo i like just accidentally called my grandfather i want you to rig all
remaining buildings and i'll remote affirmative i'll contact you when we're finished wait what
did you say jeremy you said there was a body what was the next part oh fuck that's grandpa
i'm gonna call my supervisor actually this time collect the c4 explosives plant c4 in the infirmary
plant c4 in the radio room okay so the radio room was back here the rate god damn it okay
anything else that i have here no the radio room was with the curt russell room right
and then the infirmary was with the guys lying down i can't get the whiskey it's not gettable
save it medic check no medics here okay i'm just trying to see if they do anything that's like
alien like so okay explode this room how do i blow that how do i do this this is the infirmary
right here right it has to be so how do i do that e plant c maybe over here oh right here
now how do i infirmary and then the radio room is back here right so how do i can i blow it up
shoot the c4 get out of the room i keep what it doesn't do anything no it's the game it's
not the game you think it is that's not how c4 works right all right then the uh what's down here
oh wait this is the is it fall damage now this is where i was before this is the
yes this shit wasn't the radio no i remember this i got stuck here and then where's the radio
i don't think it's down here this is where the uh ufo is was it over here yeah this is where the
uo i don't know well why would i not want to blow up the ufo it's back where i started yeah that's
right wait radio this is the radio room gotta be more specific i guess that's like kurt russell's
radio room engineer is missing no the engineer is not missing the engineer is here somewhere
although the engineer actually is missing right now you're right where is this person
me too but where's the engineer that's weird why are you not here it's probably stuck in a wall
somewhere yeah there he is well i don't know what you're doing here either but you're here
can i wrap around you can't climb over that are you serious he's infected he's not infected
why can i just walk around i have to go in and then around everybody just follow me and relax
you're gonna be fine i'm freezing not yet so this is here but no i have to go that way
wait what is this 50 and 70 chance of infection contact with an infected entity does not guarantee
infection what's this you just picked up an adrenaline hypo in situations where squad
members are suffering from extreme stress you can syringe them to calm them down go to your
inventory and then press enter on the icon in the center of the screen to take you to your items
with the mouse in the direction of the adrenaline syringe press enter when it's highlighted now
press the escape button to return to the game and approach the squad member and we used to
usually adrenaline on this is a whole that's a that's a fucking mouthful okay hold on a second
inventory adrenaline escape and then what was it right mouse button i don't i don't want to do it
okay that's how you put stuff here okay so i'm gonna put the uh let's keep that on
okay cool all right now how did i get i came in through here and then how did i get
i ran like all the way down here right i'm going the right way right there's like two different
buildings no it's follow the light that's no that's what i just did is it out but you can't go
anywhere from here oh here we go right right right yeah that's what i was trying to get in this
building this is the only one way i could get in all right i do too i can't wait till we don't have
to see it again all right so which is which is technically which what's the radio room right here
there it is return to the evac point where's the fucking evac point the place with all the flares
over here was it all the way all the way in the all the way at the beginning where i started that
was the evac point right okay dude the invention of like the fabled breadcrumb trail has ruined
all of us especially me you know i used to play games like this and i would have to know where i
was going and then all of a sudden fable 2 came along and added a gta gps system that was never
the same ever again is it guns on the ground what is all this holy shit why are there so many of
these on the ground i have five of them all right so where's the evac point then isn't this where we
landed come get us come get us i've got i'm ready to be picked up what this is the beginning this is
the very beginning the thing is in the chat right now probably but isn't this just not where i need
to be right now oh fuck everyone's gonna die all right i gotta get back inside where i got the c4
oh my god we're all dead hurry up and get the fuck in here wait past the infirmary
hold on a second i i didn't i thought everybody was saying i had to go back to the very beginning
where i got like where he started like here go back to the save point maybe it's where i found
the c4 i guess yeah i don't know the evac point everyone is wrong go through the infirmary
fucking god damn it we're all wrong go through the infirmary so here's the save point and now
is it what it's what i said in the very beginning isn't it it's the the flares on the ground this
has to be the evac point this is like look at this this is the evac point i knew it i knew it
standing by for evac anything from alpha team negative could be the storm must be god damn it
i've been getting partial transmissions for the last hour or so i'm going to assemble my team
we're good when the chopper arrives i'll have it drop me at alphas rendezvous wait this is not
my team i understand colonel but i don't have much choice pierce's team is in trouble besides
if there are any survivors i'm the only one on the team that speaks norwegian blake out
why would you do that blake do you read me why wouldn't you have like five people that
can speak norwegian nothing yet i just arrived the storm is worsening may take a while to find
anything looks like that i understand colonel i received a partial transmission from pierce
he's found something might be research affirmative did he say if there were any hostiles in the area
negative no hostiles okay i'm on it wake up this is like jack nicholson snake it's not the regular
snake okay light poles exist to guide people from one location to another when blizzards hamper
visibility use them to help you discover new areas but don't be afraid to explore beyond them
so just follow the blue brick road rescue alpha team i don't have any guns okay light bolt christ
that's got to be a few thousand volts i gotta find the power source what in the dryer vents
okay i don't i don't want to die power source is like over here
oh what's somebody just lit somebody just lit this am i reloaded is that not going to shock me
right power supply i can't do this though i'm not smart enough yes i am all right that wait
so i'm pretty messed up oh oh shit wait did somebody in here that i just get a bad ending
did i take too long identify yourself wait what captain is carter christ where's everybody
what happened here something i don't know what they had in soft luck but they attacked us
i thought they was part of the the wait a minute don't you come any closer the hell did you come
from anyways a chopper brought me in from the u.s research station what a lie out to here that's a
lie i'm hurt pretty bad don't move i'll see what i can do okay what happened why did i just get
like two different cutscenes if you were a squad member is injured and no medic is available you
do have the ability to heal him on your own using medical kits they'll indicate their need for help
by showing the i need health icon over their head when and when this is visible you can
automatically use a medical kit on the injured squad member by approaching him and pressing
alternatively if if you can equip a medic if you equip a medical kit you can heal an mpc by
approaching him yeah yeah yeah yeah just put it on your bar and mouse two cares i get it to see how
much health the squad member has at any time activate the squad menu at the bottom of this
particular panel is a red meter the fullness of it tells you how much health he has it's also
important to know that your squad members are in manned down state when they're down and bleeding
move quickly to heal them when they're in this condition or they'll eventually bleed to death
i don't do i have any health packs okay i do have a health pack let's do it i want to just
get this right since right mouse button carter isn't sure if he trusts you and he won't cooperate
with you until he does try giving him a weapon and some ammunition to gain his trust go to the
squad member menu by pressing q and highlight carter and press enter now highlight the command
give to squad member and move the okay give to sc i know you have now given carter a weapon look
at his trust meter to see if it is in the green if not let go of the mouse to what hold on i'm
just gonna i'm not gonna read this out loud like reading comprehension if you just get you know
there's a study that says if you read something out loud you're not comprehending it completely
have you heard that study it's real that's why when you go through around and you're in
your high school class and you all read six sentences of the fucking novel you're currently
on none of you understand what's going on what okay now it's uh it's jim it's jim's turn reads
fucking like a half a page all right now it's carol's turn none of you know what's going on
in the story you're anticipating being wanting to read and hoping that you like that the class
ends before they get to you i have i hated that more than anything what a fucking stall you talk
about stalling that's like the ultimate in stalling you know how long it takes for like
20 high school students to read three pages of a novel like fucking 40 minutes anyways all right
i'll be right back i don't have another weapon should give him i give the fire extinguisher
all right i'm sorry i was trying to give this to you i apparently i didn't comprehend it
okay give i don't have a weapon only have ammo i don't have a weapon how am i supposed am i
gonna give maybe you will get us out of this i don't want to give him all my ammo okay you got
enough okay he has all the ammo now now i want i need that back actually i hit enter and it gave
him everything uh can i have that back please i like empty the clip there you go that if that's
not trust i don't know what is all right please don't kill me how do i i was my ammo pistol ammo
i need that back all right take ammo with you he doesn't trust me anymore okay we're good
let's go can i did i heal him yeah he's all right all right let's move are you gonna follow me
okay let's go a flashlight thank god oh my god this game just became 5 000 times easier
i can actually see what the hell i'm doing torch oh thank god i'm so happy to have this right now
let's move all right turn the power on anything with the computers these don't run out of
batteries right junction box engineer go for it all right what's that beep closed circuit tvs
are useful in gathering tools you okay we're all going crazy this thing in the ice don't know who
is human and who isn't morale is low and i don't think our chances are good you know a face is
gonna pop up 46892 ice block code is that it and a guy in the corner with a key
all right i got the i got it let's go i didn't was that person here before that's not even a
jump scare i just activated the jump scare on myself i went in there fully ready okay here we
go uh-oh where are they are they in the ice room are they up here be be ready blake where'd
you come from what are you doing in here alien i received some partial transmission from piers
kill this guy like there was a problem shit you got that right we got ambushed by these things i
don't know where they came from man everybody lost it the squad split up have you talked to piers i
got part of a radio message from him he said he was at the north section of the base he was talking
some some medical mumbo shit he said he wanted to talk to the colonel the colonel hasn't contacted
you man i haven't heard shit from alien alien let me try my radio alien to colonel whitley do
you read blake to colonel whitley urgent alien i knew it all right let's head north and get piers
gain access to north section okay how's our trust doing don't make me regret this
wait no i don't have anything to give you i mean no okay uh there's a key on this guy
what is it for just a just a key just a key okay there's a junction box down here for power i think
power grid controls an engineer can you handle this please you got it go for it ah we go all
the way back let's get this over with i'm i know we're the aliens that were up top though
i can't open that door they were like half-life monsters in the rafters
can i open this with the key somebody shoot somebody good work why are they so little
shoot these things these things up but this is what okay this is what i would picture like if
an atst was a crab this is what they would look like with the shell off all right we're good
can we please go it's on hard mode i should have known seriously all right medical stuff
anybody need anything all right let me heal can i heal you guys what do you have for health
you could use a heal come here do you trust me hello was it you look we all haven't eaten
in like three days i know trust me i'm gonna try to find us some food for god's sakes
okay you need to be healed is he good yeah all right that's it's instant i'm not gonna
heal you i don't trust you yet i seriously don't all right now let's go back to the flashlight
do you want to do i don't have a weapon why do you not have a weapon no give me that back
you know what i'll just get it's gonna be pickman let's go sir open the door all right you open the
door go to door oh i knew it he's trying to get rid of me open it open it hard mode i don't even
need to fucking shoot a gun this is gonna be great all right with my flashlight i'll just aim the
flashlighted stuff all right fire extinguisher i have a couple of those that's not really how
this works but okay i'll take it all right let's go you guys are the only two weapons please
are you not coming because of this one fire right here you motherfuckers really you can't step
around this there there you go we can now go this way i'm looking for like a pistol all right new
area killing thing beasts as you have already experienced the very small thing beasts can
easily be dealt with using normal weaponry however any other form of the thing requires a two-stage
attack firstly you will need to use normal weapons to reduce its health the thing's health is shown
by the color of the auto aiming target with red representing the lowest level of health once the
thing beast is on minimal health move in with a flame thrower to finish it off only fire can
actually kill these thing beasts so make sure to look out for incendiary weapons and keep a good
stock on you at all times well all i have is a flashlight weapon case something there we go
help what are you doing all right i got a safe point what's what's what's my view you don't have
any ammo you need ammo here take some how much ammo do you have 134 to all right you guys have
run you guys are burning ammo what you guys are terrible at this game come on i gotta be a better
like esports coach using too much ammo fix this actually pretty good glancing over a chat i look
at chat like every 10 seconds i need an engineer yes sir it's their first time they usually play
console oh oh what's that incendiary i wish i could seriously just switch quickly instead of
having to go to the fucking menu to do this all right what is over here what are these these
grenades weapon case oh yeah i'll be the flamethrower guy i just figured it out i'm
flamethrower guy it's perfect so is that ammo for the flamethrower oh yeah absolutely you guys
attack and then when it gets to be the time where i can burn it i will burn it
all right let's go oh here they come get them i like being the overlord i don't have any more
ammo okay actually i do i'm the ammo box yes if you need ammo tell me i'm playing support
all right so this is here and then what about over here can i get in this building i don't
think so hold on get in here and recalibrate where's the save point no all right just
it's my bar that matters so do i go back here no all right and go this way i'm gonna save it again
we've got flamethrower bang left or i can go that way too let's go over here first
does it easy can i not turn that on can you fix this fuse thing what's this electricity
um did i burn the boxes how do we get over here what can i do like you go to boxes maybe i just
can't do anything i don't know or you can give me your gun for a second can you i can't tell you
to shoot that i have to shoot the boxes oh hold on no no no we gotta get um we're back to the
tent that's over here whatever this was i gotta get a gun come here okay get in here give me one
of your guns who likes me more you both like me a lot so that's fine uh you give me your gun
you'll get over it all right let's go that's all you need right go for it okay you can have this
back here there you go don't act like i never did anything for you this game is cool it is pretty
cool all right open it's right in front of you there's a door all right this is where we this
is where we actually figure out if we're capable of doing it like this save point right here no i
can't even touch it hold it pierce it's blake it's okay put your weapon down no way you're
infected just like well he just killed all of us i'm not your word ain't shit captain i found a
report that says the only way to prove you're not one of those things is through a blood test
now there's a medical kit near the kennel you go get it and come back here and i'll watch you do
the test oh just like in the movie he shot they shoot they're shooting him well turned out he
wasn't the thing just needed to see that's so funny they were just like nobody was even talking
either they're just like i guess i guess we're just gonna shoot them i guess so all right we
have to go to the medical tent go get the blood test these are grenades okay anything else in
here what's this a key that looks good save it one more time no soft locking right don't get
soft locked all right we need to go find the blood tests in the medical tent which i haven't gone
this way if you kill everybody you're gonna kill the thing yeah but if i kill everybody then i
lose this is i like this it's working out pretty well so far oh easy was there a health pack that's
it this well i guess this is shelter technically all right let's go blood all right we're looking
for medical supplies something's gonna jump around a fucking corner an engineer come here
don't get it okay break the boxes what the fuck just happened he's puking boy boy what
shoot him oh no everybody all right come here i can heal you uh how many health packs do i have
so that came out of this guy's mouth how are we all doing get in here open this everybody get in
here two shotgun shells ammo give me a pistol why can then why is there no pistol here
all right ammo wise though how you doing give ammo do you got two clips so you got two out of 20
so then you have one you only have five you've got one clip left take this take them both i think
there's a little bit more over here too is there i got so much pistol ammo all right what about
health you could use a heal let me just equip it heal them both we're good that was fucked up
back to the flashlight all right let's do it just stay here come on you can do better than that
i just like went in the building that's it area looks good all right uh this way
nice i just i want a pistol or something something small so i can contribute
blood tests the blood test hypo you recently picked up is specifically designed to expose
the virus entity when it exists in a human host you can use these to make sure a squad member is
really human and also to prove to your squad that you're not infected to boost their trust
to use a blood test hypo on a squad member simply equip it then approach him and press mouse two
yeah you so you do that and if they're an alien then they freak out and they turn into an alien
use on them where we're about to uh be tactical about using blood tests
they're a rare item and you won't find many yeah so this is where it gets interesting
nice you guys did it good work this is how you really play the game on hard don't you think
you guys are all right everyone's happy but i need to we need to open boxes um all right you've had
i've had give me your gun i don't care anymore give me all of it yes sir
there's nothing even in here what are you guys is this the legend of zelda shit or is anything
actually even in here i need a place to go in right now this is not it's am i just wasting ammo
i'm wasting ammo there's nothing there's never anything in these no way i've just proved it
it is a waste of ammo wasting ammo omega lull tactical i don't have any ammo for you just
make it last all right i got three blood tests we gotta go back where's the uh where's the road
i already went up there right yeah okay get a fresh uh fill up all right let's go
and then it was over here all right here we go let's do the blood test
i'm gonna prove hi you give me the finger you got the kid good the report said the hypo
contains a chemical that reacts with blood do it we'll soon know one way or another now i'm
gonna show you what i already know return blood test all right he's real no he's it's a it's a
thing that's a thing kill him i killed junip they were both things what oh wait wrong guy
i killed him i don't have any ammo left are you a thing that's the image you see at the end
when you lose a game and left for dead you fall down then your friend falls down right after
they were both things i give me a break they take a lot of damage i have to they have my weapons
all right i'm cheesing this giving my stuff back you don't deserve it get out of here
give me my stuff back i don't give a shit oops it takes up the whole thing all right here we go
that's a save scum what if i just no you can't you have to prove it first
you have to prove it first all right i'm ready let's go you got the kid damn it good report said
the hypo contains a chemical that reacts with blood all right so do it shoot and then burn no
one way or another this guy's flamethrower guy now i'm gonna show you what i already know
mm-hmm here we go take their guns their guns and ammo i didn't i think it will get us out of this
wait we didn't even test him we didn't test him yet all right let's go double it double it burn
him all right now burn him okay we're good although i've no ammo so i i should have trusted you i'm
sorry it was my fault you're a good you're a good guy now what the hell do i do i have to test you
come here all right let's do this okay now where do i go shoot him no i'm saving a different slot
just in case i soft lock myself in like 10 minutes so we just leave oh okay pierce pierce god damn it
what pierce must have got lost behind me somewhere what do you how wait who i don't know who's who
hey what the hell are you doing blake is that you um am i glad to see you he's throwing grenades at
people psycho yeah it's me you jackass now let's get inside i need to i gotta test this guy man me
and williams were tracking this weird animal through the base and we lost him in the storm
and then we ran into a swede norwegian yeah the norwegian guy well he started shouting and
attacking me and i started chasing him and i lost him in the storm what about williams i lost him too
whoa you're fucking pretty useless buddy and you've been wasting grenades just throwing them into the
snow like grenades i got like a key or something nice that's uh thank god you have a gun right
you got ammo for that gun what do you got what do you got for ammo i'll give you a little i'll give
you a little bit of ammo give you a clip that's all you get because i don't know if you're real or
not you could be fake all right what have i got let me equip yeah 10 regular grenades all right
just do not hit right mouse button can you get can i take these can you take these two come on maybe
i can give him some grenades give no i can't give me that back you can only give weapons
or actually you probably should have a couple of clips i'm all right with that check yourself
i already did all right let's go so now we have to go find the alpha team do you like me yeah you
look really like me i guess all right over here are you an engineer what are you soldier engineer
this ain't gonna open uh where's the box i can do this one shoot him all right you just show
that you're actually you you're worth keeping around nice work i want a light i hate not having
to lay up aim over there i need a pistol christ okay no we're not i got a radio for assistance
they're like zigzagging what's wrong what's that mean what's matter what's wrong what's
wrong what's matter you're right all right you're okay he's like what are you good yeah
i need an engineer you're not oh you are an engineer oh they're coming out of the box
can you take care of that actually no you go to the box i'll take care of this
wait wait wait wait wait wait what's over here can't open this shoot him we always do
i need a safe point i don't feel safe right now protect me lost contact with the medi center today
we set the team up to investigate but then lost contact with them in the storm they would do to
check in over five hours ago but there is no way i'm going to send anyone else out there in this
weather medi the medi center one of these guys are gonna stand up this is a cafeteria oh stay
the hell away from me i'm warning you williams i need your help bullshit you're infected just
like the rest come any closer and i'll fry your ass listen i found pace i just need to get into
the calm room to call for assistance do you have access who is the alien this time
but i ain't going nowhere with all those things out there you kill them and i'll help get us out
of here okay kill all walkers all right but do you have anything back here that i can use
i don't know we will find out kill all the walkers computer there all right walker yeah nice one more
was the last one in the oven or something don't attempt to take on any self-repairing alien entity
without the ability to cook them flame weaponry is the only way to kill large enemies when attacking
your target be sure to administer enough fuel to ignite them but be aware that the environment
and squad members could become part of the barbecue we learned that one the hard way
the flamethrower can also be used to lay down fire walls that can be used to pen enemy targets
what what do you mean wait there's a i have two flamethrowers oh shit there's a
mini flamethrower and then a big flamethrower nice nice job thank you oh i got one all right
do i stick them with this or do i save it should we just find out right now well wait till the uh
shows symptoms which is the backup in case of a soft lock i don't remember all right we killed
all the walkers for you or crawlers is what they should have been called those weren't walkers
all right this is oh shit is that fuel full fuel and there's still fuel in there so let's go
the same is not open oh come on what shit oh oh my god okay well uh yeah we do and you're
gonna fight whether you want to or not i told you to kill those things let's kill it i'm not
wasting any ammo you can do it this guy is infected 100% do you think so you want ammo you're not
getting anything you good not really those things are huge too they do puke okay so they
oh oh wait are you gonna die oh run run run run away run away get away get away got it god i wish
they'd like dropped where are they ceiling i get you gotta get healed i have to heal you
you're almost an ammo too oh shit you are here take a take a clip and then let me heal you
no it's over here i got a full inventory all right you're good there's one more of those
things a huge you got a clip you can do it down all the way across where's the last one
all right i have two where is it i hate that they can come from behind too
oh shit where is it shoot kill it kill no we're not it's dead got it you're good all right hey
what the fuck man i can't tolerate that shit i didn't i didn't i didn't get a key i thought
i got a key for that door no we gotta go this way all right stop i'm trying to remember where
we went the first time where was he oh shit i'll take some ammo here take this oh man that's a lot
of that's a lot come here take no what if it's you what if you're the bad guy all right actually
that was worth doing just come over here he's infected he's not infected he's fine i have two
rumors here now i need your help if we're gonna make it out of here alive you've got to get me
in the calm room now yes sir follow me captain all right we got hold on wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait what are you doing what no wait wait we have to follow him um so you're gonna
be flamethrower guy all right we have to all right relax damn it okay everyone's fine
follow me i have a plan we're all gonna die in here all right uh i need an engineer test them
we will we will don't worry come here oh but is it bad that i don't want to know because these
guys have weapons and they can shoot stuff in the meantime take their guns then test
didn't i get two of these test yourself on webcam where i'm leaving no i don't want to know i don't
want not yet it's not important yet you want me to do that now what if this room just fucking
erupted holy shit wait make a firewall that didn't work shoot fire fire fire fire fire
i'm getting out of here i'm getting out of here wait what about it's fucking hectic man
okay it gets loud and scary wait don't go out yet how's everybody on health uh oh he's about
he's about to crack what do i do give him weapons right he needs ammo everyone get over here come
here come here come here come here come here stop why did you just do that yes sir oh shit he's
he's like going crazy all right you pansy what's stop doing this all right how do i do
how do i get morale what do i do appreciate no they're both you just fucking psyched each other
out all right what do i do stay can i give you something that you like we have to get you out
of this room and that's the problem all right i need to use the comms wait health stop all right
now what do i have to go we have to get out of the room all right now test he's real he's legit
was holy shit that was fucking ridiculous all right where'd he go is he gone why is he gone
wait he's not here anymore what is it saving from what just wait what why is he running away
what hold on is he the thing no why is it remembering my save all right no you're all
right we're good why are you running this music here take some of that okay you good all right
you're okay now you need some healing though heal yourself don't you have your medic here
for god's sake thanks what's this machine gun somebody want to get that gun nobody needs this
gun that's i'm surprised nobody needs this no ammo in there either all right so we've got
there's a shotgun in here uh yep oops i just wasted a clip what was that everybody get in here
what he keeps trying to leave what did he just do you just wasted a you just wasted a med pack
all right follow me all right thank you okay shotgun oh we're gonna spread this ammo out
look at all this ammo oh yeah okay here hold on you come here i've got a ton of ammo no no you
don't have any other gun you keep the flamethrower that's a good idea i like that idea now you
take some of this ammo in fact take most of it yeah max i have a shotgun now yes sir all right
what about the healing plenty of heals shotgun there's so much so many guns in here all right
very cool that's it i can't take anymore so let's go it does very cool well very cool
cool i'm putting two fingers on the couch i'm not helping just looks like i am
whoa whoa whoa what how many bullets are just i just shot how many did i just shoot what's going
what's going out of the ground all right somebody get in there i'll fix you up burn it where's it
area looks secure it's not all right fix this i will then fine throw a grenade in the room oh
yeah i do have grenades you're right i don't really like the shotgun it's weird it's too hard
to use no they're not freaking out all right ready from now i can go out this way and then
through here no which one just opened one of these just opened it's this one here
oh flamethrower why is there a horde coming why am i shooting a shotgun with one hand
okay just give me the way firewall what why am i scrolling on my web browser over here
oh shit all right can that be over this should help yeah i'm scrolling up and down over here on
the right you need to blood test chat oh i would fire fire come on sub only sub only doesn't help
sub only makes it so it's easier for you to hide okay there are too many of these why there's so
many it's just waves of enemies can we leave all right we got i dig everything in here i think i
got mostly everything just wasted a fucking clip it's all right all right now do something
get both hands on the couch now all right i gotta get the fuck i gotta get the fuck out of here
this is i'm getting nerd neck that's not good all right i gotta get out of here
ammo come here no not you you what do you got for ammo five just fill up completely there's a
whole box behind me all right let's go where am i supposed to go where do i go i don't know
what i'm supposed to be doing explain the couch what what do you mean explain the couch
i'm a little busy right now all right get out get out get out get out i have to leave which
where do i go i don't know how to i don't know what to do radio room do i have to press a button
they can't open doors all right what do i do i feel like i need to do something
leave the door is closed it's like locked behind me how do i get out of here they're overwhelming
us oh shit lift him up help what what see i can't fucking leave do i have to just keep doing this
i'm so fucking lost right now i think i just have to keep fighting there's nothing i can't
do anything over here sub only what am i doing i'm unaware what's going on was the channel
fucked up all right throw it in sub only for fucking five minutes hold still and i'll fix you up
did i i think i was supposed to do that wait what this shit a big one there's a big one
he doesn't know where we are he went in the wrong room all right he went in the wrong room
he thought we were in the other room he's like i'm gonna get him i know they're in here
they can actually get in oh god wait i have to shoot him shoot him what no he's running away
don't let him run away where is he going what the fuck is going on right now the door open the door
opened no it didn't ammo how's everybody doing you need heals williams heal him all right they
save the game jesus now i can leave right can i actually get the fuck out of here
which one of these doors was this one here all right we can leave so i was supposed to do that
holy shit what happened who is that supposed to be who the fuck is that find norwegian with radio
gain access to warehouse explain the couch okay listen when you move furniture if three or four
people are moving a couch in a hall two people or three people are actually doing work the other
person that has been you before it's been me you put your hands on it and like oh i'm helping but
you're not you're like pretending to help didn't we go over this before more than two people to
move a couch it depends on the kind of couch you what you've ever moved a huge like 150 pound
piece of furniture before they're hard to move i can't get in there all right up there over here
oh clip no i'll go this way 150 pounds is feel in here must be all over the place
what 150 pounds for a couch well it depends like if you're talking a sofa a huge sofa
oh i gotta take care of something get up here burn this guy i would like a little bit of
a positive outlook here instead of we're going to die not once have one of you guys said
let's get it not one time what what just happened what just happened what just happened what
wait it was the wait he just what okay so he was that was abrupt that was very abrupt
i'm sorry for ever doubting you shit now it's only me and you oh i don't like that i thought
it was had to be like in a cut scene we turned the corner and he thought he could change and
kill us from behind that's fucked up i gotta start checking people now i actually have to
check anybody that comes new to the party can you make this jump down all right i like this guy now
it's gonna be an event did i not i can i have an adult come down here can you come down here
and take care of this apparently i'm well get in here get down here it's nice it's warm in here
get in here no not group stay get in here i can't go in here what the fuck is the point of this
oh okay no no no no no not another one where where are you don't run through the fire
where is he he opened the door okay get hold on get in here for a second that just scared
this shit out of me can we talk like can we just talk about what you're talking about here can we
talk can i can we do something can i like hang out with you and speak can we just hang out
okay so um i need to go back i need to use the fire extinguisher so we're gonna all right
give me the fire extinguisher we're gonna put the fire out in there
i can still hear somebody on the fucking like roof give him a hug you can't well you're about
to not be how are you still alive in here yes we do can you get him how you doing you're all right
he's running running get him nice all right good job you take the little ones i'm i can do the big
ones i feel the love of god what's in here weapon no it's a key key to what useful npc yeah finally
i feel bad for you know testing them what's that a key to though key to like that warehouse that
i need to go into where where's the where is it over here is this building this building over here
too can i go in this like shed i mean i'm gonna do it because people will scream if i don't
nope you're very obviously the thing right like you have to be gain access to the weather station
just did i need a save point so badly how much ammo does he have hopefully enough wait lockers
okay incoming jump scare i'm just waiting for it okay oh a tester surprising all right how many i
have two blood test kits that's pretty good that means i can use it once pretty reliable i i don't
want this guy to die you know what i mean i want to keep this guy around what's his name what's his
name pace i didn't even know this person's name but we are good fucking friends okay big guy where
we were just ah burn i tested him like 45 minutes ago i tested that guy like an hour ago what
happened did he get scooped up somewhere i lost sight of him he got infected is it really just me
when i was in the vent oh right god damn it really when i was in the vent what do i have for health
right now i don't have any friends and i have to fight a huge guy oh fuck i don't fuck you
die die burn what's going on why is he oh i don't have any friends i am
friendless i don't feel safe at all i feel horrible i don't like playing the game by myself i like
playing the game with friends that can shoot i gotta go up but this pistol finally no now
it feels like a horror game wait wait it's spreading it's spreading ah i don't have any
friends anymore i need to heal i may have been able to keep those guys around too that's what
sucks what is that if i have been testing people i have four testers i could have been testing
people and keeping them alive fuck whatever i'm hoarding my testers two people dead out there
all right i'm going up ah okay i hear somebody computer gen inc personnel were here today
again they appear to be working on something under the ground i've seen a lot of their equipment
arriving but i'm not sure where it is being kept underground right this shit is locked now
really come on that's where he went did i miss something over here yeah i'm sorry i'm sorry to
intrude oh burn burn burn burn burn burn burn burn burn i need more burn ah okay what was in
the bathroom please be a key imagine if i just walked over here why is this happening oh there's
a head there that's another tester fuck there's nothing here there's like spitters get off that
table get out of here but where's the key what the fuck how are you still alive key key key key
there's a key in kitchen key and kitchen i'm almost out of butane whatever this thing uses
key and kitchen key and kitchen where's the kitchen i don't know what the kitchen is
have i been in the kitchen where's the kitchen a kitchen upstairs key and kitchen where a key
all right i got it okay who are you and why are you running away what the hell happened
wait it's over oh it's just the this is flamethrower guy i can feel it i can get you out
you know god damn well there's only one option here no no i can't do that you don't have a choice
look i won't let you die asshole come on can't handle it come on what do we do keep around crazy
like my dad always said if you want a job done right you gotta do it yourself
oh negative turns out it was just gas what is this it's a sniper rifle that's pretty cool let
me see what it looks like how do i aim it right i don't want to click because if i click it might
shoot this sniper ammo downstairs too what else do you have in your hand holding yeah holding a
sniper rifle like this is just wrong i positioned the telescope on a large object in the ground
there's some activity and i saw people transporting equipment and containers to the site
okay so this is where the ufo is what's that anybody notice anything i don't see anything
out of the ordinary besides a giant i mean it's a flying saucer should i move the telescope interact
quick equip toggle free look left shift left shift there it is hold on a minute i
this is a first person mode die you dead oh you have to stand still to use it but that's how you
do the sniper but how do you zoom oh that's how okay i need a safe point is there anything else
down here that i can do i guess i could go in here dog food all right you can do i why did that guy
have to do that i you could have been my friend and you could have helped me i could have tested
you you could have we could have been sure is it sniper ammo i think this is a box of sniper ammo
let's test out the sniper rifle okay that's not sniper ammo what is this thing how is that not
sniper ammo i just really fuck now that sucks i just wasted a whole entire clip i had four
didn't i all right well hold on a minute here get this out of the way i can go this way just don't
fall off shit down there though should i go down there i'm almost dead um i'm cold too oh shit hold
on i have to get inside i have to get inside inside inside it oh come on is there a door
up go go go go go go go go get in get in get in get in unnecessary new enemy type
and i don't have hold on uh-oh don't use this i have to use this what is he doing
what are you doing what are you doing burn this guy sucks shoot him then i need where's my good
jesus that guy has so much health all right the noises i don't like the noises okay
okay you can open the door now what is this movement i'm sticking this guy's is immediately
blake you scared the shit out of me what are you doing here let's skip the song and dance pierce
is dead new friend get the hell out of here thank god i followed some guy in here thinking it was
the thing i trapped in here by those things was the guy from your team
no i yelled at him a bunch of times he didn't even look back could be the guy i was tailing
any idea where he went i think he's downstairs somewhere i'm so lost okay let's track him down
and then see if we can get whitley on the radio to chop us out of here all right don't let this guy
to my site and i'm gonna stick him right now we need to be certain i have plenty of them
i don't want this person to fall out look at this i got so many of these
are you immediately going to make me sad is there a safe point in here there isn't is he safe
let's do this we're good how do you feel he is not infected controls for operating the crane are
situated at the bottom of the stairs okay ensure power supply is on before operating as this may
seize the mechanism next service is due in four months ensure power supply is on before you
operate so bottom stairs operate thank you by the way how am i doing on health
i'm pretty not good i don't think let's use another there we are okay no sudden movements
no bullshit you don't have a gun i will give you one because i know that you are for real
let's give you something sniper rifle no why would i do that he's gonna shoot at stuff on
the ground pistol shotgun shock i don't like the shotgun pretty good timing pretty good time
it was a one minute and 12 seconds first lap see you again in a minute and 15 seconds
i'm gonna give the shotgun i don't i really don't like the shotgun i think it sucks
it's too it's weird it's too awkward i like this one i need a butane i will be the flamethrower guy
we're buddies that's a that's a weapon hope you can handle it let's go yes sir i'm not going to let
you go out of my sight flashlight he's already out of my sight he could be infected i'm so paranoid
about this now all of my friends have been infected what did you see something we got company where
wait wait wait follow me follow me follow me over here over here over here over here over here over
here there's so many of them what are you doing okay i think i did something okay did i do something
good i don't know where's my friend stop we're fine he shot me in the back of the head with a
shotgun start running what are you standing there for oh god shoot him shoot him shoot him with your
shotgun shoot him you fucking idiot oh what are you doing thank you he's been hit more than once
the chance of being infected is 80 percent no it is not he is not 80 chance infected i don't buy
that i don't buy that that's not real i need to heal though how you doing i'll heal you too
i accidentally pressed no it's okay i still need it thanks you're welcome let's get some weapons
there we go shotgun test him test him test him he's not test him he's infected
but we know he's not he's not infected give me the shotgun but he's not infected thanks guys i'm not
listening i'm not listening to you guys for the next 40 minutes he's fucking infected test him
test what i have to test him after every single fight no i ain't doing that okay we're good what
a waste all right don't don't do it to yourself get this off my flashlight back i still have
like these flame grenades all right i'm gonna use those grenades at the next encounter because
i'm running out of uh butane yeah i don't get any more butane all right we got some random shit on
the ground over here what about inside the crate yep there is a bunch of useless shit that i don't
need great that's fantastic reminder to whether station personnel key cards can be obtained from
the foreman in the office i'm going to go to the office wherever that is damn it it's locked
so what now i gotta go back up here foreman in the office this building over this way because
i was i came from here so wait what's this on the side all right fix it are you an engineer
oh i'm an engineer i can do it finally light wish i did that earlier oh come on what so what the
fuck is every door is locked did i turn the power on something can i move the crane because of the
power i can't like do this or touch this or anything can i climb the pipe i don't think i
can do that can i maybe i can hold on i have to test him again no he's good
i guess i do have to do that oh shit wow okay let's go can you make it up this
he's not going to come up here right no he's too stupid all right give me my machine gun
looking for a key or a way to go down an office or a box i'll take a box over here what is this
just ammo secret doesn't look like it i guess if you want to call that a secret you can
that's bad i looked over here at chat somebody said secret i'm like no see
what does that start me if i restart level all right that's fine that's not bad that is sorry
yeah this is fine it's literally right here i'm right here don't worry you the same exact thing
just played out you just you just rewound the game what is going on burn you just rewound the video
by like fucking 10 minutes okay get in here who are you we're good tap on the computer yes fun
fill up my sack you're good i gave you the shotgun you can have it again i know you're
not infected take the shotgun and all the remaining clips inside good luck i will be flame guy okay
good where's my little my little torch good put the lights on all right yep put on the lights
we have a second chance here cool all right you coming follow me yes sir he's double dead
maybe i should have you stay up here and shoot from below okay what the fuck are we getting
burned but i'm not going to pretend like i know let's do it bring it on focus on one at a time
good nice one two right behind us done good watch out good teamwork so far it's empty watch it watch
it watch it watch it watch it watch it watch it watch it watch it watch it watch it watch it watch
oh i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead don't die don't die don't die please don't die
where's it let's go god thank you how you doing you're okay now he's gonna be infected
don't say that he's not gonna be infected and he's not infected does it say it here
miscellaneous information no trust no synopsis no fear is it on that that syringe does it say it
that's so weirdly specific enough that i think it's real why does my hair look like a doormat
doesn't make any sense a doormat what what the fuck are you talking about all right if subjects
is infected wait if the subject is infected would explode to use blood test let's do this
fucking god god fucking give me a break he's not infected i'm gonna do that every fucking time
he's running out of blood all right you go repair the thing i'm gonna go up and not fall off
fucking cliff nice shooting actually for real like not kidding for real that was great
all right you got full ammo well you do now all right stay in my sight no wait i gotta go from here
okay please do not fall off i'm so paranoid now it's like kind of wonky and slippery
i can walk though what's the walk command there it is all they think everybody thinks this is
overkill it's not that ammo over there is not in a gun that i care about right he's infected no no
fall joke that's so far back you know i'm saying it's like that's it's so far back that why would
i do that i'm not gonna do that it's too far back okay this way let me just get the ammo
you just did it 15 minutes ago i'm not if i look at chat that means i'm not looking at the game
so i ain't fucking doing that that's how this shit happens because i go oh what what did they say
i'm not gonna look until i'm safe not fucking happening now i'm paranoid now i think i'm gonna
fall and i'm looking i looked over there at you okay i don't need to mute if i'm gonna be quiet
what's the point of doing that okay i'm good wait how do i get over there okay like this no
emotion oh it was a mess okay hold i can't okay i made it hold on i need the key first i need to
be safe key card computer construction of the test chambers has been relatively smooth we lost
another three workers in an accident last week but the boss doesn't seem to think that is a
reasonable excuse for being a few days behind schedule i can't get any more hands on this
project the workers have been glorifying their experiences here when they return to base and as
a result people are too scared to come here okay hold on i i can't alt tab so i need to hold on a
second okay how do i get over there all right somebody i can't i cannot alt tab it'll crash
again um some copy and paste what the what the who said it and what they said they said you stink
no i'm gonna get it turn off your lights it's it's it's a literally haha made you look it was five
it's fifty dollars five thousand bits from colonel zero and they said i made you look you did actually
you actually did do that because i didn't know what it was at first well thank you
what close the door then no thanks for the 15 thanks for the 5 000 bits seriously
are you infected they could be infected i didn't have an eye on them all right i got the key card
who gives a shit let's go don't shoot that far away with the shotgun what are you dumb are you
actually stupid you don't fire from like a hundred thousand feet away i'm being toxic damn it it's
where's the key card thing over here he's being talking i'm not i'm not being toxic
all right get in here thank god save scum test no get over here get over here where you going
it's you what why i sort of when did this happen why does this keep happening to me
i fucking knew it too when he i left him for too long why can i can't see the chat now what
happened to my chat room alone again at least i got the shotgun back not that i use it he used
a bath bomb test him what is what oh my wish i wish i had a fucking friend wish i had a friend
i don't even have any hold on i i grenades i have regular grenade um please one two three
one two three one two three oh come on you're not you're seriously gonna do this you're gonna
do the a mom from isaac no you have to hold it what do you mean we told you what do you mean
we told you you looked away scripted chat was right we tried to warn you we were right oh yeah
what was that chat was wrong all right get down here so i can see you get down here it's scripted
it is a scripted one some of them are scripted so what happens if i do this why what do you mean why
give me the shotgun now i'm not wasting that give me this give me everything you have you're not
gonna get up right i'm gonna laugh my ass off if he comes by so you're telling me that i could have
just okay wait a minute oh yeah right grenades this is oh yeah this part coming up right okay
give me the grenades and we're i'm taking care of this what's with the audio that was fucking
stupid we're always right don't run into the grenades well i have to make a trail no i'm
just gonna do what i did last time two three one two three he hit it he exploded in my hand
he hit the fucking thing in my hand and it blew up in my hand okay i'm it's a good it worked
last time it was a good strategy what else do i have here i could throw okay i'm gonna throw
flame grenades that makes sense right and then like give me just give me the shotgun and i'm
gonna spam shoot the gun this is not how a shotgun works what the fuck is happening
okay wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait this is what the fuck is happening
right now i need to let's get me a cut scene is he still alive what is that i just i just had a
cut scene oh man okay i it gave me a cut scene you all know it all right fire this thing sucks the
shotgun doesn't shoot and then it shoots like seven times in a row it goes boom don't don't
don't don't go and i get hit before the cut scene ends watch this ready cut scenes over
you just took damage t i thought i was over fuck is it okay now i need the grenade again one two
three god damn it get these little fucks out of here is it dead i think it's dead you little
fucks will you die if i die i was standing on the nest how did i survive okay everything's dead i
have to kill that from here there's nothing else here wait don't do that is that killing it these
na throws i don't think i can even kill this got it okay fix this machine no enemies right
if one thing comes out i'm dead okay i know i'm gonna die i i take one hit i'm fucking dead
i don't have any use my health i don't have any health packs
i don't have any flamethrower i have this but it's not you have to help too long
um one two three go he's in that one he's in that one don't open that one my my hands just
got itchy from that he's locked up grenade test you're infected what i'm gonna throw i'm throwing
a grenade at the room it's gonna kill it watch this this is a game from like fucking 1923 whatever
1925 it's gonna hurt him i'm gonna it's gonna head let's watch this ready i might kill him with
this i see blood one more one more one more that's it i'm done
he moved a little it's all right i did enough you're hurting the door
i i have to do i do you know how far back i have to start if i get touched hey
fucking angry cats i'm almost out of bullets stop coming up stop coming out stop
stop coming out of this oh no he's playing a fucking shooter game on me he's
fuck i'm in so much trouble hey shoot the gun why does it take so long when i'm aiming down
and going like this i'm pressing click what did you hear how many times i clicked what the
fuck is going on with this bullshit why there's so many i'm never gonna go i'm never gonna get in
this room and they do this like oh how many more are in here this is stupid oh my fucking god
i just stopped caring my shotgun is broken my shotgun is broken it's a broken shotgun
it's got like 400 millisecond lag they don't do i just have to go is it this is never gonna stop
it's never gonna stop it's never gonna stop it's never gonna stop this never ends shoot the fucking
gun shoot the gun shoot shoot shoot shoot shoot i'm gone ah where is okay i'm safe
we've taken a number of the research specimens and are running tests on them the most interesting
of which is taking place in the growth chamber access code 7291 where the dead specimens have
responded to the treatments and are showing results of up to 400 cell growth the next stage
is to attempt reanimation of cells dr dean faraday find faraday i have to go pee holy shit that was
stressful all right i'm right back i'm gonna pee why am i so mad today what mad mad all right
i'll be right back okay i'm back i wanted to get a little tea to drink as well but i have a funny
story for you it has to do with the thing so i've seen the thing a few times and uh kim had never
seen the thing so as kim you want to watch the thing yeah yeah that sounds great you've never
seen it before no okay awesome so we sat down to watch it and after maybe like 45 minutes or so
started to get really really interesting really in depth wow this is like what this this is
getting really crazy wow this is a good movie right uh another like probably 15 minutes go by
and i noticed that she's on her phone i'm like what are you doing on your phone oh nothing nothing
i look over and she is reading spoilers for the thing she's reading spoilers for the movie the
thing the movie that we were currently watching i was like why are you where you're currently
consuming it right now there's like 40 minutes left in the movie it was really funny tester
hey i'm back there's your boomer wallpaper right guys wait is it not on the right this is gonna i
think it's crashed did it no it's here is it where are my eyebrows they're here because of the way
the light is hitting my face it gives me batman eyes because i have like a large brow bone as you
can see so there they are but i have a large brow bone as you can see so they go like that see it's
not it's not the same guy it's a different guy test him we ain't doing that all right so last
what was i doing panicking thank god there's a save point so that's good uh find door three
door four i have to pick a door door one door two okay i think i'm about to open up the door
uh i'm opening up the door with the with the alien in it can they all be open at the same time
and why can i not open door one door one is broken all right all the doors are now open
what is this oh it's oh shit what is that take it yeah i know i already know it's down here we're
throwing a grenade in that room number three is the one that we're throwing the grenade
let's hope i lived that long there was something i knew it i knew it was i knew one was still alive
this is bad because i really don't have any ammo okay three what turn the corner two
there's three get it in the room fire fire i need fire where are you going what are you doing
he can't be set on fire what the fuck was that no wait he's he's coming out of the room
since when why does it change does he know where i am is it was is that my guy right here or is
that scripted that's my guy god damn it okay no i can hear him this is gonna be this is gonna be
really hard hey remember when that person said that you can really easily softlock yourself
in the thing well there he is i can hear him sprinting okay if i don't press the button
it doesn't happen right if i don't look at it it doesn't happen where'd it go
where did that just go save it what else do i have for guns i mean i i can't burn it i
gotta burn it but i've got to hurt it first oh man where is it where is he he's right there
he's like taking a shower all right here we go ready what the fuck did it go
did i did i hit him what happened i have to burn him i can't it's not gonna work
okay i'm just getting out the little torch and i'm gonna put on i don't know i don't know i have
to just burn it what do you oh this is i this is gonna be fucking hard this is gonna be so
difficult to actually get this done i have no idea all right here we go i have to light him on fire
throw a grenade under his feet it's the only way it it's like 25 feet in front of me because i
can't light him on fire in here i'm gonna bring him in the other room come here he's not gonna
open the door open the door open the door why does he do this shit oh my god why does he do the
thing where he just runs backwards and then like stands fucking still for five seconds and then
he goes you know what now i guess i'll get you seems like a good time follow me into the fucking
room in in in die ja what's going on what's going on why did it just go bang bang bang
save it i'm gonna lose track this sucks i need help big big mood what do you mean big mood
what is it what does that mean is there another one what's this new gun and a tester what is
that grenade launcher i have one shot in it i'm not gonna have the funny look at he walked into
the tiny fire joke happened to me not right now somebody else will think that's funny not me
real flame exposure you know what i was trying to say i don't know it's i'm stressed all right
so how do i open up one no health i opened up four but where's four there's one two three four
where's four i'm so busy freaking out i don't even know where four is right here uh-oh it's here
okay even the fucking sims get more than a tenth of a second when the kitchen lights on fire
it's not fair it was does adrenaline give you health anybody know you have to be so far away
from this shit give me my fire put it on all right now i have to just i have to leave i've
just run away i'm like biting my lips this is just stress what about this no all right
don't waste precious fire no i'm not i'm going right from here
right into that door and if that door don't open then i don't know what to do
i thought that fall just killed me go i'm turn i'm just turning to leave i'm just trying to leave
fucking soft walk i forgot right oh i have to save it after this too that that doesn't kill me
though save the damn game save it i'm being such a good lip biter all right let's go
what the hell is it that's why okay i'm dead holy fuck what what health i did it oh thank god
now i don't die instantly all right is there still a fire out here yes there is if this
fire exchange to die i can't do it how do i get out of here turn on the water how do i turn the
fucking water on shoot barrel where do you see a barrel shoot barrel oh guys that's like the set
it's look at it i can't see that it was come on it's tricky all right no fucking around save it
no save it save it where am i going patrol room one okay okay i know i now what what's four
i don't know man yeah i don't know either there's one two three i can't open one one's like broken
shoot the other barrel shoot the other barrel where is there another barrel barrel near one
it's possible maybe because i don't see any other way to go no there's nothing here no
barrels or anything i think i have to repair the door control but where do i go to do that
because i opened up four throw a grenade at the door well i get one shot at this
oh remember when we had friends i do let me go back this way because how did i even get
in here i was in a total panic how did i even get in this room maybe i have to look at the
ccc t vv wait a minute no kind of like hydraulic overdried does he have something like a note or
something or a code or a keypad or something hydraulic override i can't like touch it
i have no idea because this looks like the way you would want to go
there it there is a huge guy over here somewhere though i'm gonna take a flank throw
when the shotgun fires it's very good when the shotgun fires it works well
oh i want a friend so bad i need a friend right now anybody i wish it was the medic
is going on i hear a beeper alive no damn it it's amazing here too
yep okay i hear you why do i have zero what happened here why do i have zero my grenade
launcher what happened i threw it oh it's a grenade it's an actual grenade launcher
not like a grenade launcher it's a grenade device that shoots a grenade out of its cannon
why would i ever use that if i can just throw the grenade he's in here where's this motherfucker
i can hear him just stomping around he's in here i bet
yeah maybe this i think this is where the guy died yep definitely what die die would you die
already what are you doing over here you're just what you're doing is you're pissing me off you're
just pissing me off that's your goal computer bullets of course it's broken give me a break
hello hello hello hello hello die burn burn i am never going to find my way out of here
in a million years wait i don't want to miss anything what if there's like a health pack in
here do you hear that so you hear that right the little beep oh fuck is he above me or below me
i don't know i'm not going to stick around find out let's just keep going slow it down
something's gonna break through the ceiling control room i'm gonna save it i turned all
the way around and came all the way back um okay so what did i miss down here that's what i missed
one corner oh turn come here oh fuck oh fuck oh okay okay all right okay all right all right okay
all right die please die please this is the big one too this is like the big flamethrower if only
everybody i ever knew didn't turn into a monster i'd be swell again the game started with three
fucking friends and now i'm just it's just me alone in the dark he doesn't chase you he like
de-aggroes will you fucking die he's running very fast at me now now all of a sudden you want to
fight now all of a sudden right like right now this is it this is your attempt no no no actually
i don't want to fight you i don't want to now i'm just gonna like suck vacuum cleaner back to the
fucking spawn i didn't realize it was my curfew come on oh there's something over here didn't
even see this shit before take it i guess i'll take it oh what happened there i can't get that
open fuck okay let's go back hit the button activate the you know the crowd of people that
i'm gonna activate well i'm going the wrong way yeah this is back the way the way i came i almost
just said this is back the way i came by the way if you ever designed a ship like this you are
fucking stupid what your intention what is it what is this building toxic no that's reality
why would you make like a mouse and cheese maze all right i can open one you didn't have anything
else on you right do i like this game yeah it's pretty good i think it's fun i want more friends
i like the idea of your friends can turn into monsters without you knowing just wait for the
later sections oh god i don't even want to know fucking god what's up with his arm why does he
have like a what's with his arm what's with his arm why is he a super mutant where's he going my
god i need to save it you're blocking my path to save the game did he go this way i don't know
which way he went i don't know did he tether back to home yep where what he's right here isn't he
i hate that sound what
that better not be another one thank god save this game open up number one
prep lab here we go just save it here no wrong way i think it's time to do a tactic where i just
run i need another one of those rooms that has everything in it like a leopard dead safe house
one has to be coming up soon right what was that all right it broke out but where is it where is it
i don't see it shoot barrel shoot barrel he shot it he already got it but the door kill me the door
closed on me and fucking murdered me use your bang sticks what shoot barrel there it is barrel
all of you can can i didn't i say that i was not going to be listening to the chat room anymore
i did say that a while ago i did say that multiple times right right holy shit not possible
without friends not possible impossible without a group of friends i need like a whole party here i
need like a fucking healer i need a demolitions expert i need somebody that can summon like a
fucking spirit like they do in final fantasy i need everybody i'm not being this impossible
without a friend oh for the love of god don't run don't run don't run don't run don't you
don't run he's running why okay there's another one up there just trying to find a way down i
could save it here but i might soft lock myself we're going all the way to the bottom
look at all these doors oh no don't even fucking do this to me
all right that this sucks if that's what i think it is all right uh i gotta kill the guy up here
there's this tons of items up there speaking of items i know i picked up at least one of these
oh he's at the back of the door okay uh what do i got let me just use this
i ran through so many items but it separated them so that's good come here it's the guy with the
super arm all right it's the it's a power rangers villain that's what yeah i can't open the door
i could do this all day run around this i'm out of i'm out of it i'm out of no i'm not am i
okay what else was back here i did just sprint by there's a lot of random shit over here we got
okay we have a tester i can take it slow books take as many of these as i can carry
i have 10 of them now the game will not yet because i need health i mean i need ammo look
look clip look at the clip i can't i can't alt tab if i alt tab it fucks everything up
i can't do it save it what about this way i can repair this i need an engineer i know i can't
oh there's a bunch of shit in there come on what about this way
you know just check in to make sure i didn't miss anything and there's a spot oh some of my guys
are trapped in the testing chambers give me a weapon you're sure you gotta do this
when did i save it i saved it right before that right okay let's go dude i let me go save wait
when did i save it when was the last time i saved it tuber that was a tuber joke two hours ago before
the health kits all right i'm good 220 what the bottom one yeah right oh this is a long ass time
ago oh come on actually no it's not it's just what the uh the power range is going come here
just close the door ah one more should do it come on and there it is okay so i can explain um
i got startled and freaked out and shot shot him two or three times and then realized well it's
over now i'm gonna restart anyways the link the link i can't click the link you did it for the
video no i didn't i got all right i stick the guy with a fucking needle and i go like this and
all of a sudden i hear a noise and i hear a boom and i get fucking attacked in a cut scene look at
it and all right let me i'm gonna open up on my phone all right post the link so i can see it
i'm getting dizzy i'm getting dizzy laughing so hard at this picture why what does that mean
what does that mean link it link it it's not real it's not it's not real
holy shit is that real no it's not it's not real right oh my god it looks like somebody's
firing a fucking like disco bobby later ran into my face this is not real
is it real it's not real right somebody looks like i have a clip to prove that
there's no way that that's real it's not right holy shit that's fucking insane
that can't be real i was i have a full screen on my second
hold on where's give me the give me the real one there's a real one
holy shit you got me fucking kidding me i thought i thought i thought i looked like that for real
oh this is please give me the real one i'm like i'm like fucking coming out of my nose
that's fucked a human doesn't look like that okay so it's not fucking real i thought it was
i thought it was real totally fuck imagine okay just hold on a second you guys are quick
imagine looking at a picture that like is your face and it's yeah i don't know it could have been
real we i i've had pictures taken of me be going like this and i have like a huge chin
and it was real i don't know what's real and what's not anymore but that was fucking ridiculous
check the clips it's real somebody give me a clip give me a clip i'll save it new evo i mean
that's pretty that's a pretty ridiculous unedited it's not real okay yoda okay hold on wait wait
wait wait no no i have to play i have to get over this holy shit if my mother was watching
right now she'd be like what's wrong with them she is i need to just put that on screen because
for people that are watching the vod that maybe have no idea what's going on i need to show that
give me a second i need to save it that image has to be shown on the big screen
let me save the game we traumatized him you really did my eyes are like going in different
directions my mouth is huge it looked like a fucking cartoon character man it was scary it
was scary and it could have been real but why would it have been real i don't know but i thought
it was where the fuck am i no no no no it's right here okay i i'm gonna have to have to quit for a
second one second we got it saved let me just go like this this is the original one where let me
see my god okay so this is the original and then give me the fucking crazy one that's so fucked
that's so fucked up
all right so give me some give me like some credit just look i don't know you know how tough it is
to be able to determine what's fucking real and not real look this is the image this is the original
actual image that for those of you watching the vod this is the image somebody linked this okay
and they said that this is the this was real and everyone told me it was real and look at
how fucking crazy you look like really like that could it could be but it's not
it's not real it's real it's not don't fucking say that
this is killing me but i'm i know the first one's real
oh my god when i first saw that man you don't know the emotions going through my brain because
i remember it was on a cell phone this is not on my computer i looked at it on my cell phone
so it was like all blurry and fucking small okay and then the big chin thing right so of course
i'm going to be skeptical of what's real and not because those of you who are here for the big chin
we're here for the big chin i don't mean you already know i mean fucking jesus
i can't get over this yet the chin was real but that's the thing it's the reverse
the chin was real but i was convinced it was fake this one was fake and i was convinced this
one was real it's just it's all over the place all right back to fucking the thing i guess
holy shit i this how is it already a monster in here that is so fucking ridiculous that was a true
breakdown on stream i i seriously that was a true breakdown that was a real one it may have been
comedy related but that was a comedy breakdown here we go well there's a new enemy type so these
are i'm gonna be opening up doors oh wait oh faraday just the guy i've been looking for
he's the number one so don't even open any of these i gotta go get that engineer guy
all right open up one not yet though after wait there's somebody else here friends okay and that
one and nine have people in them one and nine two has a gremlin i think it's just one in nine
and then i have that engineer we're gonna have a full party here in a second all right not yet
though i want to make sure i can get over there with the engineer so let's get up here i've got
oh i'm getting like stomach pains god damn it okay engineer was in here i got all the health i
needed all right engineer to open that one oh where's my medicine i already took it today
i take it once in the morning and then once at night let me heal do i have full health
i will in a second full health let's go save the engineer all right where was he at down this way
somewhere there he is okay now watch out for the alien that shot that jumps up
what's up you need a weapon price what can i give you how about a shotgun how does that sound
maybe you will get us out of this load it is there only three bullets in there with three no it's
okay very cool okay and you're an engineer too so that's good do you have full health
yeah you need ammo uh change that give me that back wrong with you i'm gonna give you something
in a second i can give you a second one of these take that take a couple of clips take two clips
good now we're friends good awesome happy to hang out with you you don't you don't like that gun
all right well that's too bad i want you to open a door for me 10 stun grenades if you could follow
me i'd like you to open a door this one over here go for it it doesn't know the difference
yeah but i'm getting the same point across you know what i mean i'm being prepared let's go
save the game i want to give now let's actually give you the shotgun what the hell are you giving
you a shotgun and you're getting all the ammo for it because i don't like you using it because it
yes sir what did you just drop on the ground all right i am ready to save the game
everybody full health right save the game come with me you good that means he's infected
no it means he's he doesn't like the sight of people dead all right open up number one
which cannot be opened and number nine number nine is now open what the fuck what happened
what i don't understand but i was eating the little ones is it okay not gonna happen
not gonna happen i know what those things do wait my shot shoot it don't stand on the fire
he was infected he puked so they who the fuck are you what is going on why they all
i mean they're all infected immediately he gets hit i'm not opening anything till i clear this
shit out don't let him get hit then wait what the fuck happened what are you shooting oh what's up
hi um introduce yourself or don't yeah do you know what is he doing hello i missed don't let
him touch him don't let him touch him well that guy didn't he maybe because he wasn't even talking
he was just like suspicious or what all right no he didn't get touched he didn't get touched he
didn't get i just tested him he didn't even get touched he did not get touched i was watching
he's fine i mean he's a little freaked out but he's all right now okay we gotta open doors he's
good he didn't get hit that was a little weird i must say that was strange but not not illegal
right weird but not illegal you're good we're both good right you got yeah you got full health
time to start opening doors we're gonna open nine you know what just fucking open all of them
except for one he didn't get hit he didn't get touched didn't get touched he's fine you're good
he didn't get hit save it i can smell it no he's fine he didn't even get hit he did not take any
damage all the way down right i go first always because i don't get infected because i've got
strong blood like strong body strong blood if i get touched it doesn't affect me i have like
superman like what is what superman have blood the superman have blood it's like green right
the superman doesn't have red blood right it's green is it yeah so i have superman blood whatever
all right slow down i just want to make sure there's nothing here all right here comes a big guy
right here wall him off now you get the shots off because he can't get in here
shoot the shotgun in there he can't he can't move anywhere so shoot him in there
whatever nice try nice okay hey i didn't let him out see i kept one closed so he couldn't go
anywhere dr faraday i presume i don't think we've got time for formal introductions can you get us
out of here sure doc follow me oh and keep your ass covered i'd hate to see you get an unwanted
suppository all right it's do we test immediately or what should we test test them both the price
has not been touched faraday on the other hand has half health but i think don't i do i need like
his fingerprints to like scan a door all right he's clean he's good what about you are you still good
no i'm just gonna heal you do you need a weapon here take a weapon uh the sub machine gun
don't lose it and don't run away from me okay all right have i have a check myself no i don't need
thanks for the concern all right nothing else in your room here this door didn't even open
all right let's go everybody follow me anything else don't shoot me in the fucking back
where's where'd he go where's the doctor where's the doctor where did you go
god damn it did he run away that's not a doctor that's not the doctor you got stolen your body
got stolen then you wrapped around and whatever i burnt this thing on the way here he didn't get
hit just don't step in the fire look for his clothes i mean i'll just torture him if it's
i'll just kill him it's fine good let's go i could roll around on that and not get hurt like i could
just i could sit on that and i would not burn my ass that's the level of flame we're talking about
all right so i've got a team of three here so far so far so good now oh you're a medic
that's really good to know now we go where do we go now okay don't get hit don't get touched
don't let it touch you all right medic check this out there's all kinds of stuff in here where you
going don't where you going where you going where you going where you going where you going where
you going where you going it's just closed right there don't do that shit stay with me i'm gonna
just heal i have free health right there how's everybody else you good both you guys are good
stock up and now we go let's check over here refill all of our ammo i'm gonna give you wait
is there no more ammo in there i think wait there is no more in there okay let's do it back up back
up back up back up back up back up back up back up back up back up back up back up back up back
back up all right what the fuck is happening all right let's get out of here then let's go
i thought i was just shooting him in the face i'm okay good good good good
stay no no no no come over here both of you come to me i want both of you over here right now
shooting a grenade down this hallway come here come over here both of you stay here stay okay
i'll take care of this help i need a medic medic could you help me did you see that hard
blink the hard blink what are you doing what was that he's infected he's clean guys that is the
exact thing a alien would say yes no problem okay yes sir okay we're screwed it's all right i'm fine
he's freaking out you guy give me some credit here he's losing his mind we're screwed i'll
pull it together see we're gonna die here can i open the door and shoot a grenade to show you
that everything's gonna be okay what is it what do you want now what is it look good okay that's it
right that was really weird trajectory stay there nobody move i'm just making sure that there's
nothing else that's gonna are you dead okay fellas well you can't hear me through the door
let's go okay new zone what the hell stand down soldier good to see you doctor we need to talk
all in good time but first i'm afraid i'm gonna have to ask for your weapons i'm not doing anything
until i get some goddamn answers you're out of your league here blake well actually this is
this is all right i'm i'm okay with this because that means i can have them all in my party
i feel safe actually right this right now i feel safe isn't my medal of honor ceremony is it a
little premature right now we need to have you both tested what the hell are you talking about
i'm not infected my men are dying out there i've seen firsthand just testing is capable of oh you
have no idea what it could do you son of a bitch what a slow motion sprint at him
does get shot in the head what i thought you were smarter than that jesus christ what are you doing
it's just a tranquilizer faraday do you have any idea what's going on out there i have a perfect
idea jesus you've done it haven't you you there's so much i have to show you he's infected i think
you'll be impressed with the result i'm tracking somebody in the face up sleeping beauty and
help escort the good doctor he's had a long day definitely infected no doubt it's pretty
much certainly security status amber in sectors one to five non-gen ink personnel are required
to leave the installation immediately look at that nerd neck the me i think that's me what do
you think you're doing faraday the infection is spread across the base all of the organisms have
to be destroyed if it reaches the mainland there's no stopping it wait did we just let this guy do
whatever they let him do whatever he wants that the infection can be controlled no no that's not
possible the results can't be ignored doctor i will be remembered as the first successful test
no not if i can help it i don't need your help never turn you back to somebody
right before you say not before i can help it reestablished in all sectors you think you'd want
to have a detention focus elsewhere he still would have got shot everybody would have been able to
like lunge for the gun where's my friend i got nothing medibate power turn it on hey
you the guy the person with the gun you are you are you in a prison cell with a gun
who the fuck is that i probably should have looked in the window of the door that would have been
smart hey can you help me please hey hey hey hey hey hey do something help me do something
do something attack this person it's a there's no bullets in the gun what are you doing
what are you doing in here why would you be in here without what a fucking weirdo okay so
first things first look through the window first and i wouldn't have seen it anyways he was he's
just pretending to have this gun but who the why that why are you in there with a gun in the first
place okay so i can open this one or that one there he is this scary monster i would laugh so
hard if he just like swiped a key card and they walked by this guy and they like nodded at each
other okay well this is at the time this there's a lot of people around okay wait code
boston accent kind of sounded like it uh initial bio profile of test subject 873
suggests a high risk of cellular rejection if implanted with the b4 strain of the cloud virus
this is by no means conclusive but it leads me to think that subject 873 chief medical researcher
jen ink what do oh but it leads me to think that subject 873 may not be suitable due to illness
and company status so i gotta wait till he's out of the way he's turning corner now and we open the
door right next to me right here let's go get whatever i need out of here let's go fix it
oh shit what does that do hey just give me the fucking finger he why are you flipping me off
if i could haymaker right now i would okay well good to see you and who is in control of this
um i guess it's preoccupied oh i pressed the button i did that i did that
that's what that was the whether this computer explode i can't go in there oh fuck i don't have
a weapon wait let's get ammo i got ammo i got ammo i got ammo i got ammo i got ammo close the door
hey i got something for you how much ammo do you have here all right go for it follow me kill
all right i we need fire we need fire gun jf blake has been under observation for a few hours now
due to his combat training he is being considered as extremely high risk so the security gates have
been set to recognize his dna sequence his dna sequence the gates will sound the alarm if he
passes through and activate this automatic defense systems all other personnel can pass
through the gate without tripping the alarm the only problem is the malfunctioning gate in the
armory which should be fixed soon who's can you open this door i'm getting really sick of the
the saloon shootout that is just on my ears right now permanently okay sir excuse me
i don't have do you have any healing they should get you back in your face medic
did you get me to the security room i can give us some weapons a shitload of those things out
there area you following me all right security room watch just watch out for the never-ending
firing that's going on over here i don't know what's happening all i hear is fucking battlefield
can we stop the firing can you do you have any bullets get over here you
you don't have any bullets left all right but get over here i need you to open this door
can you open this door can this is the security door get it open you just stay
okay all of us into here now don't walk through that don't walk through that health pack you
yeah i don't have any more ammo do i i don't take his i can't go through this right can you go
through this okay you can go through this you're a personnel they should help just crouch no that's
going to go through my eyes okay hold on you go to just jump over the counter yes i do i've been
hearing it can you shoot this all right how do i get you to go through this you work here go
through that okay now go pick that stuff up you work here turn around turn around and get that
stuff over there over there i work here too okay cool all right wait wait there's guns over here
what the hell is that both of you get over here where do you go hey wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait come here follow me let's go in here it's safe in here for a minute we all of us are going to
have a weapon i promise stay stay stay stay right here okay what do you got i'm going to give you
um pistol and all the pistol ammo you seem like a guy that you're good with your hands is an
engineer so he can use the pistol like that doesn't make any fucking sense a chef it could
do that too chef is good with their hands okay so you i'm gonna give you ammo all right that's good
and i will be the flamethrower guy just stock up and i said what is this tab taser no actually come
here both of you you're gonna get infinity ammo yeah come here you're gonna get infinite ammo
all right you got infinite ammo cool all right let me fill up this and i got full okay how do i use
the taser can i tase people all right i'm ready we need us i'm ready to burn the guy everybody
follow me i'm gonna torch them you guys you're freaking me out get over here you guys stay here
you're just gonna cause a problem whoa why are you shooting me i gave you an order
i told you to stay and i know you just saved my life but you broke command don't do that again
i'll be fine yes sir hey oh i just turned that off imagine we just walked forward
just getting lit the fuck up all three of us it would have been horrible
because there's no sound of a save point i'm tasing this guy when he opens the door
there's a note on the ground i can hear things at night that freak me out it's also weird people
are disappearing all the time but i don't know why what are they doing to us why have i been
detained i've got to get out of this place there's a panel at the back of my cell which might lead to
an air vent only i could break it down that's all the information i needed what what you know this
guy you're an it's an air infected did anybody know this guy i'm chasing him all right don't know
we're good did he get hit it's just all right he's all right it's always the people that stand
completely fucking still like i need an access code access code i might be able to deactivate
the security gate with the correct switch sequence all right here comes a puzzle
oh my god no
fuck why did that happen that's such bullshit i don't i don't even remember i don't remember
even the chain of events that happened oh that sucks so bad i don't have any guns i did this
wrong i did this wrong i did this wrong i just kill me kill me kill me kill me kill me kill me kill
me kill me kill me kill me kill me kill me kill me kill me kill me come on this is keep throwing
baseballs at me come on oh i'm so defeated i can't believe it okay i can do it again i know everything
i know what to do i know what to do i know the chain of events i know it works hack the computer
no turn i gotta turn the power on in this room okay first things first power activate this room
you got it oh that sucks okay now wait for you where are you right now crossing pack i'm gonna
wait till you go this way yep instantly shoot this person in the head right i can i've got it all
i'm ready so we open this door and like just headshot this guy here we go grab the ammo
turn on the minigun what oh shit he can't open doors right
that's his like turning around the corner and then it's almost like he was armed like he had a gun
okay here you go yes i'm ready okay follow me please take my gun and take my ammo because
you're not gonna let me take it from you because you'll be mad okay sounds good you're a medic
follow me we need to go you need to kill these things do your best kill kill kill kill kill
good work okay new power activate we're good remember the note yes i do
hey look at this i've got a light hello need a heal take care of him
they should get you back in your face get me to the security room some weapons things out there
all right very cool yes sir dixon valchik valchik dixon we've been uh acquainted let's go
kill them good kill them will you kill it before give me the fucking gun give me the gun
give me the gun give me the gun just give me the gun you give me the gun you've wasted all the
ammo come on i need you to open this door yes please open that nice work hey look uh is that
a tester no it's adrenaline all right we're back where we were before get in here
i fuck i thought he just turned i was about to be so upset okay you know you guys could pick
this shit up too why does it have to be me every time all right you dixon i want to give you the
let's go ahead and give you the machine gun yep i'm gonna be flamethrower guy i want double
machine gun fire pistol is fucking absolutely useless okay like why would anybody use the
pistol i know i'm working on it i'm working on it here now we're better friends here take ammo
okay everybody good everybody has the most ammo they can possibly hold
i'm gonna do it too in case one of you guys turns and i'm gonna take it back
okay it's time to go both of you stay in fact don't even come out of this room
what the fucking computer exploded that he's getting knocked all the way back
okay back where we were before hi guys i'm back to refill i could also use a little bit of a
heel okay okay if you got a second they should help thank you this is grenades on the ground
no all right i'm full let's move no more fucking around all right who show this guy right in the
head i have a handgun i'm just gonna open the door of brightness but right in his forehead
what are you doing hi we'd like to come in
he waved his waving
boom i hit him in the shoulder i didn't even get him in the fucking head and then this guy like
turned it up to a hundred thank you for the help though seriously like i want this guy around
seriously like that's one of the only people that listened to me i shot the guy you didn't
do anything he did he helped i am terrified to do this i'm not gonna do it until i know for
certain what the hell the code is uh there's gotta be like a code that i need that i it's like oh
it's up down left right whatever one two four three all right i'm gonna let you guys shoot because
don't i hope you don't turn you still you know no one's been hit
save point that's so painful that this was right here if i just went this way first that's so
painful it's all right though lots of health how we doing on health i think everyone's good but i
know i have max health now code for the computer about functioning gate and armory sector they're
all for me what is this what are we looking at here i'm not sure what we're looking at here
this is the camera that was over here whatever that means is a gun this is a gun right oh fuck
it's a gun should i just what send your guy in there and then why would i think i'm gonna open
all the okay keep remember where this is yep okay i know it's gonna happen i'm gonna okay i need to
remember who this is but what on earth what's wrong which one of you is doing it who's turning
you hear that no i don't actually i did it's them who's them we can't get in here
you can't fix that here we go i might be able to deactivate it's not three two all right you want
to fuck they're just on the elevator they're just waiting on the elevator for somebody to fuck up
that puzzle all right fuck it let's go i already know all this stuff i already know all this just
do the fucking just brute force the puzzle nobody else right wait a minute all right hold on i'm
going what an idiot get him one four three two so i've got it wrong every single fucking way
there's a hair in my mouth i think i just swallowed it blah pull it out quick you can never
get it it's too hard to get the first time if you don't get it immediately you're swallowing
that here it's just the way it is one one four what wait what get out of here it was a new batch
did i do it the wrong how did i do it wrong one four two three did i screw that up
oh i did one four these four switches this four switches i was every video game that's ever been
a video game you do like you have to get them in the right sequence all of them it is very secure
let's go stop crouching open the door okay guys here's the room i i think you guys should go back
and stay in the other room okay um not watching them he was infected i get up i thought it was
gonna be way more it's like two or three little guys okay see i ran back as i thought it was gonna
be oh watch out the room fills with a ton of enemies they'll do it i cured them they both
started to go like i'm getting increasingly worried about the mental state of commander
witley i believe that he was injected himself with a b4 strain of the cloud virus even after i
personally refused him after the tests i currently have him under observation his behavior is becoming
unpredictable in addition to this i'm getting varied reports about his behavior from different
security personnel i'm not sure whom to trust on this and may have to issue a request for
termination if things get out of hand the experiments on test subject 874 blake have
proved inconclusive what this seems to be a minute trace of a cellular anomaly
that could be related to the cloud virus i will need to do further tests as the subject has an
unusual amount of exposure to the virus in its many forms that's me are you hiding back there
cell one cell 10 that's my that's my cell interesting what else we got here science
bullshit whatever that is i don't i can't hold the fire down
you know get up the stairs get up here and let me just block this off please
wow you are very very very very particular there we got company quality pathfinding that was just
like i i'm gonna i'm gonna go this way and that's it all right you're starting to piss me off a
little bit with your killing me heal me i demanded i demanded as your commander
thank you top 10 ai pathfinding clips there it is the cell but let's just open stuff
you know it's kind of fun to open doors okay get over here there's a guy in this one
i'm ready i'm ready to tase him
i speak he speaks that took you a long time you were downloading the entire
english language right there and like you want a taser are you all right fisk do i have a tester
it took him like a full 15 seconds to answer i can't give him the taser you can take the
handgun don't make me regret that do i have a tester okay okay i got it
we're good i got a whole party now follow me okay there's no reason to open this
go for it shoot shoot i'm ducking oh man oh man all right oh shit there's another guy
am i gonna have a full party stop moving no one of them has to be fake right
i'm not afraid to use this stanmore i think are we cool are you a i'm not getting any response
i don't have anything to give you but follow me i guess he's looking at me so strangely
he hasn't said a word of course he's a fucking alien shoot him yeah are you gonna go for it
not even like a sure okay i'll come with you yes sir yeah come with me you too okay
you know one of them was gonna be fucking fake all right let's go through the cell
and stanmore is a fake alien name we do is it you pretending to be a bad guy
what are they aiming it you ran by it all right let's go before you guys do anything stupid
let's get out of here get that open please i need someone to shoot this wait what no where's our get
over here i need a gun i know just to give that to you but just i need it for two seconds just
give it back you're you're hurt uh-oh you're actually pretty you're actually very hurt
come here all right you're good thanks you can have this back good how are you doing on ammo
good all right guys all right yes where'd you go where'd you go where'd you go which
don't please i'm just trying to keep track of everybody once there's more than like three of
you it's hard okay okay let's go i need my flashlight get over here where are you going
stop please he's freaking me out he's an alien only aliens would do that i think that guy is an
alien i really do come on i'm all of you need to get in here why are they what are they doing do
you guys not understand how to crouch get over here i probably have to open well now i even
could be aliens because i'm i just left them all they don't climb ladders do they no is that all
that's in there okay um how am i gonna do this sure wish i had a couple of people to be here
with me to do this would be great if there were three people with a ton of weapons because now i
have to time this and it's not gonna i he's in the corner idiot come on i just made him angry
all right into the same he's blocking him he blocked himself off i just have to deal with one
get right in the middle bang right there yes oh i got them both i got them both excellent oh that's
i feel so satisfied all right now it's just a question of how am i gonna go down this
is this gonna hurt me hey where the fuck are you okay that was a pretty good toss i will say
can i fix this i need an engineer nope i wonder if i'm gonna have a team after this
well okay guys i need you to come you know how upset i'm gonna be that they are all three of them
okay cool nice job let's save it everyone's so around still that's good all right oh cool
that's great and i got full health here and i'm gonna fill i'm gonna go back to the uh the room
with the ammo and we're gonna fill up again what was that room over here come over here
i've got ammo for you guys all right who needs it i'm just gonna give you all of it
you already have it all what about you i already have it all what about you
full refill i'll take it and if anybody anybody dies i'll take your gun because i'll have full
ammo speaking of ammo i've got full fire save the game again germ is infected i am not infected
okay so now i can go this way and you hopefully can open the door that is no not this way over here
open the door if you will no it's not this way which way was it this is like the smoky hallway
where's that smoky hallway there it is over here one two three i need you to open
this door go get it you can tell that germ is infected because his path finding is so bad
i did say that earlier so that's not inaccurate so these that turned on these computers
we're gonna get slam dunked on here request access code for elevator is two seven one zero
all right here comes the we're gonna get collapsed on let's be ready surprised none of you turned
yet usually that happens to me i actually feel fairly safe right now what we got you guys all
have weapons all right here we go let's do it what was that no this stuff over here oh it's just a
machine gun all right guys it's time for the squad get in there excellent job the squad
shoot shoot i like i like this guy's got this guy's got gumshoe no gumshoe is what they call
people and where is in the world is karma san diego you've got whatever it's called
uh-oh turn it off who did that did i do that oh it's oh it's opening and closing the door
get in here wait they could be uh items what's this do okay we do where did you come from
did you let him walk by you heal him
heal him heal this guy you're the medic they should get your back in your face
you're right thank you where you going don't press don't pull that don't press that button
damn it you know close the door close this fucking door how annoying are these
these guys are fucking aggravating yeah we're good all right oh my oh my god
fuck off keep the medic alive how much health does he have all right we need to move we need
to move now in in the door inside please this way good can you fix this
need an engineer okay hold still and i'll fix you up watch out headshot nice work all right
what the fuck is in here tons of grenades i'll just take as many as i can okay everyone's good
on ammo i can give you a better weapon now you also are gonna have a machine gun i'm gonna is
this turret surrounding me all right okay how about health everyone's okay take some ammo for
later put those grenades on and be ready i need a safe point pretty bad hopefully there's one up
here there's not there's tons of health packs sniper cctv well this would have been nice before
i guess we could come back here if i needed to escape and i don't i guess this is one way to go
but down no down here i got extreme deja vu right now coming down those stairs walking over here
why i don't know why it was very very strong though
so much machine gun fire i'm so glad i have the three of you nice work oh i feel so much better
okay
it's only a long wait eat shit just get them just go go go get them oh shit don't walk that way
okay i turned them into meat how we doing everyone's good heal up everybody all right
you pansy i might heal you too just to keep you around because i have seven of these come here
this should help got it right did i not even heal you thanks okay keep moving
you pansy he got it that motherfucker actually got it i need a machine gun oh you bastard
turn it off turn it off turn it off i can't turn it off no get over here please no fuck
i can't turn it off i can't turn it off guys i couldn't turn it off okay i went in front of
it i there was no prompt i couldn't turn the fucking thing off stay get over here that's
okay i just i can turn i'm supposed to be able to turn that off right why is this thing bleeding
i think he's in the fucking way i think his body is in the way somehow and it's blocking me the
vent hold on i'm so sad now just run no because they're all gonna die where's this wood vent
was there a vent i mean this fell from here he's vent under the turret i i i'm not gonna
be able to get in there don't follow me don't follow me don't follow me don't follow me don't
follow me don't follow me stay what the fuck was that why was there this is so far away
oh man we've got to do it all again we've got to do the whole thing again
oh it's all right it's all right now we can keep the medic around give me that give me that give me
that right now okay i now have a now we're better three two one action told you we were gonna be
better we're good back this way follow me all the way in here you guys all right okay follow me
this way this way come on come on go go go go go go go go go go go i'm gonna snipe
yes we do come on stop just get in here i don't want to shoot anybody in in in in up
god open the door what's happening behind me he's out running the bullets that's impossible
is that it i think that's it all right all righty who needs to be healed you do medic is good
we're secure i've got everything i need nice fire extinguisher but what in the name of
fucking god you gotta fix that there have been like an out run that in real life
i just like was so shocked at what you said that my teeth hit hard together and it just hurt my
mouth nobody can outrun a fucking minigun i do not believe you that looks secure freddy dredd just
gave 10 000 bits but i can't read what it said somebody copy and pasted thank you freddy dredd
what did it say it didn't say anything no there's no message it was blank well thanks for the
fucking hundred dollars holy shit all right let's get some let's let's let's fix this you i'm going
to give you the wait shotgun now but seriously though that's a lot of money thank you freddy
dredd didn't i have so should i i'm gonna give you the shotgun then no i don't have any
no i need that back shit i don't have any bullets for the shotgun it's you're gonna be useless
i have to pick up another weapon for you because you're not good right now i'm like using the gun
that you would be using normally okay what do you mean like there's just i gotta find another gun
on the ground the guards dropped shotgun rounds well i'm ready let's move if they do they do if
they don't then they don't come on all three of you please come on let's go
stay keep together all right shotgun shells hey i've got something for you now
take the shotgun and take the 12 rounds we need to find you more of those yes sir
yes sir okay how do i turn it off okay oh right grenades grenades grenades grenades
get back here oh you idiot you just get back back up you're gonna die you moron move out of the
back to the medic get over here no relax patience holy fuck like i was in the ground
so give me a little bit of slack all right i've got
all right the guy runs this way everybody be ready excellent work it's not there is it
okay i think we're all gonna be machine gun psychos yeah we're machine gunners yeah i'd
rather it be like that okay huge guy too huge okay i know what we have to do i activate yes
activate the open this door turn on the machine gun oh boy or burn the hallway
i don't know save the game how do i get in there um there was a fire started in the vent could you
use the flamethrower to activate it i i'm gonna everybody stay here all of you this is a this is
mission for me okay don't go anywhere stay right there and keep an eye on each other
all right so the fire starts right here and then i just run just run by everything and then open
the door activate turret go through vent outrun fire open door activate turret go through vent
just light it right now should i just light it up and just watch
i'm just gonna light it up and just watch okay scout you'll just have to imagine the fire
activate the turret last i'm so scared because i don't want to screw this up
when i landed last time it just started i think i'm just gonna run i don't well now i have to
get out of the fucking way that's i just closed the door guys where's my friends where are my
friends how do i get the door friends oh shit okay everybody slow down okay i can't i need to turn
the power on i need an engineer don't activate him and pull him here okay the friends okay oh
my god what's in here well this is this like a safe room okay can i like torch them or something
the fire is coming down the hallway right now it's not as if i doesn't go in this room right
activate the switches what he's not leaving is he okay those open the doors but what does this do
i'm afraid to do anything i'm afraid i can just kill him i'm just gonna kill him i'm gonna kill
him i'm gonna activate switch switch one and i'm gonna kill him or you can't yes i can can i turn
this out okay hold on what's this candy cane grenade what's it what's the candy cane grenade
high explosive grenade i can kill them i'm going for it what else am i gonna do i just
gotta open up one and that will wait there's like poison or something in here look at hold on i
think i can i think i can kill them now these switches are active so three is the door but
all right what if i go this way flip them all i can't even activate them get out of my way
what are you doing those things are so annoying did i just like activate a boss all right
where am i no i gotta go get my friends i can't i'm just gonna go fight those two things by myself
is there a safe point
fuck why
god damn it shit hold still and i'll fix you up no not over here yet wrong way any grenades
don't even know who's on my team
ah what the fuck is going on get in here everybody please i'm deja vu you know why i
type deja vu because i've done this five fucking times give me a machine gun
i mean he doesn't know
how far into the game i am right now 85 percent there's only like 20 minutes left 75 percent 80
percent okay we're safe here we go now i'm going to heal you because you need to be healed and
that's what we do we take care of each other you've been healed you need to be healed again
wow the medic can't just stick a syringe in his own mouth and swallow it okay we're gonna do this
again except this time i'm going ham i'm gonna go for it and i'm gonna kill those two those two
antlions they're gonna die if you don't know what ham means look it up again we're gonna give
everybody the items that they should have i should have the machine gun you can have the pistol
until i find one you i'm actually gonna run all the way back and i'm gonna save the game
that's what's gonna happen okay we're gonna save the game now
i'm not going this way i'm going back wait we have to go in the elevator
i don't know if we can go back up we can't you can't save it just use the stairs i would
okay let's go fix him
good bounced off his head okay this is important don't let him do this he got it
no he didn't it's not scripted it wasn't on last time use a grenade i don't think i can do it from
here i have to cook it for like four and a half seconds one two three one two three oh fuck
that's not gonna happen that's not gonna happen that's not gonna happen that's not gonna happen
you guys stay stay get over here i have to do this again and i gotta go for it i want all of
you over here please all of you get over here get the fuck over here stay all of you don't move
yes none of you i am ready to what do i have for heals why have you not healed me
what do i have for help why have you not healed me heal me all right i don't have i don't have full
health yes sir i'm too afraid just go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go we're good okay
i said stay right good i did right here we go i did it again
again good hey activate the switches i can't high explosive powered grenades we're going to
go get them and i'm going to destroy them okay okay get all those this is good to go
give me my fire extinguisher i'm so close to a save point it's right here it's literally right
here this is it as many of these as i can carry what about the turret um what about the turret
what do you mean if i open this door i have to open three i can't wait i can't even do this
i i have to open one but the switches can't be activated because i need an engineer
engineer and i can't save the game because there's no power and i can't turn the power
on because i can't do this so i have to actually go do all this shit over here can you bring the
tech through the vents i don't think they go in the vents with you all right this is really
important i don't want to fuck this up everything is this is explosives everywhere i'm already
fucking it up oh fire here's fire they fucking hate it okay one of these doors explodes
this one explodes hey who's fuck i heard a gun oh what was that what's that what's that making
that do i do are we good are we good are we good did i do it did i turn it on did i do it i just
released them what are you talking about one i didn't what are you talking about i didn't release
them this i still do whatever's going on inside that room something going on in here now so what
the fuck is going on in here i hope they're still waiting for me there's a vent over here why what's
event for i think it's just a bait just a bait really well there's another thing to power on
um i have a question didn't the game tell me to do this in a certain order or it would be bad
right it said do this and it said don't turn this on or pressure tank
i did it all right get me out of this room okay can i all right here we go one right
one is it one it's one one is gonna is gonna kill them good three opens the door he's hiding
in the corner are you really hiding in the corner how am i on fire huh what was it somebody in here
okay this is good this is good so far so far so good i have to get that engineer in here or i
soft lock the game remember this chat if the engineer does not get in here it's over open
three fire extinguisher i still have some this shit don't turn on again right this is two how do i
turn off the turret they're gonna come down the hall and get fucking obliterated hey look at me
there it is guys hey guys hey you're all still here ain't that good well i have a story for you
follow me i hope you guys have some conversations while i was gone i'll find a way around what i
already did engineer but wait no are they turning what does that mean that usually means they're
infected right you puked on the guy's body like let's at least fucking take a step to the left
jesus what door is not open that was one two three four four is locked okay but for the meantime
i ain't doing this yet we're gonna turn this on so i can save the game please an engineer right here
i know you're capable go for it all right let there be light please
thank god thank goodness how are y'all doing on health and ammo and everything good
everyone's still in good spirits
except for you well actually you were the last to puke that's true you were the last one to puke
here we go open for you're not on a job we're just trying to fucking survive man
we're just trying to live right now this is new content he was dumb i think he ran into the
stay where is he where'd he go get over here you know just all of you stay i'll figure it out
i'll figure this out all right he died trying to press the button button can't be pressed
are we gonna are we doing this shit again how can the button not be pressed
i'm sick of this shit fuck off it's safe you gotta heal okay they should help these things
are huge blast radius by the way enormous no we're not we're fine i don't like how he's
not following he's just staying here follow stop staying back i'm about to i'm about to
shoot him like because this is bad i don't want this to happen come on let's go all of you follow
me all right you too that means you we're gonna die here i need an engineer another way to get
soft-locked would be right here we're gonna die here everybody all right it's just a little
startling i know everyone's good here we go we lot i knew it i knew it i knew he was there was
something going on with him he was acting really strange and now he's gone and he took with him
like a thousand rounds of ammo i am not gonna mess around i have high explosive grenades i'm
gonna throw it into this guy's head one two three please die please die please die medics okay
you can fix this one okay you can uh-oh oh shit that lets a fire out all right all right all right
all right you guys are smart you guys coming it's just you and me let's do it okay i don't have a
tester i have no way to tell if you're really not it's not do i have to trap something in here and
pull the lever save point wait i need an engineer i'm so glad you're still here all right i'm so
happy that you're still here look at how useful you've been you have been so useful dixon didn't
remember your name you're in bad shape soldier what happened whitley he tried to gun me down
but he didn't quite finish the job very dramatic i'm pretty messed up get me a wanks
we've got a new medic i do have a weapon for you it's a shotgun uh somebody stole
okay my other weapon so i can't really do anything about it hold still and i'll fix you up
uh please can you check the results of our second test run to see if they are
in line with your specs thing molecule degre degradation 100 altered strain degradation
98 effective energy waste 1.2 residual matter 0.4 these are pc specs if these are not what you are
expecting please update your design and we will run another test in the main armory
all right i'm getting like blinky i gotta like i feel like i haven't i haven't blanked my eyes in
like an hour and 20 minutes what was that oh rifle i don't even have the rifle anymore do i
no it was taken from me and it was just just replaced right now that's swell okay where's
the safe point i hear it i hear it and we got what is who is who has the shotgun all right
did you just shoot him and you just shot him twice you fucking idiot what an idiot
what an imbecile you are so awesome please don't turn you just do so good opening doors
what are you last time somebody did this all right let's go save points in here along with
a bunch of good fire ammo pistol ammo and what is that shotgun ammo what do you have you have a
shotgun you and i can speak you need heels too okay done anything else down here to look at
there is i'm not gonna press that button it opens up the fire door one two area looks secure
don't put down no you saw their team fuck all right let's go round two now this time i'm just
whipping grenades that's just what i'm gonna do i'm gonna do just grenades only and hopefully you
guys can handle whatever else happens good like for instance okay here we go watch it watch it
watch it somebody take i'll do it fire and fire because technically it's fire and fire all right
how you doing you could use a heel but you'd be fine you'd be all right wait what happened
we good but hold on is this is this frying out on us what was the last thing you saw
when you threw a grenade oh well take a look that was you you missed something actually pretty funny
that's too bad that is too bad um they were fighting over here the the soldiers were fighting
the weird mutant thing in here and it was great it was really funny there was a whole shit show
over here are we going down again quick everyone left reload it no i'm not gonna reload it just do
it again oh i see what you're saying uh yeah hey thanks for the sympathy laughs appreciate it
okay um i had there is a thing over here i don't know what this is that us okay i was
supposed to shoot that guy and it was my guy okay well this i can't just see anything okay
we're gonna just keep going this way holy fuck come on get up get up get up
we're good hey get up i just freaked the fuck out but we all have full health
i'm supposed to be doing the grenade strategy right now what am i thinking
holy fuck he just got lit up can you heal him he's not doing so well
get him heal look at his health come on man
engineer right we have an engineer be ready for whatever's behind this door
what if he wasn't here if you weren't here what happens do you just lose
i need i can i'm gonna use a flare for the i don't have any oh i wonder if that's an alien
no it couldn't be no way not the guy standing let's go find out
what a surprise you mean to tell me the guy with no emotions standing
what are you doing no i need you alive i need you alive i need you alive i need you alive
oh no oh how do we get that off of you how do we get it off of you how do we get that off of you
you okay we need to find a door for you to open before you turn okay i need you to i need a door
for you to open something for you to press a button on because you're going to become a monster
kill him now no not yet he needs to open a door what oh my god oh my god oh my god i'm panicking
he's got us trapped he's got us trapped he's got us trapped he's got us trapped he's got us trapped
he's got us trapped don't walk over there i'm missing no what are you doing he's still alive
get him get him get him get him get him all right fine sniper sniper oh shit
watch out okay well everything's fine don't shoot he's aiming at me he's got plot armor
no he doesn't plot armor that's so fucking stupid there's so many i hear so many grunts
wait i think there's a machine gun over here there's a safe point though um oh for where is
this that i hear it's behind this door okay yes we do but they're not here yet they're behind the
door are you all right okay yes sir you don't look all right i know you just took a high explosive
grenade in the face but i need you down here down the stairs please there we go we just needed a
little nudge and you're all doing fine this is the door we have to open it's been saved
i need to get some heavy power out here i'm ready to throw a grenade right why is the door closed
behind me where are my friends they locked me in uh what what do you mean time's up
you're not even in here with me you're not even in the room and apparently oh i don't have any
healing oh fuck i got his attention it's that that's the thing that i need to deal with how do i aim
i forget how to aim this is working back back um finish it with fire i can't even get over here
we're right here do the winch what winch where's there a winch though by the way give me all your
stuff if you're not gonna help me if you're not gonna help me then give me all the shit that you
have what do you have actually you know what i take that back yes here you're gonna have that
actually because you're gonna need it eventually and i have some tons of ammo all right so let's
go i'm gonna go here we go in here i'm gonna throw grenade the winch but how do i get i know
i know i can do the winch you're in here with me now you're in here with me but why are you i might
this guy's dead you ain't gonna last stay here winch power all right what if i tell you go to the
winch all right this is this is you this is his grand ending this is where his arc ends
dixon you've been a fucking loyal companion i need you to go press the winch stand back
okay i need you to what why no what the fuck he didn't even do anything
he didn't even help me shock them all just keep doing it that was so stupid i can't believe that
just happened all right let's go electrocution fix the box he's in here all right i'm not gonna
let that happen again all right he's he's stunned he's stunned no i don't need you to turn the power
on wait what is that behind him regroup he's gonna turn he's gonna turn he's about to turn
see he's turning i told you i told you you all thought i was insane i'm telling you
oh for the love of god we should have to face three times all right so electrocution stuns him
you guys just stay up here i'm not having that scenario happen again both of you stay
i don't want anyone coming with me do not come with me if anyone's in the room with me to get
shot in the head immediately so i can okay i have now i can just sit here for a second so
so i can electrocute you but it electrocutes me i can burn you so i can i don't i have no idea
i got his attention it's not working anymore it's not working anymore why is it not working anymore
okay because i can't when he's i can't run behind him there's nothing there dude it's like should i
just run around there's not a whole lot of places to run so stun them throw a grenade run away
okay all right stun them electrocute grenade all right stun grenade run and then do it again
let me see what hold on can i i just want to take a look can i go behind him
i don't think i can get behind him there's a button what the fuck was that all right this is
what i'm gonna do i'm gonna electrocute grenade and run away ready one two three
three that's gonna kill me stun grenade run or but i just the grenade blew up like instantly
kill dixon now no he's alive he's okay all right so stun grenade run stun grenade run now what
oh i did that that was me i did that i'm sorry you thought
oh let's go no it's i didn't reverse oh run i fucking god okay okay okay okay okay
dick kill dixon bring medic so kill dixon okay fine no stop don't heal him kill him
okay you and me are gonna do some stuff here i didn't need to hold on kill me i did that i
wasted so much ammo i shot him like seven times with the most expensive rifle in the game here's
what we're gonna do just burn him you just all right come over here i don't want to burn
both of you so don't shoot him till he's ready he's not ready yet all right shoot him okay
you and me are going okay follow me let's go you and me we're going in there you're getting in
there i'm saving the game your job is to just stand in the back and heal me that's all you're
gonna be doing get over here with me i want to make sure you like get into the door get over here
okay are we standing you're right next to me right get closer get like in the fucking door
get in the door okay go just like cut him in half please be in the are you in here you're in here
right just come here stay right there stay right there don't move stay right here are you acknowledging
that you're gonna stay stay stay right here thank god what the fuck i got stuck heal me heal me can
you heal me you can even look through the door like glitch through the door come here then heal
me open the door i can't the door does not open i'm in so much fucking trouble get in the fucking
room please stun grenades i don't i don't have stun grenades where are you seeing stun grenade
i have x super like nuclear bomb and then he's not even with me better i this lip right here
that lip right there the developers need to get in there and they need to fix that because i got
stuck on it i'm stuck right now you see what i'm talking about look at this shit look at this lip
why is there a lip here why would where would there be a lip why would there be a lip
why is there a lip what's the lip for lips it's for nothing there's no let's look for no reason
hitting the button behind him i can't go over there wait a minute hold on wait a second wait a
second wait can i get rid of the boxes hold on a second hold on a second wait wait wait nobody
nobody doing it can i get rid of the boxes in front of them there's a box get over here make
sure you're standing right next to me heal me maybe you can go behind it when he falls down
i don't there's no way to get in there it's all blocked off and he didn't get in again
all right this is a fuck this is just a fuck face run no i can't get back there
what about the truck no no and no one maybe i can let's see what happens if i do this
no you get electrocuted you just get electrocuted stand in the corner what does the wench do when
you activate that i can drop the electricity on him that stuns him but it also electrifies the
ground and you're fighting you're fighting in like the inside of a blender that's the amount of space
that there is so throw all grenades then stun and shoot his neck like with a regular gun
shoot belly during stun shoot neck get in come on turn this way you beautiful beautiful
beautiful bastards get over here all right stay right there okay i think this is the one i mean
it's hurting i don't think i don't think bullets do anything all right here we go i'm gonna stun
run back heal me hold still and i'll fix you up thank you oh hey hi this should help thanks
you you stay i don't want you i want you over here follow me yes sir i want you right here in
the back where nobody can hurt you stay there this is this is the dumbest boss fight
throw more grenades throw him in the corner throw the grenades in the corner
oh get in get oh why would you fight a guy that's 25 feet tall in a space this big
because you have to why do i have to fight him here why you get in there i had it this time
you need to spam that keep spamming it spam the fuck out of that i want to see what that says
i that's all that's the only thing i want to have in the chat hit the middle part of
his body to kill him i recommend too fast i recommend you too fast i recommend you throw
grenade you need to it's going too fast i can't do it go okay you need to hit the middle part
of his body i recommend throwing a grenade to his right all right all right sub only sub only sub
only sub only something sub only sub only put do sub only sub only sub only and then i could read
from there after you're out of grenades you need to hit the middle part of his body to kill him
i recommend throwing grenades over the rightmost box and after you're out of grenades
attempt to use the stun to finish him off with your ammo i beat this game a couple years ago
okay this box but i tried that last time and i fucking ruined everything
so over the over here it doesn't work man over the rightmost but i can't
i can't throw him any higher go into first person that wasn't part of the instructions
that wasn't part of the instructions oh my god this is fucking ridiculous all right get over here
if i can get you in the room it'd be great i'm so sick of seeing this guy he didn't even come
close okay first person my fucking god just do it kill this is so fucked up this is so fucked up
this boss stupid it is dumb it's fucked up this is fucked up all right it's just it's messed up
it's stupid it's just dumb all right we've all we all agree good okay cool let's keep let's
continue our quest this is just stupid okay here we go don't fucking move just throw them all
okay i'm not missing right how could you miss he's fucking the whole he's the whole corner
this dude's the entire corner and now you're saying don't use the flamethrower just shoot him
like in the stomach stun and shoot him ah how many bullets does it take to kill this motherfucker
let's be very clear about something here that was seven high explosive grenades four regular
grenades and like five clips into his chest final shot needs to be fire wasn't part of
the instructions i didn't miss all the grenades turn on auto aim lower difficulty so you can see
his hp just look it up on you i don't know what this guy's called the final boss of the thing
he's almost in here oh thank god get in this time i'm not going to fuck this up stay there
don't move stay there okay here we go okay don't move you're not i cannot fuck this up
get a little closer holy shit i can't believe it i'm gonna die heal me hold still and i'll fix
you up it went through the stay here it's working i feel like i'm not i need to be a little further
back where'd it go is that even hitting him i'm gonna bounce it off this wall i don't know but
i'm just gonna say it is i can't move the he hit but the ones small what in the neck in that who's
neck aim for the neck thing this thing has like five necks the whole thing is a neck
okay okay okay okay time to go back i'm aiming too low what the fuck this game sucks
i didn't say kim did the neck i have to go i have to go i have to go he's a snake tongue that has two
people between the two arms like okay so this is the snake tongue you want me to shoot in here
into the middle of the snake's tongue right under the no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no can you imagine actually playing this game when it came out and try and being
like this is normal this is what you do this is just normal it's too scary
flamethrower
heal me please it's just a scratch stay back here don't go through the wall i might have to take his
shotgun hold still and i'll fix you up because just keep doing whatever you're doing there's
no there's no hitbox it's not even hitting them anymore don't go over there go over here watch
the youtube link imagine having to watch a youtube link to fucking fight a boss me too
hold still and i'll fix you up shoot higher what's the name what's this what's this thing
what's this thing called what's the name of this boss i don't care spoil the whole game
fuck it i don't give shit the hitbox is at the very top where it branches are you guys
fucking with me the thing boss two listen this is just fucking bonkers to me not the thing bird
two no not angry birds the movie too the thing boss two let's take a look the thing boss fight
how to beat the boss two hold on to three flame grenades i don't have those uh the thing second
boss is impossible i used to really like this game but the boss battles are simple hold on
i used to really like this game but the boss battles are simply frustrating to behold the second is
particularly annoying as you have to go into the first person mode to hit the boss properly
but unfortunately you're in a cramped space and get stuck on junk and get killed also when trying
to run back behind the crates in front of the door there appears to be a step that blake can't
walk over so um help me please beat this stupid game so i can be done with it and sell it okay
what do you mean sell it when was this posted 2001 okay if it's the one i'm thinking of with the big
ceiling tall thing and there are some tentacles that come out of the wall to your right it was
pretty easy wrong boss it's the one after that it's the one in the compound that you wake up
and after being captured behind the garage door in the big hanger that you enter after going
through the big tunnel i just enabled cheats to get through it but you gotta edit the registry
and start from scratch screw that okay let's continue hmm i don't think i've gotten to that
one yet i'm near the tail end of getting out of that facility but i ran my guy into an area to
explore and the floor suddenly caught on fire killing me and royally pissing me off because
there were no safe points near that area and i had already been trying to get through it hundreds of
times so i haven't played it since okay oh yeah you're much farther back than me oh yes i remember
that boss i believe it's the one with the what one trick for that one is that just inside the
door you can make shots between the crates with the incendiary grenade launcher in the back of
the boss and kill him remember to let each grenade burn out before firing the next one my brother
killed him with four grenades somebody's give 20 community subs this doesn't help me at all he's
dead did you what hey we just eat your shit watch out save save again okay you can follow me now
what was the point of this i don't know but thankfully i read yeah i've read that guide
look at my hair all we had to do was read i know i he had like two hp left you could just burn him
and run i thought you had to like cut his arm off or i don't know all right let's go game is saved
please don't turn on me now i need you that's it that's in here here we go that was the end
of the game that's the final end of the game so what now was that that was the thing christ
there's a bomb the place is gonna blow we oh we should probably run it's probably 30 seconds to
get out of here i only get 30 seconds that does not seem like a lot of time he didn't make it
he didn't make you so close you were so close was that npc what the fuck was that guy doing
am i these my friends are these people like do i know these people is i don't know if this is
supposed i'm supposed to be doing this no no way i need a save point or something nobody has fired
at me am i doing something wrong how do i get this door open there's a safe point in here open
this fucking door right now i actually can't die here because i'll have to do the whole thing over
again give me my flashlight just just keep the door open put a door stop on i don't know do
something for for excavation purposes we have a stock of c4 charges in the armory below
please obtain a pass from your superior prior to checking out any explosives
any person found carrying explosive without the correct paperwork will be detained
and c4 below those things don't open right it better not holding area access
i gotta turn the power on here power this could be like a power box or something here
those things i hope they don't get out i thought we were gonna get to see an epilogue is this the
epilogue it might be all right we'll see if this is the epilogue i wish i had a couple of people
with me all right watch out for that baby fire what was that jesus christ they weren't here
i walked in this room and there was nobody here they spawned they spawned in front of me
that's exactly what happened i refuse to believe anything else health only one you're gonna put
one health pack in here one there's usually like seven there's seven arrayed in here every single
time that's not gonna work why did i do that it was contained it was contained what was i doing
burn him how do i get into the save point oh no no no no no no no no no no no why was i
to put the fuck the sniper rifle is the worst item in the game it's the worst item in every game
there's no reason to ever put it on why ever equip the sniper rifle ever it's so it's so bad
you're the worst item in the game all right what am i doing i need to get in here how do i get in
this fucking door how do i open up this save point let me in there oh my god thank goodness
i went back all right how do i get in here guys what do you think i can't press this button i can't
do anything it's right this doesn't do anything i already tried it you walk past the switch box
what where is there a switch box i don't see a switch box no this is not i can't open this door
there is not a switch box anywhere to be found i mean there's a computer over here
it doesn't do anything it's a you tried to push it it's no i'm gonna activate a power source
i got that health pack so that's good all right let's keep going why does this keep getting
turned off you're fucking messing everything up okay holding area what wait wait wait wait
yeah it does what wait no that box can't be turned on either guys we're so close to the end
it's do you really want to like bait me into like walking through a door i already looked at five
times i need an engineer i lost i can't believe i lost my medic friend
holy fuck i forgot this is we were going forward you fucking dumb asses
i think i have to go in here it's another bait what who let me give me a weapon is it a friend
no i need a friend it's like a spy crabbing you from that bogus research team whitley sent in
yeah oh my god your ass says thanks for being saved sorry thanks for the rescue those troopers
are everywhere you the reason they're here maybe but they're taking that cargo awfully seriously
who's the cargo for i don't know but it sure ain't the red cross this is an engineer behind this that
cargo's got to be destroyed this is melted area looks secure are you an engineer tell me you are
are you are you an engineer let me give you something here take a machine gun good okay
save terminal engineer yes sir that's a safe term imagine if he had died in here and i didn't
get in here fast enough that would have been a fucking nightmare fix it all okay holy shit
thank god all right what are you fixing fix that fix everything all right let's go
don't shoot me in the back all right who was it it's phylactery lich 10,000 bits hundred
dollars from phylactery coming in with another gigantic money drop huge fucking bits phylactery
lich yeah am i not saying it right i wish there was health in here someone gave 50 gift subs
earlier that's right who gave all those gift subs somebody give a shitload what was it who gave 50
gifted subs two people well whoever you were thank you i was probably locked into something
on here and i didn't even notice it was at martin martin had a meme thank you for the subs thank
you so much what did the message say for uh phylactery no he's looking up the guide okay
here take some of this okay oh stay with me uh actually no give me some of that back actually
give me the whole thing back you can have four what did it say hey jerry's been a pretty good
stream just want to let you know literally every gun you've used he uses magazines not clips
right but it's magazines three syllables clips is one it's easier to say like i can get it out
faster but thank you for the hundred bucks that's a lot of money just say no it's a clip all right
you have everything you need we still have no healing all right that's not good i don't like
that let's head back save the game again this way we're good there's another thing for you
to open back in the beginning i'm so glad i'm the hell are you thinking wait trying to turn on the
he's trying to i know what he's trying to do he didn't get it though can i turn this on power
this place is there a box is there no box in here how could there not be a box i have an engineer
now yeah trying to scare me another somebody bala koala gave 55 dollars you missed potato
chief's gift subs too thanks to both of you thank you for the 50 50 dollars that's a this has been
a a money scream tonight apparently holy shit guys uh thank you and then they said you dingus
but i didn't read that part because i want people to think i'm strong all right this health packs
over here don't turn i really hope you don't turn what do i have for health right now i don't know
i'm not gonna take it because i don't know it's obviously not low enough to be that much of a big
deal engineer i need an engineer okay shitty ps2 game stream this is on windows this is a pc game
got him all right um jacoby jacoby just gave a hundred community subs
holy shit a fucking hundred community subs that's that's that's a that was a lot of money that you
just put down right now why do i have so many rich fans somebody just said i don't i don't know
the thing is my favorite movie it's one of my top like 50 favorite movies of all time
it's a long list um jacoby that's a ton of money that's you you just spent five hundred dollars
right i've done that it's 4.99 uh dodge what do i dodge what well congratulations to the
hundred of you that just got a community sub he he hates the thing what dodged i dodged a sub
oh right you i get it okay right i'm stupid i'm sitting there going what did i die like dodged
a question i thought you're talking about the guy that said this is a shitty ps2 game i'm like oh
yeah it's pc like dodged i'm stupid uh anyways thanks so much for the what are you doing what
are you doing what are you guys doing that's 50 now from martin had a meme martin had a meme had
like 20 or 40 earlier you guys are going nuts 50 more community subs from martin had a meme oh one
dodged again uh that's 150 subs just came in right now that's fucking crazy
and more earlier too i thought that i thought that was it that guy i was like did he why did he do
that that's ridiculous thanks to both of you seriously why do we have scary music hey austin
atlantis five community subs shoot him save the game it's okay i can fix this and save the game
i need an engineer please open that how many subs that was like 200 over the last fucking 45
minutes jesus all right we're in a good spot i need a health box something is in here okay
something in the cell but why this so why are you all in here all right i'm gonna open this
this might be stupid but let's do it he's got a key card just reset reset
what the fuck are you doing 50 more community subs that was from ab joe ab joe just gave 50
community subs and did i just miss a hundred dollars no i didn't if i like relish right
yeah no the the stream labs notifications are um late by about probably five straight minutes
uh thank you ab joe for the 50 community subs wait he gave two he gave another hundred dollars
what what is happening right now why is this all of a sudden like the snap the money stream
what do you say haunted moon 20 community subs oh my god okay haunted moon thanks for 20
thanks for another hundred dollars but you're gonna brv and tell kim kim kim we got four hundred
dollars we're going to walmart what's it what'd you say okay hold on gnarly gave five
somebody get 50 dollars what's going on i can't even read these because but i this thing this
stream lab takes over the whole thing and i can't see it uh who just gave 50 who gave 5 000 bits
right now oh no this here we go i started i said it and now all of a sudden uh kogelin gave five
subs 50 dollars from somebody i don't even know who the hell it was now we're going to target
frogman 10 community subs who gave the 5 000 fucking dollars all right
5 000 bits not 5 000 dollars potato chief 20 community subs you gotta be kidding me
20 more from potato chief bala koala five it just doesn't stop we're going to vegas
yeah i'm going trader joe's yeah i'm going to trader joe's i'm going to buy every frozen dinner
they have they last like 12 months i'm going to be getting the kale at whole foods today
no thank you guys seriously all of you i couldn't really keep up with all of you
but that's insane that is actually insane um another five from nocturnal thank you for
the five community subs and then another five from uh anti anti anti anti po anti potion double
a 20 community subs what is going on this is like this is like we haven't seen something like this
in a long time this is fucking crazy double a gave 20 community subs right now this is like four
five hundred subs right now double a another 20 ham museum 20 is this is this real this is what's
going on ham museum 20 community subs holy shit guys another five from anti potion it's a full
moon i forgot what the fuck are you guys doing that's on another a hundred a hundred community
subs from what are you guys doing this is fucking the most money i think i've had in subs in one
are you doing it again holy shit on uh austin austin atlantis gave 10 community subs phylactery
fucking a hundred more subs i'm gonna short circuit in a second more coming in and now they
can be that twitch cannot even keep up with these holy shit another five anti potions been on just
like a anti potion that's a macro that's doing five haunted moon another 10 all right all right
okay all right this is another five i'm telling the anti potion is just like pressing the button
don't let the glaze over the fact that phylactery just gave another hundred community subs empowers
what the fuck is happening all right i gotta i i gotta like do something i can do something with
my hands i don't know what to do the five more just got another hundred just came in from jacoby
you guys all right we could let's relax a little bit this is fucking then this is nuts and this is
another one from yes is online five community subs hundreds from how many subs do i have right
now i can't even see i don't even know somebody wrote in quotes stop giving me money uh that more
42 mouse just gave five community subs do you this is do you guys understand how fast these
credits are going to go by tonight oh my fucking god tingy 20 community subs austin atlantis just
gave a hundred community subs that's this is like are we are we going up to like a thousand
community subs right now oh my fucking god you could have a hot that's another 100 community
subs i don't even know what to say this is unbelievable uh 42 miles five more i i need to see
how many are are here mj martin 10 well well y'all just paid for the halloween stream like right now
holy shit uh omnium gather them another 10 community subs oh am i i'm dead what did how
did i die when did i died when did i die how long have i been dead for oh i've already opened the
thing in dr shrug five community subs which one am i on 415 five from 42 mouse five from dr shrug
thank you both of you guys thank you all of you it's just this just this is just not stopping
another five from dr stein i have to see what's going on here i need to see how many subs have
just come in because this is fucking bonkers this is insanity i'm gonna i got an alt tab hold on
hold on a second splarg just gave five community subs that's a that's a thousand subs it's more
than a it's more than a thousand subs what are you guys doing what the fuck is going on
phylactery all right another hundred community subs oh my fucking god dodge dodge dodge dodge
splarg five subs phylactery a hundred this is like i think just in the last 30 minutes there's
been like seven to eight hundred subs more than that probably steaky k l thanks to the five subs
holy shit this is i had to like mute so i could sit here for a second because they're just rolling
in five more community subs from eager oatmeal there are more there are more dr stein another
five twitch cannot even keep counting them i'm looking at my dashboard right now and it cannot
count them it's stuck it's it's going up every like eight minutes nocturnal thank you for the
five cheeseburger cat thank you for the five wow how did this even start i don't even know how this
started what the fuck okay uh necromancy mage thanks with five subs gunther gunther riddle
thanks with five subs this is just this is i'm broken i've i'm just like stuck i cannot believe
that almost more than a thousand subs have just come in right now frogman five more flug boy five
more everyone is going to have a sub by the end of the stream it's i mean that's it's already been
like 25 of everybody watching right now was just giving us up
chilled sanity 20 more subs flug boy five more subs i've been doing this for a long time
i've been streaming on twitch chilled sanity seriously 20 subs is a lot thank you uh sage
the ghost for the five subs thank you thank you speg for the five subs i've been doing this for
a long time and we've seen stuff like this before but i think this has been the most ridiculous
it's ever been in four to five years on twitch this has been just un un i can't even i can't
even tell you lucas blue five subs patrick johnson five subs yeah i i'm floored i i don't even know
what to say thank you patrick johnson for the five fizenberg for the five oh was it fizen or flizen
flizenberg live laugh love lucifer gave five subs dab for each sub i can't dab
that's like 1200 times t t t macapee 10 subs live laugh lucifer five subs okay i'm five subs from
bro to bro delicious captain cockles five subs oh my fucking god
holy shit i thank you thank you all of you
ball ball boy thanks for the five community subs just much for you ball boy
red blue thanks for the five subs is he dead germa sucks thanks for the five subs
zeke thanks for the zeke thanks for the five subs holy fucking i'm gonna get like a call from
twitch they're gonna be like uh excuse me jara turbo uh what happened on the night of uh i don't
even know what date is october 21st 2019 were those real i'm gonna be like i don't know yeah
yeah all of them thank you beaker for the five subs mr kool-aid five subs i gotta kill this thing
don't have the engineer die
69 subs from phylactery 69 of them mr kool-aid another five uh i need to heal
69 more subs holy what in the name of god is happening right now it's our team thanks for the
five subs i don't know what to say guys i'm so fucking shocked and i can't believe that
people would give me this much money i don't even know what to say this is a this is insane
i can't even count them no don't use that trotter deady dude it's just it won't stop
more subs than plebs i know i i have we talk about this sometimes but seriously
um you got this stream sees a lot of fucking money it does and i really really just hope
like i've tried to tell you before that some of the stuff i hope you guys really fucking think
it's a fun stream and i hope that i can spend that money in places that make it more fun
because there's a lot just look at what happened right now you know what i mean like there's a
lot of fucking money and i it that i don't want that to be taken advantage of and i don't want
to take granted take anything for granted any of this stuff people are just dumping in five five
five ten i don't want you to think oh he's like he's just glazing over it no i'm not
surgery but five chart shardipus 10 you guys are fucking awesome thank you so much
seriously i seriously like i don't even know what to say more are coming in than i could possibly do
i hope i spend your money wisely i hope i do sincerely thank you everybody just just retire
right here more dodges are how we getting here i just got a key holy shit all right don't don't
go in here why do i need two flashlights more of them are coming in i just hold on a minute
take this oh this is the c4 this is the c4 guys c4 c4 c4 c4 how do i turn off the
hold on heal plant the c4 on cargo planes is somebody in the room what do you have for health
i gotta heal you no i don't i don't even care the door just closed on me i need that actually can
i give you a flashlight too shit all right where were those cargo planes anybody where the cargo
planes were i'm gonna save this one down here it's a save all right let's go this way don't
forget to sub with twitch prime oh i don't think very many people tonight are forgetting
where were the cargo planes up i thought these things just talked oh shit good thing i walked
over here what else we got more guns door controls oh my fucking god that's another 20 subs
what a door what i just pick up i would do a door control what door is this so it should be open
then right that was t mccabe t mccabe t mccabe t mac t mccabe thank you all right let's go
wait i want to give you uh more ammo yeah take some you could use it i think i have to go back up
more bits so huge meg megabits what do you mean megabits it's i can't even see it on my on my
dashboard what just happened biggest bits ever no biggest bits ever hold on well i i need to move
this what the fuck wait no it was really 70 where 72 what fuck okay phylactery just gave
25 000 bits 25 000 bits it's like broken the one before that too you what you gave that's
almost a thousand dollars 750 fucking dollars of worth of bits oh my fucking god what in the name
of god is happening that was all no no that was that wasn't just phylactery it was like three
fucking people it was phylactery gave 250 and then ishanji gave 250 they say nightbot auto modded my
last donation is spam oh my fucking god 72 000 fucking look at that oh my i don't even what the
fuck this is gonna be this has to be the most amount of fucking money i've ever had on stream
ever what did the last one say shit like this don't happen i thank you everybody this is a
ridiculous amount of money kim if you open up the germa mustard bit tracking website take a look at
this oh it is a sight to behold anyways it was nightbot auto modded my last one yeah ishanji
gave 20 30 313 dollars worth of bits like 30 000 1300 the whole the website is crashing they say
germ millionaire tonight all right germa we get it you can stop donating money to yourself okay
all right this is like this is it's like fucking like six thousand dollars over the course of this
tonight all right this is you know i'm gonna play the thing it's the game that it's an old one
it's an old game oh people are like coming to my room hold on okay
okay i just have to talk kim just had to tell me something very important she's like
that's nothing to do with the bits uh i gotta move a desk like right now i have to go move a desk
she's like hey can i can i i just gotta i'm like what what what is it she's like i just hold on
i was like what do you what did you talk about she's like hey uh you gotta move a desk kim we're
gonna be getting a new desk two of them but seriously though file actor just gave another
250 fucking dollars i have got to move a desk right now because it's apparently needs to be
moved now um i'll be right back i need to process this information to what's happening tonight
thank you everybody for this insane thousands and thousands and thousands of dollars worth of
contributions to the stream i hope i spend it wisely on two desks i'll be right back i'm gonna
grab some water too we're gonna finish this game much love to all of you anybody that's been here
i'll be right back all right move a desk almost shit my pants dude all right i am ready oh holy
shit right when i come back thank you t maccabee buy new pants i could just shit my pants now
i can just buy new pants and then buy a new chair then buy a new floor
holy fuck that that was that was next level seriously file actor is still coming in with
with another another 10 000 bits the almighty dollar i gotta like i gotta like i gotta get like
i gotta move my hair i gotta thank you holy fuck new top yeah i can't even look over there that's
insane amount of money time for some free samples from trader joe's that's right we're gonna go in
there and go we're gonna go around the mall and get like the free samples from all the food court
places thank you all again seriously i'm 100 just i i'm speechless i have no idea even what to say
thanks for the fucking crazy amount of money you guys are awesome now i'm gonna try to beat this
video game someone link the germa mustard website it's you're gonna it's gonna be crashed all right
where do i need to go i gotta go plant the c4 on the hangars which is upstairs right that was a
wild ride which way do i go from here here we go up i still got my engineer where'd he go
where's my friend is he dead i think i need him don't i what are you doing hurry up why are you
stuck in the door this gap you actually just did that i need this guy so i'm gonna heal him
but what you're hiding behind the door okay let's keep going anything else in here that i can grab
just checking to see if i could break it i need to turn off this alarm before it drives me nuts
another save point and some fire good ban all subs i i don't think i'm gonna ban all subs
that would be too many of you you would hope he panned at least 40 of you all right this way
i i i can't relate so i just got like seven thousand dollars right now i'm sorry
maybe i'll give some to you man he oh man yo yeah man he hates streaming he just says that
i when this stream is over i'm gonna look at like the twitch like analytics page
i'm just gonna be like behind us quick run ads no i'm not gonna run ads michael rain just gave
another hundred fucking dollars heard we were giving you a lot of money and been waiting for
a good reason to give you some since i got a good job good to hear i name all my magic
decks after your memes thank you play ads wait till i'm let me just let me beat the game let me
just get to the end of the game and uh no i don't need to run ads play some ads at let me beat the
game uh let me like get to the end we're so close we're probably like 20 minutes away from the end
of the game wait let him fight let him fight let him fight let him fight smart he closed the door
wait just what the kill it kill it kill it kill it he just ads or i'm gonna subscribe all right
just everybody relax oh shit no no no no no shoot him shoot the shoot it he just hit his head on
the wall i hope i don't need you for anything i do need you oh my god i need to throw grenades
that's the only way this shit's happening right now ads are all cheer
whoa god damn it die will you die holy shit you little bastard i'm almost dead do i mean
i don't have any heals do i what was that he was underneath me oh that sucks okay 423 it's this one
here he was literally standing underneath me all right you are infected right now but i need you
i need you so i'm gonna deal with it because i need you to just exist okay let's go buy health
i can't purchase there's no health purchasing okay go through here then up here wait am i going i'm
going backwards shit give ads give ads i physically can't even run them i can't run ads i i can't be
run i have one health pack right no at this point i don't have any i just can't die up here
there's so many ridiculous enemies up here i wonder how the hell am i going to do this
i think i'm just gonna run i think it's time to run we're at this stage of the game where
i can't hit this like okay i'm go i'm going to run by everything it's not worth fighting
it's time just to go it's time to go go go go go go go what the fuck fight them fight them fight
them fight them fight them fight them in the elevator fight them in the elevator fight them
in the elevator bye oh my god see you run can i go in here nope i got lit up by five different
angles how are you supposed to do this how are you supposed to reliably get through that
uh i don't know this like sorry i can only afford 50 bucks this time please don't hit me like any
anymore thank you multi trip for the 55 dollars 5500 bits holy thank you what am i going to do
about this i don't think running works it kind of does but then you have to fight everything um i'm
gonna try it again this time i'm gonna go i don't know what to do slow down
i mean i i just wish i had some health because here comes that big fight with the
you can just let them kill each other just let them fight but i'm gonna try to activate the
elevator it has this constant chaos just did i seriously get hit by one of these little
fucking like drain clogs did i really let that happen yes i i already have like five times
how can there be nothing in there all right come in and go with come here come here come here
just let them kill each other who's alive oh there's two now well they're gonna break they're
gonna break the door down nice job nice job nice job nice job don't get so close why are you
getting that close he's gonna charge okay there's another one in there there's two more
there is there is there a safe around here where whoa everyone's june jupiter's where's the other
one where is he is it dead wait a minute you're an engineer open that door no get up get up i just
need you to open a door get up i need you to open that door damn it no come on i needed him to open
this door there's a safe point in there this health kits in this room oh i know but you can't
um so close yet so far damn it one of them breaks out where do you break out from
oh this sucks gotta put two flamethrower guys sit stay alive stay alive stay alive stay alive stay
alive hey i'm here get up come here i need you to do this holy shit thank god oh please don't have
any monsters in here or anything oh all right turn this on turn this on please over here do that
turn it on turn that on that's power for the whole room let's take us along what is it what's
going on what's wrong with you what are you doing all right all right i just hold on let me just
attack the computer i've locked the grenade launcher and a consignment of ammo in my office
2622 there are a lot of trigger happy men around here all right let's go let's go out out of this
room come on with me come on okay well just i'll just get out of this room out of the room okay
good get out let's go okay good okay i need you over here where's the safe point i you gotta
you gotta shine here man you gotta shine here i need you to shine need you to shine right now
be the best person this is such a this is a terrible speech all right you know the drill
we have to win hey come back back back back back back here comes here comes okay all right
make it happen you gotta shine here shine use the boxes use the boxes he's dead you shoot them
shoot them shoot i feel like i'm playing a multiplayer game right now i'm right now i'm
playing like actually left for dead okay now it's the these guys there's no more of those charging
weirdos it's just soldiers now right i think so any health packs i hear the beep in fact stay
okay where is it oh my god we did it grenade launcher and a shitload of grenades this is it
this is it i got i got a million grenades don't just go out there i know you're going to turn in
a second and you did you did a great job uh this one you did a fantastic job somebody just gave
another 55 dollars another huge amount of bits i'm who was it it was h m zine or h m zine
5500 bits so i heard you the guy to talk to you about moving desks hope this covers the fee i
think i left some cheetos in one of the drawers if you get hungry thank you thank you so much
we're at the end game here and i have a i have a grenade launcher where are these bastards i'm
not gonna do i need to even use it is he turned uh oh he's being a weirdo i need you to like come
out here come on get out there and find somebody he's dead all right almost there oh and i gotta
like use the bathroom too uh oh hope this is the final sequence because is it a key on the ground
no rifle no i'm okay i'm fine plant c4 on cargo planes you're still with me
okay be with me to the end what is going on uh why what's going on can i not am i not supposed
to go this way are we just supposed to run out just go this way i'm dying running in circles
where are these cargo planes just get the shit out of me oh fuck okay somebody just gave more
money i need to get in here i need the warmth all right we're good i might i i what was who
gives him sushi p sushi p gave 11 000 bits another drop of ridiculous fucking money
better hope this is the last sequence because pee pee poo poo thank you for the extraordinary
amount of money you're good okay i have to do this to four planes four planes is it healing
oh hey ac dc frank thanks for the five community subs it was a bait all right let's put the c4 on
this plane i don't see any health where does it go underneath in the front right here this i have
to do this three more times this is going to be horrible all right give me my rifle they're in
hangars take them out take them out take them out multi trip five community subs thank you so much
oh no not yet get in here and do this first aim for center mass but it's not you got to get a
head shot so it looks cool two to four i need please give me something in here i need health
is that this shit over here don't you freaking me out health pack thank god what's going on
over there i need a hat i need sound effects before i actually get scared of this why am
i glitching out too there's a lot of grenades over here um this is a bait this is this is fake
this is fake this is a trap right i mean it wasn't that big of a trap but it still was
i have full grenades that's another health pack thank god all right let's go
man i hate this job could really use a save point oh come on health packs we got company
what is it you've done such a great job i'm gonna be so sad when you are the one to turn at the end
of the game all right there's uh i can go over here any more of those hangars or to go forward
i hope i can just close the door on them that sounds terrible i know but come on give me
give me some credit here i gotta i have to beat i gotta go don't turn in this tiny corridor though
i hear beeping engineer open it oh my god grenade launcher grenade launcher grenade launcher
grenade launcher out the door watch it watch it get out of the way move move don't blow us both
up you're gonna kill us both oh fuck what's he doing what are you doing okay there's definitely
more of those in there follow me he's infected absolutely definitely is but i need him around
for at least another few minutes thank god i saved it right i saved the game oh thank god
so if you pick up don't it's if you stand up stay stay back back back back back back up back up back
up back up back up back up back up back up frank it was nice knowing you but if you don't back up
right now we're both dead i tried to tell him i tried to warn him i tried i tried to tell him
he was dead he was a he was a good he was he was a good person when the troops arrived i saw reed
getting taken away so i locked myself in here with the new guy started acting strangely and
then tried to attack me in my defense i shot him dead i think he might have caught something from
the creature i can hear outside the door his body hasn't stopped twitching since yesterday
well that's terrifying but i got the key i got what i needed all i don't remember his name
i don't i don't remember his name but he was nice he was a very good person and he got me this far
he got me this far the keys or anything in the bathrooms nothing else i can explore
oh it's it's anthony's gun oh no i can do it we're close
what oh i don't have an engineer i don't know why that would hurt i do hear beeps okay hello
who oh come on come on come on come on come on you good come here i got you reed best friend
ended with anthony oh no i knew best friend is reed what do you need how about a how about a
shotgun no i will get us out of this maybe and maybe you'll heal me for free i have health packs
too thanks all right i need to where's this box come on you coming okay what do you have for health
actually pretty bad come here i know everyone's gonna say dude what are you doing don't he's
probably infected check him i don't care thanks he needs to just get us to the end of the game
dude what the fuck check him dude why are you not checking him where are they in the ceiling
what just happened who just killed the lights why the lights down
whoa healing reed did it reed did it not really though i do have a friend now which i'm okay i'm
good with this now we gotta hold still and i'll fix you up i still have two more hangars to do
where the fuck are these other hangars i still have a key that i haven't used do i
reed's gonna betray us okay i can go this way that way i can go up let's go up should have looked
easy we're gonna die here
slow down it's all right i'm fine there's a big guy up here big guy big guy big guy big guy don't
get in my way like the last one it's all right don't get in my way like the last one i'm okay
nothing in here sniper ammo oh oh there are the other hangars okay sniper
sounds good to me i tried to fire the gun at least five times other side last two hangars
let's go nothing up here though no this way
everywhere there he is okay hey back back back watch out don't get in the way get it that way
read with me read read read read yes read move read i don't want to have you explode like the
last person in fact get over here read just stand here yes sir okay now let's go he's very hurt
back out out out out out this doesn't look good it would look better if you would face the enemy
oh yeah yeah goodness i'm okay safe point beautiful um but who cares i already did this
i guess there's just a safe point up here but who cares what does that do for me
we're gonna die here i'll pull it together i have to go like down but all right i guess
i'm just gonna go just it just saves the game apparently just saves the game okay
this doesn't look good oh no it's all right is he turning read are you all right read i'm gonna
need you to come over here here have some ammo that makes people feel better right here feel better
yeah good all right so which way do i need to go i need to go out and around
because i have to go to the other hanger can i not open this door data room three i guess
this way because wasn't i down here already though i was down here already this door didn't open
i have to get to where the planes are but how do i get out and then because this thing is in the
way soft locked no i don't think so it's not soft locked is it no i gotta go the other way
i gotta go that way i already did these two i have to you need i think you need the engineer
really no i was already here can i go around what's soft lock let's go i want that medic though
he may have run off i think the medic ran off did you did you just give another 275
dollars ashangi has given a 990 dollars and 54 almost a thousand dollars this ashangi that's
unbelievable oh my god i'm gonna die i've been trying to get flaccid locked trending over soft
locked all stream but no takers what gives should i stop trying to make flaccid locks happen
what what what he's talking about i've been trying you've been trying to get flaccid locked
oh right okay um oh he's back good we're lagging how can i lag it again it's not online
but seriously ashangi that's a thousand dollars is more money than i think i anyone should be
ever expected ever to ever i can't that's so much money all right cut the camera stop
i want to get the new camera oh for the love of god he's turned you couldn't have healed me one
more time i just what it looks like dr zoidberg all right i why is it not firing is he faster than
me holy shit okay worst item in any game that's right uh phylac phylactery has crossed the one
thousand dollar mark with that last 250 dollars 25 000 bits flaccid locked gun that's right
if you take a look at the top bits right now and just look at that absurd number you've crossed
the golden bits you have ashangi is right there too and so is everybody else that's given any
money today my god okay i need to move this camera sucks two thousand dollars worth of bits
just right there yeah like i said that's all i can say is thank you and i hope i spend it well
that this stream actually paid for the halloween stream like just just full on no doubt this stream
right here paid for the halloween stream absolutely so there's that one give us a give us a little
spoiler spoiler for the halloween stream no that's not fun you just just know that it's going to be a
um a secret slime stream all four of their fine sniper spot to shoot c4 i know what that is it's
up there already found that one just hope i can get it back to where i was i killed everything
though so that should be fine if it's bugleberry again i'm unsubscribing i don't i don't i don't
know i don't know who is and isn't going to make appearances on every stream could be anybody
is bugleberry the weird mask not a very nice way to talk about somebody i mean just going to be
honest what happened i want to say i can sniper two of those c4 charges from here to detonate them
once i shoot that first charge security is going to be all over this place like flies on
shit i'm gonna have to haul ass to the other side of the tower to shoot out the other two charges
oh this is going to be awful i need to save i'm not doing this until i saved again
okay now i'm ready why that didn't i just shot the wheels off this i thought there's going to be
explosions one more and then what oh here come all the guards escape escape to where where where
am i supposed to escape to escape how did you get in here already oh fuck save it i'm a safe psycho
right now none of them even fired a shot no i just went no oh no all right watch it watch it
watch it watch it watch it watch it watch it did that feel exceptionally long to anybody else
where am i supposed to escape to okay oh well i was very i was within two full rooms
here we go i was so far away from you wait these are super grenades that's why
these are super grenades die will you die the hardest enemies in the game are the
fucking tiny little shitheads is this door open now it is gain access to the armory there's more
how much more is there this we're going on nine hours i thought this game was supposed to be like
six i thought it was supposed to be like a six hour game um something's back there
oh this i'm gonna die there are two more bosses in this game how is this game nine hours there's
two more bosses so this is technically five hours in the game does anybody know oh come on do i
really have to do this whole thing again i'm just gonna run what's the point of even fighting it
just save time save money and go all right so let me let me ask has anybody beaten this game
in this chat do i actually have like less than 15 20 minutes or is this like do i have like another
couple hours not that long six six more minutes still at your well i'm in the tutorial still okay
let's see how far i get in the next 15 minutes because i do have to like i have to like i do
have to go i have some stuff i need to do internally let's see if i can get by this
without firing a shot because it's a loading screen you know what i mean it's not like i oh no
they're behind me no it's just a loading screen right here see so why even fight it all right
let me try it's it's it's getting late and i'm really not supposed to be streaming this long
for medical reasons so i'll give this like another one or two attempts and then we can
i can finish it when i come back i definitely don't have that much like left so first of all
what is in here this is an elevator this is an elevator access only first time for that
lady's voice i can go in there oh there's somebody look at this this guy's just can i just shoot a
grenade through the window i can't break this window that hurt him burn all right he's running
one more i need fuel safe point in there i hope so no but there's a lot of stuff in here
okay fire extinguisher a lot of heals tons of grenades shotgun ammo incendiaries
back up to 10 i got two of these perfect dab jupiter pretty good all right i've got plenty of
stuff okay hey are you still the i hate those things can i be real i guess i'm going this way
if we're not at the final sequence here like final boss coming up like after i go through here
hello i just got jumped okay where are we
what whoa stop stop stop running where are you going come here okay you give me a weapon why you
what are you doing what a moron come here take one cohen here they go kill it can't go up wait i
can go up here that's it which is a medic i'm not gonna give this guy the grenade launcher
all right i can go up here but why apparently that hurt what about my friend
okay oh all right i guess i could watch out for the gas does it hurt it does hurt i knew it was
gonna hurt you're okay come here well why would why would you walk into it again
that's a machine gun burn this guy talked he was talking it wasn't just like some random guy
staring at the camera there's a turret down there i just i felt myself rolling my eyes and i stopped
i still have plenty of health give my shit back you don't deserve it not a real friend i have to
go down the vent don't i the i gotta go through the vent and around somehow or i gotta throw a
grenade down there i'm just gonna kill me isn't it still alive you see even when they're like
burning to death they'll still get like a 10 damage hit on you to heal because the next safe
point i i'm gonna oh well you fuck off how many are there all right you know delete like 60 of
these things from the game and they would be like a fucking more of a better score hello why is the
whole pet store coming after me right now what the fuck what is that it or is it like another
40 of these little fucking snots that are going to come running at me i almost just died didn't
even need to do that don't catch fire back here please do i have a fire extinguisher i have plenty
of them almost done no i'm not not even close i just gotta get to a save point just get me to
a save point please oh is that still okay it's time to call bullshit when you see it
all right this is gonna be dangerous yep okay what the it's unnecessary it's unnecessary
it's unnecessary it's it on it's look it's just unnecessary i hope i got it
oh unnecessary i even waited too i even waited like the hitbox on it's just all fucked up
i'm so i i don't understand why don't you just walk into that when you make in the game and go
oh this sucks what the fuck where did you even come from where did you come from and is this
still alive oh no they're just coming through the fucking walls that my bad they're like coming
through the concrete they're going through the concrete is there a range on is there a fucking
range on when look how far back this is that's it i okay i just tried to run just run just run
through and the guy the guy was this big filled up the hole i couldn't run by him i just died
last one this is the last one this is the last try this is actually truly the last try
and then that's it and i actually really have to go let's go i'm gonna make this quick
he needs banana laxatives i actually have to take them dude the enemy ai is just doesn't
it's so strange but what are you doing it's so hard to determine because it's almost like they're
it's like randomized if the thing's gonna run away i gotta throw some weapons gray laxatives
at this fucking person just put it on easy yeah it is on hard right now that's true it is on hard
but i started it on hard i'm about to beat it on hard i'm just gonna try to sprint yes it's been
on hard the whole time i'm gonna try to go fast i know what i need to do fuck it you know what
i'm saying see you guys in a few days oh i would be so upset i just have to go fast
excuse me i've got somewhere to go hold mouse button down
i'm at it i'm fucking out of here i'll see you guys in a few days get off of me oh i'm
everything's on fire oh shit what he sees i need a fire extinguisher okay i everything's on fire
didn't i just kill him no no you can't run faster than this
i just turned into this toxic avenger see you guys later oh yeah too it's been too long
i'll see you guys later i'm having fun but i i'm i was not supposed to stream for this long
my stomach is like actually bothering me so we will finish it uh not tomorrow i'm gonna be gone
for a couple days i have a doctor's appointment tomorrow and that's why i have to go too because
i have to stay on this regiment to be able to talk to the doctor tomorrow and tell him everything
that's going on right and go for a follow-up so i'll be back when am i gonna be back let's see
because i want to stream like three or four days before doing the halloween stream and i have to
leave for the halloween stream the fuck all right we're gonna get off of this screen because it's
scaring the shit out of me does the top sub thing work holy shit uh yeah thanks for taking
around it's a late one i know i i would push through and do like a 10 plus hour stream but
i i can't physically uh i'm really not supposed to be doing that i need to go use the bathroom
and go take more of this fucking molasses so i'll see you guys what's today today's monday
i'll probably see you guys again on let me see one two i'll see you guys again on
thursday so i'll be off um tomorrow and wednesday and then i'll be back and we'll do thursday friday
saturday so i'll see you guys on thursday so on thursday we're gonna probably finish the thing
and then after i mean i can't imagine it'll take more than another hour or so
so finish the thing and then we're gonna do uh parapa the rapper and parapa the rapper too
i got a weird kind of shift there i know but if you think about it parapa the rapper and both
those two games are one to two hours long each so if there's like an hour or two left of the thing
or like an hour left of the thing talking about it'll be like about five six hours total so that
works out pretty well looking forward to it so i will see you guys in a couple days uh i
unfortunately i cannot do the bits right now because i really do have to go i didn't think
i was gonna go this long but what will happen is like we do sometimes i'm gonna go over the bits
on holy shit there's so many uh we'll do this before and this could actually be a pretty good
thing to do yeah and this would be good to end it or even to begin it because this will probably
take about an hour or so to do and i i can't i just physically cannot i'm sorry but something
that we will do is at least take a look at some of the credits and i do have to say thank you
everybody for all the ridiculous contributions let me see if this works uh it does 270 gifted subs
from phylactery holy shit i think it might even be more than that so let's do the credits
we'll pick up on these bits on thursday sorry i know i typically go over them all of them but
you know gotta do what you gotta do i do appreciate every single one of them though
and there were a fucking lot of them there were a lot of them strap yourselves in for the credits
this is gonna be bonkers let's see what happens i don't even know what's gonna happen
that's never gone that fast ever that's a you're looking at like potentially 14 13 14 1500 names
you can't even see read them let's i'll see if i can get one merlin thanks a lot merlin
and uh craig nice job craig thanks for the sub you guys uh i can't you i can't comprehend this
i can't comprehend it years later months later doesn't matter i still can't believe it
thank you this is still going imagine the credits went by this fast at the movie theater
no special thanks to all the people that worked on this movie they were like 5000 people on set
it's still going this is the kickstarter but this is bigger than a kickstarter backer list
and it's almost like i feel like it it's not this many and it repeated or something but no
that's legit thank you guys for real i'd love to stick around i really was hoping i could power
through it but i'll see you guys on thursday we'll do a bunch of stuff we'll do parapa we'll do these
bits at the end we'll just do like a big chill hangout session thank you again for the thousands
of dollars and subs i am gonna go take some medication from my stomach and go relax and go
much love to you guys seriously i hope you guys like the thing it was fun i didn't really complain
that much about it until we got to the steam but i think i'm having fun with it i definitely
want to see it to the end see you guys soon take care of yourselves ads ads all right i will run
i will i will run ads okay i'm gonna run three minutes of ads right now is that what you want
for real i guess all right i guess i'll do it have a wonderful rest i can't run an hour worth of ads
there's only yeah everyone's a sub now anyways maybe 15 of you are gonna get these
finally some good fucking content all right now see you guys in a few days take care much love
have a great night let's do samsung what the oh my god do i have to stream this i think the
stream has to stay on yeah i don't think i can't just turn off the stream this has to stay on
why did i just do three minutes that's a long time now he has to stay here and watch the ads
let's talk about non-subs they can't hear us unless they have ad block is this some joke i
don't understand um no it just everyone demanded i saw everyone demands ads sometimes i guess it
is a joke because nobody wants to watch ads i do it's serious i do i do i got a pringles ad
smiley face pringles pretty good if chat asked you to poop yourself would you do it
uh no i would not why would i do that i don't know my sub just ran out so i'm getting oh my
fucking god do you guys have any idea it was like 1500 subs tonight more a little bit more
i cannot i can't even look at that number and believe it
but seriously term i walked in on my mom and dad what do i do what on what were they eating
hanging out what do you mean you walked in on what not that i don't they were taking weapons
grade accidents will you tell kim the good news oh she already knows she was like i need to move
this desk and i go out there i'm like i'm like why am i what am i what am i doing why do i need
we need to move a desk right now she's like yeah right now and i'm like i i guess and i was like
by the way good thing it's going out good thing we're getting rid of this one i need you to move
this desk no no no we can pay people to do that now you guys are fucking awesome i'll see you guys
on thursday we'll pick back up thanks again have a wonderful rest of your night have a wonderful
midweek see you real soon good night guys take care