Hey, what is happening guys? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
Doing it with the Scout tonight, Default Scattergun, the Mad Milk, and the Unarmed Combat,
the new Halloween unlockable new Halloween item. If you are wondering why the cart is almost
kept for the enemy team, I'll tell you it's because we were getting absolutely dominated
in this gameplay. I was playing as a medic for the most part, and we were just getting crushed.
There was nothing we could have done. We were getting absolutely owned. This only took like
five minutes for them to get this far. I figured we were just gonna lose, so I switched over to
Scout just to get some kills, just to have a little bit of fun. And it turned out to be quite
a good thing because we end up coming back with a victory in this gameplay. And in other news,
did you guys see the trailer for Grand Theft Auto V? Oh my god, I can't wait for that game to come
out now. Unbearable it's gonna be in my brain when they announce, oh that's coming out in,
June 6th 2015. Oh my god, going back to San Andreas, going back to Los Santos, that's gonna
be so much fun. I can't wait to play it. I have played every Grand Theft Auto back to Grand Theft
Auto I. I was one of those guys that owned Grand Theft Auto London. If any of you guys know what
that is, if any of you know what Grand Theft Auto London is, then you get props from me because
that's an old, really not that well known game. So if you know what that is, mad props to you.
So this is kind of a derp moment right here. I jumped down here. Instead of going for the medic,
I shoot the heavy multiple times. I figured, I figured that our team had enough people shooting
at him or somebody was backing me up that I could get two meat shots on him and he would die. But
that was not the case and I end up looking like a derp derpington, which it's okay. Sometimes it's
okay to be a derp derpington. So I digress. Let's get back into this here. Barn Blitz is a crazy map.
Takes a long time to play Barn Blitz. I don't have a problem with maps that take a long time. It's
just the fact that upwards a very long map, bad waters a very long map. Most of the popular payload
maps happen to be the long, long maps, with the exception of course of Gold Rush. I wish they
would implement more maps like Gold Rush. You know, one, two control point checkpoints,
just because things go a little bit quicker. Because it can take potentially like 30 or 40
minutes to play one of these maps from beginning to end if the teams are balanced. Hopefully somebody
comes out with a map that's kind of like a Gold Rush but a little bit better, a little bit more
sleek and well-designed. I know there are plenty of custom maps that are like this, but I'm talking
more about official Valve style maps. So if you're looking for some scout tips on Barn Blitz,
here are a couple. These are the most important ones, especially when you get to this choke
point near the end of the last control point. This little area back here with the health pack
and the ammo pack is your best friend. I take out this pyro. I'm on fire. Keep going up here over
and over again. Probably go up here five or six times looking for the health pack. Sometimes I
don't find it because other people have the same idea. Get the assist on that heavy coming up here
to look for one last health pack. I get it just before this scout comes after me. Jumping around
the corner here. This is a great idea. Do this. Do a double jump around the side. There's a sentry
over there. Don't want to get myself killed so I just jump down here, shoot this scout in the face,
ruin his birthday party. The clown had to go home too. It's actually unfortunate. So this next part
is actually pretty odd. You'll see what I'm talking about. See that sentry over there?
I shoot it a few times and this engineer, rather than repairing it, he just destroys it. See,
I don't get the kill for this. Look at the top right. Nobody got the kill for it. He just destroyed
it and I think he put a new one down too. Kind of weird but you know people have different strategies.
Who knows what he was thinking? Probably trying to do something different. That's not a bad thing so
let's move right along here. Coming up to get the health pack like I told you guys before.
Jumping down to shoot this sniper in his face. Nothing he can do about it because as we all know
the machina what he was using cannot shoot from the hip. So even if he wanted to kill me he would
have to zoom in in my face. Level 1 sentry is now built up over there on the right side. Nothing I
can do about it so I run backwards. I'm gonna try and patrol the back area now just to make sure
there's only a minute left. So I want to just make sure that nobody comes around the side or around
the back door because Barn Blitz, the last point, has a couple of different places where you can
just pop out on the enemy team. So if you have a couple people on the right side and the left side
you'll be able to secure the last point. Get the health pack. Dancing around like a freak show.
Coming out here seeing if I can find somebody. I see there's a sentry and I hear the sentry as well.
There it is straight ahead. Try to get the milk on that soldier. Does not go well. I see a spy
picking up this health pack. Don't know what I'm going to do because I don't know where he is.
Probably a dead ringer. This is going to be the end of the gameplay. I make a pretty dumb mistake.
I know the sentry is out there but I'd run into it anyways. I'm just stupid. So I kill a soldier,
kill a sniper, get into a small scuffle with another scout. He disappears. I'm kind of like,
I look around like where the hell did he go? So I just run outside and get plastered by that level
three sentry and that's going to be the end of the gameplay. We win this game. I top frag only
because I was playing as a medic before. So if you're wondering how the hell did you get 40 points
in five minutes like that as a scout, it's because I was playing medic before. Thank you guys so much
for watching. I really do appreciate it. If you like this video, throw me a like, shoot me a like,
thanks guys. I'll see you all next time. Take care everybody.