I can't even put into words how upset I am right now.
I've missed the wine convention by two hours,
and I bought this special red wine suit to prove how much I love wine,
and now what am I supposed to do, throw it in the trash?
Oh hey Jerm, how the fuck out of here?
By the way, can I just say, we both look like fucking idiots.
You look like a Dead Rising character.
Look at how I'm leaning in.
Can I not hear him?
What's he saying?
Okay, yeah, I got it. I gotta be real close.
You know, I don't hear so well no more.
I look like I just work in a movie theater.
You look like an usher.
What's with the Gatorade tattoo you have on your arm?
That's supposed to be a slight lightning bolt.
That's a fucking Gatorade logo.
No.
You're doing the hacking job.
Okay, so now I'm the hacker. Got it.
I'll do the hacking.
So on the way there, I gotta hack the system.
Not easy.
Fucking no, shit.
What did we lose the height?
Don't make me laugh.
Don't sneeze like a fucking dickhead.
Give me a second.
I can't fail it again.
I failed it again.
I actually have to blow my nose right now.
Let's go.
The fucking stick up.
Another block.
Good idea.
Real good idea.
That's not so much of a good idea,
except I think it might have just worked.
Holy shit, how the hell did you pull that off?
It was like Dukes of Azeroth.
You just did like a Tony Hawk ollie off of a wall.
Okay, I gotta admit, that was pretty impressive,
but can you do it again?
Just like squeezed right there.
That was nice, man.
I think we're gonna blow up this bridge.
What?
All right, we're looking at the bridge here.
Is there a helicopter there?
Do we have to destroy the helicopter?
No, that's for us.
What do you mean that's for us?
It's magnetizing us to it.
We're gonna get sucked up by a super magnet?
Oh, did you just get out?
Did you get out of the car?
Oh my gosh.
We'll take him down.
I want an APB put out of this guy.
We're not gonna stop until he's here.
Where'd he go?
Where is he?
I don't remember anything.
Can anyone remember anything?
I don't remember.
There's nine bullets discharged from my gun.
Why did I do that?
All I remember is I'm the bad cop.
I think I'm a bad cop.
I'm gonna go home.
I'm in the prison bus.
I'm just gonna drive.
We're all behind you.
What is this car doing?
This isn't even a cop that just ran me.
Man, there's like speed demons on the road for some fucked up reason.
Did somebody fly out of the sky?
Oh, I don't want to go in here.
I actually screwed up.
What was that?
Why did the guy just fall from the sky?
You need to kill this helicopter.
Perfect.
Very, very nice.
I hope we don't blow this up.
Oh, there's a helicopter right in front of us.
Oh, and this thing's upside down.
We're just sliding down.
Come on.
Actually, oh, wow.
Holy shit.
Did that seriously just end up working in our favor?
That can't be serious right now, right?
We're not found.
Quiet, quiet, quiet, shut up.
Oh, they've had us.
Fuck.
I mean, in full uniform, but.
Shit.
Take a right at the street.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, fuck.
That's not the street.
Just take a right.
You're still fine.
He's in between.
Oh, come on.
Hold X to duck.
Hold X.
You're not holding it.
We're in some guy's garage.
Oh, my gosh.
They're coming.
They're not going to see us.
They're coming down the street.
We'll hide in a garage.
They can't even see.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh.
You're not even in my car.
Oh, you're in the back.
Hold on.
Let me get in there.
I'm so glad that worked.
He just pulled into his garage.
Yeah, we like ran into that guy.
That guy could have just called the police.
He's on the ground dead.
Oh, no, he's not.
That guy ran in his house.
He probably could have just called the police
and been like, oh, you're looking for a guy in a cop car?
He just like hit me and is hiding in my garage.
There's a car that's going to pull up here in a second.
This one right here.
Two guys are going to get out.
And you have to pick who you want to shoot
because we have to shoot them both at the same time.
How long do we have?
Like now.
Ready?
I'm going to get the guy on the right.
Are you ready?
Sure.
Three, two, one, shoot.
Now go get the we got to get the briefcase.
I thought since you did this before,
this was the surefire way to do it.
Just hold on a second.
I have to go get some snacks.
Sir, do you have any butterfingers or Eggo waffles here?
I'm craving them.
Put all the money in the register.
Hurry up.
Make it snappy.
Oh, I thought this was a handgun.
Did that really just happen?
I'm sorry.
I just wanted some snacks.
I see the guy in the plane.
Yeah.
What is his job?
Is he just like kind of circling around?
I'm not sure what he's supposed to do,
but he's supposed to pick us up.
He's our getaway.
All right.
We're about to park.
I'm not supposed to get out of the car.
You're supposed to pull me out.
No, you're my prisoner.
I take you out.
So you're in handcuffs.
Get out of here, you fucking scumbag.
Don't worry.
I got this.
I got this, asshole.
So you have to walk.
Don't do anything insane.
Oh, you idiot.
Why did you do that?
We can still do it.
I mean, this can be the hardest thing in the world,
but we can still do it.
Hold on.
We need to go.
A little premature.
Holy shit.
Did that guy just jump?
Fucking kill them both.
Oh, my gosh.
You just totally screwed us.
I know.
I can't believe we're actually still alive.
I don't even know what we're doing now.
You need to start shooting people.
I haven't seen you shoot your gun one time.
We have to get the prisoner out.
There's no markers there.
I'll mark it for you.
No, it looks like he's flying to us.
Airplane.
That's a cop helicopter, I think.
Is it?
We need to get another teammate.
I got just destroyed from behind.
Hopefully.
Oh, Jesus, man.
It just spawned me in such a stupid spot.
Holy shit.
Oh, my God.
Oh, dear God, dude.
Oh, my fucking God.
This is horrible.
We might look at we're going to lose.
I'm shooting just rockets in like every direction.
Okay, why?
Why would it spawn me in the middle of the fucking street?
With like nine cruisers and four helicopters.