Howdy, partners. It's me, Jerma, here with a Fistful of Frags gameplay live compo.
I just was getting started.
Whiskey. Pass, pass, pass, pass, pass, pass, pass, pass, pass, pass, pass, pass, pass, pass, pass, a whiskey, pass, a whiskey.
For the love of all that is sacred.
I want to go in like a at least five kill streak right now. Have to. Got to. It's mandatory. It's absolutely mandatory.
It is mandatory.
This guy's got two weapons. There we go. It's three.
Oh! Coming from behind.
Had a bullet on that.
Let me get that one more hit. Oh boy. Oh boy, I'm in trouble.
This is actually a good place to be.
I can sit in here and I can reload the gun.
Don't have to really worry about anyone coming through. There's some whiskey on the ground.
Dude, I don't want to be that drunk for this.
Because it sounds like there's a lot going on out here.
I've got to get to like at least five or six kills.
And this guy doesn't even know.
Oh, you don't even know.
Just creeping in the room like friggin' Slenderman.
I'm at four. Ready to bang.
Oh, that was close.
That was close. Show your face again.
Did I get him? Oh, I did get him.
This is five.
Oh boy, this is bad. This is bad.
This is real bad.
People around all over the place. I got to make this shot count. This shot has to count.
It counted. It counted. I got it.
It counted. Oh my god, that guy didn't even see me.
How did that guy not see me?
I don't know. I'm not going to ask questions.
But I'm going to try to keep this going.
There it is.
Give me that gun. Give me this thing. No, I don't want this thing.
I want to stay with the pistol. I want to stay tried and true with the pistol.
Try to get to ten.
No!
Must pay attention to your surroundings, son.
Pay attention to your surroundings.
Let's go with the...
No. I'm going to try to do this.
It's very important.
There is a dynamite behind me.
Guy throwing dynamite up top right there.
Seriously, you got to get out of my face.
Four.
The quest for the ten kill streak.
It is a quest indeed.
Especially on a free for all map.
It's difficult to do because people could be seriously all over you.
In every single direction.
Let's get out here in this room.
It's so scary because if you turn a corner and there's somebody just sitting there and they're ready before you're ready.
Sayonara.
You ain't going to make it.
Like that.
That's exactly what I was talking about.
What happened to my kill streak?
I don't even know what this is. I was on like four. Why does it say three?
Well, I don't believe that at all.
So I like lost pace.
Hopefully this is like at least eight.
I hope.
I don't know how many kills this is.
I've lost track. It's like seven or eight. I don't know, but I need ten.
Got to get to that ten.
All right. All right.
Just calm down. Calm down.
Calm down and whip a knife at this guy.
Oh, I'm in trouble.
I'm in trouble.
This could be ten here.
Oh, no.
No, I was at nine.
I can clean this up.
I'm going to clean this shit up.
Somebody call Billy Mays.
Tell him to bring all of his oxy clean.
Because this place is a fucking mess.
It needs like a deep clean.
Hide, hide, hide from this guy.
Holy shit.
What is happening?
Shoot the guy next to you.
You dipshits.
What the fuck is going on in that room, dude?
Look at everybody's in this room.
Every single person was just in this room.
Why is so many people in here?
Oh, I had to be quiet for that one.
There's no way I was going to do that one while opening my big mouth.
My big mouth.
If they go for a kick, just do the reverse kick.
God, the derringers are so scary.
I was so scared to use these things.
You get two shots at each side and if you miss, it's over.
You get four, but you know what I'm saying.
You understand.
You understand my stress.
I'm under a lot of stress with the derringers.
Was that three?
All right.
Cool.
Just leave me alone for a second.
I'm just trying to reload.
I'm just trying to reload for crying out loud.
Is that a grenade?
Oh, not a grenade.
A dynamite?
I don't know.
But we're going to one of the worst parts to go to because it's just out in the open.
I missed.
I missed again.
Okay.
Chill.
Getting close here.
Seriously.
Fuck you, dude.
Where are the derringers?
I got to shoot.
I got to hit this.
Get that dynamite out of my face, bro.
Get it out of my face.
I'm in so much trouble.
Seriously, I need whiskey.
Otherwise, there's no way I'm going to get to 10.
I don't even want to open that box.
I'm too timid right now to do anything besides just like chill.
Someone's going to hit me from afar.
It's going to happen.
It just is.
Accept your fate.
I'm freaking out.
I'm freaking out right now.
Oh my God.
I killed him.
Give me the whiskey.
Come on.
I just like...
No.
I was at eight.
Fucker.
One more.
Come on.
That guy's got like two health.
I wasted three shots on that guy and I'm not even going to get the kill for it.
Where am I?
I am.
Box crate is here.
Nobody around.
Give it to me quick.
Come on.
Before somebody comes in the room.
Pump shotgun.
Give it to me.
Let's get this done.
Let's get this 10 kill streak done.
What do you say?
Huh?
What do you say, mate?
Let's go.
What do you say?
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do it right here.
I don't care where you come from, you snakes.
Just like a snake.
You got to get a couple kills and you got to jump away.
You got to take a way back to your home.
I would open this, but I don't want to because I want to be sure that I'm going to get this
streak.
Go back to my snake den.
And I see bodies.
Fresh bodies.
Yep.
That's all right.
I had a little bit of a freak out moment there, guys.
A little bit of a freak out moment.
Because I'm real close to that big 1-0.
Give me that whiskey.
Give me that heavily, heavily.
I don't think it matters.
It's not going to matter.
I need to get a couple more kills here.
Oh, there's a guy.
There's a guy.
There it is.
I think I got it.
I have no idea, though.
I have absolutely no idea if I got it or not.
Is the kill streak quest over?
I hope so.
Because I really...
Let's get it to 15.
I did it.
I got it.
Hands up.
Ten.
Low left.
Kill streak quest is complete.
And that's going to wrap it up.
That's what I wanted to do.
That was the goal.
That was what I set out to accomplish.
And I did.
And yeah, a fistful of frags, guys.
By the way, hold down alt for those of you that are wondering.
Hold on.
What the fucking...
All right, hold down alt.
That's the tip.
That's the strategy for the day.
It makes your aim better.
All right.
Take care, everybody.
Goodbye.