All right, I'm just setting up the other game and wiping the lenses.
Cool. All right, this is called a chair in a room green water. I guess there's a chair in a room and
you have to investigate it. We'll see. There's more stuff in the exorcist game? Oh, oh well,
uh, maybe it's too late. All right, coming back. Here it is. Do the thing. Oh wait, hold on. I'm
gonna make sure I can see what you guys are saying. We're good. Draw two. All right. No,
relax. Here we go. This is called a chair. Okay, at some point this fell out again. I'm not even
gonna use it. I don't even care. That's like the nose guard. The camera looks weird too, doesn't
it? Don't you think? What's going on here? Hold on. It looks fucking crazy. The white balance is
wrong. There's a contrast. It's like all fucked up. Why does it look so fucking weird? I feel
like I'm, I feel like I'm stop motion. Like I'm 12, I'm like 21 frames a second or something. It's
weird. Don't you feel like I'm like, I've been animated? What happened? This is not at 60 fps.
Whatever. Don't worry. It's, it's, it's a chair in the room. Let's go. Would you have a 30 hertz
monitor? I don't have a 30 hertz monitor. I have a 120 hertz monitor. I need to upgrade. I have
1080 at 120 hertz. Intel, uh, six core processor. Don't worry. I'm gonna get one of those AMD
Rippers. I'm going back in. See you guys in a little bit. It's massive. Thanks, man.
Harris Michael, I hired you as a priest a couple weeks ago. You said this. All right. Here in the
room. Oh, Dr. Green? I judge how good a VR game is based on what is breakable in the room. And
there we go. Ladies and gentlemen, this is at least one letter grade. How do you do it? E,
E, F, P, T. Oh, I'm covering your eye. Sorry. E, F, P, O, Z, L, F, E, D, F, E, C, F, D, E, D,
F. That's blurry. Wolf and wood. Welcome to the Institute. I'm happy to answer any questions
you might have. Oh, shit. Hey, uh, is leather jacket here? Leather jacket, are you here?
Oh, change the game to a green room. Whatever. Chair in a room. Thank you.
Oh, sir. Chair in a room. Just a chair in a room. Who's in that chair? Me. It's all you yourself.
Who's in that room? Ah, probably me in that chair. I don't know.
I was a bad Tommy Wiseau. I can't hear. My ears are blocked. If I could hear myself, I would do a
sick Tommy Wiseau impression. It was better than the last one. What do you mean credits? What are
you talking about? Hey, fuck you, bitch. I lost the chair part of the room. Oh, swan.
Screwdriver. Box. Boy. Medication. Knife. Was I supposed to be repeating? Me. Head. Baby.
Look at me. Priest. Phone. Sega. Pegasus. Sega. The Sega Pegasus. What? What? Why?
Uh, I was, I woke up and I, I ended up here. You guys, I have no idea. I thought I was coming
for a checkup and you guys put me in here. Separate maybe a little. Yes, ma'am. Uh, Otto,
what are you doing? Patient six zero seven nine. Please come to the window for your medication.
Otto just like walked over here. Don't come over here. Good boy. Okay. Uh, medication. Right. Um,
I. It's for your own good. Hey, yeah. Bottoms up. That was delicious. Yeah. All right. He's over
there. He's lying down. What is this? Today you will perform simple memory tests. In front of you
is a ball and three cups. Yeah, is it? I would like you to. It's a power move. What did I have
to do? Hide the cup, hide the ball under a cup? Sure. Good luck with this one, you piece of shit.
Well, I got a new ball. Can I get a new ball, please? Can I get a new ball, please? You fucking
bastard scientist. You can't keep me in here. You think you can keep me in here? You're not
going to keep me in here. Let me the fuck out of here. I thought this was a DMV.
You want to play your little game. That's what you want. You want to play your little game.
You sicko. I seriously have another ball. I air. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Here it is.
Oh, I am going to hide this for you. Sure. Hey, Dr. Dickhead under the right one under the right
one. Done. I'm done. I disappeared. Hey, what do you see? I hit it under the I hit it under the
right one. Ah, that's a spider under there. Now. I turn my back, you put a spider under there. It's
kind of weird that you did that. I'll show it to you here. Spider. Pretty shitty trick. This is a
This is a prop table. Thanks. Any more? Any more? Any more rain busters for me? What do you want
to do with this? It's a spider. It's a spider. It's a spider. It's a spider. Okay, I see I see a
spider. Hello. I'm leaving. It was weird. Spider. Okay, spider here. Ball here. Brown like this.
Oh, shit. Give me that. Give it back. Can't get me in here. What the heck is this supposed to mean?
Bond fishing, huh? Are you gonna give me food or something? Change the you change the color
of the thing that I have here. Um, I don't what do you want me to do? Bottoms up. How does that look?
Not taking it. I can't even see where it is if I wanted to take it in the first place.
Oh, my eyes are all blurry. I don't know you like. Do you have like an antihistamine I can take?
I'll take that. But I don't want to take whatever weird drug you just gave me.
Uh, I need some other drug. All right. Fine. Where is it? I can hear. Where is it? Okay. All
right. I'll take it. I'll take it. I'll take it. You can go back to your room now. Do I eat the
spider? I hate the spider. The drugs. I didn't want to take those drugs. I can't look at this
room. I can't turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off. Oh, please recalibrate the shit. What's
going on here? Okay. This room looks normal. All of the information. All right. How do I start?
Are you ready for your point to start? I want to start a new game. Make your way upstairs.
Afters? I want to start a new game. I don't know. Maybe it'll just work. Will it just happen?
This is fucked up. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I don't want to do that.
Walk into a wall. What happened? Why can I not start what I left off? There's got to be a way
to do that. It's got to be like a load game or something, right? Load game, load game,
but not start a new game. What does that one do? Aim. Please be comfortable. This room contains
all of the information you need to get ready for your point to be dropped to green. Oh, wait.
Let's photograph. Ready to start upstairs. Photograph and then grab the handle. Point?
There is only grip. What do you mean, point? Okay. This looks more like what was supposed
to happen, I guess. For my toys. What does this say? I need to go to my desk.
The Winter. Oscar Charrington. The Holy Bible. By Oscar Charrington. No, we're going to hotel,
we're going to hotel room this thing. There. Don't open that drawer for like 30 years. The bed?
Sleep? Ah, dude, another classic by fucking Oscar Charrington. Paradise Lost. A poem written in
10 books. Oscar Charrington. What time does that say? That is 1202. I am a murderer. Who did I kill?
What? I'm a murderer. Who did I kill? I am a murderer. Who did I kill? I remember a bird on
the water. What was that? Place the clue here. I wonder. Bird on the water. That sounds to me
like a duck. This is everything I can remember. I have to hide what I know. The doctors say that
memories haunt me so I hide this from them. Things here seem familiar, they must be. Right there.
Well. Oh, that's, this is, this is, that's a vulture.
Yeah, that's some good, that's some good shit, apparently.
Carry items between rooms. That was chapter one already. Chapter two, let's go. Oh, it's just,
I love that. I love it. I'm gonna do it. Oh, we are just too wild and crazy, guys.
What? I can't make that wrap. That's a huge alligator, by the way. Let's be real.
Power lamp. What's a power lamp? Operate, hold flashlight in hand and press thumb pad.
Oh, can I fish? Power lamp. Oh, press, there we go.
Well, that's not safe. I think so, boy. Okay, um, now what? I think I might have needed that.
Nice. Now, all right, what do I do? Check all the draws?
Add debt but still want the dream lifestyle you deserve? Unlock your, unlock your potential
mortgage refinance. No application. Live the dream. Oh, there's a, there's a, there's a monster
in there. There's a fucking monster. Did you see that? That's horrible. I swear to God,
there was a monster in there. Something in this. Can I like, screw drive his eye out?
Get that there. Um, E, S, E. How do I get out of here? Driver. Oh, shit, I got it.
That's what I saw. Where? Okay, uh, take these planks off.
All right, I need the light. This. Indeed. Indeed, say. Party's welcome. Regeneration.
The locals feel abandoned. What else is in there? Why? Just didn't feel like having anything in there.
Oh, there's something in that bag. What the fuck is in this bag? What happened? Pizza box?
This is a huge pizza thing to break that with. Oh, off the walk. I get in here. I leave this room?
I can leave this room. Bounce. I bring this with me into the room? Like this. Can I open that?
Turn on the lamp. 8.7k Andy. That's great. What happened to the lamp? It looks like Otto. Um,
it's so stupid. Where's the lamp? Why does it fucking disappear? Where's the lamp?
Lamp find lamp. Search for the lamp. Where's the lamp? Where's the lamp? At the lamp?
Where is the fucking lamp? Tuck in the wall in the first room. Fuck, come on.
Well, now I'm stuck in the wall. Stuck in the wall in the first room.
What's going on? Am I going crazy or what?
I'm fucking mad at this game now. Now I'm angry. Now you pissed me off. Now you made me angry. Now
you got me irritated. I'm searching around for a fucking lamp and I'm stuck in the wall now.
I don't think it's even here anymore. Just turn it off. Just turn it off. What button did I press
on the side? Why does this button exist by the way? Why would you put this button here? The button
that you like never find again. It's gone. I have to restart the whole thing. Am I losing my fucking
mind or is it just gone? Did I like throw it over here? Do I like, do I even need it? I'm giving
this 30 more seconds before I just delete it and uninstall again. Hey, so you're saying it's in this
room? Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait. What's in here? I'm ready for my medicine. Can I take it please?
Light illuminating the wall. I think you're in the corner. It's really hard to see.
Here. You're talking about like in here. What happened? Give me his back. I thought that was
an eyeball. All right. All right. All right. Okay. All right. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done.
Wait, can I go? What might be in this corner? Is it because I like the ruin? I like the ruin,
right? I was like, oh, there it goes. And then it got like lodged in the wall.
In this wall, technically, right? Shut up and let me in. End of the circle. Detail of the game.
Hey dude, it started up. It was so promising when it started out though.
I'm not, I'm never letting go of this. Okay. All right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Let's go. Go. Go.
Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. That falls. It'll fall down in two seconds. Ready? Three, two, one. There it goes.
It falls down. I take a look over here. You read the postcard. Isn't that interesting?
Isn't that interesting? Okay. Isn't that interesting? Okay. Wow. Isn't that interesting?
Look at this. That's interesting. All interesting stuff. What's in here? Isn't that interesting?
What's this thing say? Holy shit. What's that say? Isn't that interesting? Okay. Cool. Cool. All right.
Drop. Drop that. There it goes. Okay. Drop. I thought that was outside of my window.
Oh, it was. I think somebody's just out there. Okay. Oh. There. I can't stop moving. Why am I moving?
Okay. Who cares? Open the door. What's in there? There's a scary monster. Open.
Open. Okay. Here we go. Hey. Remember that song? That thing moves. Three, two, one. Scary.
And this don't open. What do we do about that? Can I use the saw on that? Oh, dude. Oh, shit.
Man, what the heck? How do I get out of this? We open up this and see what's in here.
Oh, this means something maybe. Oh, authorities say that the plant got shut down. What the fuck,
dude? What the hell's going on in this town? What else is in here? That broke off.
Heck. Oh, something's moving in that bag. There. Who's in that? Oh. Beware. Beware. I didn't even
see that. I didn't have the lamp. Let's go. All right. What do I do with this?
Pry this off. What should I do with this? Pry the boards off. Okay. Here we go.
Pry those boards off. Let's work with the floor. There it is. And I can't grab it. I can't grab it.
Get in there. Come on. Get in there. Get out. Okay. It's blown. A couple of bones.
Otto, I'm not playing right now. He's like, I'm down here and he's like trying to play with me.
Otto. Hold on. All right. Wait. Hold on. I don't want to step on him. Give me one second.
You want to go out? Come here. Okay. I have to give this like five to 10 more minutes.
My back is going to explode. Getting kicked out of the room. Like every time I go this way,
it's like... Okay, here we go. Back to that like hospital. Nothing in there. I have probably
to go fishing. I'm going to say like go fishing. Right? Like that's a fishing pole.
Otto, we're going to scoop it out with this. Don't delete the... I left it way up there.
I need to get that fishing rod. There it goes. Oh. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. What is it?
There's a key in here. Key. Oh my god. Yes. All right. We're good. All right. 10 more minutes.
10 more minutes. I promise, mom. I'll do my homework in 10 minutes.
All right. The game just got way better. I was very mean to this game. It just got way better.
We're going to get a residency before it by that crocodile.
There she blows. Where is it? I lie down on my back. It can't get me.
Wait, do I have to steer this? I thought that was just the motor.
Oh, it's a big swan. Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey. Well, I'm going to sit down and enjoy myself. Am I supposed to be doing something?
What's that? Look, those are birds over there flying around. What's happening? Did I miss something?
Mommy, I saw something in the water. No. No. Don't even think about it. Get out of here.
Watch that tail. He's going to smash underneath us. Hey, don't do that. What a trip, Hank.
Let's go out. It's a little foggy. Don't worry about it. Okay. I'm cold. It's foggy.
We can't see anything. You want to fish out here? God darn it. Worst trip I've ever taken. Hank,
what's that? POV. You're on a murder date. Wait for the drop. It's right there.
Was that Seaman? That was Seaman. What was that? Seaman 2. I'll be honest. That was a very,
very, very, very, very, very long boat ride. The allocator did not fucking knock it over.
You know what I mean? He did get a Seaman reveal, though, which was pretty awesome.
Okay. Let's go to bed now, right? Go to bed. I want to do more in the medical place,
but she's telling me to do things. That was so cool. A teenager in the water. Who else was out
there? What was that bird in the highway? Bird on the highway. Highway bird. No, not a highway bird.
Highway bird. That kind of looks like a highway bird. No, that's not a highway bird. This is a
highway bird. We're in a motel. This might get interesting. That boat ride with that leg. Here
it comes. Here it comes. Here it comes. Here it comes. Here it comes. Here it comes. Here it comes.
Here it comes. This face in the water. All right. This is getting a little creepy.
All right. This is already way scarier than riding on the Disney boat.
Turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off. Stop. Stop. Stop. I don't want to do that.
Look, I get it. You're trying to watch the porn channel. It's not going to come through. I tried
everything already. I'm sorry. I remember what? Meet me tomorrow morning? I think the mic just
picked up her just ripping a huge one. I remember George. Meet her tomorrow morning. Oh, this is
crazy. Why would you just be taking pills at the bottom of the ocean?
Oh, this is creepy. What kind of bed is this? A weird bed? It's not long enough. What's weird
about this? Why? It's like a big marshmallow bed. Morning yet? Where the hell am I?
Like in Motel, no fake. Where am I? Like the dream reality is like shifting around.
King size beds. Can I open this? Can I open this? Uh, pills in here. Oh, take the pills.
Take them. All right. I took more of them. Oh, that's, I hate that.
Okay, snap, snap, snap, snap, snap, snap. Oh, it's the duck. It's the duck.
It's the scariest fucking monster we've seen all night. Oh, shit. Okay. Go out, out, out, out,
out of the room. Out of the room. Out of the room. We can go, we can leave, right? We can get the
fuck out of here, right? He's going to be in my face. I thought it was really going to be this
one, like chasing us. I feel really fucked up. I'm going to be really honest with you.
This is what it feels like when you're shit faced. I, this is, this is, who made this game?
You've got to give this to like people to like, to like, this is like an education. This is
educational. Like this is fucked up. All right, get out. This is, this is some, this is exactly
what it's like. You nailed it. You nailed it. God damn it. Another hallway. It's coming. Here
comes the swan again. I'm going to turn around. I'm going to see a swan behind me. Oh, I'm out
of bounds. Okay. Oh shit. There's drugs in there. I think. I don't know.
But a police spokesperson has confirmed that the victim suffered multiple injuries and it is still
unclear if the victim drowned in the swamp or if he was killed before entering the water.
Okay. Police are investigating an unusual theme park swan boat, which was found close to the
victim's body. I think it might've been the killer. Information about a figure seen using the boat in
the early hours. Swan boat was seen fleeing the crime scene on the surveillance video of the
amusement park. Bring some booze with those pills.
That's scary. Oh shit. Oh, uh, mommy and daddy are on a vacation right now.
Fuck. Who are you? Was that me in the, was that me or them?
We're at the Pelican Motel now. We need to check out at the end of that road.
Now make sure that no one tries to slip away. Officer, I'm in here.
Officer. Officer. Officer. I'm in this room. Officer. I'll break this fucking thing if I have to.
Oh, he's talking, he's talking to me. Leave the room. This is dangerous.
Oh, safe. Road safe. Don't suffer alone. Code for the safe. What are you getting that from?
There might be a code in here. Ah, eight, four, five, six, seven, five. But I remember I've
write down. Oh, dough. I can't read it. Oh, seven, nine. Is that right? I really can't read it.
Six, two, seven. Is it six, two, seven, nine? Fucking do it. Six, two, seven, nine.
Wrong code. Officer, do you know what the, what the code is for all the safes?
What do you see? Key digits. Digits. Not four. Oh, that's easy. Postcard. Oh, postcard. Why is
it doing a creepy sound like? Ace of a safe shell. Oh, right. I heard it there. Greetings from New
Orleans. What's going on here? Bitch. Eight, four, three. Eight, four, three is the only three digit
number up here. Wait, why is the bathroom locked from the inside? I don't know. Eight, four, three.
Go to the bathroom. Go to the bathroom. I can't. It's locked from the inside.
Hear him? All right, I'm gonna do eight, four, three. God, give me a fucking break. Fork in, outlet.
Don't say that. Fork in, outlet. Where's that fork? All right, maybe can I break,
I can break the door open? Okay, it keeps, it's playing a sound. I'm looking for three digit codes,
like an asshole. Hugs. Always take them immediately. What does that do for me?
No writing on the bathroom wall or anything. Writing on this? Or pro-mav-zine? Or pro-ma-zine?
Three, two, three, two, eight. Three, two, zero. Let's go, buddy. I cannot leave.
Somebody in the bathtub. Somebody in the bathtub. Somebody in the bathtub. I knew there was a
little person there. Grade 20. Oh, give it to me. Is. Hey, I need the, what's the flashlight?
Puzzle, okay? I need the, I need the next piece. Bible. I'm gonna open that. Wait for me in the
lodge. Wait for me in the lodge. All right, I will. I have to look in the Bible. Wait for me in the
lodge. All right, let's go. Get that chair out of the way. The cops aren't there anymore.
Hide the page in the Bible. Actually, pretty brilliant. And wait for you in the lodge.
We know you're in there. Me? You better come out, buddy. Whatever doesn't kill you
makes you a stranger. Three. I thought I was gonna count to three. Wait, don't you come in on three?
The dead guy give me the Bible. Why the lodge? Why me? It was a bird. One who preys on the
weakness of others. Birds. All right, I'm gonna get this five more minutes.
Five more minutes. All right, that last chapter was actually really good.
That was very good. That was terrifying. That was very good. There are hints on your hand behind
that. Really? The eyes. The hips. Like a hip MRI. That is bird lungs.
Oh, that's a huge chair. That chair looks like it's made out of... This is like a human chair.
It looks like it's made out of blood. That's a normal chair. That's kind of... That's a weird
chair. That's weird. I don't like those. It's a weird chair, isn't it? It's a scary chair to me.
Literally a chair. I feel like if I was... I'd be scared of that chair. It looks like it's gonna
have knives shoot out of those little holes and like a shot through my back. Oh, what the
fuck? Are you kidding me, dude? Are you serious? Nice. Good. Oh. Like it. Don't like it. Oh.
Careful. There's a desk there. Excuse me. What are you doing? That's it. At least. When I just
bent... I guess not. I'm having like too much fun, but VR... I can't stream VR for more than five
hours, so I can't. All right. One minute. One more minute. VR is so much fun. It's just impossible
to do. I'm gonna take a bath. Don't worry. Get down here. Oh, nice degree.
Oh, look. It's so prestigious. Eastern Teaching Hospital. Wow. You're smarter than me because
you're a doctor. Oh, no. It's a face. Eyes. Moustache. Mouth. How did you get in here?
Where is he? What am I supposed to do? Are you gonna come down here?
Should I come down here and say something about it? That says something. I need a lamp.
That says something back there. It's written up there.
This was fun, but I gotta stop before I die. Postcard on the desk will pick up on it on
Halloween night. This is a lot of fun, though. All right. I'll give you my verdict. Chapter one
was awesome. Chapter two was not good at all. Chapter three was incredible. Chapter four,
we don't know yet. We don't know yet. Hey, I'll give you a hold on a minute for this one.
The Exorcist was awesome. That was really good. Really good. Dip five marshmallows in water and
then do what? What do you want me to do? Otto? Otto's gone. He wanted to go up. All right. Here's
the plan. Oh, thank you for joining me tonight. That was very, very fun. Very scary. I lost
probably a little bit of a little bit of time left in the end of my life because of all the screaming.
Exorcist was fucking crazy. Anyways, next stream is going to be Watch Dogs Legion. I'm going to
play it at lunch. I'm probably only going to play for one day, but I mean, I've been, it could,
there's potential that it could be at least fun to play for like four or five hours.
Is it sponsored? No. Trust me. Don't worry. I'll like swear about the game a thousand times.
Trust me. I'm probably going to tell you the game's terrible. I'll play the game for like
four hours and go, this game's fucking awful. I hate this. I don't know. No, it's not a sponsored
stream. It's not. I just want to look, I'll be honest. I want to play as the old lady and
strangle somebody and then this room will be over. I'm just going to have a team of old ladies.
Everybody that's on my team is going to be over the age of like 70 and we're just going to strangle
people and I'll do like four missions. I got what I wanted out of it. And then after that,
we're going to play Little Hope with Italics and Italics is going to do a co-op stream.
Last time me and Italics played, we did Man of Medan. So fast forward like a year and we're
going to do Little Hope now. And then Halloween night, we're going back in here and I'm going to
do more of this shit on Halloween night. It'll be fun. So you won't see me for the next two days
and then we'll go bang, bang, bang three days in a row. Are you Brad? Let's see. I am wiped out
though. I'm fucking tired. I'll, uh, I'll see you guys in a couple of days. I'm going to actually
crouch down here. It's a shit load of people here. I didn't even look at like the view count.
I thought you guys were just saying like 9k, 10k Andy again. Man, there's a, you back there. You
back there. I saw what you just did. You think you can hide that from me? I saw what you just did.
I think I can't fucking notice that. Well, now you're a 7k. Well, the stream's over. People
leaving. Uh, yeah, I'll see you guys a couple of days. Thanks for watching. Thanks for the subs.
We're going to show them right now. Here they come. Let's go over and see if any of the, anything
major, uh, sub or donation wise happened because I can't really see them. Take a look. I'm going
to wait here staring at the screen for two days. I think that might not be a great idea. That's
what I do. Uh, we had the 10 community subs from Princess Hotcakes and then five from Nidhogg
from Nidhogg Man. Thank you both of you. That rounds out the community subs for today.
No, I'm not streaming till Halloween. No, no, no. I'm streaming Watch Dogs Legion when it comes out.
Even just kneeling down like this. I put my knees on the ground and I'm just leaning forward.
I'm like about to break in half. Let me lean back for a sec. Oh, god damn it. What happened to me?
What actually happened? I have no idea. I'm still on it. I'm still punching at it. Grab a chair. No,
I'm okay. I'm okay. Otto didn't do anything wrong. No, he didn't. He's a good boy.
Raid Ross. Uh, sure. What's he doing? No, not Ross from Friends. What? Ross from Friends.
All right, we're gonna go say hi. We'll go, uh, go tell Ross hello. Rubber ninja. We played Fa-
you know, maybe we'll play Phasmophobia again soon. I mean, it's Halloween. Maybe we'll try
to get like a Halloween Phasmophobia thing again. That'd be cool. All right, go tell Ross I said
hello. They're playing Super Mario Maker 2. They're, uh, I believe he's making levels.
He's doing level fixing. Let's find out. I will see you guys in a couple of days. Have a great rest
of your night. Goodbye. Thanks for watching. Thanks for sticking around as always. Take care. See you soon.