Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2. Oh, that spy got in the damn way.
That heavy just got in the way too. Playing- what the hell is going on? Oh, it's a heavy down here.
I can't even tell you what's going on right now on my head.
So this is-
What the hell just happened right there?
Okay, so I'm wearing an unusual hat in real life. It's a burning Jerma head. They go for
like two refined metal. They're pretty cheap, but it really hurts to put this on. My whole head gets on fire,
and unfortunately, you get like third degree burns on your head, which is not good.
But anyways, I thought it would be funny just to have this on.
Unusual hat in real life. When I saw this effect in my little webcam manager there, I had to put it on.
I didn't even know it existed. But anyways, what am I doing as a sniper right now? I'm being a real-
Oh!
Get that guy too. Come on! Come on, hit the spy! They're the goddamn spy and I can't-
I'm gonna- Wow.
Look at this banana peel. Holy geez. That's been sitting there for like five days.
I probably ate that before I went to PAX. That's pretty gross.
So let's keep going here. Playing on 2 for it, which- I got actually a lot of requests to do this.
People want to see me play on 2 for it, and I really don't think I have one video on 2 for it.
This is probably the only one. Maybe one more. You know what? Screw this.
Okay, don't hit him. There we go!
Scope sniper. Doing default sniper pretty much. We're gonna get this cap right now, aren't we? We better.
Are you real or what? I don't know. I don't trust anybody.
Don't trust anybody. Oh, how come that didn't register?
Get it! Get him! Get somebody through this little hole.
So scared right now. Scope sniper on 2 for it. Just nonsense. That is a spy. Can't stand in the same way.
What are you doing over here, man? Oh, let's just stay-
Oh! God! How did this guy even get up here? How did a heavy just like waltz up here?
Now, there's one. Let's keep it rolling here, boys. Let's eat a raw, gross, rotten banana peel while we're at it.
I'm gonna throw that away. Holy- Oh, no, that's two! That's two scores right there.
All right. All right. I'm gonna go down to the bottom this time. I'm not gonna stay up here. Or am I?
Ah! Get out! I'm gunning for you, you mongrels!
Right here. I'm gonna stay right here for a minute. For just a minute. My unusual hat is like really itchy.
Is nobody gonna come out here? What's gonna happen? Come on.
They just capped one. Did that heavy just go all the way through and cap everything? Yes!
You're gonna get it right here, man. You are getting this right here. I'm gonna shoot you right in your face.
It's gonna go through your teeth and out the back of your neck. And no, it's gonna be this heavy, actually.
I'm gonna get the right opportune moment. No, it's gonna be this guy instead. Hey, it still works, right? I killed somebody.
Oh, you. Oh, you. Get out of town.
Don't want you here no more. And you are not- Yeah, you're real. Okay. I'm okay with that.
You're a real spy. Do your thing, man. What did that other- Heavy! Oh, you're dead heavy.
Boink! They're gonna win. They've capped twice now. We had two caps in the beginning. And where is this son of a-
I think it's time to go back upstairs.
Try to defend the intelligence because that's not gonna be good. If we just lose right now, I'm gonna be very mad.
Hey. Hey. No, you're real. How- What is- What's with all these like crazy heavies? At least we got a sentry now.
That's good. Good. Good. Spy is up here. Bang! Two in a row. Whoa. Where's this guy? Come here, you.
I'm gonna get this pyro. Oh, you know what? Let's- Let's cap this right now. Come on. Support. Support.
I would have got him. He has no idea. Oh, baby! Oh, baby! Am I gonna cap this right now?
Sniper cap for the win? Is this- Is this gonna happen? Whoa, what am I stuck on? Oh, the stupid teleporter.
Oh, this is gonna be a sniper cap right here, guys. This is gonna win it right now. Hell freaking yeah. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Wait, is it- Yeah, it's playing the three.
Bang, baby. Well, that was a nice round. I say, uh, go grab yourself one of these unusual hats.
They don't go for very much. And, uh, that's gonna wrap it up here, guys. So,
thank you guys so much for watching. Really do appreciate it. And, uh, now I gotta go douse my head in water
to get rid of this unusual hat. So, uh, see y'all next time. And, of course, take care, everybody.