Hey, how you doing? Welcome, everybody. Welcome back to live. I just pressed the
button and ran downstairs and grabbed water. Uh, let me make a tweet. We can start to play more
gotcha force. I'm pretty into it. I want to collect more fucking robots. No, stupid trapeze
simulator. I didn't even. Okay. I'm going to be honest. I forgot. I, I, I completely didn't even,
I forgot everything. I hit the stop streaming button and instantly it deleted from my brain.
So what, what do you, what are you talking about? Like, can you guys somebody be specific with me?
Like what, what is there a certain website? Is it a gone steam or is it a, are you serious?
What it's on Reddit trapeze simulator Reddit. Okay. The number one. Okay. When I type in trapeze
simulator Reddit, the first search is Jerma promises to do trapeze simulator. Uh, what,
what is this? I know the first, okay, let me just go to this promises to do trapeze simulator. Okay.
So what is it that when I type in trapeze simulator, there's nothing here. It's just,
I'm the third result. When you type in trapeze simulator, I'm the third that this, that exact
thing is the third result. And then there's this real simulation. It's like a, an EU right here.
This is not even real. Okay. Well, all right. It's excuse me for thinking it was real.
Like this game has released 500 times as different things, different objects.
So how would I know this was fake? Replace the word trapeze with another weird, hard to hold
on to object. And that game has been made. Anyways, I got, I got to tweet that. Okay. Also,
I have a, I have something to tell you yesterday. We talked about this a little bit, but I'll give
you a little bit more details. Uh, there's a few things to talk about here. Uh, things talking
about number one, they may even be showing themselves right now. We do have new, some new
mods as of right now, I believe there are three new mods going through the process of adding mods,
mod apocalypse four. That's right. Yeah. Four, four. There are four new mods. I did this yesterday
and I don't even know. Uh, so we got, they're going to be a lot more of a presence of they'll
catch you. Oh, no, no, they'll catch you now. Uh, also on top of that, welcome them there.
There's been a process to bring some more on and we're not quite done.
Still some people would think we're going to be bringing on two. Besides that, also,
I'm pleased to, to announce to you right now that, um, on, on, you ready? On May 15th
and May 16th, Easy Bay Govan stream and green screen DLC free back to back a couple of weeks
from now. It has been confirmed has been locked in. That's my birthday. Happy birthday. I can't
wait to do like a special birthday thing in front of the green screen. Why? That's a suggestion,
right? Is it a suggestion to like come in and it's your birthday and I'm like here for your
birthday and I can sit down and I enjoy your birthday. I mean, I've got, I have to give you
everything possible. Like, Oh, I want, I've always wished German was at my birthday. I'm going to
green screen myself celebrating your birthday and singing and stuff. And you can just, I'll,
I'll open my mouth in a weird way so you can literally just put any, any name there.
Like, I'll be like, Hey, and like open my mouth, Steve, you can do whatever you want.
Parasocial relationship. I was going to record myself just pretending to be your friend for like
three hours. I'm sitting, we're going to sit in your room together. We're going to watch TV.
How about this? All right. I will, I will green screen myself reacting to the entire
Witcher Netflix series, right? Like you won't be able to, it'll just be keyed.
It'll just be reacting off screen and you can queue it up. So then it could be like,
you know, I'm sitting there hanging out, just keyed into your living room while we watch the
Witcher three, the Witcher's entire sequence together. How fucked up would that be?
Rift tracks? No, no, no, no, no. It would just be me just hanging out in your living room with you.
We're just watching the Witcher on Netflix. That's, that's, uh, that's a probably a bad idea.
Well, there's a really hard TV show. Are you making a joke and a reference that the Witcher
three is like bad game or something? This is not a joke. Not stop. I know you, you will be kissed by,
by a love life. If you repost this four times in stream Lego Lord of the Rings. All right.
Let's play. Let's play. Uh, new mods. Shut it down. Hey, we got four new mods. Hey,
shut it down. Hey, those, those new blades need to be, need to be used, right? They're brand new.
They just came out of the blacksmith. Oh, swords. They haven't been touched. There's still this,
those new swords. All right. Come on. Come on. VR Josh. Uh, you haven't even peeled the plastic
off yours yet. Come on. Come on. Let's go use them. I know. No, but I want to leave the plastic
on as long as I can. Cause I, I want it to be like new and I want to take it, just take the
peel plastic off. VR Josh left. Oh, well, okay. Oh, okay. Oh, I see. Oh, I see how it is.
All right. Let's play. Welcome back everybody. That was a vehicle. Very. Yeah. I can't help it.
He got it from me. You know, we, we hang out so often that he's, you know,
the other way around. What do you mean? We hung, we hang out so often that like, I just kind of do
some of his things. I got it from him. Full desk. Thanks. Hey, wait, what's on this desk?
There's a game cube. There's a TV changer beeper, two game cube controllers, block. Eh, kind of,
that's kind of a boring desk actually. No, I don't want to do verses. I'd say that's so cool
that you could do that though. Eraser is kind of pog though. Yeah. Veto the game. No, it's not
going to happen. It's not going to happen. Not going to happen. I love this game. I'm going to
play this shit out of this. It's just not going to happen. Let's take a look at our force. All
right. Well, I got to figure out what I was doing. Play mega man legends. This game actually is just
plays exactly like mega man legends, except it's got dashes and dodges and toys. Lisa,
the painful waiting room. All right. I don't know. I don't know how many times I have to say
I am not. Can you? All right. I'm sort of green. All right. I was going to green screen myself
playing all of Lisa, the painful and like you can just sit in your living room and we'll play
it together. It's going to be a long green screen stream. It's going to be like 12 days long. Okay.
Now let's go. Who do I want for support? Nana. Why do that when you can just play it? Because
I want to be in your living room. I want to be in your living room. I got to get this right.
It's Jerma in your living room. I'll be in your living room tomorrow afternoon. You and me having
so much fun playing Lisa, the painful. So if you're into playing Lisa, the painful,
then by all means join me tomorrow in your living room. Greg. Combine is going to be in my house.
Now he's actually going to do it. You know, dumb like that makes me laugh, but like I can't,
I can't do that in front of the, but that wouldn't make it. I can't, that would take too much time.
What's a really, really short game that I could beat in like 30 minutes?
No, that's, I'm not doing this. By the way, this character is so much better now.
It's like, it's unbelievable how much better he is. I missed bits, big bits, big bits. Uh, yeah,
you're right. $5,050 from phylactery lich. That's a huge amount of money. Thank you again for like,
essentially what has turned into about $50 a day or a stream. It's insane. You're insane.
It's so much money. I can't even believe you still give me this much money.
Thank you. It's crazy. I can't, I can't even believe it. I say, don't you ever stop playing
gotcha force. If you haven't figured it out, the yellow icons on the map are side missions
and the orange ones are important. I'm not gonna know. I'm, I've liked this game and I'm going to
play it. I, I ain't going to get beautiful Joe bullied out of this one. Nope. Cause beautiful
Joe was, uh, like $11 and this one was 250. I ain't going to get bullied out of this one.
Nope. Not a chance. Not a chance in health. And this is one of my like favorite game cube
game. Yup. No way. I'm going to beat the shit out of this game. He loves this game. I do. It's
just fun to play. And that's what matters. Are you having fun playing? Don't worry. I'll, I'm,
I'm going to record a green screen for every game you've ever wanted me to fucking play in your
living room with you. I don't, I won't even need to stream anymore. I'm just going to green screen
myself playing the entire steam library and I'll make a, I'll make a bot that's able to have,
replace every name with your name. You just put it in and anytime your name comes up, it's just,
it's me addressing you and I'll charge a modest fee for each video game. Hang out in your living
room session. I don't know, like 50 cents. That's a good idea. That would be so why not just a
live stream 50 cents. Yeah. You know, what you do is you, you, you call my, you call my one 900
number I'm going to set up, which is a dollar 80 a minute. And it's me in your living room on your
phone. Holy shit. Nice teleport ninja sex line. All right. Can you imagine, let's just briefly go over
this back when it was like four or $5 a minute. Holy shit. Can you imagine sitting on that phone
for more than 10 to 20 minutes? That's absurd. That's expensive. It would cost me
$2. I'm so glad that I have turned on the mature content filter for the channel.
Very necessary at this point, I think. Uh, who's the new guy? Ooh, arm cutter, double
Kamaitachi and then ninpo teleport and then teleport slash. Teleport's a fun one to say.
That's a, that's a radio word. Teleport. Teleporting. Teleport. Teleport. Because the
E and the L and the E. Tele. Teleport. It's like saying W. W is a fun one to say too.
And even with a lot of consonants in the middle, they're a lot of fun. www.teleport.com. Yeah,
that's fun. That was fun to do. Confuse his enemies with his smooth moves. Use the ninpo
teleport while moving to throw them off the scent and wait for your chance and hit them with the
teleport slash. Oh, I'll try it. He's expensive though. He's 400. What can I get rid of? Eh,
I got to clean up my toy shelf. This is bothering me. Can't afford anything else.
I got to clean up my Reddit. I was going to call it my Reddit shelf in the title,
but that's just dumping more charcoals onto this fire. I'm no, I could have, but that's just me
embracing the fact that that's what that is. And I kind of don't want to do that.
Okay. Choke on the joke. Choke on the joke smoke.
Oh, this guy, I like this guy. I like the little wing thing. What does this one do? Oh shit. Is
that like just a fucking, you just don't get hurt? How does that work? You can charge it.
Oh, it's okay. It's just you phase out. Does it hurt? If I get in there, is it going to be
hard to use? Play Minesweeper. This game sucks. Sorry. My Minesweeper is not a Minesweeper.
Minesweeper. Not enough consonants in there. I don't like that one. Sorry. Oh fuck. Yeah,
this guy's not very good. Maybe you like him. What about his melee? Wasn't a bunch of flying
people. Oh, that guy sucks. He's $400. Look at how much better this dude is. And he's like,
he's $500 and still so much better. Omega LOL 400 or Omega LOLs. Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
Do it. Do it. Do it. Do it. There's more huge money coming. Hold on. Huge money. Is this on
the Commodore? No. This is on the Nintendo GameCube. Just trying to level up my crew
so I can do the secret mission. The Nintendo ShipCube. Wow. That was clever. That was clever.
Clever one. Oh, that was satisfying, but it didn't hit. Come on. I'm gonna stop it. Stop what?
Thank you. Fairy-kun gave $50. 5,000 bits. Another $50 drop. They say, hey, Jermbo.
I'm not sure if you saw, but the Pentagon released a video showing unidentified aerial phenomenon.
That's a good one to say too. Unidentified aerial phenomenon. Thanks for giving me one of those
cool ones, which basically just means UFO. And I really want to rant about UFOs and aliens
from my fellow Redditor. Um, well, I mean, is it weird to think that because you have a flat
screen TV that aliens had to have existed? All right. Like, we went from like putting
corn in the ground to being able to talk to people through like a piece of plastic
and they can hear you 7,000 miles away. That's alien fucking technology. It has to be.
Ooh, a magnet robot minus. Somebody just wrote it all capitals. True. Oh, come on. Not another
normal night. Give me like a pro night. Give me like a hard mode night. Give me an insane night.
What's the minus? All right. Do I make like a comedy team or do I make like a plus and minus
team? All right. Well, what's the difference? Magnet scope, magnet arm and beam. Okay.
The magnet robot minus was created by the natural resources unit. His magnet scope enables him to
collect materials like, yeah, the Pokemon or mines. His beam is used to modify collective.
So what's the difference? Why are you $10 more expensive to use? Oh, I'm sorry. Why do you cost
10 more battery? I mean, I'll try. I'll try everything once each character gets one chance
to impress me. Otherwise they're going right in the fucking recycling. I got to clean this up.
Looks like shit. All right. Let's, uh, that's fine. The name is Jumaas, but fairy cone. Thanks for
the $50 and the interesting thought project about aliens. Yes. I, I, I do believe that.
I think that has to be alien somewhere. There has to be. All right. You telling me if we're
supposed to be, if we're supposed to be some kind of, all right, we're going to get a little
philosophical here. So if, if like God created man and God created earth, whatever, don't you
think he made probably like fucking a hundred of these? Why would you make just one? If you had the
power to, why wouldn't you just make like a hundred? How would you make one? Or if you were like a group
of aliens that were like, you know what, let's fucking let's blow something up and make a bunch
of cells. You would do that like a thousand times. Wouldn't you? How do I ban you? What? I'm just,
I'm just talking. I'm just, this is a thought project. This is, I didn't say, by the way,
everything I believe. It's a thought. I said quote thought project before we started.
I don't know if you, if you were God and you made this like cool, like if you made like water
and you, and you built like this puzzle that is land on earth and shit, you made like,
you made like dinosaurs and monsters and aliens, would you just get you done?
No, you would do that like a bunch of times. Like, oh, that was fun. Those of you aren't people here.
Would you paint one fucking picture? Would you make one painting and go, that's it. That's the
best one. That's the only one I'm going to do. I'll never make another painting in my whole life.
It's the best. I'll never, you, I'll never pick up tools again. Oh, you, you would just draw,
you'd create, you would make, you would, you would create. Like, do you know what do you think God
has in his office? Just a hanging picture of earth. And he's the annoying, what, people come over and
he's like, yeah, I drew that. I made that 5,000 years ago. Nice. Yeah. You tell us every time.
Yeah. And he is, his whole house is just covered in like earth memorabilia. No, you would have,
you would do this millions of times. If you had the power to like point your finger and like,
and there's a fucking giraffe. You know how many characters I made in Spore? How many hours did
you spend in Spore? Well, I guess it probably took a long time. No, it took like 10, it looks
seven days to make earth. No way. I spent, I spent, I spent at least like 25 days playing Spore.
There's no way. Just telling you, like if we're, if we're at experiment, people are like, wait,
we might be in a simulation. I don't know. Be the creationist. No, I'm just saying like this,
probably a bunch of like earths potentially, but I don't know. If you were God, wouldn't you make
like earth again, but just make people have no noses just because you, that's just, I decided
to take their noses off this time on earth six trillion. How many of you guys that are art people
here? Because I mean, I'm one of you. I'm like, I'm okay. I come from a video editing standpoint
on this. You know how many times I've like cut shit out and like redone, redone the whole thing?
Like we're probably not supposed to have hands. That was like a, that was like a first draft.
And then like God's looking down going, holy shit. Yeah. I remember that. It was my first painting
there. And look at the way they made their fucking hands. Whoa. That was so wrong. I've improved so
much on earth two million. We are the first draft. Okay. Somebody said we are the first draft and
then a sad face. This guy's actually pretty good. I actually kind of like this. I like the beams.
I like the beams. They're quality. I can see why you're worth 10 more battery points.
You're all permanently on the team. Why would you not be? This is right. Then why doesn't God
appear and yell to you? This is that what I'm saying is right. Um, do me a favor and yell to
your Sims. I don't, they're not going to respond to you. Why? Why? How come in the Sims four? When
you go, Hey, Hey, Julie, Julie, look at me. I'm up here. Fucking hear you. You'll pay for this.
My Sims talk to me sim, but Sims are not real, but, uh, we will, but how can you be so certain
that we're real? They obviously that was, Oh, finally I got a healer. Turn them off. Turn them
up. Oh yeah. We get big bits. I get it. Hold on. Oh, we did. Our luxury again, gave $50,
$5,000 more bits from phylactery, which brings it to a hundred dollars in bits today. Right now.
You say German, don't let German's alien rant distract you from the fact that he owns and
wears a crystal healing bracelet. I don't wear cry. I don't, I don't wear a crystal healing
bracelet. Oh, look, I got, I just, I have, I have a little bit of, look, I have, listen,
listen to me. Look, I look, I have a little bit of black tourmaline
because I thought it was cool. Not because I think it has magical powers.
And I paired that with some quartz to, uh, clean my blood and sift my, uh, through my kidneys and
make me have cleaner pee or something. I don't know. It was interesting. It's interesting.
I don't care. I don't think it, I don't think it's real. I don't think it's real. Look,
okay. Let me preface it again. I don't think that's real. It's just an interesting thought project.
It was, it's a thought project. Why'd you do it then? Why do people wear fucking like,
why do people wear rings and bracelets? I don't know, because they like, it's an accessory,
but I can't have an accessory. I don't think my accessories have magical powers.
I just liked the idea of having like a little accessory and like the black tourmaline looked,
it shined well and it was polished. Don't people believe, doesn't believe, wait, wait, wait, wait,
doesn't believe in God, but believes in healing crystals. I don't, I don't believe in healing
crystals. I, I believe, I believe in like medicine and science. All right. Let's, let me, let's be
clear. I believe in medical science. Okay. Do I have to say that? He's, now he's a Redditor.
That's a Redditor comment. Medical doctors. Oh, he's so enlightened. Why is me saying that
believe in medicine of like an enlightened Redditor. Are you guys like smearing garlic
in your assholes? What's, what are you talking about? He's an edge lord. Oh, thank God. I put
that mature content filter on. Seems like I'm getting a lot of, a lot of mileage out of that
one. I don't, the healers, no, crashed here, crash. All right. It's time for me to,
uh, uh, Bitslave. Oh, Super Bruce. Oh, Super Bruce. Super Frog. Thanks for the 10 community
subs. Super Bruce. 10 subs and then $50 from Bitslave. 5,000 Warp Bits. What's up, Jerma
Bitslave here. I'm currently trying to pass two kidney stones at the moment. Very painful.
I also recently got my League of Legends account permabanned. Stop playing. Yeah, stop playing.
I can just start reading books. You know what I mean? Like every time you have the urge to play
League, just read like two chapters of a book or something. It's too stressful and it's going to
make you mad and angry at stuff. Uh, it caused me worse pain than my stones, not because of the ban
because of this. Oh, how much money have I spent in the League of Legends? Here's how much you've
spent in League of Legends. Oh, damn. That's a lot of money. Damn. That's a lot of money.
Should I want, you want me to share this? That's a lot of money. Play Billy the egg, by the way.
I will. That's a lot. Damn. All right. Well, this makes me feel better about how many card
packs I bought in Hearthstone. You don't have any like, there's not like personal info on here,
right? All right. Here. We're going to do a big reveal. They said, share it. Damn. That's a lot.
That's a lot. And now you're, well, take that as a damn. That's a lot of money. Uh, hey, it's all
right. It's, it's just, it's, don't worry about it. It's all good. Don't go back. Let's put it this
way. Don't go back. You know what game you can play that's free. Doesn't cost anything. It's
completely free. Kickball. It's free. Well, it's not, you're going to buy the ball and those are
like probably $5. It's fun. It's like a combination of, of soccer and baseball. Just be careful
because although the ball is very, very, it bounces easily and it's like a big bouncy ball
and it makes a cool sound. I know the sound is awesome, but just be careful. I've seen plenty of
plenty of pictures, especially teachers that used to be the picture. Cause I know that everyone was
concerned about this. The teachers would always be the picture because some kids kicked it way
too hard and right into the teacher's face. Um, just be careful. Uh, you've got to be staying
back. That happened. It just happened at least three or four times with me growing up and their
glasses. They spent a bunch of time with their glasses, putting the glasses back on. It's like,
holy shit, this got rocked. Just be careful. It's gonna be dangerous, but it's fun. I'm supposed
to be playing a game. Thanks for the 5,000 bits. Remember was a delinquent. What? No, we want more
rants, more rants. No, I don't even know. I don't, I'm not even ranting. I'm doing a thought project.
That's such a Redditor thing. I, this thing is, I don't, how do I kill this thing? How do I like
bury this Redditor thing? How do I do that? I know I have to have something else even more ridiculous
and embarrassing happen so that you forget about the Redditor thing. Okay. I'm going to like take
a picture of, I'm going to have like a picture of, I'm going to turn the camera on one day and my
mouth is going to be full like hot dogs and like marshmallows. And I'm going to be like,
and be, I'm going to be like, I'm the Marshmallow Man, I'm the Marshmallow Man. And people are going
to be like, holy shit, he's fucking crazy. And then they, you'll, that'll be all you talk about
for like six months. Perfect. 12 year old. Dude, I love this guy. He's got a sick move. Tom Green.
I have hot dogs in my mouth. I'm a hot dog man. I have marshmallows in my mouth. I'm a Marshmallow
Man. I'm a Marshmallow Man. I'm a Marshmallow Man. I'm a Marshmallow Man. I'm a Marshmallow Man.
I'm a Marshmallow Man. I'm a Marshmallow Man. I'm a Marshmallow Man. I'm a Marshmallow Man.
Yeah. I mean, that's funny. It was funny. It was kind of funny. I'll tell you one of my favorite,
the absolute best thing that I've ever seen Tom Green do. He did his show back on MTV. He was
like a weird, wild guy. He did all kinds of crazy shit. But this is the, my favorite thing that he
ever did. Not like, wow, remember when he went and he like smashed the calculator? Remember when he
like peed his pants? No. He's sitting on a bench next to this old woman who's holding a cup. You
can't see what's in the cup. And he continuously is interviewing this old woman. And he goes,
hey, I'm sitting here having, enjoying a nice Mountain Dew. And she's like, no, it's just a
water. And she starts laughing. And he's like, oh, well, I mean, I'm sitting here. You're having a
great time. We're hanging out on this bench. You're enjoying your Mountain Dew. And she's like,
no, it's a water. This is a water. And he's like, oh, wow, what a refreshing Mountain Dew.
That seriously was like, I thought it was the funniest thing ever. I thought it was really
funny. Show it. By the way, you can't find this. I've already looked for it. I've already searched
for this. I've typed in like Tom Green, Mountain Dew, Tom Green, sits with old lady on bench.
It doesn't exist. It's gone forever. I didn't, I know I did not imagine it. It was the Mandela,
Mandela effect. No, no, no, this happened. And then he keeps going. Do you like the way I dance?
Do you like the way I dance? And she's like, get out of here. This is water.
Wait, you got it? Wait, how did I not find this? When was this uploaded?
No, this is fucking not even it. You're liars. This is when he's doing the daddy, would you like
some sausage thing? And was, yeah, no, here, here, here. It's not it. I've looked, trust me.
I seriously have looked for this. Tom Green, delicious soda. Wait, is this the delicious
soda? No, this is not it. This is not it. This is, it's an old lady on a bench.
This is not it. Oh no, this is important. Is this it? This is it. Tom Green, delicious soda. No,
it's an old lady sitting on a bench. He dreamed it. You imagined it. No, I didn't. It's combined
memories. No, no, it's not. No. No, it's not it. Did you find it? This is it. Somebody got it.
No, this is not it. What, what, is this it? No, it's not. No. I'm telling you, I looked at this
for like six years. You guys are wrong. Is it mixed memories? Here's a script. Hold on,
there's a script for it. Here's the script. Okay, I have to go. It's not this one. It's a pie one.
All right, I'm going to, that's combined memories. I'm going to lose my fucking mind.
Park bench. You're just relaxing here today, enjoying a cigarette and a glass of Mountain Dew.
That's water, I'll have you. No. Do you drink Mountain Dew? No. Do you drink Mountain Dew? No.
Do you drink Mountain Dew? Hey, what are you doing? Okay, I'm going to do my little dance for you
while you drink your water and then we'll go. Okay. Oh my god. There's no video.
That was the line.
There it is. Glass of Mountain Dew. All right, it was, all right, it was, I thought it was,
it was funny. I thought it was funny. I was like 15. I don't know. It's funny.
But this is the worst joke of 2020 is I didn't make this joke. I'm reminiscing. I didn't like
teleport back in time and become Tom Green and do the Mountain Dew joke.
All right, what's the team look like? Looks good. Mixed memories. All right, do I have, am I good
enough to do the, the secret one? No sound. I got you. Okay, here we go. No, it's mine. A baby
like you doesn't deserve a gotcha board, right? Kindly offered to use your gotcha board for you.
You should accept his generous offer. What are you guys doing? Stop bullying. Yeah. Oh right,
there was a video game here. Right, I forgot. It's been like 25 minutes of talking about
fucking aliens and how Tom Green was a funny reference. All right, I'm gonna, I gotta play well.
All right, it's, wait, positive versus negative. Who wins? All right, get in there and punch.
Actually, no, stay back, stay back, stay back. Ah, you got me. Punch, punch,
twirl. All right, good. I might get something good from this. I'm excited. Whoa, what the,
I thought that was my, no, it's not my ally. Remember, this hasn't, it hasn't been a game
this full time. It's just been a camera pointed at your pants. Okay, now that's funny. That would
be very funny. All right, we got some good trades going on here. This guy's gonna die.
There we go. All right, we're doing well. All right, good trades on the, on, on the negative.
Now we close it up. Thurma, your Reddit penis is out. Oh, is it? Oh, by the way,
somebody gave me a bunch of gold on Reddit. I have, I have, is that, okay, it's 200 gold a lot.
How much is that? It is, it's like an insane amount. It's 200. I don't know, somebody thinks
that's really funny that I have like a ton of Reddit gold. 200 is fucking insane. Am I,
I'll make sure I'm saying this right. Is there like other currency too? I have like three of them.
Okay, let's see. Yeah, I have 201.9k karma and 200 coins. What do I, what do I do with this?
Okay, where do I see that? Is there a way I can see how many coins I have? Reddit coins, 200.
Guys, 200 coins is worth like 60 cents. Ooh, thunder robot. You guys are telling me that I
had like $5,000 worth. Oh, okay. What is karma? Can you, all right. Why is there like a red dead
redemption thing on Reddit? Does this track like how many banks I've robbed? I don't understand.
What is karma? Ooh, hammer knight. Pretending not to know. I actually don't. I don't know what,
what that means. How high can it go? Is there a maximum it can go? By the way,
I'm glad we actually got those. How high can karma go? Reddit gold redemption. Seems pretty good.
Reddit gold redemption. Thunderwire. Ah, it's this guy. When are you going to do an AMA?
Why would I do an AMA when you can just ask any question and I will just probably answer it.
Reddit AMAs are just Jerma one guys. Like that's why I don't know why I did. There's no point.
The robot type got you board who belongs to the special attack machinery unit.
This Thunderwire shows its true power when strung between allies. Walk onto an ally to set it up.
He's a support, but they get hammer night on a POG. He's got a cool outfit on rolling
hammer and hammer shot. This got you. Borg is warrior in the night board court is a shield
and a hammer, which he can throw at enemies. Use the rolling hammer to blow away your foes.
Give him a try. Do a Reddit polygraph saying things that I don't have. I don't know what they are.
Um, okay. Who do I? We'll try the thunder robot too. They all fit. No, you're too expensive.
Or maybe you're too expensive and then we'll put a ninja. All right. I got to clean this up.
I know I keep saying that I keep opening up my closet and seeing this and going, I got to clean
this and I never do. Let's do this other one. Pro rock. What? Stop playing games in the wrong
aspect ratio. Uh, this is the game that was 480 P that's being blown up and upscaled to 720,
which is being streamed to you at what are you talking about? You want to put this in four by
three? Why would I do that? No, because it's being upscaled to 720. It'll be funny. It's too
stretched. No, it's not. It isn't. Trust me. This is how, okay. Remember this is the Wii.
So it's going through the Wii and the Wii is taking it and this is just playing a GameCube
game on a Wii. This is what it looks like. Actually, this dude's pretty good. I like the
ball. The ball, this guy's good. I think I found a character I like. That's good straight line.
Plus he kind of looks like a ninja turtle. I like him. That does a lot of damage. He's good.
Look at how good he is. All right. He does not have a combo. That's good to know. He's got a
shield too. Look at this dude. Sorry. He did a lot. All right. Thunder. All right. So let's do
lightning zap. So now we're connected. Where are we? This has to go through an ally. He's just
spraying everywhere. How do I target an ally? Z is lock on. Well, yeah, but I can't. I'm trying
Isn't this the one that goes to an ally? Z. Hold Z. Hold Z. Hold Z. Z. Is my ally dead?
Oh, he's dead. It's all right. Let's just fucking end this. Oh shit. Nice. That's what we call
performance. Performance anxiety. No, that's called performance. Although I gotta be careful
because I don't want to lose. Oh boy. I'm going to lose. What do I have left? Oh, that's not good.
It is actually time to get serious. Oh, it's fine. Oh, you motherfucker. No, I got too
caught up in not. I don't know. This little kid sucks. This thing sucks too. I like you. You can
stay. All right. We need a heavy hitter. You. You're up. You. You go first. 4-3 or die.
You don't want it in 4-3. I have to unplug the HDMI cables. I don't even have the other cables.
All right. Here we go. Let's try this again. Do it in OBS. But then I have to recalibrate it all.
No, it's going to take forever for me to fix it. Hold on. You ready? Sure. Authentic.
You don't want it like this. Yes, we do. Yes, we do. We do. What? You don't. This is like.
No, I'm going back. No, I got to. All right. I got first of all, instead of paying attention
to the putting the game in four by three ratio, I've got to win. Get this dick head out of here.
How is this default enemy beating me around 640 by 40 like God intended?
Yeah, just like God intended. Attack. Attack. All right. You got to get away. Yeah, she's
died. Got it. All right. No, how are you still alive? You're annoying me. Face cam on a riot.
No, spit. Oh, that's a riot then.
Riot.
No, don't do that. Shut up.
Come on. I got to kill you. I'm so fucking mad. I'm so fucking mad. Oh, my God. These guys are
fucking killing me. Dude, dude, this is stupid. I need flyers. That's the issue.
I need flyers. Bad. I need flyers. All right. Let's move. Cool. Nice move to have there. It's
not for me to fuck. I'm just going to spam. All right. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're
good. Shit. What the fuck keeps happening to my shitty teammate? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
feel my wrath. Who's saying that? Me? All right. This is it. I win. Goodbye. Ivan, Ivan, Ivan, Ivan.
All right. Well, what was everybody freaking out about? Oh, no, right. Change this shit back.
I don't like this at all. Okay. No, I can't. That hurt. But all right. I'll meet you in the middle.
Okay. I'm going to meet you guys in the middle. I'm not going to do four, three. We're not going
to do 16 by nine. We're going to do like five by seven. We're going to do a standard piece of
computer paper. Not stretching it yet. Hold on. It hasn't been stretched. Okay. All right. All right.
See? There we go. Look at that. No, that's we can all agree with this. We can all agree.
Not too far. Big. Not too far. You know, small. And it fits. It looks good. I knew somebody was
going to call me a centrist. That's fine. It's off center. Don't worry. I got it.
Ooh, a wind Valkyrie. There we go. Okay. Now everyone can be happy. I got it. It's not off
center anymore. Hold on. Maybe a little bit. Now we can all be happy. See? Now it's like not quite
four, three, but it's not 16 by nine and it's not. You guys just. That's all I need to say is
the same as before. No, it's not. Before it was the whole screen. Compromise makes no one happy.
What's that old saying? As long as both sides are unhappy, that means you came to an agreement.
Who said that? Who said that? What's that? There's a famous quote from a guy from Pasta Italiano.
No, no, no, no, no. There's like a, oh, if there's, you can tell if both parties are unhappy,
then that means something worked out. Winston Churchill said it or something.
You can tell if he did a good job negotiating when both parties are unhappy. What'd he say?
That was not, that was not, that was not Adolf Hitler. It was not Adolf Hitler.
I know it was not. I was like fucking Winston Churchill or something.
No, what? Both. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What is it?
A good compromise is when both parties are dissatisfied. It was Larry David.
That was Larry David. Good. Perfect. Yes. He's quoting Hitler. No, I'm quoting Larry David.
Quoting Hitler. It was Larry David. Okay. No. All right. That's it.
Oh, I love Larry David. He's funny. And it was, yeah, it was Larry David.
That's a centrist ideology. Everyone should suffer. It's a computer aspect ratio.
Holy shit, man. I can't believe, I can't believe this streamer here is,
he's just, I mean, that's, I think Hitler said this. I wanted it 4-3. I wanted it 60 by 9.
This guy's Hitler. All right, let's go. Tunnel vision? No. German's in the back pocket
of big plasma trying to push his widescreen narrative. Big plasma. Oh, but it's, it's,
but it's classic. Well, how come you don't use it for every aspect ratio then?
Put your fucking, put your monitor right now in 4 by 3. 640 by 480. Good. Wow. So good. You like
it so much. Go boot up. Go, go boot up. Go boot up TF2 and put it in fucking 360p.
Let's see how long you crack like a fucking egg. I always have it in 360. No, no, no, no, no.
By the way, I'm not talking about the people that have the Dell computer all the way at the left.
On the shelf at Best Buy. I know I've been one of those people before. That's doing pretty well.
Generic computer. Yeah, you can always tell which one it is. It's all the way to the left
and it has no specs. Just says very fast processor, Intel, Intel processor. It's just
not even a quad core. Perfect for emails. There are no graphics card in there. It's integrated.
What do you mean? What do you mean Intel in 2020? But you don't Intel. I'm sorry. I like
the company that has the clean boost technology. Makes you whites whiter and your brights brighter.
This guy is really good. Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right.
All right. All right. All right. We got some new mods here. Take that plastic off. Take that
plastic off those swords and get ready to use them. Who's our next monkey? What is it? Oh,
finally we got our upgraded ninja. I'm not sure. I don't know what's going to be in here.
It's uncertain. It's another. Oh, we can make an entire ninja party. Yep. All right. This is
ridiculous. This is disgusting to me. This is disgusting me. Well, first of all, let's read
about our new friend. Almighty type. Pretty good speed. Shuriken. Shinobi. Yatana.
Nympho. Kage. Bunshin. I'm fucking human. I'm a human. You don't sit there and like play a game
and no one's listening to you when you do it. When you just sit there and you go,
oops. Don't worry. There's not like 5 trillion people that laugh at you.
I'm just a fucking human. All right. We produce all kinds of organisms inside of us.
Did you know that at any moment right now, at any given second, there are 500 trillion living
organisms in your body, inside of your rectum and your intestinal tract and some in your stomach,
you have acid. We're fucked. Humans are gross. Right now you have a bowl of acid inside of you
in your stomach and there's pee in there too. There's a bag of piss inside of you right now.
It's a bag filled with pee and there's shit in there. You have like a big shit going down
to you right now. It's in you right now, but he's disgusting. He burped. I'm eating. Yeah.
And there's all those gross like food particles going into your stomach right now. They're getting
burned by the acid and then like humans, we're disgusting animals.
Wow. I'm playing a video game. All right. Let's wait. I can duplicate myself with this clone.
This ninja's attacks are doubly deadly. Divide and conquer. Oh, I cause you've turned into two
people. We see iPod auto. It's iPod auto. Wait, what? Why does this dog have a, I don't get it.
That's not auto. What is this? There's a dachshund with like a shirt t-shirt on. That's auto.
That's not auto. That is not auto. Why? Where did you get this? It does look like auto. Auto
has a shorter face though. Auto's face is a little, it's not as long. This is very cute dog though.
I've had auto. Show the real auto. No, I need to clean up my room. Okay. Here we go.
Okay. Look at that attack. Look at this attack damage is insanity.
Shuriken, shinobi physical attack, and then shuriken cutter. Deadliest gotcha borg in the
assassination unit. The big shuriken on his back is made of extremely heavy, durable metal
so it can slash through anything. Well, let's make our team. I want you first. Okay. I want,
I like ball. I like the shield and ball. Oh yeah. We got this wind Valkyrie. Didn't we just get
wind Valkyrie? Probably one of the fastest characters in the game. Butterfly fan, magic
shot, big fan and fly. This angel borg enjoys flying and even sleeps while floating in the air.
The winds blowing through the mega borg planet are created by the wind Valkyrie.
Big fan. Oh, we'll give her a try. All right. Let's get this squared away here.
We're going to do the ninja unit up top. Yo, you too. I want you in here. All right. Where's,
we got flying figurines over here. What's this one? What's this one, two, three? What's this? I
don't get it. Why are these here? Robots are going to go down here. We're going to have robots. We're
going to have knights. Okay. Robots down here. Knights will be here. Oh, this is a ninja,
but I don't want you on my team. All right. This is a Kung Fu master, kind of like a boxer.
All right. Well, you go up here. Press Y to sort. Borg list. No, menu, change force name,
the lead of force. Borg list. Press Y to sword. No, you can't sort like that. We need a new force
name. We don't know what we want permanently. I can't ask the wait. We'll do, okay, flying over
here. Who else can fly? Fly. Okay. Then we're going to have knights and melee characters
underneath. Okay. Melee character. And then we're going to do it by cost. This is technically not
a melee character. It's just a robot. Okay. Claw bot. Okay. Here we go. We're going to have
shooter characters after this. Claw robot under robot. I like you better. So you go here. Oh,
melee. Oh, sorry. Melee playing favorites. Yes, I am. What are you? Okay. Gunner. Guns. Guns.
Spinner girl. Uh, kind of, I don't know. Miscellaneous. Where am I? These are people
that just shoot shooters and then miscellaneous and support will go over here. I don't know what
to do with you there. And now I actually have like a decent, decent now. What is this for?
I'm going to take you for a ride. I'm going to take you for a ride.
You're just powerful. You go like, okay, it's clean now. I can actually take a look and see
this is the ninja category. This is the, what are you doing up here? This is a shooter category,
robot category, flyer category, melee category, and then support category. Perfect. All right.
So I want that's pretty much. Oh, no, I can do 350. Who, who, who, who? Tell me. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know, man. Who? This guy, I don't just get a raid. All sham, no wow. What's
going on, dude? Thanks for the raid. Welcome everybody. Hope you're doing well. Welcome to
the fucking channel. All sham, no wow is a really, really good dude. It's been a while since we've
talked. Let's change that. Here's my phone number. Five, five, five, five, five, five, five, five,
five, five, five, five, five, five, five. Good work. Hit me up on discord, man. It's been a while.
Do I even have you on discord? I don't think I do. What a fucking bad friend.
But welcome. We're playing gotcha force, a game about robots and toys and people love it.
Trust me. Who should I put in the last swap though? Don't tell them how much it costs.
They don't need to know that. Maybe just a regular night. Yeah. Two regular nights. Oh,
oh, he said there's a big team. Okay. We're good. He's not forcing us to like it.
I'm not forcing anybody to like anything. This is a completionist dream. Yes. I believe the game
never ends either. It's somebody said that it goes to infinite new game plus, but please give it a
three out of 10. Can't believe that missed a great game. All right. Let's check this dude out. He's
got 30, 30. That's a lot of ammo spots. All right. Kind of cool. All right. His, his huge
cosplay foam is getting in the way. I feel like this dude would have trouble crossing the blizzard
state. Whoa. This guy's actually really good. Let me try to get that. Did you just see how much
damage that did? This dude's fucking insane. Oh, he's got a really good movement too.
Kind of hard to catch up to a plane. Whoa. I just like flying squirrel. God damn it. All right.
Just hit the ally. Do something. Oh, I just got bombed. That shreds. It shreds people. He's dead,
but it shreds people. All right. What about this dude? Okay. I think I have to charge it and I turn
it to two. Whoa. Two bombs. This is awesome. How is it last? All right. Elastic. Let's do it again.
You have to stand still though. That's not good. Bam. Come on. Double. Oh, I was so fun to sit
there and hit that button over and over again. I'm sorry. He's slow as shit. I'll get him double
melee attack. Let's go. No, let's not do that. Actually. Let's not do that. Run away. I don't
think I can replace these guys. Oh yeah. When you get like at least 40% of them to hit.
One issue with these guys is going to be bad is when this thing's moving around very fast
and you cannot charge that up and stand still. He's got a lot of health. All right. He's going
to be. Look at that bar. He's going to be a huge chunk of that bar. His health is probably like
500. Yeah. Look at that. One more guy. It's not a tank. All right. Let's see if we can dance
around you and slash you up a little bit. Oh, how did you do predicted my movement?
There we go. I just double tapped him. These dudes have so much health.
Oh, now I got him in the corner. You're fucking screwed.
There was resolve has been tested. He's paranoid. Cool. All right. We have this is the next. This
is the story mission. Make sure we're going in with what we want. I didn't even use this character.
I like them both. All right. This is an important mission. So
I'm going to have to use the things I like. I think that too many ninjas in a row spread
them out a little bit to 410 points. That's kind of, uh, use the teleport ninja. Yeah, I guess.
I wouldn't teleport kind of doesn't make any sense to me. You could use spike head.
Now he's 470. I could take out. I'll try it. I'll try it, but I want to break it up a little bit.
No, it can't just be quick, quick, quick, quick, quick. These guys are all just quick and weak.
I'll try it. What is awesome. Yeah. I'm just kind of cooperate with us. I get to beat the ICBM tanks.
Looks like a pretty good team. Beat enemy. Gotcha. Borgs. Yes. Oh, it's hitting the lip.
No. Oh, well, you got to get over there, man. How do you avoid that? Quick, quick, quick. Get it.
Get it. Get it. Get it. Don't let him do it. That's a jump. Where do I go? Teleport out of it.
Teleport. Do I, can I get one of these tanks? I think I'm going to die. I just have to jump.
Oh shit. One didn't hit me. Die. Die before it kills us. Holy shit. I got it. You definitely can
get that nuke, by the way. No way you can't. All right. Let's keep it up. Crash Course, part two.
You can get everything, even the dragons. That's so cool. Who we go for first? Over here.
That was a double. Stay in, stay in, stay in, stay in. Oh my God. This dude is as good
as Spikehead. What was his name? Boogerberry or something. Boogerberry is just Bugleberry,
but okay, you know how Snoopy has Spike and Spike's like kind of a little, like more rough.
Boogerberry is Bugleberry's Spike. Oh, it's Bogus. What? Die. I got to trade here. There we go.
It's a Bugleberry anti-hero. What do you have that for? Is it, is it a shield?
Oh, that's all right. Out of here. Stay in front so I can use the shield. One more hit.
Oh, one more hit. Turn off the music and please sing for us instead. I don't think you're gonna
want that. Oh, it's all right. We got a, okay, teleport ninja. How much damage does this do?
Okay. Starting to understand. Oh, I'm starting to understand why this character is good.
Understood. All right. Nuke. Give us a nuke. Do I take donations? Um, I, you can give bits.
I don't have like a PayPal or anything though. Command girl. I gotta check my crystals.
Command girl is the best. Command girl is so good. Really? Uh, just zero attack. Defense,
shooting, and attack. Speed, beam, and buster laser. An assassin from the planet
Megaborp who was equipped with a beam gun. She relies on her weapons but avoids,
oh, she just can't, no melee at all. All right. What are you doing over here? You're supposed to
be over in the flyers. You're supposed to be down here with the shooters who, oh, get rid of you.
I know you're good. Uh, you're good too. You're also good, but I, we'll try. Yeah,
I'll take you off now. See how command girl is still doing the singing thing. No, it's crypto.
Yeah, I, I, we're, we, yes, I had an Ethereum address that I had there and it was,
hey, look, check it out. It's, you can send ether, Ethereum, crypto, and it was there for about
six and a half, seven months. That took in about, I believe, six or seven dollars worth of Ethereum
over six or seven months. So, which that's, that's fine. It's, it's not like, oh, I didn't,
nobody gave me enough money, so I'm deleting it. It just wasn't really used and I, it was just like,
people don't really care anymore. You are CNN ass streamer fucking nerd. What does that mean?
I, I'm trying, what I, why do I like, I'm like, I'm piecing together what you're talking about.
That's exactly what I just made fun of. What did I make fun of? What did I do? All right,
this is going to be a hard fight. Okay. I probably shouldn't have started with, uh,
with vacuum cleaner girl, whatever that is, with big boxing glove vacuum.
Oops. Well, we got to fight five people at the same time. No, she definitely doesn't suck. I just
can't, you know, I'm fighting a full team. I'm hitting somebody. These motherfuckers can't even
take me down. I'm doing some good damage. Get out. Sorry, I did a lot of damage. All right,
clean it up. Good. Focus, focus, focus on them. Don't let them get away. This is your time to
shine. You just transformed, but he's dead. Oh, you just keep his own guy. Yeah. Your teamwork
is not. All right, let's go. Come on. One hell. Oh, all right. That was a bad team for this.
Show us your J O crystal. I don't know what that is. CNN player. Okay. We're going to change this.
We need beef. Okay. Uh, you're good, but not now. We need beef. Uh, bubble night did pretty good.
You did all right, too. You can stay 230. Who can I put in? No, I need beef. I'm going to regret
this, but here's your one shot. Look at the crystals. Confirm. All right. And one, two, one,
C. Damn. I need one more. Oh, and one, two, one, B and one, two, one, C.
I need N one, two, one, a, and I get this thing. Damn it. Oh, well, go and get it.
That's easier. All right. We're giving hatchet night a chance here. I take you off and I had
a five 90. I didn't realize just how expensive hammer night actually was. That's insanely
expensive. Um, I can put you back in. I got two 80, three 30 or 80 double ninja. Yeah.
All right. We'll try this. You're ignoring chat. Somebody said they lost their J O crystal.
Feels bad, man. LODs support jail crystals. Feels bad, man. J O crystal. I'm, why am I ignoring chat?
Stop saying that. I'm what? First I'm ignoring everybody and now I'm addressing what everyone's
saying. And now I'm, don't stop addressing us. Run away. Oh, okay. That's what that is. Sure.
All right. Let's continue this, by the way, this, like I said, this is, this is hatchet night's
one shot. If you're a hatchet night supporter and have to see you in the chat,
this is the only shot he's going to get. All right. He's benched.
Maybe one day he'll get a shot. I got to focus on one person at a time. You,
you're dead. That's got like everybody. Look, I'm not, I look, I got a lot of damage in there.
All right. Here we go. Comes the equalizer. He instantly died. Are we about to see somebody
always have a spot on my team? Oh, there's always a spot for you. There's always a spot for you now.
Okay. Cocky double ninja always gets a spot. No matter what big bits by Lacta re even more
huge money drops. Ooh, it's like a punch guy. 50 Thomas, another 50 bucks. You're a J O crystal
is like a little talisman you use with your bros. You guys all hang out and just kind of do this.
Don't tell anyone. It's just for us bros. Okay. Thanks. This is 50 bucks. Don't tell anyone.
It's just for, okay. Well, I just told 5,000 people. Sorry. All right. We have to have a bench
category. Yeah. It's over here. This is the bench for 500. Maybe you'll come out one day
and Disney movie somebody and it'll be like, wow, he came off the bench and he sunk like five threes.
Now is not your time. And we won the championship because of that. I have not, but 570 remaining.
Kind of let me down, but I'll keep you there for now. Uh, where's put you back in here at number one.
I like this guy. Oh, command. Right. Command, command girl. Let's get rid of you. Put you
back down with the robots. We'll have two 60 normal night. Hmm. I feel like I haven't given
these big bulky robots much of a chance, but I'm not going to who's 60.
Hmm. She was kind of good. She was all right. You need an ally though, or maybe a flyer. Yeah.
Okay. We're going to try wind. Yeah. We didn't do wind Valkyria.
Take multiple teams. I will. When I have 500 robots, I tweet this. Yeah. Don't forget to press
fucking X. Yeah. Well, I, I was going to get five people at the same time. Oh, it's okay.
You can just stay way back. I now see the appeal. You can't even get over here. All right. I got,
I don't know why I just got cocking, but in close, you're a camper. Yeah. That's the character. The
character is a camper. Oh, all right. Let's check out this. This is the wind. What the hell does that
do? What does that do? Does this do damage? It's just knock back bench. It's going to be a nice
warm spot underneath you because you ain't ever going to get up from that bench.
You're going to be sitting on that bench for so long. There's going to be an imprint of your ass
on the metal. Command girls. Good. I'll keep command girl. And of course, a bubble bot is
always just key. Very solid player. I'm sure there's probably somebody out there that has
played this game before and is like, dude, he doesn't even understand that those, the flying
Valkyries there. So you just playing wrong. They're the best characters in the game. You
can just cheese every level. I'm sure they exist. I'm sure some three, you can do that.
But my buddy bubble bot is going to have to take that's my playing strategy. That's my playing
style. 87%, 88% dodge ratio. You kidding me? Bubble, but bubble, but yeah, my buddy bubble
bot over here. Ooh, okay. We've got two. Now here we have some benching to do. Okay. That
frees up some space. We'll put you, we'll start with you. Okay. 270. I think I want to get you
back in here though. He's like the best character I have. Who's worth putting in for normal night?
Put me in slot 24. I mean, guard witch could just be, I mean, it's just another character.
When we get to guard, which we know it's time to really try as hard as we can guard, which is just
going to die revolver gunman. Maybe, maybe one day I love revolver gunman, but you're going to
change it up. Another GF commander. Hey, GF commander, if they got you for us, you're about
to be destroyed. Uh, the guy with Woody. No, I want Woody though. Dude, you have to, you have
Woody and Jax. I want those. What the fuck? Uh, Tsutomu has an airplane now. Oh, they got a,
wait, they have a bigger airplane. I'm starting to realize why this show didn't take off.
Wait, he, that's him. All right. This is one of my best characters.
Got it. Keep up the pressure, keep up the pressure, keep up the pressure, pressure, pressure, pressure.
Come on, get it. No. Okay. Good. I got to get some shots in before he gets another per, all right.
That's a something. That's a character I haven't seen yet. Whoa. I caught him in a, well,
almost an entire revolution. He thinks this will hit. Fucking idiot. Ooh. All right. Let's go.
Bubble Bot. Stay away from the giant ship right now. It's on fire. You got to, where's your
supporting fire? All right. Keep him in here. He can't get close to Bubble Bot. No way.
He just throw me. Come on. He just had a reach. Come here, girl. Wow. Check this shit out. This
is going to be crazy. Take out the big fucking ship. Is it Thanatos? Uh-oh. Who's left? Uh-oh.
Time to try hard. I have to try really hard with Strawberry Shortcake. That means try.
Strawberry Shortcake. Actually pretty good. No, we just have the big boat thing.
Okay. Okay. Here we go. We got to, we should get this, right? Stay in the air. Come on.
Do it. Do it. Do it. Oh, I thought that was me. Am I bad at this game? I'm not. I just won.
I got a 62% hit ratio, a 97% dodge ratio. That's not, what, what do you want me to say?
You got lucky. I don't know. That guy doesn't seem too serious. We didn't even get anything
for that. Bullshit. Okay. Uh, I got, I like this team. I like this team. We need the odd number.
I remember this Valkyrie was pretty good. In fact, we're going to put you in the front here.
That makes more sense to me. Eh, maybe. Hmm. Okay. That's better. 1580 exact. How did I cheat?
Did I use my superpower? Berry bubble butt or rumble. I don't know if that's going to work out.
All right. Here we go. Battle with Sho in Yu-Gi. I'll destroy them all. I don't care if they're the
death force or gotcha force centrist. I agree with that. All right. Do I use Reddit shelf team
ninja heels? Really cool. Swords. What do you inject? I'm going to use Reddit shelf. What is
that? What is that thing? Shit. I have a major, major character. I could say something right now
that looks like that is exactly what that is. Well, I can't because I know I couldn't do that,
but that's just, but there's an exact reference to who that is. And I, I, I can't say it
as a, as a, I don't even want to say what it potentially could be referencing.
All right, let's get in there. Is it slow motion field? That is slow motion field. Oh, that's
actually cool. Cause everything's slow in here. Even projectiles. I'm so focused on this dude.
I'm not even attacking the other guy. Weirdo. Yeah. He's so fast in that little bubble.
We got him. We need that power. Cause I want to be able to just to span this.
Do it. You weren't trying before. Liar. Oh shit. Okay. I can fly. Oh, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Up, up, up. Get away, get away, get away. We can both fly. Oh fuck. We can both fly. Oh yeah. I
forgot this character is awesome, but I can't. Come on. God damn it. This guy's fucking insanely
powerful. You can just float in the fucking air and rain hell. How do I get one of these things?
Oh, this is bad. This is where you shine here. Counter, counter, counter. Get the fuck up.
Okay. Good. Holy shit. Holy shit. Don't get cocky. Fly away. Oh my God. Is this the last thing I have?
What's after this? I'm at the end of the world. I'm going to choke. I have to get something for
that, right? Huh? What the fuck are you talking about, kid? That's like a phrase that he heard
his parents say or something. And he's just, ah, I guess I'll say that. These kids are like five.
You get nothing. What? That's bullshit. Cultural anthropology. I'm going to keep this team.
I think it's working out. Yeah. Why change it? I'm something of a cultural anthropologist myself.
We just keep following these. Wait, I got to save again. That was funny. That was funny.
One of you guys is real funny. I read it. Uh, it's the same two people.
It's like following these guys around and bullying them. You come to get beaten by me too.
Sure. Uh, I want that's a new character. All right. Don't let me down. Don't let me down.
Nana. Oh yeah. See? Fuck. Oh, okay. I have to, I need to tell you guys what this is. I,
does somebody knows? Um, okay. At the end of the stream, I'm going to go into, uh,
discord and write it somewhere. This is good. Oh, he's not even, am I going to perfect you?
Holy shit. You're going to be, you're going to get embarrassed. I'm about to perfect this person.
Yeah. Oh, almost. Now I'm just BMing. That's enough. That's enough mortal combat for today.
That's enough mortal combat for today. Turn it off. Bye bye. What, where did you come from?
Keep up the pressure in this dude's dome. Oh, this, this, I hate this dude. This guy's the worst.
I got it. Yeah. I got to focus this dude now. Oh, not good. Get away from me.
Oh, not good. Bad, bad, bad, bad, bad. If I have to kill this guy, I will. What falls up must come
down. What planet are we on? Good hit. Come on. I got double teamed there. Man, you haven't healed
me one time all game. Benched. Stop being toxic. Benched. I'm not going to use this yet. Unless I
need to. Heal me. Heal me. Get over here and heal me now. Do you even have a healer character with
you? I've had enough. Finally. You did it. Fuck. No. It's not over. And it won't be. What happened
to my guy? What happened to my guy? I'm dead. I'm never using mana ever again. Mana walked around
in circles. Didn't do anything because all she has is support characters. And then injected me
with one heal over the whole course of the entire round. Benched. Permanently. He's right. I mean,
the quantum theory, whatever you're talking about. I lost the opportunity. Of course,
I picked mana for that opportunity and it's gone. Reload the save. No. He's flaming mana. Yeah, I am.
I was holding up the earth there. I'm keeping the snow. Somebody's got to go. No, we're going to
keep it. Beat the death eye unit. Ref, it's the eight-year-old's fault. Yes, it was. If I'm playing
a game with children and one of the children doesn't play well, then it was the child's fault.
I didn't do it. I have 650 points in the game of basketball we're playing. By the way, the other
team has one. They got a safety. One of them got pushed over. No, they have zero points.
Oh, okay. What? I kind of like this character. Where do I get one? Oh, come on. He jumped over
it. Did they have melee? Oh, all right. I got to kill that guy now. This is horrible. They can all
do it. Do I have to activate the superpower with this? I might. Okay. Now I remember. Now I remember.
She has one of the best spammable super moves. X, A, X, A, X, X, A. I've got a new robot in three
hours. I think I'm going to try my new combo I got. It's B, B, B, A, B, A, B, B, B, B, A, B.
This is a good heavy hitter. Oh, this dude has planes. Probably you just spam attacks.
Some of these things are so cool. I want to get satellites. You guys are so weak. Oh, man.
They're killing it. Oh, get in there. Oh, this is bad. I think I'm gonna have to bring G force
in here. What is the name? Is G red unless hold on. Why is that finding of Isaac? That's the Isaac
face. Yep. Hey, I just fly above the satellite. Done. And then watch this. Goodbye. Oh, lag.
He's so good. An emulator lag. How many satellites do you have? It's going for like a slash.
Goodbye. Oh, why did you use it? Oh, this dude sucks. All right. Don't break with the formula
here. Pac Man. Maybe that's why I like this guy. This sucks. I can't use the ability here.
No. Shit. No. Get the fuck out of here. I get up. It's too laggy. I can't move. Just get the fuck
away. Oh, shit. What do I get after this? The ninja, right? I think it's just that. I think that's it.
Oh, my fucking God. There's another one. It's bad. It's okay. This is where we just pray.
No, I didn't make two. Okay, we're good. No, there's no way I was. There's way too many.
I need to bring G red here. I need like massive artillery. You get a better ship. Fuck up.
I gotta relax. Calm down. It's all right. It's just a. All right. These are not going to happen
for you. Sorry. You're great, but not right now. All right. We need people that can
do damage from pretty far away. G red first. You're still fine. You're great.
You're good. You're not so good right now. Let's get some more of the Valkyries. Who's better? Ice?
Monado? Who does most damage? I think they both do. They all do the same damage. Will do.
What about Spikehead? I think Spikehead. I don't know if Spikehead is going to work out.
I'll try Spikehead and long range head. Yeah, I'm going to get one hit KO'd,
but that's not even his name. This Spikehead is not his name. We also need somebody that we need
artillery. Yeah. Air support, tank support, artillery, fire, big bombs. They don't move
very slow. They're slow. I got to get the way the hell up in the air. Up, up, up all the way.
Skybox. Good. Just avoid the beams. Not that hard. Stay all above them and just wait till I get the
spam ability and then just light them up. He's got a plane. He's fine. I'm hitting every single one.
They're not doing a lot of damage, but still when you can spam them, they're crazy. Almost got hit.
Okay. Here it comes. First batch. First batch of lag spam. These are EU strats. What does that even
mean? EU? And here we go. Good. Stay up. What the hell is that thing? Higher, higher, higher, higher,
up, up, up, up, up. I'm blowing. Get the hell out of here. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out.
What are you doing? Get out. Just get out. They're making the lasers, but they've moved too fast for
me to hit. Uh-oh. There's so many of those things flying around. Hold starting engine. All right.
Just get the fuck away while they do this bullshit. All right. Get up. Don't blow this. Come on. Up,
go, go, go, go, up. Keep going. Keep going. Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't,
don't. Activate the VAT system. I did it. I think I was just spamming right trigger and just putting
things everywhere. Okay. Here we go. Still have, I'm still on the Valkyrie. I was on a new character
by now. I'll get back. Yeah. I got to stick with the formula. You'd have life break from the formula.
I'm back into the corner. Get out. Uh-oh. Okay. It's all right. It's okay. It's okay. I got,
I got G-Force. It's fine. He's really powerful. And in a second I can do, I can just spam the
charge. Like for instance, right now. All right. Out. Here comes the ship. Get out. Whoa. What the
fuck just happened? God damn. I'm still all right. I got plenty of health. Move. Is that it? Or is
there any more satellite? Okay. This is one or two more satellites. Oh fuck. Okay. Who's next?
It's girl. Ultra girl. Whatever her name is. Don't stand underneath them.
All right. I got to, this is where. Run. Get away from me. Do it. Yeah. Spikehead. Good choice. No,
uh, booger brain. Uh, bogus. What was it? Bogus something. Oh, you just did kid. Ship. I want to
ship. Give me a ship. I just beat the guy that has ships. Uh, it's one of those satellites.
Oh, your stupid ice cream melted. Not a bad crew. I'll keep it. I am going to go pee though.
I'll be right back. Grab yourself a new water beverage snack. I'll be back in about two,
three minutes. Okay. Let's keep going. I'm like addicted to this game. The hot battle
will bring you bring saw blades, like wacky sound effects.
No, I can't. I'm busy. I'm busy shooting, dodging that to get out a new move.
You really are addicted. Yeah, it's fun. I wanted to, I want to have a bunch of ships and stuff.
I want to play and have ships. That's what's important to me. The ships, he's going full
Shatner. What does it call Shatner? Get back in the year. All right. These guys with the explosives,
get rid of them. I've got a really itchy mouth and I don't know how to do about it.
Here we go. God damn it. Quit exploding everything. I have had enough bookcase.
I'm staying far away. Derma eight fiberglass again. What are you talking about? I don't know.
Cotton candy, giant enemy dragon. I just said joke. Oh, he did the thing. This too.
The third song, the third albums. I've been really not even as good.
So I kind of rushed. He was just trying to get it out. Like just make a bunch of sales.
Why is it going through? I know I missed the old Derma. You remember how just how much passion
there was in giant enemy spider and giant enemy spider had way more nasal pushing.
That one didn't. He just went like tiny enemy spider had like, I miss it. What happened to this
guy? It's been a long one. Fly away. There's no reason to fight these guys up close. So they want
Did I just hit with every auto attack? Oh God, it's embarrassing. He was with every auto attack.
Who's the ally? Where's the out? See later. I'm going to take a bike ride. Have fun on your bike
ride. He's been dead. Relax. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. What is it? Can I please complete one capsule
in like eight hours of playing this game? Damn it. Kneel before me. You're cool, but I want
I want this guy back. You're good too, but I want to bring in some you. Okay, nice. And I want you
here. I want you at the very end just to get something happens. And I want you first.
Back in 10 minutes. I'm going to watch beef house. Here you go. Fresh trash. What's in here? Fresh
beef. Try. I've seen a few episodes. Here we go. Do my chores. Get them done. Good. Don't leave
streaks on the windows. It's a while for them to come off if you do. Hey, oh shit. It's a, it's me.
See who the better me is. It's me. What was that? What the hell was that? That was weird.
Oh, it's a copy. It's a copier. That's really useful if you can get one of these.
How many more enemies are here? Look at that bar. I'm not going to use it with her. I got a,
I got, got you, got you, man. Whatever. Later. Don't tell him. Tell me what? Now tell me.
I want to know. What? Yeah, I know I don't. I'm focused on playing this super fun game cube
experience. Okay. Please tell me what it is. Please tell me what it is. Please tell me what it is.
Google it. I don't know what I'm supposed to Googling. Tell me what it is. Tell me what it is.
Google it. Google what? Google it. It's already too late. Oh, fine. Let me out of this, please.
Who's the person that turns you into the newts? This character is so good. Just,
he's just so consistent. He's very consistent. Slow. He has one good move, but he's consistent.
Now we press the button. See ya. Who's left? Oh, one guy. Oh, this was the audio muted or something.
I don't think it is. All right. Tell me, tell me what it is. Or I just go to random.org. Pick
a random number and every five seconds ban somebody permanently from the channel until
you tell me. Do it. Wait. We got a new robot. All right. How fast do you think I can drink this water?
See? It's terrible, but he doesn't, he doesn't need to be good.
Copy. He was going to explore planets. He duplicates his opponents and fights with them,
fights them with their own power. Very expensive. Let's try a copy, man. Now I can be a satellite.
Yeah, that's true. Does that work? Copy the giant ship. Showdown. No, that's, that's force unit.
Battle with, all right. Let's do this one. Showdown. This team's not very good, but wait,
I can copy their best hero. Who's the strongest one? Right in the middle. All right. Copy.
Copy right in the middle. Let's go. Wait, you have to throw your, you actually have to hit them.
Give me, give me somebody. Oh, this ain't going to work out. Hey, look at me. It'd be great if you
could actually, if you're not fighting five people at the same time, it works. Okay. Sniper girl.
Gonna work out. Oh, I just got caught in the air. That was bad. I can just get one of you. Just die.
Fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly. Oh, yeah. We, this is not bad. As long as I kill one.
Okay. Keep going. That was holy shit. I'm going to get to stop. It's just you, right?
All right. Just the big guy. I try to jump over it. Shit. It's okay. Who's left? Oh, it's over.
I win. Well, now you're little. Sorry. All your power is gone. Who's the real cheater here?
When are you going to do another Hearthstone stream? That was a pog face.
Um, that's not going to happen. All right. Give me an, finally capsule. Let's go complete a capsule.
Do I have one of the one of these? I have so many singles. God damn it. It's like playing the
Monopoly game of McDonald's. Give me a break. I'm never going to win. He's got five community subs
from West Yule. Thank you West Yule. Appreciate the five subs. Now one of these little guys.
Welcome. Thanks for the subs. Welcome all the new subs and welcome all the new mods.
New mods. Please say hello. Uh, this way. How do I punchy cookie? I don't know. I missed it. Big boy.
I need a new trailer. Can I copy the big guy? Right. I should be able to copy this guy, right?
Can I copy anything in the game? Whoa. This is cool. It only has one move. This is a bad thing
to copy. This thing's terrible. Copy that guy. Wait, should I copy? You're even worse. Wait,
what is this? Oh, he's cool. I like this guy with the, with the two hands. It's actually fun.
No, it's all right. No, I like this game so much. Whoa. How can you like this so much? What's going
on here? Um, I just love projectiles. I love projectiles with travel time. It's my favorite
thing in any game, especially a third person of first person game. Reminds me. The hell am I
going to play tribes? What are we going to play tribes? Is the server still on? The game was so
much fun. We had five more community subs from Saarbruss. Thank you Saarbruss for dropping those
subs. Appreciate it. I just hit every auto attack. That's so good. First and third are the only two
options, right? Um, yeah. Well, 2D, right? Like side scroller. What am I thinking of? Bird's eye.
Yeah. Bird's eye side scrolling, but the projectiles have to travel and have to be able to travel with
in real physics. I wish I could copy that guy. How do I get that guy? The double R. We'll get
those two bowling balls. Oh my goodness. Please give me this guy at the end of this.
That's, that's just the shield. Uh, bubble butt guy, except way cooler. He just has two.
I want this guy. Please give it to me. I want to play tribes again. The best part about tribes
was when you hit that blue plate special and you were just 7 million years away and you would just
go up in the air and you'd go like, it's like, Holy, I killed that guy. This whole thing with
girl commander blue plate special was the best. And the soldier had that arcing grenade launcher.
That game was so much fun. Do they make games like that anymore? Is there a game that
think of what I feel about tribes ascend? I want a game that is that.
No, no. Well, and we didn't get anything from that last experience.
I'm going to change this up a bit. I like, I remember I was using a negative,
put negative back in here. Tribes of school, but never got updated. I think,
but wasn't the problem with tribes that it got updated, but they put a bunch of
weird dumb shit in the game that nobody wanted on robots, putting hitscan and tribes.
Well, where's the, where's the true hitscan in tribes? What are the machine guns?
But weren't the machine guns even projectiles? You had to still land them.
Sniper was hitscan really dumb. I think it was, you know, I bet you there was this an
appetite for something like that. Like a real revival of that kind of game.
This all projectile based satisfying shots. No, there isn't. Yeah. But this, I'm telling you,
this shit comes in cycles, man. Everyone, every single person was making a MOBA. Everyone.
Like if you, if you were a game company and you did not have a like top-down MOBA in development,
what the fuck were you doing with your life? That's now become BR.
Did that thing explode? Oh, I'm going to copy this guy. BR is currently like the trend right now.
It's really popular, but it's, it's going to, it's not going to be there forever.
When's like the tribes ascend game going to be the, you know, that's what I'm looking for.
There we go. No, I don't want this guy. This guy sucks. It's going to be in 50 years.
I don't think so. Oh fuck. I want to turn into this guy. Shit. Ooh, I got it. Okay. What is,
what is this thing? He has like pulsating shots. Oh, I'd love to see what the fuck was going on.
Wait, was he about to do the bigger they are, the harder they fall in the same tone.
Why didn't we get to hear that? We all, we were almost there. The bigger they are,
the harder they fall. I'm just trying to snipe this guy out. It needs to be working.
Let's use it. Jump. Jump. Oh, that was a cool hero. Too bad. There he is again.
It's probably going to be that weird bubble guy. Another thunder robot. Are you shitting me?
Fucking thunder robot. Are you shitting me? Under the warehouse. What does that mean?
I'm going to know too weird, too much setup time, too much setup time, too expensive.
There's my boy right there. Nevermind. Sit back down. Melting them down. Wait,
hold on. I changed my mind. This is ship level. I'm going to turn into a huge ship or a satellite
or something. Oh, but in the meantime, you know, I'm going back to, uh, I haven't played with these
guys in a long time. 250 and then 150. Wait, save it. Do an angry video game nerd impression.
Um, uh, the problem is it's just donkey shit. It's like the smelliest donkey shit you've ever seen
in your entire life. Now, look at this guy. This guy just sucks. This game sucks. Is that right?
That's pretty good. That was all right. Hey guys, fun, uh, fun thing about the angry video game
nerd. Uh, you know, he's like the D and D of YouTubers. You know that, right? He was doing
that shit fucking like 20 years ago. Like the Witcher three is a great game, but like it's D
and D is the reason why like the Witcher three even exists. Whoa. Look at that. What? Come on.
I can't do this. Oh, that's, that's not cool. I got to play as one of these
eye of kill rocks. Oh, that's great. Might as well. I can't even fly. Well, you know what to do.
Oh, look at all those blue plate specials. Actually pretty good character to be here.
Everyone was like, he's up. What do you have to say now? Oh, extra super powerful. What does it
look like? Um, does it look like it looks like, uh, like a mega man shot? No, what does it look
like? It looks like something from a game. He did a lot of work. We get just how much health that
just brought the G F down buster shots from mega man legends. It kind of does. Yeah. And this is a
Capcom game. You guys didn't know this game is Capcom. It's made by the same people that made
resident evil seven. It's not Capcom. It is. That's my best score yet. I think. Yes. Finally,
a fucking plane. Yeah. They also made resident evil six. Now that they outsourced that that was
made by Capcom. Hey, you guys know, I like aliens, colonial Marines. I like hat. Like the game
wouldn't even made by gearbox. You've got a death crystal. Looks like some kind of key data. Blue
striker. Fastest thing in the game. No attack. How missile Vulcan power beam. I had to type
Eric Borg who fought during the interplanetary mega Borg war. He can move freely in the sky and
possesses missiles Vulcans and a deadly power beam. Not expensive either. Lead with that.
I'll keep you here for a while. 390 remain 180. I got six people now. Cool.
He's no good at the boundaries. No, not really. Mysterious crystal. Ooh, here comes lower.
I got some strange data. Watch out at the death force.
Look at that. Here we go. Plane time. Whoa. Cool. I can't. How do I? Wait, you can hold
missiles. Wow. What's the charge do? Wally. Ooh, dodge. One of those land. Oh, that was fun though.
They had some good anti-air. That's the reason why it happened. We both have this. This is cool.
Don't think so. Watch this shit. Who's quad ninjaed this person? Get it. You're too fast.
All right. Back it up. I hear a dragon. I do. You already killed my buddy. Nice shot.
You got it. Come on. You got to give credit. Who else is here? Shit. No, that wasn't even
that. What are the 3000 GF power? Holy shit. Okay. Don't. Okay. We got sniper. This is a boss
battle. I didn't say it was. I don't think it is. Save that power though. Got me too. Holy fuck.
He's still playing this. That long. I mean, I know my streams turned into like four or five hours
long, but I mean, it's not like that. It's not like that long. Somebody said this is Warframe,
but imagine if it was a cartoon like this and I would like that. It really isn't. Another dragon.
Risky, but worth it. Copy the dragon, please. I don't have the copy guy right now.
Is he even on the team? Turn it on. No, he's not.
I look over and you guys are fucking crazy. Shit. I like the plane, but it's very vulnerable.
You have to really fly the hell out of there. Why are you a girl?
Are you looking for this? Got a death crystal. How many death crystals do I need?
I've got two. I've got two death crystals. Hey, look. I mean, she looks cool.
D though. Charge gun, beam knife, charge beam, anchor wire. Fire girl was trained on a secret
agent. Once her anchor wire is set, she can return to a set point at any time. Very useful when she
needs to make a sharp exit. That's really good. It's like teleporting, but better. That's right.
320. That's pretty good. All right. Here we go. Death commander. Who should I bring? All right,
Manny. You get one more shot off the bench. Let's go. Fly away. Are they homing? I can't hit.
Okay. I just hit myself with my own missile. That's not even possible. No, your ship is so
much better than mine. Bombing run. Okay. Anchor point. How does this work? How does this work?
You can go back to any point? I don't understand. Wait a minute. Okay. You have to fly. You fly
near it. Wait a second. Hold on. Okay. Now I've just first time ever used this character.
How did I? Oh, I got hit by the, I think I got hit by it. Oh, this one sucks. There's too many
of them. Oh, I sure would love to be healed by the best character in the game. I have a support
character that doesn't do anything. Spends all the time walking around in circles and missing me.
Okay. Heal me now. Get over here. On earth are you? Come here. Heal me. Heal me. You don't have any
other. Finally. That character doesn't even have any fucking moves. You're going to heal me or
what? When you say here, that's something that somebody on the bench would say. Kill it. Kill it.
That's it. Now you're in big trouble. Now you're in trouble. Oh, excuse me. You got to heal for me?
Oh shit. It's a nuke. Shoot it. Manna run. Manna. Manna. Manna. Manna. Thank God.
Tactical nuke. Hope I get one right here. Ooh. Yeah. That has to. That's going into the crew.
You're useless Tamma. I gave you the power of the death arc, but you still lost.
What are you talking about? Death arc was not strong enough. Where's that? There it is.
350. That's pretty solid. Bug Borg. Insect bomb. Insect slicer. Insect scope. Mech life form from
outer space. Its gate shield protects it from enemy attacks while its right arm is sharp as a blade.
Its insect scope reduces the power of enemy shots. D-Buff. You can keep Wire Girl on here too.
Uh. Okay. The shame the toys never happened. The designs in the game kick ass.
I mean, they're pretty, they are pretty good. They're pretty cool.
I would have loved to play with these things. Funded. What is there to fund?
Weren't you like 20 when this came out? Well, I mean, I was, yeah, I was like,
no, I was like fucking 19, 18 or something. 17. That's besides the point. I'm talking about
if I was like younger and played this when I was like 10. That would have been sick.
Charge dude. This is a huge one. Okay. I just found. Nice. It's so good. All right. Don't crash.
All right. Missiles. Damn, this thing is actually really good. Can you imagine flying around like
this when you were 10? You would, you would shit your pants if you played this when you were like
12. Look at those thick, thick beams. Retreat. Can't dodge that. Oh, it's all right. A lot of
good. Okay. Here we go. Bug, the bug guy. Oh shit. That's he's got recharge, huh? Did I do it?
I'm kind of hard to tell what's going on here. He doesn't suck. I just, I don't understand yet.
It's like fields that he's shooting out. It's a debuff field, right?
All right. I still don't understand how this works. I'm trying to get this to activate somehow.
X doesn't do it. I feel like touch them. Double tap X. Okay. That makes sense.
Just mash buttons. Okay. That's good. Let's put them across the whole map. Yeah. This is gonna be
great. Ready? The game broke. It would have been cool. Did she have a melee? Yeah. And it's pretty
good. It's quick. Back up. I think that's just a really good character. That's the reason why
my bug guy was just not fair. This guy's a limited edition. Bug guys are common. He's like a D or
something. This guy's probably like an S. I won the record for oldest person to play this game.
That's fine. That doesn't embarrass me. Why are that? Oh, this game is cool. It's a really neat
game. And I'm, I want to showcase this showcase Saturday. We're checking out this old showcaseable
game. That's really fun. And really, I wish they'd make games like this again. Look at this showcase.
No, it's not. It's Tuesday. It's Tuesday. It's Tuesday. I guess I have any, you guys still don't
understand how time zones work. Can you imagine if the earth was like 50 times larger than it is?
And it could be like Thursday for you. And it's like Monday for me. You'd be stuck in a time loop.
Days would just be longer. But would we have longer days? Would a day be like 75? Like what?
One day would be like a week. If the earth was a hundred times bigger than it is now,
what we might have, we might rotate slower. Thank God I got one. He's learning. Gravity would kill
us. The earth was okay. If the earth was like, okay, if, if, if how long it takes for you to get
from like, let's say like New York to London, right? Was it like a eight hour flight,
11 hour flight? Imagine you should, okay. So if you want to go from like a New York to London,
it was like four days in an airplane. Like the ocean was 50 times larger. What would happen?
The earth is still the earth. Like we, we have the same amount of countries in the same places,
but it's, but like, there's just way more ocean. Is the mass still the same? Yeah. Like the mass
of the countries is the same, but the ocean is like six million times bigger. Do I have to draw
this? I might have to draw this for you. Do I have to draw this? I don't think people understand
what I'm saying here. Hold on. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. This is important. So this is what I'm
talking about. If you clean for you so you can see it nice and good, but it's what you paint.
You have to course it is. Well, who cares? Look, I'm going to make, I'm going to fix it. I'll fix
it here. Now your eyes won't hurt. Okay. I got to get this music out of my ears. It's going to
fucking make me scream. Okay. So here's earth. I'm going to draw you earth. Here's the earth as,
as it is now. Right? So this is earth. And then like here's, uh, this is Africa. This is like
North America. Uh, this is, uh, this is Europe, right? Italy. And then over here is like on the
other side, I can't draw it. It's like, you know, China and Russia and stuff. Okay. Under here is
South America. Remember it's, I'm just, this is, you just know where it is. All right. So this is
what the earth looks like now. So what happens? And here's the sun, right? So here's the sun.
Obviously the, now the earth is spinning like this, right? Spin, spin, spin. Here's the sun.
Sun also goes like in a circle or something. I don't know. It's going to be a sad planet.
No, we go in a circle. We go in a circle. We, that's where the circle is. So we circle like
this. What? Give me different colors. I don't want fucking puke orange. What the, stop. What
the fuck? All right. So we're going like this, but we're also going like this. So what happens
in this scenario? How do I, something's wrong with my computer. There's something, something has to
be wrong with my computer. That doesn't make any sense. Um, something has to be something wrong
with the computer. Is that eraser? I'm going to try to do this as detailed as I can. Okay. I'm sorry.
I'll fix it. So what happens when you have the earth like this? So here's the earth. That's the
earth. Here's the sun right here. And now here is, here's North America. Here is South America.
Here's Africa. Here's Europe. And then on the other side is right. Where's Mexico?
Down here. You know what I'm saying? So what happens? We're rotating like this and we're
also going like this. What have, if the earth is like 60 times bigger, wait, would we not have any
sunlight? Would it just be, okay. Would there only be sunlight like here? Only. Like in one country.
If the sun was like tiny, would it be like a flashlight on one country at a time? And would
everybody else be in pitch black until it finally like moved a little bit and like, and finally,
okay. Now this right here, this part can get some sunlight. That's not how light works.
But would it just be darker? Would you, would it just, would it be darker outside? Would we
wouldn't have big sunshine? It would just be darker. It'd be harsh shadows. So what if all
the countries are like this in the same spot over here? Like typically like this is like where earth
is now, right? Imagine this is earth and there's the countries. Imagine they all were in there.
Would we have like a day of sunlight and then like 12 days of darkness? Yes, we would. Big earth
theory. That's not how days work. But like our perception of darkness would be longer. It would
be long. It would be darker for longer. Like it would be like, holy shit, it's dark for so fucking
long. Even though it's, you know, yeah. It's like this when you play Minecraft. I'm of the opinion
that in Minecraft the nights are longer and it's been coded that way. I've been told it's not true,
but it is. Includes my what if the earth was big theory. Oh, you know, there's some science
channel that's made a video about what if the earth was fucking a thousand times bigger.
Don't act like I'm some kind of psycho.
Hey, just who cares how bad you spell? Just spam your keyboard and then the computer will fix it
for you. Just mash keys. You can do this with your shit bed drunk. Hey there, welcome to life.
We live in a part of the solar system called the Goldilocks zone. It's not too hot that all the
water evaporates away, but it's also not too cold where it freezes instead. And unless you're an
astronaut, the big spherical rock will be your home for life. But what if that home suddenly
changed? What if in a split second, the earth doubled in size? Let's just write the density
remains constant. So the mass of the earth increased as well. How would that change things?
Well, first off, gravity would be very different. The earth would have eight times as much mass and
gravity would be twice as strong. So if you suddenly weigh twice as much, I said 10 times
much harder for you to walk and you'd get tired much more on the ground. Another version of yourself,
a piggyback ride all day, every day, which would look very funny. Over the years, human bones,
especially in the legs, would have to become stronger to support this increased weight.
Meanwhile, trees would start to collapse and any new trees that grow in their place might not grow
as tall. See, there's a limit for how tall a tree can grow, usually around 400 feet or so. This limit
is determined by gravity. Since the taller the tree is, the more energy is required to transport
water from the roots to the top. If the amount of energy the tree gains from photosynthesis is
more than the energy it takes to transport the water, it'll keep growing. Otherwise, it'll stop.
So if the earth suddenly got twice as big, trees like the California redwood may not be as impressive.
Luckily, even though the gravitational pull of the earth will be stronger, it still won't be
enough to break the moon apart. See, in order for that to happen, the moon would have to be within
the earth's Roche limit. This is the minimum distance the moon can approach the earth without
being torn apart by tidal forces. This happens because the near side of the moon is pulled in
harder than the far side. When the moon gets close enough to the earth, the gravity holding it together
is overcome by this cosmic tug. Inside that limit, earth's gravity will tear the moon apart, giving
us a ring like those around Saturn. And the more earth there is, the more it will heat up. See,
if there are more unstable elements in the crust and interior, more heat will reach the surface and
there may be much more volcanic activity. And I don't know about you, but I'd rather not live
in a world where there's a constant threat of an exploding volcano. Oh, wait, are we already living
in that? I'm looking at you, Yellowstone. Anyway, if you could live anywhere in the universe,
no limitations. Where would it be and why? If I could, I'd totally live in Jupiter's great red
spot. It'd be pretty dangerous. All right. That doesn't answer my question. What happens to the
sun? What happens to our sun? We live in strange times. For 200 years now, starting with Thomas
Robert Malthus, demographers have been sounding the alarm that there isn't enough space and
resources on earth and that there's an oversupply of people. Don't we the ocean? The earth belonged
to the class of planets called super earths and had a mass and size two or even 10 times larger.
Would it solve all of our problems? Or on the contrary, would terrible consequences await us?
According to the assumptions of Mickey Rosenthal from the University of California,
Santa Cruz, our planet had every chance of becoming a super earth, but this was prevented
by Jupiter, which blocked the earth's access to additional building material that could have made
it much larger. If it weren't for Jupiter, the earth would have grown and almost everything on
our planet would have shrunk several times over. And this is not a matter of proportions at all,
but one of enhanced gravity to over increase to a hundred and on a super earth with double
earth's mass, your weight would increase to 150 kilograms or 330 pounds and up to 750 kilograms
or 1650 pounds is almost 10 times greater than the was close to that of Kepler 20 B
with part of the core. This means that the magnetic field protecting us from solar wind could
disappear and the sun, anyone who survived the frequent meteor showers would wait here in such
water due to the high pressure. The ocean floor would be covered with a thick layer of ice,
which would make the carbon cycle and yeah, we would die between the atmosphere and the bowels
of the planet impossible. In fact, according to Hilkey Schlichting from the University of
California, Los Angeles, if our planet was a super earth, all the water would simply evaporate.
According to her assumption, the earth would rotate much closer to the sun in orbit,
making a complete revolution in only 100 days. Orbit is considered habitable if the star is
smaller than our son, but at such a distance from our son, all the water on a super earth
would simply evaporate. Rodrigo Luger from the center from computational astrophysics
at the Flatiron Institute suggests that all super earths evaporate, except that instead of steam,
they turn into liquid water. He believes that super earths are formed from separate pieces of
ice. Then they migrate closer to their star. That's water. And an ocean appears completely
covering the surface of the planet. Perhaps such planets are the most common in the universe. Among
the more than 4,000 exoplanets discovered by the Kepler space telescope, about 30% fall in the
super earth class. If we want to migrate in search of a better place to live, we need to focus
exclusively on super earths. After all, the remaining 70% truth, it's not a super earth.
Its theoretical mass and size are not much larger than our earths. However, all known is much closer.
Okay. Diana Kasikowski, a researcher at the Max Planck Institute for Astronomy in Germany,
believes there may be liquid water on planet GJ 357D. So she plans to search for other signs
of life on it in the near future. A little further, at a distance of 39 light years from-
Oh, you're making it sound so weird.
...is another super earth, GJ 180D.
I told you it was earths. I fucking told you this was fucking happening.
Everybody, do you- Listen to me. Four and a- Three or four hours ago, I was talking about
how many fucking earths existed. There's a shitload of earths. We're one of like a million
earths. Everybody calls me crazy. This guy has like a list of four of them already.
It's 7.5 times larger than the earth, but its main feature is unique. Most exoplanets are
tidally locked, meaning the same side always faces its star like the moon towards the earth.
This makes it impossible to form the magnetic field necessary-
...a brown and a red dwarf. Still, scientists have found candidates for life among other
types of planets. For example, K2-18b. It's considered a super earth, but its composition
is more like a mini-Neptune. This is an intermediate class of planets-
And weirdly enough, none of the inhabitants have noses. Trying to figure out
science just couldn't figure out why.
What do they name the planets like this? Why wouldn't they call it like, I don't know, like
earth five? Earth like ten? Earth like twenty? Why is it like KGI-42BE1? Just say earth like
one and just keep numbering them. It's literally trillions. So count to trillion.
It's not like we don't have the numbers to count them. It could be earth like EL-1000 whatever.
You could you could hyphen it. You could change it. DC Comics Universe trademarked that idea.
Watch TikTok compilations. Why the hell would I do that?
All right, let's go back to this. We watch more science. Name the eight planets without looking.
Sure. Saturn, Jupiter, Neptune, and Earth, and Mars, Venus, and Mercury, and Jupiter.
Did I miss one? I said Mars. Uranus. How could I forget the fucking comedy planet?
A gotcha war with supersonic powers. Enemies who are hit by his warp speed sonic
nitorio move don't even realize they've been hit until it's too late. They're dead.
I'll give it a try. Where's he? Sonic Samurai. Sonic. All right, we're gonna have to take away
Ant-Man. No, I want to test him out. All right. Command girl has to go away for now. 320.
350. Where's the double ninja? There we go. Water. Resident sleeper. Liquid water.
This is my enemy. Oh, sweet. I can handle both of you. Orochi. Let's go.
Gotcha. Slaves of the humans. I don't really follow that. Fly away. Turn and fire. I got grabbed.
I got grabbed. I got grabbed. I got grabbed. I got grabbed. He grabbed me. He got me. All right,
come on, Ant-Man. Do you have bugs? This guy sucks. Unfortunately, he's not very good. Yeah,
I'm sorry. This is a bench scenario here. This is a bench. This is a bench. Your bench. Check out
this new guy. Cool. Pretty, pretty strong. My God. Come here. The dash is good, but not against
these guys. Where'd you get that? He's weird. That's all I have to say about that. Hey, where'd
you go? He's weird. It looks like Seath. No, he's weird. Hey, welcome to the stream, guys.
Look at this guy. He's weird. See you in four minutes when I talk again. Come on. He's got such
good characters. Is there another dragon? Show us your fingernails. No, I feel like you did some
weird things you want. It's a weird request that I'm not going to give to you. I don't know. I
don't know what you're doing. I'm going to lose. Just getting stomped again because he has all the
best characters in the game. Look at this guy. Where'd you get this thing? Stop making excuses,
man. I have a little baby ninja. He has Seath the dragon and all the Power Rangers. It's not fair.
Got to train. You're okay. No, you can get grabbed. Get rid of this dumb bug. I don't know. I don't
like you. You hair. No, not for this one. I'm going with gunman. Gunman, gunman, gunman, gunman.
And then, of course, bringing you back. Solid so far. All right, and then one more. Level two.
I like it better. Just redo the whole loadout. No, I just did. And we're going to do this first.
The bench warmer crew in. We'll have enough of them eventually. This game blue. Where's Drew crew?
I don't know about that. I don't know about that happening anytime in the next
six months. Oh, if you weren't here earlier, we could talk about it.
Block may not have been here earlier. Working on your calendar. May 15th and 16th. I'll be in the
studio. Green screen DLC for free. Volume two and the Easy Bake Oven stream. We'll be back to back
that weekend. May 15th and May 16th. Pretty much walked in.
What about toon town? Yeah, we'll probably do that. We'll probably do all the we're going to do
the MMO grab bag too. Pretty soon here as well. Probably within the next week or so.
I just want to get it set up. There's a lot about toon town. I'm in the process of explaining to
you what happened to toon town and what's going to happen to toon town and where we're going to
do to town and when toon town is going to happen. What about toon town? Oh, we also have to go back
to VR too. That's another thing. I'm trying to feel better in a process. I have a ton of VR
games that I have to play that have come out. We'll do that for like a week. We'll do a VR week.
We'll probably do that at the end of May. That sounds like a good idea to me.
But when is No More Heroes 2? All right. Okay. I'll give you a date. I'll give you a date.
No More Heroes 2. Hopefully never. What? Okay. We're going to do No More Heroes 2 on Monday,
May 4th. Oh, Wing Soldier. That's my birthday. Uh-huh. Happy birthday. Get a crossbow,
arrow shot, wing sword, and fly. Wing Soldier is a former border guard and his sharp eyes never
miss a target. Use the X button to soar over your enemies and unleash your attack. Give him a try.
200. Not bad. Who do we replace? 230. I can put... Who's somebody's 200? Isn't there somebody's for
200? 330. What? 220. Here comes the end of the stream voice. Uh-oh. You're not wrong.
Let's see tomorrow, though. You're not wrong.
That's actually pretty good. Is that good enough, though, to justify having nothing else?
That's all this guy has. I mean, it has a good recharge rate. Does he even have... Oh, no,
he does have an attack. Okay. He's having a little bit of trouble with the regular default
guy. Okay. He's not terrible. He's not terrible. He's going to end the stream with what? All right,
I have to pay attention. Wait. Why is my calendar up? Please play Patapon. What's Patapon on? How do
I play it? What am I going to play it on? It's on the PSP. What the fuck? How am I supposed to do
that on PS4? Okay. Okay. I'm going to be playing Patapon day after tomorrow. That's done. Got it.
Locked it in. That's a lie. It's not. What's happening tomorrow? I love this game. I want
to play it tomorrow. I love it. I love this game. It's so fun. It's fun just to play. Come on. I
never play just a game and play. I'm always pooping my pants and shit my pants. I'm playing this.
I got just turned into. Damn. Give it to me. Play tomorrow. Yeah. I'm going to play this tomorrow.
Then we're going to do Patapon day after that. Don't worry. I'm going to get my fill out of this
game over the next 24 hours. Trust me. Have I ever played Wattam? No, I have not. I heard it's very
fun though. All right. This is it. I'm at the end. I need that helmet back. Who's my ally? Because
they're kicking the shit out of this guy. Don't die. This is all he has. I have to get around him.
I'm just doing support inquire. He'll just go in and dive in and kill him.
It is another person. We're going to play Devil May Cry 2. I don't know.
Spawning in and getting hit right in the mouth and dying. That's too bad.
Yes. Literally any one of them, but this is the third claw robot. I don't want three of these.
Give me another one. Oh my God. 100. Why are you fighting both us and the death force? Revenge.
The gachaborgs are the enemies of my father. Vito, I will give you a free lesson. The death
crystal is an important item that can bring you to the sky fortress. Next time, let's battle to
see which of us will be the ultimate winner. So his father. Ultimate winner. Finish it? I have
to finish this. What are you talking about? This is the, I'm almost at the end of the game.
What do you, how do you, how the hell would you know that? Up until like 12 hours ago,
you guys didn't even know this game existed. I want ship. I like ship. I want more ship.
I want like three of them in a row. Google. Is it, is it time to beat things on gachaborgs?
I don't know. I'm not sure they would be. I mean, it's like, it's, there's only 12 to 30 hours.
Main story, 10 and a half main and extras 22 and a half. I'm not just doing only story missions,
but you are. I'm not. As you have to remember, we've paused like three times to talk about
fucking like dog food. This has been at least a full probably 45 minutes of this stream.
And the last one had been about, I've been dog food conversations in quotes.
All right. I want to send these to the warehouse. Fuck these things.
It's taking up space. These battle girls send them to the warehouse.
What are you 350? Why can't you be 330? That's annoying. Which one are you? There you go.
I'll use. Yeah, you're pretty good. Well, here's the thing. When I play tomorrow,
if I finish the game, when I finish the game, I'll probably finish the game tomorrow.
If it's still, I'm not just going to stop streaming if it's only been a few hours.
Like I said, we go, we're going to be going like four to six hours a stream.
Defeat the special unit. Here comes the third day of this.
Okay. That hurt. That hurt. Oh, why? What the fuck? Oh my God. Why? Somebody broke something
fucking crazy. I had, I read it and it fucking made me get hurt. I fucking can't even. Why did
you say that? Can a nuke hit a plane? Oh, sick. Drop it. No, I'm going to get hit by the nuke.
Ooh, just outside. Wait, here it comes again. Quick run. Run. He's going to kill this as well,
isn't he? I'm going to hide in the shoe box. I'm safe. We should have worked. Don't fire that
thing point blank, man. Nope. One, two, three. One, two, three. I can't even do it. I have to
have like four glasses of wine. It was a fresh meme, fat earther. I think you just did. I think
you just did. Little hill. Ooh, the dragon's den. Let's do it. Same team. 7900 GF. All right.
Give them everything you got. Turn. Go. Blast turn. Go. Flat turn. Go. Flat turn. Fire. Hey.
Fucking goddamn fucking game. Play this tomorrow. Yeah, see if I play this tomorrow.
Fucking game is so stupid. What power do you have? I'm not even close. Holy shit. I'm doing it.
What the fuck? One of them is doing ice. Why did you fall out of the sky?
Okay. Mike, mute. What? I should fix it. Whoa, watch out. Did you copy a dragon? That's actually
a really good idea. You probably can. I'm still doing okay though. I'm going to save this power.
Or am I? Oh, super frog. I can't stop saying that, can I? This one's so many dragons. What
the hell? I won't ever stop. I won't. Excuse me. Do I have an ally still? Or they did. Dead.
Dead. Well, I did a lot of work. Right through the gut. Which one's more dangerous? Ice or
that's bad. It's okay. I gotta get out. Oh, come on. I didn't even see. It wasn't even on the screen.
It wasn't even on the screen. Important. Here we go. Die and... All right. This one was kind of
annoying. Glad I don't have to do that again. Real wink. It's a bad dodge ratio. Oh well. Dragon.
Nice. Yes, yes, yes, yes. Give me another one. Give me ice dragon too. Oh, that's what we call
good. How much are they worth? Let's take a look. Thunder dragon. 1100. 500 health. Thunder bomb
and thunder breath. Roger Borg, who was born from a huge storm cloud. The thunder dragon is an
incarnation of electricity and can control lightning using his horn as a lightning rod.
Cool. Fire dragon's a thousand. Fire breath and fire bomb. Huge shits. Big bits.
Uh, there were big bits. 5,000 of them from core monster. 50 bucks. 5,000 bits. They were right.
Thanks for the huge money core monster and core monster says, are you doing okay Jerma?
Yeah, I'm doing great. I'm doing great. I'm having a blast. I'm having a great time. Things are going
good. Hope they are going good with you as well. Thanks for the gigantic money. More community
subs coming in from Mick. Thanks a lot, Mick. Six community subs. Remember blink twice. Three,
480. Three, 10. I like you. Let's try the dragon. Uh, dragon over here. Let's do it. Defeat the
ultimate cannon unit. That's the longest I've gone without blinking. I have no idea. All right. It's
the mega cannon. He's so slow. Holy shit. He's gone. I'm getting hit with everything.
All right. Settle down. This thing's a fucking firework. What? He's one of those fireworks that
you sit on the ground and light like those fountain things. Bad matchup. What the fuck?
Oh, cause he. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's all right. I'll get it right here. Just don't get
anywhere near him. I mean the blast. That's probably it, right? Is it two of these? If this
two of these is going to be bad. Oh, there's like five of these actually. This is like probably
four or five of these. I need fast flyers. I know you want sex appeal with this dream,
but I don't think the dragon's for you. That's funny. I fast you. We need speed. Fast, fast,
fast. Who's fast? Battle girls are fast. Valkyries fast. Uh, other Valkyries are fast.
So it's going to be just about dashing around and flying around. Let's try it.
You also need people that are fast. So you come on in. Damn it. I had a joke there.
Restart it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. What happens if I quit? I'll do it next time.
All right. Let's make sure I have full charge. Get the fuck out. Hey, get what the where are
all these people coming from? It got me. It got me grabbed. Get away from me. Touch that.
It's like the samus ball. Oh my God. Oops. Holy shit. That wasn't fast enough. Can't shoot up. Can
you? This thing's still on me. Oh, this sucks. Ass. Okay. I got to be chunky people, beefy.
Jesus. This is bad. It's because of the dumb capture device thing. Dodge. I can't move.
Just dodge. Just dodge that. Dodge it. Just run. Just dodge that. Make a dick flatten. All right.
It's time. It's time to call somebody up for the minor league. You get in here. You get in here.
You get in here. What? Oh, I had secret weirdos. No, none of you. Not hatchet, man. He sucks. Just
give him a shot. Oh, who else can I even use here? Thunder dragon. If this doesn't work,
I'm going to do thunder dragon. 200 points. Oh, but just get a free ninja.
Yes. Yes. Here we go. Go. Get over there. He's going to make it. He's going to make it.
He's going to make it. He's going to make it. Oh, yes.
All right. Time to bring in the big guns. Can't shoot something that's behind you.
I'm going to try thunder dragon. Under dragon and it's time for thunder dragon.
Under dragon and then hatchet man. Strategy is just fly immediately. Where's the dragon?
Wait. Okay. We're going to get over there with the ninja. Just kill hatchet man. Is anybody fast here?
I didn't even mean to press that button, but we're going to use mana.
Copy. I don't think I can copy them. Made it. All right. Here we go. I'm supposed to fly.
You know, you've been trying. I said it worked. It worked. It worked. It worked.
It's going to stay in the corners. Oh, fuck. Fly the other way. Fly the other way. Get up.
Jump. Jump. You fucking worthless. Jump in the air. I couldn't do anything. I was stun locked.
Can I just have like five of these guys? Fuck this mission. God damn it.
Do X with the dragon. All right. I'm going to do it right now. Heal the support units.
Well, I mean, I just, I die instantly. If I get, if I'm on any part of the map that he's facing,
I'm just dead. It's an instant dead. You got to be all the way at his side. Are you going to get
right? And this doesn't matter. It's over. I've tried and I'm dead. All right. Get over there
and just zap them. Just keep it up. Just puke on them. Oh, that's great. And now I'm fucking
grabbed. That does a lot of damage. All right. Where's the other one? Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
What the fuck? Oh my fucking Jesus. Get up and grab your head, man. It's not that I'd get up there.
My head. Okay. X immediately. I'm pressing X the second the game starts. Oh, I got to be the
editing. Here we go. X immediately. Give me a fucking break. Does cover work? Find out right
now. Nope. He shot me through the wood. It's up to you. Okay. Okay. I'm going to get, what am I
going to do? I don't think I can copy. I will try it though. Use the jet. Jet actually was pretty
good. I wish I had more planes. I guess I could probably unlock them here. Okay. Get over there
and copy. It actually works. It worked. No, how do I? It actually worked. That's unbelievable.
I can do that. Where's the other one? That might be all I needed. Get the fuck out of the way.
Forget about the head. Just get out of the way. He's going to fucking fire at you. How the fuck
are you supposed to get the fuck? Come on. Battery man. Whatever you are. Get over there.
Dude, the thing just turns on a dime when it wants to fire. Getting close. It fires. I can copy. I
can copy. Copy, copy, copy and charge. Shoot it. Is it B or X for the charge? I don't know.
Did it fire? What is going on? Why can't I know? I was holding X and then I got hit and
all my health disappeared. That's called losing. I have to hold this. Wait, I have to hold
fire at that. It worked. Oh my God. It worked. Okay. Is there any more of them?
It's okay. I killed two of them. It comes three. Get over there. You fucking grabbed me. You piece
of shit. I can't believe it. Dumbest thing ever. Un-fucking-believable. Why? What the fuck?
Battery man. Attack him. There's another one over there. Get away. Get away. Get away. Get away.
Where'd he go? Just stun lock him. Don't let him do anything. He's up too high.
Oh, the screen. All right. That. Oh, okay. Just needs, it's foolproof. I just need support.
Heal the fuck out of me. Oh, the hatchet guy's still in here. Right. Shit. He's got to go. He's
got to go. Suck. Oh, it's okay. It's not okay. Fuck you. No. Get out of here. Fucking battery.
Wait, what? Is everything fine, right? Where'd they go? Are they here? They're in storage?
No, they're not. Are they still here? Do I just not see them? What's wrong with me? Have I gone
crazy? They're there. First column. They're right there on screen. Where? I see you. You're here.
Where's, okay. I thought I had to reset the whole thing. I got to find a character that can do this.
Nobody got deleted, right? Wait, what? Wait, what? Hold on. Speaking of wait, what? Wait, what?
Wait, what? What? Here we go. We can edit that together to make it sound better. I'm going to
stand still. The shield blocks attacks. Will it block this attack? That's the question. We found
our ultimate counter. Get the fuck away from me. I have to be in front of him. No, attack.
No cheese for you. Come on, man. What the fuck? Hold on a minute. Does battery man have a shield?
No, he sucks. You have a shield and you're better. I'll get you close. And then who does
like an absolute shitload of damage? We need something. We need somebody that does damage.
360. Wait, the pink magnet. Oh shit. That's not a bad idea.
I just, no, I picked the wrong support. Like it matters. I'm only picking this because this
guy has a shield. Okay. Get close enough. Block. But your shield not good enough to block. Wait,
what? I blocked that shit. Oh, it might be it only blocks energy attacks. Nice. Where's the other one?
Firing anymore. This thing's not firing. I can't even aim this. Can't grab you. That's so much
damage. If I could just keep this guy alive, you see how unbelievable that is. They spawn across
the whole damn map. That's horse shit. That's the definition of absolute dog shit. He just,
he turns so quickly and then just blows up the whole map. All right. If I throw the head,
I'll take 50% damage off of them. And then he shoots me and I explode and die because he
fills the whole map with a radar beam. Just build a fucking army with low cost units. I'll try that.
Peasant army. Oh wait, they're in the warehouse. Okay. I got 910 flying units too. Flying units
are pretty cheap, aren't they? 200, 230, 240. What's the cheapest thing? Can I sort by cheap?
Revolver gunman. Uh, I got 440, 240. All right, let's go. No, these guys are annoying. They help.
They can't kill us all. Stay behind them. Stay behind them. They can't fucking kill us all.
All right. Oh shit. I didn't mean to do that. They can't kill us all. Together we are massive.
Together we are one. Individually we are weak. Together we are strong. Attack. Their defenses
are down. Attack. Where one dies, one will return. Final battle. This is it. Magnet guy really helped
too. It's over. Hopefully a crystal that can be combined into a cool monster robot. Nice. Okay.
Another one. I'm gonna run out of room for these. What am I gonna do with all these Funko Pops?
All right. All right. That's it. See you tomorrow. That's it. Same time, same place. See you tomorrow.
Tomorrow we are going to, I wonder how long, how much longer it'll take us to beat the gacha
force. We beat this game in an hour or two. That's fine. We'll do something else. And then
of course I'm going to do Patapon the day after that. That's game fun. Hope you had fun. I did.
We will do Patapon on, what's today? Tuesday? Yeah. On Thursday. Play Jump King. I can't do
that anymore. I deleted my save. Somebody got a screenshot hopefully eventually. Thanks for
watching. We'll see you tomorrow. Have a great rest of your night. I'll be here tomorrow.
Good night. Goodbye. Take care. See you later. Go into the bits and the subs. Start that music.
Why don't we? So earlier this evening, Peaceful Haley gave $2.50. Excited for the green screen
stream finally, but I do hope you're doing well. I'm doing all right. I'm doing good. Like I said
before, doing this whole thing where I don't sit down for that long, more than six hours,
allows me to stay loose. I can move around. It's still a problem, but it's probably going to be
for a long time until it is actually solved. So it's not like, hey, I've got to get this figured
out. It's going to be gone in a day. I'll see you in a day. I think I just have to come to terms
with the fact that this is going to be a long-term thing that I have to figure out and deal with and
treat it and see what happens. But it's, I'm feeling better when I'm able to move around.
I am doing well though. Thank you Maxtronaut for the 400 bits. Jerma, the virus took both my job,
so I can't sub. Don't worry about that. But here's all my bits. You're my favorite streamer and I'm
so excited for another round of laughs. Don't worry about subbing to this channel. Use that money on
you. Thank you though. Cream corn. Thanks for 250. Wow. Cream corn 31. I can't believe I haven't
played stalker call of Pripyat before. This game is so good. Thanks for letting me play it on your
couch. I'm going to do it on the green screen. I'm going to sit there and pretend to play a game
like with you. I'll give you a bunch of different clips of me on a, you know, I mean me sitting on
couch, just reacting to things. We don't have very many seated reactions. They kind of need to be
there. And I'm just going to pretend to sit. I'm going to sit down on a fake chair so you can put
me seated wherever you want. Obstinawal, thanks for the three dollars and 22 cents. Jerma, when he
plays gotcha force. Hold on. Okay. We'll, we'll try this one. Is that even going to work? Wait,
is it just tiny? Is that the problem? Oh, it's tiny. What is that? I don't know. That's, that's
me playing gotcha force. What's more, why do I have a big dent in my head? I don't know.
I didn't make it. Hurly boy, thanks for the five community subs. Don't think I caught that earlier,
but thank you. Rosophila, thanks for the 250. You're rambling about how God and aliens would
create like a hundred planets instead of just one is actually a strong argument for us living in a
simulation. If a species had the power to simulate an entire simulation, then they may as well simulate
millions. And if that's the case, there's a much higher chance that we're one of the millions of
simulations than the one real one. Not a strong argument for anything. Thanks to the 250. Saint
sauce. Thanks to three dollars. Please play Spore someday. I will go back to it one day. I tried it
on stream and it was flashing and it was bugs and it was really, really bad. Maybe one day.
Super Bruce, thanks for the 10 community subs and the five dollars here. Reasons I watched
Jerma 95, 10% gameplay, 90%. He's ranting about aliens brownies or whether the random
shit never changed. We had at least 55% gameplay tonight. 60% gameplay. Something like that.
Thanks to the five dollars though. Smelly boy, thanks for the 250. I'm going to report your
alien God rant to our atheism. So you better watch out buster. Subreddit for everything.
I freak out. Thanks for the five dollars and banned from giving messages after the last time
and banned from giving messages on stream and the screen and the screen face cam. Now they said I
did it. Somebody says I did it in all capitals. Congratulations. Congratulations. I will no longer
read bits messages from that view. I'm just telling you, I've look, there's only so many times you
like give porn codes and make, talk, make up, talk about how you drink at work and stuff. I can't do
it. I can't do it. I just can't do it. Not safe. He hates that guy. I told you last time. I was
thinking about just not reading anymore. I'm going to hold myself to that. Banned from giving bits
for life. You banned from giving me money. All right, we're going to move on. Jerma's low key
and asshole. You're one of the people that used one of the porn codes like a month ago, aren't you?
Okay, making sure we know. Hey Sticks Renegade, thanks for two dollars and fifty cents.
Five grand reminds me when I spent really roughly four thousand dollars on my multiple furry
commissions over the past four years. That's not a lot. I remember a bidding war on a furry commission
that went upwards of three thousand dollars for one art. What's a furry commission? You pay
somebody to make a furry art of you? How big is a five thousand dollar picture? Is it a mural?
Furry mural. Furry mural. Whatever. That's a lot of money. That's a lot of money. Hopefully it was
worth it. Hopefully you got quality content there. I hope so. Ajax, the mediocre. Thanks for the
fifteen dollars. I just watched the public domain VOD earlier. I grew up watching The Three Stooges
and it was really cool to see it again. Love what you do. That was a fun night. Good to do that
again. I'm glad you enjoyed it. The Three Stooges and The Ritz Brothers. We have to watch more Ritz
Brothers movies. They knocked it out of the park with the gorilla. Thanks for the fifteen dollars.
Glad you liked it. A post thanks to the five hundred bits post. They say, hey Jerma, I had a
massive panic attack the night before last. It was probably the worst one I've ever had. I was crying
so hard I puked and was hallucinating. A woman that was painting her nails and telling me to kill
myself. Holy shit. I've been extremely depressed my whole adult life due to some medical problems
that forced me to be bedridden from ages 16 to 18. Even then your videos would always make
me laugh regardless. Damn. I've never I've never hallucinated before but I can imagine
that hallucinating is fucking horrible. It's just you something is there. Like a person is there.
But I can't even imagine. I can't imagine. How do I know I haven't? I mean I guess maybe I don't
think I ever have. They gave another five dollars and they say continued. They say during yesterday's
stream you read my chat messages like four times and that made me feel so much better. That alone.
I got some sleep. I actually got some sleep which is pretty rare for me nowadays. I just want to let
you know that you have been a massive factor in the maintenance of my mental and emotional health.
The bottom of my heart love you. If I can have that kind of effect on somebody I'm just happy that it
I'm happy that there's something here for you to care about and like and enjoy. But I also hope
and I implore you to if you haven't already is to try to get a professional involved. Try to get
yourself on the path to getting better. It's a never-ending process but if somebody gets something
out of this stream if you think it's fun you like to be around here that's I'm happy. I really am
happy that you're around and that you're here to hang out and have fun and laugh and talk shit and
enjoy the streams. Please please also take care of yourself because even if this gives you some
this stream can give you happiness or even if some people have said this is one of the only
things that can. I hope that over the course of the next some odd years of your life you can find
steps to find other things that do make you happy too. Trying to get healthy and trying to get
yourself on the right path is everyone's trying to do it but I wish you the best. I really do.
Thank you post. Have a great night. Thank you. It can be dangerous to put so much stock in one
thing for your happiness. Yeah and that's kind of what I mean. That's kind of what I mean by that
is trying to find other stuff that you know makes you happy. It might take a while to find it but
it's a lot healthier that way but thank you again. Silent serenity thanks for 250.
It should be noted that the UFO declassified videos aren't new and have been in the circulating
on the internet for years. More so it's my understanding that the military has a ton of
these recordings and usually they're determined to be things like birds planes or balloons upon
inspection. They tend to look really crazy just because of the flight and camera physics involved.
Videos were originally leaked by a space conspiracy conspiracy theory company
owned by the guitarist of blink 182. It's a very very strange last sentence that I've it's like
okay all right I haven't seen these videos I I don't know I whatever there's aliens there
there is aliens look we're just still here if the aliens if aliens wanted to like focus a
fucking death star beam at us do what do you think you don't think they've already would have
done that by now what's stopping them you know what what's like stopping the aliens from like
just death starring the planet I don't think they want to I don't think they care for now
it's taking a while to get here wait did you think they they fired it already they fired it like
four million years ago it's just taking like six billion years to get here it's coming they
already fired it yeah we still yeah we still got 5.9 billion years left well that's not true
that you know that that's assuming all the trees are here that's assuming the grass still grows
not so sure omega lull 2021 omega lull 2021 why is that so funny hey the boom town rats thanks for
the thousand bits i'm gonna i'm going through a bad breakup and your streams have given me so
many laughs i especially love the public domain movie night they have me in tears from laughing
thanks so much for doing what you do yeah and we'll do it again i think that was i loved that
it's already over here about your breakup hopefully you feel better about it soon
which you will a finn thanks for the two dollars and 54 cents jeremiah i want you to know your
thoughts on putting the music and community content nights between the art and videos
it'll give a good segue and save you the trouble of having to wrestle with the bits at the same
time that's not a bad idea we'll give that a try next time thanks to the 254 yoda 985 thanks for
germ i'm begging you to listen to this before you do the green screen for the love of god
please shoot stuff from angles that aren't you facing the camera at all times it makes it hard
to edit stuff that means well now i have i i only i don't have like 12 cameras just move the cameras
buy more you will earn i did i did a bunch of stuff from angles why are you showing us your
hearthstone deck i am don't call him dubas um no i don't worry i'll get a shitload of other angles
but i mean there only is so much i can work with with one guy in studio we'll see i'll try where
the hell was i oh yoda 985 thanks for the two dollars and 69 cents germ my school just did a
q and a with will ferrell over zoom what it was cool but i didn't get to ask him my question so
i'm just gonna pay you like two dollars and ask you instead what movie do you enjoy more step
brothers or anchorman i'm a john c rally fan i probably have to say step brother how the hell
did you have a q and a with will ferrell my school had like local gas station employees would come
in and teach us stuff and do assemblies let's get will ferrell that's pretty cool that's really
cool actually celebrities are desperate for attention right now i gotta go around and do a
bunch of school zoom assemblies well turn on a live stream you know i like turn on a fucking
twitch stream will come on will ferrell turn on a stream load up gotcha force let's see it
oh i can't believe oh i what did i just get no no a rare one no oh oh i'm trying i'm really trying
as hard as i can that started okay i'm trying that was like one emotion that he does no that's one
part of a tenth of his personality i kind of nailed it for one second that's it that's adam
sandler what are the other nine emotions i don't know why don't you ask him on zoom at your next
school assembly sure he'll answer it for you hey moss lion thanks for the 250 i think i recall
you saying that you and kim played animal crossing off stream during your move and then you later
implied you weren't into the idea of playing it live anymore that's all well and good but it'd be
fun for everyone to get a tour of your island at some point as an aside point much love to you in
the community you're all a blast oh i just have to hook up the switch the switch is not hooked
up in here but the ship kind of sailed on animal crossing for me because of the move that was just
what we did kim and i would just pass it back and forth and play it maybe maybe when i get the
switch in here we can take a look peaceful hailey thanks for the 250 so i was wondering your opinion
on fixed camera angles like what resident evil used to do do you think they would ever come back
i hope not people say it's too risky but they also said that about over the shoulder cameras
in resident evil and it worked well i don't know i think seeing a fixed camera game in this day
and age would be interesting and refreshing i really hope not i hate them i'm one of those i'm
one of those people that makes like the five page reddit essay about how much i don't know i don't
like them hand controls get rid of them don't ever have them come back fixed camera angles they is
really this is like a couple scenarios maybe where it'd be interesting but it was just uh no
there isn't even one remake is amazing yeah but i like to see i'm like i know it's part of it
i know though you can't see what's in front of you i want to see what's in front of me you open up a
door and the camera angle is fixed and then you have that problem with fixed camera angles and
they'll never solve this this is the this is the number one reason why i hate it because the
trigger point for the other camera angles is this one line if you cross that line it changes the
camera if you cross back it goes back to the other camera so you end up having a scenario
sometimes where you are trying to run or do something and the and the camera angle changes
like four times in 10 seconds it's it's unnerving that's the number one reason why i don't like it
now if it was a truly fixed camera it would be hard to do that i mean just only one angle but
yeah you can't do that i mean it's impossible i don't know that me saying this is like oh fps
these fucking zoomer millennials he wants he wants to shoot things he wants it to be a shooter
he wants a third person first person he wants to shoot things he's a shooter i know i know and i
look i get that argument too when both sides are upset with each other that's how you know
that you came to a true compromise larry david up down left right there he is my that's my guy
he's like wait why is he why is he god i just did i did like the father son and i looked up and i um
okay larry centrist dave no larry david don't how dare you larry david is unbelievable and
he's i would take a larry david god if larry david just came out and was like you know i i
think i'm gone and everyone agreed i'd be fine with it i'll be like this is actually kind of good
and the first thing i'm gonna do is introduce fixed cameras i was waiting for the reaction for that
one because i wasn't i wouldn't feel in that one all right though i think some of you might be
too tired to do the minus button at this point you were like reaching over like
fucking tired i don't know who cares oh i've done it i've done it like 200 times today
i'll give you this one punk hey remixed place thanks with three bucks germa i just got a job
at a casino and it's been terrible just puke everywhere no one cleans the place our clientele
consists of 20 overweight women screaming about buying a new mobile home they don't even buy
anything they just come here to scream every time i ask the manager to do something about it he
throws 20 in my face and goes back to staring at the italian place across the street he's been
watching it for four days without sleep now i'm worried for my safety i liked it hey magpied
thanks for three dollars you should play universe sandbox one day i'd love to see you try and make
the solar system according to whatever the fuck you're drawing right now is that a good game
should i give it a try all right i'm writing this down universe sandbox didn't i try to play
a game like this dude this kind of looks fun totally shit this looks really fun cool all right
i'll play this at some point let's get the credits on the screen how can the janitor be into place
at the same time just quick he's really quick here come the credits all the subs community subs
all of you they're both to run by i really appreciate it i could say it a thousand times
but it's still true thank you so much for subscribing to this channel when you just don't
have to we will finish up the bits we had sir canine gave 250 ermah is not short he's just
impacted by gravity more than most people by understanding that the understanding chat that's
probably true at some point we'll figure it out hey new york thanks for the three dollars here's
what you want to know about light the sun thank you finally a fucking scientist the sun radiates
energy equally in all directions this means that if the earth were huge we'd get the same
amount of light as long as we were the same distance to the sun visible light is measured
in lumens which are measured in square feet of coverage no there wouldn't be a tiny spotlight
on a huge earth love the streams fucking quack thanks for the three bucks it's that easy a bunch
of science a bunch of science a bunch of knowledge and a bunch of factual information a bunch of
science what a fucking loser i win omega l l not true sun doesn't distribute energy equally
i'm just kidding hope you know that right um no that's good to know and thanks for telling
everybody that was right not true i'm right you're wrong no i'm right you're wrong you're wrong you're
wrong you're wrong you're wrong the sun is not a centrist yes it is it's the ultimate centrist
actually it is the number one centrist in the fucking universe it is the definition of the
word centrist it's the goddamn center of the fucking milky way galaxy and the universe combined
sun is the fucking center of our galaxy shit is this right yes the sun is in fact yes the sun
in fact our whole solar system orbits around the center of the milky way galaxy the sun's in the
fucking middle you got jupiter the antlion planet venus super cube and a large the large jail where
all the prisoners are i know my stuff i don't need a scientist or a doctor or anthropologist to tell
me these things i know them i can't wait until we can get into that space program and go to the
super cube you're an anarchist no not even close why you want to know why i you want to know why
i'm not i would never be like close even near anarchy who the hell picks up your trash
uh-uh what do i do with it i i'm gonna have to bury it what do i do we have to all fight for
the dump what's where's the dump have we decided it's we'll just choose dumps you would just burn
it i wouldn't do that it would be in your house that's what happened my whole basement would be a
dump i'd have to build a house on top of the other house because i would my basement be full of trash
cans trash bags we shouldn't have single use waste anyways grow organic food dumas the name is dumb
ass nobody tell him where the trash goes during anarchy well judging from every video game i've
ever played about the subject it goes all over the street and all over the people's yards and
all over everything like what game is the last of us i went in my yard all right moving on thank
you sly garf for the five dollars had a dream that germa announced he wasn't going to stream
for a few days and he immediately drop kicked the face came and ended the stream that's fucking
wow holy shit that's a great idea i'm stealing that from you sly garf thanks for the great idea
when i when i want to take a few days off your dream is going to become a reality at some point
in the future curr bumble thanks for the five dollars thanks for sticking with this game even
though chat's being bizarrely negative about it since you'll definitely finish this tomorrow
i want to say you should take a look at the undersides of some of your blockier machine
borgs like g red it's a very small but cute detail on some of them also you might want to try
chozu ju mecha mg it's like gotcha force with giant robots made by the edf devs and got a fan
translation last year all right for your first comment are you telling me to to turn all them
upside down and look under the yes okay and then that other one is that a good game put it on the
list bro put it make sure you guys put in these in the recommended channel i skim through that
and i pull tons of stuff from there every month or two really it's where half of these games even
they came from the first place but thanks for the five dollars curr bumble and the that's we'll
check it out tomorrow news and coffee thanks for 250 i said it before and i'll say it again
i don't understand what's going on here anyway just me again i want to say thanks for showing
this super cool game and blah blah okay whatever that's it i'm honestly sick and tired of this guy
no this is not the message this is real i don't care how much money you give me i won't play god
hand ever now get lost you're banned so do it get lost why would you say that come on i'm not gonna
play god hand i'm sick of it i'm sick of hearing about it i'll probably play that like in a few
weeks hey drosophila thanks for 250 basically your big earth theory needs to be upgraded to a
humongous earth theory sincerely a huge space nerd this is important this is really important
this is like a this is another scientist here let's take a look at this it's a big ass days
are defined by the earth's rotation yeah that's what i said half of earth is illuminated by the
sun while the other half is in its shadow right the sun is a giant sphere beaming light in all
directions okay sure the earth is 100 million miles away from the sun fun fact an earth that's
a hundred times the diameter is approximately the size of the sun what i thought the sun was
just a really bright gumdrop it's that big i thought it was like as big as a fucking like
chevy malibu fucking i'm kidding holy shit a fun fact in earth that's a hundred times the diameter
is probably size yeah okay in both cases the sun shines on half of the sphere that is the earth
right the only way that the spotlight effect could take place or there could be a substantial
difference between night and day is if the sun was a point light extremely close to the earth
or if the earth was thousands of times bigger than the sun well what would happen that oh
we tried to tell you i look as a thought project thanks the 250 and that's cool i'm glad people
are figuring this stuff up i could be your teacher i will see you tomorrow thanks for
watching we still have a few more bits to do but i want to say my goodnights to you
goodbye we have four or five more bits or so ajax the mediocre thanks for 15 dollars they just say
yeet the 15 dollar yeet right there thank you shrimp named slick back thanks for the 15 dollars
1500 bits remember just figured i'd give you some money and let you know that you've been a bright
ray of color for this otherwise dull life especially since i've been working at the
local grocery store the past few weeks i figured i'd get this out before it's too late
ps if you're ever thinking about playing the prototype biohazard bundle it's on sale for
12 dollars until tomorrow i think you'd be right up your alley much love thanks for everything
yeah i i own i think i own a couple of them i think i already own them it was it was a problem
with streaming them because i own prototype one and prototype two i had a bunch of obs problems
the game couldn't be captured right it was all messed up it was glitchy it was laggy
i was thinking about just getting them for xbox 360 and just dealing with the xbox please ban
spammer wait what oh somebody got it somebody's spamming oh well don't spam come on maybe spam it
for anyways uh where were we uh yeah i own prototype one and prototype two probably get
them on xbox though just to make sure they work or look into some mods or patches for the game on
pc thanks for the 15 bucks edmund hakari thanks for five dollars thanks for your streams germa
i had my car stolen on the 20th that sucks between that moving and trying to get a job
with everything going on it's been a real stressful time you've made it easier and have
made me feel a lot better good job with the peasant army at the end it was fun that's how
there's always something so horrible when you hear about that kind of stuff
it's just you feel so awful because you know if somebody takes something from you
whether it's something you've it's a something you've owned for a long time or something that's
expensive it's just thankfully i've never had anything really major taken from me but man is
it scary to think about that i'm really sorry that happened that sucks hopefully you can either get
it back or your insurance can help you take care of that uh the police obviously i'm sure probably
are already involved that's really really i'm sorry to hear that hopefully you get that figured
out thanks for the five dollars i wish you luck wembley ttv thanks for 250 i've been randomly
following your red bubble shop i don't i can now buy germa eats a shoe socks for 58 dollars
which is 72 usd or get a bootleg red bubble design of an illegal quad movie stream sticker
it's a screenshot of that other germa stream during that bug game still nothing tops the
three hundred and seven dollar golden mug with your face on it do not under any circumstance
pay somebody three hundred dollars for a fucking spray painted mug with a jpeg printed on it with
like a label making program no i'm just telling you that i have nothing to do with that and you're
going to be severely disappointed when you get it in the mail that's what my that's what the stimulus
check is for do not spend your stimulus check on a golden fucking mug of my it's not even me
i do that i don't even know who that person is anyways be careful and none of that stuff is
i don't have nothing to do with it i don't have one of those i have two t-shirts on teespring
and maybe soon to be another one in like a year that gives me enough time to make sure that within
the next year some other stuff gets up there thanks to the 250 uh beta pepsi man thanks
to three dollars what would you name your casino slots and lanes of course slots of lanes please
make enamel pins of your emotes please i don't know why i thought for some reason you're talking
about tooth enamel and you wanted to put them on your teeth we are but i don't maybe you are
peaceful hailey thanks to 250 i'm rolling my eyes right now you zoomer millennial
redditor kiano reeves big chungus streamer big i can't big chungus makes me laugh it does
because even if it's a fake story i just imagine somebody coming in
to a store like a game stop and asking for the game big chungus or ps4 or whatever
and it's like the the bugs bunny picture he wanted big chungus that makes me laugh forget
about okay they make the chuckle and then i don't think about it anymore redditor redditor he's a
what okay what other likes can i ask a question what other harry potter schools of like online
can you be in i don't understand this redditor four channel tumblr
tick tock which one of them is okay which one of them well that's the four channel slitherin
that's easy which one of them is griffin door right it hufflepuff is youtube without a doubt
that's just a that's easy too um right it's a griffin door yeah tick tock is ravenclaw
no tick tock is is is is raven tick tock is hufflepuff and youtube is ravenclaw
and tumblr are the people that look into the school from outside the window nobody is ravenclaw
what about facebook facebook is just like one of the computers in one of the libraries
that's all it is what is twitch uh shit hold on do i have this wrong no twitch is
to it like we need like what the death eaters right i don't think twitch don't twitch twitch
might think they're the death eaters and the voldemort's no they're not twitch is hufflepuff
let me remember to get this right youtube is ravenclaw or chance of death eaters i know i
disagree i disagree the only fans are death eaters oh my god okay let's go
uh that's pretty much it well we have one two more sticks renegade thanks for the 250 since
you're apparently going to play any game chats throwing at you today i can i expect jackie chan
stunt master within the next 10 years yeah you probably can yeah yes and finally rip alex trabek
thanks for the five dollars hey germy nice stream bro i looked into the taxes thing and i've decided
not to do them i don't i already pay taxes when i buy shit from the store i hope i don't get in
trouble well you see uh see there are there are multiple different taxes there are sales tax
sales tax exists and that's on consumer goods this income tax the state income tax depending
on if you're in the united states this capital gains tax if you have investments uh there's quite
a few of them actually no uh when you buy um when you buy the nintendo switch at the game stop
you're not paying your year's worth of taxes just want to make sure you're clear on that
yes you are there are only few things certain in life death and taxes that word makes me angry
death and a germ of delay and shitting your pants what taxes yes pay your taxes pay look
everybody fucking hates paying taxes there's nobody i don't there's no one i'm sorry i have
to say this there is nobody that puts their check in the mail to the irs and goes i take it i love
it oh goodbye money i love when you take it please take it nobody let nobody says that nobody but
it's a necessary thing that we all have to do nobody wants to do it and nobody's happy about it
but you got it wait a minute i got a hundred fucking subs why mog at the very end of the
stream just dropped a hundred subs of 100 doing a tax rent during a sub bomb
that's a lot that's a huge amount of subs that's that's that's five hundred dollars
that why mog just paid god damn thank you for that completely unnecessary but it's a huge i'll take
it and i'll thanks for the given 100 people subs and then another one silverjack just gave five
thanks to both of you that was the stimulus check long story short pay your taxes you make
sure you pay your taxes if you owe and you'll make sure if you want to make sure you if you need to
you know get some advice from not from me because i get advice from somebody else that i have a cpa
i have an accountant that helps me so don't take advice from me because i fucking i'm stupid
find somebody that knows what they're talking about five more subs from labster so that's 110
subs thank you the three of you thank you why mog for the fucking hundred and silverjack and
labster not to be overshadowed at all so you know what hey we kind of hold on a second we gotta do
this all right watch this it's increased in speed by a hundred percent five community subs from
west yule thanks west yule let's see who it is after credit the after credit scene is just another
credits that's painfully boring backwards everyone i used to read them yeah i do i do
i do danger illustrate her area between a movie but nope read them now gas station snack boy
crashing hey look at stanktron uh no it can't no it can't no it can't he's too old for this
it's too old try harder polar wizard no once i get the first two letters out of the first one
the next five have gone by already germa tax i'll pay your taxes i just that comment's so fucking
just i want to read that one again i like that one hey germ it was rip alex trebek hey germy nice
dream bro i looked into the taxes thing and decided not to do them don't i already pay taxes when i
buy shit from the store i hope i don't get in trouble well you will if you don't report your
income if you had a substantial income that was taxable it and it was really it you come on be
careful i'm gonna take my chances i have no i i don't have any i'm not a financial advisor
i'm not your dad i am not your i'm not your mom i'm not your cpa i've no i don't know i've no
idea what you're talking about just do your taxes and pay your taxes okay goodbye no i don't want
to do it again okay good night goodbye see you later i'll see you tomorrow have a great rest of
your night take care of yourselves don't do anything i wouldn't do it's not much like for
instance eating a whole can of marshmallow fluff i would do it but don't do that don't be like me
raid raid raid raid raid raid raid raid raid raid raid raid raid raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Raid Ra
Tell Vinny hello. I'll see you tomorrow. I was just typed in slash raid space Vinny
Somebody with that name would have got a really really
Interesting scenario come their way. All right. See you guys tomorrow. Goodbye. Good night. Take care of yourselves