Oops. Okay, hi, hi. There, I'm here now. I gave, there was a spoiler there, but it's okay.
That happens when you have the wrong scene selected when you start your live stream. But hi guys,
how are you? Welcome back. We're gonna go back to the Wii today. We're gonna play a game called
Monster Lab. Will you create the ultimate monster? Perform outrageous experiments. Build your very
own mad monsters. Face creepy quests and challenges in the eerie, uncanny valley.
And pitch your ultimate creations in fierce combat against the super evil Baron and his
grotesque army of monsters. To the back of the box says, he's finally playing Spore.
Oh, this is kind of like Spore, but probably really, really, really dumbed down. The voice
today? What the? I didn't do it. I didn't, whatever. Wait, it's because I, are you, wait,
do you think that this is normal? Hey, the voice is normal today. This is why, this is how I talk
for real. Wait, the fake voice is the real voice. Confused. Just confused the shit out of me.
It's a podcast voice. Podcast voice, tuber voice. You call it whatever you want. It is what it is.
It is. Podcast. How has nobody done that yet? How is it possible that no one on Twitch
has done a podcast? Why, it's so easy. Somebody has done that. Oh, welcome to the podcast?
Like, how the fuck is that not like one of the most popular podcasts on Twitch?
Oh, it does exist. It does exist. All right. Well, whatever. Anyways, let's go. Hope you're
having a good Saturday afternoon. I know I am. This is Monster Lab for the Nintendo
Wiimote. Monster Lab. Hurry up. Hurry up and go. We have to go. Where do you have to go right now?
Where are you going? Hurry up. Go, go. I have to go. Where are you going? All right, here we go.
This game is like, look at the title of the stream. It's like Battling Mr. Potato Heads.
This was a requested video game from the Discord channel. The requested,
recommended Discord channel. I recommend if you have anything that you'd like to see.
I always give it a look. TM. And if it's something that I think would be fun,
I play it on stream to cure the strap. No, I don't need this. I don't have a strap.
This doesn't have a strap. Nunchuck. One of the only games ever that needs it that I've played.
All right, plug it in. Sick. Oh, I thought it was a real place. Who made this game?
What company? Who made this fucking game? Eidos. Hello? What the fuck happened? All right.
That was weird. I, uh, I just went to zero for no reason. Hooray. I'll give this one second to make
sure it's actually going to work. Reset stream for VOD chat, please. I just did. I just turned off the
stream and I turned it back on. So this is, this is technically a new stream. Technically, this is
a, I, this is a new live stream to make sure it doesn't fuck everything up to the bottom.
All right, let's go. Uh, welcome to the stream. Hey, what's going on? This is, uh, Professor
Fuseless. This is, uh, the Wii. Playing the Wii. Welcome to the VOD, everybody. Hi. This is the
monster Wii game. Take control of my monster Gorbok and go help the mayor. There are two streams in
one fucking day. All right. We got to take, this is a monster fighting game. You make your own
fucking monster. You missed the intro. Okay. I'll give you the intro. Uh, think of every
Saturday morning cartoon from 1988 to 1992. That's not very much time. 1988 to like 2010.
That's not very much time. That was like three years. Actually, you know what? That's probably
accurate. This guy's face looks like one of the many photo shops you guys make every fucking
stream of my face. In fact, I'm, I'm, I may in fact believe that somebody made this out. This is me.
This is what you guys do. You like drag my nose up and like pull my mouth down every stream.
Oh, did you send you, I'm glad you're here. Yeah, here it comes. I know. I know. I know.
They are blocking my path to reelection. All right, let's go. I can't wait to make my own fucking
monster. This is the tutorial. Defeat the monsters, blocking the path. You got it.
I'm using somebody else's monster. This is like Mario party, right?
All right. Is this knack? No, this is not knack. This is monster lab.
Warbark versus Mongor. How do you play?
Okay. Yep.
The monster icon in the top left corner displays the health of monster parts. They have parts. Okay.
Okay. All right. All your limbs can get knocked off.
Okay. Why are the robots monsters? That's, is that accurate?
Oh shit. This is just the surge. It's the surge too. If you want a torso is do not move the stick.
Okay. So, uh, select an action. Okay. I want to make my own monster. I want to make,
I'm going to have like a lizard head. I'm going to have fucking pirate legs.
Why would I skip the tutorial? I have no idea how to play. I'm not skipping the fucking tutorial.
And battery number tells you how much energy your monster needs to perform an action.
Okay. That's, that's your mana. Oh, you actually have to point at shit with the
Wii mode. This is their motion control. Okay. It's like an attack action. All right. So
low squeeze hook hunt. Oh, I'm selecting the arm. Okay. The head I can do chomp or roar
left arm is auto fire legs. We're going with leg sweep. All right. This is pretty cool.
He looks like your opponent has a strong face. Why don't you, why don't you face him?
Why? You don't need to face him. When you select an action, the parts it targets on the opponent
are highlighted. Okay. Find an action that targets the right arm. So this is low squeeze.
It's just going for his legs. I squeeze his legs. That's not what I want. Don't wait his right arm.
So that means his right, right? His right arm. Oh, auto fire. It does. Can I bite his arm?
Face cam or his left arm. I was going to bite him. All right. I'm going to bite him. I'm going to
bite him. It does everything bite. All right. I just bit his arm off. Good. But you can grow it.
Can you grow arms back? It's actually pretty cool. Oh shit. So your legs become useless.
You can't run. Face cam. What can face cam for? What fucking reason do you want to face cam?
Why does everything have to be face cam? Yeah. You want a face cam? Fine. Everything's got to
have a face cam these days. You get it. You get it for like 20 minutes. All right. Let's go.
At the back of the delay. To gain more energy, select the dodge or recharge.
All right. So you have to, you have to actually, you have to spend a turn recharging. This is just
like magic the fucking gatherer. All right. Let me, uh, that is like magic the gatherer.
Don't you dare minus two that. If you select dodge, your monster gains. All right. We can avoid
attacks and attempts to avoid attacks. If you select recharge, you get all energy, but you
don't avoid anything. Ooh. All right. This is pretty deep. Select either dodge or recharge.
This shit's deep. Some energy. All right. Let's do, dodge is 33 and you can dodge or read. Just
yeah, let's dodge. What was that? We both did it. All right. That's it. Oh wait. Now you just need
to know how to win. You're going to destroy the opponent's torso. How's it still delayed? It can't
be. You will be victorious. Now defeat the monster. All right. Let's kill it. All right. Here we go.
Uh, just going to bite, bite him in his, just bite him. Bite is the best move in the whole game so
far. He's got no arms. What are you going to do? Oh shit. He could spit. He can still spit. All
right. Just bite him again. Put your face on the monster's face. There's a half second sound delay.
It's not even how my mic is being delayed by a thousand milliseconds and my cam is being delayed
by a thousand milliseconds. It doesn't make any sense. There isn't. It's not. One guy. Oh,
fucking one guy. Of course it's one guy. All right. Let's go. Gorbok wins. They tell it.
We got a metal plate. You get currency and money and shit.
You're monster has suffered some damage. Use field repair to heal your monster.
This is pretty cool. Field repair restores some lost health. And you can restore. Okay. Field
repair. This is, this is pretty good. Begin field repair by selecting the wrench icon.
All right. Well, I got some, I got some stuff. It is actually delayed. What do you want to do?
This guy's an overbite. What are you talking about? What are you talking about? You are freaking me
out, man. All right. Select a damaged part with the control stick. Swing the wheel in circles
to spin the wheel and repair damage. Of course. Okay. What do I want to, what do I want to repair?
Three, two. All right. So nothing. Just the torso, right? And the head. That's going to be so annoying
after a while. Why are you wearing a Kevlar vest? I, whatever. Let's keep going. I'm interested.
Bingo. I can't wait to make my own monster. What are we going to name it? You guys get to think
some good names. You guys get on here. It's a backpack. Yeah. It's a backpack. I'm getting
ready for school early. I have to go to school in like 12 hours, but I'm ready. My backpack's
fucking ready. I can sleep with this on. All right. Here we go. We got below bog versus gore bog.
I'm thinking about that fucking right arm here. Low squeeze. Now let's, let's, let's low squeeze
his legs. Good call. He just kicked me in the fucking head. Okay. I got 71. That was a big move
from him. All right. Low squeeze again. All right. I broke his legs. I'm all right. Look at his,
look at his energy. It's terrible. And then we automatically goes to the torso. Okay. So you
don't want to be, you really don't want to do that. Okay. Should I just go for it? Hook punch. Let's
hook punch him. Take off that arm. See you later. Do I have a mailbox on my arm? All right. What
are you going to do with no legs in one arm? Nothing. I need energy. Why am I getting
gears of war vibes from this? Twist him. Yes. You can block. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That makes sense.
All right. Inward block. I don't want to do that. He looked at me. I got, I already got him.
Upward block. Roar. I don't have enough energy. All right. We're going to dodge.
Why do we both have the same idea every time? Oh, right. This is like sorcery, like stamina smash,
smash, smash. Hold on. All right. We're going to auto fire. This came out of the wiimote.
All right. It was done. Uh, I have no energy. All right. We're going to, I can leg sweep,
leg sweep him right in the chest. Optical beam. Oh fuck. I'm almost dead. All right. Uh, dodge.
You're going to love, he's a low energy streamer. Chomp. Dead. Holy shit. Wait, whatever. Harold
Elbertson. Thank you. Harold Elbertson. Nine eight five for the 10 community subs.
Fight him. Uh, Harold Elbertson, nine eight five, 10 community subs. Thanks a lot for those subs.
Also Kazzy gave five community subs. Thanks both of you for the subs. You guys are fucking awesome.
Thank you. That's a fucking 15 sub drop from two people. You guys fucking rock. Thank you.
Wake up Harold. Oh, you get items. This game rules. I remember playing it on the Nintendo DS.
Thank you. You could call it a hidden gem. That's not funny. That's not funny. Except my thanks.
Prefer to return and explore a beautiful village. Oh God. That's disgusting. Oh my God.
Return to the castle immediately. No, you're the one laughing because that's insane. Return to the
castle. All right, I'm back. Thanks. Your help was most appreciated. I am Professor Fuseless.
It's like, it's like segmented. It's like separated. Oh fuck you. It's coffee. I can't even drink it.
It's coffee. Relax. Master of mechanical mad science. Stop. Mad scientist. Oh, here we go.
What's my name? Oh, this is important. Make it poop wine. No. Oh my God. How old are we? How old
are we? How old are you? How old am I? That's more important. Forget about you. Forget about
fucking how old you are. How old am I? This is like, this is my stream and a 30 fucking plus
year old man is going to make his character name poop wine. Just be clear about this. This is my
responsibility. Me showing this. Oh my God. No, I can't. That's like, I'm 30 plus. I'm over 30.
You can't make these jokes anymore when you turn 35, but I'm not that yet. I'm 30 plus.
Okay. I don't care. Welcome to the mad science alliance apprentice. Poop wine. I was speaking,
I was speaking, what's, what's pig Latin? Poop wine pay. Hey, hey. This is a fucking 15,
this is like a 13 year old's stream. Seriously. Seriously say, is say, uh ay,
13 pay, ear yay, full day, frame say. I know he's not speaking in tongues. It's pig Latin.
That's like a 12 year old thing. How many of you guys are 12? You don't know how to speak pig Latin?
That was like a 12 year old thing. Remember those ingredients you received in tongues.
You can view them in your new Igor. Igor is your own personal data management system.
I can't, I can't get over this. You fucked me up for life. You fucked me up for life.
Every time I drink a coffee that gets separated like this, but no ice in it,
of all I'm going to hear is your, your screaming. You fucked me up for life.
Igor tracks your progress as well. Okay. So I got a skull, horn skull,
metal platter and thick pipe. Cool. Wait. We can use the ingredients you just saw
to make a mechanical part to flatten your opponents. When you want to open Igor,
use the minus button. Okay. He drew the workshop. Let me see ingredient received. Thick pipe.
Okay. So quest log, go to the workshop. We also got a scientist data, monsters. You have no monsters
in your inventory. Parts. No parts. Ingredients though. We can make it like a skull pipe person.
All right. This is cool. Let's go to the workshop. Make a royal flush. To save your game,
select the cat or saver. Right. Save, save the game. Save the game right now, actually, immediately.
Save it. Why am I desync? It's off. The audio is early. Oh, we've got to do something here. Okay.
Ready? Hey, one, two, one, two. Hey, hey. So my audio, me saying a is early. It's literally perfect.
My audio is early. You fucking with me? It's, this is not one guy. This is like fucking half the chat.
It's, this is not one guy. This is like fucking half the chat. This is a lot of one guy. I'm tripping.
My audio is early. Do you hear me first? How's this? How does this sound? Are we good to go?
How does this sound? Are you seeing this sync up? Okay. Good. Yo, shut the fuck up, chat.
You're still ugly.
Blame God. Okay. That's not my fault. You may use my equipment to perform experience, but be careful.
Oh, you can make it do experiments?
Holy shit, I've really seen that tiny arm.
Experiment and your ingredients will be destroyed. I got to keep this together. I can't.
Okay. Ingredients. Key ingredient. We can do, all right, we're going to do a bedpan
and a spool of wire. What do we get? Point the Wii mode and hold the B button to weld.
Fill the entire seam for the highest quality. What? A gun, if the gun overheats, you weld
outside the seam. A gun overheats if you weld outside the seam. Shake the nunchuck to fix the
gun. What am I welding? This is an operation. This shit's tiny. Oh my God. Why do they have
to make it like a tracing game? The worst thing you could possibly do for me is make this be a
tracing game. You guys know how much I fucking hate this shit. Wait, in here. This is pretty
high quality. It's good, right? Is this the game? I don't think so. Wait, we got a buckler shield.
I get it. Okay. Slow. It's 100% quality. Hit points. 39. So it's a block. It's a shield.
That's not bad. Put that shit on.
Hey D ward, thanks for the 10 community subs. How do you attach?
In the lightning tower. Okay. So buckler shield. Let's put it on, right?
Speak with useless in the lightning tower. The weldatron. There's a lot in this game. This is
very, very deep. Lightning tower. You have to make your own monster. No, it's not a pog moment.
No, I was thinking about it. It was close.
No doubt there are scrap parts around here for you. I can't. This is going to be so good.
Let's make a monster. Monster constructor in the middle of the room. All right. Make a new monster.
Okay. This is the monster constructor screen. The panel's on the left. Should I make it all wizard?
Let's just build a monster. Like different areas of your monster.
Just like you do in combat. Okay. Right now. All right. Let's do head and legs. Not bad.
Notice how those arrows move when you select a different area. I do. You can use those arrows
to choose what parts your monster is using. Make your fursona. Right now your monster isn't using
any part. Push up on the control stick. Point the weave remote at an arrow and press the A button.
Okay. We only have two choices for head right now? Push up on the control stick. All right.
Get out of the way. See you'll make a monster. I don't want that. I only have two options.
You can use that arm you just made. As a test I want to choose the rest. All right. What can I do?
Plated jaw, leopard skull, or none? I think I only have two so far. All right. Leopard skull,
buckler shield, flub arm, stone hacker, ogre arm. Yep. Ogre arm and uh buckler shield. No.
And stone hacker. And scale male body.
When you are ready, select the jaw. With wooden legs? All right. No. We're gonna do tree legs.
Do I want the shield? I mean this is the first tutorial monster.
Yeah. All right. This is good. Best thing to do. Monster in name. Every monster needs a good name.
Like mongor. I'm not gonna name it mongor. All right. I'm not gonna keep this one.
This is this this is this shitty tutorial monster. How do I how do I delete? Oh okay.
How about how about um how about Mr. Recycle? Because he's just I'm just gonna recycle him
and I'm gonna take all those parts and stuff. Like I'm just gonna recycle him. Mr. Poopster.
But he's not getting a poop. Not no. Why would I name everything a poop related thing in this
frame? Doesn't even matter. I can name him just like Tim. Or like I don't know like Paul. Or like
Tim. Paul. It doesn't none of those matters. None of those matters. How about David? David? Good
enough. All right. Let's take our first monster into combat. Open Igor. Yes.
You want to go to corner shop and get stuff. Now head down to the command room. Deploy the new
creation. This is gonna be pretty fun. I got a saw blade. Let's go look at him. There he is.
There's David. Actually pretty intimidating looking. Look at his health, his uh mana,
his attack, and his defense. Not bad. It's pretty good for a monster that this is what
there's only like five combinations. Let's go. Command room deploy him. Shitty. He's shitty.
All right. All right. Command room. I can't wait to make the most boring fucking monster ever.
This is the command room. Use the trouble scope to see. Trouble scope? When it's out doing well
monster. Other side of the room is the interlab link. You can use the interlab link to challenge
other scientists. There was internet on this. You could actually fight over the internet.
Well that's too bad that Nintendo shut literally all servers down permanently.
That would be fun. Now let's pick a region. We had internet. Yeah it did. Oh my god this is huge.
All right. Cobbleshire. Let's go fight in Cobbleshire. We're taking David. Deploy David.
I'm not wearing a tactical rig. Just fire him out of a cannon. All right. We're gonna get parts
because I want to make another monster. There he is. All right. Cool. Oh can I like collect
items or something? What's the actual end goal here? Just explore? It doesn't take resources
to walk around right? Tourism. We're getting an interesting new visitor. All right. Northeast.
All right. Northeast. Let's move. All right. That was like a loud cat noise. This is a cat?
I walked past everything. What am I supposed to just walk into the town?
Uh oh. It's David versus the insane. Shit. Okay. All right. What do I have? What do I do? What can
my twigs do? It's just Pokemon.
Okay.
Sure. Cool. So what does he got? What does he what does he got? I got scale male body.
All right. Let's do side kick. It hits his his right arm. I could do diagonal chop. This move
sucks. Ground pound or block or I could do no optical beam. Optical beam. Well that was that
was destruction. Oh fuck. I took it all right. All right. Hammer fists. What should I try to do?
So his legs are in trouble. His head's in trouble too. Hold on. Can I bite his head? Optical beam
again. I knocked his head off. Now what are you gonna do about that? All right. Now we're gonna
dodge. It's only plus two. Dodge. All right. He's going for the legs. I gotta stop this.
Uh right in the center of his chest. Diagonal chop. Shit. That's not good. That's not good.
Uh I'm not gonna flee. Dodge. Nice. Good work. All right. This is where we end it.
Uh bite him. It doesn't matter. He's dead. Fully recharged. Bite him. He's not dead yet.
This is arm. Fuck. Okay. Uh run away. Just recharge fully. The new monster rancher sucks.
This isn't even monster rancher. All right. Die. Let's see if I can end it with a hammer fist.
Wins three. Losses zero. This is the first fight. I got a bent screw. So I skipped the fucking
rewards. Whoops. This is the first fight. How do I repair myself? Don't I have to repair?
How do I? Where's like the repair shop thing? How do you repair? Go back and get the stuff.
What's? How much stuff did I miss? There's nothing even here. I didn't miss anything. This has all
the this is a mobile game before it's time. Yeah like the circles. Yeah. Get it. There's nothing
there. How do I how do I repair myself? I'm gonna die. What's like the repair? What's that
repair mini game? Remember? You missed a tinted rock. There he is. I'm not fighting any of this
stuff.
You gotta repair the home day so.
The ingredients you discover in a challenge will help you to make new and better monster parts.
But I can't seem to remember where I put any of them. Okay complete buried treasure challenge.
Electro trace challenge. Buried treasure. How the fuck am I supposed to find that?
Wait what is that down there? Why is that lit up? Is this it? Oh I got it. I modified the
telescope to allow you to see. It allows you to control your monster directly.
What? Point at the line. Wait electro trace. Not another fucking trace.
Stay as close as you can. Point at the line with the Wii remote and hold down A and B. A or B to
trace. Oh no. Why? No! What the fuck? No! They did it. Okay. Fuck why? It's like almost like
they're mocking me. Okay. Electro trace. Don't get don't get any fights. I'm gonna die if I do.
Buried treasure is the next one? Oh fuck. Leave me alone. He's playing webkinned. Buried treasure.
No? Let me repair first. He needs to repair. This game is... I'm not even gonna read what you said.
All right it's the workshop right? You barely took any damage. Did I? I thought I did.
It's the weldotron right? Wait key ingredient. Saw blade and worn spindle.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's make a new arm. I can't. I'm sorry. Why does it have to be a tracing game?
I thought I was supposed to make monster parts and shit. It's good enough right? Have you ever
welded something before? No I've never welded something before. Why would I have ever welded
something? Oh I got a... what is it? A muffler? What is it? It's a circular saw. It's supercharged.
Increase energy capacity. That's pretty good. How do I repair? Turbocharged backpack. Where's
it repair? Lightning tower? How do I actually do this? You probably don't need to. It's done
in the field. Well how can I go and see it? All right we need one more. We need one more treasure.
It's the shield and the pause menu. Okay. There goes the rest of the poop wine.
Oh I got... I'm good. All right one more uh one more of these quests. This is why I don't have
the face game August. Every 15 minutes every like 10 minutes there's gonna be another 20 comments
about why is this guy wearing a backpack? Because I'm preventing it from happening.
All right what about over here? Secret! Swing the weed mode left and right to dig.
Shake the nunchuck to break the skulls. There we go. That's the gig. Got it. I found a flood light.
All right I did you... I did your missions now. Give me your resources.
Hurry back with what you found. You got it.
Uh oh. Battle time. Bubbles versus David. Looks like a mirror.
All right. What are we going for? Uh diagonal chop. Side kick. Knock that arm off.
Do that again. Foster strap. There goes the arm. Laughing my ass off. What the fuck is this?
Do I not bite him? Why is this music from Battlefield? Is it actually from what?
You're gonna lose? I'm not gonna lose. I'm gonna optical beam him right in his sternum. Oh my god.
I'm gonna lose. I'm actually gonna lose. I'm gonna lose. Uh all right. Here we go. All right we're
good. I'm gonna lose to a kids game. This is not even a kids game. This is a fucking rated M.
All right here we go. Knock his head off. How did that not do more damage than that?
Dodge again. Fuck. He recharged and I didn't. The crickets and dog barking sounds. I know. I don't
understand it either. Try block. I'm gonna pull. Okay I gotta go for a block. I'll go for a block.
Block it. Yep. That was the right call. Got him. Fucking so smart. All right now we dodge.
Dodge it. Dodge. Nice. All right. This is where we end it. Right here. I'm gonna hammer fist him.
Fuck. He's still. Dodge again. I'm not gonna lose. If I lose in the tutorial I'm taking the disc out
and playing something else. Dodge again. All right now bite him. Look at this. Why is this guy? Is
this guy like three levels higher than me? I don't understand. He's taking the shit out of me. Do I
beam him? Don't put the bite again. What is he like organic? It's like organic right? Alchemy
versus organic. You gotta step it up. I am stepping it up. All right cut his arm off.
This is bad. This is actually really bad. Recharge. His chest is alchemical. Is it?
All right I win. We're good. It's not over but it will be in a second. All right.
Losing to bubbles. Did I? Because I had just won. All right. Metal platter. Horned skull.
Mud bucket. All right. We got a mud. I'm thinking mud bucket and horned skull will be all right.
Prepare now. Poop bucket. All right. So where is this? Are you saying it's in the menu?
Isn't like the field menu? Field repair kit. I don't see it anywhere. Is it the victory screen? Oh.
Well we have to go back and deposit this anyways. So I'm playing this shitty game.
It's looked interesting. This game is pretty fun actually. You don't know until you try. I don't
know how many how many games that were shitty games have we played that turned out to be
fucking phenomenal. We gotta give him a chance. You can't just write him off immediately.
You can't just write him off. At least one. You gotta give it like at least 45 minutes
till it's been an hour. Okay. You gotta give it at least like you gotta give it at least like an
hour and a half before I put in elebits. All right. Will I talk to this guy? You'll want to learn how
to make a new monster part. Yes. Go on. I'll meet you in my workshop. You have one life until I have
to change games. That's not fair. At least say something funny. I'm not a fucking woody doll.
You don't pull the back of the string and expect it.
Uh
Let's see how this fucking works. There's a string on the back of me. That was terrifying.
That was scary. Good. Why does he have that pro? It's just an easy button to press.
I'm going to the workshop and I'm gonna make a new fucking robot part. All right.
We can make the reverb. The reverb was so high on that. The difficulty level of experiments
depends on the ingredient. That was all almost all the way. That was very very very insane. I
didn't even know. Oh well. All right. So don't get ahead of yourself. All right. Here we go.
Fortunately. We are aware. All right. Let's do head end and scrap. No no no no no no.
Oh you can evolve? This really is a fucking mobile game. Shit. Floodlight and bent screw.
This is bumped you. Sorry. Shit. This is a fucking mobile game. It's like robots with the control
stick swing the remote to smash. Smash all the robots that show the wrong symbol. Complete as
many rounds as possible to earn quality. Give me the wrong symbol. Move over. Why can I not move
it? No. Move. I moved to the left. I'm trying to. The guys are the wrong symbols. Okay. I gotta. I
gotta smash this guy and the guy over there and the guy over there. How do I move it? Why can I
move it? How do I move the fucking thing? You're killing them. I'm trying to fucking use the stick.
I'm pressing everything. Okay here we go. Oops. I'm gonna kill you. This thing's gonna be very low
quality. Woody doll. Oh sick. A new helmet. Watch the clip. Hold on. Let me see what the
fuck this looks like. Never welded before. Hold on. Look at a lot of new materials.
It's fucked up. Is it that fucked up? Hold on. Let me see how fucking bad this sounds.
What a fucking woody doll. You don't pull the back of the string and expect.
That's pretty accurate to what they actually sound like. So
they're not that cursed. Yes they are. Hey butt sniffing George. Thanks to the $50 butt sniffing
George. It's 5,000 bits for Mr. Butt Sniffing Gorge. It's my 21st birthday today. Could you
please get me in contact with Bugleberry so I can ask him to wish. So I can ask him to wish
a happy birthday to George. There he was. He just ran in here. All right do I want to continue
playing this or I want to put in like elements or like raving rabbits. You gotta give these games
a chance. You can't just fucking. We're going raving rabbits. All right I'm pulling the plug.
I'm selling it. All right I'll pull the plug on it. It's fun. It's fun. I like it. I don't hate it
but it's a little too slow. I thought we were going to be able to make a robot. It's a little
too slow. It's going to take us probably six hours to get to the point where it's like the
things that I want to do. We're going to pivot. We're going to play raving rabbits because that's
going to be a pog experience. Give me one sec. I don't even own it. I don't even own that game.
Don't own raving rabbits. Fuck. No no I just I just I just I just own the raving rabbits fucking
ultimate party collection which is every single video game they made. Come on. What. That's not
even. That's not even remotely accurate. This is for a different system. It doesn't even fit in the
same tray. Why did you fuck this up? How did you fuck that up? How did you fuck this up?
It's impossible. It's not even the same size of the right fucking tray.
Big game hunter 2005. Oh fucking god damn it. Put it in. Let's I want to see what I want to see
this game's all about. What is this fucking game? Put it in. Put this shit in. Let's have a look.
Un-fucking-believable. I can't even believe it. That's like that's impossible to make that mistake.
2004. Oh my god. It wasn't a mistake. It was deliberate. They deliberately put that fucking
game in there. Like what I'm not going to know. It's not even close. I can understand. Okay maybe
if it was like if that was loud if it was like raving rabbits the first one or something right
or like raving rabbits two you think okay like you fucked up it's a game cube game for a fucking
big game hunter 2005 oh this i don't even want i'm gonna play this game for fucking 10 minutes
not even this is gonna be this game's gonna suck oh my god male 18 male 30
60 wait why do you have to be this is our presets these are ages i was gonna say why did we skip
like 30 pre male 60 i'm so fucking angry right now even no idea this is tony hawk
accuracy strength accuracy strength stealth resilient you fire a gun at something
i don't i don't understand strength this makes sense and this should it should be one stat in
this game it should be accuracy and stealth resilience what resilience for what how many
like cans of soup you're gonna eat while you wait for the deer i don't understand this all right
we're just gonna go we're gonna go all strength we're going fucking hunter all fuck accuracy who
cares we're going strength only strength and and and resilience unarmed i'm gonna be
fist fighting like a bear all right i can't take these down anymore i can't believe this okay edit
the name no no no no no no backspace no no i don't want an s there you go scam sean sean the
scammer yeah it is kind of doing that you're right scam sam we keep getting fucking scammed
with these games is this actually like fist fighting cares you still have 10 points i don't
give a shit play on easy trust me wait uh is this uh play on easy why do you know this start a new
career when i when i was a young boy my dad pete took me along as he embarked on a great quest
that he had dreamed of all his life to qualify for the hunter's hall of fame and hang their plaque
on his wall it is an admirable accomplishment that you have completed crossing all the land types of
this great country braving a range of weather taking one for each animal waking one of each
animal in all regions 65 and always took me through with forests and grasslands mountains and deserts
as he cracked the great trophy animals of north of bertha he came so close to completing his goal
he was just three animals short when he slipped down an icy hill and broke his leg
fortunately we weren't far from the lodge and the warden called a rescue helicopter for us
my dad always said we would finish one day and get that plaque but he'd never can you slow down
the teleprompter please he did now and i follow his footsteps on the quest for my place in that
hunter's hall of fame and a plaque that i will give to my dad in honor of all the memories he gave
to me i gotta change the fucking name of this stream this is not even accurate this is this
game's not even gonna be on twitch this is such a strange cabela's hunt 2004 i don't even know
what its first person oh wait hold on do i just run around and f first person all right where's
her bear do i even have any supplies or anything how do you shoot okay why is it like a shotgun
all right pretty good okay good don't run you're gonna scare animals so just like walk
don't have like supplies do i have food oh there it is okay um why do i why don't feel like i'm
playing the thing you won't find any animals on hard is that true i have to go to the lodge
case already in there let's see if i get it go back on restart put it on easy pick easy please
okay all right all right all right go back and do easy easy okay we'll do i was just gonna do easy
because like people said like this could be fucking impossible i can't believe i'm playing this right
now i'm i'm so let's do a quick hunt in the in the the desert uh the in the raspy gulch easy
what are your control pad to navigate inventory all right i want to uh spray hydration blood is
like are you like pee in this hydration bladder like pee in this and then drink it all right
okay this is fine yeah this is not how do i put it on easy is it just on what difficult what
difficulty is on bella 2005 the title is not even accurate all right so what what what what
gameplay didn't give me an option this time wait is there all right here we go how do i pick up the
binoculars okay binoculars this is fucking ridiculous on easy mode you can see every
animal on the map something over here something over here put it on easy steven put it on easy
uh i don't have to make a new profile i have to make a new fucking profile all right i don't care
about the guy's name i just want to see one animal before i take this out and never play it again and
just throw i i'm gonna throw it away i'm gonna throw this away right like i'm gonna throw this
disc away i'm gonna recycle the disc all right career no don't continue my career career no no
career options quit tournament how do i make it quit career great profile oh it doesn't matter
48 points um hold on so loud there you go fixed it okay let's go easy save all right i'm ready
now it's too quiet don't worry it'll be it'll be very loud very soon battling mr potato heads
make any fucking sense i'm just gonna title it i got scammed no i i have no idea whatever how
much was this i don't know because this is not the game that i purchased all right go to the lodge
go and talk to region warden um oh plus one letter grade that's a full letter grade
that's from an f to a d did i just buy this all right fuck i just i gotta see one animal
this thing have gas all right where's the warden okay warden is the warden here go talk to the
region warden oh there he is you know you look vaguely familiar can't put my finger on it though
hello there and welcome to my land well it's not technically my land but it is my job to look after
it name's tom hallock i'm a patrol lieutenant and the warden in this region if you intend to
hunt i'll be while you're out in the field you may also be hearing from my boss patrol captain
connor he's a nice guy but he takes his job very seriously so try not to break any of our hunting
regulation i won't why don't you visit my office in the lodge later hunting tags the region for
this region all right visit the warden in the lounge for tags and hunting regulations store
warden you have received the following tags bobcat wolverine bombie and blacktail deer
okay hunting advice when you violate a hunting law you are assessed a penalty okay regulations
you're not allowed to chase injure or kill wildlife with your vehicle you may never use
your vehicle to harm another person you have reason to believe another person might have been
injured you have the duty to render aid up to including notifying the warden you may never
discharge your firearm or bow with the intention of causing bodily harm to another person you may
not discharge your firearm or bow before 8 a.m you may not start firing or bow after 6 p.m you may
not discharge your firearm or bow from within 50 yards of any inhabited building you must have a
tag for any game animal you take or it will not be considered a legal game you may not never take
non-game wildlife you may never leave a wounded animal in the field you may not hunt the with
unclaimed trophies in the field all down game animals must be claimed before continuing to
hunt proper attire must be always warm when hunting 13 14 15 16 okay here we go this is
a 100 game you are the scammer what's this game called it's cabela's big game hunter 2005
um for the game cube it's 106 new uh unfortunately it is uh it's like
it's five dollars and 89 cents used i i think i paid more for the rabid's game i got yeah i got
scammed how much is that rabid's game rabid's uh party pack for the we how much was this rabid's
party like we yeah we're we're at a net loss we're at a net loss of three dollars and 12 cents
it's eight dollars and 52 cents used and five dollars and 89 cents for this
scammed out of three dollars no scammed out of what i wanted to i just can't even fucking understand
to cite your fire stand at the deciding booth and follow the instructions citing booths marked on
your pda all right let's go how is it marked on my pda where's my car how do i get to my pda
okay target range sighting booth we're gonna go to w let's go all right where are we going
we're gonna go we're gonna turn around and go this way okay straight ahead play super paper
mario i don't have that i have to find one animal i have to get my fucking five dollars and 89 cents
worth go back to the monster lab game wait what the this map is tiny this map is like this is like a
parking lot what okay it's okay visit right here okay what press a to enter sighting mode firearms
are most accurate if they have been cited use the control stick to cite your firearm is this
isn't this like a shotgun reload shoot something already what i'm trying got it all right did it
read motherfucker i'm i'm adjusting it to hit this thing got it okay good game sucks place open up
i was directed all right that was fun let's go oh you missed i just hit directly in the middle
just go back and play binding of isaac all right let's go find let's go find an animal
so i have to track an animal let's go let's just get out into the wilderness all right we're going
i have to go back to the lodge why do i have to go back to the lodge no i already got it i got it
i got everything let's go this is an invisible wall all right what's this lodge no i don't want
to go to the lodge it's a tree all right i got the tag so now what do i go there's an animal no
that's i thought that was like a bear on all fours that's my car fuck give me the car i gotta go to
needle leaf needle leaf all right i know where to go where is it all right i'm gonna need a leaf and
i'm gonna find an animal and then i'm gonna rip the disc out of the fucking tray straight down
it's supposed to be fucking braving rabbits all right which way needle leaf is down here
right down here here we go time to actually play the game i can't wait for the third pivot
to elevates that's gonna be great wait open the elevates disc and fucking make sure it's in there
all right take a we need to find a wolverine okay shoot why is it bullet cam how do i go into
sight mode it's isn't it a that it's nice stormtrooper training that's like fucking
mile away just catch your breath for a little bit fucking dark souls meter huge bits are you
serious holy shit freddy dread came in with 250 fucking dollars all right claim the trophy
you just value is 300 dollars oh cool that record makes high scores list
i don't give a shit about my mail it's way too fucking much fuck god damn it reload been
area for several days looking for columbian black-tailed deer and when he tried to take
down the trophy he wounded the animal and it escaped what's going on what what
freddy dread gave 250 dollars freddy thanks for the fucking 250 god damn dollars a lot of
money that's a shit load of fucking money 25 000 fucking bits there we go there we go go go go go
go right now now now now now now now now now right there right there right there
all right i gotta take this disc out i'm done i'm done i'm playing elevates
oh this is like hitting a golf ball i am at the driving range hitting golf balls at these
fucking poor animals i don't want to do this anymore oh look at these fucking things this is
so stupid i have to turn this off i have to turn this shit off i can't keep doing this just tear
it out now hold on one more all right i said uh no matter what one more after that fighting
where's my car my car is so far away hold on wait wait just wait a minute you have to have some
self-restraint get closer i know i know i just i can't believe i got one get i know i'm gonna i
gotta get the fucking car and get closer we're gonna don't i promise we're gonna play elevates
i swear play we don't have we sport sometimes it's gonna turn into shoot where's the all right
it's up here how do i not have that i don't know i know look there i know there are more copies of
we sports out in the wild and there are ants i know but why i didn't want one
all right car two hundred dollars uh yeah i've wasted like fucking five grand of ammo
this is the same one all right i'm gonna get close can i shoot while on horseback
not hit wildlife with your vehicle these are giant raccoons these are giant raccoons
all right i won't i won't i won't i won't i won't i won't
hundred dollars for a new copy yeah what this is what what hunting this is we use atvs
and long scope rifles and like armor piercing fucking ammo no you get out there with two
fucking oven mitts on and well let's see what happens two oven mitts and a stick
oh look at all this technology we're using this isn't an mmo all right i'm done i'm done i'm done
i'm done i'm done danger be more careful in the future this is your second violation
is it all right how do i like it oh my god i stick aiming is so hard to use
no no i'm done get it out get it out of the car i'm not doing it