One of these days I'm seriously going to fall back and crack the back of my skull on my tile floor, but hopefully today's not that day, because today's a very important day.
This is a vlog, as you can tell, and I got a lot of important, very important things to talk about.
The most important thing, before I take a sip of my delicious iced coffee, is this invite-only tournament that I get invited to play in.
So it's me, MLC Stealth, and Ster. We are all going to be playing in a Shoot Mania Storm tournament, and if you don't know what that game is, don't worry, it's because the game is in pre-alpha right now, and nobody's even really seen it.
This is a trailer, there is a trailer for it, the trailer's going to be in the description, as well as the Twitch.tv site where you can watch the tournament.
I think TotalBiscuit and a couple other really, really super famous guys are going to be casting this thing.
So it's very, very nerve-racking and very, very like, oh my god, at the same time, because we're invited to play.
And the winner of this tournament that happens today, I think it goes on until tomorrow as well, the winner of the tournament gets to go to E3.
And we need to win this tournament, because I want to go to E3 so bad, and I've been looking for ways to go, I've been trying to find ways to go to E3, and this is really the only option I have right now.
And me, Star, MLC Stealth, we've all been practicing, we've all been getting ready for this tournament for the last couple of days.
And the game's fun, it's very entertaining, very fun to play, very fun to watch, and of course the link in the description, I think it's 5pm Eastern Standard Time, USA, is when we are going to be playing in this tournament.
So I would appreciate it, you don't have to, you don't have to come out and show your support, but if you want to, then hell yeah, thanks for coming out to the stream.
And speaking of streams, there is not going to be a stream this weekend, specifically because of this reason, because I'm in this tournament.
And also, if we win this tournament, I'm not saying we will, but if we do, going to E3 is going to be like a four or five day ordeal.
So video-wise, if we do end up winning, and we do end up going to E3, then I will try to get some stuff schedule uploaded.
I'm not going to think that far ahead at this point, because these are all ands, ifs, or buts.
We got to win first, but regardless of all that, there will be stuff on the channel next week, so don't worry, don't think I'm going to take like a two and a half week vacation from this channel, because I am absolutely not.
And also, if we go, I will make sure to do some vlog type stuff, because Shibby's going to be there, Incredible Orb's going to be there, of course Star, MLC Stealth, and these are all guys that I've wanted to meet and go hang out with since like six or seven months ago.
So it will be really interesting to really meet these guys in person, and hopefully it all works out.
And if not, then, you know, whatever, what can you do? I had fun regardless, that's how I like to think about it.
So yeah, that is going to wrap up this vlog, and that's what I'm doing this weekend, guys, so if you want to come check it out, 5pm Eastern Time, today, June 1st, and into June 2nd.
So go check it out, links are all in the description, all the information you need is down there, go right there, down there, look right now.
So yeah, peace guys, I'll see you all soon, and take care, everybody.