Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2, playing on Gullywash with the Frontier Justice, the Mini Sentry, and the Pistol.
The D-whoa! Hi Heavy! I can't believe you didn't kill me.
Gullywash is a map that I don't normally play on, and it's not because I don't like the map, it's because you don't really see it in the server browser too often.
But it's a five control point map, it's pretty interesting, and we are getting pretty much rolled right now.
Oh, get planted! Get pla-what? How did I-come here! Get over here! Oh! Give me that! Yeah! Yeah!
Oh, I was so pumped up right there, I almost just got like, aww, is this milk? It's milk! It's not Dr. Papa. What magician put that in front of me?
Milk is good though, I suggest you drink it. If you do not drink milk, does the body good? It's good to have every so often. I drink it usually once a day, maybe give or take.
Why am I not putting down-I should have put down my own stuff right there. I'm sitting there waiting for a teleporter and I'm an engineer.
Let's go for some more punches. Get that thing out of here!
Getting kills, getting kills, getting kills. Come on. Give me some more kills. Nice. Mini Sentry for the win, hell yeah. Hell freaking yeah.
That means if it dies, I'm gonna get the mini-I thought the mini-I almost said mini crits. Full crits, baby. What are you talking about, Jerma?
I still didn't put-I'm putting Dispenser in here. Forget that. Dispenser is going up in this room.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Let's see what's out here.
We're still pushed back here? We're gonna move up. No, no, you good? Now I'm gonna do it. Here we go, baby. Let's plant it on some more people. Get some-oh!
Come on, come out here, Pyro. Come here. Come here, you. Come here, you. I didn't kill that guy. Bananas. Oh, that guy's got crits!
And a Pyro! Noooo!
Damn it. All right, I'm gonna build that guy's-oh, I am so stupid. I've had an opportunity to build that guy's teleporter up and I haven't done it yet.
I need to drink some more milk. Milk, milk, milk, milk. All right, here you go.
Now that it's there, it has level three. I'm gonna build one, too. Don't worry. So we're gonna have two there.
Jerma, being a bad engineer. Let's just go. Gotta get out the front lines. They are going to cap this, or are they?
Good, I'll take that. I'll take that. Get mine up here so we can get more people at the front lines, baby.
What the hell is going on? What? What just happened?
Scare. Nice, like, scary ghost heavy jumping around the corner.
Damn. I gotta put my game face on here, guys, because they're gonna cap this right now, probably.
Get your game face on. Or build up at the last point because they're coming in.
No, Pyro's gonna cap it if we're not careful. Where'd he go? Where'd he go? You son of a bitch.
Oh my god, it's the same heavy! Dude, that heavy has popped around a corner and, like, boo, scared me and killed me, like, three times in a row now.
And that's gonna be it! Somebody get on the-
Oh well. I wanna watch that back. I wanna see that heavy jump around the corner and, like, spoke me.
Get that built. Teams just scrambled, so that's a good thing, I think.
Maybe not. Maybe it scrambled in the same teams. Gotta go, gotta go, gotta go, gotta go!
Got my teleporter. This is gonna be my last run here, this last life. I'm gonna give myself one more life.
And we'll see if I can't pull something out here and not just die 50,000 times. Hey, are you a real spy? Yes, you are.
Yes, you are. This one's gonna go over here. Right over this corner. Right, no, right here.
Gotta watch that back area. That's a bad place to be.
Quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack.
Let's go, Jag! You gotta shine here, Jag. Get that spy too! Woohoo!
This is what I'm talking about. Oh no! Oh no! Uber, Uber and a scout. I can't do much right here. I gotta wait till that's gone.
No, no, get it up, get it up, come on, come on, get it up!
I don't care if it goes down. It's worth it. Nice. Nice job
Keep them off on here. Don't want to completely run out of metal here. You are a scout a real one
Making bacon teams pushing up. I think I think so moving up. Do I dare move this is the question here
You get some full metal. I'm moving up. I'm gonna do it. I had this my last life
I'm gonna do it
You know if I get myself killed I get myself killed but I'm going for like this room right in here
Like right here. This is probably a really bad spot, but it's all good. We got we got a capped
We got a capped move it up. Oh boy. Oh boy. Come on. Get it up. Get it up
Get it up before this guy comes around the corner. We're good
Oh
Wish I had the Wrangler cuz that's not close enough one century man. This thing has been alive
I can't believe no one's taking this thing down and push up damn. Oh man. I need it
You know, where's the teleporter exit right there? Go hurry get out of here. Oh, no
Let's move this thing up again. Let's move it like into like right here when they turn this corner
It is going to unload on these guys. There we go. I got the backup here. I get the backup
You know what? I gotta destroy this and I don't have enough metal, but I'm gonna build a dispenser up here for the crew
Where's the metal? There it is. Go go go jump up
Well, this one life has lasted fairly long time. Don't worry when he walks out this door watch this. Hey heavy
Oh
You almost took it out bill bill bill bill bill
you
Bastard. Oh, I gotta pick this up. I was lucky
This thing has stayed alive since so many times when it should go down. It's just a complete stalemate
Hey scout, you're not gonna get this buddy. I'll plant it on you and I got a century kill. Hell
Yeah, and I lived longer this one life that I said I was doing one life than the whole damn time
I played this this run. Can we can I sneak this in here? Let's go. Here we go
Suicide mission here comes guys suicide mission suicide mission. Oh, it's a suicide mission. It's a suicide mission. Oh
Oh, I don't even care. Let it die. I'm coming around the corner. I'm gonna kill a bunch of people right now
Watch this. Here we go. Here we go. I'm oh you oh
You sneaky snake. Let's go more crits, baby. More crits. Are you a spy?
This heavies gonna open this door spy got eight crits still eight crits get that level one out here kill that son of a bitch
Sweet are we gonna win right now? Is this it? I think we did it. Oh
126 damage somebody get on that. Let me get on this. Oh, oh
Oh flex the muscles flex the muscles right there. My god. Oh
Baby, wow
That's a good note to end on for sure
Thank you guys so much for watching really do appreciate it this face cam fortress to I'm out of milk gotta get more
But that's it guys. I'll see you all soon. And of course take care everybody. I can't believe I just did that