You're gonna have to step on the gas if you want to get this guy. Yeah, he's right there.
Yeah, see he's right here, I told you.
I landed right next to me.
Just wait, wait, wait.
Oh, we're here from the afterlife. We're here to kill you.
We're gonna kill you.
So, take this important advice from us before we go.
A raincoat is usually helpful when it's raining. He didn't even get to hear my tip.
It's almost impossible to roleplay in GTA V.
See, I'm trying to pretend I'm like a firefighter trying to make an honest living.
Putting out fires, saving cats.
And these two are just being like dickheads, shooting everybody and shooting each other.
Can I even, I'm gonna spray the hell out of these guys.
Yeah, that's not, you know, the roleplayers are fighting back.
I'll spray the hell out of you.
You can never stop my power of imagination.
I will imagine myself as a firefighter.
You'll take your machine guns and shove them up your ass, alright?
Shove them up your ass!
When this guy comes back from being paused, I am going to fucking destroy him.
I'm gonna stick this knife right, don't fuck this up.
Oh my god, this guy, please.
Are you gonna do what I'm doing to him to me? Please don't do this.
This is a great opportunity.
Okay, he's not. I think he's gonna help me.
Good. Alright, we're both, he takes it like the billy club.
No! You!
You know, Tim, we really should go to that restaurant.
We keep forgetting to go to it.
Hey, hey, hey, hey. What are you doing?
We don't touch a police car.
Tim, get out of the car. We got a 506 situation here.
I'm the bad cop. I'm gonna get you.
Shoot these two assholes!
Got one of them. Good job, Tim.
I don't know who I am.
I never knew who you were. Get out of my fucking face.
I'm just gonna go this way.
I don't know whose car that is, but
I really should probably go to a fucking doctor.
Fuck. What?
Where did you even come from?
You are out of your goddamn mind.
Come on. Come on, then.
Come on.
I feel like the old fat guy that ran Jurassic Park.
Remember when like the velociraptors coming out of the egg?
Okay, so I just went to go get a drink
and came back.
And this is, this is what's happening right now.
I have no fucking idea what's going on.
Oh, was I in like a cop car?
How am I still alive?
I was gone for at least like two or three minutes.
These guys have still not killed me.
And there's like nine cruisers and like a helicopter right here.
You serious right now?
I'm gonna slow this down because it's like just absolutely fucking ridiculous.
Like this guy flies out of a gingerbread man car.
He looks like a gingerbread man.
So that's what I figured. It was a gingerbread man car.
And that's the end of the clip.
Welcome to the end.
Billy told me I was an idiot.
No, I didn't.
Yes, he did.
No, you're an idiot.
Mom.
Mom, he told me.
Shut up.
Hi, I'm the third child.
I do a lot of bad things.
Do you expect me to come and hit them?
No.
I can't believe how much blood is all over me.
I look like a clown.
It looks like I'm in a clown suit.
I'm in a clown costume.
Because of this blood.
Hey kids, it's me, Bozo the Clown.
Happy birthday, I murdered your family.