Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight, gonna be playing as the soldier with the strange Liberty Launcher, the buff banner, and the vintage, I believe it's a vintage, escape plan.
So the gameplay is gonna kinda sit in the background. It is a one-life gameplay on Badwater, on Defense.
I actually change over in the very end to Offense, to try and do some goofy stuff, to try and cap the cart, but you'll see if that is successful or not.
But what I wanna talk about is the future of Team Fortress 2. I wanna know what you guys have to say about it, I wanna get you guys involved in the discussion.
But it's something I've been really thinking about, and I've had topics like this before, talking about is Team Fortress 2 coming to an end soon, is Team Fortress 2 still relevant, and that sort of thing.
But what I wanna talk about is the future of Team Fortress 2, and what they can possibly do to keep this game running for years to come.
Because as we all know, the game is very, very old, and by standards of this generation of gaming, five to six years is a pretty long time for a community to still be around supporting a game.
But I just wanna know your guys' thoughts, and I'm gonna give you some of my thoughts as well, on the future of this game.
So as we have seen in the recent months, Valve has been putting a lot of time, a lot of development into Team Fortress 2.
And we have seen not only a massive amount of items and some Meet the Team videos, we've also seen a brand new mechanic, a brand new game mode in that being Man vs. Machine.
So I guess the real question at hand here is, where are they going to go?
Because sadly, it's looking more and more and more like we're not going to get a Team Fortress 3 really anytime soon.
They have this microtransaction setup, they have this little store setup, so Team Fortress 2 will continue to make the money.
And thinking about it more and more and more, do they really even need a Team Fortress 3?
I mean, maybe you update the engine, maybe you add another class, but wouldn't Team Fortress 3 be the same as Team Fortress 2 with an updated graphics engine?
Because that was the main problem people had with Left 4 Dead 2.
When Left 4 Dead 2 came out, Left 4 Dead 1 was essentially the exact same game, they just added a few more things.
And I think that's what they've already done in Team Fortress 2.
Remember, Team Fortress 2, back in 2007 when it launched, did not have any of this stuff.
It was just default loadouts, six to eight maps, and that was it, you just played.
There was no unlockables, there was no Mann Co. store, there were no drops, there was no payload.
So I really do feel like Team Fortress 3 is what they've added to Team Fortress 2 since the beginning.
So what is the future? What is Valve going to do? Are they going to drastically change something eventually here?
They've already done, like I said, Mann vs. Machine, but what else do you do?
Do you elaborate on Mann vs. Machine? Do you create a whole new mode?
Does Team Fortress 2 become Valve's experiments for all their newer games?
Because I think that's what one of the Valve employees said a while back.
They said that Team Fortress 2 was sort of an experiment for all the things that they're working on and trying to implement in their other games.
And if we ever did see a Team Fortress 3, what would you guys want in it?
Because I'm trying to think about it, and I don't know. I really don't have an answer to that question.
I think Team Fortress 2 is as close to perfect that I'd ever want it.
Team Fortress 3, I don't know. I really can't answer that question.
And maybe some of you guys in the comments can answer that.
And that's why I'm posing the question why I made this video.
Because years ago, we had no idea that Mann vs. Machine was going to come out.
And Mann vs. Machine is so drastically wildly different than anything that Team Fortress has ever seen ever in the entirety of the series.
If you had told me back then that there was going to be a horde mode where you fought robots and you all were on the same team,
I would have laughed in your face. I would have said, what the hell are you talking about, man?
There's no way there's going to be robot teams and upgrades on your guns.
I never would have believed you.
So it's cool to speculate and to think, because really anything is possible.
So while this video plays out, this little quick one live video, I do want your opinion.
So please let me know in the comments section, whatever you want to say in a tweet.
What do you think is going to happen to Team Fortress 2?
Is it going to capsize in a couple of years?
Are they going to add something drastically different like Mann vs. Machine?
Or are we going to see Team Fortress 3 in like five years?
Nobody knows, but we can all speculate.
And that's the beauty of Team Fortress 2.
But that is going to wrap up the video, guys.
Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And I'm getting ready for PAX Prime. I'm packing my bag right now. It's almost full.
I got all kinds of stuff, all the stuff that I need.
And I can't wait to potentially see some of you guys there.
So on Sunday, on Sunday afternoon, I'm going to put a tweet out or something.
And make sure you're following my Twitter if you're going to PAX Prime.
Because I'm going to be tweeting out where I'm going and what I'm doing and all that sort of thing.
So please keep up to date with that if you want to meet me at PAX Prime.
And I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.