Little early, huh? Do you guys think it's funny that the last, probably two or three streams,
I've said? Yeah, it's gonna be starting around noon. Oh, just kidding. It's starting at 9 30 a.m. Pacific
time. How do you think that's funny? You know what I mean? It's click baiting. Am I? What did I do?
The title is, finishing in the top 10 is a win for me. That's just a fact. That's just me telling you
what's gonna happen. Finishing in 11th place is second place. Finishing in 12th place is
third place. Make sure you remember that for this stream because that's going to happen quite a few
times. You're a loser. That's not a loser. That's winning in your own world. That's called winning
in your own world. He's settling. All right, whatever you want. Whatever you want to call it.
I'm winning in my own world. That's a loser talk. No, it's not. As long as I make my rules.
Look, if I come in 13th or 14th place, sure, I lost. I didn't win. I come in 12th place. That's
third place. All right, you ready? What about 40th? How many people are in this game? How many people?
How many players are there? 60? All right, is this game any good? Be real with me. I've seen a lot of
people have been playing it. I've seen a ton of people playing it. I feel like people like it.
It's pretty average. Well, here let's let's go ahead and take a look. Does this mean that I'm the
does this mean I'm the 8300 and second fall guy? Does that mean that I'm the 8300 person to install
the game? How does that work? Or do I have to get that higher and be that's my ranking? This is a
tuber game? Well, whatever. I'm an ex tuber. I think I'm allowed to be a tuber sometimes.
I thought you were going to play this with stir. It's a little early for stir though. I think he
has something to do today, but I wanted to play it. Look, don't you guys know with all tuber games,
you've got to strike while the iron's hot. Otherwise, don't do it. If I don't play this
game now, you think I'm going to play it in like six months? No, I got I've got to jump on. I've
got to get on the ride. Let me get on the ride. I don't care that I'm sitting all the way in the
back of the roller coaster. I mean, that sucks. I want to be up in the front, but I wasn't there.
So I have to take my seat all at the last spot of the roller coaster, but I'm not going to be
able to see the big drop. Whatever. Okay. So if I press A right now, you guys are all going to
press A at the same time, right? That's how this works, right? Like you wait for me to press A and
then everybody presses A. Okay, here we go. I'm going to press A now. Oh, some of you got
fucked up there. I'm going to press A right now. Sorry, some of you got messed up. Do a countdown.
Sure. Wait, hold on. This outfits. I like the blue, uh, common kind of like the sprinkles.
Well, I like, I know lightning bolt face. I'm not putting that on people that this is the gibbous
of this game. I'm not going to wear it. People will know I'm new. I'm putting on the bird feet
though. That's important. Okay, cool. Yeah, let's go. Theatrics. Oh, this is a D pad. Oh, I don't
have anything celebrations. All right. What does this mean? Season one ways to buy stuff. Oh,
this is a buy things game. Oh, it's a buy things game. Is it? No, it's not. Right? Yeah. Oh, it's
pretty generous. All right. Cool. All right. I'm just gonna, I don't have no idea what the fuck's
going on. I only know there's like a hundred people don't lose. I guess. I don't know anything about
this game. You ready? Three, two, one, better press it. Ah, it's too bad. You were coming for me.
How about now? Oh, wait, it just does this anyways. It's not like Hearthstone where you press the
button and it locks you into somebody. Am I going to get like stream sniped? This is what this game
is, right? It's just stream sniper of the game. Cancel it. I can cancel it. Just keep canceling
and keep looking for players until I like get rid of all of you. How many people are playing
this right now? Enough. Did I miss everything? Did I miss the boat? Oh no. Did I miss the boat?
I got, you got rid of us. Somebody gave 50 bucks. I have to say thank you. Thank you. Weak
cankles for the $50. It's a huge amount of fucking money. Thank you. Am I going to, is something
wrong with my computer? It happens a lot of this connection errors, but the servers are under
maintenance. Are they done? This is not like, Oh, are they? Do I have to do something else?
Did I restart the game? Oh no. The servers are down. What? Oh fuck. No, they're not. Let me see.
Wait, ball guys, Twitter. I waited like seven days to play this. Fuck. Don't play on day one. It's
going to be overloaded. Don't play on day two. Everyone's going to be really trying to play
because like all the streamers and YouTubers all played at the same time and everyone's playing
at the same time. And then like a week later, German nine, eight, five gets on the back of
the roller coaster and still fucked up. Is that, let me see. Is that for real? All guys, Twitter.
I don't see anything here. There's no scheduled maintenance. I'm just playing it again. I'm going
to try it again. I'm playing TF2. Oh yeah. If it doesn't work this time, I'll restart it.
Put the gibbous on. No, I'm not putting the gibbous on. The servers are actually down. Oh
damn it. How are they really? No. All right. I'm going to, I'm going to reset the game.
Hold on. Let's reset the game. Oh, that stinks. Did you just do a comb stream? Oh, I need to put
on clothes if I do that. Hold on. Let's try this again. Heroes of Might and Magic three. No,
I'm not prepared for that one right now. All guys. Well, I mean, I have a shit load of things
installed. We could just, we could pivot. I mean, we could pivot pretty quickly here to the complex,
which is an FMV choose your own adventure movie game made by the same people that made,
uh, Silent Night, whatever it's called. What the fuck is that game? The one where you drive the
car. The one where you, what's it called? It's not Silent Night. What is it called?
I got it. It's called like tonight. What was it called? Let's try this. Night shift. There it is.
Yeah. Made by the same people. Read this before you start. Yeah. It's made the same for the made
late shift made a new one. It's called the complex. I don't think this is going to work.
Keep trying. It takes like five tries to get in. How popular is this game? What is this the most
popular game ever? Is this the, this has got to be the most popular game on steam right now. It
has to be, right? Two million sold on steam. Oh my God. In like five days, you got to be shitting
me. 125,000 players right now at 10 AM. Holy shit. Well, turn off your VPN. You think that's
causing a problem? It shouldn't cause a problem. Yes. Yes. Yes. A hundred percent. No, no, that's
not a problem. No, that's not an issue. That's lying. The servers are crashed. All right. Well,
I don't want to just sit here and just stare at a guy falling for three hours. You guys do that
already. I don't want to sit here and do it with you. Uh, unable to find a match. What? All right.
I'm going to, we're going to give this a few minutes. Saw waiting room. No, no. Saw waiting
room. Oh, read Yelp reviews. I don't know. I'm not going to go for Yelp reviews. No, I'll go. Go
read Yelp reviews on stream. It's just, Hey guys, all the Yelp, all the places and restaurants that
I go to are going to drop by two stars because they're on stream. I'm not doing, I don't want
to do that. Don't fall one more time. Come on. Come on. Let's go. Come on. Turn the boot it back
up. Turn it back on. Get a server back on. We can, we can do this. We can, we, one of my, we can do
this. Who's the we in this scenario? I have nothing to do with this and neither do any of you.
This is somebody at an office or at a warehouse that has to like fix this. It'd be probably
freaking out right now. This has nothing to do with me. Oh, we can do this guys. What do you mean
we? No, you can't. Warehouse. Yeah. This is where they get, what do you think? They store all the
computers. They store a bunch of computers in a fucking cold ice room. Yes. All right. I'm going
to pivot. We got to pivot. Damn it. I wanted, I wanted to fucking play this dude. Shit. All right.
We're going to pivot to the complex. I feel like that's, I want to play it. It's a choose your own
movie game. You know, we love those. Come back in an hour. We'll see how long I think this, I think
the complex is like an hour. So we're good. Right? Let's go. I'll come back and try it. And wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. What happened? Did I play? I'll come back in an hour. We're going to do the
complex and I'm going to come back. Dammit. Complex is a 90 hour game. That's, it's a 90 minute game.
I think you read the second word wrong. I got to change my title. Shit. What am I? It takes me like
two hours to come up with a title for a stream. How about like movies? Um, choose. I don't know.
The servers are back. Don't do that to me. Servers are back. No, they're not. Are there people
fucking around? Are they actually back? Can somebody please tell me that they're back?
And I don't want like three of you to say this. Servers are back. They're back. They're actually
back online. Actually online. It's better not be a debate. I'm going to be really mad if it is.
It's a lot of you are saying it. I mean, I opened the game. I was, is this real? I'm in a game right
now. They're not back. Multiple one guys actually back. Am I, I'm just getting, why did I even open
the fuck up? Why did I even open this? Why did I open this again? Why? What's the point? What's
the point of this? This is a lie. Do a political stream. That's the last thing I'm going to do ever.
No, were you lying to me or what? I'm not going to do this again. I'm not going to do this. No. All
right. Okay. It was, it was a bunch of bullshit. Fine. I'm not listening to you guys ever again,
but I don't care if I'm like standing somewhere and there was a car behind me, like literally
like, and the guy behind the wheel is leaning forward with this wicked fucking angry face.
And he's, and he's coming for me and I'm just sitting there talking to you guys and you're
going to be like turn around. There's a guy with the fucking guts, right? I'm not even going to
fucking listen to you. I've never listened to you guys ever again. I mean wicked. What? All right.
We're going to do. Okay. How was I, this is just a movie. I don't even know what this movie game is
about. We're going to play it. How about just, I'm naming this string complex. Who cares? Nobody
cares about the title. It doesn't matter. I do. Hey, the servers are back online.
They could be. Let's see how this is. Let's see if this game is any good. When did this come out?
Turn off your fucking VPN. Servers are up. Maybe I don't want to play this. Well, I, I wasn't ready
for this one. Ironically too. All right. I'm turning. All right. No, no, no, I'm moving on.
Let's go. Turn off your VPN. All right. It's no, it's not real. It's, it's not real. You're fucking me
up. No, they're not. All right. I'm, I'm opening this game. Turn off your VPN. Don't turn it off.
Don't fall for it. I don't want to play the complex. What do I play instead? I don't want
to do this right now. To open up AI dungeon. Actually, that's not a bad idea. It's not a
terrible idea. Either that or Nancy Drew. I'm ready to, I'm ready to go full on fucking just
Nancy Drew. Let me see. Is AI dungeon in the same spot that it was before? Or do I have to do that
thing again? Boy, I said the word Nancy Drew. God damn it. Didn't I? Let me just do this.
So the AI dungeon, AI dungeon.io, is that a better version than the other one before? You remember
how it was kind of not as good as the other one? That like kind of Google doc one, whatever it was.
So it's, it's good now. Let me just put this on. Oh, is German 95 emotionally today? Good or bad?
Well, it started good. And then I couldn't play the game that I wanted to play. And it just threw a
wrench into my, it just threw a wrench into my window. And so now I have to figure out what I'm
going to do. And that's how it happens. End of the stream voice. No, I should have been more
prepared to have a backup. All right. Let me get this going. Can I capture this? You'd have like
music and shit. What is this? Cause I changed this thing. All right. I have to open up a game. I
can't capture this window right now. I changed a bunch of dumb shit around. I'm just going to,
I'm just opening up Nancy Drew. I don't even care. I don't even, I don't even know what one is
installed. I'm just going to open one fall guys, but you fall forever. I'm opening up.
This is just until I can play fall guys. Uh, how about Nancy, Nancy drew secret of the old clock.
Wait, did I already play this one? Nancy drew treasure in the Royal tower. Nancy drew the VPN
clock. All right. I'm going to play Nancy drew treasure in the Royal tower. And I'm going to hate
every second of this. I can't believe that you're getting what you want. I can't believe