Let me clear it up. Let me clear it up because people are a little confused.
People get a little confused and that's okay. I can help.
I have 100% guaranteed that I would be late. I did not 100% guarantee I would be here at 420.
I just said 100% guaranteed. 100% I'm gonna be late.
I never said, what did I say, 415? I said 415 is what I'm looking at.
I said I 100% guarantee. Oh shit, I got logs. I'll be back in a little bit to start.
Definitely starting at like, at like 415 by the way. At like 415 by the way.
Like 100% chance. 100% chance that I'm gonna be late. Like like 415. I'll be around at like 415.
Yeah, it's like 415. Like 430, 415, 420, 425, 424. He's gaslighting.
No, I said I was gonna be like 415. Okay, let me ask you a question.
If on the back of the microwave food box, like let's say you have like a turkey dinner in the
microwave. If it's set on the back of the box, put in the microwave for like five minutes with a
question mark. Would you trust it? No, you wouldn't. You want, you need an exact time.
Saying like before time is not an exact time. I'll be back at like 415. If somebody says that,
that means, all right, I can't, it's gonna be like 410 to like 425. You're high on weed,
100% guaranteed. Where's the sponsor? We're not doing that yet. Can we get a comment of
your obsession with being TikTok famous? Guys, I don't own the app TikTok. I don't even know
if I'm on TikTok. All I know is that what I told you before, if I was on TikTok, I'd be huge.
People keep coming to me. Hey, Jerma, do you see like this thing? It's got like 500 million views
on it and it's like you. Oh, okay. But you still don't believe me when I say I would be huge if
I was on it. Oh, Jerma, like they dedicated like a whole entire segment to you on TikTok here. It's
like this big, it's got like 400,000 views. Oh, but no, I would not be, that would not be a thing
on there if I started. I'd go on there and I'd change the world. Okay. Okay. Imagine being,
having that inflated of an ego that you think that like you as an E-clown would change everything
if you made a TikTok account. That's, that's next level. That is stratosphere level megalomania.
Is he Joe? Of course it's a joke. My TikTok will change the world. This guy is a Vin Diesel
streamer. I kind of know what you mean by that, but at the same time I don't. I don't know why
I know what you mean, but I don't know what you mean at the same time. It's because you're bald.
I'm not at all actually, but let me, let's go over what's going to happen today. Let me first,
let me clear my disgusting throat before people get grossed out. Okay. So this is going to be an
interesting day. There's something happening on this stream that I've never done before really.
I'm testing to see how it works, seeing how I like it. So let's go over what's happening.
I've been watching a lot of infomercials. It's better than TV. As you see, I have my,
I've got my, you know, been on my list of, you know, how I feel about like greater than, less than.
I actually think that a lot of infomercials are more interesting and more entertaining than
television or movies. So I've been on a big kick of it. I get on a kick of watching infomercials
every maybe once a year or two. So I figured if I'm on the kick right now, there's so much
shit to dissect in these videos and in these products. I kind of want to like, well, I,
if it's, if I'm not going to, I'm going to watch them in bed anyways. And some of these,
some of these products are insane and some of them are just fun to watch. He's on a kick. Yeah.
AP Sensory 2.0, absolutely no fucking chance. And then after we do this, this is just something that
I was just like, I want to do this. I've been thinking about doing the infomercial watch,
like the React Andy stream for a few months now. I just didn't know when to do it.
But after that, we'll do this for a little while. I'm going to be playing the Serpent Rogue
as a sponsor stream. I played the demo. I looked it up. It's like, this looks pretty fun. I,
I guess I'll do it. Yeah. So what I need you guys to do is this is the first time I've ever been
sponsored on this stream. Besides, you know, obviously the dollhouse fucking better make me
look good. You know what I'm saying? It's not going to happen. No way we aren't doing that.
You better make me look good. But in all honesty, like I'll not mess it around. And like, this is
like, you know, this is, is Jeremy talking to, you know, I've never done this before.
So I really hope the game's fun. It does seem like it's a pretty good, fun, good experience
from what I played. I don't know. We'll find out. It looks cool. And I will say this again,
because I said it a couple of days ago, but I will reiterate it. It's Jeremy talking to you now.
I have been pretty selective so far with what has been presented to me.
So don't worry. I'm not just, this is not going to just be a, oh yeah, just I'll take anything.
Sure. How much are they going to, how much are they paying? Oh, yeah. Fuck yeah.
No, I, I've been very selective already. So this looks really fun. I'm, I'm actually interested.
No, what? No, no, I'm not, I don't, I, that's, I'm not going to even say out loud what you guys
saying. I'm not even going to say it out loud. But anyways, I want, I got a lot of infomercials
here. Some of these, I've seen these before and I want to go over these products with you.
Then by the way, some of these are like 10 to 20 years old. So
they may have been some new innovations since then. You need to sell these to us.
Guys, half these products probably don't exist anymore. What are you talking? I mean,
I don't think any of these exist. Some of these might not even exist.
You go into bed, have a good night. Hope you get a good rest. I can't sell them to you.
We're getting sold too in these commercials. I mean, let's literally, are you ready? Let's just go.
I got this, like 500 of these. I'm actually really excited. I love old infomercials.
All right. What do you guys, what do you think you want to start with over here? What do you think?
I mean, I'm on, there's like 200 videos in this playlist. So, I mean, and I know I just like
leaked it, but who cares? Look at this. These are kitchen appliances. Look at all these,
the Betty Crocker all in one basket, the miracle grill. You know what's crazy about infomercials?
You're on light mode. I don't know. What? He's obsessed with marketing. I'm obsessed with
direct marketing. Direct marketing is so, just so bizarre. It's such a bizarro world. What's wrong
with light mode? I can see. Do I, should I turn off light mode? This dude's a tab hoarder. Well,
it's not going to be bright because I'm about to, look, we're going in full screen. Look, we're fine.
It's fine. All right. So this is the fill and flavor direct response infomercial.
If you don't know what direct response is, direct response is when there is no,
there's no like middleman. They don't like, this is not like in Walmart. It's not in Target.
It's just manufacturer direct marketing to consumer. And it's always insane. Are you ready?
Let's just go. This is, this is the fill and flavor. I'm going to give you my thoughts. I think my
screen might be too big. Actually, why don't we just turn it off for each one? Can I? Let's go.
Okay. There we go. Fill and flavor. Do your homemade cakes look and taste the same old
fashioned, no filling, boring and plain? Well, not anymore. Now there's the fun-tastic fill
and flavor by perfect bakeware. Okay. The revolutionary cake making wonder that lets you bake,
fill and decorate. I've seen this one. It's so easy. Turn it up. Just pour in any cake mix. Lock
on the magic center insert. But hold on. First of all, let's before I know people get like,
stop pausing. What is this? This looks like cheese. This is Brie. What happened? Don't pause.
I'm going to be pausing. All right. I want you to do an experiment with me guys.
Every time they do a black and white, look at this person, screw something up,
or look at how bad this looks. Imagine the person is like 10 beers deep. This is just like the person
is trashed. If you think like that, it's, this makes sense. This person is shit faced and they
decided to make a cake. I'm telling you, all of them think that way. We'll, we'll, we'll stop it
each time. Boring and plain? Well, not anymore. Now there's the fun-tastic fill and flavor by
perfect bakeware. I remember so many of these too. The revolutionary cake making wonder that lets you
bake, fill and decorate. Oh, you can do, you can do it with the kids. Pour in any cake mix. Lock on
the magic center insert and place them in the oven. Okay. When done, remove the insert,
add your favorite filling, then cover it with the base. All right. Amazing. A wonderful cake. It's
so thrilling. It's still thrilling. Imagine their surprise when they see tasty chocolate.
That's a huge fucking feast. Who's, who's going to eat that? Is one of the kids going to eat this?
Yeah. No shit. They're surprised. It's like mom's given us the whole cake. Tasty chocolate. That's
so, that's so much. That's way too much. Chocolate pudding. I'd eat that. Yep. Oh, look at our shit
face. This person is, look at our shit face. Okay. Remember this person, it's like three o'clock in
the morning and they know they have a pie in the fridge and they're like two or three of them in
the room are like, yo pie, right dude? Oh, let's get it.
We had this. Did it work? Wait, hold on. Whose hands are these? What, what? Oh, I thought this
was a batting glove. I was like, why is, why is like a baseball player serving this? I thought
that was a fucking like golf glove. Yeah. I just made a few cakes for the boys in the locker room.
What's wrong with this one? I don't know about that one. That's actually, that's kind of cool.
What? That's bullshit. They don't, they won't even potentially have a center filling.
What could be better than one filling flavor? Two filling flavors. That's right. You get two for the
price of one. Two? Just pay separate processing and handling. I have a question for everybody.
I've had this theory since I was like 15 or 16, whatever. So when they say, oh, and if you act now,
you get a second one free. Almost every single infomercial that you'll see on all these lists,
one of these videos, they did that. And was that just your paying for two? We just say this is how
much it costs for one. Is that, that's how that works, right? That's, that's the idea. Oh, and
remember if you get our, get this, it's, you get two for just $19.99. The price is $19.99 for this,
but you get two. So they're $10 each, right? Has to be. I don't, it could, maybe it's not,
but I'm just saying like, I remember that was a, that was a big thing. Or they'd give you other
stuff. It was like, yeah, it's $39.99 for this. And they show all the commercial, they show everything.
And all of a sudden they'll be like, but hold on a second. You also get the scissors too,
and the swimming goggles. And it's like, wait, did you just kind of, did you just sell me three
things and just added all the prices together? That used to happen. This thing's kind of cool.
Today to order fill and flavor for $19.95 plus processing and fill and flavor.
All right. Yeah. And I, okay. Well here's the thing guys, you know,
none of these fucking, don't fucking do that. I'll be an idiot.
All right. What about the clever tongs? Spatulas and tongs have been around forever,
but try to flip and food flops, try to grip shit face. I'm telling you shit face.
I imagine somebody sitting across the table, right? Like somebody sitting here and it's like,
like mom, mom, oh, they're getting like burnt.
Whoa. Actually, this is pretty cool. So it's got like a canvas.
Hammock. I got it wrong.
The clever tong.
Why would you want to hoist a whole pot roast? Like with your one hand.
Flip potato cakes fast and easy right in the pan. All right. You went. All right.
I had to use it. This is actually pretty awesome.
All right. I got a question. How many of you guys have made burgers, right?
And here's the thing about pans. You ready for this? Listen to this. This is important.
I didn't know this, but like you can't use certain utensils in certain pans.
There's like a bunch of rules that I didn't know about. Like, oh, hey, yeah, you want,
let me flip your burger with my spatula. Don't do that. Don't fucking do that.
You're going to ruin everything. I'm like, um, what about this tool? No, that'll cause damage.
You have to use this specific tool. You have to use this specific silicone to pick that up.
Okay. Oh shit. I didn't know that. And I didn't know that up until like,
I would say maybe like five years ago. I did not know that chef Andy, right?
So a product like this, I'm just going to be very honest with you. I, I, I sport it because
this just works in any pan. Nobody's going to yell at you. Mom's not going to be pissed.
You're not going to scratch anything. You're not going to be looking at how much asparagus
can fit in that, by the way. Look at how much asparagus without it falling or scoop,
lift and serve an amazing Philly cheesesteak in seconds. Clever tongs is very clever.
Two in one helper. You need to grip and flip that king sized ribeye with ease.
And by the way, guys, that was a king size ribeye, not just a regular size ribeye. That's an extra.
That's like, that's like another 70 cents for McDonald's. That's super size.
Flip and serve a mouthwatering grilled cheese. Scoop and flip delicately.
Does this still exist? I hope so. I just get it.
And then scoop and serve the potatoes with perfection.
What was this called? The clever tongs? Okay. That thing's actually fucking pretty good.
I actually like, I always, okay, even with the right tool, I will always go like this.
Everybody does this. And don't tell me you don't because it sucks.
You got a spatula and you go down, you try to get under slowly
and you end up just moving the patty to the edge of the pan.
And then you end up just like kind of taking your finger and like
touching the edge and like lifting it and then letting go.
I'm so sick of doing that because like the spatulas, even the silicone ones,
they don't get under. They kind of just like push and slide.
I think I flip half of hamburgers I've ever flipped in my life.
Unless they were on a grill because a grill like don't matter.
A grill like who cares if you're like using the right utensils.
It's just like you just take it, you fucking flip it.
You get like grease all over. It doesn't matter.
But like it sucks doing that. Target audience.
I mean, okay, I would say I would want that one.
Also back in the, we're going to just watch, this is Egg Genie.
I'll give a preference to this though.
I don't know what it was with like the mid to late 90s and like the early 2000s
and like mid 2000s with eggs in the microwave.
I don't, why?
It was a huge thing. Eggs in the microwave.
There was so many products that did it.
It was like, oh, put your egg in this and it'll turn in a minute you'll have an egg.
Eggs don't take that long though.
If you just do like scrambled egg, I mean the pan.
Yeah, maybe you mess up the pan, you get it all dirty.
But there was an obsession in like the early 2000s
with cooking eggs in the microwave with our device.
Okay, hold on. Let's see. I'm curious.
That's a poached egg and it looks great.
That looks like a really great poached egg.
What do they mean?
Isn't that a poach? That looks good.
I would eat that to put that on a piece of toast.
That's a poached egg.
Also, I'm sure a lot of people are probably noticing the Nolan North
of all infomercial voiceovers.
This guy introducing the egg wave.
This guy probably was, this guy probably made,
God damn, I don't know, man.
This guy probably made thousands of dollars an hour.
He would probably, he probably just the guy, like the guy.
He was the voice and I think he's still going.
Oh, it's not in the microwave.
Dude.
Nice.
I thought it was, all right, that's kind of cool.
I thought it was going to be a, they're fine.
But it's like a bug zapper.
Oh, don't mind that.
It's just the bugs being zapped.
Because when you turn it upside down, it's also a bug zapper indicator.
Like shut off and continuous audible signal that prevents overcooking.
Now it's a breeze to stick to your diet with quick
and easy locale snacks that always taste.
That's kind of cool.
Egg Genie also comes with its own steamer tray.
All right.
Okay.
You got me.
Wait, what are they giving us?
There it is.
The bacon wave.
All right.
Everything had to be a genie too.
Yeah.
Okay.
So let me tell you what I think about this.
I'm into it.
I thought this is going to be a microwave thing, but I, that was unfair.
It's just a steamer that has one setting probably, right?
But I mean, that's, I probably would have used this.
The thing about all these products, these kind of like direct marketing products,
the problem with a lot of them was they kind of really only did one thing.
They just did one thing and they always made a point to like,
Oh, you have so much bullshit on your counter and so much dog shit in your pantry.
This is just, this is like, it's just a steamer that has one setting.
They always made a point about this, how you had too much bullshit,
but they were just trying to sell you a product that like was, did one thing.
Although I would say I probably would have used this
because cooking hard eggs actually is a pain in the ass,
but I wouldn't want to microwave them.
Steaming them sounds pretty interesting.
I've never done that before.
That sounds good.
That's actually pretty cool.
I'm into it.
I have not seen one that I've been like, no, no, thanks.
There's a lot.
This is so much fun.
I love this.
This is like the funnest thing ever.
Okay.
How about the perfect slicer?
Slicers are weird.
All right.
First of all, I made this reference like two months ago and there it is.
That's a Gallagher reference and I'm so glad that you got to see it.
Careful.
Bro, what the fuck?
I want watermelon, dude.
Get in there.
I'm fucking trying, dude.
Sucks.
Just imagine you hear the word bro like three times in the corner.
You fucking do it.
Dude.
That thing's scary.
Just don't hold the knife like this.
It's not like a fucking lightsaber.
Cantaloupe sucks.
I kind of got hold on.
Wait a minute here.
This is kind of, I kind of got, that kind of got messed up.
What?
I don't like cantaloupe.
They should have leaned way heavier into that.
Yeah, they should have.
Yeah.
Lean into that.
120 perfect delicious slices.
Oh, I thought the guy did it 120 times.
I thought it was like we made this guy do this 150 times and he said it was easy.
Another thing I want you to pay attention to and look for here is something technology.
Keep an eye on that.
They would say like two or three words and then add technology to the end
and it was supposed to be like oh wow that's like a scientist had to have come up with that.
Advanced freshness technology.
What is advanced freshness technology?
What's the, what is the tech behind that?
Technology.
Advanced freshness.
I don't know.
I think the, I think the cutting thing is cool.
You know how many times I've actually had like a cake or something?
Go now.
Or pineapple too.
That'd be like pineapple just cut but I don't know.
I feel like I'd be kind of scared to do that.
Wouldn't you?
Going like this and like pushing because the thing might be wobbling around.
I might be kind of scared to do that.
All right.
This looks like a pretty similar realm here.
This is the Jiffy fries.
By the way, I'm so glad this is as seen on TV blog.
Oh my god.
They probably have everything.
I'm I can't.
I'm so happy.
Nothing should come between you and fresh hot crispy french fries.
But never at home is a pain.
And freezer fries just aren't the same.
Well that was frozen.
Enjoy fresh delicious fries in a Jiffy.
Introducing Jiffy fries.
The fast, fresh, easy way to make perfect french fries every day.
Just load and push down to safely slice them.
Okay this is a small version of what we just saw.
In just minutes you've got hot delicious perfectly crisp fries.
The secrets in the Jiffy fries hot pot.
Is that an apple?
Crisp fries.
The secrets in the Jiffy fries hot pot.
Brand new crisping technology in the pot.
What is that?
Brand new crisping technology.
The pot circulates the heat above, below, and in between the fries.
So that every fry is cooked to the perfect temperature and texture.
Makes sense.
Need a quick pick me up?
Jiffy fries are a great midday snack you can make in a snap.
Thinking about burgers for dinner?
Jiffy fries makes every dish a winner.
Now scrumptious snacks and quick easy meals are just.
They didn't do it.
They didn't.
Hey excuse me.
I expect the fucking cartoon crunch.
You can make in a snap.
Thinking about burgers for dinner?
Jiffy fries makes every dish a winner.
Now scrumptious snacks and quick easy meals are just a load.
What the fuck?
What a load of shit.
Creating something cheesy?
Add sauce and cheddar for buffalo Jiffy fries.
Want something with a little crunch?
Serve up some bacon Jiffy fries for a scrumptious.
It's back.
Jiffy fries gets the oil and grease out of your diet.
Make healthy sweet potato fries.
Okay don't you think that's the kind of sound.
When you hear that sound you go.
Oh like that's something in there is not supposed to be even.
That's something hard.
Bacon Jiffy fries for.
Stop.
Oh okay you don't you don't move.
You kind of freeze and you go what was that?
What was that?
Is that a tooth?
Was that in there?
Scrumptious munch.
Jiffy fries gets the oil and grease out of your diet.
Make healthy sweet potato fries.
Who's doing that though?
For a healthy side or midday snack attack.
And it's all dishwasher safe.
So clean.
I mean I get it.
I get what they're going for here but.
If you go to the if you go to the freezer aisle in your grocery store.
And you get frozen fries.
Like what the orida has like a frozen bunch of stuff right.
Those are good.
Those are fine.
Those taste great.
They have like the fast food like shoestring style.
They're great.
You just put them out on the on a pan.
You put it in the oven like whatever.
Have a long like 15 minutes or so.
It's it tastes it's good.
It's really good.
They're great.
It's like they do it fast.
But is it really that fast though?
Because you have to cut the potato.
And I think I feel like going from potato.
Like I got to go get a potato and like wash it and like clean it.
And then put it here and then cut it.
I feel like that's too much.
I'm not sure I would be into this product.
You'll also get a complete set of Jiffy fries secret seasonings.
I'm more into that.
The Jiffy fries recipe guide to make recipes like.
Marshmallow sweet potato Jiffy fries.
I want whatever that I'm interested in that.
And more.
Yours free.
You get it all for just ten dollars.
But I mean I want what's in the secret seasoning.
What about your health?
Marshmallow.
Oh those sweet potato.
Sweet potato.
You know yams and shit.
All right.
I don't know.
I don't know about that one.
What about the Vegetti Pro?
Do you love delicious pasta?
But hate the calories fat and carbs.
Introducing the Vegetti Pro.
The fast.
Do you.
Okay.
I was going to say how much pasta was that?
Love delicious pasta.
But hate the calories fat and carbs.
Okay.
I was like wait we just what did you eat a whole thing of pasta?
The Vegetti Pro.
Wow.
Look at this thing.
Easy way to turn veggies into delicious healthy spaghetti.
Watch just slide in the stainless steel plate.
Insert the zucchini and just turn the handle.
What?
Tick tock voice.
I've actually.
My mother used to make zucchini noodle soup.
It was fucking fire.
It was good.
Okay.
I get it.
But that's not all.
What else?
What?
I thought that was an onion.
Okay.
All right.
I'm sorry.
This is cool but like totally just looks like a mess.
That's a big deal.
Okay.
That's what I was concerned about.
I was concerned about that.
I get the idea.
It's an interesting idea.
Picky eaters.
Pesto.
Oh this is ribbon slicing now.
Fettuccine or curly lasagna.
Ribbon cut cucumbers for salad.
You can eat and more.
As a bonus you'll also.
That kind of looks gross.
It looks like a salad with way too much dressing on it.
All right.
It doesn't do apples.
Right.
Okay.
So it's like a peeler essentially but a little more involved.
I'm into it.
I think it's cool.
I think that's fine.
Yeah.
Okay.
If you've had this on the counter.
And I like I can't either came you've not invited me to your house.
Something like oh hey dude like come on I'll come over.
I'm like oh I'll come over.
This sounds fun.
So I get there and I like put my backpack down and I put my baseball cap down.
And I sit on the couch or whatever and you say oh hey look what I got.
I've got the Vigetti.
I'd look over and I'd be like whoa let's do it.
Let's go.
Let's do it.
That'd be fun.
Like that'd be the fun thing that we would do.
And like that I would have a good time doing that I think.
I think it'd be fun to do that.
Why do you have a backpack on?
No it's not.
Not a grinder date.
Okay.
Fuck that.
I'm out of here.
All right the Vigetti Pro I give it a fucking seven.
What about the perfect pancake?
You flip but they flop.
Now your pancakes are a mess.
Oh wait wait wait wait.
You flip but they.
Okay remember.
Shit faced.
You flip but they flop.
Now your pancakes are a mess.
And all that butter and fat to cook them.
There's got to be a better way.
Hi Mark Gill here.
If I was trashed I would love those.
The fast easy spatula.
Yeah there was a million of these.
There was so many of these.
Watch just close the handle and flip it.
Yes.
Portland ground pancakes with no mess and no added fat.
The reason is this double-sided non-stick surface.
That's so slippery not even burnt on cheese will stick to it.
Flip delicious blueberry fluffy apple cinnamon.
Or four mouth-watering buttermilk flapjacks.
Yeah.
Fast easy and without ever using a spatula.
If you can turn a doorknob you can use the burnt on cheese.
They always use that as an example.
But watch what happens with the perfect pancake pan.
Eggs over easy.
All right.
Ever breaking a yolk.
Amazing.
All right that was kind of cool.
Gingerbread pancakes.
Fluffy cranberry or mountains of chocolate chip pancakes for the kids in an instant.
You can also make delicious dessert crepes or four healthy egg sandwiches.
Oh egg sandwiches.
Just like from a restaurant.
Why flip and flop one at a time.
Call now and make four perfect pancakes at the same time.
All right I don't know why.
I just imagine.
Okay pan the camera up and there's a person with a lit cigarette in their mouth.
And it's only like half left.
And they're just like sitting there with they're just smoking.
That's I just see a cigarette.
I see like just a lit cigarette.
Time call now.
Slimesicle welcome.
Thanks for the raid.
Welcome everybody.
We're doing product reviews.
Infomercial product reviews.
Hope you had a good stream.
Welcome.
This was the pancakes all at once.
I don't even know what this was called.
But thanks.
Welcome.
Four perfect pancakes at the same time with the perfect pancake pan.
And our fast and fluffy recipe.
Everything was 1995.
If you had a product back in like the mid-2000s or early kind of early 2000s and late 90s.
And your product was less or more than 1995.
You lost board members.
Executives would leave.
Now and we'll double your order free.
Just pay separate shipping and handling.
All right.
Yeah that's all right.
Let's go.
What about this one?
All right here we go.
Mighty meatballs.
This one is going to be interesting.
Mark Gill.
I trust him.
Four delicious meatballs at once.
It's so simple.
And believe me if you tried to make stuffed meatballs without one.
Stuffed meatballs.
All you do is.
That was huge.
That was a fucking softball.
Who's making that?
Wait a minute.
That was a softball.
There's going to be a big.
Oh I swear to God.
Grandma's Italian meatballs.
Holy shit.
Two up to seal.
Mighty meatball makes four large stuffed meatballs every time.
That was a big.
I smell that.
I've been out there.
I don't know about that.
I get the stuffed burger thing but stuffed meatballs.
I'm not so sure.
Bacon, mac and cheese, meatballs.
I feel like this is a kid's menu.
Is this the kid's menu?
Stuffed ground chicken with ham and swiss for cordon bleu that just can't miss.
Or use ground turkey with stuffing and cranberry sauce for the best turkey meatballs ever.
And it's not just for meatballs.
Make cheesy garlic stuffed mashed potatoes.
Yeah this is like.
What the fuck?
I get it.
I get the idea.
What about easy butter?
Loves butter but getting it out of the fridge out of the wrap onto your food is a real asshole.
Introducing easy butter.
Okay the problem was not the butter.
The problem was you leaving your toast in the toaster for like 40 minutes.
All right this is fucking awesome actually.
Holy shit.
This is awesome.
What?
All right do they still make this?
That's insane.
Am I insane for liking this?
Okay this is an incredible product I think.
You don't want your like five-year-old daughter saying that by the way.
You don't want to.
All right you know where's the vegetables?
Where are the vegetables?
Where's the zucchini slicer?
We need that back.
What is that?
Who's doing that?
I like this though.
But with your order today we'll double the offer.
All right so that's five dollars.
Cheese?
Wait there's more?
Why would you put a hot dog in there?
Hold on.
A hot dog?
Why would you put a hot dog in there for little kids?
But like just it's like fun to I mean.
Slicing a hot dog is not as difficult as slicing cold butter.
Bananas?
Cutting the hot dog is simple.
I could cut a hot dog up in like literally five seconds.
It's just like one, two, three, four, five.
It's not a big deal.
Cutting butter is hard.
All right that's pretty sick.
I'd say of all the products we've seen of like the ten we've seen.
I like that one the most.
I want an easy eggwich.
Okay the other steam products.
Didn't need to go in the microwave.
Was it the Egg Genie?
That's kind of thick too.
Okay.
It's easy though.
It's simple whatever.
And that was another thing too.
Why were people so obsessed with this too?
Help me with this.
Oh and cooking in oil.
No one wants to do that.
Olive oil is like fucking not bad for you.
Cooking in like an olive oil?
Like a light olive oil?
Don't and then think about how much oil you'll be using.
What was like the the war on fat?
Like fats?
No no no no no.
Don't have those omega-3s.
Don't eat them.
Don't touch those.
That's look we're gonna have a tray that all the oil drips into this tray.
And then don't eat that.
That's that's disgusting.
How vile.
Oil's like a good oil like an olive oil.
Like sunflower oil.
This stuff is not bad for you.
It's not bad for you.
It's actually has a lot of benefits.
Olive oil is fantastic for you.
But not essential oil.
Sunflower oil is bad.
I'm talking about yeah but I said olive oil.
Avocado oil.
You have you ever cooked with avocado oil before?
Have you cooked with like a good olive oil?
It's like it adds to your food.
Doesn't take away from it.
Carbs are killer.
Peanut oil is amazing.
Yeah dude what is with this war on like oil?
I don't get that.
In a cabinet so many.
But put butter all over everything.
I love butter oil.
Oh it's oil.
That's even the word oil.
It's like it would come out of the ground.
What's going on here?
All here in the one minute easy eggwich recipe guy.
And they always show like eating steaks.
Oh it can even flip a eight pound steak.
Don't cook it in that disgusting oil.
I don't get it.
Now give your family a hot fresh breakfast in one minute with easy eggwich.
Call now and get.
All right we get it.
Nah I wouldn't get it.
I wouldn't buy that one.
How about burrito perfect?
Love burritos but hate the mess.
You fill fold and roll but could never get that perfect hold.
That's true.
And store-bought burritos are just not the same.
Introducing burrito perfect.
The simple fast mess-free way to make perfect burritos.
What is this?
Watch.
It's a t-shirt holder.
Burrito perfect.
Fill it with your favorite toppings such as rice, beans, chicken, lettuce, cheese,
and guacamole.
Then fold one, two, three, and you get a perfect burrito with ease.
Now you can make quick and simple breakfast burritos.
Steak fajita burritos.
Chicken and cheese burritos.
It's a t-shirt holder.
Vegetable burritos.
But what if you-
Okay I use-
I always overfill.
What the fuck?
Hold on.
Your family will enjoy making their own favorite burrito.
Huh?
There's nothing in there.
They're making their own favorite burrito.
There's nothing in here.
You know without the mess all by themselves.
She said this is just a tortilla.
No more frustration folding burritos and worrying about getting it on your clothes.
Enjoy making your own fresh flavorful burrito without the spills.
Burrito perfect is also great for-
Yeah but okay.
Okay listen.
When you make a burrito, I don't care who you are.
I don't care what your food preferences are.
I don't give a shit.
You always put way too much in.
Because you go, oh yeah give me some ground beef.
A little bit more.
I think I need a little bit kind of hungry.
And the ground beef is like a mound this high.
Uh I want like shredded lettuce in this.
Like shredded lettuce.
Shredded lettuce.
Tomato.
Like tomato chunks.
Tomato chunks.
A little bit of salsa.
Oh I got a-
Is there enough room for cheese in here?
Uh yeah I'll put some cheese on it too.
Like a lot.
I want a lot of cheese on this.
And then you go, this is not rolling.
This is never gonna roll.
I'm never gonna have this be a burrito.
So I'm just gonna put my hands underneath it and like kind of cup it.
And eat it like a folded pizza slice.
So this product would never work for me.
Ever.
Because there's not enough in here.
I-
There's not enough.
This is not a substantial burrito for me.
Like a taco.
Yeah like-
Like fold it up and eat it like a soft taco.
I-
Kids might have fun with this though right?
If you use this for-
Because look a kid's not gonna-
Oh hey roll a burrito son!
That's four years old.
And they're gonna be like-
I-
My head!
AHHHHHH!
And they're gonna start fucking crying and it's gonna be a disaster.
So I mean like this-
You can make like little-
Pancake pastries and burritos and stuff be fine right?
I can see it.
For crepes!
Make strawberries and cream crepes,
Chocolate banana crepes,
Peach crepes and more!
What a mistake not leading with that.
For a limited time you'll get the burrito perfect for only $9.99!
But if you call now you'll also get a hard shell taco holder free!
Hate holding the taco shell and mess in your hand?
Use the grape for once.
Now just place your taco shell in the taco holder and fill it with meat,
Topped with lettuce,
Shredded cheese,
Your favorite salsa,
And enjoy classic meat tacos,
Chicken tacos,
Seafood tacos and more!
Best of all burrito perfect and taco holder is bpa free and dishwasher safe!
Enjoy the simple,
Messy way to eat burritos and tacos any day!
You'll get the burrito perfect and hard shell taco holder for only $9.99!
But hold on, we're not done yet!
Call or click in the next 10 minutes and we will double your offer free!
Just pay separate processing and handling!
That's two burrito perfects and two taco holders a $30 value!
For only $9.99!
These incredible office gear...
Stop.
Okay.
You saw easy butter.
Perfect brownie.
Alright, perfect brownie is an automatic absolute buy for me.
Because you get edges.
It gives you edges.
You'll see what I mean.
Cut, rip, and tear.
But your brownies never turn out square.
And when they're stuck, you're totally out of luck.
No.
You have to throw the pan away.
Now you're talking about the brownie pan!
The new non-stick way to bake, slice, and serve perfect brownies!
That whole pan's gotta go.
You try it.
Just pour in your favorite batter.
Insert the diffuser...
Yup.
Everything gets an edge.
Yeah, come on.
...18 chocolatey brownies sliced all at once.
The reason?
The unique design and durable non-stick coating.
Not even 18 marshmallow treats will stick.
And look!
The bottom and sides separate.
So anytime it goes on this rack...
Wha...
...perfect brownie becomes the sweetest party serving term.
Anime voiceover?
Serve crazy top brownies for birthdays.
Marvel swirl for graduation.
I mean, I was gonna say, it sounds like kind of like...
Delicious double fudge brownies at your very own bake sale.
Cha-ching!
Oh no!
This pan which bakes eats brownies.
It looks so fucked up!
Someone ate all the edges again.
No, a raccoon got in the house.
So I would throw the whole thing away.
That's not like, oh, dad!
Dad ate all the edges that an animal got in your house.
And I don't know if this is probably not standard here to eat this.
The solution?
Design which bakes each brownie separately.
So they're moist inside and chewy outside.
If you can make ice cubes, you can use Perfect Brownie Pan.
Now stack them for ice cubes and sandwiches...
Yeah, no, these are better.
These are way better than doing it in a regular pan.
It just is.
...holidays, anniversaries, or barbecues.
Just bake, slice, and serve without ever using a knife.
It's a gimmick product, but it does what it's supposed to do.
Perfect Brownie Pan comes with the gooey and chewy recipe guide for the amazing low price of just $19.95.
And it's not just for brownies.
Make fluffy cakes, awesome bar cookies, or Grandma's Apple Pie Squares.
Grandma's Apple Pie Squares.
Smart shoppers receive these decorative stencils to make listive treats,
like flags on the Fourth of July, or transform any dessert into a work of art.
Oh, that's kind of cool.
You'll get the complete Perfect Brownie Pan with Divider,
Starbucks, ten stencils, and recipe guide for only $19.95.
That's right.
Cool.
All right.
That one, that's a classic.
The Chop Magic, the Go-Grill.
All right.
I don't know.
I kind of like, I haven't watched all of them.
I just watch every single one of these.
All right, let's do the Chop Magic.
And first of all, we got, first of all, this is important.
We've got Mark Gill here, which is automatic.
Like this product, I'm interested already, already, right off the bat.
Hi, Mark Gill here with the Chop Magic.
You're going to love the way this beauty can chop, mince, slice, and dice in just seconds.
Chopping vegetables the old way takes forever.
Yeah.
It's tough work and such a mess.
Well, not with Chop Magic.
Okay.
Go ahead, chop a whole onion in one second, no odor and no tears.
Chili and pepper, squash and zucchini in just three seconds.
You got it.
That's a stir fry that makes other choppers cry.
And it's safe too.
It's strong enough to go through solid sweet.
All right.
So here's why the other thing where it was the big like Dark Souls wheel, like weapon,
like pushing that down with the blades and shit.
This is has safety in mind.
You get it on the blade.
You line it up and you're not going to touch it.
It's not going to you.
The little prongs up top.
That's good.
I like that.
I like that a lot.
Yeah.
Easily chopped delicate tomatoes to perfection.
Now make fresh egg salad.
Healthy coleslaw needs to be pre-cut in no time.
That's it.
What's wrong with that?
I mean, they're all cubes though, right?
Presentation wise, everything is a ham cube.
Everything.
Everything is a ham cube.
So, I mean, presentation wise, maybe not, but practical, I think so.
Instantly prepare fresh fruit salads, zesty salsa, or a mountain of garlic without it
sticking to your head.
Somebody called me an infomercial centrist.
You can say it sucks.
Did you not hear me talk about the fucking microwave one, the one with the eggs?
I was like, nah, I don't think so.
What do you mean infomercial centrist?
I'm being honest and being very thorough.
I'm being very thorough.
Yeah, but nobody, nobody, dishwashers, nobody uses dishwasher.
I use my dishwasher.
I've run my dishwasher because otherwise it'll get gross.
I wash by hand.
I don't like that idea of take, oh yeah, there's like a bunch of
fucking like salsa and like mess on my plate.
Just stick it in here and turn the water on.
No, I don't like the dishwasher.
I don't like it.
And you know, I also, I don't like the dishwasher.
All the people question marking me right now.
So you enjoy putting like your dishes in this thing.
And then like, for like at least one to two fucking hours, you hear.
It's fucking obnoxious.
It's obnoxious.
And it lasts for an hour, an hour, two fucking hours of this.
You can, I can wash a whole fucking sink of dishes in 20 minutes.
Dishwashers are just loud, annoying.
They take way too long, a bunch of water.
No, no, no, no.
Sometimes I'll use it if I need to, you know, no, never.
Sounds like your dishwasher sucks.
Your dishwasher is broken.
What are you talking about?
Your dishwasher is fucked up.
That's impossible.
No, it's not.
No, it's not possible.
I don't use it.
They're not that loud normally.
I don't use this.
How would the dishwasher be broken if it was, if I never use it?
That's a huge amount of food.
All right.
Cool.
Chop magic is pretty cool.
I like it.
All right.
What about the go grill?
Yep.
Holy shit.
Can you imagine seeing somebody do this?
You don't want to, you try to load
your backyard grill into the trunk of your car.
Where are you taking this?
Bugs.
But honestly, I, yeah, no.
Okay.
All these sound effects.
You know, your product is really kind of just boring where you can't just show it.
You have to have like lasers and whooshing sounds.
Or I'm going to give the credit to the editor here.
The person editing, I would love God, if I could have, I could pick like a job.
I think it'd be perfect sitting in the editing room
and just kind of laughing to yourself and being like, yeah, I'm going to put,
yeah, I'm going to put like whooshing sounds here.
It's going to be funny.
I guarantee you they do that.
There's no way they don't.
That sounds like a fun like thing to do.
But only if they win.
Or grill a seafood delight when you go to the beach.
It's a must for camping food delight.
Why is this image so weird to me?
This is a strange image for some reason.
Why?
I can't figure out.
It's because they're all facing the same direction.
Yeah.
All of them are facing this way and the water is the other way
and you can't put the cameras in the water.
So this image just looks bizarre.
Like they don't want to go back to go where the water is.
This isn't a beach.
Wait, what is this?
He just said beach.
I also feel like this guy is way far away from these two.
I feel like they did a weird camera thing with this guy
is actually like 50 feet in front of them.
It's a must for camping or when you go RV.
And it's perfect for the boat.
When you go fishing.
This low profile fold away grill tucks away almost any.
Oh, I got a bite.
Hey, hold on a second.
I got four chicken breasts on a grill.
Hold on.
Oh, you went in the water over in a rowboat?
Be careful.
It's perfect when space is tight.
Your go grill can make 12 burgers sizzle all at once
or grill 24 hot dogs for an incredible.
No, that doesn't work.
If you're the guy that likes baby bags,
the go grill can handle a full man-sized rack.
The go grill will feed your full man-sized grill.
Oh, full man-sized.
We got man-sized portions.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, it's the whole rack.
Which you'll eat maybe a third of it.
And then be like, I don't really want any more of this.
And I have a man-sized portion.
You throw it away.
But man-sized though.
Make sure that's for men.
The go grill will feed your family and all of your friends.
What do you like to grill?
Chicken, steak, or lobster?
The list never ends.
The go grill is the most unique grill you'll ever own.
Take it anywhere you go.
Okay.
If I was at a barbecue and I walked up to the person
that was like, you know, operating the grill and the grill master.
I was like, oh, yeah, I guess they're ready.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, they're ready.
You want a man-sized portion?
I'd be like, no.
Ah, sure.
It's like four patties.
Like, no, I don't want them.
No, just guys, a regular one.
Can I just have a regular hamburger?
Just regular steak?
Like, I don't want a man-sized portion.
Join me at home.
I don't thank you.
You might expect to pay up to $100 for a grill this versatile.
But if you call now, your go grill is only $19.99.
$19.99?
What the fuck did you say?
Go grill only $19.99.
What a fuck-up.
That's a major fuck-up.
Order not this 11-piece stainless steel tool.
I thought this was drill bits.
Separate processing and handling.
That's an $80 value all for the incredible low price of only $19.99.
Okay.
I will give a positive here.
Here's the one positive.
There are tons of portable grills.
There are.
There's tons of them.
A portable grill is actually not a, it's actually pretty cool.
I would actually rather cook at my home on a portable grill than the huge,
gigantic grill that needs a bunch of maintenance.
So I would actually rather one of these than like a real huge grill.
I don't know.
That's just like a lot.
I also don't like propane.
It scares the shit out of me because just a fucking bunch of gas pressurizes.
You know how I feel about like pressurized gas and stuff.
So I don't like using propane.
I like charcoal.
And charcoal is a mess.
Yeah, that one's cool.
Okay.
Big top cupcake.
Perfect meatloaf.
I'm very curious about perfect meatloaf.
A flipjack pan.
Charcoal is the devil's fruit.
Rip meatloaf.
Charcoal is.
Do you want to play postal four?
I don't, I have no plan to do that.
Perfect meatloaf.
No, I'm doing a big top cupcake.
Cakes aren't cool.
Why do tiny cupcakes take so long to make?
This one's frame rate is bad.
Big top cupcake.
The fast and.
We've got this other voice though.
Cupcakes that are up to.
What the fuck.
Everyone's face will light up when you make a king size cupcake house.
Grab your camera to remember those giant cupcakes your family makes together.
It's so easy.
Just fill with any cake mix.
It's like 100p.
That jumbo cupcake looks amazing.
This is a cake.
Big top's quick release silicone is flexible and virtually nothing sticks.
It's just a cake though.
Pops out every time making it the ultimate party activity.
Mix and match delicious flavors like strawberry and chocolate.
Oh, what?
More thrilling than a chocolate filling made easy with our magic center insert.
Fill big tops with pudding, mousse, gelatin.
Okay, it's a different product.
Tiny cupcakes won't do, but 25 times bigger feeds the whole crew.
No one's going to eat all of it though.
I might.
Okay.
I know, they keep saying that.
They keep saying that.
Store-bought cakes are so expensive.
Are they?
I don't, I feel like they're not.
It's a man-sized cupcake.
Is a cupcake, is a cake that you can buy just at like the store,
like the grocery store, that expensive?
I thought that that was like a really good cheap option, isn't it?
I don't think they're cheap.
They're not that expensive.
They're like 10, they're like 15 bucks.
Oh, it's, it's a, it's a hundred dollars.
Like what, a hundred?
Where are you buying these cakes?
Yeah, they're like 10 to 20 dollars, aren't they?
But you can join the show now with Big Top Cupcake for the amazingly low price of $19.95.
It's a man-sized cupcake.
And to make decorating easy, we'll include this idea book free.
I love the sound effects.
Where is it?
Here it comes right, where is it?
A few quick steps, fill, bake, and decorate.
Store-bought cakes are so expensive.
Where is it?
Cake mold stick and cost over $35.
This is like an explosion sound.
You can join the show now with Big Top Cupcake for the amazingly low price.
There it is.
Okay.
It won't do, but 20 tiny cupcakes won't do, but.
That's so stupid.
That's so gross.
I wouldn't want that.
But you got to remember like the kid factor, right?
Kids, a big cupcake to a kid is holy shit.
This is a huge deal to a kid.
So a lot of these are like for kids or for seniors.
You got to keep that in mind.
All right.
That was cool.
What about a perfect meatloaf?
I think chat's ready for this one.
Is that crumbly meatloaf a pain to serve?
Do you hate all the oil, grease, and fat it cooks in?
There's got to be a better way.
Hi, it's Mark.
Hate all.
Did you?
Why is there more than like two pizzas worth of grease here?
What's going on?
Grease and fat it cooks in?
There's got to be a better way.
Hi, it's Mark with the perfect meatloaf pan.
The new nonstick way to bake, lift, and serve delicious meatloaf.
Watch.
Just prepare your favorite loaf.
Place it on this tray and pop it in the oven.
When done, simply lift the handles and presto.
Out comes the entire meatloaf all at once.
The reason?
The unique design and durable nonstick coating.
We haven't gotten the technology.
Other pans force your meal to sit in a bowl of fat.
No, it doesn't do that.
Those same nasty fat drippings stay at the bottom of the pan.
Okay, what kind of ground beef is this?
Who wants that?
This is not 80-20 ground beef.
This is like 60-40 ground beef.
With perfect meatloaf, those same nasty fat drippings stay at the bottom of the pan.
And oh my god.
Elevated lifting tray with over 60 drain holes.
Fat drippings can drain through the holes and collect in the space below
where they won't get reabsorbed back into the meatloaf.
Lift and serve delicious French onion meatloaf.
Savory stuffed Italian or moist bacon cheeseburger.
Perfectly Italian and with all the extra fat.
Meatloaf sucks.
But it's not just for meatloaf.
Baked sticky pecan rolls that lift right out of the pan.
Meatloaf sucks.
It just does.
Or roast and serve soft stuffed peppers without them ever falling apart.
Holiday serves.
There's only one meatloaf I've ever had that I liked and it was my mother's meatloaf.
Nobody else makes it this good.
And I'll tell you, let's be really honest with each other here.
I don't like your mother's meatloaf.
I like my mother's meatloaf.
Nobody likes another mother's meatloaf.
I don't like your mother's meatloaf.
I don't, I'm like, no, I don't like this.
But if my mom makes it, it's like, mom, it's fantastic.
Why is that?
Yeah, your mother's meatloaf is the only good meatloaf.
Even other mother's meatloafs are not good.
Perfect meatloaf pan is a tremendous value at just $14.95.
But I'm not done.
Call right now and receive this amazing guide knife.
Adjust to your desired size and slice.
Thick or thin, you'll always win.
I like that.
$20 value, free.
But I'm not stopping there.
Collar click right this minute and we'll double your order.
Just pay separate fucking.
Hold on a second, I need to, we gotta get, we gotta get that.
$20 value, free.
But I'm not stopping there.
Collar click.
That was, that was like violent.
Right this minute and we'll double your order.
Just pay separate processing and handling.
I love this guy.
That's right, you get two perfect meatloaf pans.
$14.95.
They're undercutting everybody.
You get two of them?
Okay.
All right.
That's not bad.
All right, bacon fill.
I think we saw that one already, right?
Flip jack pan.
We'll do the flip jack pan.
Pancakes are a pain to flip.
And half the time they burn and stick.
Not anymore.
Introducing.
It's the same design.
It's the same fucking design.
Greenick.
The easy.
It's the like turn it.
With flapjacks.
It's the turn it.
Or Greenick ceramic cookwares revolutionized non-stick.
Sick effect.
So now with flip jack, just add your favorite batter,
close the lid, then flip the pan.
You'll have perfect full-sized flapjacks.
And check this out.
We're going to burn a bunch of mozzarella cheese on it
and it's proof that we can scrape it out into the trash.
So there's less mess or dress.
Wait for it.
Forget about clumsy spatulas.
Your Greenick flip jack is so easy.
You'll flip pancakes with just one hand,
then slide them right out of the pan.
The secret is the dual hinge cooking design
with our Greenick ceramic surface.
Nothing ever sticks.
What the fuck?
Burned on cheese slides right off with no...
Thank you.
I get a point.
Um, the, the, what, design.
Right out of the pan.
The secret is the dual hinge cooking design with...
Dual hinge cooking technology.
They're not using technology anymore.
What year is this?
The Greenick ceramic surface.
Nothing ever sticks.
Even burned on cheese slides right off with no scrubbing.
You'll make hot and tasty blueberry
or a stack of buttermilk in seconds.
And the kids will love this chocolate chip surprise.
Oh, I would love that.
Close the lid, then flip for full-size fantastic flapjacks.
All without using a spatula.
Does this ever happen to you?
Not with flipjack.
Actually, yeah.
Over-easy eggs are a cinch.
And best of all, no broken yolks.
So call now to get the flipjack pancake pan.
Here's some inside information from Betty Crocker.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't tell me.
I don't want to know this insider info.
What if I want to buy shares in Betty Crocker?
Don't fucking tell me this.
Hey, I got insider info.
But don't fucking come near me.
Get away from me.
The most exciting thing you can do with the inside of a cake.
Introducing the Betty Crocker bacon fill.
A delightful new pan that lets you take care of cake.
Do we see this already?
Imagine the look on your child's face when you cut into the cake.
And there's his favorite flavor of ice cream.
Her favorite gelatin.
And who wouldn't enjoy a cake filled with delicious,
no secret is these three separate sections.
Then we already did this.
The same one into the main bacon.
This is a different commercial for this special inner chamber.
Now pour more cake mix into this base pan and put them both into.
Yeah, we've already seen this one.
Remove the insert.
Add your filling to the center cavity.
What is that?
Cover it with a base in no time.
You'll have the greatest cake you ever made.
Making an exciting cake with my Betty Crocker bacon fill is so easy.
And everything's nonstick.
So there's no messy cleanup.
These are the kind of desserts you'll find in the finest restaurants.
Ice cream cakes, Italian filled torts, even baked Alaska.
What is baked Alaska?
Wait, what the fuck is baked Alaska?
That's scary.
Or you can simply fill your cake with a different Betty Crocker cake mix.
Just fill the inner chamber.
Baked Alaska is on fire?
Now make all your cakes extra special.
Make them Betty Crocker bacon filled cakes.
I didn't know that.
You'll get the bacon fill pan, the inner chamber, and the base pan.
Complete with instructions and Betty Crocker recipes.
All for only $90.
I don't think it's supposed to be like a raging campfire.
Or your money back.
All right, we saw this one already.
Brownie Derby.
All right, Brownie Derby sounds pretty great.
Boring desserts that just fall flat.
There's only one.
Juicing the Brownie Derby.
The incredible Brownie Bowl maker that looks like a hat.
This, in my opinion, 100% what I believe was a different product.
That somebody on the board was just like, can we fill it with brownie mix?
I think so.
This is, I don't, this looks, this seems like a bizarre product.
But first of all, this is not a boring dessert.
This is not enough for three kids.
If there were three brownies on this plate, they would be cheering.
Brownies are amazing.
This is only one.
Five nights at Freddy's thing.
What the fuck?
But who cares?
Okay, who cares?
I mean, if you need something to cook a brownie in, then fine.
That's fine.
But it's not cool.
Okay.
But if you want a brownie that has a hole in it to put ice cream in it, then that makes sense.
That's the only thing that they had.
It's not like a fun toy.
Like they're trying to make, it's just a thing that has a hole.
It's a brownie with a hole in it.
Like this makes sense.
But our man-sized brownie bowl.
Why do they?
The same shot.
Is it the same company?
It probably is.
It's the same company.
Probably.
It has to be.
Also, another thing that I have an issue with.
They always show.
I don't think this brownie was $80.
I would be surprised if this was like a $50 to $80 brownie.
Unless you're at like the fucking weed store.
Is this an edible brownie?
Well, dad, you sent in the wrong footage because that is $20 for it.
I mean, that's not out of the ordinary, I don't think.
The weed store.
What the fuck?
Whose camera is that?
Is it a kid?
They knew.
This was, what year was this?
This was probably like 2005.
They knew it was coming.
Oh, the tip the hat.
I like that.
That was a nice touch.
Yeah, that was a nice touch.
Now, how about magic meal?
I don't know.
It's so bit rate is so bad.
I can't even tell.
Spaghetti.
All right, but I got to be centrist Andy here.
I got to be centrist Andy.
I got to be a centrist.
I wouldn't put clams in the microwave.
I don't think so.
Plus store leftovers in the fridge.
And by the way, does it have to look like a fucking urn?
Easy reheating and it's dish.
Like it just looks like an urn.
Frozen to defrost.
Oh, what?
Imagine perfectly cooked juicy chicken
right from your microwave.
Simply unlock and twist.
What the fuck?
Right from the bottom veggies.
It's like the right crunch.
Enjoy healthy fish and hearty nutritious soups.
Even rinse and serve a healthy salad.
I have no commentary for this one.
Amazing five piece magic meal for just $19.99.
Plus get the recipe book.
All right, there is no fucking way.
Like that chicken has been like browned on the outside.
That's impossible in a microwave.
You can't, that can't happen.
In minutes?
What do you mean in minutes?
No, this didn't happen in there.
Okay, I have, I have a way to be centrist dandy on this one.
You buy this for $19.95 and it sits in your cupboard.
You don't ever use it.
You never touch it unless you get a call from grandma or call from mom.
Oh, hey, mom.
Oh, hey, sweetie.
We'll be over in 15 minutes.
We thought we'd stop by.
And we figured maybe we'd have dinner at your place tonight.
Raw chicken, pasta, raw pasta, water.
Stick the fucking urn in the microwave in 15 minutes.
10 minutes, whatever it is.
And by the time they pull up, get that out of there.
Get it out, get it on a plate.
Make sure it's like, okay, good.
Hi, guys.
Try the amazing five piece magic meal for just $19.99.
Plus get the recipe book with dozens of delicious meals.
Order in the next 10 minutes and we'll double your order.
And we're still not finished.
Okay, but most people only have one microwave.
Who has two microwaves?
This thing, obviously from the commercial, fills the whole microwave.
Did anybody have more than one microwave in their house or in their apartment?
Like who has like two full-size microwaves?
Just do it, but you can't just dump this out and clean it and do it again.
And we're still not finished.
We'll include the little red chef.
Great for onions, eggs, garlic, salsa, and more.
A $15 value, free.
You get it all.
Two five-piece deluxe magic meals.
Two gourmet recipe books.
And the handy food chopper.
A whopping $75 value.
Oh, I know you can do with the other one.
You can use this as an urn.
For just $19.99.
We're so sure you'll love magic meal.
But if you don't agree, simply return it.
But keep the food chopper as-
Oh, Jesus.
Hi, Billy Mays here for-
Oh, Billy Mays.
Billy Mays.
Oh, fucking legend.
Big city sliders.
Fucking God.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What?
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Everybody back up and everybody shut up for a second.
This is not-
I've seen products like this where you-
Oh, look, you make perfect little patties.
But then you have to cook them.
This is a pan.
No way.
What?
Yeah, yeah.
Burnt on cheese.
And they always make the pans look so dirty.
Oh, that's fucking awesome.
Whoa.
Bagel sandwiches?
Bro, I'm sorry.
I would want this.
I'd get it.
I don't care what anybody says.
The double decker.
The blue cheese bomber.
The buffalo chicken burger.
Oh, couldn't come up with one for that one.
Triple stack attack.
The Cajun bayou burger.
The pork burger.
The turkey delight burger.
Just-
Kicken crab cakes.
Mushroom swiss slider.
Curry burger.
Reuben slider.
Bruchetta burger.
All right, I gotta be honest.
The Billy burger looks fucking dope.
Dope.
What is that?
Chopped grilled onions?
Ketchup mustard slice of American cheese on a patty?
Looks dope.
Don't say dope.
Okay.
All right.
Can that do butter?
Crab slicer.
Here's how you can call or log on.
1999.
There it is.
All right, that's-
I love it.
I would get-
Okay, there's two or three that I would get.
How about shake and take my blend buddy?
That's a long name.
Okay, blenders actually are a pain in the ass.
So I will give this one a little bit of time here.
Hate fussing with the blunders of blenders.
Especially when you're on the go.
Then searching for a portable cop and messy cleanups.
Well, now there's blend buddy.
The world's only blender that mixes right inside a portable sports bottle.
So you'll always have a quick new blend buddy.
Wait.
Hold on.
Where's her other hand?
Where's your other hand?
It's not holding anything.
She's got a purse around the shoulder.
Her other hand is free.
Why don't you use the other hand?
Well, now there's blend buddy.
The world's only blender that mixes right inside a portable sports bottle.
So you'll always have a quick meal ready fast and easy.
Just fill with your favorite fruits.
Press the button.
Phone.
Oh, up like this.
Your delicious blueberry smoothie is ready to go.
Then simply-
Oh, then it's a container.
Yeah, but the magic bullet did this.
The magic bullet did this already.
Even the mixing blades are attached.
So there's no extra parts.
The large 16-ounce container will satisfy the biggest thirst.
Man-sized.
And not only is it man-sized, but look at this.
This man's out working.
Construction.
Large for a man.
Satisfy the biggest thirst.
And because it's dishwasher safe, blending a drink won't fill your sink.
But the best part-
A man-sized thirst.
20,000 RPMs of power pulverizes frozen fruits, ice, and nuts into smooth, creamy drinks.
Guaranteed.
Not that you would, but even solid rock is turned into a fine powder.
That's broken now.
GlenBuddy is perfect for executives with busy schedules.
Executive.
A must for moths.
GlenBuddy is perfect for executives, but even solid rock is turned into a fine powder.
Is that a wedding ring?
That's a huge ring.
That's a big wedding ring?
Is it executive?
No, it's not, right?
What size does a wedding ring have to be on?
That's a man-sized wedding ring.
Is perfect for executives with-
Executives.
I love its executives.
Oh, it's perfect.
It's perfect for an executive with a briefcase.
This executive?
Where is this executive, by the way?
Does he live here?
Is this another person's house?
Who is the exec-
Perfect for the executive.
Because they've shown us the same people the whole time, right?
Is this the same family?
It's the same kitchen.
Oh no, it's not the same kitchen, okay.
I thought it was the same kitchen.
Because I was going to say, are they all living in the same house?
Because they showed, like, construction worker guy.
Executive.
Mom, I'm guessing, right?
Like, I thought they were all going to be in the same house.
The Sims.
Oh, executive-sized thirst.
These are kind of-
That wouldn't be a bad gift.
That's not a bad gift, I don't think.
Like, that's a cool prio-centrist-
Whatever.
All right, how about the potato express?
What?
Holy shit!
I didn't even think this was a potato.
Oh my god, what happened to this?
This looks like a-
That's like, that's plastic or something.
A potato doesn't do that in the microwave.
45 minutes?
Did they fuck this up, and does this person not understand that it's 45 minutes in the oven,
and not 45 minutes in the microwave?
Whoa.
All right, what is that?
What the fuck?
The insulation steam pocket technology.
All right, this is high-tech.
Why are they putting it in an oven mitt?
It's not an oven mitt.
It's something, it don't-
I'm telling you, there's something in there that makes it microwave safe.
Delicious potato salad ever.
Use potato express for super quick home fries for a gourmet breakfast.
Potato express will save you time when making mashed potatoes-
Sugar and mar- I don't know.
Or present tender potato skins.
Machine washable and reusable over and over again.
Stop wasting time baking potatoes in the-
Stop opening the oven when you're cooking food.
Maybe that would help that-
You know why it takes you 45 minutes to cook a potato?
Because you go like this every fucking two minutes.
Leave it alone.
Call now and get potato express complete-
And they just sit in-
Stop wasting time-
Did you just put three baked potatoes on the rack?
Stop opening the oven.
In the oven.
Call now and get potato express-
You're drunk.
That's right.
For just $10.
As a bonus, get the perfect-
Just shit face.
Absolutely free.
Instantly garnish your potatoes with cheese and more.
I own one of these.
It's actually pretty good.
Double your order free.
Just pay separate processing and handling.
Doesn't surprise me.
You get it all.
Two potato express, two-
Was that seasoning?
And two perfect graters.
All for just $10.
So wait, you actually have this?
Does it work?
If it works, it works.
That's why I-
I don't want to-
Look, talking shit about these like commercials, sure, right?
We can do that.
But if they work as advertised and they're useful-
Good.
All right.
It works.
My friend has one of these.
And then it works.
Who cares?
There's no problem.
I am so ready for the Hulk grill
because it's going to be a ton of man-sized portions.
You've tried other grills on the market.
Some of them may drain the grease,
but don't cook the meat even-
Is that-
Is that Hulk Hogan?
Now you can enjoy juicy cooked burgers grilled to perfection.
Grilled cheese sandwiches in just 30 seconds.
Homemade golden brown Belgian waffles in just minutes.
Why was it-
Delicious panini sandwiches in five minutes.
Why did they use Hulk Hogan?
Fresh or frozen pizza baked in 15 minutes.
Amazing quesadillas in only two minutes.
Plump and juicy hot dogs.
Amazing thick cut frozen steaks-
Is Hulk Hogan in the commercial?
...perfection in only 20 minutes.
Even delicious desserts.
And your kids-
Hulk size.
...will look like this.
Oh my god.
...lives up to its name.
The Hulk Hogan?
Hulk Hogan's ultimate grill.
This is George Foreman.
Because its extra large interchangeable plates
easily transforms your Hulk Hogan grill into a skillet.
This is George Foreman grill.
The Hulk Hogan grill?
Pizza oven.
What?
Quesadilla maker.
A buffet warmer.
And then some.
That's $1,200 worth of specialty appliances
in just one countertop rebel-
I thought he was going to say twelve hundred appliances.
Okay, what is it?
What is it?
This is a fry-
No, this is like a serving tray.
Twelve hundred appliances.
...a buffet warmer.
And then some.
That's $1,200 worth of specialty appliances
in just one countertop rebel-
And it's Hulk size.
Not even man size.
Best of all, the food is filled with ultimate flavor.
The secret is the ultimate grill cooks with mechanical pressure.
Just lock the lid, instantly searing in flavor-
Why is he here?
...sides every time.
Plus with its-
We better get like a 30-second monologue
of him looking right in the camera.
Let me tell you something, brother.
The Hulk Hogan grill.
It's got the healthiest-
Yeah, please do it.
...way to the self-contained fat trapper.
The unique floating hinge allows the ultimate grill
to adjust to the size of the food,
so it's cooked to perfection every time.
Just the way you like it.
Grill Hulk-size chops, steaks, chicken, and fish.
Open it up-
You don't have Hulk Hogan on the thing
if he doesn't say something monologue for ten seconds.
...ultimate grill turns into the ultimate panini sandwich
to make grilled turkey paninis.
Make a quick and healthy lunch for you-
I thought that was Hulk Hogan for a second.
...heat settings allow you to cook different foods at the same time.
Cook bacon, sausages, or other breakfast meats on the grill plate
while the excess grease drains into the self-contained fat trapper.
Seafood is perfect to cook on Hulk Hogan's ultimate grill.
You can easily cook swordfish on one side,
scallops and shrimp kebabs on the other.
Close the grill and cook delicious savory salmon.
Grill large chicken breasts while keeping them plump and juicy-
They showed him eating half a hot dog in one bite and that's it.
...serve with grilled vegetables.
Take the leftover chicken, add a tortilla,
and you've got amazing fresh quesadillas.
Hulk Hogan's ultimate grill-
Where is he?
...you're on a special diet, whether it's high protein or vegetarian.
Stir-fry all your vegetables on one side.
At the same time, you can heat up your rice.
Place a large, fresh, or frozen pizza on the skillet,
and in just 15 minutes, you've got a mouth-watering, gourmet, crispy pizza.
Best of all, cleanup is a breeze.
Just put the self-contained no-spill fat trapper
in cooking plates in the dishwasher.
It's that easy.
Hulk Hogan's ultimate grill-
He's not here!
...apartments, dorm rooms, RVs, boats, and so much more.
That's it?
No way!
What the fuck?
He's just a gif in the corner and they showed him biting into a hot dog.
He didn't do anything.
He didn't do anything but this.
...the food is filled with ultimate flavor.
The secret is the ultimate-
He just bit into a hot dog.
Maybe there's a 30-minute version?
I hope there is, because holy shit, that's so funny.
But even if this is the short version,
you're not going to have Hulk Hogan doing anything besides bite a hot dog
in your two- three-minute spot?
Your three-minute spot has him biting a hot dog.
You've got to have him being like,
oh, this is- I'm telling you something, this is really good.
It's very flavorful, very healthy.
You've got to get him to talk.
That's it?
There's definitely got to be a 30-minute version.
When you make merch for-
Listen to me.
When you make merch for your commercial,
it's going to be a 30-minute spot.
No way.
This is the three minutes.
All right.
How about the Fresh Mex Express?
You love a delicious Mexican fiesta?
Yes, I do.
Salsa, guacamole-
Bring it on.
...but chopping, slicing, mixing, it's a chore.
Hi, David Jones here with Fresh Mex Express.
David Jones.
...the fast, easy way to make guacamole, salsa, and more in seconds.
Watch.
Just add tomatoes, onions, and cilantro.
Put the lid on.
Give it a couple of turns.
In less than five seconds, you have unbelievable fresh salsa.
I don't know, but I don't know.
I don't know if this is a new character.
David Jones?
I don't know.
I don't like new characters.
I don't like new things.
Maybe we'll warm up to him.
Easy.
Take some avocados, onions, cilantro,
for a full bowl of guacamole in just five seconds.
That was way more than five seconds.
...the three ultra-sharp stainless steel blades that chop, mix, and prep in just one step.
Thick, medium, or finely chopped with Fresh Mex Express, the choice is yours.
This is fucking stupid.
Make a spicy guacamole, mouth-watering mango salsa, creamy chili cheese dip,
flavorful black bean dip, even make fresh, healthy hummus, and-
What the fuck?
...nothing's better.
Top burritos with guacamole-
I can't, man.
This is fucking so dumb.
...make cheesy steak fajitas, load up nachos,
that bulky food processor is a pain and takes forever to clean,
but Fresh Mex Express chops, mixes, and serves in the same bowl,
and it's dishwasher safe.
Now get Fresh Mex Express complete with our South of the Border Recipe Guide for just-
We found the whole cut.
Good.
I'm happy about it.
...stackable storage lid to save tasty leftovers,
but call right now and we'll double the offer free-
They keep playing the same-
Oh, it's killing me.
They keep playing the same 10-minute clip.
The same 10-minute music file.
It's like, oh, come on, man.
You don't got anything else to put here?
...stackable storage lid to save tasty leftovers-
It's so fucking dumb.
...call right now and we'll double the offer free.
Just pay separate processing and handling.
And to really spice things up, you'll also get our Tortilla Express free.
Microwave moist steamed tortillas in just seconds that stay hot for up to an hour.
You get it all.
Two Fresh Mex Expresses with storage lids-
Who's that?
...and the Tortilla Express for just $19.99.
All right.
What if it might be fun?
If it's doable to work with the kids.
We found the Hulk one.
All right, hold on.
All right.
Let me- I gotta go pee.
I'll be right back.
Try modulating video speed.
I'll be back.
I gotta pee.
We'll be back with more.
I'll put the Hulk one on.
Oh, shit.
I forgot the- Oh, well.
Oops.
All right.
Where's the link to the-
Okay, we got it in the mods gave to me.
Is this the whole thing?
Yep.
28 minutes.
Oh, hell yeah.
The following is a paid for the Hulk Hogan Ultimate Grill.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Okay.
Let me just pull this.
So this is the Hulk Hogan Ultimate Grill.
It's probably going to be in like 140p.
Just to let everybody know.
Come back over here.
We're not going to watch the whole thing.
Maybe we will.
Let's find out.
You guys ready?
The following is-
That was very loud.
Paid advertisement for Hulk Hogan's Ultimate Grill.
Brought to you by TriStar Products Incorporated.
All right.
Let's go.
Hey, guys.
I'm Hulk Hogan.
Stay with me for the next half hour.
I'm going to show you my latest invention.
My invention.
Finally, a grill that lives up to its name.
Hulk Hogan's Ultimate Grill.
It's the ultimate because-
Okay.
The large interchangeable plates easily transforms your-
You know what?
They definitely were just like,
Hey, Hulk, Hulk Hogan.
We're going to run the camera for three minutes.
And just do whatever you want.
Do like three or four promos.
And you can literally say anything you want.
Just kind of flex and shit.
And we're just going to put you around the commercial.
And then I think he's in person here.
This is important.
To a skillet.
Panini sandwich press.
He made this.
Pizza oven.
And then some-
No, he did not.
Ultimate Grill cooks with mechanical pressure-
George Foreman did 10 years before this.
Just like the lid.
Instantly searing in flavor and juices.
You have evenly perfectly grilled food on both sides every time.
Plus with its two huge cooking surfaces,
along with the dual variable heat settings from 210 to 425 degrees,
you can easily cook healthy meals.
While excess fat drips away into the self-contained fat trapper.
Just remove it, empty it, and put it in the dishwasher.
The unique floating hinge allows the Ultimate Grill to adjust to the size of the food.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Excuse me.
I- Men don't like healthy things.
We like chicken, cheese, bacon, and cheeseburgers.
Grilled cheese sandwiches in just 30 seconds.
Homemade golden brown Belgian waffles in just minutes.
Delicious panini sandwiches in five minutes.
Pressure frozen pizza baked in 15 minutes.
Amazing quesadillas in only two minutes.
And coffee.
Juicy hot dogs.
Amazing thick cut frozen steaks cooked to mouthwatering perfection in only 20 minutes.
20 minutes?
Even delicious desserts.
And your kitchen doesn't have to look like this.
Stay tuned to discover how you can replace over time.
You stood from the back of the room and threw those puffs into the sink.
With just one countertop wonder that's simple to use,
simple to clean, and is as easy to store as a box of cereal.
Here's our host, Bob Wharton, and the man who demanded the Ultimate Grilling Machine.
To discover how you can replace over $1,200 of appliances with just one countertop wonder
that's simple to use, simple to clean, and is as easy to store as a box of cereal.
Who's putting a box of cereal down here?
And is as easy to store as a box of cereal.
Why are you hiding this in like a safe down here?
A box of cereal?
Here's our host, Bob Wharton, and the man who demanded the Ultimate Grilling Machine.
Oh, the man who demanded the Ultimate Grill.
Finally, we've come up with a grill that lives up to its name.
It's the Ultimate Grill, and it's definitely the Ultimate Cooking Appliance.
And we promised everyone that they'd love my grill so much.
Don't you dare talk over Hulk Hogan, right?
Like, he's like, don't you dare.
Okay. Well, this is one of the most popular grills on the market.
It cooks on a slant, and it may drain all the grease.
But what are some of the other problems it may have?
This grease is horrible here on the tray.
Oh, what the fuck?
Because this has no temperature control.
Wait, they're making it look like shit.
The hamburgers are well done at the back while they're still rare in the front.
And it's a real problem to clean up.
Now, watch this.
Oh, that's supposed to be the George Mormon.
But we're going to put six burgers on there.
Hey, guys, notice this.
These aren't ordinary burgers.
These are Hulk-sized burgers.
And we are going to show you how we get them to cook evenly from the front all the way to the back.
Here's where the difference is.
On the back of this, we have it raised up so that the hinge will automatically pop up.
And then on the front, we push down and we...
You know why I don't like these grills?
Because I can't see it.
I can't see what the food...
I need to kind of look at it, right?
I feel like I want to see it.
Oh, there's nothing on it.
Oh!
It's just meat and bun.
Oh, what the fuck?
Look at how small that looks in his hands.
This is tiny.
This looks like a toy.
Like, he actually has to, like, lean down and go, like...
This is very small.
I wouldn't consider this to be Hulk-sized.
No, he just took out a third of the burger in one bite.
That's not Hulk-sized at all.
Grill.
Or ultimate grill.
The horse can't live on burgers alone, brother.
What about this panini sandwich maker?
This is a professional panini maker we went out and bought.
Costs $430.
What?
And it does a great job.
And what we figured out...
What?
That's...
Seriously.
...does a good job is...
I think that was a genuine reaction because that's horse shit.
...and the weight to actually cook the sandwich from top to bottom.
You said weight.
This thing looks like it weighs up.
A ton.
Yeah, well, that's a lot.
Okay, who's gonna hold this thing around?
If even Hulk Hogan's having trouble with this, you know it must be very heavy.
Well, that's the only thing you really use that for.
Take a look at those paninis.
Those are huge.
Now, do you see how that indent line is there?
That's the mechanical pressure and weight that we're able to put on with ultimate grill.
I want one of these shirts.
Those look great.
I think those look better than those beautiful burgers.
I want one of these shirts so bad.
Look at that cheese.
You know what I mean?
Look at how beautifully that smells.
Like the Hulk Hogan ultimate grill.
I feel like we'd be glad we got them inside.
I want one of those.
Now, get rid of that.
Pizza is my favorite.
Really?
Well, what we did is we went out and bought this pizza maker.
It takes about 30 minutes.
It's a little bit faster than heating up your whole oven,
but it takes 30 minutes to make a pizza.
Take a look.
And we got this pizza maker from some shitty infomercial.
So take a look at our infomercial.
Ours is better.
I'm gonna slide this off and I'm gonna cut a piece because I want you to see.
That one's hot.
It is hot.
Believe me, it is very hot.
Hold on.
Wait, wait.
I feel like I missed something here.
It takes 30 minutes to make a pizza.
Take a look at that.
Is that a pizza?
What?
That is a pizza.
Now, I'm gonna slide this off and I'm gonna cut a piece because I want you to see.
That one's hot.
It is hot.
Believe me, it is very, very hot.
Dude, what's with the pizza cutting?
Holy shit, bro.
I cannot believe how good this is.
Come on.
I did a smell.
What was that?
Oh, that was.
Isn't that great?
Now, let me show you the bottom.
God, it looks good.
Look at this.
Oh, it's grilled perfectly.
What is he?
Isn't it?
He's like scratching it.
He didn't even bite it.
Very, very hot.
Now, this is probably gonna be too hot to eat, Hulk.
This grill's amazing.
I cannot believe how good this pizza looks.
Just to get a smell and a feel of that.
A smell?
It's pizza.
Isn't that great?
Now, let me show you the bottom.
God, it looks good.
Look at this.
Oh, it's grilled perfectly.
It's perfect, isn't it?
I actually think the one on the pizza maker looks a little better.
In the morning breakfast, without a doubt,
this is the most important meal in my family.
I do the cooking in the morning.
So one of the problems I have is sometimes the eggs
aren't ready when the sausage is ready, the pancakes aren't done.
All right, yeah.
It's a real pain for me.
I have to figure out a way to make it all work at once.
OK, well, that's because even though this griddle costs over $100,
you really can't get every piece.
I mean, the problem is you didn't get Kathy Mitchell.
Look at all the grease.
The grease is in the pancakes.
Wait, did you just tell him to shut up?
That is ridiculous.
So if we could, well, that's because even though this griddle costs over $100,
you really can't cook everything at the same time.
Wait a minute, stop.
Look at all the grease.
The grease is in the pancakes.
That was an annoyed stop.
If we could separate the eggs in the pancakes from the bacon and sausage,
we'd have the solution, right?
You got it.
I put a griddle plate in here and a grill plate here.
I've already grilled the sausage at about 350 degrees.
I turned it down because I have the control to just warm about 200 degrees.
It's not following.
I cranked this up to 375 because now I'm ready to make pancakes
and now you can make your eggs to order.
Let's throw some eggs on there, buddy.
We can actually do a dozen eggs on here at a time if we want or about eight pancakes.
How about that for breakfast?
That's great.
That's unbelievable.
But okay, what's but a skill with this is it's good.
It's fine.
I think it's very interesting.
God damn it.
You know, one thing that I wish whatever ever happened to me in my life,
they used to do an infomercial of these.
Look at we're in a mall.
Come try it and come check it out and be on TV.
God damn it, man.
I wish I wish I if I if I ever see this ever,
I am running up to that fucking thing and being first in line.
I want to be that.
I want to be the weird guy that's just like it's so fresh.
It's delicious.
Better than better than grandma makes.
I want to do that so bad, even if it sucks.
I wish I could show you an infomercial where I was one of these people.
You can do all this with the one one system because we have a waffle iron.
We have a little sandwich maker and then we make our pizzas in the regular oven.
So this is very good.
I like the idea of this compared to other girls.
It's a lot different variety of foods that you can cook,
whereas the others just sort of limited to certain things.
I'm a vegetarian and so it would be really easy for us to make it just like his neck muscles up.
It's just nice to be able to get something done for the whole family
all at once instead of having to break it down into little pieces.
So everybody can sit down and eat at the same time.
I'm too busy to talk.
I'm eating the delicious food.
Oh, that was a bump.
I can't wait to get this for my dorm room.
I can make like waffles in the morning and eggs.
I envy this.
Watch, make some pizza.
Don't get some hot dogs.
My room is going to be the life of every party.
I'm a tall big guy and I definitely like eating burgers.
Nice large burgers.
The executive is so perfect for that.
Cookies, pizza.
Perfect for the executive.
Burgers, waffles.
The best thing in the world.
See, as far as I know that I wish nothing on the market that cooks frozen steaks.
Are those frozen, buddy?
Get out of there.
Yeah, those are frozen.
Okay, get them out there.
What's going on with the music here?
I could finally hear them talking to each other.
I was like, oh, this is like better somehow, right?
When this came back, wasn't it like, oh, cool, nice.
They're talking to each other.
As far as I know, there is nothing on the market that cooks frozen steaks.
Are those frozen, buddy?
Yeah, those are frozen.
Okay, get them out there.
Geez.
Now, what we're going to do is we're going to unlock the back.
These are frozen.
We're going to unlock the back of the grill.
Two inch frozen steaks.
They certainly are and we're going to put them on here.
Those are frozen.
Now, I know you like them.
Yeah, they are very frozen.
I'm going to take a couple of potatoes.
I'm going to put them on here with it because they're frozen.
They're going to get up at the same time.
They're going to cook perfectly.
In about 20 minutes, you're going to have perfectly cooked steaks.
Those aren't even the same shape.
Here's how we turned the ultimate grill into the ultimate party buffet warmer.
Party buffet.
Again, we opened it double.
In this case, I used two griddle plates.
You can use a griddle and a grill.
I turned the dual heat settings down to warm.
Now, we have 10 of your favorite orders.
No, I don't say that.
I don't know.
All you have to do is come in and enjoy.
It's going to keep it warm.
I don't know.
Okay.
Open or closed, big or small, fresh or frozen, Paul Hogan's ultimate grill truly does it all, brother.
I can't wait to see this.
But wait a minute.
It hasn't done its all yet because I haven't even showed you your favorite thing, waffles.
And I know you like Mexican food.
How about quesadillas?
What?
Let me come back.
Oh, I'm on the edge of my seat right now.
On the market.
Some of them may drain the grease, but don't cook the meat evenly.
And the cleanup is a mess introducing Paul Hogan.
Thank God there's something to finally call to it because it's extra large interchangeable
plates easily transforms your Hulk Hogan grill into a skillet waffle.
All right, we get it.
We get it.
We know we get it.
Show me the show me the duo again, please.
Hi, guys.
Welcome back.
Bob and I just showed you how my ultimate grill replaced over $1,200 with a professional kitchen
appliances.
All right, we're not done yet.
We can't do quesadillas.
Well, remember just before we left, we put two two and a half inch frozen steaks in here
along with a couple of potatoes.
Let's see how they came out.
Are you ready?
Boomer century video.
Take a look at that.
Well, here's the deal with the frozen steaks.
Yeah, I've never seen or heard of anybody cooking frozen steaks and getting them totally
perfect.
Even cook perfectly on the inside.
Well, let's just see.
This is just the way you would just thought that juice
look at that.
Now, that's what I call it.
It's always about the juiciness of the steak, right?
It's always like, look, I'm going to press and it's because we have juice is going to
come up at the same time.
They care more about how much water is coming out of cheese sandwiches.
I love grilled cheese, but you told me you had a problem with it.
It's never get the center finished the same time the outer edges do.
And I always make a mess and I always burn them.
Well, how about if I told you we're going to make these grilled cheese sandwiches, four
of them oversized, by the way, as you can see, in about 30 seconds.
All right, 30 seconds.
Now, the way we're going to do that is we're going to use pressure.
Give it a press.
It locks in place.
30 seconds.
Are you counting?
All right.
But a grilled cheese is like a grilled cheese is very easy to make.
It's very easy.
What is he saying here?
Problem with it can never get the center finished the same time the outer edges do.
And I always make a mess and I always burn them.
But I fucking love Paul Cogan.
How about if I told you we're going to make these grilled cheese sandwiches, four of them
oversized, by the way, as you can see, in about 30 seconds.
Always, man.
Always.
You burn it every time.
I'm imagining this is like, oh, well, I want to make grilled cheese sandwich.
I burnt it again.
I burn it every time.
Turn the heat down.
Give it a press.
It locks in place.
30 seconds.
Are you counting?
I'm getting ready to call you out on this one.
Here we go.
But we don't know how much.
Wow.
How about that?
Now, that was 30 seconds.
We've got molten cheese sandwiches inside.
Molten.
Now, the true test is if they're the same all the way through.
I get his point, though.
They're too hot for me to handle.
And just take a look at that.
How about that?
Let me see that.
Okay, grab a bite.
Now, careful.
Don't burn yourself because they are hot, hot, hot, hot sandwiches right now.
Instant replay.
Just in case you want to see those grill marks.
I wanted someone to explain to me here.
What is the obsession with the grill marks?
Oh, but look, it's got grill marks on it now.
Who fucking cares?
Who cares?
Dude, it's a hot dog and it tastes exactly the same, but this time it's got grill marks on it.
Okay, who cares?
Why is that such a huge, huge selling point?
Yeah, it's somebody just said it's just a racing stripe.
The grill marks on a real grill, it's like, okay, you're cooking on a fire or with propane or
charcoal.
Is it having just like a grate that makes marks on your food doesn't make it cooked on a grill,
like doesn't make it cooked on like a charcoal grill.
It's like pretending it adds texture.
Not really, though.
A hot dog.
This is a great time for a party that if you're going that way, all right, give it a press.
It'll snap into place and those hot dogs are going to be like, oh, they're going to be like,
snap into place and those hot dogs are going to be done in about two minutes.
It adds swag.
Hey, look at that.
It's party time.
Just roll it right out.
Oh, if only you had that canvas scooper.
If only you had the canvas scooper, you'd be just fine.
What was it called again?
The hammock grabber.
I love the instant replay.
I cook shrimp and steak and it's done quickly.
There's enough for everybody.
We take it to the beach.
We take it to a cabin.
And it's done and steak and it's done.
He's not sure about this.
Quickly.
There's enough for everybody.
We take it to the beach.
We take it to a cabin.
And the cleanup is so simple and easy.
It's the ultimate grill.
We love to have our friends over and to entertain.
And in the past, it was bringing out the hors d'oeuvres from the oven,
putting them on the tray.
They would get cold.
He's like, now with the whole cold and ultimate grill,
we put all the hors d'oeuvres in one place.
They stay warm.
And we have enough time to spend with our friends.
That's an application for this.
Having like it's served but on low heat.
I could see that as kind of like a party tray sister
because shit does get cold.
I could see that.
This is an application for this.
What kind of waffles do you like?
Well, not this kind.
It's too small.
I like big golden brown.
Perfect waffles.
Fluffy and big.
Well, this is a professional waffle maker.
It costs $90.
What's wrong with that?
Job of making waffles, but this is how much waffles it makes.
So what we did with the ultimate grill,
remember, we give you interchangeable plates.
These are optional to your Hulk Hogan grill.
So all we do now is we swap out by pushing the button here
and here.
I love Hulk Hogan.
Your waffle plates.
Now Hulk Hogan is like a real Superman.
This is the same amount exactly of batter as that reason.
Hold on.
Pause, Andy.
I know the reason why I used to love wrestling
is because Hulk Hogan was a real superhero.
He was in real life, like the ultimate warrior macho man.
These guys were superheroes.
I saw Hulk Hogan not as a wrestler,
but as like Captain America, essentially.
I loved it.
It was just like, wow, there he is, like a superhero.
He like fights for good.
He was like Captain America.
So that's one professional machine's worth,
two professional machines worth, three professional machines worth.
This grill got recalled.
Wait a minute.
You said that was a $90 machine?
That was a $90 machine.
We're going to do four.
So we're making four waffles at the same time.
So that's like having a $360 machine right here.
Well, we're going to see how they come out,
but they're going to be absolutely perfect.
Give your machine a little love.
Press it.
Now we've got the pressure in there.
We know that we're set at 375.
Top and bottom.
They're going to come out good.
We finally read it.
Let's see how are we done with our waffle.
Really?
Beautiful.
How about that?
Now, is that an ordinary waffle?
What's going on?
I just bought a piece of the pizza.
It was really good.
I can't believe how crispy the pizza was on the bottom.
Does it not?
Yeah, remember the crispy pizza?
The secret is the ultimate grill cooks with mechanical pressure.
Just lock the lid, instantly searing it off it.
You'll love your Hulk Hogan ultimate grill.
I'm not going to give you a 30-day money back guarantee.
I'm going to give you a 60-day money back guarantee.
I love that.
Because I'm putting my name on it.
When you call, ask your operators how you can get the waffle.
Oh, cookies.
We're going to say this.
Cookie baking machine.
Now we can do little cookies.
Those are huge cookies.
Now that's a little cookie.
In here, we got a Hawks.
Whoa.
Now, want to decorate that?
Nobody's going to.
That's too big.
I put my smile and face on the whole thing.
That's just a pancake.
I've bought cookies the size of the grocery store.
And they're like $40.
If I bought three or four or five cookies.
That's a pancake.
That would pay for my whole machine.
That's crazy.
There you go.
Wait, did you say that buying three cookies at the grocery store?
Because not only does it make a ton of delicious meals,
I can also make a giant cookie and surprise my kids and my whole family.
Now everyone wants a cookie.
Our family absolutely loves quesadillas.
What's with the cookie thing?
It's fast.
It's fun.
The kids have a bowl making it.
And we know we're getting something good when we're eating at home.
That looks pretty good.
We love pizza.
And as a family of five, the whole family can make pizza together.
And we can have dinner on the table.
And I've bought a ton of quesadillas.
Everybody participates.
Everyone wants a cookie.
Our family absolutely loves quesadillas.
And we know we're getting something good when we're eating at home.
We love pizza.
And as a family of five, the whole family can make pizza together.
And we can have dinner on the table in 15 minutes.
With fresh ingredients that I bought for a third of the price of pizza,
Paula pizza.
Well, I love to make it's big enough.
It's got a wide surface.
I could put two large paninis on there.
And it's done in like three minutes.
Everybody lives in the same house.
How big is this house?
Sausage on there.
We can make waffles, pancakes.
Dude, I'm sorry.
Only so many people can use the Hulk Hogan grill at 8 o'clock in the morning.
I promise you guys, you're going to be so happy with Hulk Hogan's ultimate grill.
You're going to use it each and every day.
It's the ultimate cookie maker, the ultimate panini sandwich press,
the ultimate pizza oven, the ultimate grill.
The ultimate cookie maker.
The ultimate quesadilla maker.
The ultimate waffle maker.
And it's the ultimate grill, which truly makes it the ultimate kitchen appliance.
So big or small, open or closed, fresh or frozen,
Hulk Hogan's ultimate grill does it all, brother.
Thank you so much.
We're a champ.
Let's go practice our wrestling now.
Come on, I need some help.
Hulk is going to go wrestle this guy?
He's going to go kick the shit out of this guy.
Hulk Hogan's ultimate grill does it all, brother.
Yeah, like, is he saying that?
We're a champ.
Let's go practice our wrestling now.
Come on, I need some help.
Is he saying that to production?
Like, guys, I'm going to need help over here on the right.
He's talking to production.
Grill does it all, brother.
Thank you so much.
We're a champ.
Let's go practice our wrestling now.
Come on, I need some help.
I don't know, what an enjoyable experience that was.
The ultimate grill.
Hulk's ultimate grill.
All right, what's what I got?
Oh, there's more.
We were back here.
All right, perfect meatloaf.
By the way, I hope everyone understands.
I'm doing this more often.
I'm doing this way more often.
There's so many things to watch.
There's so many products to watch.
I was just testing it today to see if this was fun.
Absolutely.
We're doing this again.
This is, like, amazing.
This is so much fun.
I love watching this stuff.
And I'm so glad that I can share it with you
because I would lie in bed, put some of these on.
I haven't seen any of these ones, but, I mean, maybe I have.
Maybe I haven't.
But I would just sit there and, like, think these things.
I want to just talk about it.
So, yeah, we'll do this again.
Okay, what about the perfect meatloaf plus?
We've seen meatloaf before.
Growing up, my family made the most amazing meatloaf.
But we had a secret.
Look, delicious seasoned beef on the outside.
And, oh, boy, loaded baked potatoes on the inside.
How they do it?
It's the perfect meatloaf plus.
The new non-stick way to bake and serve the perfect meatloaf.
A baked potato on the inside?
Watch.
Add your favorite meat to the pan.
Press to make an opening.
Pop in your favorite stuffing.
And all more of this stuffed shit.
Now seal and bake.
You don't need, you don't stuff a meatloaf.
You just made a yummy cold cut stuffed meatloaf.
Cool.
The main choices inside are endless.
What?
Like asparagus caught on blue.
That was real.
You heard that.
And then loaded pizza, vegetable medley, even ooey gooey.
Did you guys hear that?
Now that's delicioso.
All made simple with our easy press and sealer.
Best of all, my old country elevates your meatloaf.
So all the oils and fats drain away, making it healthier.
Why make crumbly, boring meatloaf?
They use that same image.
Moist, delicious stuffed meatloaf.
Just like my Aunt Nancy makes.
Which like my Aunt Nancy makes.
Moist, delicious.
Nancy's meatloaf is an egg, spinach, cheese, and like bananas?
Are these like maintains?
Stuffed meatloaf, just like my Aunt Nancy makes.
What's in there?
With my superior nonstick surface.
Just lift, slide, and serve.
No messy cleanups.
Imagine beef meatloaf with stuffed manicotti.
Turkey with Thanksgiving Day stuffing.
Or chicken with portobello mushrooms.
All right, I'd eat that one.
I'd eat that one.
You can also do cornbread, pull apart cinnamon bread,
even strawberry shortcake.
I'd eat the turkey one.
Plus it's all dishwasher safe.
Other pans sell for up to $40.
And they don't even have a lifting tray or easy press.
You should try these and do reviews on them.
But order right now.
I can already tell you all the reviews.
Is only $14.95.
I can already tell you that each one of these
is going to be like a mess.
And I'm just going to be like, I don't like this.
OK.
The pasta-fina.
Pasta-fina.
To make pasta on the stove, you boil, stir, and toil.
And watch out.
It's sure to make a mess.
Then you strain.
That first is trashed.
Pasta is not a choice.
Then you strain.
Make a mess.
Why would you dump the whole thing up?
It's balancing.
On the edge of the sink.
And you dump the whole thing into it.
This person is trashed.
Or they're, yeah, wicked high.
And the thing is, what they should show is,
they should show, like, they should cut to the person's,
like, over here.
And just have them be like, with these red eyes.
And have them just go, I don't care.
And then reach into the sink and, like,
put it back into the strainer and put it on a plate.
Right, because, I mean, come on.
Making pasta is not a chore anymore.
Hi, Chef Tony.
We've got some Chef Tonys in a row.
The new way to make great pasta in as little as three minutes.
Simply add pasta, pour in boiling water,
and snap on the strainer lid.
What?
In no time, Pasta Fina cooks your pasta to perfection
right before your eyes.
Pasta Fina's unique vertical design surrounds the pasta
and uses thermal control to maintain the ideal temperature
for perfect pasta.
Does this work?
Just pop the top and drain.
No lumps or clumps.
Spaghetti.
All right, hold on.
Rigatoni.
Ravioli.
Macaroni.
Even tortellini.
All in as little as three minutes without the mess.
And pasta's just the start.
If you like veggies, Pasta Fina makes them fast and fresh.
Does that work?
Cheese and carrots.
Asparagus.
Even mixed vegetable medley.
And look, we cook broccoli the old fashioned way
and the Pasta Fina way.
Look at the water.
There is all your flavor and your nutrients,
but not the Pasta Fina way.
Look at the water.
Oh, yeah.
And look at the broccoli.
What do you mean, look at the water?
Bright, brilliant, and bursting with flavor.
Cook veggies and spaghetti at the same time.
Pasta from Nevada.
Even cook macaroni and sliced hot dogs together.
Add cheese.
Toss for mac and cheese.
That's sure to please.
And for cleanup, just a quick rinse or rack it in the dishwasher.
For a limited time, my Pasta Fina and complete recipe guide
are yours for just $10.
But wait, order in the next five minutes.
But this actually looks kind of useful.
And we'll send a second Pasta Fina and recipe guide for you
or to give us a gift.
Boiling water is annoying, right?
Let's just be, let's be real.
Boiling water is annoying.
It takes like a long time to boil water
unless you get like a kettle and boil it
and then pour, you know what I mean?
It takes a while.
It's a, this is a plastic tube.
I don't know.
It's obviously fake.
Is it though?
You have to boil water for this.
Wait, what?
Wait, it's not, wait a minute, hold on.
You boil the water and then pour it in.
Wait, it's not a machine?
You do pour in boiling water.
Oh, I missed that.
I thought this was like a device that you put the water in
and put this in and in three minutes you got pasta.
Okay, all right.
I thought you like turned it on.
It's interesting, but I don't think that's going to work.
All right, what about the fresh and crisp?
Is it an air freshener for your fridge?
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Why is none of this covered?
You just open your fridge and just throw a head of open
just lettuce and a pineapple and like strawberry.
You don't cover it?
Why is it in the trash?
That's like throwing money away.
You need to put it like you need to cover it
and put it in like the humidifier thing.
18 days.
Just eat the, eat them.
Strawberries were bought at the same time.
Just look at the difference.
Oh, six dollars.
And look at iceberg lettuce after just eight days.
Fresh and crisp looks fresh.
No way that's another 250.
See the difference in these bananas.
The bunch stored with fresh and crisp is still fresh.
Okay, but what is the fresh and crisp?
What is it?
Baking soda is not the enemy.
It's the ethylene gas that's naturally given off
by fruits and veggies as they age in bags or in the fridge.
That gas is what makes your produce go bad.
The secret to fresh and crisp is in its proprietary technology
that uses mineral-based active ingredients
to trap and absorb that natural gas.
Dramatically slowing the aging process.
And fresh and crisp will last three months.
Baking soda in the fridge,
like an open thing of baking soda, they sell them.
That works for like odor and freshness.
And you'll save tons of money.
All of the fresh and fresh products are made in the USA.
Call or click to order right now
and we'll give you two fresh and crisps.
Enough to give you six months of freshness and savings
all for just $9.95.
But wait, just hold on.
Right now, we'll also send you fresh and fridge.
The amazing fridge and freezer odor-eliminating free.
That's baking soda.
Just place the fresh and fridge in any location
in your refrigerator or freezer to remove odors
and prevent odor cross-contamination on fruits and ice.
But how long does it last?
Laboratory tests prove fresh and fridge absorbs odors
97% more effectively than baking soda.
Hold on.
In fact, you'd need an entire fridge full of baking soda
to do the job of just one fresh and fridge.
Oh, fuck out of here.
You get two fresh and crisp produce savers
and the incredible fresh and fridge odor-eliminator.
I don't, I'd like to see the science.
All for just $9.95.
Call or click to order yours right now.
I'd like to see the science on that one.
If it works, cool.
I'd like to see some of the,
I'd like to know some of the science on that.
How about the no spill chill?
Oops, uh-oh, look out.
Let's face it, getting an ice cube tray to your freezer
Shit face.
The only difference is, this is not regular ice.
This is like, this person that with it,
they're just high or they're drunk
and they're just like, yeah, man, I got an idea.
Let's put a fruit punch and like Kahlua in these
and freeze, that'll be fucking awesome
in like a few hours, dude.
Revolutionary ice cube tube.
That's 100% spill proof.
Watch how easy.
Just fill the flexible.
That's not enough ice.
Slide in the ice cube insert and freeze.
Wow, what a breeze.
How many cubes is that?
Now look, just pop and the cubes drop directly into the cup.
It's that easy.
Not enough.
Grab that with a regular tray.
It was bigger.
Go ahead, pop and drop into any size glass.
Quickly prepare ice coffee for work
or create refreshing drinks without ever making a mess.
No spare chills, advanced interlocking technology.
That's really easy to fill up, though.
That's very easy.
Even over this expensive computer.
No, amazing.
The secret.
No spill chills.
Flexible sleeve and expensive computer inside.
So they always.
How expensive is this computer?
Divided insert.
Secure the cubes inside.
So not a single.
Oh, this expensive JPEG of a computer.
I see.
Drop amazing.
The secret.
No spill chills.
Flexible sleeve and divided insert that secure the cubes.
If this was two, if this was a double and it was a little longer,
I'd probably be into it.
I guess maybe you get a bunch.
Flat, vertical, upside down.
Anywhere in your freezer.
They're even fitted to stack and store.
Perfect for home, office.
Yeah, I mean like a small fridge.
We all love homemade soups and sauces,
but who wants to stand in front of the stove for hours stirring?
And if you happen to step away, you can end up burning your food.
For one second.
What?
This is ridiculous.
That's not really stirring.
It's kind of just moving around.
It's battery operated and so sturdy it can stir for up to four hours
and stand heat up to five hundred and seventy two degrees.
Four hours on your back on your food and it won't burn.
Robuster is great for gravy soup for soups and stews and for beans.
It's the best mixed marinara masala.
It even has the straight fold alfredo and turn your cheese sauce.
The secrets, the orbital gyroscopic action that ensures no spot is unstirred or untouched.
From underneath, you can see how the Robuster keeps everything moving.
So I don't even say with the Robuster,
you finally have that third hand in the kitchen so you can get two things done at once.
Cleanups easy and it's dish.
I don't know.
I don't even say it stirs so you don't have to.
I mean, it's just I guess it's like solves some kind of issue.
But I mean, how many pans do you have out?
Like, what do you do?
How much food are you making?
I'm making a lot of different things.
All right, we got the Shogun steamer.
This is the urn that they just repurpose it.
We already see this.
Now you can enjoy all the flavors and healthy benefits of ancient cooking secrets
right from your microwave in just minutes.
It's the same fucking product.
It's the modern version of this timeless classic and it cooks meat,
fish and vegetables, even frozen foods faster and better than a dozen pots and pans.
Is the impossible.
Watch on the left boiling water on the right, the Shogun steamer.
We place fresh veggies in both.
And a few minutes later, the vegetables are soggy.
But the Shogun steamer done perfectly.
Vitamins and color don't have a chance to boil away.
These fish fillets are frozen solid.
One goes in the oven, the other in the steamer.
Minutes later, the oven fish is cold as a pot.
Minutes later.
The steamer fillet is done to perfection.
Minutes later, did you stop it before it was done?
You can't put the same rules on two different cooking appliances.
Hey, look, we put this frozen salmon in the oven for three minutes
and we put this frozen salmon in this in the Shogun streamer for three minutes.
And look at the difference.
You can't apply the same rules to different appliances.
Is that what they're implying?
No, it can't be right.
Are frozen solid.
One goes in the oven, the other in the steamer.
Minutes later, the oven fish is cold as a popsicle.
But the steamer fillet is done to perfection.
Simply add water, then choose the larger small basket depending on your meal.
Then pop it in the microwave and press.
And the Shogun steamer does the rest.
Is it magic?
No, it's science.
You see boiling.
No, it's.
All right, listen to the audio stop.
Listen to the audio splice.
Is it magic?
No, no.
No, it's the steam technology.
Is it magic?
No, listen to this.
The rest.
Is it magic?
No, it's.
No, is it magic?
No, steamer does the rest.
Is it magic?
No, it's science.
You see boiling water is hot.
What was wrong there?
Steam is hotter, so it cooks faster.
Why did they need a dubter?
It washes away vitamins and flavor.
Steaming locks them in.
So your meals taste twice as good in half the time.
And the twist and drain feature lets you save the broth.
And it makes perfect pasta every time.
Enjoy a delicious seafood feast.
It's the same.
We saw it.
We see a lot already with the thing.
Perfectly done rice and potatoes.
With the drain at the bottom.
The Shogun steamer replaces a cabinet full of pots and pans.
And it's just $19.95.
Plus, you get our Shogun 10-Minute Meals Cookbook.
Packed with easy and healthy meals.
And as if that weren't enough...
Yeah, all they did was change the name to the Shogun steamer.
They added like a gong in the commercial.
That's the only difference between the two commercials.
What was the point of that?
Two steamers and two cookbooks.
Just basic processing and handling.
You must agree it's the most time-saving,
flavor-sealing cooking tool you've ever used
or return it for a full refund.
But keep as a free gift our handy cut-and-cut chopper.
These are ridiculous.
These are so...
I love this.
Okay, how about the Miracle Grill Mat?
Do you love to grill but hate the messy cleanup?
All right, we got Mark Gill here.
First of all, it gets one full letter grade.
Do you love to grill but hate the messy cleanup?
Me too!
Hi, Mark Gill here for the Miracle Grill Mat.
It takes any grill...
These green screens somewhere.
...and makes it completely non-stick.
And...
Where is he?
...it eliminates cleanup.
Here's something you could never do at home.
I'm gonna do breakfast on my barbecue.
I'm even gonna add...
Oh, it's like a mat?
...an egg.
Look at that.
And for a special treat, in just a second,
a little bit of shredded cheese.
I've even got my crispy bacon,
my savory hash browns.
If you come to the other side,
I have french toast,
sausage,
wonderful ham,
tangy pineapple,
and toast.
A whole breakfast for the entire family!
Stop!
On my barbecue!
By the way...
I don't know if anybody's household was like this or not,
but like...
I'm sorry, my like mother or father
is not going to make like separate fucking breakfasts
for six different people.
Oh, you got your ham and pineapple for Jerry.
You've got your cheese quesadilla
and eggs over here for Sally.
Oh, and then you got your french toast.
Like, who the fuck is doing that?
My mother's gonna...
My mother's making like scrambled eggs, bacon, and toast.
I'm not being like,
Mom, can I have pineapple and ham instead?
Why?
They always show making like eight breakfasts
for eight different people.
No, you're just gonna be...
You're gonna get what mom or dad makes.
That's not how this works.
They're probably on my barbecue!
Hey, you want non-stick?
Mom, I want a ham steak today with pineapple.
And I still got my grill lines.
Okay.
Now, remember that special treat?
Watch the egg right into the cheese.
I'm gonna grab my toast.
Toast, eggs, and cheese on my miracle grill mat,
and nothing sticks.
Whoa!
Are you kidding me?
Delicious, and I never have to clean my...
Ooey, gooey, delicious,
and I never have to clean my barbecue again.
Grill lines.
Everybody loves thick, juicy, restaurant-quality steak.
Restaurant-quality steak.
Restaurant-quality.
Restaurant-quality shrimp.
Restaurant-quality steak.
A steak is a steak.
Let's just...
We have to clear this up too.
If you go buy like a ribeye somewhere,
it's of the same...
It's a ribeye.
Restaurant-quality steak.
It's just a ribeye.
It's not like a special thing.
Onions and mushrooms right beside my steak.
How's that wrong?
Wait a minute for a second.
Grilled vegetables are amazing,
but trying to do them on an open grate is almost impossible.
Oh no, Mark.
They'll just fall through.
You'll need half your meal.
Have a look at this.
With the miracle grill mat, everything stays in place.
I can grill my vegetables right beside my meat.
I never lose a bite of food.
And here's the best part.
I can see this for like...
I never lose that great barbecue flavor.
Yeah, vegetables and fish and stuff.
That makes sense.
Flare-ups can ruin your meat and your hair.
What?
So with the miracle grill mat,
there's never any flare-ups.
And burnt-on sauces and marinades make for a cleaning nightmare.
But check this out.
With the miracle grill mat, clean up is a snap.
If you've ever tried to grill fish, you know.
It just flakes and falls apart.
But with the miracle grill mat, you get perfect fish every time.
You've seen just some of what the miracle grill mat can do.
Now get your very own miracle grill mat.
There's applications for it.
I mean, you can just use tin foil, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, and then just throw the tin foil away.
You have to like clean this thing.
That's true.
All right.
Fresh toppers.
No matter what containers you buy, you end up with this, this, or this.
Not anymore.
What?
Introducing the fresh toppers, the ingenious new food saver.
Fresh toppers pops right on your food to instantly seal in freshness.
Wait, you put it on top of an orange?
The one on the left was stored in a plastic container.
The one on the right, it's open to the air, isn't it?
Plastic wrap?
That's a storage trap.
Just fresh top them.
Fresh toppers form a protective seal like your food's natural skin.
Top on any fruit or vegetable.
Top on cans and jars.
Top on to seal on air.
Okay, jars.
I can see jars and jars make sense.
Fresh toppers keep odors in.
They're FDA approved.
Yummy.
Dishwashers safe and so easy to store in a shelf or in a drawer.
Cans.
What container can say that?
Now it's easy to top fruits and vegetables with fresh toppers.
I love my fresh toppers.
Why do I feel like this would be kind of hard to get off?
I feel like I'd have to like peel.
I feel like I'd be paying the ass to get off on some stuff.
Why they keep smelling?
Stop sniffing it.
That's weird.
I don't like that.
Money and keep your food fresher longer.
Call and order fresh toppers today for only $10.
How many do you get though?
Because if you only get like four, you get four.
Okay, let's preserve one half tomato and like a lime.
That's not enough.
Colors tomato, red, carrot, orange.
It's going to be double.
It's going to be green.
But wait, there's more.
Can be a call now and we'll include this three piece stainless steel knife set.
Exactly what I told you before.
Precisely what we talked about.
Precisely.
This is a different product.
This is a knife set that this is also now what you have now too.
It's completely different product.
Perfect for cutting any produce.
A $25 value.
Just pay separate processing, but that's not all.
Order now and we'll double your order.
And more knives.
Two tomato, red, two carrot, orange.
We've got to get rid of some inventory.
Two pepper green and two three piece knife sets.
All for only $10.
This offer is not available in stores.
Don't wait.
Okay, I still feel like this kind of odd weird number of stuff.
All right, we're probably going to move away from kitchen appliances.
I got this tons to go through.
Don't worry.
But there's other stuff too.
There's other products that are not just in the kitchen.
Big Boss Sliceroo.
Are you tired of spending all your time slicing and dicing and shredding and chopping?
Tired of those other so-called slicers that can be dangerous?
Well, say goodbye to all of that.
Introducing Sliceroo.
In seconds, you can slice onions, apples, potatoes, and cucumbers.
Shred cabbage, carrots, and beans.
They're fighting each other now.
And curl zucchini, squash, potato.
Turn your meal time into fun time with the Sliceroo.
This is not the vej-ju...
Wait a minute.
This is the vej-ju-roo?
No, it's the vegetti.
I thought this was the vej-ju-roo.
Okay.
Well, we already know that one.
We don't need to see that one again.
The Big Boss Sliceroo.
All right, the Stone Wave.
Hi, Mark Gill here.
There he is.
The Stone Wave.
The new ceramic cooker with the steam-released chimney that makes dishes so delicious
you'll crave cooking in the Wave.
Poached eggs are such a pain to make.
They are, but...
Put an egg into Stone Wave.
No need for butter, fats, or oil.
Just pop it in the microwave for one minute.
Eddly smooth, velvety poached egg.
Stone Wave is non-stick.
Is it po...
That's a poached egg.
The legs just fly right off.
Let's just add your favorite ingredient and cook.
The hollow handle stays cool enough to hold.
Look how fluffy that is.
Eat it right out of the Stone Wave.
No pans and no dishes.
The secret is the unique chimney releasing just the right amount
of steam.
The domed lid recirculates heat.
Cooking food to perfection.
Look, it recirculates heat.
Why does it always look like they don't like it?
Those eyes tell me, like, not very good.
The unique chimney releasing just the right amount of steam.
The domed lid recirculates heat.
Watch out, it's going to blow up.
It's going to get too high.
All right, now that's application.
If you like apple pie, I see it.
Or like a s'more or something.
A little soup too?
Like a little...
Okay, hold on.
How do you do that?
How did you do that?
How did he do that?
Recipe book.
You get the amazing ceramic stone wave and recipe book.
It's going to get cut off.
Mr. T?
Are we going to get another...
and cooking and cleaning up the mess.
Well, I challenged some friends of mine
to come up with a cooking invention
that would make it super easy for me
to whip up a tasty meal
quick enough to hit off a big fierce appetite.
Another like celebrity cooking thing?
What is it?
Whoa!
The flavor wave turbo is not a microwave,
but an amazing invention
that combines three types of cooking
to turbo cook all your favorite foods
up to three times faster with no added fat.
Mr. T is giving it a good effort here, I think.
...right from the freezer
and have it fully cooked for you
three times faster than an ordinary oven.
Plus, it eliminates 75% of the fat.
Imagine mouth-watering turkey in 20 minutes.
Eliminate all the fat?
Is this a food processor?
Now, whether your food is fresh or frozen,
you can bake, broil, roast, toast,
sear, brown, barbecue, reheat, and more.
Faster than ever before.
That's weird looking.
Best of all, when you're all done cooking,
guess what?
The flavor wave actually cleans up for you.
What?
The flavor wave turbo oven is life-changing
because I can throw dinner together
in a matter of minutes
straight from the freezer
right into the flavor wave turbo oven to cook.
I really like the fact
that the flavor wave turbo oven
defrosts frozen foods.
I could just put something...
It's an air fryer.
...from the freezer into the flavor...
Was this an air fryer before air fryers?
I don't use any fats or oils in the flavor wave turbo.
Don't ever.
And that's quite surprising
because you don't need them.
No, who needs, like, fucking flavor?
No, I don't use any marinades.
I don't use any fats, any oils, any butter.
I don't season the meat either.
I just put in a frozen chunk of chicken leg
and the machine just does the whole thing.
And I eat it and it's dry as fuck
and it has no flavor
and no fats and no oils.
And get all that out of here.
I want it to be like a dry ass chicken.
Wait, what's this end here?
This ending.
It just comes out wonderful.
The push and prep.
Oh, more cutting.
It's a pain in the ass.
Oh, you're gonna slice your fucking hand off.
It's just a spawn.
Push and prep, the new miracle cutting tool
that lets you chop, slice, dice, mince in seconds.
This tower of power is actually three cutting blades
in one compact stack designed to double the...
Oh, we're getting duplicates.
Watch, just click in the...
These things do work though.
It's that easy to...
They're just, I mean, there's a lot of them.
Look, the quarter blade to push and prep
and through potatoes...
Is it repost?
I mean, I think it's a different company.
...for zesty zucchini sticks, french fries,
or sweet potato fries.
Use the slicing blade to power through peppers.
I think most of these are early 2000s, mid 2000s.
Push and prep for the fastest veggies yet.
Slice even the toughest pineapple.
Slice and dice peppers, tomatoes and onions
for a spicy salsa.
With sure grip handle,
the stay sharp stainless steel blades even cut...
Yeah, we've seen this already.
The best pot pie maker.
Oh, yup.
Let's go.
Why is he on the phone?
Wait, why did he call in?
Why did Chef Tony call into the infomercial?
It's like, was it radio?
Was he like being interviewed on a radio station?
Why is he calling in?
Do you love delicious mouth-watering hot pot pie?
But he's here.
But store-bought pot pies have lots of potatoes
and fill as you may not want.
And where's that beef?
What beef?
Why, Chef Tony, for best pot pie...
He's calling...
...now you can enjoy...
He's calling from prison.
There's nothing better to make with holiday left
than my best pot pie.
He had to finish the commercial.
He's contractually obligated to finish the commercial.
Do you love delicious mouth-watering hot pot pie?
But store-bought pot pies have lots of potatoes.
Oh, that's not fair.
He seems like a really nice guy.
He really does.
But Chef Tony, just use the crust cover to package the homemade dough
to form the bottom.
Spoon in your favorite...
Why?
But that was so weird.
...veggies...
Why have a call-in segment?
What the fuck?
Now, just heat them up and eat them up.
The best pot pie.
Make best pot pie your way.
Skip the carrots, load up on the peas.
Skip the carrots?
What are you, crazy Tony?
...into delicious new meals
for the whole family.
Make an amazing quiche for Sunday brunch
filled with your favorites.
Ham, cheese...
Who skips the carrots?
...mushrooms...
...and a pot pie?
You're out of your mind.
...so easy.
That's the best part.
...make pot pie chili smothered in milk...
Okay.
...Greek spinach and pet pie
and my favorite pepperoni pizza pot pie.
My kids love making s'mores pies for dessert
or sweet fruit tarts for mom.
They always...
You gotta give them credit, right?
It can't just be a pot pie maker.
It has to be...
It has to make cakes.
It can't just be a thing that makes pot pies.
It has to...
Look, it can be a muffin maker, too.
It can be...
It can make a pizza.
Dude, it can make pizza.
No, it's a pot pie maker, man.
That's fine.
That's okay.
It doesn't have to be like...
Oh, no, no, look.
We can prove that it can make a bunch of other food.
It doesn't have to make a pizza.
It's just...
Best pot pie is oven safe and...
It can make pot pies
and like other pastry type things.
Doesn't have to be a pizza.
Please now get my meal size best pie set
complete with double baking tray,
top and bottom crust cutters,
and recipe guides for only $10.
I hope there's a phone segment again.
Please.
For dipping and processing.
And to make sure everyone in your family
enjoys their own favorite fillings,
you'll get an additional double baking tray
and this great list of specials.
Come on.
Just pay separate processing.
That's a $40 value for one special low price.
And ask about my pop-up tray.
It makes getting your pot pies out a snap.
Call or go online to get your best pot pie right now.
No, it was just a weird segment.
There's nothing better to make with holiday leftovers
than my best watch.
I don't get it.
Get it.
Nothing better to make with holiday leftovers.
This is so interesting.
I love it.
It's so just odd.
Magic steam wave.
I think we've seen plenty of these.
Okay, we'll go down to...
We'll go down to 50.
Microwave ovens are quick when you want to reheat.
But they can make your meal dry.
Especially meat.
And that chicken is like rubber.
And no...
I'm telling you.
It's fun to edit these.
It's time to get the magic steam wave.
The brand new way to use your microwave.
Wait, we gotta analyze this.
Look at what's going on here.
Especially meat.
And...
Look at this lady, right?
There everyone is like...
This lady is like...
That chicken is like...
She's like, oh my god.
She look at how embarrassed she is.
That all this food was put in the microwave.
All of it.
Everything here.
This is like one, two, three, four, five, probably six cutlets.
A whole side dish.
And this is just like a...
Ooh, sorry.
I put everything in the microwave.
Everything.
No one will eat.
Oops.
It's time to get the magic steam wave.
You wouldn't put all of them.
The brand new way to use your microwave.
Magic steam wave uses the power of steam
Another microwave steamer.
These were so popular.
Heating food evenly and locking in moisture.
Your food tastes like it's fresh from the oven.
Look, this day old bread is already hard as a rock.
But 30 seconds in the magic steam wave...
Day old bread?
I've eaten like week or two old bread and it wasn't like that.
Huh?
Simply add a little water to the steam capsule.
Day old bread.
The new patent pending technology quickly creates and circulates steam.
Making your microwave work like an expensive convection oven.
You get moist, delicious gourmet meals in a microwave minute.
Perfect every time.
No sticky plastic wrap.
No wet paper towels.
With magic steam wave, you can steam all your fresh foods fast.
Everything cooks evenly.
The paper towel works just fine.
No spots for uncooked areas.
So call today and get the amazing...
PFOA free.
...for just $10.
But wait.
Order now and get the magic steam wave caddy free.
Here's the thing that it comes in.
It holds all your plates or bowls...
...while allowing steam to circulate and cook your meal evenly.
And the handles are always cool to the touch.
Delicious.
Reheat.
Restore.
Okay, we don't need to say anymore.
The perfect bacon bowl.
This is a classic.
I think everybody's seen this.
Everybody's seen this, right?
This is the perfect bacon bowl.
I've seen it.
You have.
Everybody loves bacon.
The sizzle.
The scent.
The mouth-watering taste.
Didn't think it could get any better?
Watch.
We're turning bacon upside down.
It's a muffin tray.
Introducing bacon bowl.
The easy way to make delicious edible bowls...
It's an upside down muffin tray.
...have bacon for fun, savory, crunchable yum.
Just wrap your favorite cut of bacon around the bacon bowl form and cook.
And put it into the oven.
In just minutes, you'll have tasty, toasty bacon.
The big crunch.
...and hash browns for breakfast.
It's better in a bacon bowl.
BLT for lunch.
Bacon bowl makes a whole new way to munch.
The patented design allows the bacon...
I'd eat that.
Talk all the shit you want.
Everybody talk a bunch of shit.
You gotta talk a bunch of shit.
If you drizzled like mayo, mayo, mayo, mayo.
I'd eat this.
This would...
I would probably enjoy that.
That actually...
As long as the bacon was like cooked and it was actually crispy and good.
It'd be like drizzle, drizzle, drizzle, drizzle, drizzle.
Just a little bit of mayo.
Just a small line of mayo.
And I would eat it.
I wouldn't be excited.
But I would be like, that's good.
...while Grease collects in the channel.
So you can pour it out of your diet.
Go from unsatisfying bacon bit snacks to hot crispy bacon bowl stuff to the max.
Or make healthy egg white turkey bacon bowls.
He's a mayo addict.
I'm not a mayo.
Mayo is good.
Stop.
I'm itching my nose so much.
...bacon bowl cooks bacon to perfection in the oven, microwave, and toaster oven too.
Feel like mac and cheese?
Serve up the...
We're moving on.
All right.
We got the easy meatball.
Easy meatball.
I feel like it's gonna be...
We've already seen one of these.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is the guy that typically does all the voiceovers.
But he's like talking like he's from New York.
Is this the same guy?
Wait, what is this thing?
What?
That's not gonna...
That doesn't happen.
Right?
Will this actually do this?
I feel like it would just not...
It would just move around.
Meatball hot dog?
Oh no, that was a meatball sub.
Okay.
I can't see shit with only six pixels.
Yeah, I couldn't really see that one.
Onion Bloom.
I think we already know what this one's gonna be.
These were so popular because of Outback.
You just don't.
Well, this one's a lot more work than some of the other ones.
Some of the other ones are just...
You crush it with the thing.
I think there are versions of this that are better.
All right, but that's not the hard part.
I feel like this is the easy part.
And deep frying the fucking thing is the annoying hard part.
Like, this is the part that sucks.
Like, the part...
Dumping it in the oil sucks.
And it's annoying.
It takes a lot of work.
Oh, I thought the onion was dishwasher.
I was like, why would you put an onion in the dishwasher, dude?
Okay.
All right.
We don't need to see muffin top magic.
We already know what this is.
It's gonna be another one of those cupcakes.
It's like, look, you can put filling in a cupcake.
You can put filling in a cupcake.
I'll just prove it to you.
What?
Who's doing this?
You throw the whole bottom away.
Have you tried those so-called muffin top fans
only to bake an inedible waste?
Then you're gonna love muffin top magic.
The best...
Shit-faced, yeah.
...to make the best part of any muffin...
I'm interested.
...and other sweet and savory tasty treats.
It's so easy.
Just add a...
There's always an egg sandwich.
...to each cup.
Place the patented muffin top...
Always an egg fucking sandwich.
Egg sandwich, egg sandwich, egg sandwich.
Every one of these makes egg sandwiches.
...muffin tops rise higher.
See the difference?
The result is super moist and flavorful muffin tops every time.
This fucking phone number is fake.
This number is not real.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Maybe, oh, it might have been because the number didn't exist anymore.
They...
Maybe for like re-uploading it to like YouTube or something
because it probably doesn't exist anymore.
They just made it a fake number.
That would make sense.
...while the muffin top rises to a glorious crunchy golden brown.
And muffin tops are only the beginning.
Make perfect poached eggs.
Cheddar garlic biscuits for dinner.
Healthy after-school pizza snacks.
And these incredible cupcake tops will make you a winner.
Even delicious stuffed chocolate crescent rolls
or sliders that will warm your soul.
You need to use all these?
That's a whole other ordeal.
Maybe.
And we're gonna get two.
...and get one free.
Five, five, five.
Five, five, five, five, five.
...to lift and serve your...
Ooh, you get a spatula too.
...and we're still not done.
The first 500 callers get the better buddy too.
It dispenses the...
Also, how does that work?
What's the idea behind that?
If you call within the next 30 minutes, then you'll get this.
Does that mean that like...
Okay, so if the first 500 callers...
What if your caller number 502, 503, 501, 504?
What happens?
Can they say that?
Because like the first 500 callers,
at the start of the airing of this commercial, right?
Or like, oh, if you call in the next 30 minutes,
the commercial is constantly airing somewhere, right?
So if you have syndicated commercial
that will play in every time zone,
30 to 40 minutes away from each other,
it'll always be 30 minutes, right?
Always.
How does that specific...
How does that work specifically?
It's just a lie.
It builds FOMO.
I know it builds FOMO,
but if your caller number...
Okay, let's say that if you were...
Okay, let's say I got 500 people that all were like,
I want to buy this product.
They're like, okay, everyone call and buy the product.
And then the 500 first person calls
within the same like hour or two, right?
And like the 500 first person's like, I want to buy it.
Do they...
If I can prove that this is caller number 501,
what would happen?
Everybody gets it.
Everybody gets it back.
Yeah, I know.
But like, what if you proved it?
They don't care.
They're not counting.
You're just lying though.
How many people aren't actually gonna call?
You say that, but if you turn on like QVC or HSN
or like home shopping networks, right?
Like all those networks that existed.
They ran...
They would sell out during the presentation.
They would sell out.
They'd be like, okay, we only have the red ones left.
People do this.
People call.
People do.
Unless it's manufactured.
But people would go on...
I remember they're like, oh, we've got this vacuum on QVC.
And it'd be like in three colors.
And the person would be like, oh, I'm getting word.
We don't have any more blue vacuums left.
And they'd have like a little sold out thing on it.
Why would they say you can't buy it?
Old people buy that.
But why would they want to limit the amount of product they could sell?
All right, how's the mix and bake?
Do you love to bake a delicious homemade cake?
Mix the batter.
Let me guess.
It's going to be silicone and it's going to be...
There it is.
Mix and bake.
So let's you mix and bake a cake.
What the...
Whoa!
Actually, that was cool.
So there's no messy...
Whoa, dude.
Mix and bake is a full-size deep dish bowl.
But can it make an egg sandwich?
Put it down.
Place it in the oven and bake your cake.
The Dory baking...
I don't know if I want this unless it can make fucking poached eggs.
...from the silicone and the cake.
No sticking.
The secret is...
That's cool.
...jewel chamber design that lets you mix and bake in one pan.
This is a cool thing, I think.
...for perfect cake every time.
There's never enough room for baking pans.
But mix and bake...
Do some organization.
...for easy storage full of dishes.
But mix and bake is the perfect way...
Just take it all out and you can put it...
You could reorganize that in a minute.
...to make this cake clean up.
Takes the cake.
Just mix, pop, and bake in one pan.
I like that, though.
That's pretty cool.
No mess, no stress.
Plus it's BPA-free and dishwasher-free.
BPA-free.
Grandkids love to bake a cake and enjoy the magic of mix and bake.
Grandma, just mix and bake a cake that company will love.
That cabinet is actually my house.
Pop, pop, pop of birthday delight, that first bite.
Now you can mix, pop, and bake...
These companies know a very, very important constant truth across all of us.
And that constant truth is always this.
You have in your place right now, in your home or your apartment,
you have probably three or four randomly fucking sized random-ass oven pans.
That you don't know why you still have.
You've had them for potentially fucking years.
They're like...
They look like shit.
They're kind of like discolored and like kind of weird looking.
And you have like four of them and they're just randomly sized
and you just won't get rid of them.
Ever.
And you just use them.
You just use them always.
So they know that everybody has that.
So they just tap into that by going,
Look, you don't...
I know you have that cabinet full of those randomly like discolored random-sized pans.
So just get this and you'll be fine.
And then people like me or like you will do that.
Because like, yeah, fuck man.
I guess I do have like a baking tray that I've had since like 2003.
And it's...
You don't even know why you still have it.
Why won't you just replace it?
Replace it.
Why?
I won't do it.
I should.
But I'm not going to.
I don't know why.
All right, what about the brew stick?
We all need that morning cup of Joe.
But brewing a whole pot is a waste.
It's like pouring cash in the trash.
Introducing brew stick.
The amazing new way to make delicious single serve coffee in seconds.
Watch.
Just scoop the brew stick into your favorite brand of coffee.
Lock it closed and stir into a mug of hot water.
Just stir it longer if you want it stronger.
The secret is our exclusive micro mesh that infuses coffee into hot water for rich...
This is not...
This is not going to make coffee.
...the perfect cup of coffee.
Stir mouth-watering French vanilla coffee at your desk.
Drink delicious hazelnut when you travel.
While camping, enjoy piping hot amaretto coffee.
Single serve disposable pods cost 70 cents a cup.
Brew stick holds the...
Hold on, I'm biting my lip.
...but without the expense or the waste.
Brew stick works with tea...
Doesn't coffee need to pressurize through beans?
Lock it closed, stir, and enjoy.
You can even make iced tea or iced coffee.
Here are some first-time reactions to our blind taste test against instant coffee.
This is definitely a much crisper, fresher taste.
This one's very good.
This you can tell is like instant.
Well, what they didn't tell him is we used toilet water for the left one.
Very rich and full-bodied.
Brew stick is dishwasher safe.
So you can enjoy delicious coffee over and over again.
Single serve pods are expensive.
Store-bought coffee at $2 a day adds up to $700...
That wouldn't brew coffee though, would it?
...fast, fresh, delicious single serve coffee with brew stick in red.
It would be kind of flavored water, wouldn't it?
Call now and double your offer.
Get a second brew stick in black.
Just pay separate processes.
I mean, maybe if you left it in there for a long time.
Simply latte absolutely free.
Whipped milk for a light, airy topping.
Perfect for cappuccinos.
You get it all.
You wouldn't have to be in there for a long time.
Or a simply latte for just $10.
Click now.
I mean, I get the idea,
but I feel like it would take a lot longer than just simply going like this for one second.
All right, let's, let's...
Oh my god, time flies when you're having fun.
I've been doing this for three hours.
All right.
Wait, I got a lot of shit up here.
Let's go over here.
This is a different playlist.
This is like automotive products.
Oh my god, this is so bright.
Now I understand what you guys are talking about.
So what is this one?
Pretty good music.
What?
Holy shit.
What the fuck are you doing?
It's a second mirror?
Wait a minute.
Whoa.
Okay.
But how, what if it spalls off?
That looks like it's just kind of clipped on.
Revealing what's in your car's blind spots.
It couldn't be easier.
Clear zone mirror installs in seconds.
Adjust and you're ready to go.
Look again.
Clear zone instantly reveals the tractor trailer in your blood.
They've made it look like you're putting a webcam on top of your monitor.
If that's secure, then that, that's kind of helpful, isn't it?
You say clear zone makes parking in the tightest spots a breeze.
Back in with only inches to spare and let clear zone steer you clear.
No.
No, honey.
You can't pull.
That's too small of a space.
I got this.
What are you talking about?
I got the clear zone.
No, it's not big enough.
It's not, you know, you're going to hit something.
Please don't, just easy, easy.
You're going.
No, no, no, no, no.
Turn, turn the wheel.
Turn the wheel.
And then they fucking crash into the garden dome.
Clear zone comes with a 10-year money-back guarantee.
If it breaks, get your money back.
Look at how close this is.
Parking in the tightest spots a breeze.
Back in with only inches to spare and let clear zone steer you clear.
No fucking.
I am not parking here.
If this is how much room I have to spare, how am I getting out of the car?
How are you getting out of the car?
Built to last, clear zone comes with a 10-year money-back guarantee.
If it breaks, get your money back.
As a former police officer with over 25 years on the force,
I've seen a lot of serious collisions.
Clear zone gives you better visibility and can help keep you and your family safe.
Call now and get the innovative new clear zone now for just $10.
But wait, there's more.
Now you can double the offer.
Get them on both, right?
You're covered on both sides of your vehicle.
Just pay a separate fee.
We're still not done.
Act now and get clear zone headlight restore free.
Reuse them up to six times.
Restore those oxidized headlights in a flash.
Absolutely free.
Get clear zone mirror and clear zone headlight restore.
Okay, clear zone.
All right.
If it's secure, if it's secure on there and it's really like on there, secure.
I don't want to watch screwdriver ones because who cares?
It's kind of boring.
The stream machine.
What's the stream machine?
We need to know.
Offer some annoying commercials.
Introducing stream machine, the clever little gadget that connects to your phone or music
player and streams music right through your radio.
What?
Being able to enjoy all your favorite songs broadcast with crystal clarity with stream
machine.
You can because it makes you the DJ of your very own FM station.
Here's how it works.
Tune your radio to any unused FM station.
Adjust the numbers on the display to match and you're done.
That radio station now plays only what you want.
What?
And if you're using it in the car and you get a call, no problem.
Hey, honey.
Hey, are you close?
So just left the grocery store.
Stream machine is also a hands-free mobile device.
No wires and no Bluetooth required.
Stream machine works with any device that has an earphone jack, including tablets and
laptops, which means you can use it to stream music from apps or internet radio.
What's going on here?
Any sound system with a radio tuner, no matter how.
No, no way.
Other wireless solutions are complicated to set up.
Can cost hundreds of dollars, but stream machine is so simple to use.
Just plug, tune, and play.
And it can be yours today for just $14.99 through this incredible TV offer.
So why suffer listening to other radio stations?
We're just about to play your favorite song, but first some more annoying commercials.
Oh, come on.
When you can create your own commercial-free radio station.
This lady's pissed.
This lady's angry.
Plus find out about special pricing.
This lady's very mad.
Just attach it to your air vent, insert your phone, and you can select songs or answer
calls without taking your attention off the road.
And there's more.
Order today and you can get a second stream machine.
Just pay a separate fee.
Are these even real cars?
And there's more.
Order today.
Attention off the road.
I mean, he's in it.
He's green screened in, but I mean.
More.
Order today and you can get a second stream machine.
Just pay a separate fee.
That's two stream machines and special pricing on our smart grid for just $14.99.
Apparently this technology works.
Back in the day, back in the mid-2000s, this probably would have been a very good idea.
Right?
The car of L.A.
The car cane.
What is the car cane?
Have you ever struggled to get out of the car?
Does back or knee pain make it hard?
Do you push with your arm when you try to stand?
Or ask someone to give you a hand?
Then let us help you out with the incredible new car cane.
Now you can get in and out of your car with ease.
This new portable handle locks instantly into the door latches of any car.
Simply open your door and snap it on.
Car cane locks into place.
Actually, it's kind of.
In fact, car canes.
Well, don't get down from there.
Get down from there.
If you're having trouble getting out of the car, don't go climb up there.
What the fuck?
If you are recovering from an injury or suffer from back pain, knee pain, or hip pain,
you need the car cane.
And when it's slippery outside, car cane gives you a handy grip so you won't slip.
It's perfect for those tall SUVs or low compact cars, too.
So stop struggling and get up with ease.
It was difficult to get out on my own.
Now I carry my car cane and help myself.
I mean, that's a pretty decent solution, I think.
And look at this.
Car cane has a built-in flash.
Yo, come on.
Look at that.
Right LEDs can last 100,000 hours.
What?
The car cane is so well built, it will last a lifetime.
100,000 hours?
Call and get your car cane today for just $19.95 plus processing and handling.
On this exclusive TV offer.
But wait.
I think that's helpful.
That's useful.
Swivel seat free.
Just pay separate processing and handling.
Oh, wow.
Actually, I want this.
This unique center cutout to reduce pressure and provide a soft seat for the driver or
passenger.
And when it's time to get out, it pivots and turns for an easy.
That's okay.
All right.
This is helpful.
That's pretty helpful.
The car cane and the swivel seat.
So help yourself.
That's helpful.
Get your car cane today.
The extra view mirror.
Another one of these.
Whoa, look out.
Wait, what was in your rear view?
You still can't see everything.
Now you can practically say.
But wait a minute.
You check and check and you still.
What was going on with this lady's mirror?
I know what the fucking problem is, lady.
Your mirror is turned all the way in.
So you're only seeing your reflection driving the car.
You need to put the mirror out and fan it out, lady.
What are you doing?
Where did he come from?
You check and check and you still can't see everything.
Now you can practically say goodbye to blind spots with extra view.
This is a wide screen that gives you a true 180 degree view.
Look, ordinary really give you a field of view this wide.
But extra view expands your visibility to a full one.
How much does it take up though?
I feel like it'd be a lot of space.
Anti-glare chrome coated glass that lets you see up to three lanes wide.
So nothing will hide with extra view.
You're seeing when this get in the way.
Look at the difference of your actual vision.
Children, I am constantly adjusting my old mirror trying to get a view
of the entire car with extra view.
I don't have to touch anything.
I can see the entire vehicle from window to window, top to bottom.
With extra view, you can see the entire three lanes.
All three lanes?
Now turning around before, after.
The difference is crystal clear.
And extra view makes night driving easier.
How does it do that?
Watch high beams and those new LED headlights
can really hurt your eyes at night.
But extra view reduces glare by up to 50%.
Making night driving safer and more comfortable.
Okay.
Ordinary mirrors make you twist your neck to check and recheck.
But extra view lets you see it all.
What just snaps on?
It's so much more comfortable.
Extra view quickly attaches to a regular mirror.
Snapping on or off in seconds.
Now when you're merging, changing lanes and backing up.
Extra view makes it safer and easier to do.
Is this somebody said is this legal for being on for road use?
I mean, I think so.
Day and night.
Similar items sell in catalogs for up to $6.
Yeah, I don't know.
Why would it be illegal for just $14.95?
As a bonus, we'll send you a second extra view free.
For what?
For another car?
You get this incredible double offer.
Log on to extra view mirror.
I actually have one of these.
It works as advertised.
Yeah, all right.
Hey, look, I'm not saying any of these products don't work.
I'm just saying it's interesting, kind of strange oddities, right?
HD Vision Ultra.
Oh yeah, this is going to be a fucking doozy.
Just imagine being able to see your entire world in high definition.
The clarity is just unbelievable.
That's what I'm saying.
It's just like gunner optic.
High definition.
It's impeccable.
It's gorgeous.
It's like, wow, HD Vision.
It's crystal clear.
They're amazing.
HD quality.
They're talking about HD Vision Ultras, the brand new sunglasses that give you
our trademark high definition color.
And you're probably wondering why our commercial is not in HD.
It's actually in 480p.
Reduce glare and increase color and like no other glasses you've ever.
These are amazing.
And these do the job.
It's incredible.
Other glasses just make things darker.
Oh, the world looks like shit.
HD vision lenses enhance colors and they have great styling.
I got thumbs up from the wife.
I'll take them.
I can see how blue the ocean is, the sky, every cloud.
I mean, really, it's unbelievable.
They're really very cool.
These sunglasses are just phenomenal.
Excuse me, cut that one.
These are HD glasses.
As a special offer.
They're not sunglasses.
Giving away HD Ultras for just $10.
Wait, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
We're giving away.
HD Ultras for just $10.
So you're selling them for $10.
You're giving them away for $10.
That's right, $10.
Other sunglasses sell for 100, 200, even 300.
I don't think that's what that means.
And they don't have high definition lenses.
That's an awesome price.
Are you kidding me?
I've got a $129 pair of sunglasses that are not this good.
And that's the truth.
Plus, as a special bonus,
we're also going to include our amazing HD Vision
night vision glasses free.
Just pay separate processing and handling.
They really are like counter optics.
And they're free when you get HD Vision Ultras for just $10.
HD Ultras.
They really are high definition.
Don't wait.
Call now.
Night vision.
I got HD night vision now.
All right.
We got, seeing Mark Gill down here.
Paint chip repair.
Bumper shield.
Tack wrap.
Fiber fix.
All right.
I'm thinking Popsident.
No more cars.
All right.
One or two more cars.
I want to see Popsident.
Who are you paying?
I remember these.
Popsident makes embarrassing.
Yeah.
I remember these.
You like pull the car out.
It's the same dead removal system used by body shops.
Except they charge big bucks.
Dense cars by hail.
Pop it.
Dings from car doors.
Yeah.
I think these things actually work.
Damage from shopping carts.
All right.
One more car.
Easy view HD sun shades.
Speed out.
What is speed now?
It's a screwdriver.
HD Vision night vision.
Easy glass.
The hook and hang.
Why is this person the shelf under?
That looks like mine.
That didn't really change very much.
Do flex seal?
We've all seen it.
But why this lady had a blindfold on?
And everything fits in place.
How is this for cars?
You can store your weights.
I know you guys want to hear the...
You want to hear the...
Okay.
Oh, that's a lot of damage.
I know.
I know I do too.
Okay.
I do too.
I know you want to hear it.
I know you want to see it.
Sure.
Fine.
They're really awesome.
Wait.
Clear?
It's clear now.
Okay.
Now one at a time this time.
Would you want to do it with sandals on?
I feel like you don't get that on your feet.
What happened?
Didn't this guy used to like take access to doors and like
throw like fucking barrels in the wall?
Didn't this guy used to like have a chainsaw?
That's flex tape.
Oh.
Actual.
Actual users.
Oh, this is not the one you guys wanted.
I'm sorry about that.
All right.
No more cars.
We'll do...
Oh my goodness.
That was loud.
How about the potty patch or the kitty shack?
I think we got to do kitty shack.
This is the cat house.
But it's just a bed.
Shack to convert from a comfy tube bed to a full-size cat.
I mean, that's kind of interesting.
I'm sorry.
But then like my dog or whatever,
they would sleep next to this,
but this wouldn't even use it.
Now, it'd be really funny if she was like,
I love the kitty shack too.
And she's like her like head sticking out of it.
She's like sleeping.
That's cool.
Add the kitty shack.
Is she wearing it on her head?
All right.
Okay, that's...
What?
All right, that's not...
That's affordable.
$14 for like two kitty shacks and the cats like it.
No, it's not the kitty shack.
That was cool.
All right.
The potty patch.
Is this just like a little patch of like grass?
That guy's not happy.
All right.
This guy has been to this house like a dozen times a month.
This carpet cleaner is getting sick and tired of coming to this house.
He's not peeing.
This is not real pee.
This is edited in piss.
Why would your dog be peeing that much?
Okay.
Where does it go?
The potty patch is the perfect solution.
The potty patch is ideal for training puppies.
Oh, there's pee everywhere.
Oh, what the fuck?
When dogs are left alone all day, they're going to have an accident or two.
I would rush home for work and would still find a mess.
There's no surprises with the potty patch.
And no more waiting...
Wait, that guy has a steamer.
The potty patch is ideal for apartment living and even works outdoors on your patio.
Potty patch is the best training aid ever.
I've seen it work the very first use.
So before you spend...
Who is that?
...a fortune on dog walk...
...a patch is the best training aid...
...a fortune on your patio...
...which is the best training aid ever.
I've seen it work...
Award-winning dog trainer.
So before you spend a fortune on dog walkers or dog mats that sell for $150 or more.
Order your potty patch today for just $39.99.
That dog is cute, though.
We'll upgrade your order for free.
You'll receive our plush deluxe potty patch made of antimicrobial odor resistant turf.
$60 value body patch is also available in a big dog. The body patch is also available for humans
Just like some guy like get out of bed and just like fucking pissing into this
body patch million soul the guy's like a bathrobe on like put his hand up and just like pissing into this a
Man-sized piss. All right. What about the uh, the cat lick stick?
There's fur on the couch the rock. Oh, we
We've we've already seen your hair. So hair balls end up here and what's the dog Betty?
doggy VD
To keep kidding perfectly groomed and perfectly happy cat lick stick is the only brush that what the fuck?
What's the dog in VD?
Let's look like a tea party friend too tired to play our aches and pains
Ruining his day if your pet is suffering from the signs of aging now, there's dog Jeopardy
Okay
All right, it's like a vitamin
Promote canine health and vitality in an ongoing clinical study. I thought it was a tea party
All right. Look at that. I look at the thumbnail though. I thought this was like a tea set
I thought it was like the dog of edie like tea set. I don't know. Whatever. What the hell is the amazing tank?
It's like a fish tank
All right. What about the sweat belt the blood type workout?
the back bridge
The the active bright. Oh, there's like a toothbrush the vibrating razor
What is this?
Now there's an incredible new handheld power tool that oh, it's a power tool
Rasps and grinds like no other tool you've ever used. I used to get so pissed when things come on
When a power tool infomercial came on because you never knew what you're gonna get
At like one two, three four o'clock in the morning. It'd be like give me the turbo cooker
Let me see the ron papeel showtime rotisserie oven. Come on
I want to see it and it was like the the following is a paid advertisement for the vibra razor saw it'd be like
God damn it power tool ones always sucked. That was just boring. It's just like, ah, I couldn't anything else
Or if it was like the following is a paid advertisement for the blah blah blah supplement from supplemental medical field
I just like no get this. I want give me the fucking turbo cooker. Give me like the new wave oven
They were just boring this uh, uh, the drain wig
If you've ever had to clean out your clog shower drain, then you know how gross and disgusting that holy shit
Well, never again. Oh solution is finally here introducing drain wig with drain wig
You'll never do what the fuck rain again. Why was it?
Why was it like it and every few months you just pull it out and dispose of it
You don't have to touch the oh stop showing this to me. It just takes seconds to pull out
My god
This is fucked up water and hair spin down the drain as it spins
The hair gets caught in the drain wig stainless steel chain and wouldn't this get clog up your drain
It can easily be removed and disposed of there's no more need for harmful chemicals that are dangerous and can ruin your pipes
No more need to dredge out. Oh get oh get up. Stop lying down
Easy solution to a very nasty problem. You can also get a drain wig for your tub
This drain wig allows the stopper to seal. I mean this is this thing probably works
Because they make the products like this exist
Okay, I have five daughters and they all have beautiful why what is it why are they doing the fan thing?
So we invented the drain wig out of necessity and now over a hundred thousand people the ac vent
Why is there so much hair in your air conditioning vent?
What was that? That was like an air conditioning vent
Are being protected I promise you it really works one visit from the plumber can cost over 80
Dollars drain wig can save you money and all the hassle to order just call or log on to the website
Practical it's practical. It's got practically
I don't want to say it out loud, but i'm gonna somebody said it probably somebody said it probably smells like puke
To a full three months, no questions asked money back guaranteed
It's fucking disgusting. Don't wait that nasty hair. That's fucking disgusting larger every day
Call or log on to drain wig.com right now
Like imagine if he's just like he's like
That would have really sold it for me
He lifts it up. He's like so close. He just goes
And then they cut
Okay, i'm not clicking on something called my bidet hamper hoops
Yeah, this is nothing new this is nothing new
Oh he shoots he
Is a kid so he doesn't understand like aim and knock the lamp over and shattered glass all over the corner of the room
I think I had one of these when I was younger
Never swish read right here sound effect added really
Yeah, that thing
That thing's gonna get broken. Do you know why that's gonna get broken?
because
If you're gonna have a friend over or you're gonna have
Like somebody's gonna be over your house or something and it's like oh my shirt
I gotta roll my shirt up and like throw it away and you're gonna do like a fake basketball game
In your room and you're gonna try to like dunk on your friend or try to get it behind him
He's gonna swat it out of your hand and shit
Like that that's how that happens. You're gonna break two or three things in the room
Yeah, this is like you're gonna have like two or three friends will be over
And you'll they'll actually bring a basketball into the fucking house
And actually shoot like a basketball in this and everyone's gonna laugh and it's like, oh look
And then you break the vase you you scuff up the furniture
And then mom and dad are not happy about it
Oh dad got it almost fucking ruined it dad almost didn't get it dad
God, don't you just want to see him in his other hand with the fucking like the the smoothie thing like the executive size smoothie
He's just like I got it son
I can take care of this
Oh behind the back behind the back too
Yeah, that's no don't give that because then they're gonna use that they're not gonna even use the clothes park
You turned this into a toy and not a way to have the kid help out around the house
You just made it a toy. They're not going to attach this now
They're gonna just play basketball in the bedroom. What is going on over here those weights?
He does a dartboard
Darts that's how do you play darts here? Where do you stand?
Uh, and you're gonna miss a but I
My kids don't have a dartboard in his room
Okay
Oh the snackies and the 2015 product of the year is snackies there it is one snack and drink up and it just got better
What'd you change?
It's everything you love about snackies, but now lightweight and recyclable snackies duo. Okay already ready and perfect for your crowd
Ooh
Solid up top pass them out at a birthday party the big game sleepovers
barbecues wherever they're snacking snackies duo holds your 12 ounce drink and
Bounces of your favorite snack in one container. All right, that's cool juggling cups in place when the party's over snackies duo can be reused
Or discarded responsibly personalize snackies duo so no one sneaks your snacks. You can call or go online to get your snackies duos today
You get 10 multicolored snackies duos in a pack. That's 10 cups you get 10 of these and 10 straws for 9.99
Tear open a pack and the party's on
Yeah, that was quick that was to the point and as it sounds like a great product
That was just to the point. We know exactly what we're getting with the uh with snackies duo
Didn't have like a 30 minute infomercial didn't have like a four minute commercial that was to the point and it works
What about the song?
Holy shit. Wow
What the fuck turn that up tear open a pack and the party's on
That's a home run that's an absolute home run that they probably have like 50 million sold what an absolute home run
All right. Well, uh the hydro moose
Spray on grass seeds. Oh, that's boring. But hold on do the bidet. Uh
He's like feeding chickens high traffic areas and shade what a night you see water and what's the only thing growing are the weeds
It's no wonder the seed gets washed away blown away by wind and eaten by birds
Not anymore introducing the revolutionary hydro moose liquid lawn liquid lawn technology the grass grows where you spray it
If you can water your wall, that looks cool
Simply attach to any garden hose and turn the dial to see okay the guesswork
Hydro moose shows you exactly where you're planting the green moose formula contains an eco-friendly solution that attaches the seed to the soil
And a conditioner to loosen hard dirt allowing it to absorb water resulting in a terrific looking lawn
We sprayed hydro moose on this vertical burlap wall and look the seed locks in place even upside down
Does it grow on there and the grass grows like crazy?
Even on a vertical wall
It grows that works heat or cold conditions. It's perfect for dog spots high traffic areas
Large areas and shade and no more guesswork. This thing's kind of cool includes a mixture of high quality seed
How much do you get though? That's the thing is that enough to do like a whole backyard or a what that how much do you get?
That dog was fucking crazy, by the way
It was like a six foot vertical leap. Holy shit
I just want to spray this right? I'd like
This is the thing that like dad would ask me if I wanted to help
Like with the lawn and I'd be like can I spray the can I be the hot can I spray the seeds?
Like I spray the seeds and I'd be like, of course you can then I'd be like, yes
It'd be fun to like spread seeds
And then I would go back inside
scour power
Smart shelf amazing grip the shower. Wow
uh
What shower now shower? Wow?
shower now
Shower wow what the fuck shower. Wow, the amazing new shower head that transforms water into a cascade of color
This would be fucking annoying, which is why kids never want to get in
This would be annoying
Does it happen? Does it turn on every time you turn a faucet on all the colors of the rainbow from orange and purple to blue
And then green
Your kids will be begging to get in and get what you don't turn that on now
And replace it with our high quality
And you're done just like that when you turn on the faucet no
Cascade of color no hardware and no batteries no batteries
What are you talking about? Wow is powered by water pressure for years of continuous use and the high quality chrome finish goes
So you have listen to me
You have to unscrew this off to make it stop great with any decor
Everyone loves shower wow from formerly fussy toddlers to teenagers who were bored no more. It's awesome
I wouldn't want this. That'd be fucking annoying
That would be fucking irritating
That would probably especially like in the morning
Like I don't want to like turn it on and look at like a bright like blue fucking light like a like
Green light in my eyes. It'd be like
No, that would be horrible
Air bead cushion the wonder watch
The window vac. All right, what's the window vac?
It's a gamer shower your windows it's a big problem because dirty windows cloud
Limit sunlight dirty windows are depressing. Oh, yeah dirty windows make your whole house look and feel filthy
But you would not have the curtains open
The dripping the big pile of paper towels the hard work of scrubbing and scrubbing and then there are still streaks and smudges
Ruining your windows appearance. Shh. You may have a dirty little secret. You don't clean your windows as often as you should
I hate okay. So what's the product?
Wouldn't it be great if there was actually a vacuum to clean your windows for you introducing window vac
The fast and easy way to clean your windows leaving no streaks or spots
Just spray window vac and walk away your hands never need to get dirty
Okay, secret is the window vac dual state squeegee cleaning system
First the professional grade pure rubber pad creates a cleaning suction seal right against the glass as it moves
Dirt and debris are removed right down to the glass level
A little dirt solution and dirt are then instantly suctioned away by the powerful on-board water vacuum
Look, we took a window and baked it in the sun with grease dirt and watch how the dirt is vacuumed off
House slipper that would be kind of fun
Just vacuum it up and empty it out in a single and look all the fat and grease
Just dump it down the drain except don't do that
Easy take a look at this window. It's filthy, right?
But no match for window vac just one wife and you're worry free. All right, whatever done with this one
Uh, what about the uh
the plumber's hero
Oh not this thing
I feel like this would blow up my sink. I would be scared
Offensive and if there's water on the earth, you can't wait anymore. Just press
Holy shit, dude, that's so much pressure
I would feel like I would do that and it would the sink would blow up my face
That's scary
A unique formula that when combined uses that water as force to jet propel it through virtually any club
It's safe. Is that safe with those harmful chemicals that even make you wait upwards
It even works right through a garbage disposal. Check this clog out veggie shavings rice grease and coffee grounds
Stop putting that
Huh hair ties toothpaste shaving gel and hair
Oh even this old lady
This is crazy
Ah shit, we were just about to go out
Uh, no, wait, hold on honey. You're telling me that like the fucking mondo massive dump I just took before we leave the house
Oh great now we can't go to the opera
Oh, no, we can't thank god
Do they have to make this sound so disgusting too the sound effects are like disgusting point and clean
I do I could do this all day, but I'm I I could do this all day
You guys want to do this like once a week. Let's I let's actually do this like once a week
Let's do this until i'm sick of it. This is funny. I love this
Okay, we're gonna do i'm gonna do the ultra bulb and then i'm gonna pee and we're gonna
Your light bulb burned out again
They don't even make those old light bulbs anymore and those odd shaped led bulbs shine a harsh light in just one
LEDs are amazing now aren't they?
Do you buy you need the new ultra bulb led from bell and howl it's the smarter light
Ultra bulb uses new led technology. So it's an led
Okay, so it's an led old bulbs did look compact fluorescent bulbs are dim
Incandescent bulbs always die and most led bulbs shine light in just one direction
But the new ultra bulb shines a warm bright light evenly and how many okay your original bulb?
Just look at the difference. That's so bright though. I don't want that bright new 360 degree reflector wrapped with 28 super bright
technology
In every direction that would be too bright can last over 10 years without burning out same leds do to reach light bulbs
It's an led one ultra bulb can replace 25 ordinary bulbs, but not leds because it's an led
leds last 10 years
Ultra bulb is always cool to the touch
It uses eighty five percent less energy than your old light bulb
Just one ultra bulb can save you a hundred dollars over the life of the bulb and ultra bulb turns on instantly
No waiting to warm up like those other bulbs. So why is this like a
Like the freezer room from like a ninety seven eleven. What are you talking about?
What are they talking about ultra bulb turns on instantly? No waiting to warm up like those other bulbs
So you don't spend there's a five nights at freddy's like what are you talking about?
At the home improvement store now you can get two bell and howl ultra bulbs for just
1999 but only two no, it's gonna be four now and you can double it's four. Of course it is. Yeah, that's four ultra bulb
This is probably 2004. That's true. That's true
Won't burn out for 10 years or simply return them and call now to find out about multi-packs at all right
One more these are so addicting. I can't help it. What's the living bubble?
Living bubble anyone can hang a picture to decorate a kid's wall
It takes almost no imagination at all. But when you have an open wall, what else can you do?
How about trying something completely new?
It's the living bubble the clear acrylic semi-spare globe that decorates any wall and provides a living space for your child to have their
Own vet. It's so simple
It's as easy as hanging a picture on a book and gives your child's room a more decorative
Look the living bubble makes any room come alive make it a fishbowl and watch their sharks swim and dive
Even a bowl where plants stay alive
It's flat in plants. It's on the wall and it's round in the front
So it holds anything at all living bubble will inspire their creativity and makes any child's room
Oh fucking no turn that shit off. What the fuck?
Has a ring of led lights what the fuck and makes the living
bubble into a special
Dude, whoa
Don't tap. Yeah, what the fuck? I don't want one of these
I wouldn't even want one of these for like the plants. I don't know. I think it's weird
My data hot spot. I don't know about that one
The soothing shawl the magic mirror. This is uh, this doesn't talk
Why start your mornings off in the fog? Hi, Anthony Sullivan here for the magic mirror
This guy's in a lot of these too
That makes steam disappear like magic you wipe wipe and wipe and can't see a thing and it makes you late steam
Can't stick to magic. Whoa. Hold on
You're wearing your watch in the shower steam can't stick to magic mirror. You see clearly every time and you look your best all day
Watch this even with this blast of super hot steam. You can see this mirror. All right
Okay
Stays crystal clear. It works each and every time. So how does it work? The secret to the magic mirror's amazing performance is its patented
Nanotechnology, okay, nanotechnology
Providing a clear view every time you use it. So it's a second pane of glass
Nanotechnology there's nanomachines in here
Just line it up. Oh, it's just a piece of and turn any mirror into a magic. It's just a it's just tape
Dorm rooms or apartments. I thought it was an actual physical mirror. It's it's just like a piece of tape
You won't have to wipe it. What that's all right. It's easy to clean. I will stay they made it look like it was a big physical
Mirror for life guarantee the magic if that comes off easy
All right, I don't got a problem with that
If it works, it works over and over it looks like an easy to use right now and you'll get the amazing fog-free magic
Easy plus shipping and processing but that's not
Magic mirror
All right. I gotta piss. I gotta pee. We're gonna do this again. This is a lot of fun
There's hundreds of these and we have more 30 minute ones to do too
There's a lot of old classics that I really want to watch but for now i'm gonna go pee
We're gonna come back and we're gonna move to
my first ever
Sponsored video game stream. Are you ready for this? Are you ready? Never done this before i'm excited
I hope the game's good. Looks like it's pretty fun. Uh, you'll see this again real simple
This is probably like an I I kind of want to keep going you you're all flush
Yeah, I mean maybe I have to pee
All right, I'll be right back. We're gonna move on to the serpent rogue. I'll see you guys in a minute or two
I didn't want to press that button, but I did
Oh, there we go. Okay. I'll be right back. I'll put music on this time actually