Hi everybody, it's me, Arto. This is my second movie, Arto's Big Adventure 2. This is where I invite all my friends over and we eat cookies.
Let me introduce you to all my friends. This is Moose and Mari. They're a couple. They're married.
Hi. Hello.
This is Boo Boo.
Hello. Oh jeez, I'm not that good on camera. Please don't put the camera on me right now.
And this is me, Arto. Hi.
These are so good. I love these.
Oh jeez, these are the best cookies I've ever eaten in my entire life.
Mmm, yeah, they're actually kind of gross.
Mmm, that was good. Now that we ate our delicious cookies, it's time to play outside in the snow. It's snowing.
Let's go outside. What's that, a leaf?
Give me the leaf. I don't know what this is, but I'm going to keep it.
Hold on now. I've got big bones here. I'm coming, I'm coming.
Let's go and see what that is. Everybody, let's go. Come on, come on, come on.
Hey.
What is it?
Have you guys tried the snow yet? Oh, the snow is just so full of flavor.
Where's the rabbit?
Give me that.
No, there's a rabbit over here. Stop it.
I'll bite your face. I'll bite your face off.
Let's go back inside.
Okay, let's go inside and eat some more cookies.
Oh no, the cookies are all gone. Someone stole the cookies.
Who would do such a thing?
We need to find out who did it. Which one of these dogs took the cookies?
Let's see, are the cookies in here? Are they in the kitchen? Where are they? Who took them?
What about outside? Did somebody bring the cookies outside? Who did this?
Okay, I don't want to alarm anybody here, but I'm sorry I may have taken a shit in your house.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen. My name is Frank O'Leary.
I am the director and producer of The Great Cookie Mystery, Otto's Big Adventure 2.
I'm joined here for the director commentary. Thank you for joining us with Otto the dog.
Hi.
Otto, thank you for joining us.
I like cookies. I eat the cookies.
Yes, of course.
This is going to be the commentary of the piece and why certain things were done, a couple of funny stories and that sort of thing.
So we'll start by saying that when I got the script from Burger Boy, it was an absolute masterpiece.
I wanted to change a few different things, but the studio wasn't really on the same page with the creative team, which I was leading.
I was in this movie.
Yeah.
I was in this movie. Do you remember how I was in this movie?
OK, so what we were trying to achieve from the yin and the yang perspective of this movie was to show the real struggle of the everyday man and make a metaphor towards the beginning of a new life.
And that's one of the most important things as a visionary creator that I like.
I was in the movie. That's me.
Yes, you were in the movie and you did a fantastic job.
Yes, thank you.
As the lead man behind the mask, which is exactly what I was trying to do with this piece.
And that's the end of the film.
So thank you, everybody, for watching my magnum opus, Otto's Big Adventure 2, The Great Cookie Mystery.