Hey, I probably should change the title to uh instead of five plus hours if two free three plus
two plus maybe five is a lot that's a lot of picking up fruits and vegetables and raking leaves
but good afternoon how are you welcome to the stream today you didn't know if you just like
clicked on the stream and you weren't you didn't see the tweet you didn't you just here i am uh
we're gonna be playing animal crossing new almost said leaf uh new horizons it's a it's a different
it's new animal crossing new horizons it's out it's out now on the nintendo switch uh i played new
leaf on the ds i thought it was fun and i kind of i mean we can just chill for a little bit and then
start our world right after last night's insanity i wanted to slow it down a little bit if for some
reason this game it bores the shit out of me in three or four hours then uh we'd go back to
fuckface city was a wink wink dink city is still available for us to continue if after a few hours
um then kind of we'll see i might play this all night i might play it for four hours i might play
it for seven hours i don't i can't i have no idea i cannot give you the answer there boiler alert the
game is boring every sometimes that's what you want sometimes i just want to rake leaves it's like
fish and stuff it it's a chores game it fits under the category for me of number one genre
you guys all know this by now i'm ready to fucking harvest carrots why am i always playing chores
games because i don't know i like them why do you eat fucking gross ass raisin oat bread no no because
you like it i don't like it i think like raisin bread is disgusting but that is you you can you
can like raisin bread but i can i can put my hands up and go no thank you i do not want
fucking i don't know i don't want hard sweet boogers in my bread no thank you we all are
allowed to have things and like things that we like anyways let's move on to
animal crossing the word on uh new horizons here it comes here it comes friends online
oh you have one friend online oh that's good i didn't even know that you could have friends
in on nintendo switch don't they not allow that wait there's more than one tom nook good afternoon
we're so excited to have you here have you here let us be first to congratulate you on your wise
decision to sign up for this adventure welcome to the check encounter for your deserted island
getaway package there's so much to look forward to but first let me introduce myself i'm tom nook
and i'm tom nook too we'll be flying to the island with you to help you get settled
think of us as your partners we're in it for the long haul so let's get started shall we oh please
oh come on all right i forgot we got some fucking animal crossing fans in here i should be careful
what i say okay all right all right now then we'll need to look up your application can we have your
name and birthday you're not getting fucking wait you're gonna sell this shit nintendo you can't
change this this can only be seen this can be seen by others uh you just ruined the game for me it
just came out like a day ago you'll be all right this is the first 15 seconds all right how about
uh this doesn't even matter naming the character doesn't even fucking matter make sure it's super
funny you can change it later it says you can't change this in red letters you can't change it
how about uh uh sweet uh sweet um yummy oh
this isn't complicated just use your name oh yeah right that's what that's my name
that makes a funny noise hold on oh right it's just my name are you okay with jeremy the world of
animal crossing is welcoming to all so don't include personal info or offensive words uh
okay what's your birthday you cannot change your birthday later people you cannot change your
birthday later people you don't know might see this oh so does it also include the almost three
or four thousand people that are staring at the screen right now oh well i was born on the fucking
fourth of july jeremy jeremy let's see fourth of july oh yes here you are our next step will be
to take a picture of you wait there's a camera on this thing don't worry take as much time as you
get yourself look wait what do you mean this is a camera is there a camera on here is there a camera
does the switch have a camera on it oh i don't know why i was like why please choose your style
oh yeah you just you make a meet you make you make a uh a me mode right okay that's kind of
accurate is that it for hairstyles what kind of eyes do i have oh okay those are kind of my eyes
hmm hmm those are kind no those are my those are kind of my eyes and i have a nice i have a nice
cool slate gray blue eye like that no it's like it's simple between here and here it's like that
it's like this one it's blue yeah but i want it to be perfect hey you want to make your animal
crossing character the way you want i'm gonna make my animal crossing character the way that i want
and this is my come my face is this constantly yeah that's pretty accurate uh what is these zits
oh can i put the zits okay now all right that's good good does everything look okay it does i'm
not that pale great you're all set all set i'll just go ahead and add that picture to your records
and now let's start talking about your new home so exciting exciting for sure you see we're quite
proud of the work we've done to help you feel comfortable in your new life oh yes in fact if
you want you can you can even experience the seasons the same way you're used to them what
i mean is we have islands in both the northern and southern hemisphere the village is going to
throw a birthday party for you on july 4th that's all right it's the fourth of july we're going to
have a party anyways we recommend choosing an island that has the same seasonal pattern as your
current home current home why the fuck am i doing that so tell me jeremy where do you live now i
live in north america ah excellent that information really helps us focus on just the right island for
you naturally we'd recommend that you relocate to an island in the northern hemisphere there are
a few more decisions to make but does that sound okay to you so far so far oh okay if i do that
again i want i want everyone to leave if i do that again everyone leave watch another stream if i do
that again okay here we go there are a few inches should i go to southern hemisphere uh no i want
to stay here we have a number of lovely uninhabited islands in the northern hemisphere to choose from
now then all of our islands are approximately the same size and they're all quite natural
but don't worry about whether you'll have enough space or comfort you can't go wrong
just follow your instincts and choose an island with a layout that looks appealing that's how i
do it oh look at how cute this is i'll show you some maps now and you can choose the best one
for your new home um okay which one do i want a penis one um these okay these all could be
penises guys so i don't know what you're talking about everything on this screen right now could be
a dick so and some so you could interpret it somehow so i don't know what the fuck you're
talking about i'm going i'm going to go with the one that you that could there's no way
could possibly ever be interpreted as that which is this one i mean there is a small there is a
little there's like a mini okay that's okay i get it why am i even doing this all right i'm going
to do oh what have i done i'm gonna do this one wonderful choice i can't wait to show it off to
you what do you mean ruined ah but before we depart i have just one final question
if you could only bring one thing with you to a deserted island what would it be sleeping bag
a lamp some food something to i don't know why i thought it was i didn't read the last word there
something to kill i was like what sleeping bag lamps food something to kill coming to kill
okay i bring food a bunch of it oh they didn't like that answer oh i'm sorry that was just a
hypothetical question uh nook inc will fully cover all of your basic needs yes your attention please
this is a service announcement the chartered flight for nook inc's deserted island getaway
package is ready for boarding any customers waiting to board should make their way to the
gate at this time ah perfect timing let's all board the plane together wait they come with me
hello everyone thank you for taking this chartered flight as part of nook inc's
deserted island getaway package please sit back relax and enjoy a complimentary video presentation
about deserted island life cutscene opening cutscene oh look it that's our beach oh wait no
that's somebody else's beach oh oh i don't want to be here ah bugs everywhere huge bugs this place
sucks i want to go home i don't want to be here why wait why are we doing like the end of the movie
breakdown of where all the characters ended up we haven't even started all right i can't wait to
pick up my first shell oh i can't wait i can't wait to have a bag full of useless shit that people
desperately try to tell me please get rid of the fucking five claims you have in your backpack
it's a waste of time so what's my i don't wait does everybody gets different fruit right what
did i get i got peaches i got peaches all right uh listen i was gonna go a little louder is peaches
good everybody gets different fruit right we're here and huge now i know you must be incredibly
excited to explore your new island home but i have one small request would you please join
us for a short orientation session yes our fearless leader himself will be giving a presentation so i
hate for you to miss it fearless leader we're heading there right now if you'd like to move
follow us all right if you hear them if you hear the term our fearless leader uh i might i might
start swimming oh this is cool dude it's like look it's like mario galaxy the world like moves
with you the world spins give me one of these fucking give me these how do you pick up something
oh how do you pick up feed what i can't pick these up are they gonna are they gonna rot
oh hi all right is that everyone let's see the way these are the two suckers that took the trip
is phoebe here and how about flip and there's jeremy of course yeah great we're all here i'll
turn it over to you mr nook our three adventurers are ready to get started all right so we're like
on the deserted island this is uh these two characters are not main characters it's just
okay these two these two are the first to die on the deserted island right i'm the main character
of this story so what happens to these two yes yes very good let's see how i mean this is
brand new introductions we don't know these people that this is the in the movie these two
this guy gets like his head like dropped like a rock on him or something right they're my friends
wait did i did they come with me these people come with me these are my friends they came with like
wait they got on the plane with me oh well we didn't all get like smash brothers invitations
to be here oh okay let's see how shall i begin yes of course welcome everyone welcome to your new
island they're my friends they're my parents oh no what okay these are my parents what okay let's
just play welcome to your new island my name is tom nook and i'm the founder and president of
nook inc yes yes today is the first day of your new life on this pristine lovely island so
congratulations and this is a package deal as such nook ink staff will always be here to support you
and ensure your comfort and safety but first things first i'd like each of you to choose a
spot of your own it's the first step of putting down some real roots i'd like you to dream big
i do have certain connections in construction and real estate and how about i'm getting ahead
of myself let's just get started with a simple tent shall we at least collect your tent from
timmy or tommy and then choose a spot to place it saw here you go jeremy your very own tent
and a funny hammer once you find the perfect spot press x to access your inventory then select
your tent don't worry you'll get a chance to see what it looks like before making your final
decision and you want a little breathing room so take your time finding a space that works for you
oh i suppose it probably should set you up with a map too once you've put your tent please find
your way back here use your new map if you need to well off you go hope you find a great spot
okay stick where do i want my oh shit all right what do i uh oh i got all right i'm in
direct competition with these motherfuckers all right no uh i want my house right here
this is my house i want it right here right here wait don't do by like the river this is
a competition guys this is this is like this survivor we're gonna do like challenges and
shit people gonna get eliminated maybe right here i kind of like it right on the crest
right here right where the waterfall is that's perfect is that too is that too basic that's very
basic right how many people okay everyone is streaming this game literally literally every
fucking human on twitch is streaming animal crossing like right now is this the spot that
everybody picked i don't want my house to be the same spot no nobody picked this no this this
spot is based okay i don't i don't really know what that what that means in this scenario here
i'm doing it right here too close to the water oh what is it what about this big rock
does that matter too close to the water should i put my tent here is it all maps are random you
idiot uh okay check the box of check the box of i i i played maybe like two hours of new leaf
and that's the only time an animal crossing i've ever had center it i'm not gonna center it just
to make you angry no that's gonna fuck me up um i need to rethink this here we go let me imagine
it oh oh it's so beautiful look at that look at that photo in the background we'll have to do a
little landscaping but we can make this work don't build over the rock please why this is part is
beautiful what's wrong this is like a fucking picture perfect place it's the way do it don't
do it don't do it the rock respawns rock rock let them go on garbage i set up my tent
that's a big first step do you sleep on the rock all right i did it i got the best fucking place
oh you're gonna dream of this real estate look at that imagine imagine having that in your backyard
and what's the cost of competition doing let me see oh are you gonna put your shit in like the
weeds next to trees and no water that's not even gonna be prime real estate you know i guess
that's not gonna appreciate in value over the next decade mine will fucking idiot what about you
where's the monkey now whatever ah jeremy you must have found a suitable spot for your tent
talk to them the first one back so i suppose the others must still be searching for the right
location you know since you've already done some scouting the others may appreciate your assistance
oh you want my help sure you're wait i got it don't tell me you're jeremy right see told you i
had it i'm phoebe i gotta tell you i'm excited to do this whole island thing sparky you already
found a good spot huh i was trying to just feel for the best spot but i was having trouble because
every spot feels like the best one i couldn't just sit here thinking it over forever so i grabbed a
stick and i threw it here's where it landed so now this is my spot okay i know there's only so far
i can throw that stick but i'm liking this that's pretty i like this person wait i can find a spot
for you why don't i just like put both their tents right next to each other and like the weeds down
all the way down but then i have the best spot don't do that don't do that please
wait this game is about positivity oh yeah this game is about never-endingly paying back a bank
for the house that apparently i couldn't afford that's a positive game i'll i'll find you a spot
whoa for real you're gonna pick out the perfect spot for me you do that for someone you just
met you know you're all right jeremy in that case here you go it's your show now sparky
this is where i turn around and just javelin throw the flag as far as i can over the horizon
into like the water and i make like a very audible like
so it goes flying i'm gonna wait at the plaza in the meantime okay
all right let's wait i could have had a beach house i could have had a beach house can i build
on the i could have had a beach house fuck i want to be i can i replace my okay can i take you can
have my house i want this one i could have had a beach house oh oh fire's remorse no no
it's too late oh look at how good fuck okay i want you to have a beach house because i want
to be able to visit your beach house yes cool oh that's so cool all right the other person
has a he's gonna have a beach house too yes wait the tide's gonna come in
oh shit the tide comes in it just wipes out that's all right is that possible
that's not possible right no this is fucking this is a kid's game all right where's the where's the
monkey how do they want their houses in the worst no i'm giving you want beach house nice to meet
you you already set up your tent hey i'm still trying to find the prep spot i'll be doing some
serious cardio first kind of have lots of fresh air i think this bottle do trick but i don't know
what do you think jeremy i'll find you a better spot how about on the beach
you'll find me a sweet spot to put this tent oh you just bet and you're already doing some heavy
lifting on our friendship jeremy okay then can't wait to see the epic spot you picked for me
excuse me what did you say the epic spot if you need me i'll be over at the plaza visualizing how
awesome island life is gonna be all right you are fine you get i want to be they both have a beach
house wait should i put this guy up should i put this guy underneath the airport like that's not a
good place i don't want to be too far away i don't want to walk that far no here's my fucking play
guys i'm gonna have to talk to these two all the time so why not just put the their tents right
next to each other i'm gonna be coming over here and like talking to you and then talking to you
and then i can move on with my day i don't want to walk across the entire map to talk to somebody
okay you guys are both gonna have beach property this is the laziest thing ever
or is it the most efficient thing ever look see can i make everybody live down here
beach property welcome back everyone hope you all i just found the right spot to set up your new
homes of course you can sleep on it for a while really get a feel for how it suits you and with
that taken care of we can move on to more serious business like throwing an island warming party
we'll have it right here in the plaza with a roaring campfire any marshmallows involved like
this is where you lean in you lean in and like move your hand a little bit like twitch twitch
twitch switch up to your mouth like leaning in like talking very quietly but loudly and you
lean forward and you say are there marshmallows involved you know your finger flat pointing up
you know i'm saying and everyone goes oh we just need a few supplies yeah good oh i feed off of it
oh i feed off of that negative energy and chat ah you made me ten times fucking stronger
timmy phoebe tommy and flip can set up things in here in the plaza
meanwhile jeremy and i will work on gathering firewood that this guy's a free oh fuck i gotta
okay i gotta and i gotta stop being like a fucking weirdo because like this is animal crossing this
is a game that came out within the last week the first time i played a new game in probably a year
this is the first game time i played a game that came out after 2006 and probably like a year and
a half um so they're probably just going to be coming looking for animal crossing gameplay and
like i'm fucked up so i'm going to like tone it down a little bit from here on out
all right everyone let's get to it literally yesterday city skylines came out in like 2007
when did it come out 2010 would you come see me for a moment well i could walk up there what
are you like a judge oh jeremy i just wanted to go over what we'll need for the campfire
i think roughly 10 tree branches to do the trick and find them scattered about the island
when you find one lying in the ground press y to pick it up we will i'll investigate the peach
like items growing in the trees i suspect they're real peaches how did you get to the top oh any
tree branches you find on the ground or shake out of the trees will work just fine come on it
yep i just want to make sure i have these first quest free branch got it one two three four five
rock give it to me take the trees wow six seven eight nine ten done i get it should i click the
peaches and stuff or no i got them welcome back i trust you had some success foraging for tree
branches very well allow me to lighten your load yes that should be plenty for our campfire you
made quick work of that i'm quite glad that i'll be sharing this desolate island with such a hard
worker oh ho i think if you're surviving on a desolate island our next task is to run up
something to snack on while you were collecting branches i was evaluating the fruit that seems
to be abundant here they look like peaches they smell like peaches and they even taste like peaches
in fact they are 100 without a doubt genuine peaches so will you collect six of them for me
if you see a tree growing peaches you can press a to shake it and then pick up the fruit
i need peaches for us in no time we're gonna sit at a campfire and eat peaches
this is such a great saturday morning children's cartoon i can't wait that is the perfect quest
for wait what oh i just wait is six seven eight nine bug because what i've been saying
why people saying 34 34 that's how old i am that's cute that's fine yeah i can be 30
i could be 34 and enjoy a game about eating marshmallows around a campfire what's wrong with
that well i knew you were right for the job thank you once again i'll go ahead and take those
peaches off your hands and get started on the preparations ew he's 34 hey relax time for the
campfire now is that everything yes i believe it is let's get started with the festivities
is there like a dance button this is a huge fire what the fuck this is like burning man why is
this so huge the last allow me to properly welcome you to the new island i have participated in many
ventures and endeavors over the years but this may be the most exciting helping develop a thriving
new community entirely from scratch will truly test my business acumen okay now please if you
would pass this chalice around and drink from the blood and it's like you have to pass it around a
fucking blood chalice and perhaps my skills as an outdoorsman now we may not have the kind of
numbers that i originally envisioned that just means we'll have to rise to the challenge and
i have no doubt that with hard work and perseverance we'll shape this deserted island into
i suppose we can't call this a deserted island anymore what would should we call it
i just rang the back of his head and well that was weird i sense a great opportunity
as the first residence this island we should be the ones to name it
and in the spirit of democracy we should put it to evoke majority rules i told you this is my
competition you guys didn't say so present your ideas just a name for the island uh about um
um it's like a it's an island like basking i'm not gonna name it wink dink island
how about um sea salty salt salted salted crest crested salt cause salted crest island
i like that salted crest island salted crest what salted salted ct no salted
crest you know i'm getting real sick and fucking tired of video games doing this shit
if you have a character limit do not under any circumstances have extra hangman spaces after
the fucking limit is there it this does every game does this shit um crested i want i like the
crested part crested crested crested crust crested salt can i do crested salt crested salt
crested salt crested salt it's crested salt salt crest done salt crest island
oh it's perfect salt crest island has to be all one word why i know it doesn't are you okay with
salt crest the world of animal crossing is welcoming to all so don't include personal info
okay don't include personal info are are like kids putting in their home address here
that's like god that kid it's gotta be bad right are you okay with salt crest yes what's wrong with
salt crest it's nice it's got a nice ring to it it's an ugly name salt crest make it one word
why it's salt crest it has no flavor it doesn't know it doesn't matter look at
all right is everyone ready let's try saying our ideas at the same time
ready go rocks a lot isle del biceps salt actually like the one on the right actually i like isle
de biceps can i vote for that guy clap for the one you think is the best jeremy seems to have
the enthusiasm and the naming sensibilities let's start there so jeremy suggested salt crest
yeah wow that's an overwhelmingly positive response wait how come the how come the the
little monkey guy got more spaces than me you just go with salt crest now this island will be known
as salt crest well jeremy since you've proven yourself by naming salt crest i'd like to rely
on you for other critical decisions we'll need to make on the island yes i hereby name you the
resident representative of salt crest wait uh yes uh jeremy your hands in the air uh just why is
your hand up uh i just um where's the salt water around us right there's not like fresh water
otherwise we're gonna have to go with the fucking bicep one i was surrounded by salt water right
where are we oh it's so easy it's so easy howdy a word or two you can count on me
i'll be the new spokesperson he acts like it was intentional
i'm a fucking mystery we've settled on a name for our island and we've settled on our resident
representative it's been a big day but it's gotten rather late let's have a toast everyone have a
beverage at hand fresh juice made from peaches our new resident representative harvested on
this very island and without further ado a toast to salt crest and the happiness of its residents
cheers my poop cocktail what the fuck all right that was fun uh now that's all i can do in animal
crossing till i wake up tomorrow morning cool that was fun i don't know yet you could play an
instrument i feel like i'm on vacation but we actually get to live here re-rack we all just
met but chilling by the fire like this makes me feel like we've been best buds for ages sparky
i like to sit down what am i doing oh there we go ah that was fun different music
oh i can't put things here all right so all right ah jerry we're having a good time
and this is all that much if you like taking a short nap in your tent by all means go ahead
keep the fire going well i'm not tired yet
enjoyed the moment
all right that spam is fucking stupid i'm not even gonna give it the
fucking not even gonna read it out loud all right what about these boxes i just start picking stuff
up i mean okay isn't there like something you can only do at night in animal crossing
fucking fucking funny and i'm the guy with the minus twos i'm the one piling up the minus twos
oh yeah i'm just gonna i'm just gonna go to bed when do i get my shovel do i have any mail oh no new
mail fuck what does the inside of my house look like i should probably chat with tom nook before
i turn in why do i need tom nook's permission to go to sleep what can he just tell me to do that
oh yeah wait you have a flag in your hand salt crest salt crest what a great name just rolls
off the tongue thank you for offering such a wonderful idea to the group ah jeremy having
a good time i know so yeah so take a short nap in your tent go ahead we'll keep fire burning i'm
gonna go to take a nap you'll probably want this bleep it's your very own camping pot you'll want
to set it up in your tent before you lie down there are a few packages waiting for you in your
tent as well just a few items that might be useful okay for a second hell to crawl into bed
you got another big day tomorrow so rest up that's all from me sweet dream cool all right let's go
wait you got electricity in there where you going what's in there excuse me we're setting
up a resident services facility in there but it's not ready for you just yet please give
us a little more time we got fucking lights in there man do i have a lamp let's see hiding i don't
oh a radio it's a fucking silent hill turn it off i don't want to hear this turn it off
that was scary what's this oh i have a lamp all right i want the lamp in the corner okay i want
this in the other corner actually this could be right over here do i need to use the cot
or can i like lie flat on my back staring at the ceiling put it down see that's good and i put i
mean i'm not sure about the design here but look it's comfortable all right let's go to bed rest
my head for a little while yes i'm getting sleepy oh there he is there's uh there's what's
his name queen qua his name's queen qua okay okay okay slider right so it looks like you decided
to make your own way in the world get out there explore new frontiers all the way right daddy oh
you don't need to live by anyone's rules but your own the world was made for exploring you know
you know living free being out there is a great feeling queen qua slider yeah i don't know
yeah if you take it from a cat who's been on the road being by your lonesome can grind on the
soul you gotta make friends along the way rambling this crazy world is squaresville
without some pals yeah man friends are where it's at speaking of rambling i'm doing a bit of that
my bad maybe it's about time for you to wake up to your new life
listen up that rap i just gave you about friends pretty key you'll dig this island life a whole lot
more if you share it with some friends if that's you're saying i don't have any friends an island
paradise with your best pal sounds pretty groovy to me cool when you wake up you'll be in sync
with real time dig that island life and catch you later we're in real time now jeremy are you in there
oh i hope i haven't woken you abruptly uh but i do wish to discuss something with you yes
i'll be here with you ready save electricity ah there you are hope you had a pleasant nap
oh well i suppose it was a bit more than a nap wasn't it it's fucking bright out it's a brand
new day uh i needed that oh yes it's quite normal to be worn out from such a long trip in a major
life event speaking of which i have a few more things that i might you might find useful as you
adjust to life in our little paradise first you need one of these oh wait they added iphones
you knew it was coming eventually you knew it was coming eventually it's your own nook phone i had
these made especially for island residents i want to make sure it's working right so could you try
turning it on for me yeah welcome tracking good good looks like you're getting you good reception
as well feel free to put it away hey jeremy have you ever used a smartphone before um i i don't i've
i've never done i don't know what that is sunny is that so how wonderful of you i dare say do you
seem especially well suited for life on this rustic island nevertheless i believe you'll find this
nook phone quite handy so do take the time to learn how to use it i have one more thing for you
the deed of the house is your itemized bill this includes everything airfare accommodations
labor tax and of course your nook phone i mean your grand total to the modest sum of 49 800
dollars okay yes well then wait they don't have any bells i can't believe i didn't think of this
oh of course well no need to worry i was prepared for exactly this type of tricky situation
for the getaway package you can pay your fees with miles instead of the standard bells
i call this extremely helpful service the nook mileage program what the fuck are you talking
about quite extraordinary if i do say so myself for the nook mileage program you can earn miles by
simply living your life here on saltcrest i dare say the more you enjoy your island life the more
nook miles you can earn and you can use them to pay back your move-in fees and much more
the bottom line is you need 49 800 bells to pay your move-in fees but with this new service
would you believe it it only comes to 5 000 miles just go ahead and register you so you can pay in
miles yes yes but there are more details available with your nook phone just open the nook miles app
and you see that you've earned some miles just for traveling to the island and joining the program
holy shit now if you'll excuse me i must get back to a few other matters but let me
heartily congratulate you once again on your arrival so happy to have you as a resident of
saltcrest and a client of nook incorporated fucking miles my new life is underway i can do
whatever i want woohoo let's go from now on island time will match the flow of time in the
real world do not touch the power button when you see the auto save indicator in the top right
screen you can also save and quit your game by pressing the minus button 4 45 pm march 21st
saturday the phone camera take pictures using various filters and effects what pictures will
be saved to the album on the home menu and other users who use the same system will be able to see
okay wait how do i take a better picture than this oh wait yeah that's my house that sucked
do it again why are these so bad why are these so out of focus it's an emulator glitch no
this is what you do when you buy a new camera you're just like i love this thing you take
like a thousand stupid fucking pictures okay i'm done is that my low on battery is the miles
you're enrolled in the nook mileage program earn nook miles for completing island activities
and trade those miles for perks and goods at the nook stop in the resident services center
make the most out of island life earn nook miles you got the bug island together saltcrest miles
get miles who traveled a long way just to move on our little island and you enrolled in the plan
the plan so you earned your first miles there are lots of ways to earn miles by just enjoying
island life oh let me get them you got 500 miles uh learning how to fish is an essential skill for
living on a remote island nook inc encourages all island residents who are aiming to become
yes one of the goals of nook inc is a resident togetherness our gregarious greetings initiative
aims to reward you with nook miles just for chatting with residents try to talk to all your
neighbors every day they earn miles just for catching creepy crawlies every buck you catch
is one that won't be surprising someone in their sock drawer planting flowers makes our island
beautiful cool you'll get nook miles based on the amount of fruit you've sold remember if you
sell our island specialty fruits on other islands you might be able to get better prices and go
ahead and be selfish and sell okay this is like a thousand of these wait you took your first island
oh did i have any more oh edit credit your passport has some information you can edit nook inc will
give nook miles to folks who customize their profiles take it slow think about it make your
own oh okay custom designs with this app you can create custom designs to wear on clothing or
display around the island when you save custom designs to the app you can share them with other
residents there's a chance that your custom designs will be seen by other players during
network play but when you visit it whatever please don't create anything that infringes on
others rights don't use private information or offensive words or images design display change
design what um wait why is this the thing in the middle wait it's if you can make it face paint
hold on a second what it can be why can it be face paint okay well that's interesting no you know
i look like i'm about to go i look like i'm about to go to like a 49ers game where's my points
there we go the san francisco clowns can you guys could do you have any idea just how fucking
popular and how insane it would be everybody would eat it up it would be the most popular
fucking team you have so many fans if they if there was like if they were like the cincinnati
clowns and they all they have uniforms which is clown fucking colored and they had a clown hair
and shit i would be the biggest fucking fan ever what why you guys spam this link all right all
right i got it i got it and what the fuck is that what the hell is this why is there a giant
weird like satan qr code scan it wait i can scan how do i scan that with the phone app hold on
map you have to upgrade the app first all right how did you get that check the map for your
current location you can also press x to change the settings and choose whether to display the
activities oh look and on your irl phone oh real so wait i feel like i have to download like the
nintendo app and like log in and like sync it and shit your passport information is shown here
this information may be seen by other players and visiting another island for example okay
you can change your photo title or comment at any time customize whatever what did you lie for
that's fine wait take photo rescue service use the service for an emergency situation on the
island when your path is blocked and you're stuck and be sent to a place such as your home
or resident services nook miles are generally required to use the service okay
all rescue services no fuck are there more of these how many more of these exist
oh some fireman dude should i do the face paint of that face all right how long is it gonna i don't
even know what my i guys i can be honest i don't even i don't even know what my nintendo account
is it would manually do what like hold on i want to go in here who's got that fireman qr code
ah jeremy welcome welcome you can see it's quite cozy in here it's funny how cozy doesn't always
mean comfortable hmm you know if you need advice on how to spend your time on the island or anything
else if you need some advice about basic island materials you should talk to timmy
it's essential for you thriving in the paradise if you want to earn some bells he has a rather
generous policy of purchasing just about anything advisable from a business perspective but quite
generous yes oh one more important thing i'm offering a free diy workshop that can help
you really build out your island i think it would be quite useful did you hope you take me up on it
hmm all right yeah i'll get it i got peaches for you welcome welcome you don't waste any time do you
we're still setting up our starters we intend to small for small selected goods
space is limited right now but we'll try to have some fresh stock each and every day
okay sure you're busy but feel free to take a look at some of the items we're thinking of selling
i'll take a look inflatable sofa oh fishing rod flimsy net watering can slingshot uh medicine
sapling peach okay cool how do i sell you stuff anything catch your eye we're not just sellers
we're also buyers because we want to support efforts to beautify the island we'll even pay
you a little bit in return for weeds or trash you bring in okay i got stuff i want to sell
of course you do what exactly you're offering i'm offering peaches
some peaches sure how about if i offer you a thousand bells uh yeah somebody linked the
fireman QR code nice uh i gotta tell you something about the fruit when you eat food like fruit you'll
find yourself energized with more power than you might have possibly imagined has anyone shared
that with you what i mean is you can break open rocks or maybe even dig up a whole tree if you
had the right tool now it's fine for you to sell me your fruit but you should try eating it once
in a while all right well i have some other stuff for you i have like twigs and rocks and shit right
here um you want here take this i don't want this anymore a sailor style shirt how about if i
262 bells yeah take it please come again i'm gonna help you i want to sell i can do more than
one at a time i'm an idiot why i'm an idiot what now he's stuck with the shirt so what
i that's that that's oh sorry i sold the tutorial shirt no i don't want to sell it what's up i
what's for sale all right i'm gonna buy the what should i buy fishing rod flimsy net i want the
net to catch the bugs i'll take it okay i also get the fishing rod and i want the watering can
too that's important okay and the fishing rod you can build one for free you know what wait
why the fuck do you sell them diy for beginners it's free the game is trying to make me not
all right all right all right okay okay let's do that diy class about that workshop yes
yes oh can i sell these back yes i would yeah i'd love to do that i just got fucking scammed
welcome to my diy workshop i suppose workshop is overselling it a bit
you see how simple it is to diy or do it yourself you'll understand what i mean
basic ideas to gather materials follow a recipe and then crap using a workbench like this one
so today we'll be constructing a fishing rod using common materials that you can find anywhere yes
yes we need five tree branches a little flimsy i'm seeing once you collected the materials
five tree branches i come on it okay one more you're not wearing a shirt this is body paint
so what punch tree punch tree here you go i'll take a fishing rod please
project from the workbench and get started go ahead give it a try craftable three branch five
let's go flimsy fishing rod well this is a flimsy fishing rod one for sale is a normal fishing rod
that was perfect you see crafting is quite simple provided you have the correct recipe
that concludes my free diy workshop there's one last thing i have a few common diy recipes for
you free of charge naturally i just need to send them to your nook phone would you mind opening it
up oh diy recipes ready for you to use the diy app and the flimsy fishing rod you just
crafted is yours to keep may not last forever it should serve you well for a little while at
least in the fishing i'm no master angler but perhaps i can give you a few tips
aim in the front shadow you should aim in front of the shadow of a fish when you cast your line
yes i'd love to see anything you can manage to catch i'm quite curious about the local fauna
all right let's take a look at our fucking app take this app for info on the diy recipes you
collect and also register frequently crafted items as favorites i don't even i don't need to
make it now pain in the ass i gotta get my miles all right i didn't make five have a nice diy okay
a lot of stuff to do all right i got my tools i'm ready i'm gonna piss my pants he's addicted
to his phone how do you pause the game oh you can't i'll just fucking look at my phone that's
like pausing in real life anyways right back all right you know how a cow has like four stomachs
sometimes i'm convinced that i have four or five bladders and they just all fill up over the course
of like a week and then i just pee like a full three minute piss all right let me
see 507 pm what the fuck have i been doing wait eat eat and then hit the rock with my head or
something right oh i don't have anything oh wait fishing rod wait watering can wait give me the net
hold it how do i use it okay i'm gonna go get a butterfly what is it whoa i caught a common
butterfly oh that's not very good this one's yellow this one must be rare yes i caught a
yellow butterfly shouldn't all butterflies be yellow ah that's cute yo jeremy i'm getting a
real good vibe from the tent plot you picked for me thanks for the hand we gotta look out for each
other you buy you mine that you don't mine is doing i didn't do that some of you guys really
don't understand the what the nest the concept of minus two and plus two and it's you minus twoing
me the game made the joke i'm sitting here saying the same damn thing as you what what do you want
to click on another fucking look i know that there's like 5000 red bubble scam shit like
shower curtains with my face on it and stuff i know what the fuck i what what this just that's
just not even this just not even legal that's illegal stop all right i what do you mean it isn't
oh yeah that that character that's that's creepy chris and i created him on stream an hour ago
that's my intellectual property i was about thinking about how to thank you they came up with
a recipe for a leaf umbrella what do you mean i didn't copyright it doesn't matter i sat here i
said that's creepy chris and i sit here i created the character and it's it's legally it's legal
tender at that point it's legal tender all right so the first thing i wait is like making an umbrella
it's a lot of weeds that's kind of where i got the idea there's a diy project that uses weeds
think about it weeds are the most abundant natural resource we have may as well use them sparky
all right how many do you want why are these coming french fry boxes how many do i have let me
look at my diy fucking project list wait didn't was i not paying attention i was i'm back for more
huh must be my winning personality sparky i have to learn it okay to learn it you have to learn it
learn it in your inventory ah why sparky okay it's like a little card you have to learn
huh okay sweet another diy leaf umbrella and i need 15 clumps of weeds well fuck your house
i'm going to my house to take care of the weeds you gotta do your own house see i gotta take care
of my own house that's going crazy there we go you got mail from from nintendo nintendo
congratulations on your big move we hope you enjoy your new island life celebrate this fresh
start we'd like to give you a gift that's sure to come in handy from nintendo fuck you can't
throw it away what's in it all right another one from nintendo thank you for downloading the update
okay you get free stuff for downloading updates what is it simple diy workbench
i learned a diy for a simple diy workbench okay what about the other one open nintendo switch
wait i just i just got a nintendo switch i won a nintendo switch holy shit hold on
oh my god what wow can i oh yes i always wanted one of these things all right this is the tv for
now you can watch like netflix on this right there is the tv i have to lie flat on my stomach
and put my head down all right let's make the umbrella that sounds like fun and oh i need a
workbench oh wait how do i make the workbench hardwood and iron nugget okay let's make the
umbrella wait did i just smash his tent yes let's craft a bunch of weeds a leaf umbrella
cool uh that's all i can do now so should i give this back to phoebe phoebe i have an umbrella for
you phoebe phoebe phoebe unit i just came back what's on your face um i don't know can you get
a lawnmower it's got to be a lawnmower unlockable right this place is a fucking mess why am i doing
this remember you missed it you missed one um it's a cleaning game of course i'm gonna sit here
how many do i have should i sell these remember why you said you won't stream luigi's mansion
oh shit you're right yeah i'm an absolute freak show when it comes to this kind of stuff
wait how does this work get it get it go get it go get it tap tap a yes i caught a black bass the
most metal of all fish i have 75 weeds and what are they stacks 100 okay that stacks 100
hey what can you tell me oh jeremy it's great to see you that campfire was a lot fun
we're keeping resident services open at night so feel free to stop by if you need to talk about
anything oh yeah don't stores close that was my biggest problem with the 3ds one i i played new
leaf and every time i turned it on i remember it was like always 10 11 12 a.m and i could never
play the game i would turn it on and be like ah time for animal cry i can't play everything's
closed oh well this i'm not playing this now not this one okay the time being i'll be out and out
checking out with everything see how i don't know what's wrong with my brain a few things if you're
ever unsure about what you should do don't hesitate to stop me for a chat that's what i just did
i want to get a couple more fish what else can i craft i'm in a super crafting mood today
a campfire a diy bench is miles can i sort these by ones that are available to claim
seller of unwanted stuff first time buyer first custom design okay 2200 miles cast master oh okay
get 10 fish that's the quest i'm doing right now wait seashell in a row no failures that's easy
without missing that's easy what are you doing fish are all asleep oh no giant bird
monkey s what the fuck is that back there all right that does look like phoebe is like 600 feet tall
giant bird come here right in front of you get it oh phoebe unit hello anybody in here
looks like no one's here phoebe are you here looks like no one's here gotta wait for the bite
jeremy i know i know i know i know i know i know i gotta find a place where there's a lot of fish
wait yellow butterfly shouldn't all butterflies be yellow damn it and i got the net wet
wait what what is going on with it like spam bots in here i i i can't i literally can't even see
what they're writing the job mods are doing great work throw it in sub only sub only sub only
sub only sub only sub only wait what is it what i'm gonna give it attention oh hi guys this is such
a fun bug collecting and weed pulling game wait that's like a monarch butterfly isn't it let me
get it that's a huge one come on fly over here i think it's gigantic shit i can't i can't get
over there can i no i don't have a bridge here we go ah fly over here right into my trajectory
please what okay i got it yes i caught a tiger butterfly i've earned my stripes the bridges cost
200 000 bells well that's a fucking ton all right i'm gonna start uh i'm gonna sell the weeds
you can get a pole vault that's funny tax everyone i i'm not in charge of the taxes
shit okay gone you missed a peach i'll go get it so do you sell these what do you do with these
animals i can't care anything else swap it swap it with oh um common butterfly i mean at least
a common butterfly all right i'm gonna go i'm gonna go sell all this stuff white peach ruined how
those ones are rare are they hello hello what would you like to talk to me about
i'm all ears um i found a creature a tiger butterfly soft locked what a catch i do believe
this is a tiger butterfly if this island can support a tiger butterfly why who knows what
the fantastic creatures we might find living here hear me i have an idea an old friend of
mine runs a museum and would love to i'd love to send it to him for a closer look would you
be okay with that yeah oh that reminds me okay i said this is no way tied to your generous
this is in no way tied to your generous donation just now but i have a useful app to show you
oh it's why critterpedia i sent you the critterpedia app it's a terrific resource
for an aspiring island researcher such as yourself with this one app you'll get all
the important details about the bugs and fish you catch yes i do hope you'll continue to fill
it up with your discoveries and share them with me too i'm sure i'll be able to come up with some
kind of additional reward cool all right now sell them wait critterpedia check this out for
information on the bugs and fish you got this is like evolutions common level one common butterfly
level 99 whatever that joke is somebody will make it people do people think that's still funny
from the response it doesn't seem like it okay okay i wasn't sure if it was still well i didn't
know if it was still a relevant thing people thought it was funny and it looks like that's
not the case anymore okay yes but please quick re-rick roll him again send him the the video
again you guys just want to have your cake and eat it too it's not fair seasonality oh that's
cool tells you when you can get it that's cool oh that's look at the point this is just butterflies
okay that's a lot of butterflies look at all these butterflies oh it's just okay it's insects
i see well that was i thought this was the butterfly tab okay i have some things to sell you
i want to offer you a bunch of weeds peaches a bunch of butterflies a sand dollar giant clam
a some twigs a bass and a cowrie what don't sell the butterflies well i can sell all the
butterflies but one of each type right yeah so yeah i'm good look at all the fine things you've
brought today allow me to do some numbers 4500 bells that sounds good to me sold greedy weeder
137 oh i don't give me a reason to pull thousand weeds please i'll do it the greedy grinner okay
cool let's go this is atm make sure you donate all the new animals you find for the amazing rewards
yeah i will let me just go back to collecting look at it look i just sold a rare fish i did
there's no way that was a rare fish definitely not oh you sold a rare fish it was but okay
is there a way to switch between tools quickly or do i just have to there we go oh this is cute
there's another yellow butterfly what it exploded oh no the end of the line from my flimsy net
oh more bugs dark souls streamer to animal crossing how the mighty have fallen what did you say
what because you've played dark souls doesn't mean you boy you're not allowed to play animal
crossing dude if you play dark souls you know you can't play a game like animal crossing
wait this game doesn't have a dodge roll then fucking don't even load it don't even install it
no i frames yes there are excuse me there are i frames to catch the bug you have to
there are frames no that's invincibility frames not no they're not in here everywhere rare i caught
a prussian carp my skills are sharp you need i frames to dodge the bees there are scorpions
are there scorpions oh wait yeah there are there are all kinds of bugs i am relaxed the fuck out
right now this is i like this i'm just relaxed the fuck out i'm gonna clean up my area i want
to look nice it's a perfect germa sleep stream
whatever that's all right come on come here i missed a bug it's fine get it can i influence
this at all or no the debate i can yeah can i influence this at all oh maybe maybe i could
if only i uh started talking about uh powdered fucking gatorade maybe the fish would come over
here hey look at that i caught a bitterling it's mad at me but only a little is that rare
very rare oh yeah dude it's very very rare 0.5 chance ah now my front lawn looks good
don't just don't ask us about anything yeah yeah that i'm gonna refrain i think
what's the point of asking you guys anything at this point hey guys is that rare
yep no and in between there somewhere is somebody saying i i shit my pants or something so
i'm not sure how much useful information i'll get out of chat today i gotta be careful i don't
want to take all the fruit right don't i want to okay so i have to plant a peach right don't
i have to dig a hole and plant one of these in the ground so don't throw them all in the trash
anymore weeds nice and clean oh i'm asking questions right sorry do you take this game
seriously please um how do you take this game anyway i'm curious it's a game where you clean
your lawn and collect items is there a like a correct way to play animal crossing is there
like a serious way to play i thought it was just like have your eyelids closed halfway
and throw your line in the water and collect fish while you dig a hole
speaking of fish oh big one huge huge rare fish i wonder how rare this one is oh come on
fuck oh i got fucking faded i thought it was gonna be there no no he'll be back
don't worry he'll be back uh i just gave 5 000 bits 50 from hyaluronic acid just gave 50
dollars thanks the huge fucking money drop they say hey germa this game is amazing just like you
well that's very kind of you thank you thanks a lot thanks for the 50 000 bells but seriously
that's a lot of money thanks with 5 000 bits 50 fucking dollars i will use it to buy a nintendo
switch thank you come here he's emulating an emulating day one switch game i guess is that
it i i don't even want to discuss this because that's i don't even want to think about that i
don't even want to get day two fresh water it is fresh water it is fresh water it is fresh water
so i asked i did ask the right question in the beginning everyone made fun of me it is this is
there's no salt water here this is not an ocean i have to rename this pretty place fresh crest
now it's it will now will be a toothpaste it's a river yeah but that's but what do you mean it's
a river rivers have fresh water dummy hold on if a river is connected to the the ocean is supplying
the water to the river the river becomes fresh water logic much wait what's this it's a fucking
smash ball how do i get that how do i get this smash ball present how do i get this
i need a slingshot okay slingshot oh i want it right now yellow perch those yellow birds have
to sit somewhere throw rock at it i'm not gonna be able to get it it's over every single time i
get a fish people are gonna spam rare with a hog champ new viewers are gonna think you guys are
fucking it imbecile oh listen there's an animal crossing stream but we got a perch
fucking rare what the fuck rare what the fuck is wrong with these people need to be right
hey settle the slow down there i didn't say that got a yellow perch nice all right yeah but if i
bring if i bring a bunch of rares to somebody to sell doesn't that mean they're not rare if
you have a bunch of them then that defeat the whole purpose of them being rare that doesn't
make any sense they wouldn't be rare anymore they wouldn't be only two perch in existence
oh i love just picking up weeds i can't play this game what's this guy doing yo germy that's what
you found for me is just incredible thanks you can keep looking out for each other like this
it's good to have buddies rewrack all right i've got something here for you rewrack
thanks again for finding a place for my place that plain cap is perfect for salt crest
you can try it on oh nice choose where if you want to put it on you can always change later if
you need a workout rewrack that's not even the right color wasn't it red wait can i paint on
this come on you gotta have something in there i want another fish ah this is what i love this
accrucian carp my skills are sharp okay i gotta get the give me the slingshot how do i make this
can i make a slingshot this is presents everywhere and i'm missing them i gotta go i'm buying the
slingshot i don't even care it's presents everywhere hello i'm gonna my message is not unique
with the you're with a sad face what what are you talking about you're good hey hello hello
would you like to talk to me about uh uh uh i found a creature i found a freshwater gobby
yes stop picking i beg you stop picking up weeds that are there less than chump change you get more
from fish or bugs please look at the atm uh almond or wi-fi i'm not sure what you mean
you take advantage of the diy bench what do you all wonder one guy i have seen you tinkering
around a bit over there keep up the good work that reminds me i've been meaning to share some more
diy recipes with you mind turning on your phone wood along with the recipe to craft an axe
yes yes i think an axe would come quite useful on this island because so many other things have
made a wood if you'll keep bringing me new discoveries to examine it's all part of the
island experience uh let's how do i make it let's craft something all right we can do
bonfire tiki torch i thought those the pencils i thought these were pencils log steaks birdhouse
cool how do you make an axe stone and a tree branch i need one more tree branch
all right i'm gonna get another tree branch go to the atm somebody said sure
oh how could i forget uh to give you an explanation about that terminal
that is our nook stop it's a terminal for services that will further enhance your island life
at the moment you can use two services generally nook shopping the catalog shopping service for
items second this terminal serves as an automatic bell dispenser or abd for the bank of nook
we're also working on a service by which he was a redeemed nook miles for various things
please take advantage of these wonderful services quite beneficial indeed yes
welcome to nook stop a multimedia terminal from nook incorporated once per day accessing the nook
stop will award you bonus miles day one 50 miles all right nook shopping um i don't i don't care
i'm instantly buying this i don't fucking care what if it's i'm just getting it immediately
loafers oh nice i want these can i get two elephant slides no all right abd does it get
interest what do i put this in here for set your system time a year from now uh future rama already
made that joke pretty good one the future rama fry has like a savings account that has like four
dollars in it and then because he fast forwarded like thousands of years it was worth like
billions of dollars that's a funny show that's a good show this is a good one all right anything
else this chop to it but inflation made it four dollars again when you do a future rama react
stream i can't do that i what are you talking about all right let's go let's go get a twig
oh by the way has anyone ever used the the twitch watches thing or did that just absolutely fail
miserably they just delete that because nobody used it a hundred dollars in that tree yeah so
that's what i'm that's what i mean that's how i know that it was a failure you guys don't even
know what i'm talking about which implemented a feature where you could watch like amazon prime
tv shows with your audience like as a group with like your community but you couldn't have a face
cam and you couldn't talk so you just were in the chat watching the tv you just it was
meaningless it was absolutely meaningless let's make that act like i could do that on discord
right now i could say right now hey guys uh we're gonna watch um we're gonna watch who frame roger
rabbit right now if you have it uh just go on the who frame roger rabbit discord channel i need to
have a viet it's a great movie is there anything else i can make wait campfire yeah sure let's make
what's this toy box how silly man need to give you a brief introduction to the box over there
that's a recycle box for all the island residents to use using it for items removed during
construction and such if you see anything you like feel free to take it right on home
if the box gets full we'll get rid of the oldest items first don't delay in picking up what you
want what cardboard box ah i'll take a fucking yeah give it to me i mean i'll take the rock
well just okay i want to sell some shit sell sell oh that's a lot that's a lot and you can take all
the peaches and the butterfly and the perch i want the campfire and that and free free branch and
this 700 bells holy shit don't sell the weeds why not i didn't show the yellow butterfly to nook i
didn't about a creature uh this is leftover spaghetti you said you had an animal on you
yes send it please proper reward this time i've given you a red hyacinth bag just a little
sampling of a product we sell go ahead and do some planting and after a few days they'll have
beautiful blooming flowers cool good world if you enjoy gardening stop by and buy more
you'll keep bringing me new discoveries to examine it's all part of the island experience
yes all right now give me that stuff this dumpster stuff i'll take it okay bye another slide
all right i'm gonna break the rock with the axe right you've got some rare shit in here what's
that iron all right that's all that's in there cut this tree down oh the trees don't get cut down
you just keep hitting it as quickly as possible there's a timer what do you mean timer on the
rocks oh okay all right what about this big rock holding an axe outside their tent this is how
every jason movie begins i already got these what's wrong hey it's gone they're really easy
to make just make like three of them is my slide arrived yet okay i guess i can make some other
stuff wait i'm gonna plant these next to my house i'm gonna put them right here huge ass fish that's
the biggest fish i think i've ever seen but it bit it i was walking away whatever oh okay plant
plants again cool all right now we water them how much do i need to water them just once
oh they're sparkling so that's how you know they've been watered ah wonderful reedy weeder
all right i've done this somebody's saying don't pick up weeds but i need to pick up
10 000 flower tender miles for that nice okay so now i'm gonna what is this thing
venus comb hey nook why no i want cash pay off the debt i want cash oh jeremy hello
what would you like to talk to me about i have a creature look i got look at this thing this is a
bitterling i bet you think this is real cool
yes
you have to mention something about the flowers the flowers that grow will be very strong they'll
spring up even if you just plant them and forget them if you water them each day that's where the
magic happens watering opens up the possibility of propagating and cross breeding your flowers
to develop rare colors and how might you water them well i've already have already my accountant
warned me about giving this sort of thing away for free i already bought it here takes another
thing found another creature i found a yellow perch oh what a catch send it
oh hold the phone someone's calling lathers is that you oh what splendid timing yes do
you remember the venture we discussed well it's coming to fruition i'm currently stationed on an
island that we decided to call saltcrest yes the local fauna are as abundant as expected just as
i told you how many precisely you asked well there's no way of knowing just yet but i have
received let's see five outstanding specimens so far oh seriously well that is very exciting
oh but you'll have to excuse me i'm with the customer right now i'm so sorry to keep you
waiting that was my friend blathers one who curates a museum believe it or not he's going
to come to our island to help us identify and preserve the local creatures i could use your
help jeremy as you've done so much scouting and collecting would you be able to help find a spot
for blathers need a good size space to really build out a world-class museum so do that keep
that in mind going down to the beach everything is going on the beach because i will always know
where the fuck it is i'm never gonna have to open the map it'll just be whatever it is it'll be on
the beach somewhere i want to i can craft some shit can i oh look at this log stakes what are
these for to kill vampires simple diy oh i need more hardwood i can put this in my house all right
i need another axe okay i'm gonna make like three of these here i'll pay my debt down about
my moving fees yes very well you owe me 5 000 miles what i just got these
this is a happy day for us both reading clear of debt living on a thriving scenic island what
could be better well that wasn't actually a rhetorical question let me be more specific how
is that tent treating you that could be better sorry to hear that no one ever said that developing
an island paradise would be easy we don't do things because they are easy we do them because
they are profitable well yes i suppose the time is right to discuss the possibility of building a
custom house now there are certain challenges to building fabulous homes and remote locations such
as this challenges that do translate directly into costs i'm afraid with zero interest financing
an extremely lax repayment plan anything is possible so terribly if you ever find yourself
interested in a new home do come see me one more thing we have a miles redemption service for nook
miles you've collected you access the nook stop you'll be able to redeem your miles lots of
interesting things and the chat is just purple with a link what the fuck okay i would say that
this is funny but it's kind of scary this is scary this is like a you just why why is it like this
yeah it's it's you but it's like a hospital are you freaking me out man it's a fax machine
okay let's go hope you continue to enjoy your getaway package i want a house wait am i going
to redeem miles for redeeming miles all right i want i want a house about my house oh jeremy
have you made a decision about home ownership ready to move forward in comfort and luxury
as fun as living in a tent can be a house gives you more space and as you put down roots
now building house means tagging out a new loan in the amount of 98 000
i yes let's do it you get to choose eight different colors for the roof please select
a roof color from this list red pink yellow black different i don't want red i don't want pink
i don't want yellow i don't want what different color blue aqua green purple it's going to be
green or aqua if you had a wouldn't a wouldn't a black roof just absorb all the sunlight and
make like your house really hot green or aqua aqua aqua is my favorite color why would i not
do aqua homeowners get an automatic nook mileage program upgrade give me a moment
so what does that do do i get bonus miles nook miles plus benefits look miles plus includes
a nifty way to earn additional miles for special circumstances you'll see the details when you
launch the app so please give it a look when you can for me your wonderful new home should be
ready tomorrow quite exciting i'm excited i'm excited can you tell all right i need a
i gotta go down to the beach and put somebody's house down there feel free to chat with me anytime
if there's anything you need to help to get used to reminds me they use the nook stop inside the
residence services center you should even if you don't really need anything accessing it once per
day will get you some nook miles don't even more miles if you use them multiple times in a row
an easy way to earn miles all right i need um i need some twigs okay so what do i want this
all right residents residential will be on the left side of the beach and oh dna residential
will be on the left side of the beach and shops and stores will be on the right side
presidential sleeper i'll get it a little bit further up almost gotta go further to the right
here we go perfect spot yes perfect is this a good spot it is glad this can set up his place now
what are you doing out here you again is this island not big enough for the both of us do we
need a bigger island sparky what's the latest hey how'd you sleep last night this island's so quiet
at night it's almost weird sparky i mean don't get me wrong i slept like a log but i wouldn't
mind some more action around here what's up sparky nothing you're scaring the fish get out of the
way yes i caught a horse mackerel of course mackerel hey look at this what do you think about
that all right now come in i want a photo of the two of us come here i want a picture of the two
of us no come this is fucking weird d-pad i was pressing the d-pad okay hold on let's try this
one more time a d-pad only moves the camera so far there's me i did it hold on wait wait wait
wait wait this is a horror movie trying to get the other people i'm trying to get two of us looking
over oh camera milestone nook miles with a plus your rank has increased and you can now use nook
miles plus make it even easier to earn miles as you go about your enjoying your everyday life
special redemption options that only nook miles plus members get take advantage of this amazing
opportunity we have a lot of claims nook miles plus dude capture like what what earn bells by
selling items oh it's times two i get it all right let's go what did i want to do all right from
back uh you give me a break for a second i thought there was the pyramids back there
in fact i'm taking a fake vacation photo me the pyramids no you're not in here you didn't come
with me you're not on vacation with me get the fuck out of here out out out yeah so just meet
the pyramids just hanging out this picture sucks why is it so blurry wait wouldn't there wouldn't
be a tree try hard focusing i can't trees down i can't i'm not even strong enough all right there
we go i need these twigs because i need to make an axe what was that they stung my eyeball out
uh is there a doctor on the island ritz cracker eye that's a good one i want to make like two or
three axes it's not permanent why would it how would that's not permanent why are none of mine
that message is unique what the fuck why people keep saying that hey jeremy i think you found a
suitable spot for blathers to set up i'll let blathers know that he can move in as soon as he
wants good i'm gonna go break some rocks okay make a axe can i make more than one do i only have
enough rocks for that i cannot i mean i can make another log stakes i don't make the birdhouse
i need soft wood okay i want a bird house i'm gonna have a huge fire next to my house i'm gonna
surround my house with fire the house can't burn down in this game right all right anymore branches
let's go we need a rock you um maybe you're going for a new look but that seems a little bit extreme
let's talk isn't that the hat i gave you looks great really shows off your head muscle
all right now i'm gonna i'm gonna i want to make the birdhouse talk to phoebe jeremy
i will eventually let me just pick up this cheese okay i want a rock is there a rock that i didn't
smash into but first let's catch this big fish did i time travel i did not i did not yes you did
did eat it uh swap it with oh should i have all this stuff camp wait a minute oh man i got
cardboard box log stakes and shit dna strands all right i'm gonna put it back throw it away
i need a net when do i get my house okay i'm gonna put down we got cardboard box put it down
i mean what's the point of having a cardboard box sitting outside your house
okay log stakes here we go i'm gonna make it like a fence over here right here
um this is not a fence this is like i'm gonna put cans on here and shoot it with an
old-fashioned revolver i'm going to bed the bb gun yeah go to bed oh right it's real time
the game's in real time right right right right right all right but i love you is currently playing
um okay so if i change the system clock to tomorrow what if i want to play this tomorrow
i have to set this i'm gonna have to do this forever well i'm not done that i was done who
cares don't it's gonna fuck your game isn't mr rissetti gonna come out and be like you think
you can pull that shit not this time motherfucker it's gonna happen what's this place dodo airlines
hmm hang on a second how'd you get in here i could have swore i locked the front door
doesn't matter we're still getting set up in here so uh there's no flights today
sorry but that should be open for flights tomorrow though so be sure to come back then
time traveling is safe all right so i i gotta set you i got a scenario for you so if i time
travel to tomorrow okay i time travel to tomorrow and then my system clock i change it back tomorrow
to the right day does the game break probably no yes your switch explodes
oh i should be careful then don't you fucking dare if you time travel you have to commit so that
means that i would always have to have my switch be one day forward forever or what if why are you
asking us i don't know oh you're cheating cheating all right yeah cheating in the game that's
specifically designed for you to play it over a long period of time i have another scenario for
you so what if what if we just checked up on this little village and did like some chores and stuff
and then just did what we were gonna do on like the regular stream you know what i mean what if
this is how i like ended a bunch of my streams over the next oh i fucking got it in instantly
instant instead of the end of the stream screen i'm gonna read bits and do the end of the stream
hang out and just do chores and animal crossing figure it out it's a done deal but i'm not done
right now i'm still fine i'm still gonna play you're gonna get bored in like a month well that's
all right i mean that's that's fine that's even if it only lasts a couple weeks or whatever i don't
care get it get it turn the mini map to always on oh this is new oh right i have to give this to uh
i gotta give this to uh tom no angling for perfection i got it oh there's another one nook
miles plus i love how they just they get replaced there's only one black bass in the whole game
got a new recipe what did i learn oh i can craft this now should i make this and put it in the
house or should i just make a shit load of these bird house how much uh okay it's the tree branch
and hardwood and iron nugget okay we make a bird house take the bass no no what should i do i have
a creature it doesn't want it anymore oh furniture right now i have to wait okay well
i'm gonna sell some stuff and then buy some more furniture i'm gonna have like two slides in my
house all right sell all this crap i want the campfire i want i all right uh i don't want all
right get rid of the coral uh clay uh bass that's fine two thousand holy shit don't seek wait keep
the keep the clay keep the clay attention keep the clay attention keep clay okay thanks for the
attention i need the stones there we go i sell the nest sure why not 2100 attention do not sell the
nest it's over now all right let's get some let's get like a coach your account is registered miles
redemption services good redeem miles uh nook shopping the price go up on this this is all you
have abd all right deposit uh 2000 now buy uh nook miles oh nook miles ticket design pro editor
pretty good tools recipe tool ring it's essential pocket organization top eight pop hairstyles
bandana cap eye mask socks pikachu socks tool ring it does say essential on it now generating
tool ring is it like a printout your order has been printed yeah i see this totally makes sense
i learned how to easily switch tools when i'm outside i can press i already know how to do that
your character is suffering oh no this is just like a all right i'm like body painted i got like a
bruised eye okay this really is i you know those events where a bunch of people run through like
mud and dirt and shit and climb the nets and so what are they what they call like like warrior
weekend or something i'm about to go to warrior weekend they do the big outdoor obstacle course
like mud and shit all right what else can i buy no nothing all this all is a wait what there's a
okay i thought that never mind i thought i was like i thought oh i thought it was a ping pong
it's a fan the dog can get better floors should i get the glasses and be wicked fucking sophisticated
oh right okay it's an eye mask well i need it anyways i'll put some fucking cooling gel on it
and put it on my eyes what's this for take this ticket to the airport to participate in a special
tour oh shit i want to do that how much money do i i got i got money in here bells number all right
all right um what can i buy from you what do you have for sale now oh man yep i want inflatable
i'll take it medicine singles or bulk how many would you like uh just one please wait four eight
twelve six twelve oh you don't get a discount oh what else you got down here flimsy watering can
flimsy axe already have it slingshot oh okay yeah i'm gonna make it with throw okay give me the
slingshot recipe i'll take it i'm done right that peach looks good no i those are all over the
ground i think the hairstyles here we go birdhouse done yeah get gone i could also do what do i need
to make a i have to learn it first should i make more of these i was gonna do it make like four of
them i need tree branch all right let me learn it first all right what do i need it's probably
gonna be tree branches and what else do anything oh i can do it that's a lot of wood but let's go
i'll take those miles get medicine i already have medicine or just use the medicine on my eye
all right use medicine take it back to normal i'm fine all right i want to go i got a lot of
deliveries how does this boring stream of this many viewers oh well it's very simple to explain
um i'm doing my entire family reunion on stream it is all just family members yeah i went i went
to ancestry.com and found out every single living person that i'm related to and we're doing a big
family get together oh this is uncle steve uncle steve always comes back with the funny shit
there he is dad dad there he is dad what's your username big thick ass oh dad you probably should
change that dad we'll probably change that all right log stakes put it down see look there's an
it's off center but it's all right you can't even have that fucking name you can't even have that
name these can where's the birdhouse gonna go next to the cactuses oh back here all right this is a
good spot for it yeah yeah there we go i didn't move these here i mean in two weeks this will look
cool look i'm moving see the box is because i'm moving there's no way that that's a username
there's no way big what that's all right well congratulate that name will be gone in probably
two days dad he's subbed there's no way that name lasts more than 24 hours i'm gonna be honest
okay that's a good spot i can't fucking believe it do i have any deliveries where
am i gonna put the sofa you have to mod your dad no i don't want to mod my dad all right inflatable
sofa nice see we can like both have we can both have a bed and watch the switch tv
you guys remember those little hot dog bag things that we could squiggly it was weird like gooey
slippery thing inside and you could pull it hold it around it was like a little toy you guys know
what i'm talking about right it was a toy that you held it and it was hard to hold and it slipped
around and shit it was like a little baggy tube like that what are those things called they got a
name right it was filled with goo and fake shit yeah it was yeah those things what were they called
i'm not that's not what they're called that's not what it's called hot dog bag that's not what it's
called water worms there we go all right well let's see water worms no that's not correct
water wiggler bingo you got it water wigglers yeah that's it looks like all right let's let's
hang out and watch some switch yeah oh it's hard as a rock i'm gonna deflate that thing man
it's way too much air in there i thought i was gonna go like suck down in the butt crack frozen
water bed are these already watered they're they're sparkling and glistening now chores i
got in trouble for selling those in school wait a minute hold on you you used to sell at your school
water wigglers what do you mean like you brought a bunch in a backpack and we're like hey man check
take a look at this and i took it out like a wet piece of spaghetti and dangled it in front of
people hey uh we're good let's move on from that freeze anymore same eye too oh you have to run am
i not running wait what there's a resident evil run button okay well at least i got the honey
okay portable radio campfire oh right i want to campfire in front of the house right here
light it there nice okay now uh i need to find another rock oh what time is it why it looks so
dark out whoa whoa what's up with your face you get stung by a wasp does it hurt are you okay
yeah they can be mean sometimes or all times gotta be careful around them you know
uh well it's kind of too late to be careful now but you know what i mean sparky i bet that
does hurt though if i had medicine with me i'd give it to you tell you what i'll show you how
to make medicine my mom taught me when i was little here we go oh thanks just get all the
stuff for the recipe together and you can whip up some medicine in no time good luck nice so i said
mod mod her okay here we go that's what i need uh we had 50 just come in right now five million
dollars in bits thanks to the 50 z curve z curve one thanks to the 50 fucking dollars
and you message of course i don't have a fishing rod anymore so i can't even do this
how does this work what did i even shoot that at uh you say it's my sister claire's birthday today
and she want her favorite she wanted her favorite streamer to wish her a happy birthday p.s
play hearthstone battlegrounds because bad streams are good streams uh
uh hearthstone streams are bad streams and hearthstone bad streams are not good streams
but anyways thank you for the 5000 bits and hey claire have a good fucking happy birthday
from me durban985 now happy birthday for real thanks for the big money appreciate it
i need to find a floating present now wait what's that how do i not shoot how do i aim
happy birthday hope you had a good one hope you continue to have a good one
take an ice cream is all in the way that's right right do i run out of bullets
no stop i put this way i'm gonna it's gonna run out just collect a bunch of sticks why even
not why why not just collect them do they use rocks or ammo they do all right i did get the
new thing let me see how it's worth using ah that is pretty useful that's pretty useful all right
i'm gonna make another axe and i want to try to find one more rock happy birthday in the chat
right now yeah look at everyone's wishing you a happy birthday look at this uh i see there's a
present floating it has to be right underneath it how does this work what is it open it open it
open it open it spinning wheel whoa wait is this like uh rumpelstiltskin what's that fairy tale
that's cool anymore i gotta put this down in my house toronto uh where should it go uh right here
i kind of want to cut the tree down it's kind of annoying it's messing up my view
sleeping beauty no rumpelstiltskin what did rumpelstiltskin do who's the old
guy that slept for like a thousand years and had a big beard and he used his beard to make string
no well who am i thinking of who's the guy that used his beard to make string with this stuff
not fucking gandalf hold on rumpelstiltskin this is correct right rumpelstiltskin
is it fairy tale yeah yeah yeah okay yes the guy that spins straw into gold the liar rip van
winkle is the guy that slept for a thousand years let me put the radio back over here if you eat
fruit you can move trees with the shovel i don't have that what do i get the shovel oh i want to
go on that vacation i want to go on the vacation and put the radio over here next to the switch
this is where the media center is there we go here's like our media center turn it off though
conserve battery the next day is at 2 a.m for you really what did i just get board put more
furniture in your house oh okay cool i need two thousand uh miles all right we gotta do cast
master cast your line carefully if you want to reel in this row you need to get you need to
nab a bunch of fish in a row without a single one getting away all right i'm gonna do this
i need another fishing rod stink redeemed what give me fishing rod take it real wink
wink's already the channel points are all fucked up right now and what else should i make another
what another uh bug net you guys hold on to your channel points trust me you'll use them eventually
there'll be something to use it for no he's got market manipulation but okay uh fishing rod
fishing rod let's go get i could get six more fish in a row like this guy right here this will
be five earn earn earn oh you're using your points it's a big mistake just being real that's a big
mistake just wait till at some point in the next week where um if if uh if fucking i don't know if
if a million channel points come in during and i fucking missed if a million channel points come
in uh in a stream next week i'll eat a shoe how about that i'll set it up i'll make it i'll have
it just like shoe deposit it'll be like 100 000 points we'll see if you guys can get there i'll
eat a fucking shoe rock oh i don't have enough no i need to make another axe i'm gonna have 100k
right now yeah but i mean it has it needs to be it needs to be more than one million collectively
i need a million points i'll let you know i'll turn it on it'll be like shoe eating deposit is
what i'll name it you get to a million i'll i'll eat the shoe off my fucking foot i'll pull it off
and eat it on the second we cross it the second we cross that threshold i will turn it on and
i'll take the shoe off and i'll eat the shoe on camera that day that day i swear i thought
what am i even gonna catch me to lie uh mods add the word liar to banlist please make the medicine
forgot about that the drew crew literally literally spent two million points on that
stream to watch for three hours and you didn't do it so you don't understand is the drew crew
came together with two million points but i got a stockpile of a hundred million points so wasp
nest and clump of weeds oh that's it that's actually pretty easy he's a market manipulator
actual liar see the thing is guys i don't need to even lie to you because i'm the one giving you
the points i'm the one that produces the points i'm the bank i'm the point factory yes i am the
senate so it's pb8 unit then okay i need a weed i cleaned up all the weeds i there are no weeds
left i picked up all of them picked up like 500 i picked up 500 there no more i cleaned the whole
town there's no i every single weed is gone did you already donate tom nook i did there are no
weeds i can't even make them i have to wait for tomorrow for the weeds what the hell did i do that
for what is this bulletin board we use this board to post important notices another useful bit to
information everyone yes island residents and visitors like should feel free to use the bulletin
board to communicate with each other celebrate special events and more i'm just fucking erasing
we don't erase this time can i put something up here yeah i can wait but i can't write like i
can't write like fuck you or something i'll get banned right uh okay so all right is this like
baby jesus what am i doing what am i doing here
he's doing the walk fuck he really is no not eat eat eat up uh eat shoe okay how do i move this
no shit how do i erase the guy in the back because he's his signature that's tom that's
sick okay how do i get the grid of the guy in the back i can't i can't like move him around
how can i can i make the text like a different color it's posted wait my signature is on it
why would i sign that i forged his signature and then wrote my signature on it underneath
i gotta take credit for it apparently signing a forged letter what the fuck are you doing
influencer all right i need another what how many hundred i need 550 miles so let's see bugs don't
bug me you can earn miles for filling out your critterpedia can you find every bug and unlock
every entry uh using a tool until it breaks is proof of your hard work i need a lot of materials
giving away nook miles based on how much wood you've chopped from trees i could probably try
doing that all right planting flowers flower tender look at the bunch fruit you've sold
yeah number of seashells you see seashells number of seashells you sell seashells you sell seashells
seashells you sell by the seashore seashells you sell by the seashore seashells you sell by
the seashore seashells you sell by the seashore is that crit faster wait my axe my axe and my bow
and my sword and my axe and my bow and my sword right how does it go all right go go go
it's a limited time limit where's that bug where's that bug damn it it was like a centipede too
shit oh yeah i'm what if i just like fucking smashed my controller you think anyone's ever
smashed their controller over animal crossing before not gonna fucking get away this time
got him yeah i caught a centipede 99 more and i'll have a dollar pede
oh okay dad i need more wood i know have i gotten all the wood from these trees today
i feel like there's a few i didn't do yep here we go oh miss don't miss too hard one two three
why can't he do jokes like that don't you i do jokes like that sometimes and people
freak the fuck out is it a bug wait what was that that was a bug wait what tom small tom
get the fuck out of the way got it yes what is it cinnamon bag worm guess i'll brag worm
ah you knew it was gonna happen eventually present up top no that's not a slingshot
give it to me what's in it open clay furnace what all right put it in my house uh i'll put it
right here everybody steals this stuff right this is no crime in animal crossing holy shit
what is this actually use it it's a pizza oven that's awesome display furniture outside
oh what else did i get anything okay well did i get anything else can i cook on this or something
i kind of want to put it over here yeah that's fine that's better do the nook miles plus
quick miles what we got plant trees i could buy a tree and plant it okay catch a bitterling
earn bells by selling items okay catch bugs catch fish all right let's just do some of these
let's catch some fish how much shit do i have okay i got a lot of shit i need to sell
this game's very cute very cute game okay sell uh this this both of these uh actually i can't tell
the worms the museum's not open yet wait until tomorrow sell these to give this to the museum
920 bells sold all right let me make another axe do i have enough i need one tree branch put
them on the ground out you can put them on the ground outside the museum but the bug will stay
there won't the bug crawl away i'm gonna lose my mind okay i have a question is there is there a
bot that is just pulling every frame from this stream and selling it what the fuck what the
fuck man all right let's go catch some fish catch some bugs and hit a few rocks who would buy this
i don't think i look i understand that there's like there's a market out there for the strange
and the odd oh man it'll be really funny if i have oh yeah i'll buy a germa 985 shower curtain with
the germa rumble face on it as big as the whole curtain yeah i'll do that and you'll leave it in
your closet forever and you wasted money and like three people will do it it's not profitable
business it's not you somebody will accidentally maybe purchase one of them or two of them and
it's not worth it it's not profitable business this is where i look over and i say how long you've
been here for oh you know six or seven hours what did that take me two minutes excuse me
i want to show you how to do this it's rude oh look at that all right i'm almost there i almost
have enough for the ticket i need to catch one more fish and catch two more bugs you got it addicted
the whole point of this game is to get addicted to doing random things it's not like a problem to be
addicted to animal crossing it's what's that you have to hit with an axe collect it oh it's a
hermit crab i think it wanted to be left alone oh wow okay cool i'm out of room uh just drop it
this thing's worthless wait somebody's here all right i can just walk in you have one of these
weird sleeping bags these sleeping bag bags are scary i wouldn't want my head to be covered like
that i feel like if i freak out in there welcome to my top secret hideout re-rack let's chat this
can be so pumped breeze crashing waves nature all around it's all awesome i just want to jog
laps around the island and catch bugs and fish and lift and lift and lift and re-rack how's it
going re-rack at least he re-racks like eight out of ten people that go to the gym don't
so i'm glad he's making awareness there i need to catch another fish there we go come get it
put the bugs on the ground bugs on the ground bugs on the ground bugs on the ground so if i put the
bugs on the ground they're gonna not gonna they're not gonna run away all right i'm gonna try it i'm
gonna put centipede on the ground just wanted to make sure you saw it place item oh wait they have
their own little containers cool i can make my own little pet shop wow there's no room oh turn around
wait there then you you need a bigger you need these guys need bigger cages
this is just a moth um i don't i don't want a moth that's a moth there's like 50 million of them
i wouldn't look in roach ranch is back i never played that game ever again after that i need one
more fish oh Russian cry i think i have enough for the ticket should right i do but uh let me
just get one more bug wait this is i have more go ahead be shellfish oh i picked up a bunch of
seashells on the seashore nook miles for miles earning nook miles for earning nook miles yes yes
you just earned miles for finishing nook miles plus goals but where will it end probably never
does you get one for free tomorrow i do but don't buy this with 2000 um i must have channel points
go get the inventory upgrade and the haircuts i will i seem to catch one more bug
weeds i can make medicine maybe there we go wait this is the same moth that i had before
you just get a free ticket tomorrow so just stockpile my points then let me see what else
i can buy i didn't really look that hard it's 5000 points for a bigger inventory let me take a look
it is that custom design pro pretty good tools recipe
question of six dy recipes tools with excellent durability that's better market organization
guy there it is top eight pop hairstyles change your look at them at a mirror or vanity with
these pop hairstyles cool hairstyles stylish hair color t-shirts adobe premiere pro cost
900 million nook miles yeah this is this kind of does remind me of weren't there some old
websites where you could redeem points for shit it was like 500 million points like an ipad oh
i want to ask something uh i saw something on tv about this website where you can buy like tvs for
like five cents and shit they were like auction weird like fucked up website where it's like i
got this plasma tv for 98 percent off how does how does that work how is that even possible it's
just a way it can't be real it's like i got this i i got this ipad pro for only three dollars it's
just like a weird penny auction sites you have to you pay regardless if you win you're the one you're
the 10,000th person to log in you don't actually pay three dollars you pay for bids so wait so if
i pay like 50 dollars to bid three cents then i won a you pay to bid so i i pay a hundred dollars
to bid 10 cents on this ipad pro so if i bid five times i paid for the ipad pro why would anyone
ever ever do that for any reason can you actually get something for like a dollar it's impossible
it's just gambling they take your bid even if you fail to win i was so confused i was like how does
it make any fucking sense because idiots like you aren't sure if it's real what hold on whoa hit the
brakes here for a second pump the brakes i said this is bullshit this is that's fucking impossible
those are the first words i said i did not go hey guys i'm thinking about buying an ipad for uh
five cents tomorrow i opened the statement with this is ridiculous there's no fucking way it's
real but anyways how does it work i didn't say i was doing it all right am i buying this or not
i want the hairstyles pop eight cool hairstyles did i get the cool hairstyles pop hairstyles
no don't it's not worth it all right i'll save them let's uh put some more money in the bank
deposit i got some cash do the pocket upgrade all right what is there anything new in i think
i have to wait till tomorrow for this i'm gonna buy another hey good thing i i just put that money
away because i would have bought a third elephant what do we got in here so i think i have exhausted
everything i can do in the game today the first day that's pretty much all i can do right oh i need
to make medicine i'll do that yeah do i how many weeds do i have one weed wait did i only need one
how much did i need no i'm not i'm not done streaming this is what we're gonna keep going
uh we're probably gonna go back to uh fuck face city for like an hour or two check on it maybe
make a few adjustments but i do want to see one thing i want to see how much it what it takes to
do the uh no i need more than one all right yeah okay all right that's it for today or no not the
stream but this like animal crossings how do i do do you just leave do i just hit just save the how
do you save the game helicopter rescue get me out of here oh there we go ready to wrap things up for
now yes i am okay all right i'm gonna take a quick break i'm gonna come back when i come back we're
going to open up um the city skylines city and hang out for another little bit longer
maybe like another hour or two we'll see i'll be right back