Hi, what's up? How are you? Yeah, we can we can skip the formalities here. We're doing Super Mario Sunshine the final chapter
You guys already know we need a pre-stream wink. No, I I I did it already
I did the pre-stream wink already
They did it in chat. Well now now now we do it now we do a real one
The wink stuff is so awkward. Well, i'll have you know
It's going away permanently. It's gone as of sunday
Sunday is the last day for winks
no longer can you make me awkwardly turn a camera on and like look over like a deer in headlights and
Wink blink and then turn the camera off. That's a god. It's gone on sunday
They're gonna be
Very significantly reduced in price
It's gonna be a whole thing
That's sunday. It's the last day
Your voice is high pitched
What are you talking about?
It it shouldn't be
My thing has turned off. How is it? What do you mean high pitch? What are you talking about?
Turn the compressor. There's no compressor. That's the same settings from you literally yesterday. What are you talking about?
I haven't changed shit
We have 58
Shines in mario sunshine. I'm gonna finish it today. I could have finished it yesterday, but I was like
I didn't want to just rush through it. I know I probably could have finished the game in like an hour or two
But i'd like to take my time with the game. I've never played it so we're gonna go
Erase
Do a new game start new game
All shines and blue coins or else hold on. I gotta mute these things. Uh, I gotta move my microphone. I don't want to like
All right. There we go. Okay
so
With the last thing I did
What is left to do?
But I could very slowly
Very cautiously do
We have
Deontah village
I think I have seven stars in every single one of these the only ones I don't have are the coins
Oh, what about here?
Airstrip there's only one on the air. How do I get to the airstrip though?
Didn't somebody say that the airstrip that this was like the weird yoshi thing, right?
Like what's over there?
somebody else's game footage
That'd be so
Mad about well, no, there's you know how you could tell if this was somebody else's game footage
As if I was back here and just fucking hanging up
Oh look out. I gotta get that
Oh, I guess I can go this way
All right, that's kind of cool
So no like i'm i'm in i'm leaning i'm forward. We're not leaning but i'm microphones up here
What's over here?
This is the thing with the yoshi, right?
I need to get yoshi over here and somebody linked me a video
They said this was horrible and they linked me a video. I didn't watch the video
Put out his fire
I was shipwrecked and washed up here three years ago. I have to think about the far shore, but I can't swim
I've never left this island. Isn't that just awful?
I mean that is pretty awful
All right for what?
Okay
There's a boat right there
Should I get the egg?
Get the egg onto the boat put egg here
Get fruit
on boat again
Holy shit, this is gonna take this is gonna take forever
Okay, uh, where does this where does this boat go? Where does this boat end up?
Why did I fall off?
Where's this go?
Oh shit, there's a banana
Should I get the banana?
Should I get should I get the banana? I think i'm gonna try to get this banana
Why is there a banana up here? Makes no sense
Why would there be banana here? What's this? Oh shit
What?
All right. I have I got the banana
Should I eat it?
Redeemed we at home. We actually
It's for bringing yoshi over. He needs it. Wait, I have you now you're stuck for three years
So
Wait, should I leave this?
But there are bananas at the market
This is this is there's no reason for me to do this
Does that despawn?
All right. I gotta let me get a yoshi. Let me figure this out. There's a yoshi of egg up here, right?
Buy local bananas
All right. What do you want? Okay, you want one of those?
I can get you one of those
Can I not pick you up?
You can't pick the egg up. All right
Not those things on these trees
Give me one. Oh, there was one right next to me. All right. Here we go. So
Get on boat
Yoshi, we get it. We gotta get on that boat you and me
How do we get on that boat?
Do you hate this game yet?
No, what?
Why why would I hate this game?
All right. So
I'm thinking can we do it from here?
No, I can't reach that boat
Should I get on the okay? Wait, I can get on that boat
So get on that boat and then jump from that boat to the other boat
Wait a minute. Does that actually go all the way? All right, I get on the boat
I got I get plenty of food
You're gonna push me off. What the fuck? This is not like a party prank time. Get the fuck out of here
I got my phone in my pocket you asshole
Wait, it's very funny. You're gonna pay for that fucking new iphone x
God damn it
All right, I can I can get another one
Please don't do this. It takes a half an hour. What? All right, which boat should I get on? Just stay on this one?
Okay
I get off. Wait a minute. Don't touch it
Oh my god, I forgot. It's like if you
It's that fucking yoshi can't touch any water. I forgot it even if it's shallow. It doesn't matter
Right when I jumped I was like that's knee deep. No
video games from
2005 and backwards
Insta die water. I forgot
Oh, you want a fucking pineapple god. I had it too. I just didn't really there when it started make him suffer
Hey, no, don't make me suffer
I'm doing this and i'm gonna get this is the i'm finishing my chores
It's too early to be this mad. No, it's not it's it's it's never too early
I want the blood to flow through my veins
I want to be I don't want to have I want to have like blood pumping through my body
That's how you know, you're healthy. He's coming back to life
As opposed to no blood
All right, let's get on this
Fuck you buddy
He almost did it too. It was close
And turn it around what's okay if yoshi gets sprayed by water does he die
Yoshi yoshi conserve your energy
Wait this fruit on the island, right?
Okay, what's the good opportunity to jump?
Is there um
I'm not close enough
Not close enough. Not close enough
All right. I made it. I need I need these
How do I get off yoshi?
Okay like that
Oh, you've got to be fucking kidding me game
What on earth are you doing?
All right. I'm ready. So now I gotta ride the boat over there
I so I have to
It's a long ride
To the tower. Wait, is the banana on that tower still?
With banana on that tower
It better be
Does it matter what boat I get on what does it have to be can I get on this one?
No, that one just goes back right? It has to be this one
Wait, what I just walked two feet and yo yoshi already is hungry again
Hold on. All right. I'm gonna get on this one
Wait, what I have to wait till it comes back. What was the point of getting on the island yoshi?
Why are you so fucking hungry? What what's going on? Is he in the sun?
Here we go. Ready?
Fucking too much. Oh my god. It's hard to determine
I'm so paranoid of going to the water. I was shooting the fucking thing
Just skip this
All right. So the youtube so the person that donated last night said this is the worst thing in the entire game
Should I just not do this? Is there any reason to do this?
Besides like I got to the island. Hooray
Is there any reason what's over there? It's gonna be one blue coin. What do you want?
All right. I'm doing this one more time. It's too early to be this angry
They gave I got I got a youtube video linked that was like dude, please for the love of god
Don't do it the way you're supposed to do it. It's the worst thing in the entire game, please god
Just do the exploit. Please. There's a youtube video tutorial
I didn't even watch it
I'm gonna get it this time
The issue is do do not do the yoshi
a herring jump
Only to get on the island. I don't have to do the herring jump. I just have to jump. You know what i'm saying?
That's my that was my ride. This is my ride
This is my ride why?
Nintendo
All right. I'm on i'm on i'm on i'm on i'm on i'm on i'm on
All right now
Jump I have to get on the island
I need to get a little higher
It's like pushing me. It's pushing me. It's it's pushing me backwards
I feel like i'm gonna jump forward to get on the roof and it's gonna i'm gonna hit the wall bounce me back and die
I knew that was gonna happen
I knew that was gonna happen. I knew that was gonna happen
I can't
Don't jump don't jump
You must be on the roof. Do I have to be on the roof? What if I don't what if I don't get on the roof?
What if I don't get on the roof? What if I don't get on the roof?
Don't do anything
Just don't move
What if I don't get on the roof?
What if I don't get on the roof? Can I get with my tongue? Oh my god. I have to get on this one
I did it. Okay. Now what?
Wait and wait, I gotta wait. I gotta wait for this
I'm gonna eat this banana when this boat comes back
Wait, does this respawn? This is gonna respawn if I eat this
Eat it should I this is it but what if it doesn't respawn eat don't eat the banana
This is too much eat banana do not eat it starving starving starving, but what if I don't eat this
Eat it you fucking idiot eat this banana
It doesn't respawn
All right. We're gonna wait till we're gonna wait till he's almost dead and then we're gonna eat it
There's a warning right? Doesn't it go like
When you're about to die
There's a million of them. All right, just make the jump. I gotta make this jump. This is the biggest jump of the day
Just a regular jump. Nothing crazy
Just a regular jump. It gets close
Right there bingo. Just land. Holy shit. Okay. I got it. I'm good. I did it. I win
Oh my
Huh? Huh? What?
What what what what why what?
What why what?
Why did it do that?
Nobody tell me what happened. I didn't do anything
It's just fucking through. It just just pushed it shoved me off. I didn't do anything. I was standing right in the middle
What?
Oh my god, it was right fucking there
I I did it. I did it. I don't have to do this again
I
I have to move with the boat
It's a fucking boat
Why I have you mean I have to steer with the boat my body
I should have been in like the uh
What the fuck
That's not fair. I was there
I did it. I was there. It was over
I was here. I was actually here
Move the move with the boat
I didn't move with the boat last time
I just stood there and the wind was pushing me a little bit but not like a full like three or four feet
That was very clearly like uh, that wasn't like a oh be careful that you're starting to move it was like
I I instantly moved back like 15 feet. Oh my god
What the hell
I'm so uh, we was over. I did it. It was done. It was actually done
Like okay. I'm I've made it into the I don't
I'm into the boat. I made it. Okay, good turn with the boat. Why am I I don't have to do that now
Hey move in the boat, right? What's going on here?
What's going on here? I gotta be in the front of the boat
Wink with the boat
This game this game fucking sucks
I love when people it's just so funny just seeing the one person just like writes just just be so mad at this
All right. We're good
I got it
Jesus christ, this is so
Okay, this is the one right this is the one this is the one right here turn
I can't believe it
I can't believe it. There's a lot of winks going on right now. I thought I fell off the boat. Sorry. That was a double
Okay, get
Jesus dude. I'm not doing that
This is stupid. I have to jump from the roof
I last time I tried that I I couldn't I can't get on the roof from here press y please
Why?
I I don't care. I'm not doing this. I didn't want to be on the roof because the roof fight
That threw me off the fucking roof. Give me the exploit. What's the exploit?
Where's that? I'm going to the donations from yesterday. Where's where's the exploit to beat this? Let's watch it
Okay, get the yoshi. All right, get on yoshi
Go to uh dancing dancing. There's a dancing guy
I don't know what they're doing. You're jumping over
Uh, what was the point of that?
Where are we? We're over here. We're we're getting red
Wait, what is going on?
Okay, he just fell through the earth
So you eat a hot pepper and you jump off. It's this is immediately when the hot pepper goes towards you
And it floats in the air and then you run into this guy a couple times
And then you you run into the wall in the back
What?
Okay, i'm ready. This is you doing your chores, but you're putting your laundry under your bed
No, that's not true
That's not true because this would be way way less than 30 minutes already
It would be like two
Okay, give me
Uh, well i'm gonna go to the market
Okay, yoshi come here. There's the hot pepper
Can we see this?
Cheater cheater cheater. I'm writing this in caps because i'm angry yelling but what?
Wait, hold on. I'm writing this in caps because i'm angry or yelling
I'm not angry or yelling but merely because I think it increases the chances of you reading it
There in one of the islands there's a mountainside with a secret pipe or the secret stage that you need the rocket nozzle to reach
I mean it worked but I that's
Just hold on
It did increase the chances
Well, I thought I was gonna say like dude, you can't do this unless you have a different nozzle
I was concerned that it was it was it had to be a different nozzle
Like dude, dude, don't waste your time man
Like you you need the rocket nozzle after you jump off yoshi and you fall down to that pit
No, I don't know. Okay, here we go. Let's try it. Here we go. Let's do it. So here we go
Let me watch it again. All right floating floating pepper is there he then runs
He knocks into the fruits and it makes the guy go. Oh
And then he turns
And he just goes
It's this little spot right? Okay right here
You guys have freaked
I did it. I did it. I did it. What did I do wrong?
I did
Wait, you have to keep jumping you have to keep jumping
Okay
I just spit everywhere. All right, let's do it again
Now I got now i'm interested. What does he want for a fruit? Yeah, you want the expensive shit, don't you?
I can't believe it. Whatever
It passed they patched it yesterday
Well, at least I know where it is I don't think it's gonna be that hard to do this again
I said I didn't know how to keep jumping see what happened was
Uh, I stopped the video
Because I saw him jump a couple times and I thought he was just kind of bored jumping
You know what i'm talking about?
bored jumping where you just do this because
If you're just you don't want to walk walking is boring but going like this is fun
Okay, here we go. No, stop eating that one. What are you dumb?
Get in there. Where am I? What where did I do it? Okay. I did it. I got I got I got it. All right
Where where am I what?
Where is this?
Am I actually in the sewer
How do I get out of here? I clipped into the sewer
Get me the fuck out of here. I went too high
Let me watch this video again. There's this part. All right, so he's down he's going left
Just little short hops left
There's a little island. He's going over towards that green island
Okay, then he goes under the boat
Okay
There it is right there right there going going going going. Ah cheat harder. I'm trying to cheat as hard as I can
I'm trying to get in there. Well, there's no shame. No, there is no shame right now
Do it normally you normie wouldn't the normie way be to do it normally?
Isn't that what isn't that what normal is?
Come on get in there. I did it twice already
That's literally what he said but he was calling me a normie
So he said I should do it because that's what i'm a normie. So I should do it the normie way
Is it normal?
No, what the god why did it did the jump the second jump?
It did like the second bigger jump. I was trying to just time it so I wasn't doing it
If you bunny hop you end up doing the ha
And jump wicked high you can't bunny hop
Yoshi's dead
He's not how much time do I have before?
I'm doing this one more time. Then i'm playing again
Is it his last try final try?
And you got you can't I cannot have him do the second jump guys. Um, you hit the kill plane
The red coins of the lake invisible laser wall
Was I not doing jumping fast enough?
Do it normally no, I I don't know. I don't know either i'm not sure
Wait, I need a banana
Are there bananas over here? Are the bananas where's there a good banana?
We have bananas at home
Yeah, that that's the the grocery store shuffle
Oh, these bananas look good
Jeremy there there are seven bananas that are getting to be overripe at the house right fucking now
Oh, oh right, right, right
Banana spotted guys. He's not a chat anymore. He cannot lift nor can he play a kid's game
What did you just say?
What did he say?
Didn't think I could play a kid's game
How to get proven wrong
Mr
Jump jump. Okay, let's go. I'm just jumped off the edge
All right red coins of the lake red coins of the lake
The thing you have shoes on yoshi or you would instantly disintegrate
You can't walk on you can't walk on ropes of the yoshi. I think that's the first time i've ever tried to do that
It's not a banana. Is it you tried that? Did I try that already when did I?
Because that was like two days ago. That may that may have been like that should have that's like 10 years
In fucking streamer time
Do I even need yoshi for this? I I just saw yoshi and it was like oh
Immediately do because I just go go get fruit bring back warcraft fetch quest to get yoshi
I don't even need yoshi for this
He's gonna go to the lake. How's that not hitting them all mario broke his foot
He's all right
Okay, red coins of the lake
It's it's it's not poisonous, right?
No, this what what the why would I get what? All right, i'm i'm mad at me not at anything else
The name of this mission is called coins in the lake
Let me go get the guy that melts like fucking candy bar
When he touches water I got the wrong fucking nozzle for this, too
I gotta get the fucking other nozzle. Maybe I can just jump on the bug but that's I could just
What was that? That's a fucking illusion. Oh, it's right. It's a it's not in the water. It's above
I just got i'm the guy that would jump head first into the water. That's the mirage there it is
Clean crystal cliff fiji water bottles. Oh my god. I can't even no germa. Those are rocks
But they're not okay. There's
Probably up higher probably if I was there i'd be higher
Okay
They're definitely all the way up could they be in the line is definitely in right here. No
None of them are up here though. They must all just be down in the lake
Do I know about the infinite rocket launcher glitch? I don't uh, but as you've seen for the last 25 straight minutes
I i'm not going to just try to do an exploit. That's hard to do
I've not seen a single other red coin in this lake coins in the lake coins of the lake
This is I see two
Got a super coin. This is so frustrating. Just push the buttons
All right, fine
It didn't work
Ban that guy
Is there any shit down here? No, it's all
Where the fuck are all these things? Oh, there's a couple over here
Oh god, there's no one down in the lake
I got lied to it didn't say in the lake. Yes, it did. That's what that's what the facebook post said
Or where they don't sum up in the windmill over there. No nothing in the lake. Let's head back that way
Get the flower is there gonna flower in this one? There's no fire in this is there
corn
Watch out, dude, dude, dude
John, holy shit. What was that? We got one over there. Leave me the fuck alone. Leave me the fuck alone
I don't even want those. I just want the red ones. Excuse me. Excuse me. Get your head out of the way
What do I do with this guy? That's what you do about that guy
Crush his skull with your legs
Well, this sucks
Jesus come on get it before I get hit again
All right
Come on. Oh
Okay, i'm good. I'm good. Everything's fine. We're almost done. I need two more. There's one two over there, right?
It's a blue one, too
That was it's moving around. It's like it's a it's a different speed. It's a weird speed
I said I didn't see it. I didn't see it. The camera made me see it. Where was that?
Where the fuck was that? I just saw it. It's right there. Okay, come here get it
nice
The last one's right next up on the windmill up there now this one I can just I don't just well
There's a blue coin though. Let's try I should try to get the other coin try to get the blue coin impress everybody impress someone
Someone's just gonna tune in and see like a
Over there and go holy shit. He made it
How long streamed it up 54 minutes?
Hopefully I didn't miss anything. You didn't don't look don't watch
Bounced
Fucking bounced off the goddamn thing. Why does mario have bounced physics yodel laugh?
Stop
Give me the coin wait, is that I clean that is this cleanable? What the fuck is this?
All right, where's that coin? I'm just gonna run into it. Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? Come on. Where is it?
I don't know
Oh
Uh
The fuck he got all eight coins. Yep. Yeah, I gave up on the blue coin. Yeah, I did I have to move on
I can't just keep failing at something
That being said let's try the yoshi skip one more time banana. I can get you one of those blue
Blue coin over there
You know what to do. See that's what I have to be careful of is it one one two one two three
So what if I do one two one two?
One two one
Two one two one two. I think that's the way I think that's the way it is
I think that's the way you do it
Here we go. One two pause one two pause
God, you know, i've got to give some I gotta hand it to you're a speed runner of a game
And you have to do this the first time you go over here and do this
And if you do what I just did right there you turn off the whole thing
One two pause one two pause one two never do a third
One two pause one two pause. What the fuck is he doing? Oh, sorry guys. I i'm back
Um, I had to go pee
And I dropped my controller on the ground and it was accidentally holding right stick
Sorry
Come on didn't take this long
Never takes this long never takes this long
Oh shit, you lost your touch kid
He's dying. He's dying. I was like, I thought I was doing it like oh nice i'm doing it one two one two
one two
What?
Fuck you what?
It's the kill plane
In the movie he's doing in the movie he's jumping one
jump
He's but he's jumping high and but he's not hitting the
He's trying to I don't know what the fuck he's doing
He gets over here and he spins but yoshi's in the water. He's not dead
Oh, this is gonna be bad
Movies aren't real jeremy
Okay. Yes. Oh, okay fine
I'm going to do that. I'm going okay. I'm going to play the game
Or first let me turn my coins in
Shit, I thought I was I thought I was doing pretty well right there, too
Uh, oh well
Can't win them all
I'll take two shines, please
Of 61 shines
You can probably jump high when you're away from the sewer probably I don't know that's something
It probably takes a little bit of practice
So, where do I want to go? I want to I did all the stuff in the hotel
I gotta go with the
This place I only have five here
This place I have five and a place where I have six, right?
eight eight seven
six and five
So I need where's noki bay, where is that the cannon right the cannon no, that's the park that's the park
Oh, it's this one
I have to beat this
Oh, no
All right. It's a fresh. It's a new day. It's a fresh day
The new it's a fresh day
But I just have to look at it
What? Yeah, it's a it's a fresh day. I'll get it first try
Just stare at it for a minute
Look at it. Just stare at it
This doesn't work doesn't
No, that's not that would be cool. That'd be great if it worked
Just don't just stare at it
eat it
I can't
Okay. Here we go. Get in there
So it's there
Yeah, all right
I'm just gonna give me the spring
I don't need the spring. I can just jump. Can't I? Yeah, I can I can make it from here. I can make it from here
I think I can
Yeah, I can
It'll be tight, but yeah
We're just gonna go across
into the
That's the kind of camera move that bucks up a whole plate
Attention germ of virus link attention virus link. Well, i'm not gonna click a virus link and delete it
This actually kind of sucks. I remember this
Can I not move you?
I can't I have to jump over you
And then jump twice
Okay, the camera is gonna make me fucking want to yeah
camera camera camera the camera the camera
The camera
It's not a virus. You sure this guy's unstable
Unstable that's
I told you all I needed to do was eat breakfast and I was gonna get over here
Oh
That it's the camera just like rips around it does these the camera in this game does these like extreme
45 degree turns in a second. I'm just trying to go forward man. You should have got the nail
No, they're my dumb ass
Do the second set of nails?
For a one-up. It's a lie. I've done them already. I've already done it. This is the second set right here
If there's no one up in here i'm gonna be for real i'm turning chat off for a week
If there's not a one up in here, I hope you're ready
Oh
They're not all the way in
Seeing a week wrong second set what those ones? Oh, i'm not even gonna need them you got grounded
Oh
Do I feel like I can't get that fucking thing to work like 40% of the time like how am I doing that hot mic
Like what's what the fuck is going on?
What does it fucking hit the nail?
I tried to do this
It's a stupid that side jump, but sometimes I just can't get it to work
Like back forward. Oh, oh my god, the same exact fucking thing
Like do it
Um down up down up pain in the ass
Thanks coke gaming
God damn it, man. That one's so long too. Fuck
Fuck
All right. Come on. Damn it. Fuck me
Ah, let's do it again. I just did two. What are you talking about? All right. I gotta go this way
No, I don't. I said i'm right. Do a yoshi trick. No, I want to do this stupid fucking secret
long ass
Level where if one mistake means you're out strike three you're out. It's that last part
It's just the stupid back board
I can't fuck it up all the time. Yeah
I'm only jumping with that and burning it in my brain
I'm gonna watch i'm gonna do this and i'm gonna get tuned. It's nervous
I get too nervous and I go is it down up and a is it up down a is it down down down down b
Oh, I forget go from here and actually I did it from here last time
Camera refuses to go behind me. I have to go the complete other direction. Just wait that way this way that way
Is this this I should I should probably go this way, right?
Because like i'm giving i'm making this way too hard of myself. I have to go this way
What should I just say fucking and go?
Bird brain what it's really my choice
Oh, whatever
Oh, wait, this is the this I remember this
the camera goes
Didn't do it this time fucking stupid fucking goddamn fucking game fucking dumb fucking stupid fucking game
I can't get the camera in the place that I've wanted
What the fuck just fly in there?
All right, tell me the truth on that second set. Am I is there actually a one up in that second set?
Tell me help me tell me is that is it really one in there?
Is it one in there? Please tell me there's one in there. Is it one in there?
second set
please
Tell me
There aren't there isn't though remember I did this before it's random. Oh
Whatever i'm not i'm not messing around
Maybe it's not the nails
What would it be? Here's the second set
Is it one up in here? Are you saying?
I hope there is so that I can just do this
I hope there is please tell me that it's in here
They're not lying
Wow, they're not liars. I can't believe it
honest chest
Sick
I'm, sorry guys saying ai ai ai
Is is so many people say that
Remember the little robot from power rangers. That was his catchphrase. So
Sorry, you don't get to have this one
Holy shit, that was really really bad. I got stuck. I'm okay
Okay, here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go
I feel like my hair is in my mouth, but it's not it's impossible
Okay sloppy, but we're here. I was here
I was here. I did it
Wait, I'm so I can't I have to get just pick it up, right?
Okay, I almost fucked that up a half dozen times on that last one
That was I was so sad
but you this is why I don't have face cam on because
Once I missed I had to do this like the third jump and I landed on my butt the part when I landed on my butt
I looked like this
You don't even know
I'm sitting there going like no, no, no, it can't be
I'm right there
We want to see no, no, no
Cameras fucking stupid fucking cameras fucks up on me. I'm fucking all the time. Hold it shadow mario. There are kids watching
Oh, yeah, it's that it might be
Oh, yeah, this is like super mario sunshine
All right. Okay, we're gonna we're gonna be friendly today
Come here. Hey
you oh
butthead
better you you little
You little bastard
You
Just jump he just killed he just killed what?
Did he go is that him all the way? No, that's a blue coin. Oh, I see him. He just he just resets
I feel like i'm racing myself and fucking like mario kart
You're a pain in the ass. Sorry
I'm sorry. Why are you saying sorry? Did he jump off? Shouldn't I be like shotgunning?
I should be shotgunning him like in the face, right? All right, come here you fucking little asshole
Got it where it's 62
Language, right? Right, right. No, i'm not gonna say anything bad for the next 25 minutes
Ilfino plaza
Go, wait, shoot spray birds
Somebody said spray. Oh, okay. What's this?
Whoa, you want to work for me for a little bit? I'd love for you to bring me some fruit
I'm craving some pineapples bring me three just bring the fruit here and put it in this basket. Okay. Yeah
I think so
So what is left?
seven eight
eight
six
seven
We have six here at pionta village. Which one is that pionta village is the one?
The I need the rocket right?
And that in one of the tubes they're like up here
That's a tube one, isn't it?
Red coins. Oh, this is not it. It's the other one
Well, let's take a look
Uh, yeah, I did the police door already
No, I don't want to you can be going to pop in gamer this year
What's going on gamer? How are you? What's up, dude?
That only works once
That only embarrasses me once
never again
All right, this is number seven, right so this is shadow mario again
Is this the this is the last shadow mario that's available, right?
Shadow mario runs wild
Dun dun dun dun dun dun dun
Oh, he's got fire. Why does he got so much fire?
This one was very very easy
64 stars
They're all very easy. Well, that one was just a straight line
Uh, yeah mario 64 sick
elfino plaza
here he is again
He's all the way back there
Oh the whole this whole town is flooded
Holy shit
alert flood delfino plaza has recently
experienced
a waterfall like
deluge of rain
in all areas
Presidents are advised to seek shelter
on rooftops
To avoid the rising flood
This is the what is it's at this point the guy looks out his window and he's like, oh shit
I haven't left yet
It's five feet above his window
Probably should have got out
Was it two days ago?
Oh shit
All right. So can I should I get yoshi?
I guess I can just kind of go should I just i'm just gonna go over there
Wait, this is shine. Oh, I hear shine. You hear that. Where is that? Is it in the box?
No, it's right there
How do I get in there? No, no, no, no, no, I don't I don't want this is
I don't want to do pachinko. I already beat it. Uh, I can go in the sewer thing
What's going to one of those sewer things?
Look at all the fruit up there. Is there a sewer on up top?
I don't know. Okay, this one right there
Break this shit. It's my favorite chewing gum
uh
the one with the zebra
I want to break this though
Ooh
Let's
Not go this way
Oh, no, let's go this way
because i'm
Wait
That's a big launch
Can I just walk over here blue bird?
Got one. Hey, I made it final level. Oh, this is the last
Okay, corona mountain
One up. All right. Now there's a okay. We got a jump
Not an issue. Not an issue. All right, keep going. We're going right. We're going right side
Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. We're good
Fill me up what's in here two one ups
All right, get the cannon ready into the boat
This way, okay. I mean I was in a boat. I didn't
I think the boat was going to just capsize
I didn't know what the fuck I was doing
I didn't know what the fuck to do
I don't even need to wait
Why even wait?
Unnecessary
All right this time don't go so hard
Thankfully, I can do this forever because of the one ups
Okay killed. Let's try this again
So gently gently row the boat
Is it sinking? Don't crash into anything
Oh slow slow turn turn turn
Turn turn
Oh, this is gonna be
It's all right. It's up
Okay, you touch anything. It's over if you tell that's what happened the last time. I didn't do it
Okay, I get it if you do it too. I get it
If you touch anything, it's over. That was really really stupid of me. I was trying to go too fast
I was just trying to skip this whole section
Not worth doing that. You can do it here and that's about it
I just didn't get that
mother
All wonder over the Wi-Fi Wi-Fi over the Wi-Fi
No wonder
Wi-Fi
That game is so fun
Holy shit
All right. It's not a big deal
I made that a big deal for no reason
All right. Let's go
so
Let's use my binoculars
Left side or right side i'm gonna it looks like left side
I want to turn this fucking thing
Well, we're going right side
Abandon ship just go look at all these blue coins. There's so many blue coins over here
It's attempting to get back in the boat and get the blue coins
Is the boat still there?
No, it's long gone
Hover and get them. No, that's too dangerous
All right. So what this
Hole right here
Do the clouds disappear? Oh, this is gonna be bad
This is gonna be very bad
It's actually jump king
Wish I could see
Okay, not bad
Don't fall down into the bog
Where are those we're okay, they're going across and down and left and right
It shouldn't be too bad
We gotta hit this here
Here comes this one
Nope, we're going over here
You can go through them. So that's good
All right, we're just gonna go straight up
Not bad
and then
again
Wait the actual bowser
He's huge
All right bullet bills
Jump on bullet. All right, he's coming for me put him out put why am I shooting lava?
Shoot in his mouth
Baby shoot baby bowser
Try to tilt the hot tub like i'm tilting the hot tub
Don't do it. He's naked
Perhaps you could use your pack to gain more. Oh, thanks for the tutorial at the end of the final boss
boom
That seemed to be effective
Oh, man, the the sky is falling the sky is falling
It's wicked crunchy. I'm sorry the audio is crunching in my ears
uh
Fucking emulator. It's a fucking emulator
All right. Oh
The game knows sorry about the crunch
Sorry about the crunches. I can't help it. There's nothing I can do about the crunches
It's gonna be wicked crusty ass crunches
Come on no fucking way launch
Come on, man
Give me a break
This is the crunchiest audio too. I have to turn it down drink that drink bowser's
Getting thin here getting really thin. Holy shit. Oh my god. I got super launched
Ah, it's it. Wait, damn one more. Hey, come on
Not fair. I gotta go all the fucking way around dunk this thing. I hope you two learned your lesson
Except you never do. Why are they not in jail?
Mario it just ran out of battery
Relax. When was the last time you plugged it in?
Junior i've got something
Difficult to tell you about princess peach. I know she's not really my mama
Why he just did like the youtuber thumbnail face
mario
Pretty cool like bowser revealed the end of the game
That in this green ass hot tub that has been clean all the fucking algae is building up disgusting
Hey
There it is super mario sunshine
Vacation never ends
Do metroid prime
Maybe but I want to there's still a couple things I want to do
I want to see if there's anything else I missed. I'm going to get on that island with yoshi
I need to see what's in there
I already beat the game. So it's all right now we can do some of the extra stuff
I'm not gonna 100% the game
There are 240 blue coins damn go get the sunglasses
Do pachinko again. No, i'm not doing pachinko again
Two hours stream. What when who told you I was turning the stream off?
Save it. Oh 65 stars
Oh
And i'm kind of not happy about that
All right, let me look at something 120 shines. No
That's not happening
I'll tell you what is happening though
Doing this the right way
I'm gonna i'm not no cheating. No exploiting
You want a pineapple? Okay
I'm gonna get you a pineapple
I'm not watching the boat tutorial. I'm just getting on the boat
Ground pound mini game ground pound mini game. What's a ground pound mini game?
Go get the vacation shirt. Hold on
The house in here
Let me try this one more time
I'm gonna try this the right way get to get on the roof watch the turns
Get over here stay on this
And I gotta I gotta get on the roof
on the next one
Yoshi can spin jump
What if I just know you have to get on the other one at the island, don't you?
Why did you tell him that what?
Sewer goes to the first island
Hey, thanks for telling me that
Thank you. Seriously, you just saved me a bunch of annoying time
Thanks
Let's test that theory. Yeah, okay cool, but don't tell why did you tell him?
Why wouldn't you
Why let's right there. Oh, I i'm so glad you did because this is now I can actually attempt to do this a few times
Goodness
You want a banana?
All right, i'm gonna go to the market
Sunglasses guy. Let me do this first
Get the shirt get the shirt. I will I will I will I will I will I will I will he's right there
I just i'm hold on
He's right there. Where is he?
Which one is he this guy right here?
Come here
Sure, it's gotten a lot brighter around here
What where is it? Where is he?
It's the guy on the beach this guy right here
Okay, thanks. Give me the sunglasses
You also need one of my custom tropical shirts
Oh my oh my haven't seen anyone look that good in my in my gear and ages come see me again when you want to return them
It just made this game ugly
It just dropped my brightness and contrast
Hmm
I can't make that jump
You missed the bus. I'm not trying to get on the bus. I'm trying to skip the first bus entirely missed a wink
Did it just throw? No, okay
Okay, that's the one right there, right? This is the one that's the one this is the one right here
I didn't get on the roof. I didn't get around do it again. Do it again, right do it again
I didn't get on the roof. Yeah, I can't get on the road. I do it again
Why why are you spending your winks? Oh because they're gonna be useless in one one day. Yeah, you're right
I think you guys would want to hold on to them too, but they're gonna be gone. Yeah, they disappear in one day
I guess that's right. That's true
I would probably do it too
And again, you could probably do it two or three times for your money on sunday
I thought you just called me wink you stalker. I was like, why am I a stalker?
All right, here we go. Gotta get on the roof on the roof. That's not even right. It's coming over here
Where is it?
On the roof get on the roof get on the roof
Get on the roof on roof get on the roof
Land on the roof. How can I do any more like mario vacation games? This is the most winks I think in one day
One more day of this and then we're done forever
Here we go on roof. Okay, we're good
Now just don't fall off get right in the middle. Now. I have a question. Do I have to actually get yes I do
That's a dumb question
And then on the second boat i'm gonna get in the boat not on the roof
Um when I change boats up here after I get up to the banana
Do not get on the roof
You know what I mean?
What I mean, this is the wrong boat
How could this be the wrong boat? Don't get on the roof
Stop texting me
Isn't that the problem?
How could this even be the wrong boat? What are you talking about? This is it's going the exact way I want it to go
Just get on here and then we get on the other boat and just be cautious
Be ready
Not yet
Okay, just get on this other boat
Now I want to confirm
Jump not on the roof
In the boat or should I just try to get on it and just don't and try to stay on it?
Just does the roof. Okay, doesn't matter. Okay, i'm going for it
Just get on the boat the last time I got on the boat threw me off
Oh my god. Oh my god
It's too fucking far
How
It's just like I just did a little jump and he just went way over it
Ah
I'm just gonna walk off. Oh, okay. I'm doing it again. I'm walking off the edge next time
I'm just walking off the edge
I'm not jumping. I'm walking off the edge
This sucks such an ass
What do you want for a treat? Yoshi?
A pineapple. I haven't even reached the level yet. I know like what the fuck
I'm i'm gonna just fucking
Just slowly fall off the edge
Get over here
Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up. It's here. It's here. It's here. It's here. It's here. That's it. That's the boat
I don't even need the juice. Excuse me game
Find me find me
And what happened there you could hold your breath underwater now
Don't get upset by that
Calm down. It's all right
No, it's not a big deal. I'm don't be very upset by that. Yoshi's been pretending this whole time
He's not dying guys, he's just disconnecting he's ripping his fucking wi-fi cable out. It's there's a difference
Damn it, man. Get over there. I hope you make it but miss the last jumps. Don't say that
It's such a small jump
It's so small. It's just like a little
I'm trying i'm jumping a little too much and i'm just overshooting the fuck out of it. Let's take a look
Crosses over it's just like a little a little
You didn't have to like
This is the wrong boat. Fuck. It's the wrong boat
wrong boat
I mean everyone's saying that it has to be real if it's the wrong boat
It's just a little hop just a little pop
Just a little pop that's it
Okay, just a little pop from here. Just a little like pop just pop just a little pop
Toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat got it. It's just a little like pop
Just pop just a little a tiny one. Just a little just hop
On the top. Okay, here comes just a little pop
A little don't say fall joke incoming
It's just a little pop here comes pop
Just a little pop
Pop game over don't say that yet. This is gonna throw me around
I'm i'm so paranoid that I gotta get up like a little
There's a little pop
No, I already did that
But I don't know what to jump off
What what's the correct time to jump off?
And I have a better idea
Why not just put some of yoshi's spit in a bottle and dump it on there when I just take the fucking fairy
Why do we have to do all this? I just can you just spit in a bottle for me and I can dump it on there
Okay, when do I go off?
Not now. This is too far
Not now not yet. Not yet
Not yet. Not yet. Not yet now
I did it
Thank god
Holy shit. Here we go
This is I've never seen this. How do I take the sunglasses off? Is it food here? There's no food here
Whatever. Let's go
What?
Wait, it's just a water slide
I have six
This is gonna be fun
Wait back back back back it back. No, no, no back back back back back it up back it up back it up back it up
Back it up back it up back it up back it up back it up
There's a current I can salvage it. I can salvage this just
It bumped into the fucking wall
It bumped it like it did this like extreme spin
Digimon no, what's the that's the spinning tops the spinning top to our cartoon with tops spinning to each other and fucking break
What is it called?
Did what's what's it called beyblade?
This is extreme
Grab the edge grab the edge
Okay, all I care. Okay, I can just I think like some delight and I think I still do this. Does it respawn?
It's gonna respawn
It's the lily pad comes back
I it definitely does
Is it there?
There's some there's a pipe at the end of the level
Oh, I think I can get that coin
I think I can get that coin
I can get that but I can retry. There's no reason to do that
What uh, just get the one off at least there's no reason to do what i'm doing right now
If I if I can retry it by going in the pipe then just do it
Go in the pipe what i'm going
Stop don't pipe is don't stop don't go in the pipe. No, what don't don't one guy one guy
What do you mean one guy?
Cat is lying about the pipe
That's a trap
I'm going in it. I'm fucking whatever. Okay, I i'm gonna ride it the whole time
I was looking at the chat room and I pressed the wrong tilt. I tilted a little bit extra looking at the fucking chat
And I come back and it's a little bit too far. All right, i'm just gonna go in the pipe
Just get me in the pipe
Wave of people that said go in the pipe
Brings you to the start
And then a show of people said don't
So I thought those people were just trying to be like stomp like pepe left. Don't fucking tell him to do that
Oh my god
But there were green pipes at the beginning of the level
There were there was like three green pipes that were right at the beginning and I believe the first 500 people
dude
I got actually
Extreme one guide did I
No, I didn't did I did that happen? Is that the only one I've read?
It can't be no it was more than that. It was like a thousand people
It was like a thousand people
Uh, no, it was at least at least a few hundred
It was no it wasn't one person. It can't be
Everyone was saying don't do it
Yeah
It's like the boy who cried wolf with this chat man. I'm telling you
Some people say shit. That's just fucking inaccurate
And then I go no, no, no, they're fucking with me and there's a wolf eating us
We're all being eaten. The the the chickens are all gone. The house is getting knocked. There's a
There's a the wolf is here
And now I have to do that all over again
To go back there. I'm not doing that again
Why the one guy the no the the 201 guys that were responsible for what just happened are sitting there just like
Fucking they're just rubbing their fucking hands right now. They're like, oh
We got him
so
You don't have wait what?
Oh, I don't have to use yoshi again. Oh
What?
It's I don't have to spray the thing anymore
Oh, let's go
I thought I was gonna have to spray the thing again
Going I can't I I'm seriously
Year of the bait
What did I do? Did I not do the eighth one here? Let me see. It's in here
Is that okay? Is there anything cool I can do?
Besides the regular levels. Well, is there something else cool to check out before I stop my rest on time?
There's another this other secret another secret level. Oh the ground pound mini game. Yeah, I want to do that. Where is it?
Go to the airport go to the airport air strip
Where is the airport from here?
I haven't been back there all game. I don't even know where it is
Wait, what's that? But behind where yoshi is?
Wait, is there's more to do here smash time
Smash time. Oh fuck. Whoa, look over there. Look over there. I need a different nozzle
Eel boss. Oh, let me do this first
That's the air strip. Oh what?
nice, dude
nice
I'm just pretending to know what you're saying. What oh that's okay
Spray the beach
Okay, that's not I mean, that's kind of cool. I guess
There's more of these
Okay, cool. Okay, dude. I just found uh, I just found that star. That's like a secret star. Can we get a hype train?
I just found something that like everybody finds in when they play a game
Uh, let's start a hype
cool
scams scams
Local streamer runs scam on his audience and it's just me
It's just it's just like the
I'm completely silhouette it out
Just like this
so why
Why why did you do that? Why did you continue to try to bait people into giving you money?
well, you know, it's
honestly, it just uh
It seemed like the easiest way to just make money
I
Know if I said hey, yo, we're doing a hype train of this get hype
People who did that for hundreds of dollars would just come in so I just figured why not
What did you spend that money on?
Uh drugs a lot of it, uh, mostly drugs
I'd say 92 of all the money that came in went into drugs. I just did drugs all day
and then maybe five percent to mcdonald's and
Seven or eight percent to bills. I guess I paid some bills. I lost a lot of it too. Actually I got out of the bed and
Just kind of didn't know where it went
At least five to ten twenty percent of it
Okay, that that comes out to uh to to a hundred and twenty eight percent
Yeah, let's uh
Yeah, I would say that's accurate
and I mean
It's not like I uh, but you got you're not like showing my face, right?
I whoops. I fucked it up
There's the crack head
Why am I biting my lip?
Because I always bite my lip. I'm a constant lip biter
And I put like vaseline on it to prevent myself from doing it
What the hell is this? This is not the airstrip. This is not the airstrip
Um, let's try again, what even is this a picture of
This is not the airstrip though. It's a surf map. It kind of was a surf map
behind you
Talk to the guy behind yoshi
This guy behind yoshi, this is behind yoshi
Shall I take you out to the airstrip? It's only ten coins
We'll get ten coins
Something something and a aim. I know whatever nine really nine
Nine points because you can't put ten there. Remember reacts to only finding nine coins
That would be a slow youtube day
That would be like I have extra footage that I haven't had a video go up in like two or three weeks
And i'm just like fuck. Um
Uh auto's dog farts messing up my game
All right
What's this was it been like six days since the video went up shit? Okay, how about like a yeah, that's that sounds good
real video by the way
If some of you new reviewers real video this is real
All right back in the airstrip now what it's it's been the whole game since i've been here
Oh, no, should I come here with the nozzle the nozzle's here
Oh, thank goodness
uncensored germa
Red button. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, i'm just taking a look
What's what are these?
You can melt them. Where do I get I can get fire. Oh, you just know you just melt them
Dark matter
All right, let's do uh, i'm assuming these are coins
You might my dog my dog just farted
Stop we don't watch videos from 10 years ago
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on
Yes, 68 where do I want to get one more one more baby one more
one more
No, whatever anything ground pound minigame ground pound sound delay again, why does it keep happening with this game?
Where's the ground palm minigame?
It's in a building. I already got this one
house to the left of the big shine thing
It's very ella. I like your description. That's I very easy for me to understand
This thing probably has a name
like
Shiny mount stadium or something but like a big shine star thing. I know what that is
Now it's building over there. Okay, actually I might have the wrong thing for this
Oh wait, can I go through this? I hear one. Why do I hear one? Okay
Uh building here it is
Break all the crates within 30 seconds to win a prize. You want to try? Yeah, sure
That was great. You're the best three misses and I died. It's fine
69 shines
We did it. Yeah, we did it. Hooray
Ha ha ha ha
This crap everybody laughed really hard
Come on, let me make it even funnier
Why did I spend any of these blue coins?
I mean too bad. It wasn't
69 three times
Right. That would have been pretty funny
Actually, that kind of would have been pretty funny considering it would have taken me so much longer to beat the game
Because at least seven or eight of these stars or ten of them are blue coin stars. I hear this thing
Where is it?
Can I not how do I get in here? All right this guy?
This guy's a chuckster
Oh, howdy throw me a coin. I'll throw you for a loop. Ah, anyway, here you go. Okay
We are gonna
Take a quick little break. I'm gonna go pee
We're gonna change
To something what do I what do I want to do?
The we the game cube shit's already hooked up and it's already set
So I might just maybe play a Wii game or something play another game cube game
Because it would be i'd have to switch out a bunch of cables
And recalibrate some stuff to change anything else. Uh, let me take a look. See what I got. I'll be right back