Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with Smite Sunday.
Welcome to the first Smite Sunday on this channel, where I break down a god, or I show you a good gameplay and talk about it potentially,
or I do a live commentary. But today is going to be a god breakdown. I'm going to talk about the god Anubis, the god of the dead.
And the reason why I'm picking Anubis first, to do sort of a god breakdown and sort of small tutorial video,
is because Anubis is one of those characters in this game that he's not a free god. He's not one of the free gods when you install the game.
But he's the one that I feel like everybody unlocks first and then plays him completely incorrectly.
I was one of these people that when I first downloaded this game, I said, oh my god, Anubis, the god of the dead.
Oh my god, I got to get this guy. I got to play with him. He's so cool. And I would just get trashed on.
Because Anubis is one of the most damaging gods in the game, but he also dies incredibly easily and incredibly quickly.
So I figured because of my early struggles with Anubis, I figured it would be a good one to start with.
Anubis, the god of the dead, the Egyptian lord of destruction. That's not even true, but it's Anubis, the god of the dead.
So instead of reading off of the wiki page and telling you all the damage numbers, which are very, very easy to find on the internet,
I'm just going to tell you what the moves do and when you should be utilizing them and when you should be not using them in different situations.
So we're going to talk about his number one, which is Plague of Locus. It's on the one key skill key number one.
And upon activation, Anubis will stand still and launch out a bunch of bugs at people in a cone. Kind of disgusting.
It lasts for three seconds and ticks for damage every 0.5 seconds. So when should you use this move?
Now, I would typically say that this should be part of your non-ultimate combo. I'll get into that in a few minutes.
But besides that, this move, although it does a ton of damage, you won't really be using this early game.
And here's why. Anubis does not have any escapes. And if you don't know what an escape is in this game, it's a jump.
It's a dash. It's really any way to distance yourself from another god or from another player.
So trying to utilize a move like this when you have to stand completely still, you're just going to get destroyed by the other lane.
Think of a situation like this. You're level one, level two, whatever, like really, very, very early game.
You're up in a lane with a buddy of yours. You're in playing Conquest and you have this move. You go up and you use it on a minion wave.
And you're standing still. The other team sees you. They know you're Anubis. They know you cannot get away.
So they jump on top of you. You got to play it safe. And standing still up at level two in a minion wave when there's two other guys about to kill you is really not playing safe.
You need to use your three early game for Anubis, I would say. But we'll get into that when we get to that.
Also, that kind of leads me to another point about some beginner tips for you guys. Standing still is bad. It's very bad.
If you stand still in this game because everything is a skill shot, well, most of the things in this game are skill shots.
There's so many stuns. There's so many slows. There's so many people that will be able to hit you with all of their moves.
You don't want to be standing still. So that's another reason why the number one is not the best choice early.
So moving on, let's talk about his two, which is arguably his best move. And that move is called Mummify.
And basically, this is just a stun that you can do very, very frequently and it wraps up anybody you hit with it for a maximum of two seconds.
This is an offensive and defensive move because if you're trying to run away from somebody, landing one of these can literally save your life.
He doesn't have a dash. He doesn't have a jump. But landing a Mummify can really get you away, especially if you use something like Sprint.
You can get yourself out of a lot of trouble. And there's not very much else to say about this move just yet.
We're going to cover Anubis's three and four and then return to this bad boy and really talk about the best times to use it.
So Anubis's three is something called Grasping Hands. It's an AOE ability. It ticks for damage when you put it on the ground.
You just place it underneath people, whether it's a minion wave or enemy god for harassment purposes, and it slows them as well.
And it lasts for two seconds. Now, this is probably one of the best wave clearing moves in the game.
I would say this, Ao Kuang's tornadoes, Ra's number one. There's a lot of gods that have fantastic wave clearing abilities.
And this is one of them. It's also one of the reasons why I suggest putting points into this first rather than Locust Swarm,
because you can use this on the move and it slows people. You can get a lot more utility out of this.
You don't have to stand still to use it. And it's a little bit better in team composition situations where you put your three down on somebody
and your teammate can potentially help out because of the slow.
So before I go on any further and talk about his number four, his ultimate, we're going to talk about what I said previously.
And it is the non-ultimate combo. This is really what you should be trying to accomplish when your ultimate ability is on cooldown.
What it entails is pretty much this. You use your two, you wrap up an enemy with your mummify, and you instantly place your grasping hands underneath them.
And while they're still wrapped up, getting them in the cone of your Locust Swarm, you do your one instantly as well if you're close enough.
That's, I guess, assuming you're close enough. It takes some practice, but late game, you can really instantly kill people with this combo.
You don't even need to use your ultimate late game in a lot of situations if you're fed.
You can just place your three, mummify, bang, the person is dead. And that's one of the best things to do as a noob.
And one of the bad things about this is if you do not kill the person, let's say you do this non-ultimate combo,
you wrap the person up, bang, bang, do both those moves, and you don't kill them,
there ain't a whole lot left for you to do besides turn around and run away or try to auto-attack them to death.
So having a teammate nearby is a very good thing.
Because let's just say, for instance, you do this to somebody at level 20.
You're both max level, both of you are equally as fed, and you don't kill them.
This person knows you don't have any moves left. You did every single move that a noob has had, and your ultimate's on cooldown.
They know your ultimate's on cooldown because why wouldn't you have just ultimated them?
So they might just come after you and just smoke you with some of their moves because a noob just dies very quickly.
So it's gauging these situations and knowing, okay, is there somebody in the jungle? Do I have a teammate nearby?
Can I just kill this guy instantly with all three of these moves, or am I going to have to wait for my ultimate?
These are things that you have to assess, and it just comes from learning the maps and figuring out team compositions
and the best time to go in and the best time to go out.
You'll get that over time, but this is the best thing to do as a noobus for sure.
And finally, we're going to talk about his ultimate ability, which is very, very self-explanatory.
I'm not going to spend that much time on his ultimate because it is very, like I just said, it's just a line of death.
That's it. When you use the ability, you stand completely still, and a line comes out of your face melting anybody that you aim it at.
And it's kind of like his one where you stand completely still and it does a lot of damage ticking over time,
but again, it's in a straight line and you have to aim it at people.
It's very much a skill shot, and the lag can really play a huge part in this.
I have aimed at people with this, and they've ran around in a circle around me, and I hold it on them, and I don't hit them at all.
So it can be pretty tricky to hit moving targets with this and land it because, again, it's just a one, pew, straight line ahead.
But the ultimate combo, I talked about the non-ultimate combo. Let's just briefly bring up the ultimate combo.
The ultimate combo is wrapping somebody up with your two, instantly placing your three underneath them,
and instead of trying to hit them with your one, you just instantly do your ultimate and melt the person to death.
It usually kills anybody in the entire game at max level unless they are building tank or unless they are very, very fed.
So before the video wraps up in the next couple of minutes here, I want to talk about a very specific tactic with Anubis,
and it's something that a lot of new players don't try, and it has to do without damaging somebody rather than just running away.
So as we all know, Anubis does a lot of damage, and he takes a lot of damage,
but people underestimate, I think, how much damage he does late game, and they will try to kill you.
So it can be sometimes in your best interest, instead of running around away from somebody,
turning on them and using all of your abilities, even if you're at very low health.
So you can put people in a very, very large false sense of security when fighting you if you are very confident in knowing you can land your moves.
This is another thing that takes a lot of practice, because if you turn around, let's say you use this strategy,
you attack somebody, you try to kill them, you know you can kill them with your one and your three if you mummify them,
or your three and your ultimate, but you miss your mummify.
Oh dear lord, you're dead. You are dead. If you miss that mummify late game and you have low health
and you're trying to use the out DPS tactic, you're screwed.
I would say that in general, if you're playing as Anubis and you miss your mummify, you're screwed.
So it's landing your two becomes the most important thing to practice and the most important thing to land as Anubis,
because if you do not, let's just say you land your two on somebody and you don't kill them,
one of your other teammates potentially will. So if you wrap somebody up and you're in the jungle
and you got like an Ares behind you or you have a Ra coming through the jungle that's on your team,
he might kill the guy because he's standing still in your mummify.
So your two is the reason why I said it's the most important thing for you to utilize as Anubis
is because it does so much stuff for everybody else, not just you.
So learn to land your two. It is insanely important.
So that about wraps it up here, guys. I think I've covered most of the things I want to cover with Anubis.
And the next God will probably be Ares for Smite Sunday.
I'm going to break down Ares. I'm going to talk about why he's my favorite God in the game.
Yes, Ares is my favorite God in the game at this point.
It used to be Anubis, it used to be Loki, but now it is Ares.
And we're going to talk about him next week, going to break down his moves, going to break down how I play him
and some of the things you should be doing as Ares. And that's going to be next Smite Sunday.
So thanks for tuning in, guys. I really do appreciate it.
I'll see you guys all next time. And of course, take care, everybody.