Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Super Meat Boy.
Gonna be playing on Chapter 4 tonight, Hell.
Which is scary.
I don't want to go to Hell. Nobody wants to go to Hell. Why do we have to go to Hell?
I am just gonna skip this cutscene. Just kidding.
Let's see what happens here. Meat Boy and Dr. Fetus are running at each other with crazy anime backgrounds all over the place.
Oh, a clash of the titans indeed.
Meat Boy is down. He's gonna get thrown. Oh no, Meat Boy is down for the count.
Oh, he's dead.
I don't think that's actually true. I think he's alive and well in Hell.
That was a rhyme. Don't know why I'm rhyming. I'm kind of crazy right now. I'm drinking a bunch of coffee.
So let's just go. Chapter 1. Well, yeah, Chapter 4, Episode 1. I don't even know what you'd call this, but let's just go. Boom!
Now, this is notoriously hard, Chapter... That's not where I'm supposed to go.
Chapter 4 is very difficult, so I'm hoping... Oh God.
I'm hoping I can just smoke through a lot of this.
But you know, Super Meat Boy, it is not an easy game.
Just by the skin of my teeth.
Just by the skin of my teeth, I'm gonna jump, jump, jump, jump.
Gotta be careful, gotta be careful.
I tried to jump off of it.
What the hell?
I didn't want to grab onto the damn edge there.
What just killed me?
I sandwiched myself against that wall.
That's fine.
Just barely. Holy crap.
Oh my God, my life.
This is where it's gonna get really hard.
This might be a freaking 50 minute episode.
I hope not. My sanity will be lost by then.
Just go!
Wait for it, wait for it.
It's right here! Oh, he took me!
I wanted my bacon.
Oh, I'm good here.
Maybe not.
The worst part...
The worst part about hell is the fact that a lot of these levels take patience.
You can't just speed through them, because sometimes you have to wait for stuff like these fireballs of doom.
And of course, these things.
Sweet.
But I'm not a patient guy, as I'm sure a lot of you are aware of by now.
Oh, hi!
A lot of you guys are probably aware of that.
That I am not a patient one.
I need to just go, and if I lose, I lose.
Alright, gotta be smart here.
Jump at the same time.
Hello, Suzy.
Leviathan.
I could have guessed that was gonna happen.
Wait for it.
Go!
Oh, I just overjumped it.
I overshot that by a lot.
Go! Just go!
Do I dare get this damn bandaid?
No, there's no way I'll get it.
I'm going for it anyways.
Stupid! No, stupid!
Go, get it. I'm gonna get it.
Get it!
Don't get it! Just forget it, go!
Oh, god damn it!
Jeez Louise.
It's so addicting to try and get these things.
I got it!
Just go!
I'm gonna get it. I have to get it.
I refuse to not get this bandaid.
Oh my dear god!
I'm going to shoot myself with a BB gun in my bum.
That's not very pleasant.
Time to end the level.
I'm getting to that point where the heat's turning up in my brain.
I'm gonna start to scream.
Just go. I'm not gonna do this anymore.
Let's just end the damn thing.
Rickets.
Oh, this place really, really sucks.
No!
You have to go like this.
Like that.
No!
Come on.
I don't got all day here.
Here we are.
Slide down.
I almost just jumped over her.
How did I get an A plus right there?
That doesn't make a whole lot of sense.
Just move it.
And shake it.
And move it.
And...
Not cool, Meat Boy.
Not cool.
I thought that was gonna move up higher.
Jump.
Wait.
I'm gonna burp in Meat Boy's face right now.
Crap.
Slow down. Slow down here.
What do these things do?
Just go.
Speed. It's all about the speed.
It's all about moving as fast as you freaking can.
What am I doing wrong here?
I need to get out there quick.
How am I supposed to...
I think you have to go like that.
Yeah, okay. I get it. I get it.
I'm just being a real stupid idiot.
No. No! No! No!
I'm gonna scream.
I'm going to scream.
I didn't do it fast enough.
Oh my god.
Can't wait to watch this one back.
Holy crap.
There we go.
Get. Me. Out of here.
No!
This is where the tears start flowing.
Oh my god. I'm going to throw up.
This is gonna be the one right here.
I'm just gonna go over it.
Wait.
Jump.
Jump over it.
And then, get over here!
Okay, let's watch this.
Everybody...
Oh my god. Look at that centipede of Meat Boys.
I want to...
Yeah.
40 to 50% all died on that first little thing.
Well, that's one way to do it.
Let's continue here.
The Deceiver.
Oh, that's right.
You have to just jump through like this.
And then, go like that.
Oh, that wall just screwed me over.
Can I get that bandaid?
If you have to fall into it like that.
If I remember correctly, what should I do?
I got it.
Let's go.
Just be safe here.
Don't do anything crazy.
You need that bandaid.
And this one is like this.
Get the key.
Gotta fall down.
Patience is a virtue.
I hate this part.
Whoa.
Wow.
Oh, wow.
Christopher Walken.
That's who I...
It's Alan...
Too busy doing like a bad Christopher Walken impression to play this game.
No, just fall down it.
Yeah.
Butt head.
I was too busy doing a bad Christopher Walken.
Okay, enough Christopher Walken.
Let's just play the damn game.
Oh, goodness me.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Be patient.
I hate being patient.
I did that with my mouth.
Don't worry.
Oh, my.
This is just going to get even worse.
I don't even know what's going to happen in the later levels.
I think we might actually see some germapuke.
Do it on this one, then go.
Now, don't hit your head on the damn ceiling.
Oh, my God.
Just do it.
Smell that?
It's called being really mad at this game.
I'm not really that mad, to be honest with you.
It's kind of fun dying in this game.
Only because you know you're going to be able to just do it again.
This time, I just undershot it that time.
I undershot it that time.
Will you just jump down there, you son of a beast sting?
The sting is going to be so strong when I sting you in your face.
Jump, jump, jump.
Now, get over here.
If I don't do it this time, I'm going to swallow my freaking mouse.
All right, here we go.
I got it.
It's down.
I don't know why I'm having such trouble with this one.
This one's not even that difficult.
You just have to jump into the damn hole.
Just jump into the damn hole.
Why is it so hard for me right now?
Why?
Thank you.
Let's see this.
I was going to say, did nobody get the key?
I wonder how many people die at this little ball.
At least one or two.
Please, we have to make it to the end.
Oh, no, no, please.
Goodness gracious.
What level are we on?
Eleven?
We're not even halfway there.
Oh, okay.
Oh, got to be quicker than that.
Up, up.
Now, I got to fall in the...
Quicker be quicker.
Just jump in.
Oh, my God.
Up, just like the movie, up.
This is what happens when I don't play this game for years, and then I try to...
I'm going to throw my controller against the wall.
It's going to smash.
How am I still missing this?
I'm going to smash my controller against the wall.
It's going to break into a...
Oh, God, I think you have to go like that.
Oh, it's getting harder.
I'll get out of here.
Oh, give me the key.
Do the same thing.
This time, go the other way.
Oh, my God.
Don't want to...
I remember this part.
You don't want to touch all these things because you have to do it again.
Oh, no, I forgot to get the key on this.
I'm not going to do it this run.
There's no way.
That's good to know.
You have to jump.
There you go.
There it is.
Now, just grab the key right when it falls.
Get it.
No, that was a trick I used to do, and I never got...
I can't get it.
Goodness.
Goodness me.
Up, up, and away we go.
Okay, now what?
I'm just going to wait.
Now go.
You know what?
Just kill me.
Just freaking kill me.
Go.
That one, that one.
I hit the ceiling again.
How many times am I going to hit the ceiling?
Way too many times I've hit that ceiling.
There it is.
Get me out of this level.
Easy.
Just get in there.
All right.
I'm going to play with command video here.
I remember command video did this quite well.
Up and around.
Oh, come on.
The jump didn't register that time.
Are you out of your freaking mind, dude?
Up away.
Oh, patience.
Just stand here.
Just wait.
Just be, be the meat boy.
Be the meat boy.
There it is.
Here we go.
Be the meat boy.
Yeah.
Oh.
Be the meat boy.
Round and round.
Wow.
That was very risky.
I should not have done that.
That was not a good move.
Get up here.
Oh my.
Let's go, boy.
There's my boy.
That's my boy right there.
Come here to video.
Maybe not.
He's a little too slow.
Come here to video.
Command.
This is what.
Go back to meat boy.
The noises are getting a lot stronger.
I can feel my blood boiling right now.
Oh.
Oh, no.
I will get it this time.
I just got it.
I just got to get this part correct.
Need to stay up there for a split second longer than I already am.
Why?
Why did that not work?
In all that is sacred.
Why?
Make your way up.
Oh, I'm definitely doing something wrong, and I just don't know what I'm doing wrong
right now.
Maybe I should just make a run for it up there.
Pull this thing back, I think, maybe?
Like this?
Like that?
Okay.
Exactly.
All right.
Figured it out.
Now it's just a question of getting over that.
Whew.
How many lives is that?
Half of them died.
I want to see this.
I want to see how many of them actually perished up here on this turn here.
Here we go, guys.
Wee.
I'm going here.
Go.
Oh, is this thing the thing that shoots the stuff all over the place?
This needs to fire me.
Come on.
Hello.
Wow.
I've got to stay up there a little longer.
Maybe not.
Yep.
That's how you do it.
What?
Oh, my God.
I hate this part.
I hate this.
Why?
Why are you doing this to me?
Okay.
Obviously.
Obviously, I need to jump first.
No, that's not what's the matter.
Yes.
No, it wasn't.
Oh, no, it wasn't.
God, I can't handle this.
I can't handle this.
I think I maybe have to stand still over here.
No, that just gets me killed again.
I think initially you got to do it.
Then you got to run.
Yeah.
Oh, dear.
Oh, my God.
I got through it, and it didn't even matter.
Wait for him.
Silent.
Silent anger.
All right.
Just wait.
This is not cool.
Get me out of here, please.
A plus, apparently.
After all that.
Oh, up here.
Easy.
Easy, breezy, beautiful cover girl.
I know that commercial.
I've seen that commercial before.
I'm just trying to not psych myself out.
There we are.
Good.
Getting close here.
I think there's only one or two more that I'm at the boss.
Please don't kill me.
Oh.
Oh, God.
He's relentless.
Please.
What?
I was out of range.
Oh, these things don't have range.
Oh, I was about to just say a very bad word right there, but I didn't.
Get away from me.
Here he comes.
Of course it's going to go in that spot.
Right where I'm landing.
Of course it is.
You hungry, hungry hippo.
You know, I was just standing there just blanking out.
I was just standing still saying to myself, I just stand here.
This is all right.
I'm safe.
The torture is almost over.
I'm almost through hell.
And then I have what's left?
Rapture?
Whatever it's called.
Okay, don't make that same mistake.
It's so much trouble to get through that.
Phew.
The hive.
Get me.
I have to wait till this is down.
Oh, it was down.
Almost down.
Why am I going through there?
Just wait till he jumps and then wait till he does it again.
Go.
Oh my God.
I just almost choked.
That's how much I'm raging right now.
Gotta be quiet.
That's the only way I can do this.
As if I'm just...
Stand still and jump over.
It's such an easy pattern.
Why can I not get it down?
My blood is just on fire right now.
I could just...
I'm going to...
I can't even think of words right now.
I'm so mad.
Just do it again.
Do it again.
Now go.
Just nice and easy.
This is it.
And then we're at the...
We're at the boss after this.
I remember this level.
This level is so terrible.
You have to...
This level is so long.
It requires so much patience, which I don't have.
Why did I try and get the bandaid?
I thought that was a key.
My puny brain thought that was a key.
I can't believe I did that.
Gotta stay confident here.
It's the last level.
I can't let this beat me.
Gotta push forward.
Can't let it beat me.
Come on.
Let's go.
And go.
One, two, tie my shoe.
Three, four.
What?
I wasn't even sticking out.
I could be mad right now, but that was just stupid.
I was barely sticking out right there.
Even Meat Boy is mad.
Look at him.
I'm so mad right now.
What?
What the hell is going on?
Just go.
Just get her.
This is it.
Time to play.
I have no idea how long this is going to take me.
Let's see, though.
What was that?
What the hell is going on?
What are these bodies doing falling down?
Dude, are you dead?
Weep, weep.
Dude, you gotta get up, man.
What the hell?
Okay, that plus Spike equals death.
Help me, please.
He's got me.
You'll never get away.
There's lava here, stupid.
Man, he's right.
There's lava.
Oh, look.
What the hell is that?
Oh, my goodness.
Okay, this is getting old.
Oh, he's mad.
I remember this part.
I remember what happens here.
This is really hard.
And he...
Oh, I remember this.
This is going to take forever.
This is going to take a million years.
Oh, guys.
I need to like...
Oh, no.
I'm so scared right now because he does this punch move.
Here it is.
Jump.
He does it again.
This is all about patterns here.
And he has to do that three times.
So then he punches once, twice, and then in the middle.
So, go for it.
One, two, middle.
One, two, three, two.
one two middle yep okay now what is he gonna do he's gonna punch the side and
he's gonna come over this way yeah he's gonna do it again no he doesn't jump no
so this might be a 97 minute long meat boy cuz this is gonna take a long time
to get this pattern down wait go so like six hours later well I'll see you like
breakfast tomorrow what are we gonna have bacon eggs cheese what we're gonna
have for breakfast tomorrow when this is done all right okay this is the one and
only time in this video well I'm going to be like totally silent okay here we go
smashes his head let's do this one more time I forget what he does here forget
what he does he goes left right does he I don't remember here we go good oh I
did it I did it I did it I did it yes oh oh my god okay here comes the cut
scene whoa jeez look at all these bodies oh my god what's up what's over
there what is that thing huh what oh I'm no
you're not getting away from me dude yeah yeah it was his girlfriend oh god
yeah that was your girlfriend see what I did there that was a trick I tricked
you oh I'm dead chapter complete so I almost lost my crap there guys there's
only one more I think real level after this let's see it's the Rapture yep and
then there's the two bonus levels oh well thank you guys so much for watching
and and I guess listening to my crazy rage talk because that was that got
pretty crazy in the middle there but thanks a lot guys for watching really do
appreciate it and we'll see you all next Monday meatball Mondays take care
everybody