Good afternoon. What's going on everybody? How are you?
Uh, right when I press the unmute button, there's a hundred community subs from an anonymous gifter.
An anonymous person just gave, uh, like a trillion dollars worth of money.
A hundred fucking community subs. Thank you for the hundred community subs.
If you missed the interview, that was fun.
I don't typically do stuff like that, but it was a really good time.
Tyler's a really good dude. We've, that was a plan for like the last year.
So there was a year in the making just about, or at least like six or seven months.
It's on Valve News Network right now, if you haven't seen it.
We go over deep shit. Like what my first name is.
Never heard that one before. But hello, I am back.
After another absence, I seem to be taking more absences than streaming these days.
And I do apologize for that, but you know,
shit, you got to deal with shit half shit happens, right? You got life happens, right?
So we were making a return to the 3DO. I was going to do two 3DO days in a row.
I did one and then I took off for a week.
But I'm here now. Good to go. Excited because the game we're about to play
is a game that this is like, what's the, this is going to suck because I'm going to say this.
And then everyone's going to be including me is going to be pissed off when this is the worst
game of the entire lot. Cause this is why I got the 3DO.
The next three games that you're going to see are the reason why I got this thing.
So let's hope they're okay.
An absolute shitload of community subs are coming in right now and I am going to address them.
Oh, that's a lot.
Non-descript civilian 10, John Cena is kill five, IA Elliot five, non-descript another 10,
Jamie two, eight, oh three, five, seven from nocturne, six from mystic quests,
and then $50 from Dupa, 5,000 bits. Thank you guys for the extreme amount of money.
It's, I hope I use it well. I really do. I say that a lot, but I really mean it.
Is it going to play plumbers without ties? I don't know. Maybe, maybe I'll have like a porn day.
I'm not, that's no, we're not going to do a porn day, but you know what I mean? We'll do like a
porn day. Hey, 3DO week, PS1 week. Oh, PS2 classics. My favorite porn videos.
I don't think that would go over very well. Porn day. Yeah. All of my favorite,
it would only fit in one day, right guys? Who the fuck are we kidding? Don't even try to kid
yourself either. A porn day? No, take like three weeks. Oh, porn day. Sure. Nice lie.
I just punched the microphone accidentally too. All right. Are you ready to do this?
Are we ready to get another hundred community subs? This is ridiculous. There's no reason for
this. There's no reason for this. You guys are giving me too much money. A hundred more community
subs from PQR? That's another hundred. That's too many. That is 100 too many, but I will gladly
take it and say thank you. That's an extreme amount of money. You spent $500. Do that. That's
a lot of fucking money. Let's move over to the game because I am ready for it. There it is.
Jurassic Park Interactive. This is going to be just as fun as the ride that's at Universal Studios
and the ride is not very good. So hopefully this is okay. It's the same ride. I think I actually
think it's just the ride on a disc and I'm starting to realize that right now, but no way.
The back of the box does not show that at all. We're getting so many community subs. I can't
even keep up with them. This is fucking crazy. AGB Clown 10, Obstinarwhal 6, Technic Stars 5,
Philip Rivers 10, Crank Elm 5, Habbie 5, Little Hat 5, Ink Cat 5. This is too much money. You guys
are spoiling me. You don't need to do this. It's okay. I really appreciate it though. Thank you,
everybody. Jurassic Park Interactive. Here we go. Do I do normal, intermediate, or advanced?
It's not going to be advanced. It's going to be A or B. It's just going to be A, right?
I can't do advanced. I'll do B. B sounds fine. You ready? Oh, I can't wait. I can't wait till
Jon Hamm shows up and tells me about what we have to do. What's his name? Hammond, Hammond,
Hammond, Hammond. That's his name, right? What do we do? Okay. Security systems, animal systems,
engineering, security systems, security systems. That's Jon Hamm. Select tracking location.
Who is this? Dr. Ellie Sattler, Dr. Alan Grant, Robert Muldoon. Oh shit. These are
breakfast cereal actors for the actual actors, aren't they? Oh no. Dr. Ian Malcolm. Select
destination. Oh shit. Okay. Is that supposed to be me? All right. We're going to go to the
Brachiosaurus pen. What? What was that? Malcolm is surrounded by spitters. Help him out of the
jungle. You have a taser weapon. Charge it wisely. It has... What the fuck? How do I move? Oh shit.
All right. I got to charge this up and shoot it. Why did he run in here? What was the point?
My health. I think I'm going to die. There was some team rockets right there. Okay.
No. The screen's going black. I'm dead. Sorry. You did not make it. There may be more stranded
guests and staff. Check your computer. What is Malcolm dead? All right. What about... Hold on.
Animal systems. Animal systems. Select tracking location. Holy shit. This is a large game.
Okay. Wait. We're going to find my favorite dinosaur. That could be me in the costume.
We have to see. All right. Velociraptor. Let's go. Animal tracking. All right. So the
Velociraptor is here. Okay. So let's go to security systems. Security systems. Select
tracking location. Here we go. Okay. Tim and Lex. Don't put the kids in with the Velociraptor.
Select destination. A Raptor pen? Displaying video. Why am I putting kids in a... Am I playing
roller coaster tycoon or like planet zoo? What am I doing? I don't get it. Lex and Tim are trapped
in a park building. Help them find their way out. You will need to find the keys to get through the
locked doors. Raptors are here. Is this an FPS now? Are the kids with me? Okay. This is actually kind
of fucking scary. Do I have a punch? Okay. But what am I supposed to do? Is he chasing me?
He's not very fast. Okay. So let's just keep going. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. There's only
one, right? What happens if he touches you? Do you get killed? Lock five. Lock six. I have one key.
Oh shit. There's the... I got to make this a little suspenseful. Does he not care anymore? Oh,
fuck it. Didn't work. I couldn't open the door. Okay. That's really, that's clearly a guy in a
mask. That's great. That was just a guy in a mask. That was a guy in a mask from like Spirit of
Halloween. All right. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Sensor registers no life signs.
Oh, there he is. Jon Hamm. Select destination. Jon Hamm. Let's go to... Let's go to your house
and just hang out. Displaying video. Camera malfunction. Uh-oh. Hammond is trapped in a
park building. Help him find his way out. You need to find the keys. Oh, give me a break.
You will need to find the keys to get through. All right. They all locked in these weird, like,
hostile dungeons. But where do I find the keys? I don't want to do this. Is it... Wait. I hope to
God it's not a raptor. I hope it's another bitmap image of another dinosaur. It's better not be
a velociraptor. All right. Hold on. Oh shit. There we go. Maintenance area. The fuck just happened?
What? You open the... I have to close the door? Everyone's gonna die. Literally no one's gonna
make it out alive. No one's gonna make it out. Shit. The ride is more fun than this. Oh no.
What have I done? The ride is way more fun. All right. Engineering. Engineering systems.
Engineering systems locked out. What do you mean locked out? What are you talking about? Security.
Level one security. Access permitted. Okay. What does that get me? It's a music player?
Okay. You must score 20,000 points to enter the next security level.
That's not even a spitter. That's a gremlin. This... Am I hacking the game? What's supposed
to be hacking the computer? Like Newman does, right? I'll be... I'm gonna... Actually, I'll be...
What do I need? 10,000? 20,000 points? I'll get it. This is the shit that the guy at the security
system is doing. No. This is not unlocking security shit. This is what the security guard is doing.
He's on miniclip.com all day. All right. 10,000? What is it? 20,000? Who's the guy? Is that
supposed to be Newman? That's supposed to be Newman, right? Whatever his name is in the
universal dress park. What is it? I really hope security clearance two is not this again,
but with other pictures. He's the best security in the world. Could be better. Okay. 20,000 is
coming. You can still shoot when you're dead, by the way. Now, that's the real glitch way to win.
20,000. Okay. So, should I just die? Just let the things kill me because I get to 20,000?
What the... All right. Just kill me. I got to 20,000. It's 30,000? It's 30,000 points? Oh,
my God. Thank God. No, no, no. I can't die here. Okay. Actually, I'm going to stick the fuck up
and play well. I don't want to die. I'll get it here, right? I'll get it right here.
I did it. Level two. Level two security. Access permitted. Yeah, I got level two access.
You unlocked Winnie the Pooh Baseball. Oh, it actually is Winnie the Pooh. It's just
Flashgate. Okay. All right. 20,000. You know, I'm going to do it because why not?
Gallagher. It's actually kind of fun, though. All right. I'm curious. I want to sit here for a
little bit. Chex quest? It's hard to dodge that. The screen's tiny. Please stop. No, not yet. I
have to get to level... I got to get security clearance level five. And then after security
clearance level five, I'll open John Hamm's door. I'll at least save... I got to save one person.
Okay. The back of the CD has like you riding in a car and the T-Rex chasing you. Spoilers,
but this franchise is like 25 years old at this point. How do I do that?
Did it. Okay. All right. Move up to level three. Why is he a pirate now?
Level three security. Access permitted. What am I doing this for? I don't know what I'm doing it
for. I'm playing Ong versus a dinosaur. I don't want to do this one. I like don't actually want
to play this one. Wait, why is it just turning into the guy from dinosaurs, the TV show? Remember
that show? It was like the Muppets. They were the big puppet dinosaur things. Didn't that show end
really horribly, too? Like a fucking meteor hit the earth or something at the end of the last
episode? Something horrible, right? Yeah. Yeah. No, something horrible did happen.
That's really fucked up. I still love the baby. The baby was the best. By the way, every single
family oriented cartoon with a family of people was all based on dinosaurs. Family guy,
Simpsons. They all came after dinosaurs. The big fat, the big fat dad who's kind of dumb,
but he means well. The baby, that kid has magical powers and is funny and is sinister.
Simpsons fucking copy dinosaurs. I just lose. I got 20,000 Flintstones. Oh, they got inspiration
from the Flintstones, not the other way around. It's a woke take. I don't want to play anymore.
Just let me just get the security level five. I'm trying to lose. Hold on. This is even the
dinosaurs theme song. This is the shit that plays when the big dinosaur guy is driving his car to
work. Okay. Security level five. I'm going to do this. Level four security access permitted.
Do the baby impression. And the baby kind of loved me. Then I do a poop in my pants.
Something like that, right? You might actually think I'm making that part up. He actually says
that part. He actually says what I just said. I didn't read this. Oh shit. Yeah. Let's respect
nature and the dinosaurs. Arm the laser cannon and shoot them. All right. What is the 20,000?
Spawn cam, spawn cam, spawn cam. Fix it. Fucking Activision. Fucking idiots. Did I do my good,
like fake, like pissed off thing? You guys like that? Did you like it? Why move? I got this all
wrong. Why move at all? I think they just keep spawning. Yeah. This sort of reminds me of what
a really over enthusiastic history teacher would do. Like a science teacher. This is like an
over enthusiastic science teacher's little side project that the kids get to play for like 15
minutes at the end of class. And although you don't think it's very fun, you don't have to
listen to him talk. So this is the alternative and it's better. This game probably took dozens
of people to make. Yeah. The 3DO is awesome. I love this thing. I'm going to wrap this thing
up. I'm going to laminate my 3DO and I'm never touching it ever again after this.
3DO sucks. No, it doesn't. 3DO is pretty fun. They made this in Microsoft Publisher.
It's probably made in Adobe director or something. I have to die now. All right. It's fun. What do
you get for doing this though? That's why I have to do this. Does he know the 3DO sucks? It doesn't
though. This is fun. Interactive media. All right. Level five. This is it. Security clearance level
five. Level five security access permitted. What's the number five? Okay. This is wrap attack.
Oh no. No. The science teacher roped in the math teacher to make their own and showed him how easy
it was. How are we going to play the same game next period? 20,000. And then what? It's just
asteroid. What? Horrible. You can die by the fan. What's with the environmental damage? It's not
cool. NA classes. Don't you guys know what NA classes were? Wheel the TV in, play a movie,
or look at this cool shitty thing that one of the teachers made and we're all going to exploit for
the next six weeks? Or get everybody into the gym to sit there and here's an assembly for two hours.
I don't think we learned anything. I don't think I learned anything. No, no, no. You know, you know,
I learned how to go to the bathroom really fucking fast because apparently if you took more than one
minute to go to the bathroom, you were like a terrible student. That's what I learned in an
NA education. Can I go to the bathroom? Yes, you can. But hurry the fuck up. Okay. Okay. Yeah. I'll
pee pee and it hurts. It hurts. I'm peeing as hard as I can. It hurts. Get out of the bathroom. Oh,
what are you doing in the hall? I decided to go to the bathroom. Yeah. Prove it. Okay. I'm going
to go back to class. Get back there. That's what I learned. And then all of a sudden one of the
exits would open. It's like one of the bad kids. Hey, man, you want to skip class and go to X-Men?
No, no, I'm okay. Yeah, I do. But no. Did I get level two? This is sick. You are a loser.
Just shut up. There was always that group that like, and guess what? There were people that I knew
that weren't like friends with them necessarily, but like you knew some of these people that were
in like your class or something. They'd walk into class and they would just smell like the bottom
of a bowl. You know what I mean? Just like, oh, yeah, you must have, okay. All right. That's
what you were just doing somewhere, I guess. That is a marijuana reference. It's just like,
oh, yeah. All right. Well, hey, what do you think? Good? Yeah, I'm all right. I'm good. Cool.
CVD. This actually can't be what NA education is. No, that wasn't the teacher. That was not the
teacher. The teacher sits down and it smells like weed. Hey, how you doing, kids? Hey, hey,
you want to go see, hey, fuck this class. You all want to go see X-Men? Who wants to go, hey,
who wants to go see X-Men? Why does everybody have to turn into Mr. Satan? All right. You do,
all right. You do know what to do next, do you? No, I don't. Access permitted to all. Oh shit. I
was supposed to do that. Rebooting systems. What? Alert. I was supposed to do that. That was return
to priority one command. Return to Isla Nublar priority one command. Will comply. ETA 16 hours.
Two crewmen lost. And two kids, right? Two kids as well. I know you don't want to take the blame
for that. But that's what happened. Two kids are dead too. Okay. Is that what I need to do?
Level five security access permitted. Wait, we just go right to level five security clearance?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
just crash into stuff. How am I still alive? So many community subs are coming. Oh my fucking God.
I can't even read all these. There's so many. Destroy dude five.
Chungi five. Jerma sucks five. Tiger fam five. No flaw. That's a zero on there. I didn't see the
zero. That's 50 community subs from tiger fam. Holy shit guys. Another, I, you guys, this is like
600 subs over the last 15 minutes. Thank you tiger fan for the 50. That's insane.
Add Dan. Thanks to the five and Coilia is gamer. Thanks to eight. Please just let me die.
Why can I not crash? Will we ever make him cry again? I don't have a reason to cry right now.
Okay. Get me out of here. Now, what does that, like, what does that do for me? All right. There's
Dr. Alan Grant. Select destination. He's in the restroom. Wait, he's just in the bathroom?
Garage. Garage. Time for the car. Displaying video. Okay. Is this security feed of Jurassic
Park or is this security feed of like people running away from the house when like your,
when like dad gets home? Like you had somebody over that wasn't supposed to be there and they
like snuck out the window. Help grant to safety. Use the explorer to get to the next safe location.
Oh my God. Save game soundtrack on. Sound effects on. Timelapse. Warned. Why am I getting a
mirror view? Right. Steering is L and R. Okay. Brake. Accelerate. Turn.
Turn. Mirror. Steering is L and R. What? Wait, he's already right there. He's already right behind
us. Oh shit. I ran over some twigs. Objects in mirror are closer than they appear. Rab, really?
Do you really need, I know the dinosaur is huge. Holy shit. He's right there.
Okay. Did I crash? It did great. Go through the windshield or did the T-Rex eat us? I don't know.
Okay. He's dead. Those kids are dead. John Hammond is dead. What about the weird guy?
Select destination. Okay. Should I go in the shed? Back to the garage? How about shed two?
Displaying video. It's going to be him running. Yeah. Where is that son of a bitch? I know he
was in here. You can't lie to me, Cindy. I know that little fucking asshole was here. I told you
not to have him in my house. You have a taser. Oh my God. Not this shit again. No. How am I
supposed to kill all these things? All right. He's dead. They're all running into the woods
and dying because I can't save them. Guess when? I can't. Is there anybody left on the island?
Should I just leave? This was just a really complicated VR. Okay. Robert Muldoon. This is
the guy that's like, she's got you. Run. Right? Select destination. All right. What about the
Brachiosaur pen? I don't think we, did we go there? Restroom. T-Rex. All right. We got some
choices here. T-Rex paddock. Restroom. Or the Brachiosaur pen. I don't want to, this is going
to be another velociraptor is just in the shed. T-Rex paddock. Toilet. All right. Toilet. Displaying
video. Camera malfunction here. Muldoon is trapped in a, in the bathroom. Help him find his way out.
You need to find your, oh, it's this shit again. It's this shit. It's the stupid thing. He's trapped
in the bathroom. Okay. Well, whatever. I'm just going to go here and just run. I'm, he's always
right behind you. Just go. Run. Walk to, I don't know. Just run. It's high voltage. Drop that on
him. He'll electrocute him, right? I don't, can I drop it? Oh shit. Nice. Okay. He's going to,
he'll get killed. He's not going to be right here, is he? Oh shit. It's just a big, drop it, drop it,
drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop,
drop, drop it. Oh my, what? He was waiting for me on the other side of the door. He wasn't running
around. Oh, clever girl. They're all dead. Whatever. I'm going, I want to go to the T-Rex pen and just
like take photos. Who else is alive? Oh wait, Dr. Ellie Sattler. Everyone else is dead. Okay. We have
to save Ellie. At the breast room. No. At the Raptor pen. Oh my fucking God. Raptor pen. Displaying
video. There's a lot of people leaving out of this person's room late at night, apparently. There's
a lot of people leaving. How much footage of people like running away from the house do you have
here? Already? Okay. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Drive. I have the fucking dinosaur bones in the middle
of the road. All right. 1.4. 1.3. Okay. I have to drive 1.3 miles. This is going to take forever.
I have to save one person. I have to save Dr. Ellie. Come on. This is my favorite character.
When she puts her hand on the Triceratops's belly and says goodbye. Oh, that was such a touching
moment for us all. What? This is impossible. It's not possible to drive. It's impossible.
It's not possible. It's impossible. I should have done normal. Okay. Dude, you didn't do very well
saving people. You did notify the cargo ship in time. Rating Brachius. How did I notify the
cargo ship? Is that the computer hacking? What's going on? Why did he move? His face just moved.
His face just moved. Okay. Well, that was Jurassic Park Interactive. It was the science teacher.
There he was. Okay. Let's move on. Let me just make, let me just take this out. I liked that one.
It was terrible, but I loved it. Did I miss anything in it? Oh, we saw it all. We saw it all.
Nothing else to say really. Well, you can, while I get the next CD, you can watch the intro video.
It's pretty cool. Hey, Kalissa. Coming up next, we have something that I just want to get out of the
way because I know that it is going to be, it's not going to be very good, but it doesn't matter.
Next one is called Club 3DO Station Invasion On The Air. This is a, this is like Nickelodeon
Magazine, the CD. That's how I can describe it, the way it looks. Wait, is this just the actual
intro to Jurassic Park? I didn't even watch this. Oh yeah. No, no, I know what this is. Yeah.
This is torrent underscore zero four four two point one zero underscore torrent Jurassic Park
full movie underscore one one one one underscore two. Jurassic Park, located on an island off the
coast of Costa Rica, was conceived and built by John Hammond. Hammond, an extremely wealthy
dinosaur fanatic and his company InGen Corporation, leased the island of Isla Nublar from the
government. Okay, you already know the story. Let's play Station Invasion Club 3DO. You're going to
get bars across your screen. Just want to make sure you wear that 3DO just through the way that's
getting captured. It's going to be like incoming in about three seconds. Three, two, maybe not.
Just do it. Anyway, I did air. All right, coming up here comes Station Invasion Club 3DO.
No idea. I don't even know why I got this. In the inside cover, there's a dog with a suit on.
So, I got high hopes. Show dog. I will. Hold on. Let me just get it in. God, I love this 3DO.
Let's go. Show auto. No, not right now. He's sleeping behind me. This one's kind of...
Can you hear that disc chugger? It's going... It's like a PlayStation 3. I almost said 2.
All right, Club 3DO Station Invasion. Awesome start. Here's at the TV station. Kids.
Oh, it must have been really fucking failing. It must have been free.
I know my ratings haven't been that great, Mary Lee, but the babes still dig me, huh?
He's not talking about... Who is that young man over there?
Wait, what? That's Jake Smits, the...
Look at that shoe in there. That is an elaborate fucking shoe.
Obnoxious little bugger, isn't he? Wait, Mary, don't you want to ask me some more questions?
Let's do lunch sometime. Okay, now get rid of that guy. No, get rid of that guy.
Why not? So you're the new president? That I... Do you have any... No, we're going to hire some
new blood in here. We're going to take the top five shows and put the top producer on each one.
Am I going to be a producer? These kids will be the best.
But I'm not a kid. I mean, who knows TV better than us kids?
That's a good point. How about some new recruits coming in today that look real promising?
Me. Well, we wish you the best of luck, Jake.
Thanks, Mary. Maybe we can do lunch sometime? Yeah, that makes more sense.
Why are they all the same dialogue, though? Why does everything have to end in
let's do lunch sometime? It's just the writer just didn't care. I always had to end a sentence.
Even if it was like a 40-year-old talking to an 11-year-old.
Like, I just looked at lunch sometime. I don't know how to end sentences.
I love this board. This is awesome.
It's got a baseball bat, too.
Abuse adults? Like, just like let's torture adults? The network?
Hi, I'm Billy Sparks, the star of the sitcom, I'm Grounded. I play a guy,
also named Billy Sparks, coincidentally, who's always either grounded or getting grounded,
with the good help of my friend, Igor. I get into a lot of trouble, but it's not my fault.
I'm just misunderstood. I'm Bryce Banyan, host of the show,
Mystery Smistries. We answer all life's burning questions. What happened to the missing sock?
Why is there always one shoe lying at the side of the road? I don't think of Mystery Smistries as a
show, as much as I think of it as a journey. Okay.
Do we get to do all these things? Do we have to like play these mini-games or something,
or do these shows?
Okay.
And my new best friend. Okay, this is important. This is the biggest decision of the whole day,
but I gotta pick my show and my new best friend.
I think, yeah, Mystery Smistries.
Too desperate. Way too desperate.
There's only one show for you, and that's Sundays of Our Lives.
I'm not a big fan of like Sundays, really.
Right, okay, yeah, that's to the point and incredibly accurate.
I like having fun.
I mean, he's like, okay.
No, I don't. I don't.
I don't.
Mystery.
Oh, okay, my name is B.
Up to 10 letters? How much is E?
This is like freaking me out. I thought that was a Y. All right, let's go. Like difficulty.
Easy. Or not easy. Easy. This is a game for children, right? This is a game for kids.
How about hard? This is a good beat. I like this track. I'm gonna pick it by the music.
What is it? Let's go here. I'm ready to produce my TV show.
It's up to you. Press A for complete game. Press B for fast game or press C.
Listen, what is a complete game?
First week of Kid TV begins. There's a dog with a tie on.
Mystery Smystery is produced by Jeremy.
We need a lot of tomato juice for tomorrow's episode on why tomato juice is used to get rid
of the smell of skunk. We need to figure out how much we need and how much it will cost.
There's a lot more to do before tomorrow. I didn't pick the smell TV one. I'm actually
a little irritated about this Mr. Mystery Smystery. I thought we're going to be solving mysteries,
not smelly puke stuff. Use the joy pad to choose a number block and the A button to rotate it.
Solve all three problems and press C when done.
Oh, shit. Wait, is math wrong? Two, seven, uh.
Twelve, six divided by. Where's the three? No, where's the?
I didn't lose yet. I need a four. Six, four divided by one divided by four is four. Where's the one?
Sixteen, four, eight, twelve, sixteen, four, eight, twelve, six. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Eight, eight, twelve, six, twelve. I don't know. Six, seven divided by two, four, six,
eight, ten, twelve. Okay, now we got thirty-two, thirty-nine.
Twelve divided by. No, what is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it?
What is it? What is it? What is it? Twelve? No, no, it's like eight. It's like three. What is it?
What is it? It's three. Yeah, he's smart as hell. Jeremy gained six points. That would be the
Ukulaka tribal victory dance. Feel free to join in at any time. How is this a mystery?
This is doing shitty math problems. It sure was an exciting week for television, don't you think?
Look at the ratings for the week. Come on, you got to put two human hands up like, like Swedish
chef style. This is just a, this is Mario Party, but it, this is the twisted game, but with kids.
Let's look at a clip from one of this week's top shows. All right, here we go.
People pick their noses when they get in their car. It's not like we can't see them. Why do they
do it? What luck. We just caught Dak Jones. Not if you have tinted windows. I wasn't picking.
I had an itch. Isn't a guy allowed to scratch an itch anymore? What's this guy doing over here,
by the way? I did it. Is that what you want to hear? Yep. I don't think it's that gross.
Well, we brought a gross meter with us, Dak. Gross meter. Let's just see how your pick score.
It's a two out of 10. Those meters don't prove anything. No, they don't. They aren't even accepted
in a court of law. That's bullshit. No, no, no, no, no, no. I disagree. Disagree. That's a one or
a two out of 10. I hate you. Now if he ate it, it would have been an eight. He didn't though.
What is that guy? That guy in the background at the newspaper stand is scaring me. He's freaking
me out. Where are the cue cards? They're all gone. I never remember my lines. You have to help me.
I know you're not a script writer, but you're going to have to be for today.
And what does that entail? Let's see. Select each word requested by using the joy pad and the A
button. These mad libs? I'm pretty good at these. All right. Pick a verb. Verb. Okay. Creepy. Pizza.
A verb. Smuggles. Scatters. Cleans. Syrupy. Hot. Hot can be a verb, right? How about cleans?
Clean is a verb. You're cleaning something. Clean. Pick an adjective. Adjective. Stale.
Pick a verb. Verb. I have one second left. Wow. That wasn't very good, was it?
I didn't realize there was a timer. Agree, John. This week was fabulous. Look at the ratings.
You're not even going to bark? You lost it. I thought it was mad libs. I didn't think it was
actually get it correct. Couldn't agree more. Better be mine. No. I don't want to watch this shit.
Do you think it's interesting that in the kids TV where they want to get rid of all the adults,
all the kids just pretend to be adults? It's weird, right? That kid had mustache hair? Yeah,
good. Mustache hair is going to become a big trend sooner or later and then everyone's going
to look back and be like, wow, I know where that started. This guy. All right. Now I understand.
It's vocabulary. The art director quit. She just quit. She says she's not appreciated.
I'll go have a talk with her. In the meantime, you have to take over. I don't know anything
about art. Do the best. Neither do I. You're asking the wrong person. All right. Select two
pieces to exchange using the joy pad and the A button. Press the C button when done. What do
you mean? George Frederick Handel, water music. Oh, okay. It's one of these.
George Frederick Michelson, waterbender.
Get this big ass hair. I don't. George Frederick Handel's water music was performed on a boat for
King George, the first of England. Nice. We're going to get our show on TV today. What can I
say? You're the best. Thanks, man. Yes. And it was the same clip twice in a row. That's how you can
tell it was even better. All right. Let's get, let's see what we got on TV. I thought that was
funny. You did too. I don't care if it's 11 year olds that I laughed at it. I don't care. Hey,
how many of you guys used to have contests? So who could throw that fucking exact football
as far as possible? It didn't even play catch. Wow. That's great. Hey, you want to come up?
There's a ladder over there. It's just a bunch of fucking eighth graders blow out their arms,
trying to one up each other. Betty Primrose. Just what do you think you're doing on that ladder?
What? Hi, Mr. Sparks. Guess what? This is the angry dad. A thousand times and never gets caught.
Betty has to come over once. Wait. Once. That's the thing that was happening in Jurassic Park.
A dog. I love that dog. Okay. Fourth week of kid TV season. When do we get canceled?
On week five. There's some problems that need to be solved. Get to work.
Okay. What problems? Match an animal with its proper classification by using the joy pad and
the apron. Oh dear. This is not going to go well. Choose a mammal. Mammal. Okay. Mammal is,
that's an elephant. Choose an insect. That is a fly. Choose a fish. That is a goldfish.
Choose an amphibian. That would be a frog. Choose a bird. A bird. That would be a chicken.
Choose a reptile. Reptile. That would be a turtle. That was easy. That was a very respectable
performance. Why was I talking as? Why was I talking like that was impressive?
Billy Madison. I'm like sitting in a third grade class as a 35 year old.
That's a turtle. I win. I'm smarter than all these children.
Like Jeremy, we don't win in class. Oh wow. You sure? I do. As usual,
we follow the ratings chart with a clip. Smarter than a fifth grader.
Do a Jerma Madison stream. That would take a lot of convincing. Do you understand?
What's he holding? What the hell is this thing? This is not a real thing, right? Isn't this the
thing you skipped over? What is this supposed to do? What is that supposed to be doing?
One by by. We take cash. If it gets lost in the mail, it's not our fault. What the hell was that?
Did you put a thing around your waist? What was that thing called? Skip it. Skip it. What's the
song called? The thing that used to trip a bunch of kids. What was that thing called?
We need a lot of tomato juice for tomorrow's episode on why tomato juice is used to get
rid of the smell of skunk. We need to figure out how much we need and how much it will cost.
Yeah, how many of you guys used to cheat with the skip it? You just put the hoop under one
of your ankles and you spun it as fast as you possibly could to try to get like a thousand
points by cheating. Oh shit, I went and said, what does three point 45 minus four, I don't know.
I don't know. The cashier does this for me. I don't do this. They just tell me a number.
Uh, one, one 20, just three point two, four plus four point two, five plus one.
That's that would be four, five, six, six, uh, 24, six, seven, uh, seven, six, five.
What's this three? That's four, three, two, four, six, three, three, six, three, 75.
Some mysteries are tougher than others. You know that that was a tough one.
Wasn't even tough. The cashier does that for you. None of you guys could just do that right now.
Sean, you're just cool. Is there a new gal in your ratings?
What was that? What is that? That was a big cat puke. Stop pretending. I'm not. I'm just
hanging out, man. That was a dog puke. Let me roll a slip from one of those shows.
Oh, that smell. Smell. Shitty TV show. Remember folks, Mr. Slugs is doing this in one whiff.
You'll never get this one. I'm the champ. I'll get it. What is that stuff? That's disgusting.
Want one more whiff? It's a fucking. I'm not going near that jar again.
Mr. Jones, it's your. And she stole a gangrene in his toe.
That means he was decomposing right on the person's body.
They had to amputate this guy's toe and my sister stole it.
There's a lot of wrong with what he was talking about.
That was super. And John, I'm going to get you to talk about your.
Way too many things wrong with that. Okay, so you stole somebody's toe from a hospital.
Okay, that's felony one. Then you put it into a jar. That's serial killer one.
And then you made somebody smell it. That's both felony and serial killer combined at
the same time. So every felony to serial killer to see if cows get lonely when they get lost from
the herd. Isn't that ridiculous or waste of money? Of course they do. Who wouldn't?
Anyway, we want to conduct our own tests, so we need to fly all around the country.
We'll need maps, information about different cities, states and a bunch of other junk.
Now that's where you come in. Information is your middle name.
I don't know these. I don't. Nobody does. People that pretend to be or see button to
all right. I know where every major city is in the entire state of Delaware.
I don't fucking have any idea which of the above states was the first to
ratify the United States Constitution. I don't know if Delaware.
Now that was a mystery to be said. I said to get that right.
I'm proud. Jeremy, you really don't know what the third capital of Delaware is.
Didn't like it. He really didn't like it. He hated it. He doesn't like this week at all.
Just me slapping myself missing socks. For years, people had their theories.
Perhaps they were stuck to the wall of the washing machine or dryer.
Maybe you dropped one on your way to the laundromat. Or maybe there's a little man
or woman possibly related to whoever turns the light off in the refrigerator when you
close the door. And maybe that person likes to mess with our minds. They're taking socks
one at a time just to screw us up. Or maybe we're not losing socks at all.
Maybe we're gaining new socks one at a time. That's some 500 IQ shit right there.
Maybe we're just gaining them one at a time. I don't know why I just thought that headline
was going to say that they were fired for something like a scandal of kid TV.
Person that put severed toe in jar somehow turned out to be a fucking criminal.
How much water do we need? Why so much grape juice? These are bonafide mysteries, my friend.
I've said it a million times and I'll say it again. Research is everything on this show.
Let's go do some. I'm ready. Use the joy pad and the A button to select letters and
unscramble the correct answer. Press B to erase and C when done.
Unscramble a word. What is the angular distance measured in degrees east or west of the prime
meridian called the equator? The angular distance measured in degrees east of or west.
Long deep to it. Longitude. It's not longitude. It's longitude. I thought it was longitude.
All the mysteries. Now, you know, I thought it was longitude, longitude,
not longitude. I thought it was longitude. Longitude, not longitude.
Like a long L O N G D I T U D E longitude, longitude. I'm still in first place.
That's not pretending. I promise. I think I'm pretending. I thought it was longitude.
Parsley flavors. Sure. Whatever. You're a snake.
Whatever do you mean? Betsy Skinner said she saw you and Nick at the movies last night.
Your anger seems a little misdirected, Parsley. Perhaps it's yourself you should be scolding for
not keeping him on a better leash. Just watch your back, Angelica Dujour. When you least expect it,
I'm gonna- You'll do nothing. You are but a small speck of dandruff on my shoulder that I just flick-
Oh, you have dandruff? Disgusting. I'm gonna spread that around the class as a rumor now.
Oh, no, don't. I'm kidding. So there. Terrific. Somebody needs to prove the press releases that
are going out. The press release gives the critics updated information about our show.
Could you look them over and fix any words that don't belong?
No, kid. All of the words on the screen are the same part of speech.
Choose the word on the next screen that is that same part of speech.
Roll nouns, okay? All right, so I found a noun. Compute planet.
Come on, kid. Learn from the best. Is this guy still picking his nose?
Is he still the nose picker? I miss the Star Wars game. We'll see it again.
It's been an hour? Yeah, I'm still interested. I gotta get to the end.
Meet people. This is every show on Nickelodeon now.
Hey there. I was driving by and I couldn't help but notice your fabulous voice. Have you ever
thought about playing Vegas? I'm a big agent. No, no, don't lump this guy in with Vegas.
You could be the next Inklebert Humperdink. Better yet, the next Elvis.
We could leave right now. What do you say? Really shitty security system around this place,
by the way. There's a laugh track. There's a laugh track on this. This is horrible. This is
like terrifying. Hey mom, can I go with a stranger? He's not going to take me in his car. Why are they
laughing at this? This is fucking horrendous. In our show, the music is really important.
It creates a mood and an atmosphere that is essential. We need to find more music. We've
been using the same stuff for weeks. Would you mind going down to the music library and checking
it out? Thanks. All right, let's do some music. Use the joy pad and the A button to select the
three instruments playing the melody. Yeah, I can do this. That doesn't sound like any...
Hey, so this is not just me going like... That's an oboe? I don't know. I don't... That's a piano.
French horn. Almost. One time I got hit in the head with a baseball and my coach told
me to shake it off. I'm not quite sure what he meant, but I offer that advice to you.
Shake it off. You okay? When did this happen? Yesterday? Or like a couple of years ago?
They work all hours of day and night. And let me tell you, their work is paying off. These shows
aren't great. Let's look at... I'm almost there. Week nine. Come on, get me to a hundred.
Fifty. It's gonna be fifty. What happened to the dog? I don't know. Yeah, where's the dog?
Where's the dog? Where's the dog? Maybe another weird like fitness thing?
...by Jake Smith, president of the newly founded KidTV, which you're watching right now. He's also
my boss. Hi, Jake. Hi, Silva. Tell us, what made you decide to run a television station?
Well, a bunch of us kids decided we could do anything if we put our minds to it,
so we started finding good clean ways of making money. We rode lawns, sold lemonade,
cookies... The intro again. Eventually, we raised enough money to do something
real big. And we didn't like the old TV station that used to be here,
so we took it over and made it our own. I think we did a good job, don't you? Absolutely. I'm
proud of the work we've done. Is there any message you would like to send out to kids with dreams of
grandeur? Yes. I'd like kids to remember they could do anything they want if they just put
their minds to it. Anything. If you could dream about it, you could do it. Good segment. Good
segment, son. Superlative. Oh, thank God. There's John. He's fine. Sweep's week begins. What a sweep
week. Uh-oh. Another adult got in. Uh-oh. Well, I had originally called you all here to tell you
about Sweep's week, but it seems I have some other unfortunate news to announce.
Dac Jones apparently has broken in and vandalized the station. What? Stolen property from us
and generally wreaked havoc on Kid TV. So let's kick his ass. This is going to make your jobs a
lot tougher in the next week. Everything you do will be worth triple the regular rating.
And now you will have more problems to contend with. Thanks to Dac, it will be one challenge
after another game. What? There's a guy just like hiding in the halls and shit? They can't get rid
of this person. They can't get security or anything. I can't like, I don't understand. Why?
Press the A button to stop the lights and choose your three challenges.
To use my three challenges. Oh shit. It's like whammies. Oh no. Take three, sound and rewrite.
Solve the three problems by using the joy pad and the A button to select the correct damsel.
Okay, okay, okay. That's two, four, four, thirty, five, four, fifty, six, seventy, four, six, five,
no, four, seventy, one, two, two, thirty, sixty, two, sixty, three, sixty. Thank you. Two,
twenty-five, five, two, two, twenty-five, two, four, four, twenty-five. Hey, you tried. You'll
come back. Select each word requested by using the joy pad and the A button.
Alright. Adjective. Is Sunny an adjective? Geek. What? Geek is an adjective. Goofy. Hachi? Adjective. Noun, noun, geek. Geek. He actually doesn't. No, I do know. Geek is a fucking adjective.
Are you describing? Like, if you are a geek, isn't that like you're describing somebody as like a geek? I don't know what that is. I have no fucking idea. Bird? It's a piccolo. To put it in front of a noun, moron. Hey! Hey! Hey! Geek. If somebody's a geek, you're describing them as a geek. Uh oh. Is this the awards show? Is this the guy walking around the studio?
Geeky would be the adjective. Yeah. I know. Whatever. Whatever. Whatever.
I hate these award shows personally. I'm only here on behalf of my producer. I get the best in town and the least I can do is show up and get the award. So you're pretty sure you're gonna get one? I like to think positive. But if we can't, what do you do? Awards aren't everything, are they? Of course not.
This kid just dresses himself. Like, look at those shoes.
Okay.
Why am I not there?
Oh, it's the creep! Why does it fit him?
Little dachy boy when he steals your little trophy. Smelly kids.
Hit him with the trophy!
Bite him!
Go bite him!
He got it! Nice job!
The stage light falls and crushes his head.
That's a little too far, but you know what I mean.
We won!
We did it! We won!
That was great. Cool.
What happened to the Vegas guy? He didn't show up and put on a weird overcoat? How did that guy steal that jacket? It was on the kid.
I have a lot of strange questions here.
He put the coat down next to him? How did he get it?
It's freaking me out. I pray we never see anything like this again.
I actually thoroughly enjoyed this one. I thought this was gonna be an immediate next.
I thought it was pretty good.
Okay, alright. Want to speed run one more? One more? Speed run it? Do like a fast run?
No! Okay!
There was so many no's in less than a second that my chat froze for a second. That was fucking hilarious.
Alright, let's move on. I might come back to it though.
Wait, is there an after credit sequence?
Next up is going to be, probably, like I said, there was a couple, two or three here today that was the reason why I bought this.
This is the one. Waited a little while to do it.
About to play. Exclusive to the Family Feud. Fucking just, how did I, I just spoiled it.
Exclusive to the 3DO. Family Feud FMV.
I messed that up.
There's a full FMV Family Feud 3DO game. Exclusive to the 3DO.
I cannot fucking wait.
Why don't we take this opportunity to take a small break. Let's go pee.
I'll be back in about two minutes.
Back. Ready for Family Feud.
What are you guys saying? Cringe. Cringe. Cringe. What is this?
I'm so looking forward to this.
Give me the link. Quick.
Well, we do have a minute.
Before I press play, what is it?
Look, I cannot. Look, do you understand how much convincing it would take to let me be in a classroom and just disrupt the class?
I would need to hire a bunch of people. It would have to be, I couldn't do it for real.
It would be a total disruption.
Actual stream. You clearly want to do it.
Sure. I think that would be really fun.
If I spent a month straight in a fourth or fifth grade class.
And I had to actually pay attention and take tests and shit.
And see if I could get over an 80.
I think that would be really fun.
I might ruin my entire Twitch career doing that.
Because if every stream was just me in a class.
Like a fourth grade class.
I could get detention and stuff. It would be bizarre.
It wouldn't be fun.
That's why I'm not going to do it.
Alright. Let's go. Here we go.
Family Feud coming up.
Do that hamster stream. No, I can't.
I can't do the hamster stream.
Who's the host in this is what I want to know.
I wonder if it's one of the actual TV show hosts.
Because the whole thing is FMV.
Game tech.
Family Feud. Fuck yeah. That's right.
What about the chocolate factory stream?
Just give me a minute.
Let me just say quickly.
Thank you for the $50 FS Woods.
5,000 bits. Insane.
Glad to see you back streaming.
Was super happy to hear that Valve named the scout after you.
Can't think of anyone more deserving.
That's unbelievable that that was confirmed.
I can't even fucking believe it.
Family Feud. Thanks for the 50 bucks.
It's a ton of money. It's too much money.
Mole King also gave $50.
I'm watching since my brother showed me a channel in middle school.
Now I'm an adult and can pay you back for all the years of entertainment.
You're just being here is enough man. Don't worry.
That's a lot of money to give somebody.
Thank you though.
I'm ready. Let's go.
Game options. Start game.
All right. Game options.
Music on. Yeah. Rapid play on.
Difficulty. That's fine. Customize the rules.
Customize a family.
Yes.
How do I customize the family?
Oh shit.
Name. Okay. Hold on.
These are the bumps.
Absolutely. That's Pecky Bump right there.
How do I? Oh shit.
Okay. Hold on.
All right. This is the bump.
Right. The bumps family or is it bump?
Yeah. It's just not. It's not bump.
John bump. That don't matter.
Hobbies. Chess.
That's fine. Occupation. Doctor.
Intelligence. Genius. Yeah. That's good.
Pecky Bump.
You don't have to go through everybody's.
Q. Pecky Bump.
Bump. Remake.
No, no, no, no, no. This is the bump in Netflix special.
This is real actors, man.
Age of 43. Dancing.
Nurse. Intelligence. Good.
Sure.
Max Bump.
Max.
And Eric Bump.
Eric Bump.
Might be a little.
Not Eric Bump.
Zero.
Eric Bump.
Okay. Intelligence.
Zero. All right. Max Bump is going to be pretty dumb.
Hopeless.
All right. Let's do.
Let's do hopeless.
John bump is definitely not a genius.
Max Bump I would say is pretty good.
Peggy Bump I'd say is.
Peggy Bump is a genius.
Max Bump is hopeless.
Kathy Bump is poor.
And Eric Bump is hopeless.
Should we do that? No.
Because are they going to answer questions for me?
Okay. That's fine.
That's fine. That's fine. That's fine.
All right. The bump family is done.
Customize the. No. I want regular rules.
All right. Here we go. Family.
Family versus. Family. Family versus.
System.
3DO system versus 3DO system.
We can watch.
Keep that in mind.
All right. The bump family.
That's me.
I'm so excited. Let's go. Let's go.
Let them kill each other.
We asked 100 people.
Name a food that's terrible when eaten cold.
Terrible when eaten cold.
A food that's terrible when eaten cold.
Hot dog.
No. Eggs. Eggs.
Hot dog. Egg.
Terrible when eaten cold.
Hot dogs are suck.
Hot dog. Cold hot dog.
That's disgusting.
One word.
Gravy.
Tea.
Ice tea is amazing.
Corn.
Ice tea is apparently disgusting.
Where they are. Corn.
You grow a field of corn.
Let's see what the survey said.
All right. Let's bring it back.
Bring it back. Bring it back to the family.
Hi.
Was this like the bonus round?
How come we don't bring it back to the family?
What? Hair?
Hair piece?
Eyeglasses.
All right. So what?
Bullseye round?
If you're short on money, name the bill you delay paying.
The mortgage.
Rent.
Yeah. This is the bullseye round.
This is just to get some money in the bank.
Wrong. What?
Clothes bill?
Is it the bullseye?
The clothes bill?
You have to pay?
It was like a subscription service?
Like a fucking loot box?
For $5,000, can you give me the bullseye answer to this?
Come on.
Name a year round sport.
A year round sport.
That would be darts.
Play darts at any moment at any time ever.
League of Legends.
Darts.
Oh, fuck you. It's darts. It's bowling.
Golf. You can't play golf a year round.
Fucking bowling. God damn it.
I thought it was going to be darts.
It's all right. We've got a little bit of cash.
Let's go. Bump family. Bring it back.
$7,000. Let's go.
Who the fuck plays darts?
I didn't say anybody played it.
I just said it was a thing you could do year round.
Try and give me the most popular answer to this.
Name something fathers and sons do together.
Shit.
I don't think so.
Let's see what the survey said.
No. It's going to be zero.
What? I get a chance?
Okay. Wait, he passed it?
Name something fathers and sons do together.
Catch.
It's going to be at least number two or three.
Oh, yeah. Talk, though.
Talk is a great answer, but not catch.
Great. We have to get this.
Okay. Name something that fathers and sons do together.
Fishing.
I'm going to say fish. Yes. Fine.
It's not even accurate.
Fuck. Wait, this is like 1993.
That is accurate.
Of course it is. Yeah, this is like 1991.
All right. What else?
Fish. What other father and son do together?
Yard work?
Yard work.
Mow the lawn? Lawn?
I want just lawn. Lawn care.
Like yard work. Yard.
I'm going to say yard work. That sounds good to me.
You go out of the yard, you mow the lawn.
Yard work.
Shit. I tried catch. Catch didn't work.
What other father and sons do together?
Hunting? Camping?
My dad didn't go fucking camping.
Camping. Barbecue.
Good answer.
Go camping.
Did you go fishing?
No, I never went fishing with my dad.
I think both of us saw that as something we didn't want to ever fucking do.
All right. What else is there?
Mow the lawn.
If hunting is on here, I mean, remember, anytime you go outside,
my dad's going to be there too, apparently.
Is there anything outside of the house?
Like if you open the door and leave, I might as well put...
This 12 answers here.
There are 12.
Should I just put go get the mail?
There are 12 answers.
I don't know. What the hell could possibly one person have said?
Golf?
At some point, if you run this show, I think you cut off like three or four of the answers and just put like...
Get ready to steal.
Oh my fucking God.
You catch? I did catch.
Drink.
Dad?
Who drank with their dad?
What he did.
Ball game.
I knew it. That's what I said.
I said catch, but then I said go to a game.
It's going to be number two.
Play ball.
Ball game.
Business.
I said golf.
You eat with your dad?
Yes, of course you do.
You live in the same fucking house.
Of course you're going to eat at the same place.
I don't like that.
I have a goldfish. Do you eat with your goldfish because they're in the same house?
We asked a hundred people.
Name any member of Britain's royal family.
I have no idea. I have no idea.
Don't pass it. I don't know.
Queen Elizabeth. That's it.
That's the only one I know. Queen Elizabeth and Prince of Wales.
That's not their name though.
That's not their name.
Fuck you. You didn't even say their name.
Don't pass it. Please play it.
Play it. Don't pass it.
Queen Elizabeth. Queen Elizabeth.
Harry.
Charles. Who else is there?
Peter. Well played.
Queen Elizabeth. That's number three.
That's weird. Okay. Harry.
Harry. Peter.
No, it's not that.
Harry.
And then I'm going to cheat. I'm going to write just like Dutch or like Duchess.
Right? And I'll get something.
Let's say Harry.
Dutch.
I'm just going to put Dutch.
Duchess. Get ready to steal.
You didn't even say. You said Prince.
What about Duke? Oh, wait.
It's not Dutch. It's Duke.
Duke and Duchess.
Fuck.
It's not Dutch and Duchess.
Come on. Give me Duke.
Give me Duke. Duke of...
The Duke of...
Oh my fucking God. I don't know.
Princess.
Princess Fiona.
Princess Fergie?
Good answer.
Sarah Ferguson.
Prince Andrew.
Well, I would have gotten one.
I was about to take a sip.
I was about to take a sip out of my drink.
And I like had to stop because I would have spit it out.
Is this a commercial?
What's going on? Oh, okay.
We asked 100 people.
Name something that's written on a college diploma.
Congratulations. Good luck.
Congratulations. Good luck. Congratulations.
Wait, but this isn't a birthday card.
Hold on.
It says congratulations.
Congratulations.
How do you spell congratulations? Am I doing it right?
I feel like it's a fucking million letters long.
This looks wrong.
This looks incorrect because it's so huge.
This is right, isn't it?
What?
Type of degree.
What are you talking about? What do you mean type of degree?
Like field of study?
It says congratulations on it.
It's like a birthday card.
That gives you access to jobs.
Oh, shit. Okay.
Something that's written on a college diploma.
What's the thing called?
What is it called?
It's like with...
It says like some Latin or Greek or something, was it?
The name of the school.
Name of school. That's good. Good.
Good answer.
Name of school.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Just name. Right. Like your name is on it.
Well played.
Latin words, right?
Oh, the Greek letters.
Greek letters. Greek or Latin?
Latin. I'm just going to write Latin.
Latin words. I don't think Latin is on it.
Greek letters, not Latin letters.
The name of the school. We just said name though.
College name.
College. What about...
College is college name?
The university's name?
The date. Oh, date is a good one.
Date. What did the survey say?
Okay. Your name, the date, the type of degree.
And like good luck or something.
Like a check for five dollars from your grandmother that you don't even want to cash.
Because it's like I got to go to the bank and cash a check for five bucks.
I don't know.
Signature. The dean.
Whoever the dean is, right?
Signature. Yeah. Yeah.
Somebody has to sign it. Somebody has to prove you did it.
Signature.
Come on. Yes.
All right. We got one more here, boys and girls. What is it?
Dean's phone number.
Name of college. Name of the...
That's what I said before, but name was our...
Name of school. School name.
School name. School name. School name. School name. School name. School name.
School name.
Get ready to steal.
School. Just school. Just type school.
Only school. But why can't they tell what I was trying to say?
Major. Oh.
No. No, no, no. Wait. Isn't that already there?
As like field of study or like what you did?
School. I'm sorry. School.
Type of degree is already on there. Yeah. Okay. School.
Let's like spell it with a cool. You know what I mean?
Now it's your chance to steal.
Type of degree is already on there. That is major.
What is it? Pass.
Pass or... Oh, you wrote pass.
You just wrote pass.
I wrote school name. I wrote school.
I did that twice. They couldn't decide what I was trying to say.
That's fucking ridiculous. I'm still in the lead. I'm fine.
All right. Come on, Peggy Bump. Let's go.
We asked a hundred people.
Name a place where you sit in an adjustable seat.
Airplane. Yeah. Not fast enough, huh?
Airplane. Air. Plane.
It's going to be number one. Airplane.
Airplane. Movies.
What did the survey say?
Dentist. The dentist.
I'm passing this. They're not going to get this.
I don't want to do it. I'm passing it.
Beauty? Oh, you're writing beauty.
A beauty chair? Let's see what the survey said.
Barber shop. See, they give that shit to them,
but not the school name shit to me.
Player pass. I don't think they're going to get it.
All right. I'll play it. I'll play it. We're going to do movies.
Movie. Car. Boat. Dentist.
Movie. Movie chair or just movies?
Like movie theater. Do I have to write theater?
Cinema. Cinema.
Car. Dentist.
Come on. It's going to be like movie theater. I know it is.
I'm going to write car. It's going to be number two.
Number one. Good answer.
Car. Airplane. Barber shop.
Movie theater. Dentist.
I'm going to say dentist. Or theater.
Okay. Is it theater or theater?
I always forget this. Like, is it theater or is it theater?
Theater. Right? It can be both. Yeah, I know.
But what's the American spelling?
Let's see what the survey said.
Movie. Can I say movies?
No, I said cinema. I was too smart.
Shit. This is going to be one dumb thing.
It's going to be dentist. That's going to be the one underneath this.
It's dentist. Trust me. Dentist.
Yes. I told you guys. You didn't believe me.
You didn't believe me. I knew it was going to be dentist.
All right. How about office? Office chair.
Office. Bus. No, you don't adjust a bus seat.
I'm going to say office chair. Office.
Is it up there?
How do you adjust a toilet seat?
You either put it down or put it up.
There's no comfort settings on a toilet.
You don't recline.
All right. Money round. Fast money.
Let's get Peggy in there.
And Peggy.
All right. Peggy and Dylan bump.
Oh, it's Max. Max bump. Right.
Name a meal dieters skip.
What do you mean? Like time of day? Like dinner.
Dinner? Lunch?
You mean like what kind of meal? Like steak?
Dinner. Dinner. Lunch.
Breakfast. Lunch.
Lunch. She looks so concerned.
Lunch.
Name something people do when they're on a health kick.
Lunch. Healthy lunch.
Lunch.
Diet. They diet.
I don't know. They eat greens. Green vegetables.
Vegetables.
You'd be surprised how many people just don't eat them at all.
Vegetable.
Name a way of preparing foods that is healthier than fries.
Of baking?
What's all this food shit?
Name something you do at dinner at home you wouldn't do in a restaurant.
Name something you would do at dinner at home you wouldn't do in a restaurant.
Blow my nose?
Into my hands?
I don't know.
What would you do at a dinner that you wouldn't do in a restaurant?
Burp?
I'm going to say burp. Burp like fart and stuff.
Yeah, burp.
Name something with stripes.
Name a meal dieters skip.
You said...
Let's see what the survey said.
That's pretty good.
Name something people do when they're on a health kick.
You said...
Huh?
Name a way of preparing foods that is healthier than frying.
You said...
Baking is way, way better.
Yeah.
Air fryers didn't exist, guys.
Name something you do at dinner at home you wouldn't do in a restaurant.
You said...
Let's see what the survey said.
Look at these answers. Just tell their own story.
Name something with stripes.
You said...
Lunch, vegetables, baking, burp, zebra.
Let's see what the survey said.
We need 80 points.
Name a meal dieters skip.
Dinner.
We got this in the bag. It's done.
Name something people do when they're on a health kick.
Exercise.
No.
Name a way of preparing foods that is healthier than frying.
Screaming at it until it heats up.
Foods that are healthier than frying.
Baking, pan searing.
Boiling.
Boiling food.
Is that right?
Name something you do at dinner at home you wouldn't do in a restaurant.
That's so stupid. That's such a joke answer.
Scream? I don't know. Would you yell or talk loudly?
Fart. It's an easy one.
I'd be so pissed.
If I was sitting at a table across with somebody and they just leaned up and just fucking ripped one,
I'd be like, get that fucking person out of here.
Now.
That's unbelievable.
Name something with stripes.
A tiger.
If somebody did that, I would be looking around for the hidden cameras.
Name a meal dieters skip.
You said.
Good answer.
That's it.
Name something people do when they're on a health kick.
Vegetables.
Exercise.
Name a way of preparing foods that is healthier than frying.
You said.
Boils their food.
Oh, that's disgusting.
Name something you do at dinner at home you wouldn't do in a restaurant.
You said.
Name something with stripes.
That implies that you're farting at the dinner table all the time.
We lost.
Isn't there a none professor don't they go around the table and just like fart and stuff at the table?
I want $695.
Okay, cool.
We asked 100 people.
Name something made of brass.
Horn.
Horn is made of brass, right?
No! What's more brass than a horn? A trombone. And that's not a horn? That's not a horn?
Yeah, you're trying to steal- you- you- you just c- bed is made out of brass.
That would be really uncomfortable, is this like the fucking 1200s?
Two thousand dollars, can you give me the bullseye answer?
That person copied my answer with horn and tried to make it more specific.
Name one of the Roosevelts.
Uh, duh-duh-duh-daci...
Yeah, gonna get higher than Teddy.
Hail Man!
Show... show... showbiz.
You knew that answer. Somebody fed you these questions before you don't get showbiz.
I gotta get this one.
That's important.
Where fuck let's see what the survey said
Rome has corners. Yeah, all right. I gotta fold this. I gotta get this your jawline
This is for
5,000 I have to get this one name a household chore that needs to be done again right away shit
How are you so fast that was gonna? Yeah, I was gonna say dishes too god damn it. I'm losing bad. Oh
I'm in trouble
Restart I don't even start. I'm fine. I got this
$17,000 this is great. It's just two we asked 100 before answers
Name something people take home from the office for their own use pens
Computer don't do people take the computer home pen good answer. This is not very many
Stapler
Okay, they're gonna get it. I'm passing. They're not gonna get it. It's way too weird and specific paper
Are you taking paper from the office for what are you gonna use it for?
Would you use paper?
What do you need that for and soul paper paper again taking paper clips from the office good answer paper?
That's you
Typewriter
You know I told you computer. This is the computer of like the fucking 1980s
I told you that was right, and then I lost all my confidence
The TV okay, let's go who takes the tie
Yeah, I don't know what it was even oh no
No, this is too many too many the top 12
Oh was way too many on the board name something you see in a town square statue and by the way
I don't think we're gonna get these statues number one or
shops well played
Events
festival
Let's play it. Let's go say go people. Yeah people and event shops
Hey, I don't know
What there's no people in a town square okay? Hey shops now do I have to spell it?
Like the like sh ho like PPE you know what I mean like like I have to spell it this way like that
You know people spell it like this. I don't think so
Why would they pan over
All the way down there why okay?
Was it fountain fountain fountain a fountain in your towns in your town square the fuck do you live you've got a fountain
Okay, fountain I've he was kind of pissed off with that answer all right
Town square there's like eight more fucking responses. How about um a
Like a festival right like that you do like in the town square a festival there
Get ready to steal cannon. Why would it be a cannon in the middle of times? Oh what the fuck you're right?
There is a cannon there is a cannon just always there for some reason
What okay now? It's your chance to steal bench
Okay, okay. Yes seating you can sit down benches. There is a cannon everybody has a clock. Why why hey?
Hey, oh oh freeze church. I thought they just got them all or they stole it big here
Otherwise, it's not gonna happen. I'm not gonna be able to do it. We gotta win big Hermes from Boston
He doesn't know about non cannon towns. Yeah, that's true every town square has a cannon in it
You're right try and give me the most popular answer to this name a white flower. I don't know
I don't I'm gonna guess I
Have no idea. I don't know and it can't any flower be white by the way like I swear to God
There's like white roses white tulips white every well. I don't know tulip oh
Right carnation, it's not a rose. It's a carnation
Actually, it's a guy take it take it and play it for all I care play it. Don't pass it. He's actually mad
Lily yeah Lily
It's a daisy the daisy white. Where's it like orange good answer one trick wizard gave a hundred dollars
They said naked grandma. Thanks the thanks for the 100 fucking dolls. What else is there? What is a white flower?
But isn't carnation the thing already there is kind of do rose. That's carnation though, isn't it in there to get it?
What about a?
Daisy a lotus is it up there
Otis
Orchid is a lotus is a lotus white is a lot like purple no no no no no that's just the name of the expensive magic the
Gathering card right okay. Yeah
What um?
Orchid I don't know I don't know guys. I'm sorry
I've got like a
Garden I don't know you know the last time I picked up a flower and went like
Mmm, I'm probably the third grade and the survey or dead yeah
Marijuana flower no, sorry, that's green. I think I would know that one
You know what I mean if roses but roses carnation surely is this an actually is it up there good
Okay, we need one more
Carnation daisy lily rose orchid our nation lily daisy rose orchid daffodil
Dandelion a poppy is it a poppy, but because only one poppy. It's gotta be
Ready to steal
Magnolia
Magnolia would even come up with these names by the way
I feel like you just kind of hit your head on your desk as hard as you could and wrote down whatever letters came
Up Magnolia like what does that? What does it mean?
They're not going now. It's your chance to steal ah
You have no idea we win we win we win. What is it gardenia?
Gardenia sure okay, this is a warcraft zone. That's not even real how far away how far behind to all my number the lead
We asked 100 people name a relaxing form of recreation
sleeping
No, that's not right is that rec a relaxing recreation is taking a nap sleeping. I would say snap nap TV nap
I was napping not relaxing recreation. I love that's what I do all the time rugs. Let's see what the survey said
Watching TV is that far down the list so what the hell could number one be they're gonna play it right?
I passed that there's so many options okay
relaxing form of recreation um
I feel like I'm writing this because it's probably it's a big big blanket that will probably take up like cigarettes and alcohol and
relaxing form of recreation uh
But golf is so I don't it's not as a golf though golf seems way too stupid of an answer to be that high
Well played of course golfing golfing is higher than watching tv
I don't get the golf thing by the way. I hate golf
Why is it that every male over the age of 30 years old is magically supposed to love that sport?
It's just the day you turn 30 you just it turns a switch flips in your brain
And now you have to love golf and if you don't then what's wrong with you. Are you okay?
I hate it. I think it's boring and I think it sucks and look it takes a ton of skill. I think it's a great what?
Can you imagine the amount of mental fortitude it takes to hit that ball in that hole what a skill
I don't like it and I refuse to like it like no they're not like somebody
Relaxing form of recreation. Oh
Uh golf fast fuck get ready to steal
Okay, I need something that's more than tv
Pogo stick no not you nobody said that
Reading yes, good read fucking yoga. Nobody
Reading now, it's your chance. Nobody reads no read no reading
reading
We're still gonna win because they have no idea. Why would you not even take a guess?
Reading swimming
I said read boating sunbathing
bowling
music and movies
That's absolute. That's dog shit
Boating
Boating is not relaxing boating is stressful who i'm i'm good
It's the i'll get it try and give me the most popular answer to this
Name something that must operate on a strict time schedule
Doctor plane
That's not even accurate. That's really funny that you write plane. I've never been on a plane that's ever been on time
Oh, wow funny
I've never departed on time and by the way, i've never been to the doctor's appointment
That is ever when the doctor's ever been on time. So, um, I don't know what you I guess all these things coach
Plus, okay. Yeah, a bus has to be on time. That's true. What else class class has to be on time. Shit. That's right
uh
Dentist hey the dentist is always on time. Can I tell you that?
You don't just take a guess. Why is the computer so stupid?
You're gonna pass three times you could have just guessed that right now
You could have played tv s to be on time. Oh, right is the scheduled tv programming right office
Like going to work, right? If it's not there i'm gonna say work. Okay
They get these filling answers and I don't train not gonna be there. Let's see what the survey said
I'm still in the lead by the way still time for final jeopardy. How did I lose? I got more points
I got how did I lose? I got more points
Uh
Name something little girls pretend to be names little girls pretend to be mommies
Wait, we get to watch at least name something besides jewelry that people wear around their necks
A tie. Yep. Nice. Good god. Good god name a fairy tale. That is also trying to say good job
Fairy tale, it's a love story cinderella
Name a food that comes in a cardboard container tv dinner
Pizza shit
Past or present name a famous tv newswoman, uh barb barb walters. Yeah, that's what you're doing
Yeah
Okay, name something little girls pretend to be mommy you said
And the survey said
Name something besides jewelry that people wear around their necks
Yes
You said yeah
Name a fairy tale that is also a love story
You said anything disney made?
Is it up there?
Name this dude's gonna win the whole thing in a cardboard container
You're gonna need to have another person come up. Is it up there?
Past or present name a famous tv newswoman. You said pizza that look is it up there?
He almost won on his own
Name something little girls pretend to be
wrong
Name something little girls come on you can do it
Name something little girls
Bob
Name something little girls. No, that's wrong. It's not mom
My
Name something
Name something little girls pretend
Name something little girls
Name something little girls pretend to be
Oh shit, she figured it out princess
Name something besides jewelry that people wear around their necks
That was bm. I just got bm'd god damn it
Fucking bm. They need three points. Of course you would bm. It is also a love story
sleep oh
Yeah, but I thought we were I thought I'm really gonna lose name a food that comes in a cardboard container
Yeah, that's true
Past or present name a famous tv newswoman
Arvo authors here we go again, but they're gonna get the three points. That's unfortunate. Oh well
That's so sad. I really thought she's gonna get stuck on different ways to say the word mother
Past or present name a famous tv newswoman
She can't brute force this answer correctly. I'm sorry like move on
Past or present don't you feel like this lady is locking direct eye contact with the host every time
Barbara walters
Sorry, that's wrong
sure
Name something little girls pretend to be the princess is just you said
What did the survey say?
Name something besides jewelry that people wear around their necks
You said okay. Is it up there? We're gonna do something interesting
I'm gonna play one more that is also a love and then we're gonna have a fun little bet
You said you guys get your own family. Is it up there?
And we're gonna put all the computers name at the same intelligence level cardboard container. We're gonna have our family side
Well, I mean is it up there?
Past or present name a famous tv newswoman
You said make them all stupid. I feel like there would be no answers though. Do we make them all hopeless every single person is open
Sounds like a question we can answer
We're gonna sit there for like 10 minutes. Oh, no. All right, i'm going back. I want to play another one though
I'm gonna play another one
I'm having fun. Yeah, it just ends if you don't win. It just ends
Yeah, if you win you keep going we asked 100 people
Give me a slang word for face. Um
Oh shit, uh the survey said
Mug yeah
Somebody said good posture
Good answer
Is too big ass
Bum, but bum, but two t's is just one
This is for three thousand dollars name a holiday that ends in the word day, uh christmas day
Turkey day thanksgiving day a um new year's day new year's day new years
Is it up there?
What?
they
valentine's day valentine's day sits, I think below new year's day in the day holidays, i'm sorry
Right. Oh labor day. Okay. We asked 100 people name the newspaper section that people read first
funny
I win name the age everyone would like to be again
um
Do I just spell this out or can I just write it 20 25?
I think it's a that's a good year 20 to be talked 25 25
How what how what how do you want to be 19?
And the survey dumbest fucking thing i've ever heard
Why would you want 21? Okay, that makes more sense. I don't want to go back. Why would I be 19 again?
We did okay, I mean it'd be great to I mean, oh, yeah, you get to be young again, but like you
You lose a lot of your uh, like adult privileges. We asked 100 people
Name something men try to impress women with shit. Um
cologne their car. Yeah, okay
Their car. Hey, you like my car
Yeah, but uh you suck
Uh, I didn't really thought it was gonna work. Okay, name something to impress women. Um
Uh muscle like uh, like you're big strong strength tall fuck. God damn it. Whatever
muscles hair honey
your body again, um
Personality, uh, how smart pass this shit? I don't know your brain
Well played but it okay. I thought they were gonna write penis. That was a better thing to write than pass
At least you gave yourself a chance money money. Yeah, it's gonna be up there
And the survey said money
Okay
Nope, I guys guys come up with one. Come we gotta get one. We gotta get one
Get ready to steal money. Uh
job
Candy
Well, what do you mean? Well played?
Fucking candy. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, they they just blew it. What is it?
Funny funny you could still all right funny. Yeah, if you're like funny. All right, let's go funny
That's if humor if funny's the same thing
What charm sex appeal and job
Uh, well checks out guys because I didn't get very many dates because people thought I was funny
I got side eyes
And split checks try and give me the most popular answer to this
Besides clothing name something specific you wash by hand. That was exact. Come on
You were never funny. I've had that guy for a month. Is it up there? Wash by hand
Yeah, like dishes I don't know how many
Dishes is definitely number one, but I don't think I want to play this
I feel like there's too many weird answers here body right you wash your body by hand like yourself
When you're in the shower, you just like slime the body, uh gel all of you, right?
Your body pet what else a car?
What do you mean your hair? Yeah besides clothing hair. Yeah, you guys don't take hold on. Wait a minute
How many uh, how many how many slimers do we have here? That's a very important question
I don't squeeze a little bit into a little loofah and
What did the survey say? I squeeze the slime the gel into the palm of my hand
And slime it smear it all over me who doesn't do that. Okay, wash my hand car. It's a terrible way to clean yourself
Lather it first. Yeah, but I but I just smear it all with my hand and then just
Swish it around till it lathers all over my chest and then I go all over the place
I do in the palm of my hand
Go like this really get it in and smear it all over my chest and then I use my chest
To get lather and then go all over the place and come back to the chest for more lather and then go under the armpits
And who doesn't do that? That's weird. Apparently. Okay, what else? Uh body like your body you wash your body with your hands
Good answers. I know this is how a body cuts hair. There's four more of these
Uh hands you wash your hands by hand with your hands, huh? Right you brush your teeth
That was a good answer anime figurines. Uh, can we just say toys or something?
What get ready to steal? I don't know
Windows washing the windows, I guess maybe but I don't think that's I don't know wash windows
They're probably gonna pass anyways, though laundry. Didn't we already have that? Oh shit
Is laundry up there? No, it says besides clothes. No clothes
You can't say clothes besides clothing the floor wash the floor by hand
Not really you use a fucking swiffer wet jet 2.8. I don't know. That's not accurate. That's not right wash vegetables
That might be really specific though. I'll try i'll give it a go. You know, what do you mean you wash food?
You get you get like your plate of steak onions mashed potatoes gravy and carrots
And then you just hold that whole thing under the sink with the water running all over it. It's so gross
Well, then what is it then it better not be floor who's washing the the floor with their hands. Oh no
Oh no, no
Money washing your crystal that was crystal and jewelry not the same thing
And crystal was higher than jewelry who has a bunch of crystals. We asked a hundred people
Name an occasion when a lot of people kiss you
um
Wedding right a bunch of people like oh, congratulations
When what do we uh wedding you get like a kiss from?
Whoever you're marrying and then you're like parents like kiss the cheeks wedding. Let's see what the survey said
Okay
any large family kind of gathering
Uh christmas thanksgiving
Uh any family kind of holiday we have to I have to play it. I have to play this
I gotta get them all I think we still lose though. Oh, somebody's a birthday. Yeah. Okay. Like happy birthday
Where a lot of people kiss you well played a wedding birthday. Now we're getting more specific. Is it funeral?
funeral funeral
No, your own funeral what i'm surprised. Okay. Um christmas thanksgiving. Yeah, we're gonna get the major holidays out of the way
New year's new year's christmas
What does the survey say?
Uh new year's valentine's day. Um, I feel like if a lot of people kissed you on valentine's day
I'm not I don't i'm not sure that's correct. I think that would be no, okay
Um, what is it there new year's new year's new year's i'm not going to type in orgy
I don't think that's going to be up here in this g rated game
Okay wedding birthday new year's day of christmas thanksgiving. It's going to be true. It's going to be thanksgiving is what it is thanksgiving
We already got wedding up there wedding's already there thanksgiving
Uh-oh get ready to steal. Uh, and like I don't know a party graduation graduation's not bad. I don't know
Graduation's not a bad one valentine's day
Yeah
Graduation or valentine's day i'm gonna say i'm gonna say uh, it's not gonna be valentine's day. I'm gonna write it though
No, i'm not. It's not gonna be it's graduation
graduation
Okay. Now it's your chance to steal
Congratulation
What are you writing?
Reunion
That's not fair. That's all of these things
Everything up here is a reunion fuck out of here weddings of your whole family your birthday
Everyone shows up to reunion new year's christmas. What the hell are you talking about?
Now we have to watch them do the fast money again
Grandma wasn't invited
Name something in a child's school bag
lunch
Mommy name a way of preparing foods that is healthier than frying
Wow repeat
repeat
Not cool name something comfortable to wear that was once cheap, but now isn't
um
Shoes you can get cheap shoes name an animal with lots of hair
I would have said like a lion something the family takes turns using I don't know why I was just gonna say toothbrush
Name something in a child's school bag
You said
Name a way of preparing foods that is healthier than frying you said the vape pen is it up there?
Name something comfortable to wear that was once cheap, but now isn't shoes art. You can get cheap shoes
And the survey said
Name an animal with lots of hair fine. You said and the survey said
Name something the family takes turns using you said car. Yeah, that's good
All right. Let's see how the other person does
Name something in a child's school bag
Book that's wrong name something in a child's school bag. Yeah, come on. That's number one
Name a way of preparing foods that is healthier than frying
And
Name something you are halfway there that was once cheap, but now isn't not shoes
Name something comfortable to wear that was once cheap, but now isn't
Sweater, okay, you only got that wrong once good for you name an animal with lots of hair
Name an animal with lots of hair
Lion just say lion or tiger or something name an animal with lots of cat dog. Yes. There you go
Go
Name something the family takes turns using
Don't pass come on
Name a way of preparing foods that is healthier than frying
Name a way of preparing foods that is healthier than frying. It's duck
Yeah, you have no more answers
Name something the family takes turns using how much would you be freaking out backstage?
Television
Name something in a child's already watches the same thing you said
Good answer
Name a way of preparing foods that is healthier than frying
You said
Name something comfortable to wear that was once cheap. Okay, you guys you guys ready for the competition
You said good answer
We're gonna we're gonna watch the computer name an animal with lots of hair in a 1v1
You're gonna make them all hopeless and the survey said
Name something the family takes turns using what no that's too. It's gonna be unbearable to watch. It's gonna be horrible
And the survey said
He's still lost hopeless no one's gonna answer any questions. It's gonna be a tie
Do it fine. Okay, we're gonna make everybody hopeless me versus you. I already got my team
I have to make you guys real quick make one genius per family. That's a better idea. Yeah, okay
Okay, so we need
Here's me. Okay. Here you go
Okay, here's chat patricia chat
andrew chat
William chat
Okay intelligence
hopeless
intelligence hopeless
These girls eyes are closed
Hopeless. No, this is the genius
Just probably one person's name out of chat trying to find out who there we go. No plank man
Uh, okay, is anything higher than genius?
All right hopeless
hopeless
Here you go. This is your this is you guys
Customize my family
Peggy bump is gonna be the genius still
She will carry this entire team
Okay, hopeless hopeless hopeless genius hopeless
Sounds good
difficulty
Amazing
Right. It should be like hard
No, no, no, no, no, no, no to average or just good. You're not gonna get any questions
We'll do amazing with geniuses next time. Oh, no, not amazing. No one's gonna get anything right
Okay
Radio versus 3do. Let's go. What's on the line?
Wait, is this even the right family's 100 people name something that london is famous for who's my team?
Is famous for big ben aren't they all hopeless?
And the survey said
That's supposed to be not supposed to be smart
For two thousand dollars. Can you give wrong families? I answer to this name something associated with the game of billiards
How is it? Why is it the wrong families?
You have to every single family has to be customized. Okay, which is to make every family hopeless for the genius
All right
i'm gonna say
Okay, there are only one two three four. There are only four families in the whole game
Is our genius? All right, we got our one genius. This is my team
uh
the
We can know it's team germ. All right. Next we've got
Customized rules. No, no, no, no, no chat again
Okay, we have our one genius. There already is genius here. So let's go ahead and just change this
Okay, we're good. So no matter what the outcome is
Here we go. It's time to start the game
radio versus 3do
What if both are chat?
We'll just have to do it until we get the right one
I we're good. I think we're good a thousand dollars
Name any civil war general of the north or south lee
That's quick and the survey said both me
We'll find out a second. Oh, it's not two thousand dollars. Can you give me the bullseye answer to this?
Name a famous character with kid in his name. It's don't
billy the
Kid rock the survey said I thought they're supposed to all be stupid. Why are they getting these so easily?
We asked 100 people tell me how many pets you have three
Or
Yeah, it's it's three. It's two or three. Uh
One holy shit for four thousand dollars name an occupation that keeps people on their feet
Uh waiter doc well played
Uh
I got it my team would have had it try and give me the most popular answer to this
Name something mothers send to their kids in camp letter
Okay, so who whose team is on what did the survey say?
What food why are you sending food to the kids at camp? All right, here we go. Let's see
We got the right teams, right?
Regardless this all hopeless in one. It is the chat family versus the chat family
Okay, what do I think?
They're all the same. It doesn't matter. I'm just on the left. Okay, i'm the i'm team one
Try and give me the most popular answer to this
Tell me a type of place that has uniform guards
Uh buckingham palace
Thank you. I died these these these are my guys right here. That's wrong. That's not no, it's not
Rids, they're a prison. Okay, you guys said prison. Is it up there? Stop giving them the answers
Tell me a type of a place that has
Uniform guards
Are they gonna all pass?
Bank a place with uninformed guards. Okay. What did the survey say? Hey, come on an
Embassy
Oh, that's smart
And that's not hopeless
milk
milk military base
Guard the farm
So this is my team, right? They're doing pretty well
This is team one, isn't it?
Mush museum?
They got them all right
Well, this is just chat versus chat. No, I picked one
I was team one. Yeah, that's you guys over there
I can always tell because you guys have the guy you guys have like the stomach posture guy
We asked 100 people give a word used to describe steak brah. This is you guys. I gotta stop saying
Did I love what did the survey say?
All right, let's see if you guys can do something with this you're gonna pass it to me. Wow. Okay might be a smart idea
We'll find out well done tasty
Delicious, is it up there? I just do all the temperatures beef. I would hope so
And the survey said thick thick steak. Yeah. No, that's I good answer. That's true 12 answers
Is this anybody's game delay? What did the survey say?
Right, what do you want if you win this? Um, I don't know
Juicy nothing delicious. Mm-hmm. I don't know why you guys passed it. That was a bad idea
But wait a minute. You could say like tough gross smells not just good things think about the bad things
That's right rotten. Don't pass it. There's no reason to that's two wrong answers. That's the only one good good good good
Defensive dry real right? There's a hundred percent real beef. It's like steak. Um,
It's gonna be a steal because the passing just get ready to steal shit tender. Wait. All right, don't pass
Answer the question. No, you idiot. Why?
You just gave them a bunch of points because someone's gonna get it
Okay. Now it's your chance to steal
He bone he pose right of course chat writes that shit they're gonna and they got it sir line. Yeah, that's all right
It's just that's all that's just round one. We're fine. You got kids. No, we asked
I need 174 name something white that you put on top of and mayonnaise mayo mayo mayo mayo hit the button mayo hit the button
Mayonnaise hit the button get it salt. I guess that's true. That's accurate. Well played. Isn't salt technically transparent
It's a rock a see-through rock soup
All right salt sour cream mayo cream cheese cheese topping. Yes
Yes, that's what we're looking for. We're what?
White topping what is white topping it comes to mayo. Yeah, that's like number one
That's pisses me off that that's not number one. What's over salt or a white substance cream
It's not whipped cream. Isn't it whipped cream? What sugar?
Frosting that only goes on like one thing just goes on a cake ices this steak. It's not like a toaster strudel ass, right?
Why is it always my team that's doing the double pass bullshit?
Get ready to this is triple pass. Yes it is
Okay, now it's your chance to steal hopeless. Okay. What are you guys gonna say white? Oh, come on
White sauce
That's so vague
Vagueest thing ever. Hey, what's something you put on your food white sauce a sauce that is white substance. That is white. Yes
Thank you. That is what I asked you to do a whipped cream could be a white sauce mayonnaise could be a white sauce
That's all what this doesn't make any sense. Well, good luck
Popping yeah
Name an ingredient in black guys name a state with a desert
Yeah, you guys only know that because I wait, you know, it's not what you're writing
Name something that makes people feel better about themselves
Name something comfortable to wear that was once cheap, but now isn't
Name something parents warn kids not to play near
Name an ingredient in bread
You said
and the survey said
Name a state with a desert
You said
What did the survey say?
Name something that makes people feel better about themselves
You said
good answer
Name something comfortable to wear that was once cheap, but now isn't
You said
Let's see what the survey said
Name something parents warn kids not to play near
You said
Good answer
Name an ingredient in bread name a state with a desert
Name something that makes people feel better about themselves
Name something comfortable to wear that was once cheap, but now isn't
Name something parents warn kids not to play near
Name an ingredient in bread you said
Is it up there?
What I missed what I missed what I missed what I missed with a desert
You said utah, okay bread. Yeah, that's good
Name something that makes people feel better about themselves. Okay. Yeah, I would say uh, you said
Yes, yeah, is it up there?
You guys are gonna get it name something comfortable to wear that was once cheap, but now is shoe fire you said
Let's see what the survey said
Name something parents warn kids not to play fire
You said don't hit the street. Let's see what the survey said
Don't they you guys won unbelievable
You guys not hear me say I was I had to go pee and I ran down you can hear that
Oh shit, my mic is delayed
By like a full second. I don't think yes, you guys didn't hear that did you?
All right. I want to play one more. I want to play one more
I want to play one more and I don't want I don't want any help at all. I'm not is it just me
Me versus you that's fine. I just want to do one more and then we're gonna move on to
Uh road rash that's coming up next for one thousand dollars name something hats are made of
uh
plastic cotton plastic plastic hat a wool hat wool
Wooden a wood hat plastic hair plastic leather plastic. No, don't give me enough. I don't want help. No help
Don't give me help you guys can help yourselves there
I'm versus you
Put an emote only mode. All right, fine put it in emote only mode. I'll win this on my own
Let's see what the survey said i'm gonna get this on my own make it impossible for me to cheat make it
So it's not possible look they got it wrong too
They said felt try and give me the most popular answer to this
Name something a person who is afraid of heights won't do sky dive
Done. That's definitely number one. Is it the bulls eye? It is
What do you mean climb climb
climb up a ladder
Climbing a ladder is the biggest fear for somebody that doesn't like heights
Not jumping out of a fucking airplane name something you see if you look up guide
Yeah, you really wanted that sky answer. Didn't you good answer? I'm gonna win this one on my own
for
$4,000
What might a polite person say instead of huh? What?
Oh that is it up there?
damn it
Excuse me
That's the same thing. Excuse me. And what what is and the survey said, excuse me
Okay, this is just for money. This isn't for points for
$5,000 can you give me the bulls eye answer to this?
Mm-hmm name a creature that probably feels slimy slug
slug or fish
Is it up there? Give me that five grand
What's slimer than a slug?
Squid that's debatable a squid is not slimer than a slug. No, I was a snake
Slimy, maybe the leathery smooth and leathery kind of but slimy that doesn't matter
We both didn't make any money if we won. That's fine. All right, four answers. Let's go
The top four answers are on the board name something that a motorcyclist wears
Yes, it is
uh
Like pads so high it's 80 percent of it. Okay
elbow pads
Uh, i'm passing it. I don't think you're gonna get it. Yeah, all right after that. You have no idea. We've got the d
Goggles maybe ab I don't think so though and the survey said
Better than that ass here comes the steel
Get ready to steal a helmet pads pads elbow pads and right pads
Helmet, okay now goggles pads
um
Music motorcycle like they listen to music, but that's not what they asked pads elbow pads like knee pads
What?
They wear a jacket and gloves don't you wear like elbow pads knee pads shin pads wrist guards only you on a bike
I mean, no, that's okay when you're like six years old you wear all that stuff because you don't you wear that though
I'm picturing like a little kid with all that stuff all over
I don't know the top seven answers. I gotta win this one name a compartment in refrigerator
Uh humidity draw. I don't know shit humidity draw the blood the lettuce the crisper the crisper draw
I don't know. They're just all the same things. It's the thing that you just put food in there and it stays cold
I don't know what do you mean compartment frid the freezer?
Shit the cheese compartment who has a cheese. How big is your fridge?
How big is your fridge that you have this food apartment complex where they apparently all have their own space and their own doors and shit
How big is this place cheese compartment? Uh, all right the freezer. That's the easy one. I mean nay
What?
What are you talking about cheese compartment the meat compartments? Okay, I don't know about you guys
But when I put food in the fridge, I just put it in there
Yeah, you put like your meat on the bottom like the bottom in the draw, right?
But you I don't know you put everything else in there
You just put vegetables who cares just put it on the fridge. I'll do the same thing. Is it up there
meat
Condiments the mustard compartment the ketchup compartment the condiments. Yeah, usually you put your condiments kind of off to the side a little
Yeah condiments is it condiments or condiments condiment condiment condiment condiment condiment condiment ready to steal
Cheese meat veggies the vegetable compartment. That's definitely it vegetable compartment. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
And the story one said not vegetables not meat not cheese not condiments
What else do you put in a fridge clothes? What else do you put in the fridge eggs?
There's a compartment for eggs. Let's see what the survey said
Just put them on the top and just slide them back egg compartment a
Poppings drinks beverages. I'm saying drinks. I don't I don't know anybody that does that drinks
Still win the game alcohol beer wine. No, most people keep their alcohol not in the fridge fruit compartment
I said vegetables if fruit is up there, that's bullshit. You put them both in the same one. They're the same one
You guys want that's what did the survey say?
I think fruit compartment for what?
Butter compartment and the ice compartment the freezer is okay
We don't say freezer it keeps ice in their fridge just melts into water and it's gonna ruin your fridge
Why would you put ice in the fridge?
Was that a refrigerator or was that a cooler at a tailgate party?
The top five answers are on the board. Tell me what you think the national speed limit should be
Wait, like you like talk. Okay, uh
60 65
65 more than 100. What did the survey say?
That's right. 65
Okay, let's take this one because I know that there's gonna be a bunch of psychos out there that are like it should be
It should be 80
But i'm playing it you guys aren't getting it 80 the national speed limit should be 80
Okay, that might is that a little high?
75 70 75 is definitely it's definitely 70 70 is probably number one. There it is. All right
60 in the 60s and 70s. It'll all be up there
We're going 60 55 is another one or potentially higher than 80 like 90 70 60 65
75 here come the fast speeds, right?
Set i'm gonna say 75 or 55. We'll go low 55. Is it up there?
It is okay
One person wants to go really fast. It's probably 85
That's so fast. Get ready to steal ridiculous
Okay, was it 50 50s of it 50s too slow
50 it's definitely not 50
What you could still win the game you go faster than an 85 or slower than 50. Yeah, you passed I went
Is it 90?
It's gonna be 90
Didn't I write 75? I thought I wrote 75. I was wrong. I didn't
Oh shit, whatever one. Oh you i'm in the lead. Good luck
We asked 100 people name something everyone loses at some time besides hair and
Shit, I don't know what the second one was
Besides hair and what was it time besides hair and time. Okay, uh wallet
Teeth people are losing their teeth more than they're losing their wallets. How do you lose your teeth by the way?
I don't fucking understand that I find that to be insane
Your teeth are in your mouth and you need to eat with them
You need to be constantly aware of their presence where how are they coming out to enough times to lose them?
Don't you just take your teeth out and put them in a glass next to your bed
Are you taking your teeth out and playing baseball with them and then they get lost in the stands?
How do you lose your teeth play like basketball with them? Okay something
It loses at some time besides hair and temper teeth not wallet keys
It didn't winston turtel used to take his teeth out and throw them across the senate and stuff like that
Good answer. Maybe that's how okay teeth. He oh, probably watch I would say right. This is like back in the early 90s watch
Hmm not a wallet keys, but you lose
Um, I don't know you lose keys wallet phone
But that this is 19 like to lose your phone guys. You'd have to unplug it from the wall and throw it out the window
uh
Losing your mind. I don't know
Keys teeth hair temper time wallet, um phone
um
I mean if teeth is up there then you're like eye
Like you lose your eye or something or you're like a ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring ring
Absolutely money
Okay. Now it's your chance to steal wait lose weight over at some time
I was gonna write that too. I actually was gonna write that it's a really interesting thing that you might lose
I think I still won today. I did I went I had 284. Would you guys end up with 250?
Name a room people frequently add onto a house you guys
You add a bathroom
Name someone famous whose last name is marx
Um, I think this is like only one guy that's like what's the other answer name something that you can buy
in the shape of a heart
handy
Name a popular mail order catalog, right?
No, no, no, no
I name something that people want their food to be low in
Just heard the word mail order and like I haven't heard the word mail order
In like 20 fucking years name a room people frequently add onto a house
You said and the survey said what the fuck is it ll bean?
Name someone famous whose last name is marx
You said good good answer
Is it up there?
Who's higher than carl's barn something that you can buy in the shape of a heart
You said
Let's see what the survey said. You don't know. I know what ll bean is name a popular mail order catalog
You said it's like
Good no, you might jc petty
Name something. Oh, you guys are not doing well food to be low in or your food to be low in salt
Yep, let's see what the survey said
low in um
Processed chemicals. I don't know
Name a room people frequently add onto a house
A bedroom. Yeah
Name someone famous whose last name is this is gonna be interesting to me
Chico marx name something that you can buy in the shape of a heart
Name a popular mail order catalog
Spiegel name something that people want their food to be low in
Calories, yeah, I don't think it's gonna be enough though
Name a room people frequently add onto a house
You said and the survey said
I don't think it's gonna be enough name someone famous whose last name is marx
You said
Is it up there?
Who would number one name something that you can buy in the shape of a heart take candy said
Lock it good answer
Name a popular mail order catalog
You said
And the survey said
Oh good old spiegel name something that people want their food to be spiegel and spiegel
You said self pet products
good answer
Liz
But we are going to move on
I think of continuing the journey through the game list. I play road rash next. It's been fun
Let's talk about helmet. What do you mean? Talk about helmet? What do you mean?
What is there to talk about with helmet?
H e l m i t
Well, you see my brain was spelling hermit on autopilot and I added an l consciously
All right, uh, let me just switch the game
You're gonna get the those bars again
switching to road rash
No signal. Yeah, no signal
Now road rash was not necessarily a 3do exclusive. What was it?
I think it was originally the original one is I think right
One and contains mature themes it does
Mature themes don't you just ride around on a motorcycle and like punch people? Well, here comes format not supported, you know
We'll see
All right, let's go road rash. This is classic. Oh, yeah it is
I'm not even sure i've ever played this original version either
Still have baby teeth
No, I don't still have baby teeth
The banger
What was that cop the other way?
That cop just did like a seven point turn to get out of it
The reason why it looks like this. Why is it all purple?
So it looks like it's on a game boy color
Holy shit
Why does why does it explode? All right, i'm ready
I'm ready to experience it
road rash and adobe surround
Road rash 3do production team and game credits
Road rash copyright electronic arts. We hope you find road rash as entertaining as we do
Games are a great way to act out fantasies in a virtual environment when no one gets hurt
The game is meant for entertainment purposes only events in the game in the in the video fantasy are not meant to be modeled reality
In any way in the real world if you run from the police and you'll go to jail if you ride expressly involved
Bike, you'll be like it put your back up. You might get hurt. You're gonna use your head. You can hit your head. Okay
Crash mode the arcade version of road rash no character selection. No bike shop and no unnecessary gossip
Whole jimmy changa five levels of head-splitting speed start by choosing an alias complete with a smelly rat bike
And a handful of cash compete. Oh, this is the one go to the bathroom
All right, let's go big game mode
well, uh six one two hundred bucks
uh
Six three two ten five hundred bucks
Five three hundred eight thousand thousand bucks
Uh five ten hundred and forty five pounds eight hundred bucks a psychotic with rabies
What?
Competitive and reckless retro punk pearl wins for anarchy on the open road
What about what about slim jim?
Dropped on his head at an early age mike is a gonzo wild man fearless unpredictable and brain damage
It's limb jim would have been the class clown if he hadn't dropped out voted most likely to die young
Jesus
Next con with the death wish john's daredevil style strikes fear in the hearts of seasoned writers
I feel like all of these could have been a 10 second photoshop that has come through thousands of times in this chat
What do you think?
I think I kind of like I like pearl but curty
poor ronda
a psychotic with rabies
Spoiled rich girl living on the edge three sid writers who throw a tantrum on your face. What does that mean?
I think i'm thinking ronda the rat
I like ronda ronda has rabies and is a psycho
Hang out with your buds and pick up your next race
Low discount prices people killer sports bike. I don't have enough money for that. All right, let's we're gonna hang out here
with dear panzer
All right with schmooze let a fellow rider bend your ear a bit find out who's your friend and who hates your guts
Sign up for a one for one of the happening races in the area
Well, get out of here. Let's smooth a little bit
Scratch my cold tough exterior and you'll find a heart of stone
I'm the real thing and I can tell you know when you see it
On order are the shoe shine boys of the ruling elite
You know what they say about bikes the heavier they are the harder they are to turn
What did that do for me? They did nothing for me
The point of that the guy on the ride
With that beer
That's just how I feel when i'm sitting on the couch
Watching any among us live stream
That's me
All right, we're gonna go to the gold board
Nasty traffic and zombie pedestrians in the urban wait, what do you mean nasty pedestrians?
All right, we're gonna do city. I got 800 bucks 5.3. I don't know how to play
How do you play?
You drive they didn't tell me how to do anything
Aim loading get ready to race. Is it with this only a b or c? Oh jeez
loud
E all right, it's b
All right, that's punch. I just have a punch right now
I can get back on the bike. Wait, I can walk
Where's my bike?
Where's the bike? Where's the bike?
Can I steal cars like in gta?
Run there. No. All right this i'm into this
god
I just bounced off that person. All right, I got I got a rider right here
I got a rider right here
I'm gonna get this
What is this mario kart? Is it the eighth place?
Who's pac-man?
Run away from pac-man quick
Placeman 14th
Oh shit
13 12. We're good
I think that that slime on the ground was sentient
It just I just that just just felt pain
How do I get weapons?
Holy shit. That was just air. That was huge air over that business man
Going way too fast
Shit, what did I bump into?
Come on punch it
sixth place
That person on the street was just trying to punch god damn it
Is there a kick or anything? Do I have to unlock punches and kicks?
You idiot
Like what a fucking asshole
And I i'm gonna can I grab him?
Get out of the way
Oh, you can kick. Okay. How did I do that? It's down
When does the race end am I gonna i'm gonna lose
Kick is op. All right. Good to know
All right. Here we go. I got time
Just don't even focus on hitting anybody
Don't you get a weapon eventually like a baseball bat or something or like a chain or something?
Wow, that was a lot of people there
Okay, I just kicked that guy off the map
That is the biggest taxi i've ever seen
Third place. Let's go
Second place. Let's go
Let me win this race
Fine
Everything's fine
Oh
Damn it. I really thought I was gonna pass him
Give money for placing
I was gonna say with the mask on
winner
Second place. All right
a second place winner
nice
Second place. That's 750 bucks
All right. Now let me go buy a bat or something. Here we go
Okay, mechanized rodents of the urban jungle. They squeak they crawl rat bikes super bikes. All right rat bikes
These are way too expensive. These are three thousand dollars
I don't have even close to enough money
All right, uh the street get out of here sports bikes. I don't have enough money
All right back into the uh, the bar
It moves. I think it's the exact same
It's the same thing. All right the street
Nothing else I can do
All right bulletin board
sierra nevada
Thunder through what's left of the great northwestern timberland into the nappa valley
avoid tourists
Uh blast through the traffic congested suburban wasteland
Face dead man curves and sheer cliff walls
Oh, yes, we will
tourists tourists, whatever
Click on the link. Hold on. Let me see
Let me screen this one
I don't get it. What is it? What am I supposed to be looking at here?
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait
What?
That's that's me. I mean that's the exact clothes that I wear and it's kind of the same hair color
I guess that's all that's the only resemblance. All right, let's go
Oh
I don't even know why I ran that guy over that was uncalled for
It's so hard to do this. It's so hard to get somebody
like that
I can't even hurt him
Come on. Hurry up
God dammit, whatever
I got plenty of time
No ronda
Just run the whole race. I'm not why would I torture you guys like that?
It would be torture. All right, here we go
That was tight
Okay, am I crazy or do you get like a bat and like a whip and stuff?
Yeah, you do. Okay. Yeah, just i'm just checking
I gotta get in first place for that
It's the other game. Oh
So focused on hurting people that I can't even drive
Come on. Fuck you, dude
It's the barefoot bandit. Yeah, it kind of is isn't it?
That's a good pass right there
Should I do enough to at least buy a new bike? I should have it if I get in first place. I'll have it
Yeah
second place
first place
Wait
I'm in first place. How did I get in first place? Was I supposed to go right?
Did I miss the shortcut? Are you sure or did I accidentally do the shortcut?
first place
So quiet like eerie
My brain is telling me that the game crashed because of the audio and I know it didn't
first place
All right, make way for the champion
uh
What the fuck was that?
What the fuck run to the rash finished in first place? I got another thousand bucks
All right. So now I have enough for a bike
I'm, sorry. I just punched you. No, I don't do I come on two thousand bucks
rat bike
Shit, I need to win another race. What about a super bike?
No, these are this is like you're gonna play the game for more than 40 hours. No
Trade in
I can trade in my bike
What do I have?
Oh wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Why why shouldn't why can I read?
Okay
This one is
This one here. How about this one?
250 cc the thing that no one ever picked in mario kart because it was way too hard
50 or 100 cc only these games the game became fucking possible after 100 cc
Uh, what was I saying?
How about the killer rat? How much is that one? I don't have enough. We're gonna do the
I'm gonna do the kamikaze
Let's go. It's pretty good. This little two-stroker has smoked some bigger bikes in this time. Now it just smokes
Handling crisp moderate acceleration substandard top speed
I think sucks
How much is a what about like a a super bike or a sports bike?
No, these are all way too expensive. It's worse than what I have sports bike
13 grand
11 grand. No, I don't have I have to buy one of the shitty ones
Yeah, I gotta buy one of the shitty rat ones
Corsair bike
All right. What about the corsair bike?
RGB bike
Oh
Let's get it
non top speed non negotiable
acceleration imperceptible
Handling. Yeah, I mean like these are huge words
Wait, this is like I already have
Oh, all right. We're gonna go with the paro
Acceleration a bad joke a bad joke. Whatever. I'm just gonna get it. You bought yourself a new bike. Keep the rubber side down
All right. Let's give it a try
What we got on the board here
Your panzer club hang out with your buds and pick up your next race
All right napa valley fix the mic delay. Has there been a mic delay?
Couldn't be
There is a delay. How bad is it? It's a very slight delay
You said there was a delay. Yeah, but I compensated for it by making my microphone of 1000 milliseconds slower
It's a new bike
I'm seeing your moves before you do them
Um
No, one of us get by that car that's fucking ridiculous. No way somebody had to get hit by that thing
What do you mean the bike sucks? Look at the handling
Funniest part about this is it really had a mature audience warning
I really think they do this in mario kart now. This game reminds me of what you hear when you get a concussion
It's true
Oh
That was some wacky racer shit right there
Can I pass this guy? I need to get into first place
over the car
I can't unhear that now
What happens when you get a concussion?
I feel it and I hate it that I feel it
What how did you not fall off?
Yes, I have been concussed before
I need to pass him. I don't want to be in second place
Guys did I tell you the story about me and my brother when we were playing like, uh, like hold on
Sorry, I don't know if I was trying to avoid that person or trying to hit them on purpose. I don't know
I fell off the side of my bed when I was a little kid and I was like probably
10 12
I hit my head on the back of the front of a fireplace and I had to get like six staples in the back of my head
Oh, yeah, that's oh, yeah, that's real
And here we go again
Here I am
Doing my trophy
All right. I think uh, I think we've seen all we need to see from road rash
important look
Important important important important. Hold on. Right. Yeah, now this is what we're talking about. This is a daily occurrence on this stream
$1,000 each
All right coming up next we are going to put in
Uh, I have no idea what this one is. I'd
Not I think it's another uh, it's a japanese. I think
No, there's another japanese. I have another japanese game
Yeah, this is another uh japanese game there not this one
This is called guardian war
For use with the 3do systems
That I don't know that's like a bunch of animals with like swords and shit. I don't know
It could be yeah, it could be pretty pog
I believe this also is an exclusive never heard of this before anywhere else
This is
Guardian well, this could be this could be an rts for all I know
Let's go
This is an rts. Is it though? What would you do an rts with just a game pad and three buttons?
I guess you could didn't they didn't they did it on playstation 1 right guardian war
1994 micro cabin corp
1994 for start
Oh, okay
Can't follow any of this and everything lost its vital energy, okay the powers of darkness
Millions finally the goddess
That's a person
They kind of just they feel like they don't belong in the same universe, right this would be us guardian war, okay
Guardian wait, it's one word guardian war damn. Okay
How do you play new game isn't gonna be like a 150 hour long rpg is it
Okay, give me energy give me life this one might actually be pretty good you might have a gem here
It's like a very long time
golem
guardians of powers kingdom
Use my strength. Okay your peaceful followers sleeping in their shrines all over the world
Have been prevented from waking reddit war awaken them and help crush the evil azrael
Uh don't like this
Don't like that. I hope that's not the whole game
It's a cringe war
Okay, go to the northern shrine and release your friends from the dark powers. At least it's got the doom ost
uh, I get
This is just a really really zoomed in shitty ipad mobile game overworld map
Oh, no
We have to get three stars on this level
Is this action game?
Wait, this is another party member blinks the cat by the way blinks the cat will be
Played shortly here in the next public few weeks. I'd like to watch that
Okay, cool. So we have two party members
These characters look kind of cool. They really do
The reason why the quality just dropped wait, so she was talking to us in person now she's talking to us on a phone
Battle time
Weemote speaker
It really was there are 16 enemies defeat them all
It's like an old old school rpg, huh?
How do I swing?
Don't run away
Oh, wait a minute. Okay, so it's
night
go
slash
It's like a grid based rpg finished moving. No
No, wait, wait, wait, go back here. All right. Holy light healing. Holy light
No, don't do anything
Holy light do damage
Fire emblem. No, just don't do anything
Golden eye music. Yeah, it is
All right slash again
What's going on? I'm not close enough
Flash there we are. Okay slash him
Okay, you can be no, he's still alive I should heal myself I need no
Priest doesn't do anything
All right, priest just sit there do nothing
Holy light, I don't think holy light does damage
The audio is definitely ahead
Are you telling me right? Okay. I'm ready. I'm gonna pick I can't I can't really do it
So i'm gonna veto this one
I don't know. It's like wait, we'll give it a chance. But hold on now
I have to kill 16 of these guys and this is how long it's taken to kill two
All right, fine fine now I won't fine I know you like the little eric cartman guy, I know I get it
Holy light
Pack it up. Let's see it
Nice. Is it heal?
Does it heal the enemy?
Oh shit
We win
All right, well, let's get a little look at the map. We're gonna go up and left
What's that? Oh wait diamonds
Never mind. That's the starting zone
This actually is pretty no, it is cool. It's cool. It is
There's 16 people here this is a tiny map
Whoa danger danger. Oh shit already doing fang 40 out of 40. All right 40 hp
Newgrounds flashbacks. Yeah, it kind of does have that vibe doesn't it? I gotta heal the uh main character here
Pumpkin knight is level two now
Shit cool
Should I do holy light?
Yeah, you have to protect the protagonist good so far
Yeah, I could see myself being
13 14 years old and just being on newgrounds and beating this whole game five times
Bear back there banjo kazooie character. I gotta heal this guy
All right, you do heal
Healing there we go good effects too for a game made in like 1993
Nothing to remember. This is also back
When super nintendo was still the most popular console wasn't it back in like 94?
So this is all right this ain't bad
Hurry up and veto. Well, hold on. Let's see what the next character is and then i'll veto
It's very cute. Yeah, it's not this is a nice game. I give this one a solid 14 year old jeremy play through five times
All right, this looks like a
An encounter wait, what are they doing back there?
Stay here
All right, I think this guy's hard
Defend you're gonna walk over here. Oh shit. He is walking over here. Okay
Flash
What is that you are new bear or bandicoot or something? I don't know
Holy light here is a companion. You can't stop here. Oh
Kobold. Oh, there we go. That's what it is
Foxy from five nights at freddy
Oh, he's faster now he's shimmying a little more
danger
All right, look there's chests over here
I gotta open up at least one of these chests
I got 63. I'm okay
Behold pumpkin basic level is now two
Just clean this up. Holy light
Everybody's gonna get addicted to this
No, no, I will not
I just want to see the at least first level and maybe the next party member your new power
All right chests, let's see there
Listen, it's a different weapons
And a stone. Oh, that's cool
Probably have to grind
I'm sure you do
What's in this one? Oh, where's stone? Cool. All right, let's keep going
I got three enemies let them come to me. That's good. That's fine. I'm dead right off the bat
Uh
The disc just made a really awful noise in there
That was not a good sound. I don't know if my noise gate might not have picked that up. That was a crunch
Just went
uh
My you remember the last time remember I told you
The 3do gets really hot and maybe it's mechanically breaking
I don't know how long it's been four and a half hours. It's all right. We're okay
How hot is it? It's a little hot. It's a little warm
You're smelting the disc
It's all right. We got what's after this
Let me see
Psychic detective is gonna probably a whole stream. I need to be honest with you
You guys have a wire head
I'm getting lots of wire head vibes from psychic detective. That's probably gonna have to be an entire stream
I'm saving some of these ones
We'll go through some of the fun ones to veto and just play for like 30 minutes 40 minutes
But there are some that are going to be probably at least four or five hours
It's gonna die
Wait, what happens if he dies?
Okay
But why did he buy see a 45 health down?
I didn't lose. Well, do I need to kill for this?
They do it
No, this is the boss zone
I need to heal
It's a missing texture, I don't think it's a missing texture
Don't lose all your bad
That's okay
I'm not concerned about that
What you worms dare oppose our lord azrael, all right, then die
Music change. Why do we get a music change? Okay. I gotta heal him
Four that's it. The soundtrack's pretty good. Yeah, it is
These defense panels maybe they are
Well, that hurt all right. Well now he's off that panel. Let's see if we can get him
Yeah, yeah, that's a little better
Holy like this guy
You got a new soundtrack you can play
It's true
He's focusing the healer. That's smart. I'm not gonna do you any good though
Holy light might affect multiple targets. It's lined up
maybe
This is cool, this actually is pretty cool
What IGN give us?
52 damage. Holy shit. That was a lot
Are we surprised if IGN reviewed this game?
7.8 out of 10
That's not bad
Wait, oh this is the this must be the boss there's a ton of health. I gotta heal myself
Look up the meta critic scores
You just said i'm gonna veto this game
I know I know but I just want to get at least to pass the first level or two. I don't believe this
Feeded all the enemies nearby
Okay, let's go done
You win
You go very talking. Who's just talking? Okay. Well, do I have to go there? I guess we this is the next squad
Land of east canal. There are 17 enemies to feed them all. All right
This is a fun game. It's a cute game, but we got a lot of 3DO games to get through
It's cool though. I like it. Let me just try to see if I can get holy light on more than one person
You know what I mean? Like I have to figure that out first. I know just wait. I vetoed it already
It's it's vetoed trust me. I just want to see if I can wholly light on one person in the line like you know
two people
Holy light
Even get these both these people
No, they're not lined up. It's just right there. All right, that's cool. That's cool. All right. All right
It's fun game. The game's cool
That was guardian war. I highly recommend it if you
Um want to have like a bag of cheetos after school late for like a couple hours a day
That's what I would do
All right. Let me put in let's put in the probably one of the last one or two of the night
today
Do probably a couple more
I gotta pee again
I'm peeing on the hour almost every hour
Let's give me a break every exactly. It's been exactly every hour and 30 minutes, hasn't it?
It has been
First time I went pee was an hour and 30 second time was three hours and now it's four hours and 30 minutes
I'm on an exit i'm on a schedule apparently i'll be right back
Okay, this next one
is
Probably the one that i'm most interested in
Not because I think the game's gonna be any good
Because like the game's gonna be fun to play or there'll be something interesting
But just because this is one of the most expensive 3do games
The game is called captain quasar
Made by studio 3do and it was the most expensive game. I don't know why
Break it
Yeah, all the expensive ones we smash over our heads
How much was it? I don't want to say
I don't want to say because it's embarrassing
But hey remember I own it forever and it's mine forever and I have it and it'd be worth probably three grand in five years
No, it was not more. Okay. It was not more than a hundred dollars. Okay, I promise
Captain quasar that's not captain quasar. That's captain quasar. Apparently this game's worth more than 200
The universe was once a lovely place to live broad smiles beamed from every planet in the milky way
Law abiding galactic citizens thrived under the happy twinkling stars and goodwill flowed from one end of the cosmos to the other
But then things changed
Are you hearing my voice first?
Is this the sad twilight of our glorious civilization are these the last ticks of the cosmic clock? Oh dear
Where are we to turn? What are we to do? What? Oh, what is to be our face?
Relax oh my goodness here he comes captain quasar
Me
I hope there's a musical interlude before every level every awesome
Watch this be a fucking card game a disappointing, right?
That's a clap for me there that was awesome captain quasar
reviews
Always watch previous first before the movie. I hope it's the same basketball game
Battle an encounter between opposing forces
Same bet is the basketball game
Battle sport, do I have this?
Holy shit, I don't think I have battle sport
I might
Would you actually play ball?
Rocket league, but
I don't say that
Don't say that
Is this like rocket league?
It is rocket league, but there's no weapons in rocket league. There's no missiles
That looks fun
All right remind me to go over my collection of like 30 games that are still left over here and look for battle sport
It might be in there. I don't know. Okay captain quasar new game. Let's go
Oh
Yes, more cinematics my favorite
Get in here quasar sit anywhere quasar. I have a tough assignment for you direct from intergalactic headquarters
I'll give it to you straight
A dastardly crime syndicate is intent on conquering the galaxy
Leading this space riff raff is a butt ugly strong man named
Leapfrog determined to take over one planet at a time aiding ox are two other hoods dubar a renegade
Synthetic who threatens to addict the galaxy to a heinous spice he's manufacturing and zang the head of an intergalactic terrorist ring
You quasar our last chance for stopping them
Your first mission will be to defeat dubar on his home world of crag a dry desert planet in the oint
Justin roiland doing a bit
And you can purchase equipment and supplies from the police armory if you've got the cash now get out of here and don't let me down
Ha ha ha whoa now those are look at those things
Dive into his ship. I hope he does
And I hope he gets stuck
Knew it. Yes, I love that trope from every cartoon
What's he doing in there?
No
This guy's drives around the world and just giggles. Oh, no, he's like me
This way
Headquarters to quasar the renegade prime lord dubar is manufacturing a heinous spice that threatens to addict the entire galaxy
Now dubar is using cargo rockets like these to transport the terrible spice all over the cosmos
Your mission is to stop dubar spice rockets before they launch and to penetrate to destroy the nearby factories where the spices process destroy the spice factory
This is a creepy pasta game
Fuck I stop stop laughing
Don't be this character. These are good loading screens
It's a fun game. Anyways, this looks cool
Okay
Wow
I got missiles
I got grenades
Holy shit, this game might be the best one
It's like contra. How am I supposed to be on this creepy alien planet?
Where's our space suit?
What we can't afford many more screw-ups like that
What are you
Wait this this actual destruction
Holy shit. Okay, cool. Hold on
Let's hurt myself. Watch out
Please wait ammo ammo money
We help
This is so loud
Okay, let me help you there
Go help. I wonder. It's probably bosses
What's that?
crack
Okay, I mean wait, don't let it fly. Don't let it fly get it
Is it destroyed?
I think so
Yeah, this music's giving me anxiety
So this is a crackhead game
Whatever
Get up. Get up. Get up. Don't let it go
Get it
Got it
What?
Up here. Holy shit
A three how many more do I need?
Oh my god, there's like silos here. There's like to get the recycling bin
I'm out of ammo for everything
I have nothing left
What do I do now?
Wait, can I get in the water?
Where do I go?
Where am I supposed to go?
When I was getting lost to find the box
These earthworm gym
It does kind of look like okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait
I got that one
Map shit. Hold on. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Nobody stop. Stop shooting me
I need ammo
Find the find the what?
Let's try this
Diddy Kong racing
Wait, there are people in there
There were people in there. Why did I do that?
How many people were in there?
All right down
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. All right, there's two more
Oh, i'm alive. Oh, i'm good. Good. Good. Good. Good. We're fine. Fine. Fine
Diddy Kong racing
That hurt
Okay, I can get a password
Now that's a good link is it though?
Not bad
I'll put it up
Pretty good
Oh, I can't kill him. That's
All right
Good thing I didn't enemy interrogation a teleporter will take you to a secret storage outpost
Use the password bb a a a a bb
bb a a a a bb forget it. What is it bb a a a a bb?
nice
All right. Now I come and steal whatever it is i'm stealing
I don't know what i'm doing here
What's the point of that? How do I get back? Oh, can I not go through this? Why?
Yes, I can just load up
Weird level design. Okay, we're good
Penis music wait, wait, no, no, no, what is it?
Oh mighty quasar do not overlook the splendor of the surrounding desert. It is not as bare as it may seem
What is the objective though, what am I supposed to most dead again
I'm gonna die. I'm dead. I have one more tumor health
You can upgrade your weapons. Holy shit. That guy blew up
All right. I robbed the bank
I gotta get down here. These are the silos, right? He took off. Fuck. All right
How do I leave?
How much more of this shit is there to do?
Like a power-up. Oh nice
I can't lose
There's no losing in captain quasar
Shit, someone got away
All right double power-up
Why am I dying so fast?
This is not really space music to me
There's only so much I could like destroy silos. How do I leave?
I want to end the mission
I think I did enough
I did enough come you get to choose what space sounds like
Um, I don't know. What do you why do you get to choose what it doesn't sound like?
shit
How many more silos?
I don't want to do any more silos, dude
It's endless
Don't shoot me. I'm just a cadet. Um, my name is dumb star
Head i'm cadet. My serial number is baba
Aba no, that's not it. Hey, I never got a serial number. So baba. Aba gotta go in that teleporter
Oh, it's different. This is like a spreader
Come on, don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't
baba aba
Oh i'm surrounded
Here it comes here comes the best part, right?
What is the objective?
This is stupid
There is no objective there has to be an objective
Don't worry. I never wanted to be a criminal
I thought I signed up for a bellhop position on pleasure planet power-ups. I'm invisible and I have super speed
This is this is not fair
Teleporter if you insist on attacking i'll have you know that this boot camp doesn't fall easily. Okay. Goodbye
This is 200 dollars down the toilet
No, it's
This wasn't 200 dollars. We need to get that clear
This is the same room of just firing machine guns
Destroy it
I don't know. I think i'm gonna puke
Is there anybody else getting sick?
It just hit me right now. It doesn't be like a ton of bricks. It just smashed into me
Shit, i'm gonna be sick. I'm gonna be sick. I'm gonna be sick. I'm gonna be sick. I have to stop
I'm gonna be sick. Uh, oh
All right, I stopped that that was captain quasar. That was pretty fun. I I mean, I don't know
It's not very fun. It was stupid
But I mean it's expensive. So I mean that means something right?
Uh, here come the bars. We're gonna do one more. The last one we're gonna do is
Hey you the fuck think we got all day in here. You've got a galaxy to save scared the absolute hell out of me
All right, here come the uh the bars. Yeah, i'll put this you know, i'll put this up
So I don't like hurt anybody's eyes
All right, give me a sec the last one we're gonna play for today. What do we got?
He owed
He owed and it's in like booger writing go to try
He owed like pissed off he owed
Yeah after this this is okay. I gotta this thing's gonna take a break
I'm gonna be sick for a second
The music the how fast the screen was moving
He owed 1995
Game load game delete game
Not sure i'm in that
Food yet. Let's go new game
Okay, this is
I'd like to watch
I'm over 30. I have my arthritis in my fingers. I don't eat
quiche
I'm over 30. How about yeah, that's accurate be
begin transmission dear mom
What a crappy day or really crappy it just seemed like a sweet deal back at base
Imitate an ice cube for three months eat some dumb mercs for two weeks and then three more months in the fridge on the ride home
Two weeks of work for six months of pay not bad. Not bad at all
Well, the cook is always the last to know what the hell is going on
This is like a riddle of what food am I?
I never would have taken this if I knew it was going to be a bug hunt
I hate bug hunts the mercs got greased inside half an hour. No surprise
They were all a bunch of sorry-ass stim freaks too bad
They're the ones who knew how to move this crate
I've been awake three hours help is three months away and the bugs that we already managed to blast a few holes in this ship
I figured my chances are better outside than being a sitting duck out here. The weapons are gone
But my firing brain is gone gulps got to run things are heating up
I guess it's time to find some fresh meat love ox ai dungeon
Hey, that's good. Okay. Here we go. Is that good? Let's jump. What's my I have a frying pan
That's actual frying pan. What's the top left supposed to indicate? Is that my health? What is the feet? What's the feet for?
How do I get over this?
It's there's a feet cam
All right, kill him
Why is that? I don't know why that whose feet are those those my feet. I don't get it
All right, i'm gonna go this way. Don't I did I jump too far?
Okay down something behind me
I got stuffed under something
I can't just die in the first room. Okay, I made it going up. Can I get a gun?
Okay, what's this log in? I can't log in there. I have no login. Oh shit. Okay in here
The weapon no, it's just health
only pan and feet cam
Nice am I okay?
So what happened the lower health that I get do I get like a doom when my feet get more crusty or what?
What's no, what's the indicator up? What does that mean?
Like do I get we get dirty bare feet for the more health I lose. Let me try this again
I just put it on easy. Let's just go down. It's your feet level. Somebody's got the speed run on this. I'm sure it's insane
Switch to the feet weapon. I only have a frying pan. I don't have anything else
Get out of there and only so far we get drew crew. It's time for a feet fleet
All right, don't fuck this up. Just go here. Let me go across is this hurt
It's not I want to get to at least one new weapon
Eat fleet feet fleet now. None of you guys actually want to see this game played you guys are painfully typing that and then
Rolling back in your seat going. Uh
And somebody just look up poed. What does the feet meter do? It has to be a reason for its existence
It doesn't just exist for no reason. I see a weapon over there. It looks like a weapon, right?
Oh shit. What is it then?
Oh, get me out of here. Get me out. Get me the fuck out. Get me out. Just get me out
I don't want this on my history
It's on no it's on my history and did I fall through?
I'm gonna go up
What the fuck just happened why did it go up I can't ride it up
Being crushed
I don't think I can take it anymore. I don't think I take it. I think I have to stop
I can't take it anymore. It's I can't do it. It's freaking me out. This is fucking me up. I can't captain
Quasar made me physically ill and now I don't know what to do
What this is your basic travel mode? You can change your foot speed between normal and turbo
Press x what?
What?
It's just to put shoes on button
That made it so much worse that made it worse, but I wanted to be a feet again. I'll throw up
Wait new weapon. How do I change that? What's throwing?
Nice. Okay. What is this fucking game? I don't know man
Something that's about to get vetoed in exactly 30 seconds
It wasn't even running shoes either
Go up. What the fuck get up there and quasar i'm gonna puke in my own lap
All right, which one goes up? Let's go over this way
Okay
Okay. Okay. Okay
Okay. No, i'm done. I have to veto this I have to veto the whole stream actually
I gotta get up. I'm gonna puke
I'm not even kidding either. That's the worst part
We made it to five hours. We're good
That was a bare feet
video game
I'll see you guys tomorrow
Tomorrow, I don't know if we're gonna do 3do
Um, I mean we might need a 3do break stream tomorrow
I'd do something else or we might just start one of the long form 3do games
So tomorrow we're not gonna blow through like six seven plus games on the 3do. If I play it again
We're gonna do like psychic detective or we'll do something else
I will see you guys tomorrow. Thanks for watching. Thanks for sticking around as always
Uh, thanks for the like 800 subs. It's been an absolute insane amount
Oh ftk, right? I want to tell you ftk is happening
on october 3rd
That is the new date for ftk saturday the 3rd in the afternoon. I believe starting at 3 pm
Pacific time it is not happening next weekend or this weekend. I wasn't exactly sure the moment I was going to come back
So I just decided look let's just push it out. So I know that i'll be back, right?
So october 3rd is the new date. That's when everybody can kind of reconvene and do it all over again
And I will see you guys
But let's show the credits because it's probably going to be insane because there were like 6 000 community subs earlier
Look for battle sport. That's right. I will let's uh go over there. Here they come
In alphabetical order going at insane speed unreadable. Thanks everybody for subscribing. Thanks all the community subs
It's been a lot. I think I missed a lot of subs
It was just coming in so hot that I I couldn't even catch them
Thank you everybody to continue to give this stream insane amounts of money. I hope it's worth it. Thank you
Turbo credits, that's right. Yeah. Well, maybe well maybe we'll switch away from 3do tomorrow
There's so much I have for it. I'd rather let's spread it out a little over the next couple of weeks
What do you say seems like a good idea to me saw saw saw
Let's do a raid. Yeah, you know what somebody is streaming right now that uh, mr
Sark is streaming right now is one of my favorite internet funny people
We never catch sark streaming. So we caught him here. We're gonna raid. Mr. Sark. No raid spoilers
What do you mean don't spoil? Yeah, i'll see you tomorrow. I really just got like physically ill, although
I have been streaming for like between four and a half to six hours lately and i'm kind of have the way it's gonna stay
You know why this is credits is insane. This is so many people
We're not even past the v's
This is a stupid amount of people. It really is. Holy shit. Thanks again guys. We'll see you tomorrow
Go, uh, tell mr. Sark. Hello
Say glad to catch your stream go ahead and read raid the mr. Sark the mr. Sark
Is it right? Yeah. All right guys
Have a good rest of your night. We'll see you tomorrow
Take care and goodbye