Alright, should we back to normal? You guys can hear me, right?
Should be back to normal. Alright, so what uh...
Ooh! I know! I know! I know! I know what we can do!
The reaction test! Remember last night we talked about the reaction test?
I was gonna prove to you guys that I see the world at 1.14 speed.
Okay, where is it? Reaction test. So human benchmark?
Let's get the camera back on. Wait, is the camera even gonna be able to work?
Let me uh... oh no, it's still this like purple shit.
You could just see every individual here. That was disgusting.
What's the best reaction test? Is that the one?
Or is there a better one? Let's change the title to...
Well, we'll just hang out. We haven't really... we haven't had a proper
just sit around and chill hang out stream in like a month or two.
So how about uh 1.14 brain speed? No one's gonna know what the
fuck that even means. Do they have to... do they though?
All right, so let's get a... let's get the camera back.
I'm like ugly right now though. Should I like... should I really be
broadcasting myself to IRL? With the pasted on
dog hairs that are on my face right now? You know what I'm saying?
That looks okay. All right, we look... we look terrible.
Let me get that on screen now. This should be just a window, right?
What the human benchmark stuff is there? Is there some other cool
shit to do? Do a shaving stream? I can't... I don't have like the
necessary means to do that. Space bar challenge?
All right, so you have to wait for green.
So you have to do this five times. Do it over here. I'm not going to
shave at my desk. Shave at the desk? No. I'm gonna get in
trouble if I do that. Won't I get in trouble? All right,
let's do it. I just want to see what it looked like.
Let's see. There's like number memory, react verbal memory, visual memory.
Okay, let's give it a go. Which one is this?
Why do I have so many windows open? Which one is the real one?
Can I not? Why do I have an Xbox gaming overlay?
What the hell are you talking about? Xbox gaming overlay.
Let's try it again. There we go. Okay, finally. Move that and move this.
All right, click to start. This is going to see how
fast my reactions are. You're gonna get a fucking bird's eye view of the whole
thing. What's the blue? Oh, fuck. It's the...
Here we go. Ready? So when the box turns green, click as quickly as you can.
207. 210. That's not bad, is it? 24... That was faster than the last one. How
was that slower? 216. Okay, you're
currently in the top 89 percentile for this test.
That means I'm better than 89. That means I'm better than 89 percent.
Right? That's pretty good. Let's do it again.
Let's do it again. I can get a better one. You ready? It means you're 89.
Three people have taken the test. No, that's like 50,000 people have taken
this test. Under 200. Fuck yeah. Almost under
200. Look, I'm as good as if you connected to
like a server in Asia, right? That's pretty fast.
I'm as fast as a packet of data going from my computer to Asia and back.
That's fucking so fast. 50 dollars came in
from Visual Warlock. Thanks for the 50 bucks.
And you say, sorry you got scammed. I have this on top of the two shirts I
bought. Speaking of t-shirts, they're available
right now if you do exclamation point shirts.
There are two... Well, that's not true. There's one new shirt,
and there's a returning shirt. Glueman's back. They're both 20 dollars.
If you want one, they're there. And they're going to be there forever.
I can do this again. Top 93 percentile. I can get under
200. But thank you so much Visual Warlock for the 50
fucking dollars. It's a huge amount of money. Thank you. Somebody's like,
somebody's having like a party downstairs. Do you hear that?
No, that one doesn't count. That one doesn't count. I gotta refresh.
There's like a party going on downstairs. What am I missing right now?
This is not going to save as my average, right? This is a fucking...
There is a rave going on downstairs. I'm almost curious as to go check and
see what it is. Okay, here we go. Under 200. I know I
can do it. It's a six out of five. What's what's
going on? No, don't save this score. Just refresh the page.
Ready? What if I caught that? Two... Same exact number.
Do it again. I can get under 200. I know I can.
The first one was, I was literally the host of the server.
Keep it under fucking 200. Got it. 186 milliseconds.
Average rate. Let's see, what's that? Currently in the top 92 percentile for
the test. Okay, pretty cool. How about number
memory test? This one looks cool. So this one is...
The average person can remember seven numbers at once. What's the longest
number you can memorize? I feel like I had some decent
practice with this one. Two. What was the number? The number was
two. 72. 72. Honda. Honda. Honda. Honda.
406. 1048. You're gonna have to start... Remember, I'm gonna have to start
thinking about phone numbers. Fuck off. Not you. No, no. I was
pointing at the car. 72. 228.
22. 228. 99. 52. 99. 502.
968. 5736. 968.
5736. 968. 968.
9736. 125. 0314. 125.
03414. 125. 03414. 125. 03414.
492. 8348. 87. 4928.
34. 887. 4928. 34887. 4928.
4928. 88347. What about verbal memory?
Verbal memory test. You'll be shown words one at a time. If you've seen a word
during the test, click safe for work. If it's a new
word, click not safe for work. Wait, what's the actual thing?
You'll be shown words one at a time. If you've seen a word during the
test, you've seen it. Amilas. No, that's new. Mango.
These are all new. Garments. Mango. Seen it.
Heartland. New. Seen it. Seen it. Seen it. That's new. That's new.
Convet and that's new. Seen it. No. Seen it.
No. Seen it. No. No. No. Seen it. No.
No. Seen it. No. Seen it. No. Seen it. Seen it. Seen it.
Seen it. New. It's new. New. Seen it. Seen it. Seen it.
Seen it. Seen it. New. New. Seen it. New. Seen it.
Seen it. Seen it. Seen it. New. Seen it. Seen it. Seen it.
New. Seen that. Seen that one too. Stop. That's new. Seen that one.
Top 79%. Top 79%. No, this is not. I'm doing pretty good.
Visual memory. You have to change how this one is.
I'm being squished. That's all right though. Okay.
Memorize the squares. Every level a number of tiles will flash. Memorize
them and pick them again after the tiles reset.
Okay. It's getting bigger. I'm gonna do all right on this one.
Sorry. Let's stop. Top 66%. His IQ is increasing. Somebody stop him.
You are never gonna stop me. Okay. What is about a little fun little
game so we can play? Let chat do it. What? How can I let chat do
that? Do a personality test? We don't. We did those before. Google
feud. Is that just a family feud that I can play?
I want to play family feud right now. Where can I get one?
Where can I actually get a family feud? I'm like into that right now.
It's on SNES. No, this guy's gotta be like a new
family feud game, right? Is it on Steam? Is that for real? Family feud? I don't see
family feud on Steam. Do Google? We did Google
feud before. I kind of got most of it out of that.
Try to beat Christopher Robin baseball. I almost lost my fucking mind playing
that game. Kahoot? Don't I need to? No. Kahoot
was a mess. I can't play Kahoot. The last time I
played Kahoot it was an absolute disaster.
Online family feud. Oh like Jeopardy. I want to play Jeopardy.
All right, I got it. I got it. This is probably gonna be loud. I'm on like
MSN zone. Does this site even work? I don't think this site actually still
works. Oh boy, there are ads all over this.
Oh thank god you can't hear this. One, two, three,
four. There are four ads. There's two playing video ads
here and here. There's a banner here. This is unbelievable.
Here's the thing. I had adblock on and I had to turn it off to load the page.
Oh my fucking god. All right, here we go. Let's hope this is worth it.
Buy the full version. You can fuck right off. Where's my headphone?
There goes your like credit card. Um, just like to add for like chicken
nuggets and stuff on the bottom. I refuse to have that show up on
the screen. Look at this bullshit. All right, family
feud. I feel like doing this right now. Let's do it.
Play it. Let's play the family feud. We surveyed 100 people.
Top seven answers are on the board. Here's the question.
Name something you'd find in a school lost and found box.
Uh, keys. Survey says. Nobody know kids have keys? Yes they do.
Uh, Game Boy. Survey says. What? Um, a coat.
A sweater. Coat. Jacket. How about, uh, why would you lose your socks?
All right, I'm gonna take off my shoes and my socks and then I'm gonna lose
and I'm gonna put my shoes back on. Why would that happen? Lunchbox.
Survey says. Glasses. Everybody loses their damn glasses.
Survey says. Yep. Jacket, glasses, lunchbox.
Backpack. Survey says. Strike three. Too bad. Fine. Let's take a look.
So what is it? Jacket. Can we see two, please?
Hat. Let's see number three. Gloves. Let's see number six.
A book. Seven, let's see it. Shoes. How does somebody lose their shoes?
You don't, how do you lose your shoes? Let's play some more Feud.
All right, give me something else. Brown suit. We surveyed 100 people.
The top six answers are on the board. Here's the question.
Name something people need good posture to do.
Office work. Fucking. Survey says. Paint? Painting? Survey says.
Streaming's not gonna be on here. This is probably, this website is
running on like MSN games. Good posture to do.
Surgery? No. Yoga? Survey says.
How is that the last answer? Lift exercise.
Weights. You'll get it. Like weight lifting.
Survey says. All right, what do you need good posture to do that I'm not
unaware of? That's not office work. Look at what you missed.
Let's see number one. And we see two. Untrue.
How do you, dancing? You need posture for dancing.
Typing. Let's see number four. Walk confidently.
You need to be able to walk, do like the Chad walk.
Why would you ever type walk confidently and play the piano? I mean
you do, but you. Betcox. Sacrifices you make.
No, what? What is this? Late nights. The weekends.
And early mornings. What's it for? Not a big deal to other companies.
Right. But they are to us. What company is it?
That's why our fast internet and scalable voice solutions are backed by 24-7
personal support. 24-7 personal support.
Right in my hometown. Isn't small to us. Right.
Switch to Cox business today. Don't do that.
We surveyed 100 people. The top five answers are on the board.
Here's the question. I'm gonna get an ad every two rounds.
Name a cartoon movie that features animals as the main characters.
What is the name? Zootopia.
Oh god. Why did the seven animals? Those are dwarves.
Beauty and the Beast. Well he wasn't really technically an animal.
He was a person that was an animal hybrid. 101 Dalmatians.
The Lion King. Number one. Finding Nemo.
Fish aren't animals though.
Fish aren't animals. They're like aquatic frustations.
Babe the Pig. Madagascar.
And Bambi. Let's see what Cox can do for you.
Let's find out what do you think we're gonna get. Cox? Well we're gonna get
like a fucking KFC ad or something.
We surveyed 100 people. The top four answers are on the board.
Question. Babe is also not a cartoon. Yes that's true.
Name something on which you might need your boss's signature.
Eviction notice. No um pink slip. Your report card. No that's your
parents. Um what you need a boss's signature
for? Like to get permission to go on a
field trip? A check. You wait your boss has to sign the
paycheck? What about direct deposit? Um tax info.
Vacation. Like I have to go on vacation so I have to have the boss
sign the vacation slip. Vacation. There it is. Vacation request.
Um vacation time. Sick. Sick leave? That's not the sick you go
when you're sick.
What do we need permission for? A contract.
And a raise. Contract was that that was so vague though. Anything can be a
contract. Ad coming up.
200 points and the bonus. Answer in 50 seconds.
Block please. Name a job in which you need to wash your hands often.
Uh janitor. No uh cook. Name an animal you would find in the ocean but not
in a pond. Turtle. No um shark. No
shark. Name a good excuse to eat soup.
Sick. You're sick. Why might someone's phone number be unlisted?
Uh criminal. Uh criminal. Because they like call I don't know. Name a
place where a child makes friends. Playground.
Cook. Chef. Thank you. Animal you'd find in the ocean but not a pond.
Shark. There's definitely there's no sharks in ponds. Thank you.
You eat soup when you're sick because it it's easy to go down easy
to digest. Someone that has an unlisted phone
number could be a criminal or could be somebody trying to scam you.
Playground to school. Give me 55 seconds on the clock.
More? Name a job in which you need to wash your I um
wash dot uh doctor. You find in the ocean but not in a pond.
Turtle. No uh find in an ocean but not a pond.
A sunfish. No a a whale. Name a good excuse to eat soup.
Lazy. Because it's really easy. Snape. Why would somebody's phone be
unlisted? Privacy. Where a child makes friends.
School. Unlisted because they're dead. I'm gonna get over 200. I got it.
$326 plus $205 plus $20,000 equals $20,531
dollars. What were the top ones? Medical professional right?
Shark. I got that top answer. Good excuse to eat soup.
Sick. Why would your number be unlisted? Because privacy got that one
number one. And it's definitely gonna be school.
School child. I got it. Look at me. Look at me go.
That's our game. Hurry on back and play the family feud.
It's gonna be the ads gonna be so loud. Wait what?
Uh I can't I don't think I can play the game anymore.
Get unlimited play. Download now to own it.
Uh I don't can I click the button again? I don't want the ad to blow everybody's
eardrums out. Here it comes. Play the game again.
Yeah here comes a business. We see the sacrifices you make.
The late nights, the weekends, and early mornings
may not be a big deal to other companies but they bus.
That's why our fast internet and scalable voice solutions are backed by
24-7 personal support from experts right in your hometown.
Because your business isn't small to us. Switch to Cox business today.
That was a double middle finger. I win.
That's a lot of subs. Uh Colossal Chief
uh just gave 10 community subs. Thank you so much Colossal.
That is a lot of subs. Thank you so much.
What might a person make when first learning how to knit? It's a sweater.
Absolutely. Grandma a blanket. That's a pretty good one I think.
Blanket sweater uh hat. Hat is pretty easy
correct answer I think. Blanket sweater hat.
Tie. Gloves. Gloves. That's a good one. Gloves or
mittens is better. Only three people said mittens.
Um blanket sweater hat mittens. Socks. Can you knit socks? That doesn't
work right? It doesn't. How do you knit slippers? Wouldn't
they just be like old fucking pizza? That'd be like
walking in a pizza. It'd be like like squishing around
moving around. Wait what is it? Uh what's number one? What is number one?
Socks. Slippers. Mittens. Blanket. Sweater. Hat. Scarf.
One more. Scarf. Blanket. Sweater. Hat. Slippers. Socks. Mittens.
Quilt is blanket though. Quilt is blanket. We already got it.
Um leg sleeves. A beanie. A beanie is hat. Uh bed.
Yeah I remember when grandma knitted me a whole bed.
It was really comfortable. A pillow. A doll.
That's not a bad one. Doll like a little action figure.
So what is it? Potholder. Grandma I'm gonna burn my fucking hands.
That is the most dangerous gift grandma could ever give you.
That's not very heat resistant. All right name a kind of hat that would be weird
to see a magician pull a bunny from. Um a construction hat.
Construction. Construction. Chef's hat. Yeah hard hat.
Chef's hat. Not from a chef's hat. What kind of hat?
Wizard's hat. A wizard. Wizard's hat. A cowboy hat. Okay cowboy hat.
Hard hat. Sombrero. Hard hat. Cowboy hat. Sombrero. What is number one?
What do you guys think? From a wig. That's not a hat.
Like a baseball bat. You'd be a such a shitty magician.
Baseball hat. Cowboy hat. Sombrero. Hard hat. Football helmet. That's not bad.
A fedora. No it's not gonna be fedora. Top hat is a magic. That's a
magician's hat already. Isn't a top hat what a magician pulls
their rabbits out of? No it is a top hat. A beret. Still doing
better than average. No!
I'm not gonna tell you what movie that was.
I don't want you guys to know. We surveyed 100 people.
The top five answers are. What is it? Here's the question.
Where do many teenagers have their first kiss?
In their car. In a car.
Yeah. In a car.
Movie theater. Like at the movies. Like movie.
Right. Will you pick up on that? You will. Okay at the movies.
At dinner. No that doesn't happen.
Like outside. Like at like at the park.
Where do many teenagers have their first kiss?
On their mouth. I mean you're being very literal about that. I don't think
that's what they're looking for. Under the bleachers. That's like a
meme right? That's like a teenager meme. I mean like
school. That's what like that's what I was going for.
School dance. Yeah that's that's true.
Prom right? Cars. School dance. Movies. Park.
That party is a good one. At like a party.
Birthday party. No you don't get a kiss on your birthday party.
Beach. It's not a bedroom. One guy said something here.
Front door. At the front door you're gonna do that? You're gonna do that?
You're gonna you're gonna kiss? You're gonna get a kiss in front of
dad? Don't think that's gonna happen.
We surveyed 100 people. The top three answers are on the board.
Only three. Here's the question. Name something you find out about a word
by looking it up in the dictionary. What the hell are you talking about?
Name something you find out about a word.
That could be anything. Find out about a word?
Yeah definition. Definition. Survey says.
Adjectives. Verbs. I don't. Noun. But what do you find out about a word
by looking it up in the dictionary? Yeah like answer try again.
That's all right no it doesn't work. Thesaurus.
Survey says. Description. Survey says. Pronunciation.
Survey says. If you're not looking for a definition of pronunciation or
description why would you look something up in
the dictionary? Meaning. Make meaning. Right but that is
definition. How to spell it. Survey says.
He's cheating. You go on to fast money.
It's fast money. You'll have two chances to get 200 points and a bonus.
Tell no one answer you'll pass and we'll come back. Could you read them?
You'll have 50 seconds. Clock please. Name something you have
a one in a million chance of experiencing. Jackpot.
Name a time when you exchange gifts. Christmas.
Name a way that someone might cheat in a baking contest.
Boxed. Boxed food. But how do you always say
boxed ingredients. Prepared. Already prepared food. Boxed food. What the fuck.
Packaged. Pack. Packaged. When learning to drive what might
your teacher do that indicates she's afraid?
Scream. Name a person who might call you by a childhood nickname even
after you've outgrown a neighbor.
You didn't give me points. Why do I have a time limit?
Name something but you're not gonna if you get a jackpot you're not gonna be
good. What I have to do what do I have to
do? When exchange gifts. Christmas. No what. Oh shit.
Easter. Boxed food. Scream.
Jump out of car. No what the fuck.
Ask money and get those 20,000 bonus points. Let's see.
We asked this question. You said we asked you.
That's one in a million. Christmas. I don't know what's
happening. It's still giving me points for
questions I answered already. It's starting over again.
Okay let's reload it. This game sucks. I'm gonna turn it down. It's gonna be
loud. I'm sorry. Full screen option.
Full screen option. I can't it'll take over my entire laptop.
Yes that's I stream on a laptop. I have an Intel
i7-775,000 M. I have an i7-67,000
K. M. There's no full screen you liars.
i7-750,000 M. No what what is it 7700K?
i7-770K right. Name something your car would be less safe without
brakes. Game's muted. Oh I'm sorry. Your car would not be safe without a
wheel. Survey says. How would you drive a car
without a wheel? It would just go straight and you'd crash into a wall.
Name something your car would be less safe without um
seatbelt. Survey says. Look at those two dogs.
A driver. Survey says. Lights. Like headlights.
Survey says. Epic boomer bumper stickers. That's a good one.
Brake seatbelt lights. Survey says. Strike three.
Too bad. Let's take a look at what you missed.
Let's see number three. Airbags. Let's see number four. A car alarm. Number five.
And locks. Let's see how you did. Well some of those okay we were being a
little too literal. Like safe as in crashing a car versus safe as in
someone's gonna break into your car. We were thinking too literal.
Let's play some more feud. Round two. We surveyed 100 people. The
top six answers are on the board. Here's the question. Name a part of
the job that flight attendant must get sick of.
Um the safety instruction right. Just the safety instruction.
Survey says. No no they don't get sick of safety. I'm talking about like
the say the instructional thing where they like talk at the beginning.
Survey says. Not like the instructional portion.
Not babies. The bathroom. The small bathrooms.
Survey says. Strike three. Too bad. Okay. Let's take a look at what you
missed. Let's see number one. You get sick of flying. You might
you get sick of flying around serving food. Sick of all the
passengers. Smiling. Let's see number five. Walking. Let's see number six.
Traveling. Let's see how you did. That's okay you can still catch up.
Okay. Time for round three. Lost it all. I mean just sick of the job in
general. We surveyed 100 people. The top five
answers are on the board. Here's the question. Name a profession
that helps people but from which people I hate getting helped.
That would be the dentist. Nobody likes going to the dentist.
Survey says. The doctor. Survey says. Nobody everyone hates going to the
doctor right. That's like a the dentist is on the doctor.
Helps people that people don't want to get helped. Um
a mechanic like a plumber. Survey says.
Um I don't want to go here. A tutor. Tutor or
no. Survey says. Teacher. A lawyer is a good one.
Lawyer. But I don't know people people like to get a good lawyer. They're
very proud of it. Survey says. Oh speaking of lawyer.
Speaking of lawyer. From the recommendations tab
in the discord. Ace attorney. All three of them right now are on ipad.
Full games. HD releases. Phoenix Wright.
Coming up very shortly here. What uh
I don't know. Strike three. I thought you were getting sued.
Speaking of lawyers. I need a good one. Anybody here uh
specialize. Let's see number three. Police and
president. Let's see how you did. Somebody you want to get help from but
you don't want it. The president. The politician.
Good work. Uh so I got I got questions about Phoenix Wright
and ace attorney. Point values are tripled. Is it are they good?
Are those like stream games? Are we gonna have fun with those?
They are right? They're excellent. Yes yes yes.
All right we'll probably do that very soon then. Name something a doctor might
ask a patient to do during a checkup. Cough. Survey says. They don't do that
though. I've never had somebody tell me to
cough. Ever. That's like everyone pretends like that happens.
Uh yeah like pee. Survey says. Say ah. Say ah. Survey says.
What? Stick out tongue. Tongue. Stick out.
Stick tongue out. Stick out tongue. Survey says.
Open wide. That's the same fucking thing. You know you say ah
kick. Oh no. I mean the I'm not that's not one. I'm not writing that.
I'm not writing. I'm not writing that. That's not on here. Let's take a look
at what you missed. Let's see number one. Let's see number four. See?
We would have failed anyways if I typed in the thing everybody's writing.
Where's the donate button? I don't have a donate button. I'd have.
At Cox Business we see the sacrifices you make.
You can't inception this into people. You mean you can't do that.
Just because you keep saying the same things over and over again doesn't
mean that I'm gonna listen to you. You understand? Like I'm I'm not
gonna listen to this. And it's so loud too. All right let's go.
Fast money. But yeah actually you know what?
Fuck it. Uh the next stream we do we're gonna start ace turning.
Fuck it. You know what I mean? Why not? Fuck it.
Uh what do you eat that has a hole in the middle? That would be a donut.
Name something that would tell you your blind date is British.
Accent. Name a profession where you may receive lots of mail from
strangers. Celebrity. But that's an actor.
Name a household chore that you do less frequently because it's barely noticeable
when it's done. Broom. Sweep. Name something about a
food that would prevent a kid from eating it.
Good for you. Did I have less time? When did that?
Sorry I'm gonna get it on the next one don't worry.
Bagels. Bagels gonna get me up on the top. Accent.
Just listen to them talk. Actor. Actors, props, and 3d words.
Sweep. I might yeah I barely I barely need a second round.
So all these are really specific though. Bagel will get me over the top
for sure. That's pretty much guaranteed. I would
guarantee it. Give me five. Uh what do you eat that
has a hole and that is a bagel? Something you you tell your date is
British. What flag do you own? Um how the fuck else would you know
that? I'm not no I'm not writing teeth.
All right we got just pick something doesn't matter. Name a profession
where you may receive lots of mail from strangers. Chore.
Food that would prevent healthy.
I win. I win. Barely notice the dirty dishes. Yeah if you don't do
like six months it's just like it's in one spot. Doing the dishes
that they're in some this is such a tiny central location
that you can just walk right by them. Accent was number one.
Celebrity. I wrote celebrity at first and I took it out.
Dust. I mean that was sweep. Smell. All right what about some other fun
little fucking online video games. What's what's one we haven't done?
Is there one that we haven't seen yet? We've done GeoGuessr
Lemonade Stand. Lemonade Stand. What is that?
Lemonade Stand game. Play Lemonade Stand at cool math games.
How does this work? Your goal is to make as much money as you can in seven
14 or 21 days by selling lemonade at your Lemonade Stand.
Buy cups, lemons, sugar, and ice cubes and set your recipe based on the
weather and conditions. Start with the basic recipe but try to vary the
recipe and see if you can do better. Lastly set up your price and sell
your lemonade at the stand. Try changing up the price based on the weather
because at the end of the game you'll see how much money you made. Write
it down and play get to see how to beat it.
Let's do it. Let me just get this in the right spot. It's not going to be in
the right spot. This is going to be all fucked up.
I'm gonna get that. Looks good. Yeah I don't want a bunch of like website
bullshit all over this. You know what I'm saying?
I want it to look like clean. Okay so far so good.
Let's make it a little bigger. So this is Lemonade Stand.
Somebody like wrapped in tin foil spider manning on my walls.
Can you hear that? Oh what fucking time? What is it?
Okay that's strange. This is Lemonade. I think is it raining? Is it raining in
Las Vegas right now? I think it is. That's weird. All right
so uh you have to deal with the weather
which plays a big part when customers are deciding whether they want
to come. Customer satisfaction. As you sell your
lemonade people will decide how much they like or dislike it.
Let me get my fucking face out of the way. Sounds easy. Let's go.
We'll do seven days. Okay you have zero paper cups zero lemon zero zero
everything zero. I have 20 bucks. It is 80 degrees and it's hazy.
You have zero okay 25 cups. Let's do 50 cups.
Let's get some let's get 30 lemons. I don't want it too sweet though.
No not too sweet. Eight cups of sugar and 100. You don't want to I
don't want to water it down. Vice lemon flavor without without the
the sweetness. Okay got 14 bucks.
Now I'm going to be too watery. Price per cup
25 cents. Lemons per pitcher. Five lemons per pitcher because we want
it to be nice and sweet. Two sugars per pitcher. Ice per cup.
Three. 25 cents a cup. Not enough sugar. No that's too
sweet. You don't want it to be that sweet.
All right let's go. This is me. Anybody buying
cups? It's 80 degrees outside. There we go.
Did you like it? Oh you really liked it.
It's like monsters in this planet here. Yuck.
Yeah go back to Sesame Street buddy. Go get angry at Grover for the spaghetti
he fucked up. Get out of my game. Yuck yuck.
Everybody wants their lemonade. It's so sugary and sweet that's not
why would you want it like that? More ice yuck.
More ice yuck. This guy keeps going back
to my stand. If you don't like it don't come back.
All right what about the monster? What about the Sesame Street monster?
Liked it. More ice yuck. More ice everyone.
Ice more ice more ice yuck. More ice yuck.
Fuck you all. Oh you managed to sell 21 cups to 105 potential customers.
Considering the weather I'd say this is pitiful.
With two percent popularity because they didn't put another ice cube in my
remaining ice has melted. Well all right we're gonna get a bunch
more ice then. More ice. What do I have for sugar?
You have four cups of sugar. Let's do more sugar and I will cut
back on the lemons and let's get some more cups.
Price per cup 25 cents. Cut back on the lemons. Add
sugar because that's what people want and add ice.
Go. More ice. Why do you guys want so much ice?
Nobody likes that. When you go to like a restaurant and they just
they give you like four tablespoons of Pepsi
and then two bricks of ice. Nobody wants that.
People are more sad. More ice okay. More ice more ice.
Mmm more ice. That was pitiful. Your remaining ice. Two of your lemons
have spoiled. Bugs are in the sugar. 77 degrees. All right I'll give you
fucking sugar. More ice. I need more lemons.
Okay I'm still up. I'm still up a dollar 13
since opening the business. Let's do seven to eight cubes per cup.
I think the the taste is there. The flavor is there.
Look at all these customers. What's sold out?
I don't even fucking cups. All right price per. Let's go 30
30 cents this time. We're gonna do five lemons per pitcher.
Five sugars per pitcher and eight. No 10 ice cubes per cup. No
eight ice cubes per cup. It's 53 degrees outside.
Make it cheap. Cheap. Very cheap. 15 cents.
I had to get rid of the inventory. 58 degrees.
So do people even buy lemonade when it's this chilly? Why? How would I make
them get it? Who's gonna buy it? There's just no
ice. They put like less ice in it. Okay I got plenty of lemons.
I'll get some more. More sugar and then just like a little bit of ice.
Back 25 cents. Let's get like six. Four. Five is fine and like
four. Like three ice cubes. No two. Sugary. Really sugary and less ice.
Do more ice. Three? That's cold out.
Seven sugars. Seven sugar per pitcher. Three ice cubes. Four ice cubes.
How are we doing on lemons? Lemons are fine. 58 is not cold but it's not
lemonade hot. It's not it's lemon. It's not
lemon. Let's go. Is it too expensive? 50 degrees.
You have no sugar. Do you do you want I need to put more sugar in?
This is a that's very very decent lemonade. You're telling me I had 10
sugar. Six lemons. Three ice per cup. 25 cents. That's worth it.
Four ice. More lemon. Less sugar. Seven lemon. Nine sugar.
Four ice. It's too expensive. It's too expensive.
That's the problem. It's not 25 cents is too much. It's gonna be like 18.
18 cents. Bring these down a little. Five cubes.
Go. See? That was just too expensive. What's that? I ran out of ice?
Zero percent customer satisfaction. It said that's pretty good.
End of season. Total income. Liquidated inventory.
Net profit. Five dollars and eighteen cents.
We're in the green. Oh that was it. 14 days. Okay.
Let's get cups. 30 lemons. 20 cups of sugar.
A shitload of ice. We'll go on. We've got to make some money here.
15 cents. Five lemons. Six sugar. What is it? It's 81 degrees out.
We're gonna go with like seven or eight cubes. Seven cubes.
15 cents a cup. Sold it out. It's gone. I needed more.
How do you go from like 90 degrees to 54?
Keep the lemons I have. We're gonna make it more sugary.
Bring down the lemons. 18 cents. Bring the cubes down to two. Okay.
Pretty average. 91 percent customer satisfaction.
78 degrees and it's raining. So it's still hot though. Bunch of sugar.
Bunch of ice. More lemons. We did that the worst possible way.
All right. We're gonna do. So it's hotter. We're gonna do maybe five ice
cubes. Drop the sugar. Let's put the price
at 18 because it's hotter. And bring the lemons up. 50 cents.
50 cents. 50 cents. That's way too much ice.
For 78 degrees? It's too expensive. Pretty good. 36 to 103.
High customer satisfaction. Not. Here we go. This is where we're gonna make all
the money right now. 91 degrees. It's clear and sunny.
Buy a shitload of 30 lemons. 48 cups of sugar. 500 ice cubes.
More cups. More lemons. 30 cents. Six lemons per pitcher. Eight.
Made it all back. All you need is one day. Sold out the whole inventory.
62 out of 98 customers. 90. We're doing it again. Here we go again. All right.
This is where we're gonna milk everybody. Completely, completely dry here.
Here we go. 71 to 86. That's pretty good.
97 percent satisfaction. 23 percent popularity.
It's raining today. I have a lot of lemons. I'm not gonna buy. I'm gonna
buy one small thing of ice. I gotta get rid of these lemons. I
got plenty of cups. Price per cup because it's raining out. We're gonna go
drop this down 25. Get rid of these lemons. Eight.
Seven. Let's go with like maybe maybe like five
ice cubes. Four ice cubes. Five ice cubes maybe.
No, I need more ice cubes than that. Let's go with five.
Eight. Seven. 25 cents. It's hot out. Yeah but it's raining
though. So you're getting cooled down by the water particles that are
hitting your head. Don't fuck with the recipe. I'm gonna
drop the price. I need more lemons though. They're
gonna spoil. Definitely not 10 ice cubes though.
Eight. Then I'll buy it. Drop the price. 20 cents. 22 cents.
Fucking rainy. Sold it out though. Good. 34 bucks.
Still doing just fine. 71 degrees in rain.
I got plenty of cups. I need a little bit more sugar.
I don't think I need any more lemons. Let's bring this shit down
though. So let's do like seven lemons. Six
sugar. Six ice cubes. 20 cents. 18 cents.
Whatever I know. Lemons. That's still pretty good.
68 degrees in rain. I have plenty of cups.
I don't think anyone's gonna want to buy any of this shit today.
Let's do, let's go for it. 68. Keep it at 20 cents. Six lemons
per pitcher. It's eight sugars. Five ice cubes.
They're not buying it. They're not buying it. They're not buying it.
Dry it. Liquidate. Quick. Liquidate. Make it free.
We need some more hot days. 72 degrees. I still have plenty of lemons.
Plenty of cups. I need to tweak this. It's still not that nice up to like
you drink lemonade. Six lemons per pitcher.
Let's go with, keep it at eight because I have
no, let me get another thing of sugar so I can do it.
That's six. 12. 18. That's fine. Let's go 20 cents. See if they buy it.
What do we got for ice? Increase that price a little. People are paying for it.
I sold it all out. Lemon sale. 83 degrees. Here we go.
Change the game category to lemonade stand. I guess I could.
So it's gonna be, it's overcast 83 degrees.
It's time to buy. 75 lemons. 48 cups of sugar. 1,000 ice cubes.
This is the one. 25 cents. 7 lemons. 10 sugars. 8 ice cubes.
30 cents. 28. 28 cents. Come on now. Come on. All right. All right. We've
got the late customers here. Good. Good. Beautiful. 83 degrees. A little
cloudy. Let's get some more of that sugar.
No. Give me more ice cubes. Don't fuck with the recipe. It's still 83 degrees.
Keep it at 28 cents. It's all right. That's pretty good.
It was a little too sugary but it's okay. I made money.
That's pretty good. I sold 48 customers. Right now
we gotta slow it down. 360 ice rip. This is fun. It's so easy
just to play it. All right. 56 degrees. I'm gonna sneeze.
I'm gonna take the sneeze cam off. I can't. I couldn't.
My button's not configured to the right thing.
Let's get some more cups. Let's get some more sugar.
Way more sugar than that. Let's go with 20 cents.
8 lemons. 8 sugar. 3. 4 ice. 3 ice per cup.
7 sugars. 7 lemons. 20 cents. 18 cents. Buy it. It's good.
That was all right. 60. Keep the same recipe.
30 lemons. I'm gonna cut the sugar a little.
Let's go. 4 cubes. No. 5. No. 4 cubes. Cut the sugar just a little bit.
Add some extra lemon. 20 cents. 18 cents.
I got a liquid 8. It's the last day. Final day.
It's time to make money. Watch this one. 87 degrees outside. I got 21 lemons.
We're gonna do. We're going all in. 20 ice?
I can do 10 pitchers. 10. 20. 30. That's. Just make it 100% ice.
No. No. I got. That's a good strategy right here. 45 cents.
10 lemons. 10. 12 sugars. 10 ice per cup.
33 cents. 35 cents. 35 cents. 30. I was wrong.
30 cents. 30 cents. I had to go all in. It was just like at the New York
Stock Exchange. Sell it. Sell it. No. Sell it for less.
Sell it for a little less than him. Less than that. Please.
Somebody please buy it. 20 bucks. Profit. Nice. That's cool.
New York fucking stock exchange. I just undercut myself. That's the difference.
20 dollars in a month. Look. All we need. Hold on a second. Wait a minute.
We just need one person to buy one glass of lemonade
for like 30 dollars. Um. So let's do like
5,000 cents. And there are going to be 40 lemons.
50 sugars. And like 30 ice cubes. Somebody bought it. How did I sell out
if nobody bought me a thing? Well anyways that was fun. The ice
melted. Oh. That was cool. Uh. So. Uh. Oh it's under the
ice. Under the stream voice. No. Uh. But maybe. Depends. I think.
Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. He's gonna. Here he goes.
McDonald's manager? What is McDonald's manager? Is it a game?
It's the McDonald's game? Duh. Now I want McDonald's.
screaming i'm turning the stream off hold on the mcdonald's game play mcdonald's video game
uh no i don't want to do this this looks like a diner dash now but we okay here's what i want
you guys to do ready this is what we're gonna do let me let me let me increase my size here
so what i want you guys to do is in the discord in the discord i have that channel for
recommendations let's lay out a plan here the next stream which will be oh it's today saturday
we will do hmm should i start ace attorney on like monday what do you think am i gonna finish ace
attorney will i actually do that or maybe i'll start it tomorrow all right here's the plan
i'm gonna start i'm gonna start ace attorney tomorrow i'm gonna get it on ipad i'm gonna
plug it in get everything done um also in the meantime go to the discord and there is that
recommendation channel by the way you're gonna follow the rules there are rules in that
channel you don't just go over there and just like spam shit if you're is there if there are
flash games and i mean like online fun interesting like mcdonald's games that we didn't have i've
never done right i want to do them because it's fun just to kind of hang out and chill
and just relax and play some fun little games so we'll do that after i probably finish
ace attorney so we're gonna start ace attorney tomorrow and then i won't be streaming after
tomorrow i will be taking a break for a day or two so after tomorrow's ace attorney stream
we will pick back up on wednesday and depending on where i am with ace attorney we'll see how
it goes i think that's a pretty good plan how many ace attorneys will i play that i mean i
don't i can't really i don't know there's i don't really have a gauge to tell you that
right now because if i have fun playing the first one and i actually get through the first
one i'm like this is great i can't wait to play the next one then we'll just do them in succession
at least for i mean i'm not going to do ace attorney ace attorney ace attorney ace attorney
ace we'll break them up so they're not you know awful to do that that many times in a
row i have never played an ace attorney game i don't know what they are the only thing i
know is that meme where you point your finger and you scream objection right so i don't know
and i don't i don't even know what that means that long as hell how long is the first
one is the first one more than like eight to 12 hours 10 hours 17 hours they're too long to
beat in a day about 17 hours how long to beat says 17 well whatever i mean well that was the
that was an incredibly highly requested thing so i'm going to try it if look if after like
a few hours it's like all right this was fun but i don't know if i'm going to stream it
who knows i might i might get really into it and we might have a great time
so look i'm not going to tell you we're going to do a full completion run of all the ace
attorney games but i've blindly never played them before so might as well start the first
one on stream and see how it goes your eyes are really popping like out of my head
what do you mean should i that is it a problem that sounds like a problem very
bright oh i don't think i did anything with my settings on my camera uh but yeah we'll call
tonight that's that should be it for tonight because i really wanted just to kind of close
the book we'll do three we'll go three days in a row so i really want to close the book on the
dreamcast stuff which is now done Shenmue still exists that's going to have to be dedicated to
a completely different day seaman and space channel the first one are not going to be
part of like the dreamcast streams i'll do them completely separately we'll just do them
on a random day where they get in so and don't think that this is me just spouting off my
typical bullshit uh i loved space channel so i'm absolutely going to go back we're going to play
the first one absolutely so uh i will see you guys tomorrow we'll start ace attorney
jet set radio abandoned and forgotten by big boomer media i'm going to go shave i'm going
to go get some mcdonald's so literally the literally the one guy that said mcdonald's is
the end is the reason why the stream's turning off just want to make sure everyone's well aware
of that uh end of the stream yeah we're going to go tomorrow ace attorney i'll see you guys there
if you show up you know if you don't then that's fine we'll see you another time i have to go
get this thing off my face but let's do the uh the bits let's check it from earlier
a little bit shorter tonight but i kind of had the inkling that i was going to go three
days in a row anyway so a little bit shorter stream in the middle here and 50 dollars just
kind of blasted it right now tyler mike just gave 50 bucks 5000 bits 5000 glad to hear you're
playing the ace attorney trilogy i finished it recently and i really enjoyed it i think you
will especially like it if you get into doing the voice uh the voice is like you did in
sorcery also just want to remind you that it's been over two months since your last
stream with vinnie uh that didn't go too well you guys said you try again so just
thought it would remind you germa hart and vineheart yeah i mean we it's just kind of
whenever we kind of both feel like it right i i we didn't put like a set in stone hey let's
do something else it just kind of happens i still have to do the gamer challenge with joel
joel and i are going to do a stream at the same time where we do a gamer challenge and
the first person to complete the challenge uh wins the trophy we're going to get a custom
made trophy built i'm making this up now but now it has to happen because i just said it on live
and we're not going to do getting over it because he already has practice in that game
i played that game a year and a half ago he has the edge there i'm not going to give him the
house edge we have to have a game that when neither one of us has played both completely
blind going into it that's a highly skilled game and that this trophy is going to be worth
2500 is going to be is going to be made of solid gold um that's a lie too but i'm going to say
that that's not going to happen because i'm not going to do we're not doing that but yeah we'll
figure that out all in due time but let's go back to the beginning uh no 2500 gold statue
just want to be sure you know i don't want to put any pressure on and you know people that
maybe think well holy shit we're going to do 2500 why'd you say that jeremy
unfriended uh you know hey dork cube thanks for the one dollar i've come to the realization
last few years that way oh because we streamed yesterday this is all from yesterday
and that makes sense okay so yeah the last stream was less than 24 hours ago that's right
so there we caught those earlier thank you though everybody just give them a top banana
hey sad vega thanks for the one dollar hey germa i come bearing gifts this is
resident evil 2 on 500 facial animations here's the video what who the hell made this why
what so you can go in and mod the game oh my god that's unbelievable
this is crazy you can do body animations too that's unfucking real showed on stream here
look at this shit all right maybe maybe i'll what if i do clare b what if i do clare's uh
storyline with this it goes underground that's it that's our way out lieutenant branna marvin
it's scarier than some parts of the game it's time to go we need to get you to a hospital
right now no no i can't save yourself got you go look we can still make it out of here
it's too late i tried leon it's too it's really weird but i could stop it you can't let this thing
spray it's all you now go those eyes bouncing around every single face you see here is a g mod
youtube video thumbnail all of them take any screenshot from any second of this video
and you will have a youtuber thumbnail video that's hilarious but thank you uh sad vega
or didn't even know that existed that's hilarious thank you some guy nine for the
ten dollars all right enough with the phantom of the opera memes to make up for the
admittedly shitty joke i decided to make a an oc video although my editing is a bit rough
so please be patient wait a minute uh wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute i don't
know if i can show this is this like attack on titan spoilers hold on i need to watch this with
sound off okay well you promised it wasn't a fan of the opera video and uh that turned out to be
alive so uh just want to make sure we are aware are you making okay are you making that
up or is this something that i'm missing somewhere by the way if you haven't seen
attack on titan this is god is there's like a there's like a character in this
in case you just didn't know there's there are like there's an attack on titan character in
this clip so like if you don't want to know who's even in the show just don't click that uh but
thank you for the phantom of the opera uh meme video some guy thank you for the 10 bucks too
snooze and copter thanks for the one dollar i think it's finally time it's time to bring
the old schedule back that's right no schedule just turn the stream on and surprise us
it makes everyone happy because nobody expects it really though do what you feel like expect
except not playing god hand uh do play god hand even if you don't like it feel like it
i'm gonna get more bits now to fund the god hand stream how much is it 20 bucks oh whatever i'll
let my subscription finance it now if you're wondering what what are you uh what he's referring
to so earlier in the stream i had a little heart to heart with chat about how um i had
shown up you know getting rid of the schedule right but something that i did since moving to
vegas and i think it's helped a lot i also think what will help a lot uh is not necessarily
help but the sus command shows a timer and the timer goes to zero and a lot of times
the stream doesn't start when that timer reaches zero and even though i have oh three-ish p.m
like no schedule like afternoons i'll let you know kind of the days it's probably time
to get rid of the countdown timer for sus because if i don't have a schedule and i'm
starting somewhere in the afternoons between like 2 30 and like 4 30 p.m pacific having a
timer countdown is just very it's it's it's it's irrelevant so maybe the timer could stay
but instead of it being maybe instead of a no but then i don't know if it would work
like that maybe it could be set where it's like you sense a stream starting today between
like two and four p.m pacific right because i feel like i'm uh burning a lot of people
when it comes to stuff like that because you know oh hey tomorrow around like three o'clock i'll
be starting and then you know oh he's starting tomorrow at three the sus command it's like
counting down to three p.m three zero zero pacific and the stream doesn't start it's like
well i'm here where is he oh yeah i was eating i'll be you know i'll be there in
like 20 minutes oh the countdown went to zero you're supposed to lie you know what i mean
you're supposed to be live right now i think 99 percent of people are joking yeah but even
still i i personally don't want to continuously have people think there's a stream starting at
an exact moment and then you kind of just sit in here that one guy got to him no i've gotten
complaints from a lot of people before about oh i wish he would just go back to the schedule
because he's just kind of randomly streaming and he's late all the time and i get it i
trust me i understand uh i i am very sorry that streams just sporadically happen sometimes
during the afternoons but that was kind of the intention of getting rid of the schedule
moving to vegas and we're all well aware of this that since moving to vegas there's been
more and longer streams streams should start around 3 p.m yeah that's that that's a decent
way to or like give like a it's like a window like stream starting like between like
three and four p.m pacific right because then at least it's not a countdown that people are
going to be like oh fuck or have the countdown be somewhere in the middle and have it say
like starting around this time or just give like the day time zones are a tricky too i
just i just it's become very clear that i'm not adhering to the sus countdown it's been
like that for months and your time is valuable because you're here watching my stream so i
respect your time and i'm i'm kind of i don't want to disrespect it by just kind of haphazardly
showing up when i feel like it and there's a countdown that just went to zero i hope you
understand just show up on time but there is no time because i threw the schedule out the
window you see it used to be you know tuesday thursday friday 7 p.m eastern that's when i
was i had to be here now it's just i i might stream tomorrow oh well maybe we'll do another
one on monday or i'll still i'll do that on tuesday there's no set schedule or dates or
anything anymore and i'm not i don't want to work on a schedule carve the schedule into
your chest why not because i had a schedule for two just about two years and when i have a
schedule of three days a week that is the only time that i allow myself to turn on the stream
because tuesday thursday friday that's it that's when the stream turns on and that's it and i
take three days off every week four days off every week and it would be i would essentially
find myself sitting there you know friday afternoon going oh okay what are we doing
today rather than oh i can let me get this going and i'll do it on saturday just
i don't have to do it on friday i can get something ready and then do it on saturday
it's been a lot better have you really tried to be on time yeah all the time but with the
nature of like what the nature of what we do on this stream it's hard to like be exact
you know there's weird technical we play like consoles from fucking 25 years ago
sometimes like i'm playing up to today i'm playing a ported game that the graphics
don't even work and need like troubleshooting and i gotta figure that out sometimes it takes
it's not as simple as hey the stream is on because this is what i'm guaranteed is exactly
what's happening every day but i know a lot of people say i want you to be on a schedule
but i don't so at the end of the day i have to do what i know is possible for me to have
the best possible streams that i can and that's just all there is to it so i want to
begin the process of starting to detach from hard days and hard times
because i've in two and three plus a year streaming i've not adhered to them
because that's not the way my brain has ever been able to work or function properly
streamers afraid of commitment afraid of the nice girl i like no schedule because i like
chaos no no but no schedule and no hard there's a lot of people to do it and they and they're
doing just fine i know a lot of people at least a handful of people offhand that don't have any
schedule or any time frame and they it's it's it's going very well disciplined emotional
i like uh i just sort of tune into the stream when i'm bored so no schedule suits me really
well if it means more streams and longer streams then that means i get to watch more
yeah i mean there's two ways to look at it there's either go back to the schedule and
actually hard time yourself and stream three days a week or dump the schedule like i have
and i mean i streamed simpsons hit and run for 12 hours you know why i did that because i
knew that the next day i probably wasn't going to do anything and that i could take a break
the day the day later if that was on a thursday and i am scheduled for friday it's
like oh well like i don't want to stream that long on thursday because it's just a lot of
moving parts there and it works it does it works better for a lot of people some people the
schedule makes them it fixes all their issues it lets them be incredibly strict with themselves
and on time and ready but i'm never fucking ready every day it doesn't matter what it is
and some stuff that we try to do here takes extra time or takes extra moments
and i would rather be able to know and go when i can rather than say i have to go at a certain
time people work in different ways and people can create things in different ways there's no
real correct answer it's just how well you handle however you're doing things you're doing
germa you're actually thinking of the best choice for fixing this problem that you blew
out of proportion in your head just make the sus timer show a time range i don't think i blew
it out of proportion considering that one of the uh one of the biggest channel memes on this channel
is how i'm never on time and it's a joke but it's it's there you know there's a reason
why that joke exists you admitted it was a joke no yeah but i mean like but do i necessarily
want one of like the number one things people say as a joke on the channel is that i'm not on
time and i'm late every day i mean it's funny but at the end when you think when you put the
microscope on it's like well why the fuck is he late every day but i figured i'd bring it
up talk about it because then uh the more accurate it can be it'll be better for everybody
so we also call you short and stupid well all right come on let me let's go over this ready
short stupid and late you know when sometimes when you look over here and you see those things
all the time it's like okay all right do any anything else that people have to say
you know what i'm saying but all uh all quips aside i uh i i do i think it's the right call
so sus ain't going away let's let's move on sus is not going away it's changing to a small
time frame the day will still be there the time frame will still be there just no countdown
i've said my piece well let's move on where are we hey divas thanks for the two bucks
divas uh demonic cucumber thanks for the one dollar i may have told everyone to make this
joke and not explain it to you earlier on sorry about that what oh it was the hey peter thing
it was the hay beater well demonic cucumber was a funny joke and you got me it was the beater
thing hey smelly boy thanks for the one dollar i'm hearing some nasty rumors about shido can
we hear him please jeremy i'm sure nothing bad has happened shido went on vacation to the
downstairs living room he's enjoying himself he'll be back soon he's not dead he's very
much alive hey demonic cucumber thanks for the one dollar hey hey chew chew i don't like your
girlfriend hey binary man thanks for the five dollars it's a youtube link is this what is
this what is this saying what the hell was that was that me talking uh thank you binary
man for the five dollars i appreciate it thank you fuzzy muffins for the 10 bucks small cheer
to supplement doctor income thank you though please some love for the eu the move hurt us
badly and the schedule really helped us i i hate to say this but that's that statement
is incorrect the streams have pulled back at least one full hour since i moved to vegas
i don't know where you're getting that statement from i used to start streaming
at seven or eight p.m eastern every time i start at like six p.m eastern i don't i don't
know what you mean what does it mean i've pulled the i pulled the stream back an hour
like telling me that i'm used to start earlier is just that's not true i started
like three p.m i used to start at seven p.m at least seven to eight p.m eastern every time
it's hard it's hard to respond to somebody asking a question like that you know what i
mean it's hard because i i've it's we've gone back a full hour and i've already talked about
how i'm i can't i'm not going to start a stream at like 10 a.m it's just not going to
happen i live in a certain time zone that's very very far away from a significant portion of
european people that that's just that's just the way it is i i can't like turn my stream
on at like nine or ten a.m i can't i'm not going to do that it's not going to happen
just move here but i'm i'm sorry if you can't watch the streams live or if they go
too late but i already because remember i'm starting the stream in the middle of the afternoon
which is something that i never did before because i moved across the country america's
huge there's there are four time zones in the united states and i went across all of them
to the last one britain is more important than vegas well i've told you like the data
on my analytics i think almost i think 80 something percent of every viewer is from
north america so think about if i were to start a stream at like 8 a.m a more than a
majority of every viewer would probably not be here 20 percent of me does not reside in
north america it can't be late if you never turn on the stream it's the same boomer antics
as always but it's i to put a cap on this and to move on from it there's nothing i can do
it's like if if if there's a show that is airing right just think of it like television
if they like let's say game of thrones for instance is airs at like nine p.m
it airs nine p.m eastern time like game of thrones the show producers don't sit in a room
and go no no we got to pull we got to air it at like edit like 11 a.m
no because it's it's like it's a video it's it's not live a live like the reference like nfl
right if there was a football game that played at 7 p.m eastern time they're not going to
like pull the super ball back eight hours because they want to make sure that people
nine time zones forward you know what i'm saying it's a it's a hard that's very
difficult thing to balance stop comparing your stream to the super ball no i'm just talking about
like live all right here's a shittier example um i don't know this is not a that's the wrong word
and that's not this is not even right like the jimmy fallon show that's a that's pre
it's pre-taped and they pretend it's live later on are you trying to please everyone
no i'm trying to tell the people that are not pleased by the schedule that it's not
going to change because there are it's not just one guy i get a lot of feedback about how late
these streams start for eu so i'm i'm replying to that and saying that it's just it's not
going to change anyways let's go uh thank you to keldos for the one dollar it's a perfect
germa defo fuck why would you taste it like that how is that germa defo i don't why is that germa
defo uh thank you though thank you juno for the two bucks would you consider playing sunset
overdrive since you played jet set i know it's never comparable um probably not not at the
uh sunset overdrive looks interesting but i'm not sure not now uh thank you though thank you
jamona cucumber for the one dollar you had a big rant about it yesterday so i thought i'd tell
you that kingdom hearts 3 is actually canon in the toy story universe i'm not joking look it up
well they have they have don't they have to do that isn't the whole game canon
they look they gotta find a way to keep sore around they're gonna make up a toy
it's that easy but thank you mini clips for the 10 bucks 10 dollars from mini clips top of the many
contributions thank you so much mini clips did you know that nine out of ten doctors don't
recommend smelling chlorox well 10 out of 10 mes would also tell you not to do that either
i would tell you 10 out of 10 times don't do that what's going on what's going on what's
what if it was spamming oh i did it i stole disc one you finally got it you stole it from me
that's how did you do that that fast that is lightning like reflexes but thank you mini clips
for the 10 dollars thank you door cube for the one dollar space channel five reminds me
of katamari and the way that it's a piece of art that exemplifies what makes a video game
such a great medium yeah i would agree katamari is sort of otherworldly in its own genre so you
could kind of say that about space channel although there was i wouldn't call it genre
defining but it was on the dreamcast so i might have to but i do agree it was a great work
thank you tomorrow cucumber for the one dollar i kind of get what that guy was saying about
red dead redemption theme just listen to the similarities and here's the next one
how did you pick up on that shit you're you were right that's so funny thank you so much
tomorrow cucumber and for the one guy that said that earlier uh thank you nuk for the nuk shock
for the one dollar thank you is a pogchamp freudian weapon thanks for five bucks space
channel looks like a hoot are there any other rhythm games you've considered streaming
rhythm heaven is going to be added to the list just kind of wish i didn't give away my wee you
but i really didn't think i was ever going to use it again i will find a way
but thank you for the five dollars and absolutely rhythm heaven is going to happen
keith ward thanks for the one dollar can my two dollars goes toward go towards a treat for
auto yeah sure i'll give him a snack thank you keith uh platadonius thanks for the five
dollars hey germany any chance you played rez it's from the director of space channel five
it's funny you mentioned that game because that game was really really awesome but i couldn't
play it that game gave me a headache it's a lot of bright lights and a lot of weird
spiraling colors and i uh i couldn't play it i actually got kind of sick playing it
i think i believe i'm thinking of the same game i hope i am but thank you for the suggestion
and thank you for the five dollars demonic cucumber thanks for the one dollar tonight on
my strange addiction my name is uh jeremy i'm addicted to crazy taxi on the dreamcast
he scratched my name on put italics there thank you mindless films for the one dollar
hey jeremy my sister and i have been loving your streams we made something for you and
i tweeted it to you i hope you like it he he he he he um i don't have twitter on hand
but i will definitely i will definitely watch it after the stream my phone's not
there it is okay let's see on twitter let's see well i don't know what your name is on twitter
germa shitted and farted no that's not it that's not it i know that's not it that's not it
there it is okay my sister and i spent three hours of our saturday making the rats
okay that's fucking awesome i need a link to this
let's see here we go stop beeping at me that's so cool uh does this work
yeah there you go somebody got it faster than i did no no no no that's not it
it's this one rats made out of clay i think that drawing is fucking hilarious too clay rats
excellent work everybody loves the rats and those are very well made i like the other
picture where they're at that they're getting a nice drink from the fountain rat stuffed animal
when i don't think i can do that because that's not an original character somebody owns that
somewhere and if i was selling like hey 3d movie maker rat somewhere somewhere up the
company corporate place somebody would not be okay with that i could like just i could just
make a rat right hey it's a rat stuffed animal but that exact design somebody fucking owns that
somewhere buy the copyright i would love to but thank you mindless films for the uh clay rats
hey alec thanks for the one dollar germy you should just do an irl stream around vegas
i'm not i don't i don't really want to do those maybe if there was something very
specific but just walking around las vegas is i mean and i would need a very specific goal
not just kind of a walk down the street stream there's a lot of interesting things to do in
vegas though so it's not like i wouldn't thank you tingy for the one dollar this
stream is sponsored by honda and toyota a portion of it was not sponsored by them but
they were certainly given a lot of random attention hey balls cromp thanks for the five
dollars left right left right chew chew chew thank you for the five dollars thank you coca
ronas for the one dollar hey german would you consider trying jet set radio future
for the original xbox uh it might be a better fit for you in the soundtrack this jest is
good well uh is it better is there actually like a better version or i mean that's kind
of that's kind of meh i'm not sure to say oh the first one was better the second one
was better there's probably there's so many people fighting over the last jedi and like the force
awakens like you can't make how am i going to make a comment on that if i've never played it
but i don't have an xbox i would have to track one down if it was on the original xbox
both of those suck
future is a better game okay uh thank you banana aneurysm for the one dollar here use
this to buy the other disc i think we kind of have to bury that one into the ground
i want to that one's dead and buried forever thank you though thank you sir feline for the
one dollar no rat shirt you've lost a fan and a friend well like all in due time rome wasn't
built in a day it took them like three weeks to build rome and t-shirts can't be built in a
day it took me three years to have another one come up so rome wasn't built in three years
took a little longer but thank you thank you door cube for the one dollar fish aren't animals
the man who receives hundreds of gift subs every stream fish are they are animals but
they're a certain type of animal i can't keep up the bullshit on that one i'm sorry
uh thank you mindless films for the one dollar uh linking i think accidentally didn't put the
link in last time but there it is we saw it already thank you thank you scar for the one
dollar i found this guy wandering around the street and i think he's missing his owner his
tag said germa 985 but i don't know if that's his name or what i don't know
know why is this why are they so funny to me i don't know why they are
it's that tag i don't know who he belongs to that's fucking fantastic you guys are quick
thank you timmy tim tan for the one dollar hey asshole you fucking idiot you absolute dork you
fucking hey what's up jeremy love your streams man you're so funny i love you fuck you idiot
thank you super seal for the one dollar local streamer ends his career as a streamer
to pursue his lifelong dream of giving lemonade to aliens sometimes or one time thank you novi
for the three dollars and 33 cents germa do you ever sit in here and think i can't believe there
are thousands of people watching me play this shitty game not trying to be a jerk i'm genuinely
curious i think i may have actually said that on stream to you guys at least on more at
least on four or five occasions so sometimes yeah but that was a good game what are you talking
uh thank you dork cube for the one dollar i need some advice there's this guy who works at the
local talking donuts who has really beautiful eyes would it be weird for me to tell him this
it's not like i'm trying to hit on him i just want to tell him he has beautiful eyes
is this all right hold on is this real are you doing like a reverse meme on me
but thank you though i would just say i would just say hey you got glasses because i never
mind i don't know i don't know i can't i don't know thanks for the one dollar thank you
freudian weapon for the six dollars and 51 cents i can never think of anything funny or
witty for these messages i always enjoy your irl streams though i do too they're fun just to
kind of hang out just relax and just play lemonade games i do enjoy them thank you for
the six dollars and 51 cents uh awesome stevie thanks for the one dollar uh i've been pretty
lonely and depressed lately and your videos and streams never failed to cheer me up despite it
all enjoy your mcdonald's short man he's just a big man but thank you so much uh awesome stevie
for the one dollar glad to be here happy that you can hang out here and have a good time
thank you uh thank you something errata for the one dollar you are germs what are some of
your favorite movies uh gremlins 2 ghostbusters 1 um are there other movies if there are i haven't
seen them i thought there were only like four movies i thought i almost have seen them all
star wars guys i don't like star wars that much i just get i just have a lot of clothing
of star wars i've already we've talked about this like a few days ago you you have like
a 10 chance to own a star wars shirt for your wardrobe they're everywhere if if 10 of your
entire wardrobe is not star wars related i'm not sure how it's possible it is too frequent
it's too out there this it is in every store on every corner a star wars t-shirt
is the starbucks of coffee it's just the starbucks of coffee have you ever had a
starbucks coffee before in your life if you answer yes to this question you have a star
wars shirt in your drop so if you have never had a starbucks before maybe you don't have a star
wars shirt just admit it that you like star wars no i love star wars of course i do
i must have the clown horn i don't know why uh thank you dork cube uh we linked that artwork
from before the i did it i stole disc one thank you thank you and on a list for the one dollar
derma after every time your stream ends the duck stream keeps getting rated by a grill master
and dr phil do you know anything about that also please play clarity on stream it's shorter
and then i couldn't stop that one it's shorter than leon a and you could always
play the revengeance dlc after it which by the way that dlc is better than the base game
that's what i've heard uh but about the doctor phil does not have a twitch account
i can guarantee you that no way but grill master on the other hand he's he's just a bastard that's
all that needs to be said hey metal waluigi thanks for the one dollar hey germa i've been
watching your stuff for about five years i want to thank you for all the hours of joy you
brought me you're welcome thank you for the years of support it means a lot thank you so
much right to miss thanks for five dollars thanks for staying true to yourself and your
fans here's to the great times ahead yeah i look anytime i talk about changes or things that i want
to try things that i want to do things that i want to say i i have to do them i i'm not gonna
just i'm not gonna do something because i think that i have to right because once you start
doing that i feel like that's when you go through like the you're going down the path of
i have to do this i have to do this i have to do this no but i that that that can wait i have to
have to do this this has to happen this exact specific way once you start to do that you start
to kind of lose in my opinion at least in like a creative sense you lose what you started
it for in the first place wanting to do something and having having to do something
they're very very different and i never want these streams or me anything that i do online
to start to bleed into the have to category because i've seen a lot of creators over the years
start to get into the have to categories and that's the place i don't want to be
and even if it is in a detriment to my business i don't i that's the way it is
jimmer who is your crush her name is kim let me see come on come on yeah come on they give
me the points those were points i deserve them i deserve those points and i'll take them and i will
stand at the back of the court and i will throw a shot put the basketball swish but thank you
all of you that yes i do things that a lot of other people don't do i'm all over the place
i'm scatterbrained some of the streams are all fucked up but that's the way that it is
i i'm not i'm not gonna be able to change some of the deep rooted personality traits that
i have and i don't want to don't let the jokes get to you no no no no no no i'm not talking
about jokes i'm talking about actual real concerns that people have and that i have too
you know you don't just to harp back on you don't think i think about all the time
like you know see me look at the clock like oh fuck it's like it's it's it's 11 o'clock
at night right now it's like this late for like it's like fucking 5 a.m for 6 a.m for
some people you don't think i think about oh what that that stream i want to do this stream is
that gonna be funny people gonna think that's cool and then oh they did all right awesome all
right that was worth it oh how people can react to that i think about all the time
i want everyone to enjoy as much as they can and i want the stream to be as fun as possible
it's upstairs all the time this guy is well you're very self i'm not i'm not self-conscious
self-conscious is not the word i've like shown you guys might like boogers on stream
i was like naked on stream one time i don't give a shit about any of that i just haven't concerned
with because the channel has grown so much that i want to make sure that we can stay true to
what we're doing here i can stay true to why i started i can have the same fun that i had
two three four or five years ago i don't somebody just mentioned i don't know if it's
self-conscious thing as much as it's a like a like somebody said personal integrity for me
like jet for like for me i'm not standing on a soapbox and telling you guys that i'm
let me tell you this about me and why i'm so much better it just internally if i don't do that
then i lose why i did it in the first place
maybe you should stand on the soapbox it'll help us find you that was that was almost me
uttering the words forever ban i'm not gonna do it though all right we're at the end of the
bits only like a couple more uh zorro carlos thanks to the one dollar i just want to point
out that sega neglects their properties so much that they even stopped making sega racing
and they're just making sonic racing and that makes me sad that is that is pretty sad thank
you mugellan for the five dollars clue the sniper for the one dollar banjo boy for the
one dollar uh hey germa to get right to the point i've had stomach issues that make me feel
nauseous 24 7 it's been going on for about about two years and after thousands of dollars in hours
spent on medicine tests and procedures and doctor after doctor no one can find out what's
wrong but in the midst of all that your streams have given me something to smile at and on a
rougher day it's the only thing that makes me laugh thanks for everything i'm really sorry
to hear that banjo uh i have firsthand medical problem experience so i can know how i can know
the hellish road that that is i'm really sorry that you're still trying to find out what's
going on hopefully you can get on the right track soon with it yeah thank you for being
part of this community thank you for watching take care for real have a wonderful rest of
your night and thank you so much for the one dollar thank you to razzle for the one dollar
hey germa will you please consider doing the clare resident evil 2 campaign i've considered it
i've considered it it's a great game we might fall into that at some point in the next week
here uh mugellan thanks for five dollars how much must we pay for shido's safe release
i told you she does fine downstairs irritable boomer syndrome dare you show shito on stream
to prove it i don't know he cheetos did he's downstairs singing right now practicing using
his vocal chords he's fine don't worry thank you for the five dollars hey tingy thanks for
the one dollar i'll be honest here germa since watching your stream for the first time i enjoyed
them i've been on this site for six years now and there hasn't been anyone who gets me to
scatter to my computer and onto twitch than you hope that speaks volumes and never change
what you're doing because it works yeah thank you i'm happy that that kind of reaction can
come out of somebody for this stream and i there is like a there is like a constant battle
between uh like the different parts of my brain and some things i want to try i want
to do something differently i want to do this differently maybe i don't i gotta change that i
gotta do this but the core has to stay the same otherwise i will not be interested anymore
so thank you so much for being here i appreciate the message and the fact that that yeah i can
have that kind of effect on somebody thank you it means a lot and finally and on a list
with one dollar i've never mentioned in chat but i've had 13 or 14 major surgeries
over the last 14 years on my bad pain days your funny videos helped me get out of bed
to help the all the animals also when will bits be raised as i have a hundred more
i want to use them before then the bit minimum is probably going to be raised
i said like a few weeks last week so probably at some point before the middle of february here
maybe like another couple weeks just so people can know but thank you that's i'm not sure
exactly exactly what you're going through but that sounds like a lot that's a lot of surgeries
i wish you all the best i can't even imagine what it would be like to have to have a surgery
every year hopefully you take care of yourself hopefully your doctors
and everybody in your life can help you too and with that we're going to play through
the credits and here they come thank you everybody all the subs all the resubs
and i don't i did i got i got a little preachy today and i don't i don't mean to i'm just trying
to make things as clear as possible so i apologize for the beginning of the stream
it was a little preachy and we touched upon it a little bit at the end too but i had a great
time the stream was a lot of fun space channel five is phenomenal i can't wait to play the
other one and i'll see you guys tomorrow we'll try ace attorney you can play pick cross on stream
you mentioned a few weeks ago yeah i mean if okay if ace attorney is not what i was thinking
and i'm not enjoying the time in ace attorney then maybe we'll just do like a mouth open
pick cross stream yeah it's pretty much up in the air i'm down for anything so we're
gonna have ace attorney the original phoenix right tomorrow and see how it goes i have an
incredible rest of your evening see you soon take care everybody twitch ad twitch ad on germa what
do you mean twitch ad what is that what do you mean twitch ad yeah i got ads on germa
recently wait me in the middle of during a stream not during a stream right at the
beginning because i don't run ads on the stream free roll ads yeah i've i've said this before
if i could turn ads off on the channel i would just turn them off you can't do that
i would toggle that button in a second if it was possible i only get them when i first join
when i'm not subbed that's weird but yeah you shouldn't be getting them in the middle
of the stream because i just don't run them but anyways guys thank you so much
uh half of you go half of you go to italics half of you go to vinegar they're both streaming
right now and tell tell them germa985 sent you and joel and 33 percent of you go to joel
and 10 10 15 percent of you go to the ducks all right guys good night i'll see you tomorrow
take care