Good afternoon. Welcome back to another edition of ME! Hi guys. It's been 14 minutes since
Jerma said 10 minutes. That's not a big deal. An extra four minutes. Sometimes I say 10 minutes
and it's 40, so I'll take the four this time. Long minutes. Yeah, you gotta count them slower.
That's four minutes of my life I'll never get back. I'm sorry. Anyways, hi. We are going to
do, just pick up right where we left off yesterday in Disassembly VR. Maybe just joining us. And you
weren't here yesterday. This game's a treat. I like it. I'm having a great time. You take
things apart and that's it. That's the whole game. But it's fun. I don't know why. It just
like, it just squeezes my brain. It's very relaxing. It's very fun. And today, I've got
news for you guys. For the first time ever. Ever. That's right. For the first time ever,
I am going to be sitting down in VR because standing up takes too much energy and moving
around room scale takes a lot of out of me. And so I could probably stream for more than
four hours today. The chair! There it is. Never, I've never done this before. It's,
how does it feel? First impressions. The seat's a little springy. I like the color.
But here's the, hold on, for all you office friends. How's the spin? I definitely should
not have just done that before going into VR. We're going to take a minute here.
Just sit here. Spin? Well oiled, I'd say. It's pretty well oiled. Okay. I think I'm good.
Try spinning. That's a neat trick. Take apart this chair. No. You're going to be sitting
there the whole stream and you have workout clothes on. I'm going to get up. This is just,
look, this is my, when I'm sitting at the desk and I got the screwdriver,
I don't need to go in like this. Where's that screw? Okay. Where is it? Like I'm like a
fucking T-Rex. Like, now don't do that again. I'm not doing that for after part two.
God damn it. It's cause I'm too far away. I can't like see what I'm doing. You know,
I like, sometimes when I'm this close, I can see what I'm doing over here. I can't see what
I'm doing over here. Sometimes I'm just going to do random dumb shit like that, apparently.
But where am I? I'm doing Raptor part two. Spin in VR. Are you trying to kill me?
You're trying to kill me. I'm not doing that. The, the, the cord's going to get all tangled up.
But let me get the audio on. I can't fucking believe I just did like a dinosaur again.
And I didn't have the mask on this time. So it's all right. Sometimes you make mistakes.
I just happen to make them in front of a thousand fucking people.
All right. Disassembly. Are we good in the frame here? I think so. Yeah, this looks fine.
You guys can hear it. Uh, I've never done this before. How am I going to do this?
Around the back? I don't know if this is a good idea. We'll find out, right?
Hey, look at that. Oh, this already feels way better. All right. There you guys are.
I can see you. What do you say? What the fuck? Screw it in a little.
Is that bad? Did I even scoot in? There we go. Webcam on the floor and sit on the floor. I'm not
going to do that. This is not the way it should be. It should be like this. I don't like that.
It feels like I have a big piece of hair. All right. When we last left off, this like fucking
feels weird. I feel like I shouldn't be sitting. Fuck it. All right. How it's made theme or
riot. We did that last night. All right. Where we leave off? We left off here
at the missile. Do I, we already did. Do I have to do the missile? Do I got to take
up off this whole missile? It's like 5,000 parts. Okay. All right. All right. I'm going to,
I'm going to do it. I feel like I have to do, I have to turn, right? That's the only
way this is going to work for me in my brain. I have to like, all right, this is fine.
So we got, if you don't know how this works, lower the seat. What is the seat too high?
Why is the seat too high? I don't know. Yeah, I get that for you guys. I got it.
Is this it? I don't know which one it is. I'm afraid to press a button.
Oh, I just like flipped a switch. It's the eject button. Wait, it's this one here. I
think. Oh, better. Is it fine? All right. All right. Here we go. I'll see you guys later.
This is how you work with this game. This game is a game about disassembling things
and not, you don't, you guys are over here, right? And not putting them back together.
I kind of like this. This is, this is better screwdriver. How many parts are there? A hundred.
This is going to take a while. I hope you're ready for the long haul here.
Top part comes off. It's going to explode. It's not, we already tested it last night.
This thing is a dud. Oh God. I already don't like this. Okay. We're fine. Everything's fine.
Stand up. No, I can't. I, my back has been bothering me and like stand up and moving
around. I need to sit and work at my desk with my tools. That's the tinkerer. Okay.
Isn't that a good title today? All right. That looks fine. Can I get any of these off yet?
Oh, one of the fins comes off. Yeah. No cheating. I got to beat all these.
Room scale, seated VR. I, I got the wrong settings, but it's okay. I'm improvising.
What is holding this on? Is that it? If you're just joining us with, oh,
oh, I think I can get this off this plate. No, right here. This will come off in a second.
Guy like disassembles a nuclear bomb sitting in his living room. It's not even my living room.
It's my office, right guys? All right. Am I going to bloody nose? No. Am I? I can't tell.
Well, how do I get this off? There's blood everywhere. If I just didn't know,
there's just blood just all over me. That'd be so fucked up. The whole stream,
I just have like a faucet coming out of my nose. That would be insane. There's a lot of
screws in this thing. How many more screws are there? Someone call the camp. He doesn't know.
It's a missile. I don't think it's made to be disassembled. That's true. You're all right.
Okay. How many more? Oh my God. I got to get, oh, that was a big juicy one. No.
Whoa. Okay. There's the nuclear reactor. That's what it looks like inside guys.
First ever image of a black hole. All right. So can I get this out?
I don't think I can get this out. Can I pull it? I can pull it. Don't blow up.
I got to get a better fucking view than this. I'm sorry guys.
That's better. Can this come off? What is holding this on?
Don't explode. It's not going to explode. Oh, my rocket contest.
Oh, man. I'm going to win first prize. What do I do with this? Can I take this apart too?
I think so. The wrench. That one wrench. I don't, I got no idea. Oh, I got no idea.
Can I do anything else with this thing? Whoa. Okay. Put this down. This is the engine.
Can this come out? Oh, wait a minute. Ah, these are going to look at that.
We got extra lazy. No, I think this is done. What do we got left? 57. We're almost halfway there.
Can I pull the middle out? Yeah, this is where we're going to be careful.
So really slowly. Like a fucking magician. So there's a charcoal filter. The thing that makes
it explode. This is the thing to purify the water. That wasn't the thug. It's going to
roll. It's going to break the window. Oh, that's unfortunate. That was going to keep
rolling. Hold on. Give me that. Fuck. No, here we go. Yeah, I dropped something. Yeah,
it's over there. It's rolling towards the window. Oh shit. That's going to cost some money.
Those cheap windows made out of candy ribbon. I shouldn't have done the candy ribbon.
What's in here? I think that's it for this. Give me another one.
Oh, stay here. This is the brain. I got to get the snippers. There it is. I'm trying to roll it.
I'm trying to roll it and break the window. Wait a minute. No. I thought it was going to
keep rolling. Riveting content. That would have been funny if it fucking broke the window
and you know it. He's still covered in blood from his nosebleed. He's losing brain cells.
What even makes this thing explode? This is supposed to be true to life.
It's reaching there again. All right. I don't even know what to grab. Can I pull this? Okay,
I can get the panel off. There it is. There it is, guys. Be careful. What does it say?
Explosive Tritonol. S-P-E-O-1-O-2-9-D. Total nine kilograms. So this is explosive.
Just sit that there. I don't know whatever that is. What else is in here? How many parts
are there? 50 parts? Am I missing something? Where are these other 50 parts? Are they inside
this dome? Hold on. Ricochet. That was worth like five points. It's still stuck in there.
All right. Give me the little guy here. No. I don't understand. What is holding this in here?
How do I get this out of here? There's another panel? I don't see another panel.
Whoa. This is dumb. All right. Here we go. We're going to be very careful here. No. Okay.
Easy. Don't let me near in nuclear power. It's still being held in.
There it is. Look at that. Interesting stuff. There's still 42 parts. It doesn't
explode apparently. Okay. So just set it over here. Just put it on the ground. This thing's
making me nervous. What is the other like 50 parts? What? Wait a minute. Damn it. Okay. So
it's this thing. Oh shit. There's more in here. Oh, this is the computer. This is the other
computer. There's two CPUs in here. All right. Let's get this off. Pliers? Jesus. All right.
Do I have to take this shit off too? No. What is this? All right. Can I take the top off?
Yeah. Okay. Let's hold this on. CPU connector. Can I take this shit off? No. None of these need
to be removed. Damn. That's kind of cool. All right. Cool. Now can this be removed? It can.
Nothing in there. Last piece. We've got, oh, there's one more internal thing. I got to,
no, not the crowbar. This thing. That's not the right tool?
And what world are you talking about here? No. Not yet. Where are these other? Oh shit. Okay.
Does this, that's it for that? No. One piece there. That's it. This comes off.
This comes out. Wow. That's what it looks like in there. Well, this is so cool.
All right. I got the lens off. Well, this is where the 50 parts come from. My God. Wait,
is that a reflection? Oh, I can't see myself here. All right. This is that.
This is just the toy at the doctor's office for the little kids. Is that it? Two more parts.
Bring up the beeper. I did it. Excellent. What's next? I unlocked the magnifying glass.
Am I talking to you? Yeah, I am. Oh, I hate when it does that. So let me just
fix myself here. What's next? I have to take apart a screwdriver, then a rice cooker,
and then the Titanic. This is going to be interesting. Take apart the Titanic. This,
I take a 30 set. This is going to be easy. All right. Let's see this one quick.
Get a good look at it. Turn it off. Turn it off. So I got a magnifying glass. Let me just
put it out here. This is cool. That's really cool. It just is. I mean, it just is. All right. I
got a magnifying glass in this hand. I really am the tinker. I can't do a hammer yet.
How do I pull this apart? Are there screws on the screwdriver? Yes, there are. I'm not very
good. Precision is key. Get out of here. Put this down for a minute. What's the last one?
Oh, look in there. That's where the batteries go. Anything else over this? No,
I think we're done with that. Look at that. That's so cool. I don't know. That's a film
canister. Batteries? That's not a screw. I'm almost done with this thing. There's a
little power switch. I need the little one. Give me the pliers. Make this easier on myself.
That's it. 18 parts left. This little guy? Give me screws? There's such a weird smell
in my room. All right. Interesting. So now let's put it in its... There we go.
One, two, three. That's it. I have to battery. Take the batteries apart.
Oops. I don't know what happened here. That's fucking cursed. What just came...
Is it flying around the room? I caught that in the corner of my eye.
I can't get this little tab. Come on. Give me this little tab.
Final boss. I can't pull these apart. I'm an expert disassembler, guys. Well,
this is definitely the next part here. There's the bit. This comes out the back way.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. That's where all these parts are coming from. Look at how
tiny this shit is. Get it in there with the tool. The middle part? No, that's it.
Six more. I believe it's right here. Yes, it is. What do you got in here?
There's the actual spinning thing to the drill bit. I don't think I can get it yet.
There we go. I think that's it. There's only one more thing in here. What's left? Two parts.
What is it? It's the battery, isn't it? Is it the battery? Oh, I got it. No,
I didn't. I can't get this. Shit. What is it? Use the gun. No, the gun
deletes the whole level. It makes it so you can't do it. What about my neck?
All right, hold on. How do I get this open? How do you open this thing? Right here. Got it.
Done. Ladies and gentlemen, it's time for the Titanic. I have no idea what this is going to
be like. No, don't replay the level. Get out of here. I have to destroy the whole Titanic,
I guess. So we're going to go this way. I'm going to stand up for this one. Are you kidding
me? I have to take the Titanic apart. In my chair, there's 151 parts. Swab the deck, babies.
Out of the ocean. Did we hit an iceberg? Is this like a level that's already pre-determined?
I just wanted to put my hand on the railing. I just wanted to put my hand on the railing.
I was going to do a captain bit where I've been on the seven seas.
Holy shit. I'm not going to be able to find that. Oh, look out. Here comes the iceberg.
It's just like a drunk fat guy in a chair. Oh, I got to get over there. Why?
Why was that an explosion? Okay, here we go. I need to go fast. I need to go fast.
I'm going to be the shittiest like James Bond villain. You thought you could make it out alive,
Mr. Bond. Not on my terms. Hey. Stop it happening.
The dining room. Not the dining room. Why did it just come out like that?
It's sinking. I didn't have to do anything.
Okay. Got it. I hit the skybox. No. The skybox is going to shoot back up.
It's alive. That's a whale. Oh my goodness. It's back. Oh no. The sentient wall is coming
for revenge. I don't think this is historically accurate. Hold on. Hold on. I don't want to do
this again. It's hitting the ground under the water. All right. Get me in there. I'm
already seated so it's good. Okay. Where's the dining room? Oh my god. This is so huge.
Is the dining room down? I don't know where it is. There's no map. I'm just
no clipping through floors until I find it. Hold on. Get out of here. Where's the dining room?
There it is. Okay. No. No. No. Not yet. Not yet. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop it.
No. Come here. Come here. Come here. He's gone. Sorry for that interruption. What the fuck?
I just wanted to put it down. I wanted to put it down. I can't. What? No.
I'm just. I'm trying to do a bit here. Why? I just put my hand down and grabbed.
Are you good? No. There he goes. You know what? Fuck it. I think we just have to destroy it.
All right. This is fine. Welcome to the restaurant. Yeah. We pride ourselves on
highest quality food. Do you have a menu I could look at? It's a little cramped in here,
don't you think? Yeah. I'll take the swordfish. God. Nothing can destroy the Titanic. I can't even
do the bit anymore. I was going to set up like three people and have a discussion about the
Titanic. I can't even do that now. Yeah, I can. Yeah, I can. You guys are going to
like this one. I. You watch. Just. Hold on. I got to. I got to get in there and make
people not flip around. Is that like I put wine bottles anywhere? I don't think so.
And can I go? Is there like a captain's chamber? Let me just see what's up here.
That's probably like a captain's quarters, right? That has to be.
Play the Titanic OST. Yeah, I can't move. I got to let me fix this. This is all tangled
up on the chair. Which way is it going? I have no idea. What the fuck is this going?
How did I wrap this around like this? I've got to go the other way. Saved. All right. We're
good. All right. Let me put on the Titanic. Wait, what was that Celine Dion?
Wasn't that one? That's a definite claim of the vaudeville.
Bye, vaude. Go, go, go, go, go. Get there. Get there. Get there. Get there. Get there. Get
there. Get there. Get there. Get there. Get there. Get there. I got to do the T pose.
I can do the T pose up here, right? No, no, no, no, no, no. Like I, you do. Can I
move his arms? No, no, dummy. Stand. Sorry. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it.
Fucking God damn it.
Fuck you. Jack, you already killed two people. Just let me help you. Do it. Is it going to
do it? Is this it? Is this the song? I don't think this is the song. Is this even part of
the soundtrack? Jack, I don't know if I can... It's not... Look. Do you see the sky in front
of you? Yeah, Jack. It's beautiful. It is beautiful. I never watched this whole movie,
so I don't know exactly how the scene went down. Oh, it's beautiful, Jack. It sure is.
Let me put you down. Oh, it's beautiful. I know. Just watch out. Watch out for the railing.
Where'd she go? I don't know where she went. Oh, Julie. Julie. What's her name?
The ship is all right. I can go get her.
She just got wicked, witch of the western.
Jack! Wait. Come with me, remember? This is me.
Jack! Jack!
Jack!
I'll never forget about you.
Jack, did you hear that this vessel only costed $29 a dollar?
I've never seen the movie, I swear to God. I've never seen Titanic. I don't know what happens.
This iceberg, I don't know the history, but I don't know what happens between the
wind and the category of it.
Jack, look!
Oh, my God. Holy shit. I didn't know it was going to be that loud. I'm sorry.
Now drive the boat. All right, I'm looking to do a boat one.
Can I hear a clip? I need to know how loud that was. I'm so sorry.
I had to turn it up for the music. Was it that loud?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. I'm so sorry. Holy shit. Oh, my God.
I really did not know that was happening. Holy fuck. I'm so sorry.
I've never seen the movie. That's why it was so loud. I had to hear.
Holy shit, man. All right, let's turn this shit down.
I gotta go pee. I'll be right back. I know you can see me. I'm still processing.
Oh, man. All right. We're going to have to reel it in here.
We're going to go back and disassemble a toaster or something.
We'll go back to the Titanic. Let's open it back up.
I'm going to sit back down. Oh, my goodness.
We'll do the rice cooker. We'll do the rice cooker.
Kim check. Okay. Do you want to know?
Nobody in there. I got this.
That's pretty much all I need to say. All right.
Subs. A lot of subs just come in. I missed them.
Oh, there they are. Hans Beats.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Thank you for the ten community subs. Ten subs from Hans Beats.
Thank you. Much love to you.
Congratulations to all those that were blessed by the sub dusting.
And let's go. Let's do the rice cooker.
I think the volume has been lowered to a nice level.
You can tell me if I'm wrong. All right.
I don't know what that is. Why is there an assault rifle?
Oh, it's okay. All right.
Back in. Where are my hands over there?
Let's clean this off real quick.
Max volume. No, I can't do that to people for a long period of time.
Okay. Really loud shit is funny.
But imagine if you just clicked on the stream.
You just came to the stream for the first time or you just loaded it.
You went to like, oh, Twitter or I got a notification.
And you're not ready for that.
I don't want to do that for a long period of time.
All right. Let me get another sip of my coffee.
Fresh brew. Let's go.
We'll go back to the Titanic and I will do it normally.
I don't know what that means. It's left-handed.
I just thought of the dining room hitting the skybox.
I got to get out of this level.
Why am I getting like worms vibes?
Look, they're the worms.
It's like worms, Armageddon.
All right. Let's get the fuck out of here.
Why do I have this in my hand?
Back to the main menu.
Oh, my mind frame. Can you see me?
I'm going to turn that down. That's better.
All right. Let's take apart a rice cooker.
This is so much nicer. Look at that.
Am I out of frame?
No, no. Let me frame.
Can I turn it?
It's actually has water in it.
Don't need that.
It's dirty.
Cut that shit out.
All right. So we've got the button here.
Can I lift it up?
The bottom. There's a screw on the bottom.
Can I rip this off?
I don't think so.
How many parts are in this?
59. All right. Well, this is a screw.
Oh, shit. Okay.
Probably more of this.
Let me lean forward here.
Let me get a good lean.
No, no, no.
Give me the pliers.
That's tiny. Look at this.
I can make it. I got to get the microscope.
This is next level small.
God damn it.
Let's pick it up.
All right. Now I can.
Can I grab these?
You can grab this.
Stop doing that.
All right. I need a little screwdriver.
And up. That's a bomb.
This one. Really?
Look, is it the other one?
I can't get that.
Shit. Am I crazy here?
No, I'm not crazy.
I'm not crazy.
I told you I wasn't crazy.
Is there another one?
Now I got to use this.
No. What tool?
That's a tiny little screw.
I didn't think I was going to need this.
All right. There's another one here.
Oh, okay. That comes off.
Beautiful. Then this thing's going to come out.
Snip those.
All right. Get in there.
Snip these with the pliers.
That felt fantastic to do that.
I'm not even kidding.
I'm not even messing around.
That felt so...
I'm not even kidding.
Okay. There goes those.
This whole thing.
Oh, that's the dirty part.
Oh, shit.
Okay. I might have to deal with that later.
Fuck. 24 parts left.
In what world?
What has 24 parts in it?
Ring.
All right. 24.
Is this still something I didn't see in here?
This whole...
Is this going to come out?
Oh, look at these screws.
Is there more?
There's another one.
Oh, my God.
All right.
So I think this one's done.
Anything else in here?
Yeah, there is.
Flip it around.
No. Which one?
Pliers?
Guys, I don't know where the other 20-plus pieces are.
Am I missing something?
Inside the lid.
Really? This is so weird.
I don't... What?
A wrench?
How do I get this out?
All right.
What the hell's going on?
Hey!
Got it.
No.
Why is it locked shut?
Give me my thing.
Are there this many things up here?
That are...
Shit.
No?
Hey.
Hey!
How do I get this off?
This lid is locked shut.
Six more parts, apparently.
Why can I not get in here?
Check the hinge inside the lid.
Yeah, I'm trying to, like, wedge it in there.
You think I would be...
I think I fucked it up.
This looks like I can move it out, but I can't grab it.
Wait, what's going on?
What's going on?
Where's everybody freaking out?
Stick your face in there.
I think I may have bugged it.
Because this was opening before,
and now it's not opening.
The hinge is just gone.
Ah!
It's... Hmm...
What the fuck do I do about this?
I can't grab this lid.
Maybe a crowbar?
I gotta pry this thing open.
Ah, something ain't right.
Something ain't right.
Unfortunately, something's not right.
It's worth a shot.
Damn it!
No!
Oh, the work!
Just shoot it.
Turn it off and turn it on.
Use another part.
Uh, I'm so curious.
Is that the only thing that's left?
I can't use the hammer right now.
Okay, there's apparently something right here.
What is right here?
This thing?
I mean, this looks like it's more than one piece, right?
Yeah, it's this thing right here.
I can't, like, open this?
Or is it this?
Oh, shit!
It's right there.
What do I need?
Fires?
No, not the wrench.
Pliers?
What do I, how do I open this fucking thing?
I can't just grab that?
What?
Is something holding it?
What is holding this on?
Is there a screw?
Where's the magnifying glass?
Where, what am I missing here?
Look, I think there's a,
there's a tiny, oh my god.
Ah, Jesus.
Okay, don't shoot it.
Look at this little screw.
Hey, hey, blink and you'll miss it.
Is that the regular screwdriver?
All right, who's that?
How many more?
Four pieces left.
Shit, really?
This maybe?
All right, let's see.
Shit.
I might have to shoot this.
Damn it!
What about, is it, maybe it's behind it?
No, come on.
I have to ruin the level.
Just glitch out with it?
Not a bad idea.
Open the lid!
Fuck!
Now the level's ruined.
I've disappointed.
You don't get a check if you don't do it right.
God damn it, really.
A phone, a jigsaw.
Let's do the car.
This is a real car.
Okay.
How many parts?
103.
Cool, cool, look at that.
Oh, this is a manual.
Nice seats.
Let's get everybody in here.
That's fine.
Road trip.
There's too many people in the car.
It's the clown car.
Hey, can you move back a little?
He's, all right.
Can you at least go out the other window?
That's, whatever.
All right, I need to get in there and drive it.
This is like a subway.
Like, oh, Jesus.
This, ding, ding, ding.
No, you get, oh, don't cough on me.
God.
All right, that's good.
Let's give it a try.
Oh, is this some kind of a car engine thing?
All right, shut up back there.
This is like nobody.
Get the fuck, man.
Even when I'm sitting down,
you're like caught up your ass.
All right, here we go.
Can I beep?
Can I turn on the radio?
Where are we?
The clowns!
Get them out, quick.
Out the back.
Save them.
All right, let me go back.
This is cool, though.
I like sitting in here.
All right, should I load up with clowns
and play clown music in the background?
And then like just drive them?
Maybe like, let's go with 50.
And my computer might crash.
Stream's probably gonna turn off.
I gotta place them perfectly, though.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Eight, nine.
I feel like I'm hiding in a bunch of stuffed animals.
You're not gonna find me.
I lost count.
I don't even know how many are in here.
Is everybody counting?
Jesus.
My computer, that's it.
No, that's it.
That's it.
My computer's gonna break.
Oh, God, that's it.
I can feel it already.
That's 42.
Oh, eight more?
I can't do that.
We need 50.
The stream's going to turn off.
Funny clown music loop.
That's not a good one.
Come on, what's like circus music?
Am I gonna like upload one of these?
Should I make one?
This is circus music.
Okay, here we go.
Ready?
What happened to the music?
I'm running over the cord.
That was weird.
All right, I need to take this apart.
I gotta do this for real.
Jesus Christ.
That's too many mannequins.
I wonder what's gonna happen to all this wood.
I'll see you guys when I stream next.
I didn't do anything.
Never mind.
Move on.
We're good to go.
I restart this before my video card dies.
All right, let's get it.
Let's take it apart.
All right.
How many parts?
103.
This should be fun.
Nice hair.
Does my hair get fucked up?
Get in there and stay in there before I get angry.
Does the mirror come out?
It does.
Tires.
I don't think you can do that with a car.
That's it for the door, right?
You can't do that either.
That's true.
Or this.
Are you serious?
I can't lift it with this.
No one is making my life hard.
Physics damage on the car.
Impressive.
God damn it.
I was gonna...
This is what a windshield is like, huh?
Okay, ready?
Whoa, underneath.
I was trying...
Never mind.
Do I need to pull this?
That...
All right, that doesn't break.
Let's get onto the hood.
All right, turn it on.
Let me see if I can find out what the problem is.
Yeah.
Let me get a better look.
I think it might be the battery.
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot.
Oh, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Give me some juice.
Ah, no, it's not the battery.
I think it's the radiator.
Oh, oh, hot, hot, hot.
Okay.
No more hot joke.
How is this still on?
There's no way it's still on.
There's no way this is still on.
Somebody getting in.
Let me get in there and see.
Yeah, it looks like there's a couple of issues here with your glue gun.
Um, what did I just do?
Oh, that's the...
Oh, this is where you pilot the car.
Right.
What the fuck?
I think that's it.
Did the dash come out?
I want to see if the car will still run after all this.
Oh, a crystal.
Blue crystal.
A dragon egg.
All right, I'm going to have to get some tools here in a second.
Wait.
Ah, hold on.
Why did that?
I can't back it up.
This is fucking Nintendo Labo.
Oh, broke my headline.
Oh, no.
Jesus Christ.
Get...
I need to get a glass.
That worked.
Get the back fin here.
What have we got?
72 more parts.
Holy God, are you kidding me?
Wait, did I fail it?
No.
Okay, I didn't know if it exploded was a fail.
Anything more to the seats besides just the seat?
Nice, like, gamer chair.
Wait a minute.
Is a gamer chair just a car chair?
It is.
What?
It is, isn't it?
Okay.
All right, down here.
All right, I'm going to have to stand up for the next few
because I'm actually getting motion sick sitting here doing this.
After we're done with the car, I'm going to have to stretch
and I'm going to stand up and move the camera
because I'm actually going to throw up.
It's just like this...
Oh, no, I got to get up.
I got to get out of this chair.
Movement without movement is just...
You're going to hurl.
And plus, this is like...
I'm spinning around and coiling myself up like a snake.
Get this out of here.
Both mufflers?
Goodbye?
I think I got to unscrew some shit.
I think so.
Can I move the car back?
All right, no, I got to stand up.
Hold on.
I'm going to puke.
I'm going back to standing.
This is a failed experiment.
Okay.
All right.
I'm going to move the camera.
Yeah, I got to move around.
How are we looking?
That's all right.
Maybe a little bit lower.
Maybe a whole sleeve of Oreos will make you feel better.
That's not a bad fucking idea.
That's not a bad idea.
Like an entire sleeve?
A little bit more head room.
All right, let's get untangled.
This, I feel better already from standing up.
Good.
Very good.
It's a bit?
What's a bit?
I'm not joking.
Do you think I'm joking?
No, I'm holding back puke.
I'm kidding.
Ah!
All right.
Better.
Let's keep doing this shit.
I feel better now.
Already.
Better already.
I don't even know what I picked up.
Let's get this shit out.
So this is a, uh, this is a, no, wrench.
No, wrench.
Wrench, right?
Get back here.
Flyers or wrench?
Wrench.
Can I do it with flyers?
No.
Upcap.
I think I need the, uh, yeah, I need the, although sitting down, you don't do that.
It's a brake lock.
Nice.
Give me the, uh, give me the, uh, yeah.
Down with you.
I think that's it with here.
Oh my God.
What's going on?
People giving community subs?
Uh, pixel bike.
Thanks for five community subs.
There was another one before that I missed.
Big subs.
Thanks a lot, guys.
I missed, uh, probably a couple that came in, but thank you.
Oh, Pogchamp.
No, thanks a lot, guys.
More community subs coming in.
That's what I wanted.
Throw it off.
These can come off now.
All right, now we're just down to, like, the meat of the car.
Dude, why, why doesn't, like, the gamer chair companies make this?
It's a double gamer chair.
Do they make this?
A gamer couch.
Uh, what else is free?
Anything else?
I got to just do the tires.
Uh, do all four tires.
Get it over with.
Wink.
I use the crowbar.
Pull the shit up.
Brake pad.
Uh, it's a turn device.
Whatever it is.
Now, how do we get this shit off?
A wrench for that one?
Is this connected to something?
I'm not sure what this is exactly connected to.
I think I have to get rid of this first.
I think.
Let's find out.
Hmm.
Shit.
Is there a screw here?
I don't think so.
I think it's just wedged in up here.
Crowbar?
I don't know.
Chainsaw.
Uh, I'm gonna flip the car upside down.
What's that?
Why is there, like, why is it leaking?
All right, this is connected to here.
There we go.
Can I pull these off?
Yeah, I can.
No, I cannot.
Said tool required.
Maybe not.
We'll find out later.
I think I can rip this out with the wrench.
No.
All right, let's go for gold here.
Never mind.
Will you please just pick it up?
I'm about to do it lefty.
You ever see somebody hold out javelin like this?
Just get away from me, please!
All right, tool to rip this off.
Got it.
I can pull these up now.
Very nice.
This is bolted somehow.
Or is it?
Okay, I did think I was gonna be able to do that.
All right, now I can flip it back around.
What's left?
33 pieces.
I might have to take the whole engine apart.
All right, this is the, this is the orbit.
This is the tuba.
Okay, don't tell me you didn't blow into the top of that thing.
It wouldn't make like four separate weird noises.
You can probably harmonize with that thing with one note.
All right, engine.
Engine is detached.
So it's a big staple.
Now, here we go.
I think there's more to meets the eye here with this thing.
Maybe not.
Tires.
And then we gotta go searching for the next little bit here.
In a minute.
Oh, I got the turkey leg.
That's it.
The meowing engine.
Is it meowing?
All right, only a few more things left, I think.
Yeah, we're down to like the last little bit here.
It's the two tires.
Lovely.
You can get that off.
Does this have to, does this come apart?
Oh shit, it does.
I don't even know if this is.
How would you go back together?
Oh my god.
Get out of my way.
There's the, there's the rumor.
All right, here we go.
Yeah, this is it.
I got it.
Victory.
And other tire right here.
Finally took long enough.
19 minutes.
We did it, Reddit.
All right, what else we got?
It's Titanic.
Car, airplane, toaster, coffee grinder.
Train, deep tank.
I kind of want to, what do you think?
Go back to the Titanic.
I need to like stretch.
My body is so broken.
All right.
How do I, okay, I'm going to say like we're going to pull the bottom out.
I think that's the most reliable.
Just rip the bottom out.
Just take the napkin from underneath all the shit and it'll all fall down.
Watch this.
Down, down, down, down, down.
And what is in here?
Is it like the engine room?
All right, I'm going to take the bottom.
I'm just going to pull the bottom out.
I'm just going to take one piece.
Right like down here.
I'm just going to rip the whole thing.
Ready?
Almost.
Fucking explosions, man.
They're so intense.
It's that easy.
Or is it?
I might have to go to the bottom of the ocean and clean this and rip these apart.
Well, that would be a pain in the ass, wouldn't it?
God damn it.
I got to turn the thing on.
That makes me move faster.
This bubble's just too big.
Damn it, it's like a gunshot.
Pick it up.
Grab it, grab it, grab it.
Now, I don't know if I'm going to be able to...
This is going to take so long.
How would you not do...
How would you do this without like a fucking grenade?
Oh, 144 parts.
I got to go in and disassemble every stool.
Oh, there it goes.
143.
What's it going to do?
I got to go in and take out everything.
All right, give me the super speed.
This is going to take forever.
Because the thing is, if you try to destroy it one little piece at a time, it just explodes.
It just goes like, boom!
I'm just like an anime character blasting through this.
And here we go!
I'm just going to go through the middle.
Watch this, ready?
I think I did it.
Kind of.
Fuck.
Here we go.
Sorry!
I can't stop!
Oh!
Can it be done?
Oh my god, I have 109.
I'm going to explode.
I am never going to be able to do this.
Would you touch anything?
I'm going to destroy these things.
No, I'm not!
Oh, it's taking like 20 minutes when I make my way over there.
No, just gravity gun.
It's just, it's too wedged in.
All right, fuck it.
I can't do this one.
It's going to take like two hours to do this.
I'm just going to suck it up.
I feel like I'm in the middle of that mission in Half-Life when you first
roll the cart into the electromagnetic spectrum thing.
This is 70 more times.
All right, I can't, I'm done.
I'm done.
I did it.
This is going to actually be the same.
I have no idea where these other 24 pieces are.
I know they could be anywhere.
It's 21.
I think it could be anywhere.
It could be any one of these.
It's 21 still!
It's not possible.
Where is the other piece?
Is there any more?
Does this count?
Okay, that's it.
I'm sorry.
I don't care.
I don't care if I get a heart attack on this one.
My like psyche is going to break down.
No, no, no, what are you doing?
No!
That's not what I wanted.
Why is this killing me so much?
Now give me a headache.
Imagine the guy in the inside.
I got a headache.
Oh, it's like times 10 headache.
My friend says you have a long plantain face.
Oh, good.
Isn't it fucking chiseled?
I just chiseled plantain.
I don't even know what that means.
I can't do mind show right now.
I'm going to...
Fuck.
These VR streams are fucking killing me.
It's like every day I lose.
Every day I lose a little more energy.
Doing it like two or three times in a row.
It's so fun though.
I think I can do a couple...
Hold on.
Plantain's a banana.
Oh, whatever.
I've got like a banana face.
That's fine.
I want to keep playing that.
I thought bringing the chair in was going to help.
I'll bring a chair in and sit out
and feel like I'm going to throw up.
It's all right.
I just need a second.
We'll go back in.
Where's my library?
All right.
What happened to it?
There it is.
Okay.
Let's go.
There comes a puking stream.
Nah, it was just zooming in really fast.
Sitting down in the chair.
Blade and Sorcery got a big update.
Maybe we'll check it out.
All right.
Let me get in here.
Let's do the computer.
The computer sounds fun.
I'm going to be honest.
Any next game in VR is going to be like
Blade and Sorcery.
I have to fucking move around and swing around.
I might not be able to do that for very long.
I'm getting like that fucking like puke reflex.
It's from sitting down.
And you know when you like get that after a while,
you get that feeling and then like you can't get rid of it.
Getting up made it better.
And then like there.
Oh my God.
I was being just attacked.
Let's do the computer.
Drone, TV, submarine.
Some of these are so fun.
Microwave.
What is happening here?
Something is not right.
That's odd.
Is it like the pizza?
Did I fry my GPU?
I don't think so.
Hold on.
Oh no.
Now wait.
Fixed.
We're good.
The window wasn't in focus.
Weirdly enough.
All right.
So let's do microwave.
We've got 113 pieces.
Let's see.
Let's cook something.
You're not supposed to put metal in the microwave.
Why is it not doing anything?
We're going to eat good tonight.
I can't put my head in here.
Okay.
Jesus.
All right.
Let's try it again.
Why is everything so fragile in this game?
Seriously.
Look at this.
Ready?
Watch this.
It's just a piece of lettuce.
There's a piece of lettuce.
Well, the plating is very important.
You've got to make sure you put your greens
right gently on the plate.
Oh, whoops.
It fucking broke.
Just restart it.
God damn it.
All right.
Forget about this.
We're going to open it up.
What does the microwave even look like inside?
Probably scary.
How terrifying is a microwave?
Microwave the gun.
I did it.
The door wasn't shut all the way.
Hold on.
Cooking with Jerma.
What?
I guess I'll have a pizza.
Oh, it broke.
What's going on?
All right.
I'm going to do it for real this time.
I broke the pizza.
All right.
Panel, door, back panel.
Can I get this again?
I got screws here.
Oh, I'm going to move way too fast.
There we go.
This little room, you can't go that fast.
So let's open this up.
This one's going to be cool.
All right.
Can I get this back panel off?
No.
How do I get that down?
Hold on.
Uh-oh.
Wait, wait, wait.
Cool.
That's it for the panel.
Holy shit.
That's what it looks like.
What a weird machine.
Can I get that screw?
I can get that screw.
Is this top not going to come off?
I got to cut these.
Get that off here now.
Oh, shit.
What did I do?
Oh, my God.
What's happening?
Oh, it was the glass.
All right.
Broke right in half.
Can I get this one out too?
I don't think I have to.
Play it out of there.
Why does it have to load this?
I'm going to just get out of here.
This little thing here.
I think I got to take all these off, don't I?
Yes, I do.
Really?
Come on.
Does this still work?
Does this still turn on?
The door's not on it, so it won't work.
Might need it later.
What the fuck is this?
A bulb?
Oops.
Whatever.
Somebody will clean that up later.
Every time I go like this, I want you to edit a lightning strike.
Hmm.
Screws?
No.
Those screws, right?
Do I got to flip it?
I think those little tiny things are right there.
Shit.
I like the little screwdriver.
It's never used.
Only the boss baby one is used.
I want the little one.
Let's go back to that.
Give me the pliers.
I can't get rid of this shit.
Look at this.
All right.
A little fan came out.
Can I get this off?
What was that holding in?
I was holding this in.
This piece right here, right?
Why can't I get this shit off?
You figured I could get this off with the pliers.
I don't even know what that's connected to.
All right.
Here we go.
I got a bunch of straight wires.
Is there a screw?
Screw?
Crowbar?
I think it's too small to put the crowbar in here.
I'm surprised I can't do these.
That's not a real table.
Look at that.
Oh shit.
Flip it upside down.
This is the problem right here.
Just figuring it out.
Okay.
Now what does that do for me?
What?
I don't know.
It just knocks something off.
I think that's good.
Can't remove this yet.
Is this screwed in?
Nice.
Now, can I get it off?
Oh, dick.
Come on.
This thing can be...
That's scaring the fuck out of me.
Stop doing that.
What is happening?
It doesn't like when I pick this up.
Damn.
All right.
This is the middle of there.
This is where all the radiation comes from?
All right.
Let's go...
I still can't get into there.
It's not a real table.
What is holding this thing?
Electromagnetic radiation.
I still don't get what's holding all this shit in.
I guess they're latched in like that.
Stay there.
Stop breaking my game.
I paid good money for this game.
All right.
I think we're getting close.
Six...
Oh my...
Wow.
Did not fix 61 parts.
This is an intricate one.
Gotta get in there.
Yeah.
After this, we'll play Blade and Sorcery.
Until I puke and then leave.
Get your camera ready because there might be a throw-up on camera.
I think that's good for that.
It's still being held in.
By what?
How do I get rid of this?
Is there a screw?
There is a screw, isn't there?
That it?
Yes.
Easy, easy.
The panel can come off.
Right?
Yes, it can.
Excellent.
Shake out the excess.
These are connected to here.
Ultimately.
So the question is, how...
Why can I not unscrew these?
Fucking hell.
Is there a screw?
Help me out here.
I can't get this.
I can't get that off.
Gonna watch wrestling a bit.
What is going on?
What is this paragraph?
What was all over the...
Wait, what's going on?
Did I miss something?
Oh, that was part four?
There's a nut on the screw.
Give me the...
Let me get a good look at this.
I don't know, man.
I'm kind of confused.
Nerd neck.
I mean, I have to be like this.
You unlock tools by completing levels.
So the more level packs you complete,
the more stuff you get.
I'm kind of stuck here though.
Because these can't...
You can lift these up.
Hold on, wait, wait, wait.
Wait a minute.
Give me the pliers.
Come on.
Fuck.
No.
What the hell is this?
Can I take this off?
Oh, shit.
I think I can pull back panel off.
Come on.
That was a eureka moment.
Why?
Oh, you're kidding me.
What?
Shit.
Is that a screw?
I don't know.
I can't tell if it's a screw.
No.
Ah, babe, I'm stumped.
Because I can't get in here
and undo these.
See what I mean?
Ah, there we go.
I did it.
I figured it out.
Yes.
Lovely.
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay, let's get this out of here now.
Take it all apart.
Fantastic.
Flop.
And this is still connected somehow to something.
What is this connected to?
Nothing's even plugged in here.
These are all just straight wires.
I can't get under there.
Nothing's even attached.
It's just floating.
Do I have to grab it with the pliers?
I'm going to throw it out the window.
Oh, it's been too long.
Don't do that.
All right, this doesn't make any sense
in the laws of physics.
Is that a tiny little screw?
No.
Every connector needs to be disconnected.
They're not?
I mean, what is disconnected on this one?
I can't even tell.
Ah, no.
Oh my god.
There's another one of these fucking things.
Look at this hidden ass screw.
Are you serious?
It was like stuffed in here.
Are there any more like hidden screws?
This still can't come off.
What?
Why?
I'm getting inside of here.
There it is.
Right here.
All right, come on.
Oh, thank god.
Jesus.
That took an eternity.
I'm going to get out of my face.
Now, how do I?
Ah, 38 pieces.
I'm about to shoot it with the gun.
I need to get in here.
The bottom right panel needs to be pulled out.
I mean, is there some magic hidden screw?
That I didn't get?
You know what I'm saying?
There's going to be some one fucking screw
that I didn't get.
Is that it?
I can't even tell.
Screw on the top?
That's not a...
These, they look like phantom screws.
These aren't even real.
You see, that's already been unscrewed.
I think.
I don't know.
Look at the side opposite the wires.
Damn, Jerma.
It's like you've never disassembled a microwave before.
Oh, that hurt.
It's like you've never...
Oh, that was good.
That was a good one.
What the fuck, man?
Oh, this is not it?
I thought that was a screw right here.
Oh my god, you're killing me.
Where is this?
I keep thinking it's here, but it's not, right?
Oh my god.
I can't like get into here
to like get out of this thing out of here.
There's nothing even in there.
Screw in the center?
I need a better angle.
Mom walks in.
Jeffrey, what the fuck are you doing?
I'm sorry, mom.
I thought we were going to go to the hospital.
Jeffrey fucking scrapped up his face and got a black eye.
I'm trying to take apart the microwave.
Give it to me.
Press the life alert.
No, that's...
Are you sure?
Where'd it go?
Where did it go?
Right there.
That's not it.
I don't know.
I can't do it.
I don't know where the last little...
I gotta pull this apart.
Wait a minute.
Damn it.
I'm stinking.
Micro wheel.
No.
Make sure the connector on the wires is disconnected.
Is it in the north corner?
Please for the love of god try the bottom connectors on the motor.
That's what I'm trying to do.
I can't get them.
I tried like five times.
See like they can only go back this far and I can't do anything with it.
You stupid fucking game.
Are you serious right now?
I did it.
You just gotta get your whole head in here.
I didn't even do it.
That didn't do anything.
No, it didn't do anything.
No, what was that screw for?
What was it for?
Middle inner microwave.
I'm going in.
Other side.
I can't even get the damn panel off.
I think I give up.
I can't like reliably get my fucking hands in here.
No, no, that was it.
That was the end.
That was it.
What happened?
What's wrong?
What's wrong here?
Just unscrew the side panel.
What are you talking about?
I've unscrewed every screw.
There's nothing holding this shit.
There's nothing here anymore.
What the?
What?
This is just floating in midair.
Wiggle the connectors.
Pull the connectors down.
Aren't they all down already?
The bottom panel is red.
Bottom panel.
Guys, you're talking about right here, right?
This is what you're talking about.
Talking about this panel.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is what you're talking about.
Where's the screw?
Where is it?
That's not a screw.
I can't remove this.
This thing's all fucked up.
There is no way to remove this.
Crowbar.
Don't even tell me it was the crowbar.
Slide it?
It's red.
I can't slide it.
There is no sliding.
It's red.
Something is keeping this here.
But fuck if I know what the hell it is.
That's not a screw.
It's almost like this screw was supposed to be here.
But it's like a JPG.
It might be broken like the rice cooker was.
Hex key?
No, there's no indicator.
There's not even an indicator.
There would be an indicator, watch.
There's no indicator.
This thing just doesn't exist.
Have I really been just scouring this whole thing
and it just glitched out and I can't even do it?
Smart click?
No, there's nothing here to unscrew.
There really isn't anything to unscrew.
Looks like that but there's a hole.
Where's the screw?
Didn't exist.
There was no screw.
That was so long.
I got baited to 45 that it's a microwave prep.
Let's do the computer.
Okay, what we got in here?
DVDs?
Okay, we got...
How is there this many parts?
There's not a hundred parts in a computer.
There's the brain.
We'll see.
Here's the...
Why is the power supply up here?
Shouldn't the power supply be down here?
This person installed this upside down.
It's supposed to look like this.
But, right?
Doesn't the power supply just sit on the bottom and the...
People do a hanging power supply like that?
They're not even fucking computer experts.
Okay, there's the little...
This will all come out sedazy.
I don't know what that was.
The heat sink.
CPU.
All right, let's get our workstation clean.
What is that?
16 gig?
What, you only got 16 gig in here?
SSD?
Nice.
All right, let's get out of here.
Is this tool-less?
Nah, not tool-less, unfortunately.
It doesn't even have tool-less.
It makes a cool noise.
All right, so that graphics card is wedged the fuck in here.
I don't know who installed this, but they did a terrible job.
You know, where's the tab?
I mean, just awful.
Absolutely awful job.
If you take this part too, that'd be cool if you take that apart.
There's the small battery.
All right.
Oh, god damn it.
PC repair shop.
The guy that covers his hands in oil before he touches it.
I've got some screws back here we're going to take care of.
We'll deal with you later.
Oh my god, now look at this little thing.
It's causing this much of a problem.
Artery?
All right, let's pull this thing out.
We're going to take this whole thing apart too.
Oh, joy.
Flyers probably.
We'll deal with you later.
You stay there.
Anything else on the main frame of the computer?
I don't think so.
Well, there is.
Screwed up.
You know, take, I'm going to do the whole skeleton too.
Drop on the wall.
Backplate?
Get this backplate.
Is that it?
That's got to be it.
No, I got this shit too.
Grills?
No, I think that's it.
Now the rubber things.
No, come on.
We'll go up here.
Oh, okay.
I thought that comes off.
I think that's it.
We'll check back on it later.
So we've got some parts left to do.
There's a lot of shit in there.
Can't just pull it out?
Oh, okay.
I'll do it again.
Why not?
Bullshit.
Turn, tilt.
Come on.
This is just fun to do.
It really is.
Oh, my back.
Dude, I swear to God, something's fucking wrong with me.
My spine is so fucked up.
None of these come out?
I'm going to hold mono just in case.
I feel like something's going to come out of there.
No?
Okay.
The video card.
Let's take a look.
Uh-huh.
Is that it?
Can I pull this apart now?
Yep.
Whoa.
There you go.
That's it looking like inside.
Take a look at the teeth.
And I think that's it.
I can't pull this out, can I?
All right.
Yes, I can.
See you later.
That leaves us with a CPU.
What about that?
I'm going to have to take this apart too.
No?
I guess not.
Hard drive?
I'm going to do all this shit.
Wow.
This is pretty cool.
This is a solid stare, right?
Noises.
Three.
Oops.
Cool.
Anything else to pull off of you?
I don't think so.
I don't think you have anything either.
That leaves us with the final piece.
The motherboard.
Scratch it up real nice.
All right.
Is that it?
Is there something else?
Oh, dude.
What is this?
EVGA?
Oh, wait.
GIGABYTE?
What's left?
Something over here.
What about this?
Another piece here?
Does it pop out?
Oh.
Okay.
Oh, the graphics card.
What would it be?
Oh.
There's a bunch of random shit.
There is something else on here.
Or on here.
This piece?
It would look like this little slap right here.
Really?
This little thing?
Six more pieces.
A table?
Apparently.
God, fuck you.
Two, three, four.
Well, that's almost all of it.
Just two more.
The fan?
Dude.
Will you pick the fucking thing up?
You're making me crazy.
That's it.
Computer.
You forgot the seasoning.
All right, let's do Blade and Sorcery.
Let's try the update.
This game is so much fucking fun, but we'll try something else.
We'll do the Blade and Sorcery update.
That was way easier than the microwave.
There was no other screw.
All right, let me go pee.
Let me grab some more water.
And we'll do Blade and Sorcery.
Be right back.