Hello everybody. We're a little late, but it's all right.
We were trying to get um, Ster, you could go ahead and give a small explanation
if you want. Um, it's really hard to make Elden Ring mods work with other Elden
Ring mods without doing a lot of shenanigans to
merge things properly and have them load in the right
order. And I had everything perfectly working,
but our greed to have it all working really kept us going.
What's the downfall? Me. Well, no, that's it.
So we, everything seems to be working as intended. We have the Diablo 2 loot mod.
We have Diablo, we have, I almost said Diablo 2 reforged.
We have Elden Ring reforged and a new randomizer seed with new
randomizations. The problem is Elden Ring reforged
probably doesn't work. One part of it doesn't work.
Okay. It's a really big mod to be clear. There's a lot of stuff in it
and we don't know what doesn't work in it, but the options when you sit down in
a bonfire, a tree kills us when we select them.
Yes, so we cannot explain that. We are instantly killed
when we, and we don't know what it says. There's no text string. It just
says like text goes here and we don't know what we're selecting.
So maybe. And then you say yes and a tree kills you. A tree kills you when you say yes.
And then randomizer works, but the item randomizer does not work.
So only enemies are randomized, but Diablo items
are randomized. So here we go. So we're good.
All right, are you through the tutorial? We're gonna do, let's just get through
the tutorial first. Just so we can get in there. Wait, did you make a
character? No, I was looking at the, what, my starting characters. Oh, okay.
All right, so I made somebody. So I'll just, I'll just do that part first.
Did you, did you choose based on like? I choose, I choose
based on the starting stats because I've been,
and plus I got, I'm all right. Oh, I was gonna look through and see like the
starting items because we have for some reason very weird starting
items and this one character for me looks like very OP. Interesting.
Oh, grab it. I might, I might. This is the character that I have.
Because I see what I want to do if I can. I want to do
like frenzied flame shit. My character's name is
My Eyes with an exclamation point. Because your eyes hurt.
Well, because it's like, the fire comes out of their eyes.
Oh, the three fingers, dude. Yeah. All right, so hopefully we,
everything went fine. I don't know. Yeah, I think I gotta pick my warrior.
I'm not gonna be able to use my starting weapons for like hours.
What is, what is your, what's your starting weapon?
The meteorite beast's greatsword is dual wielding them.
So how are you gonna be able to play with, you're gonna have to wait like
two days to play it. Yeah, I think it's worth the wait.
Excuse me, dual welding. Get it right. Say it correctly.
All right, I'm going up. I, so I'm gonna show everybody what we're talking about.
Does anybody know, I wanted to play the warlock character.
Yeah, so Elden Ring Reforged has classes that you get to choose immediately when
you sit down in a bonfire. You can buy an item to activate a class,
but the tree kills us if we try and do it, so I don't think we can do any of
that. There's three other classes that are like dropped somewhere, so we'll be
able to find those, and I don't know what they do because it
doesn't tell you, and I don't think you can get the classes
anywhere else. Yeah, because I don't, I don't know what any of this stuff does.
I don't think it matters what you want to do. So what, so if I want to do that,
the like warlock class from Elden Ring Reforged. I think you're
out of luck because it will kill you. Okay, wait, wait, wait. Somebody said,
no, the tree, hold on. The tree, it kills you because you changed the difficulty
setting in Reforged settings, but the text is broken due to compatibility.
Make sure your config files are everything in the right order.
That makes sense. So this is not where you pick a class,
or? It is. From one of those option menus, it eventually gets you to a
class choice. Okay, well, did anybody know which one?
If I want to do warlock, does anybody know where that is in here?
Because I don't know. First, third, fifth, wait, what happened?
That's just hilarious that someone, I don't believe, how can they actually know?
Three, two, four. Okay, one, three. There's no two here. I want to do warlock.
Go outside the first door to the right of Vary under the cliff.
There is something I need as a fortune item to change classes.
Is that for real? All right, let me get out of here first, but the Diablo loot
should be working, which it is because I picked up this.
I have an uncommon club on. I have an ancestral holy giant seal of the
God Slayer. Is that like, is that like a really good fucking item?
It's ancestral. I feel like that's like, did I get like a god item rolled at the
very beginning? I don't know. I don't know what's going
on, man. Well, we're going to figure it out.
Oh, also there's one secret mod in the pack. There is?
Yeah. What do you mean? And it only affects Ronnie.
You, you, you, you didn't, you didn't put it up. You didn't know.
There's no way you did that, although I did just,
hey, dude, take a bunch of these files and put them in your folder.
And I was like, yeah, sure. That makes sense. So you could have probably put
anything you wanted in here. Oh, I'm glad that you trust me, um,
but not enough to be like a mod on your channel. Ah, that's too much for you.
That's too much power for you. I agree completely. All right, I am,
I'm like ready to get in your game. You're at, you're at the church,
I assume. Well, no, I mean, I will be. I'm running to the church and then I'm
going to open my world. What do you think of the halftime show?
Um, it was kind of like, it was good. I don't even, I, I have no, I didn't,
guys, I didn't even, I forgot the Super Bowls today.
Same. I forgot the Super Bowl was literally today.
I thought they stopped doing sports. Okay, I am at the church.
Now, there's been a lot going on. There's been a lot going on, right?
Like I, I, my brain, I just, I would have normally probably watched it.
Okay. Strengthen, strengthen arm in or event to talk, whatever.
Common sleeps, Erd tree seal. Okay. What does that mean? Causes sleep buildup?
What? I'm very confused by how this works. Okay.
Oh yeah. Like, uh, all of the, uh, status effects I believe got changed.
So like sleep functions a little bit differently, like poisons a little bit different.
Like reforge did a lot of stuff. I don't know what any of it is.
Okay. All right. So I can burn my, all right. I'm ready to join your game.
Are we ready? It's open.
Let's go to the Red Sox one, the Super Bowl.
I can't believe the Red Sox one again, dude, if I sell both of my starting swords
and they are Diablo a fight, mythical burning, falling star beasts
of piety requires 60 strength and 54 in and 32 decks.
I am never equipping these. Okay.
We need to get like item. Well, we didn't, well, we have items
because items have random stats on them too. Rare.
Does it have, do the items have like stats? Okay. This is mind plus one.
All right. So gear has actual stats on it. Increases stamina regen by 8%.
Okay. Yeah. You look ridiculous.
Yeah. And I believe they have random ashes of war because it's just scream.
Can you even, can you swing them? All right. So what, what's, what's
plan number one is, do we look up screenshots of how to pick a class?
I don't know that there's any. All right. All right.
Is anybody, can somebody please help us?
It was working, but it's not working in the specific mod load order,
but we kind of had to stop, you know? Yeah. We had to, we had to turn the stream on.
So, all right. If I want to play warlock.
Well, I know that they all cost a hundred souls.
Okay. So we should at least, you should at the very least sell something and have a hundred.
What is it? So that you can potentially accidentally buy.
I already don't worry about anything.
Both of these swords are worth 15,000. I ain't selling.
Okay. So I have enough to, to pick a class. I want the warlock. I, because I want to,
I want the frenzy flame shit to be more powerful. So which one of these is pick class?
First one, the third one, second one, first, third, second one.
How would you, your chat's just going to guess.
Stop saying no elf. Stop that act. We need help.
And here's the problem. If you do choose the,
apparently the branch that kills you, that those are difficulty options.
So you may accidentally change the game difficulty to like hardcore.
Okay. Wait, wait, one, somebody said one, two, one, two, one, one, wait, one, two, one.
Good luck dog. One, this gotta be a way to fucking know this.
One, two, yeah, we need an Oracle effigy.
All right. Yeah. That's what,
that's what you buy from this. Normally there would be a shop here to buy them.
So, but there's no shop. I mean,
that is too silly. Sorry, bud. We can't help you.
Well, they changed it. This is an older version of reforged
so that it could work with Diablo loot. Well, look, let's just go. Let's just go.
Somebody will figure it out. I don't think, I don't think anyone's
going to figure it out. Well, we, we, we have gear right now.
We can go at least go kill like Margaret or something.
Yeah. Man. Oh man. What a, what a nice day out in Limgrave.
You want to go to the, where are you going? I'm just, I was just going to walk into like
one of these random directions. Oh, well we need the horse millennia
Melinda. So anything can drop Diablo loot or everything.
There is no more regular items in this game. There are regular items.
And then there's also Diablo items. There's a lot of things.
This does pretty good damage. I don't have nearly the stats for this.
And I one-shot that enemy. So pretty good. It's like a phantom.
Yeah. And apparently I'm like stealing their souls.
What? I don't know.
Are we classes that we don't know what they are?
Do we accidentally pick classes by killing ourselves with the thing a few times?
Our starting equipment has mods on it from Diablo mod.
Oh, right. Right. Right.
Okay. Yeah. My armor strengthens golden order incantations by 10%.
And I probably have something that is healing me.
Oh my God. This weapon. No, don't please. Don't kill me.
Yeah. My helmet restores health on kill.
It seems like it works. Even if you kill something.
Ooh, I did some damage. Oh my God. I'm dead.
What happens when I die? Oh God. What did you die to?
No, but I'm poisoned. I mean, it's coming close.
Can I respawn here? I'm getting the bonfire.
Whoa. I think my game crashed.
Oh, I rested the bonfire and it's the Molina cut scene.
So maybe your game did crash. Oh, it just pulled me to you.
No, you're not. Give me one second.
Just talking to me about feet. I don't.
I do see the subs, but what I want to tell you is that's way too much.
I really appreciate it. But one of the reasons why I don't like to address subs
is I feel like it encourages it. And that's a lot of money.
That's way too much money. That's way too much money to be giving
an individual streamer like me. So I do appreciate anybody supporting this stream,
but that's way too much. Thank you so much.
But that is, I would say that is enough. That's a lot.
That is far too much to give one individual person, especially me.
Especially me. So please just be careful.
Do not put yourself in financial burden. Do not give this stream money,
because you think even if you think, even if you think I deserve it,
you guys take such good care of me already.
No one individual has to give like hundreds or thousands of subs.
I really appreciate it, but I don't think that worked.
But one of the reasons why I don't address subs is because I don't want to encourage people
to get into this loop where they give so many.
It's something I don't like to encourage,
because I don't want it to be something that people think that they should do too.
So that's all I'm going to say about it. I appreciate anything that anybody does
to this channel. Please take care of yourself.
Don't give me that much money. Give me five bucks a month.
That's your decision if you want to pay five bucks a month to this channel.
You absolutely do not have to, but I don't like to encourage subs, if that makes any sense.
I would rather you spend that money on something in your life.
Maybe on some other smaller streamers.
Not me. Do not give me a thousand subs individually.
I'm just going to tell you.
Thank you so much, everybody.
Now we game.
Did Elden ring mods?
Yeah, I turned on an option.
Can you rest of the bonfire again?
What'd you do?
Hold on.
Okay.
I turned on the option that always to spectate you after dying.
I have seen these menus before and I realized that I stumbled onto the correct option,
but I don't know if we both need to turn that option on.
So for me, when I die, I will not respawn ever until you touch a bonfire.
I can guide you if we both have to have it.
So where do I go from here?
The bottom event text for talk.
Wait, was this? I don't remember.
I don't want to touch anything.
Let me just get my horse.
Well, we'll see how I think I know which one it is.
Three, two, one, two, three, three.
Stop saying numbers.
Three, two, three, three, three.
Okay, I've got torrent.
You level up.
I died, so I don't have any I don't have any crunchies.
No crunchies.
Okay.
I mean, you want to grab the items from around here.
I think that's probably let me wait.
Let me get this on the bar.
Wait, how come?
There it is.
Okay, move that switch.
Okay, there it is.
All right, I don't have any crunchies, so you can level up.
Okay, wait, wait.
No, come to the bonfire.
I know which one it is.
The bottom event text for talk.
Okay.
And then the second from the bottom event text for talk.
And then yes.
And what is this doing?
That is whenever you die, you are forced into spectator mode.
Okay.
Nice.
I activated it.
I didn't die.
Yeah.
And the one below that is when either of us dies, we both die.
So don't touch that one.
Unless you want us to be soul linked.
I don't think that's a good thing.
That's probably a bad idea.
I mean, I would.
All right, we ready?
Pay a lot of money to be soul linked.
All right, let's go.
Help me.
What does it look like I'm doing?
Missing every swing.
Okay.
Oh, yeah, the items are not going to be randomized.
It's just I don't know where Diablo items spawn.
Like that was a talisman of fury.
I don't.
Do you know what would have been so cool?
If if when I joined the game, a little.
And this is just like funny things that they could have added on the bottom.
Like a little text pop up that says so and so has joined your game.
Diablo's minions grow stronger.
Did you even get that item?
What?
You just you're just running in a random direction again.
Wait, what happened?
It was a where where?
Well, like you.
Oh, yeah, right, right, right, right, right.
You can loot this.
We can we can go down and get the thing that lets you apply ashes of wars.
And it's a really important item.
If the items aren't randomized, we should probably get that frost long sword.
Oh, yeah, then our Diablo loot is different because I got a talisman from there.
Well, all right, take a look.
Hey, hey, take a look at this then, because you were a magic.
I don't know how to drop it.
Where is it?
It's dead.
Don't delete it.
Watch out, bird.
So the difference between this one and the last time we played this.
OK, it's leaving.
All right, well, whatever.
So this is a new seed and it's the best enemy in the game.
My jumping higher.
Maybe there's a lot of there's a lot of very small changes.
You might notice like sitting at the the bonfire.
The animation is quicker in reforged.
It is.
All right.
So let me let me level up.
And I believe your jump animation starts sooner.
So there's a lot of tiny things.
Well, I definitely need this.
So I'm going to put it in there.
So are we just trying to get to let's do one of the little dungeons over here.
Let's like, yeah, let's go for it.
Yeah, let's respawn the enemies again.
Let's like kill one enemy and then like let's respawn them again.
Well, I had to level up.
You told me to level up.
OK, well, I had to not level up.
OK, so let's kill let's kill the crab again.
No, just get on your horse and let's go to the place we need to go.
Well, no, there's the done.
Come back right now.
Get back here right now.
There's the catacomb in this area.
Oh, there is sword that you need to use ashes of war.
We have to have like the big enemies spawn here.
Yes, this this this ant is a boss.
Where even am I?
Whoa, valid questions.
Whoa, I'm going to die.
Bro, you're getting three fingered.
You can't use that until I actually have the power.
OK.
Oh, you just got to Claude.
Wait, why can I do this?
Your sword's ashes of war is going to be randomized with the album.
What the fuck?
Yeah, so this one is the stab myself.
I got the kill yourself poison sword.
Jesus treasured furious.
Holy shit.
OK, hold on.
Plus one holy damage percent plus one extra magic damage taken.
I said that so badly.
One extra damage.
It's like a two year old.
I take extra magic damage.
Look, look, daddy.
Look, daddy, magic damage.
Daddy, look.
And then the dad never looks.
Bro, come on.
Oh, also, another thing I know is it's easier to to deplete poison enemies
because they don't regenerate it as quickly.
Give me one sec.
Move this out of the way, move this out of the way, move this out of the way.
Oh, fuck, please don't kill me.
I'm hyping.
I mean, you you you stop moving in the middle of Main Street.
For some reason, I think there was going to be anything over here.
I thought like we killed it all.
That thing is so bad.
Dude, stop swinging.
Can you help me?
I'm going to die.
No, I am.
I probably am going to die, too.
Let's just reset it.
Let's just come back here.
No, we killed everything.
Please, please don't do it.
I'm helping.
I'm coming.
This thing's going to kill you.
He's the last thing we got to kill.
Well, let's ignore him then.
Come over here.
We just got to go in the basement.
Fuck.
I thought I could keep him staggered.
I'm dead.
I said ignore him.
I know, but you're going to die in the basement over there.
There's no enemy in here.
That's just a chest.
Well, whatever.
It doesn't matter.
It really kind of does.
You shouldn't downplay.
It matters that you're dead.
All right.
I got to get a lot of people.
I got to get I got to get into the swing of things here.
OK, you respond.
I'm back.
Don't die.
OK, let's fight the crab.
No, we're going up.
Let's do what you said.
Avoid, avoid, avoid, avoid, avoid.
But yeah.
I'm avoiding that should.
I don't even know how that hit me straight from here.
Follow me.
Cave.
Yeah, in in going in cave in cave.
OK, the whetstone knife.
Perfect.
Pretty good piece of equipment there.
Uncommon magic moon veil.
So what are the rarities?
Is it is a common uncommon?
I have like an ancestral.
It's Diablo.
So I imagine it's Diablo.
But also, I don't know.
I actually think they were kind of weird.
There's like a like above legendary.
There's like epic super ultra mythic.
And then there's a beyond good and evil.
That can never come out.
No, it didn't.
The second one was like really supposed to be coming out, right?
Yeah.
But then they started trying to outsource their game to random people to make.
And then I haven't heard anything about it since then.
All right.
So we're good.
We got what we needed from here.
Ready to rock and roll?
Rock and roll in which direction?
My what we should do.
Here's what I'm going to propose.
Summer jail.
Storm but not summer.
Today is a lizard.
Just a little off.
It's that's I read the S.
Jail.
I'm very confused on where we're going.
I want to go to the ever jail.
Hold on.
Okay.
Storm Hill ever jail.
Not summer jail.
It's behind us.
Can we go up?
Oh, no, we have to go through Stormville Castle.
Okay.
So you would go up that hill and then you turn around and hook left.
Yeah, we could just go game progress or we could try to wrap around there.
I mean, remember, we're like level zero.
I know that you got spoiled last run and you got like five remembrances by this point.
Right.
But you're actually very low level right now.
Did you jump off?
I went down here.
I mean, we really you know what it is.
The map is revealed and it's like freaking me out.
Like being able to see literally every single thing in the game.
Like, I don't know what I don't know where to go
because my brain's like look at every single thing is here.
Would you like to be to mode it?
I think we just go up here.
Okay.
What a mess.
Oh, my God.
What the fuck is that?
Okay.
Did I birdie good?
Yeah.
So we could let's try to fight whatever this is.
There's got to be a bonfire right here, right?
No.
But if you die in here, it just puts you here, doesn't it?
As long as we say the statue.
Yeah.
Statue right there.
Let's go into the summer jail.
It was the storm hill ever jail storm jail some real jail.
The words just mixed together.
Well, that should be easy.
Listen, this is a good fight to do to fear like I load it into the game.
Let's go.
We're so dead.
Is there a phase two as well?
Probably.
Okay.
Good luck.
Where are they?
Are they?
Where'd he go?
Where did who go?
Wait, are you coming back in?
No, I died.
I just died too, but it's not.
Okay.
I'm not going to touch a bonfire.
Yeah.
You feeling okay?
I mean, if you saw my screen, you'd be pretty confused.
I got a bike's war sphere, which is well, probably it won't have the same ash of war
on my screen right now.
You are in the ever jail still and summer in the summer summer hill.
I think I was going to say summer hill jail.
I don't know why this is the S blended into the other word.
I touched a bonfire.
Are you okay?
I am back alive.
Did you respond at the stake?
I respond at the stake near the jail.
I would recommend coming up here to the bonfire
because there's a charge to your flask along the way.
Um, and I don't think that we should be picking fights like spawning into the game
and then fighting Godfrey Godford fry in the summer jails.
No.
Okay.
So let me get my souls.
Did I even have any souls?
Probably not.
I had 2000.
All right.
I'm coming to you.
I mean, there also is always the chance that we go to fight Morgoth.
And it like really now because the randomizer is a little bit more random.
We could be getting that mad soldier.
Oh, I would love that.
Or or or whoa.
Wait a minute.
I just got like I got like a legendary thing.
Hold on.
Rare bolt charge dragon communion seal of the something.
Okay.
What the hell?
I got like a rare legendary helmet.
Night sorceries by 30% strengthen them.
Holy shit.
Are you going to use sorcerers at all?
I have no idea what I'm doing.
I kind of had a plan, but then, uh, we die if we try and do anything.
All right.
With this, what happened?
I thought you touched another thing.
Okay.
You know, it's the complexity of these mods can creasing.
There you go.
I feel like this is probably not even as good as it's not.
All right.
So we have a million options.
Option number one is to just go fight whoever's up there.
Like you said, option number two is to go check out, you know, one of the shacks.
I think we should do some of the easier catacombs and get some more random mythic items and level
up because it requires 60 strength to use my weapons that I currently have.
I basically have nothing.
So then let's go do one of the catacombs.
Yeah, we don't have any smithing stones.
We don't have anything.
Remember we played this recently and we were pretty strong.
Uh, we're not, we don't have anything.
Yeah.
I think it could, because we just did randomizer and we just did this.
My brain's almost like, oh, oh wait, we're new characters.
You're blaming a lot of this on your brain, but I feel like you are the one in control
of your brain.
You ate meat.
That was over 16 hours.
You don't get to say anything.
And I lived and I was fine.
Isn't there a merchant man in here?
I think so.
And then up the road.
Some ways there's a catacomb.
All right.
Where did, okay.
Bernard.
What should we say to Bernard?
What do you mean?
Should we say my faith holds firm?
Yeah, sure.
My faith is firm.
I'm pretty fucking firm right now.
Ash of War.
No skill.
Um, yeah, I know a lot of this stuff too.
I know like the kick got buffed, like a lot of stuff that would normally be kind of bad
got buffed with reforged.
Hmm.
So I'm going to buy kick and use that instead of stab myself.
I have fire on mine.
Actually on this.
That's kind of cool.
Huh.
It won't let me change anything.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
None of my weapons are showing up in the ashes of war.
So maybe Diablo items are like hard set.
You might find them.
Is it possible you can change them out at the blacksmith?
Uh, I don't know.
It should be the same exact mechanic.
You need an item to change them.
Okay.
We have to have an item.
That's what we got in that basement.
I thought was the whetstone blade.
Don't you have to have a blacksmith do it anyways, though?
I don't think so.
Yeah, the whetblade.
We got it.
Anyway, let's, uh, let's go this way.
Yeah, we need to level up.
My health bar is so, how much health?
How much bigger do you have?
Like 14.
Diablo does not let you change them.
You can only level weapons up twice.
What do you mean when you say level weapons up?
Uh, that's I'm screening from chat.
I'm not sure what it means.
Yeah, I'm asking them.
What do they mean?
Okay.
I mean, we could see what's in Margaret's room.
Wait, like you said, what if it's a mad soldier?
There's a catacombs right up here, man.
You keep saying you don't know what you want to do.
And then we go do something.
And then you say we could go do the thing that we're not doing.
Well, we just did something.
Just calling it as I'm seeing it.
And there's a chest in here.
Do you want to open the chest?
Or you want to just immediately abandon and go to Margo?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Chest on table.
You left some gold in a rift in just a common side.
Look, claws.
This thing's still better.
Okay.
Did you get something good?
Uh, I got a weird war pick.
It says inflicts damage when rolling into enemies.
Oh, and these claws have vacuum slice.
These items are pretty weird.
What vacuum slice?
It's a magic hammer that deals damage when I roll on things.
Vacuum slice is the gargoyle attack that shoots like the air blast in a line.
I think that I that's what I got.
I got that air blast thing too.
Yeah, right down this road, there should be a cave.
And I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Like, I'm really pushing us to do it.
I know that I'm being a bit of a I don't want to do a cave.
I don't want to do.
I want to do market the whole time.
We did the last run.
I want to fight market.
We should really do some of these starting caves.
I'm just I'm kidding.
I'm kidding.
I'm I want to do the cave.
I wanted to do market.
I wanted to go to Wendy's.
Actually, let me level up first.
Is Wendy's your your fast food of choice?
When you want a chicken sandwich, where are you going?
McDonald's.
Wait, hold on.
The original McChicken from McDonald's.
Not this new spicy bullshit.
Let me be honest with you.
The original McChicken sandwich from McDonald's.
I like it a lot.
But this this new spicy McChicken that they put everywhere
and they want you so badly to order that and not the original one.
Come on.
I want the original McChicken.
I don't want the spicy powder all over it.
Do you feel me?
I I got to be honest.
I I don't really know.
I don't know much about.
I didn't even know McDonald's had chicken.
You do.
Come on.
I've never had one.
But you knew that McDonald's had chicken on the menu.
I know that they have chicken nuggets.
Well, that I mean, that counts.
I didn't know that McDonald's had chicken.
That's like saying I didn't know that Campbell's had soup.
Hold on.
Hold on a second.
One guy.
OK, never mind.
It's a weird comment.
And it was just stir healthy and based.
He doesn't know McDonald's has chicken, therefore healthy and based.
I like that.
I don't know.
Like, there's so many places now that like specifically would call themselves
like we're chicken places.
So for you to pick McDonald's to be the best chicken sandwiches.
I don't know.
It surprised me.
I didn't even know that they did it because I haven't been in a McDonald's in a long time.
The thing is, I went to a McDonald's.
It was the only ones I've really went to are like New York, like in the subway.
This guy's really hard, by the way.
He's going to kill you in one hit.
Healthy and based.
Well, I didn't say here's the thing.
Oh, my God, my game crashed.
That's not fair.
It's not fair.
I didn't say that it's not the best.
I don't think it's the best chicken sandwich, but it hits pretty well.
That was the question, though.
Yeah, but it kind of is the best for me, even though it's not quality wise.
It's not the best sandwich.
I would say for me, I prefer.
Oh, that's not good.
What's not good?
It didn't open three times.
Hold on.
Is this you just acting out that you don't want to do this cave?
That would be actually pretty funny.
But no, the issue is McDonald's.
You know exactly what you're getting every time.
It's incredibly consistent.
A McChicken from McDonald's is the same McChicken
that has been to the last 10 years.
But unfortunately, now they added the spicy shit on it.
So it's not consistent.
Unfortunately, it's not consistent.
Well, I mean, in a way, that backs up your argument
that they changed something one time and it upset you
that they should have been consistent.
They should have been.
All right.
Normally, they are back.
Did you kill that thing?
I did.
Can you put your thing down?
My thing should be down.
Well, I wonder if I spawn in a weird place.
I'm going to separation, miss.
Did you join me?
Did you try and join me?
I just did.
I was separating.
I'm now alone.
I'm wandering.
I'm looking for you.
I have appeared.
Well, kind of.
OK, the quality of your Diablo weapon is what material you need.
And then all Diablo items can only be plus two.
OK, so you are you still?
I'm still in that catacomb.
I don't know if it put me in your game.
I don't see you on the mini map on the compass.
I never said you joined my world.
That's interesting.
Maybe I can't do it down here.
Maybe because the catacombs make you like you can't fast travel to and from them.
Says I'm going to know.
OK, let me go back to the bonfire.
Wait, no, it does say you were in my game.
OK, you joined.
Hey, that was weird.
There you are.
Yeah, it must just bugged up.
Yeah, McChickens for me were just like, oh, yeah, of course, I like my chickens.
I'm going to order a chicken.
Of course, I will.
A lot of other places that I've been to, it was not that consistent.
And I know it's just like a patty, right?
That's why it was consistent for me.
Have you gone to the McDonald's in Japan?
No, I heard it's good, though.
Well, you're saying they're consistent everywhere.
But have you been everywhere?
I did.
I've not been outside outside of North America.
Well, then is the McDonald's consistent outside of your limited small bubble worldview?
I guess.
I don't know.
Whoa.
OK, you were you were just fighting nothing on my screen.
And it just poured it in and I can't hurt it.
Can it hurt me?
I don't know.
I don't know what's happening.
I'm poisoned.
It hurts.
Oh, he's poisoned.
I'm going to die.
I'm running back.
I have a lot of souls.
All right.
What's your favorite chicken sandwich?
Oh, boy.
Yeah, I have infinite stamina, too.
Yeah, that's part of a reforged.
I'm going to die like right as I touch this.
Oh, lucky.
I don't like there was that big craze a while ago where every person in America was literally
murdering people for like the Popeye's chicken sandwich, right?
That's why I thought like you were going to have some like exclusive.
Like I killed a guy for the sandwich.
I don't like a lot of places.
But I don't really care that much.
It seemed like the kind of thing you would care about.
No.
Oh, I got to eat every chicken sandwich from every.
Why do you think I care that much about chicken sandwiches?
It like falls under the category of like fast food or cereal, which is like one of your biggest.
Dude, the last bowl of cereal I ate was honey bunches of oats with strawberry.
Back in fucking 2019.
You talk about cereal mascots so often that it just seems like.
Oh, I can't be a fan.
I can't be a fan of cereal.
I have to like eat every cereal.
I can't just like cereal.
I can't just like watching the cereal.
I can't like enjoy watching like the characters.
Do they do commercials?
Oh, I gotta go level up.
What?
I got distracted.
Hey, I was the one that was supposed to be dumb today.
I got 4k souls.
OK, we're just starting.
I got a level.
Yeah, like watching the cereal like mascots, you know, do their fucking vlogs that they do.
What?
You watch you watch the cereal mascots do their vlogs.
You're following them on Insta when they do like their makeup tutorials.
And Captain Crunch is like, oh, you want to look like a pirate?
Are you telling me that if Captain Crunch had a YouTube channel where he was like,
oh, hey, Crunchtastic Cruncheteers, me, Captain Crunch, you wouldn't watch every single one?
I don't even watch the Gorillaz YouTube channel.
And that's basically what that is.
No, no, no, no.
We're talking like Captain Crunch is doing what Chuck E. Cheese did.
He's like streaming Elden Ring.
You wouldn't watch that?
Captain Crunch is streaming Elden Ring.
I will take a look.
Yes, you of course you would.
I probably would not stay longer than like a minute.
I would have to look.
He's got a rare.
Oh, nice rare.
Poison plus three and yeah, we saw how streaming worked for the mascots.
Yeah, but here's the thing.
Chuck E. Cheese didn't talk.
The Chuck E. Cheese that streamed didn't talk at all.
Oh, watch out for this guy.
This guy.
Captain Crunch was screaming on Twitch and he was like, oh, my Captain Crunch cereal.
He said that before every single sentence.
People would fucking go crazy for it.
Get wrecked.
The Chappy Challenge.
It would suck.
No, it wouldn't.
It'd be fun.
For a minute.
Oh, this guy again.
I think that never mind.
He like leaves them like the camera on or something.
He like leaves like hot mic on.
Oh, that's kind of funny.
I had you all see when Captain Crunch hot mic'd.
You know what?
I'll see you in a moment for some more Kevin Crunch gameplay.
And it's like you hear shuffling.
You hear like fucking hate this fucking game.
I just fucking hell in the ring millennia.
I've just bought millennia.
Piece of fucking garbage.
I feel like we're not far off from a future.
Like it always takes the corporations like five years to catch on to trends.
Five years from now, Captain Crunch AI generated stream down here.
Jeremy, it's going to happen.
And I think we go in this secret tunnel door.
Okay.
Is it gone?
Oh, oh, did you just got crunchetized?
I would know.
I would want Captain Crunch to play a street fighter or something.
Right.
Are you uncomfortable when the kids in the commercial are like crunchetize me, Captain?
And he's like an old man.
And like all these kids are super excited to like get on his boat alone with him.
Well, I always thought the tricks rabbit was weird.
Like, oh, silly rabbit tricks for kids.
And he's just like, oh, give me that box.
It's like what you can't just.
Why do you have to like, why can't you just buy one?
I don't know.
I got a dragon.
Hold on a minute.
They would wait.
They were taking it.
They were taking it from him.
I got it the wrong way around.
The kids are stealing it from him.
Yeah.
Why silly rabbit tricks are for kids.
Like he wasn't allowed to eat them.
Yeah.
And then the rabbit would starve.
I think there was a different one.
Like the the cookie crisps.
That was the wolf.
I think that was trying to steal.
Watch out.
Grandma.
Corner grandma.
When he said America is so stupid.
Come on now.
America is so stupid because what we have because we have Captain Crunch.
Captain Crunch is a legend.
Oh, it's the Elden Lord.
Who is it?
It's you.
Oh, it's.
Oh, we'll go.
Oh, my God.
What the heck?
Take this.
My Captain Crunch cereal will knock you out of your park.
Take that.
Sir.
Got to protect the captain here.
I could fucking do it.
Can you imagine Captain Crunch just becomes like a huge streamer.
The number one streamer is Captain Crunch.
I wouldn't even care.
I mean, do you care who it is now?
I mean, I don't even who is like.
I would care more if it was Captain Crunch.
That'd be kind of a wild.
Hey, VM.
All the cereal mascots have like huge channels.
That would be so fucked up.
Oh, OK.
We need to actually look at this stuff.
Ancestral star scourges, profit trousers of grit.
These names are definitely Diablo item names.
OK.
And there's a chest over here.
I don't think I can really even put these on.
This is strength scaling off of intelligence.
OK, strengthens death sorceries by 10 percent.
Poison moth flight.
OK, that's kind of cool.
Mind triggers every 2.8 seconds plus one HP every three seconds.
What the hecky dude strengthens gravity sorceries by 30 percent.
Yeah, they get they get kind of wacky, don't they?
An arc plus three on the same item.
They do.
They do for sure get kind of wacky with it.
OK, not that any.
Well, I guess some of the gravity spells are pretty strong.
I don't want to be fat rolling.
I can't wear this.
All right.
Why do we start a new run?
Because we have two new mods on and we're just trying to see how fun it is.
We have the Diablo to loot and then.
Elden ring reforged and randomizer and seamless co-op.
Fire damage dealt and I have fire.
I guess I'll use it, I guess.
Returning to entrance and you were trying to go faith magic.
I want to do faith arcane if we can.
If I can actually figure out how to turn on the warlock class subclass, whatever it is.
OK, I'm really not sure we're going to be able to do that.
Well, it's all right.
All right.
15 vigor.
That's better than 10.
Still fat rolling.
Oh, my God.
I don't know why I thought friendly fire was on.
That was an enjoyable adventure amongst traveling companions.
It was enjoyable.
But now we actually have stuff.
Read the lore on some of the items.
When every single misbegotten revealed every single misbegotten's greatest falsehood,
they wore this legendary restorative foot soldier cap of the Mad Tongue
to show their love for dominula.
All right.
Are they randomized?
I might be.
When Margit attacked the fire giants,
they wore this legendary knight's dialios mask, flaunting their allegiance to Hieta.
What about this uncommon club?
When a commander, when a commander stole a shard of destined death,
they swung this uncommon club so that the knight of the black knives would never reoccur.
Okay.
Yeah, they used this ancestral bolt charge club to win the hand of Merchant Kale.
When Zorias forged the Elden Ring, they struck their enemies with this
common duelist greataxe of the novice mage,
but it was not enough to save their trusted friend Margit.
Pretty good.
Oh, what the?
Not bad.
Pretty good.
All right.
Cool.
Say, where do you want to go?
Far away from that enemy.
Isn't there usually like an item back here that's relevant?
We can go do Margit.
That was kind of your thing.
We did my thing.
We can do your thing.
We can do trade-offs, you know?
That sounds fun.
I want to get some spells.
The lance talisman.
That was a lance talisman for me too.
What does that do?
Okay.
To Margit, who is going to be like millennia.
That would be very sad.
Go to the foot of the urn tree and become Elden Lord now.
I mean, is there anything else to do?
I thought that was Kenneth height.
That's a pot boy on the hill.
Anyone else there?
I'm kind of leading you in a direction that is the opposite direction of Margit.
I know that I'm doing that.
No, I'm aware, but we don't have to.
We can just do whatever.
I was kidding when I said we had to do Margit.
Jump.
My goodness.
I didn't make it.
And we go this way.
There's another cave.
You want to do another cave?
Yeah.
This is my ancestral great club charged with bolts.
And it's going to make merchant Kayle want to marry me.
Where the heck are you going?
I think you got to go up this.
Right?
I know there's one here.
It's probably down here.
Turtle meat.
Right here.
Oh, shoot.
We don't got any torches looking like a dark one.
I wrote a cave and it could be darker.
I heard you love that game.
I love dark and darker.
Oh, man.
I've been addicted, man.
Like, I really just love when I get the item.
I think you're just a hater.
I know.
That's what they all think.
That's what they're all thinking.
You feel any more new or two?
Yeah, I got to like near the end of it.
They're still getting the game is very long.
Are you enjoying it?
What?
He grabbed me from such a weird angle.
Yeah, I was liking it.
I was just getting a little exhausted.
I played a lot.
I had like 60 hours in it.
I was like, I'm doing pretty good on that.
I'm still pressing some Neo buttons while we're playing, but.
It happens.
I don't know what happens.
Hey, you want to go down and there's a giant vacuous tunnel.
Only if we go together.
Just you, me.
Grab my hand.
Captain Crunch, the Cocoa Puffs bird, Tony the Tiger, all of us in our party.
You would collab with, I mean, that's a ton of eyeballs.
A ton of eyeballs.
All the Tony the Tiger fans tuning in.
How many boxes of Frosted Flakes have you ever eaten?
These are way more famous than anybody on here.
How much money would you value?
You, specifically you getting.
Oh, my fucking God.
There was an explosion person here.
I just kind of watched.
So you want to spectate or?
I mean, I guess you have to.
I can't touch the bonfire.
You got to hold the L.
I mean, I respond, but.
Oh, did you?
Yeah, it's very dark down.
I can't see.
It's so dark and darker.
It's like someone's been turning all the lights off.
I'm just going to come down there.
Help, help.
I'm going back.
I'm scared.
How much would you value Frosted Flakes for life?
Like monetary value?
OK.
You're like I can pay right now to unlock all of the gods and smite,
but it's actually Frosted Flakes for life.
I don't really.
I mean, I don't.
When you open your cabinet, there will be a fresh box of Frosted Flakes there.
Whenever you want.
Did you go down the second fall?
Like in the hole?
I don't know where you are.
Did you go down the second drop down?
I'm where you died.
There's multiple drop downs.
I destroyed the fire.
I'm there's a single candle.
I died right here.
Here.
Here we are.
All right.
OK.
Now to the left, you can clearly see that there's a tunnel.
Yeah.
But what you're saying, what's the monetary value for that be worth it to me?
When I open this cabinet, it's filled with it every time.
Humble bundle, choose your own price, but be fair of what the value is.
Well, then I don't care.
Like so I open up my cabinet and it's like I get to decide
what I pay for a box of Frosted Flakes today.
Is that what you're saying?
No, no, no.
You pay up front.
OK.
You pay like a hundred dollars now if you think that's fair.
And then you get Frosted Flakes for life.
OK.
But can I give this to other people?
No.
This is why I said specifically for you.
So I can't like open up this cabinet.
Scarlet rotting us in a cave where we can't see.
Well, you wanted to come down here.
No, forget.
Don't forget who wanted to come down here.
I'm just saying we're having this conversation while we're dodging them
and not actually fighting them or trying to leave.
OK, so here we go.
If I could give it to people, I would just keep opening the cabinet
and just putting boxes and boxes into like a storage facility
and then people can just take it.
Like it would be like a never ending supply of food, right?
You cannot do that.
Stop.
You're cheating.
OK.
Well, then so well, then who cares about I don't like,
I can just go get it to the grocery store.
Oh, three HP a second.
I put it on.
Holy shit.
This thing's cool looking.
I had some HP per second pants or something.
I also have some pants that regenerate F.P.
F.P.
Oh, the pants.
I have a pretty good.
It's got bleed.
I don't think I can really use it.
I need more strength.
OK, make sure you don't die.
Noob.
What's the most you would consider paying for one normal size box of frosted flakes?
Yeah, and then multiply that times your life expectancy of like three weeks.
I don't I I don't eat that much cereal.
Dude, I'm getting so many items.
I know I'm getting like an overwhelming amount of things to look at.
Oh, but there's a big boy.
I also I swear one of us killed themselves and put it on easy mode.
I don't think that happened.
I do think that happened.
Well, it had to have been you because you're the one that coached me through pressing the buttons.
Oh, this thing is a taunt.
I don't want this either that or like we are getting like mythic God weapon
and they're just dealing a shit ton of damage.
I think that's probably more accurate.
Where do you drop here?
You just drop right here.
I believe you.
Yes.
Oh, can you make this jump?
I hope so.
Nope.
Oh, damn it.
Fucking God damn it.
This game is absolutely fucking broken.
How could anybody want to play a game like this?
Stir.
It's really great collabing with you.
Make sure to check out my Kevin Crunch new all Crunch Berry cereal.
God damn it.
Ah, I couldn't make the jump.
I wait.
I'm up here.
I'll make it.
No, this is fine.
I thought I was going to get knocked down like away from everything.
Good save.
Thanks.
Yeah, good save.
What was that?
Stop doing that.
He's going to keep doing that.
Okay.
You don't like frosted flakes.
But too long.
Didn't read.
I don't eat that much cereal.
You're okay.
What do you eat?
If you don't eat cereal, what?
Oh, what that?
I don't know.
Oh, I thought I thought that was one of those things
that like shoot you from the ceiling.
Oh, no, it's an albinoeric.
There's supposed to be something going on in here.
There's usually a giganto octa in here.
Oh, nice teamwork.
Nice.
I can't believe you wanted to come in here
without even getting the lantern.
Well, how hard would it be to talk to you
to tell you that I want to go by the lantern
from the specific lantern spot before you got distracted?
Two minutes.
Are we going to drop here?
Look if this is the right.
Yes, this is the right way.
Oh, this is the right way.
To top yourself off.
Don't be an idiot.
You can mean top myself off.
Heals.
Don't be an idiot.
I'm full HP.
Okay.
You ready?
Are we both using club?
Yeah, because the only thing we can both use.
Okay.
We need stats.
Guardian Gary Garris.
Oh, no, it's Gary.
Of course, Gary.
Who could forget?
Wait, it's Gary and a bunch of other.
What?
I don't know what these are.
It's motorbike snails.
Gary.
All right.
These things are actually kind of dangerous.
This is definitely uneasy for me.
What do you mean uneasy?
Reborn has like a difficulty setting and I must have picked one.
I don't know.
What is that?
Oh, fuck off, Gary.
Oh, don't call me Guardian Garris.
My friends call me Gary.
Okay.
I got a bunch of shit.
This is more sorceries.
Okay.
What about this shit?
Golden order incantations.
Stamina regen by 8%.
That's actually kind of good, but no.
I've got the planets.
I love that weapon.
Do you want this baby rattle that is also the moon veil?
Or no, this is just a regular katana attack.
I use that in my regular playthrough.
Pretty fun.
I don't think I wanted to act like a katana, though.
That seems really kind of bad.
Okay.
Well, you're bad.
We got to go to a bonfire.
Make sure it's not on easy mode.
I'm starting to understand it.
I get it.
We just need stats first so we can actually put some of this stuff on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is physical damage.
Physical damage.
We got to teleport.
Has to happen.
Okay, hold on.
All right, let's go.
I posted pictures of the mod's menu trees in the Discord.
What?
A hero?
A hero is the right word.
Oh, they're fully labeled with red lines on what they lead to.
Really?
Jesus.
Wow, that's actually amazing.
This has the stomp.
Isn't this thing insane?
Sir, this thing's broken, right?
They nerfed it a lot, but it is very strong.
Okay, I'll take it.
Oh, hold up.
That's why I was confused earlier.
Yeah.
We don't have a fortunes menu that we're supposed to have.
I don't know what enables that to exist.
I thought you had it from the beginning in Reforge,
but underneath flasks it's supposed to be fortunes and we don't have it.
Okay.
And I don't know why not.
I think we need an item, somebody said.
You need an item and you buy it from Kayle.
Okay, let's go warp to Kayle.
Okay.
Oracle's Effigy is what we need.
Trying to go there.
It's doing that thing.
I can't go.
We'll have to try it again.
Wait, is it earlier than Kayle?
An item you pick up at the first bonfire after you go up the elevator.
Yeah, we just ran right past that.
Oh, so like the graveyard or like the first step?
The first step.
Okay.
Oh, oh, I don't know.
I thought there was an item down there usually.
I'm starting to understand it.
I'm starting to get it.
It was a lot of overwhelming items and stuff and I think I'm getting it.
It's supposed to be that first stake.
We might have gotten it somewhere else then.
Okay.
I think somebody tried to give me directions very early on saying.
Is there an item there for you?
There was, but I think it was just the pick it up just absentmindedly.
I know that the item that is usually there we picked up like in that dungeon
because it's usually like a furled finger or something.
I don't see anything new.
You buy it from Kayle on the patch you're currently on.
It's there on the newer patches.
Okay.
Yeah.
We're on an old patch so that it works with Diablo items.
Okay.
So now let's just get over there then.
My mom brought me fish sticks and garlic bread.
This rules.
That sounds pretty good actually.
He's not selling anything particularly interesting.
No.
No, not really.
Yeah.
We had to do a bunch of goofy shit to get these to even run together.
So maybe we just can't do it.
It's all right.
You buy a torch though.
I do want to level up.
Hmm.
I want to do faith and arcane but I'm kind of scared that my endurance is literally eight.
So I'm going to fix that.
Okay.
Follow sit down for a second.
Reforge is not really compatible with randomizer plus DSL just with okay.
Okay.
Do event text for talk the top one.
Then do the top one.
Okay.
Then three down.
So you mean like one, two, three.
Fourth one.
Yeah.
The fourth one, three down.
Okay.
Say yes.
Then say yes.
What the fuck?
Ow.
What did you do?
That you have to die but that's to change the difficulty.
The difficulty changing kills you so you don't like carry over souls
or I don't know what their rules are but that made sure that we're both like on actual.
There's a normal difficulty.
We're on adept mode.
Okay.
We're co-oping like why not?
Oh, don't look at Ronnie when you respawn.
Are you actually being serious?
You're not being serious, right?
No, I'm not being serious.
You're such a joker.
One too many mods.
I forgot I left that one in for my personal archives.
Will you shut the fuck up?
Okay.
Bell's over there.
Ring my bell.
So I got this new item.
Things got that frost stomp.
I think we'd be able to stomp through the castle.
It goes a little bit like a wha-bam.
Damn.
You look like a bro.
Thanks.
You were scaling intelligence and arcane, you said?
I'm doing arcane and faith.
I want to do frenzied fire with three fingers.
So if I had like a faith arcane weapon.
I would probably use it if you had it.
Okay.
He would probably use it.
How about we go kill Margo?
I think we could at this stage.
What did that do?
It's a bow.
Okay.
I have a strengthens night sorceries by 30%.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I just got a lot of...
I didn't look at one or two things
because they're throwing a million items at us.
Okay.
All right.
Let me buy some arrows.
I'm going to keep the strength one on.
I'm poor.
Never mind.
I bought one arrow.
Okay.
Let's teleport to storm hill shack.
Yeah.
And let's go fight Margaret.
Why not?
Yeah.
I can't wait to open up Margaret
and it's going to be Shrek.
Is our warp like not working again?
It does it sometimes.
Do it again.
Hey, how about we go down here to this cave?
We could do that too.
Hey, follow me.
The universe was telling me through its bizarre powers.
You need the dingleberry drinker mod
if you want to drink.
Yeah.
I'm sad the classes thing is so goofed.
The new gimmick for this stream here.
We have the Diablo 2 Ludon, a new randomizer seed,
and then Elden Ring reforged,
which we probably can't use some of the stuff with it,
but we're just trying to we're just checking it out, you know?
Yeah.
It's pretty big overhaul.
We're checking it out.
Mechanics.
We're just seeing what happens.
I mean, anything could happen at any moment.
Even right now.
Something could be happening that we don't know about.
Well, I this weapon is probably way better.
I'm going to be doing that frost stomp.
It's going to be so insane.
You don't even have any idea.
Frenzy flame doesn't scale with arcane.
The oh, wait.
OK, so the warlock class that I can't choose
scales frenzied flame with it changes things.
So but I can't do that.
So all right, I need to figure out what to do.
Um, shit.
Hold on.
I don't want you can't drop it from the equipment on you, right?
I think it has to be in your inventory.
It's just faith.
OK, cool.
It's still decent.
Well, it lights up the hallway, so that's helpful.
I'm curious if this is good for you.
I dropped a weapon here.
Ancestral tempered lightning likes war spear.
OK, three in three arcane stamina minus 18 percent.
I need I don't have the stats for it, but I'll definitely keep it on.
OK, cool.
Oh, yeah, I'll use it eventually.
All right, let's let's explore this cave.
Oh, I have another faith one.
Actually, this one might also be cool.
I'm just going to drop it.
You can look at it later.
It just I know I didn't drop it.
Never mind.
Let's just let's just go.
Let's just let's just let's just game.
Game on.
Oh, I have F.P. Regen.
I mean, this is like kind of all right, I think.
I mean, you killed shit that was not on the screen.
I can't I'll be torch guy.
It's not really helping, but it's kind of doing stuff.
It's like staggering people.
It's OK.
It's not bad.
This is the ancient ancestral dragon's torch of light seeing.
Is that what it actually is called?
No, I made that one up.
Demi human chief soldier.
Watch out.
Are you sure it's not you put it on easy?
OK, rare, rare lightning night rider flail of shadow walking.
Treasured talisman of restoration,
treasured minor invigorating bloodhound.
I dropped like his whole house.
This guy was moving.
You had a you haul in this frickin little room.
OK, hold on a minute.
Oh, look at that.
Look, look, look, look, look, look, look.
Strengthens frenzied flame incantations by 10 percent.
Where do you usually get your first frenzied flame?
Because like the item that's not random,
we can go get that for you.
I just want them all.
That's what I mean.
We can we can go get them.
I've never done it, so I don't really know where they are.
Well, I'm sure someone in your chat will make a fully
fleshed out diagram labeled which one of these is more efficient 3fp every 2.5
before fp every 3.5 which one mathematically it gets you more and you
don't want to play path of exile no you're gonna ask that question and you
don't want to play okay but yeah we just got in a lot of stuff or HP fire damage
I'm gonna keep that one on all right cool oh this is fun I like this this
is actually really cool yeah I didn't expect that like this much to get thrown
at us I think it was very easy to get very confused and overwhelmed in the
first like 45 minutes to an hour so I think we're good did you go back to the
word you go through I ran up to the dragon communion area and that's all
like all that's all the same so we can go warp to the shack now do the shack let
me just yeah because if you have it then I should have it too then right the
I love this shack you got a shadow walk-in weapon okay I wonder what that
does if these mods are funny this this armor strengthens bestial incantations
by 10% strengthens bestial incantations by 10% neat it just does them both but
they're the same when the frenzied flame left grandsacks behind they presented
this rare madman skeletal mask of the fire Giants to hide among the peasants
fleeing limb grave that's pretty crazy lore let me level up I'm gonna just dump
it into let's get bigger up to 20 or make any decisions okay all right market
hold on sit back down sit back down are we doing another we are we're doing
another kill ourselves difficulty change yes okay because there is a co-op
difficulties and I feel like that might be overriding though it doesn't have an
easy it only has normal and hard and master it like that should be fine okay
hold on frenzied flame frenzied flame read more descriptions when Hayatah
joined the militia protecting Farramazula they domed this treasured
emboldened talisman of restoration as they liked how it looked that's it
that's all the war nights on horseback are deadly foes they see all below from
their lofty position meeting little meaningful resistance as they charge
ahead it's accurate yeah they liked it they like the way it looked you'll get
that come on I got it nice watch out it's the perfect human all right
market what do you got I deleted them I killed him all right who's in here but
your foolish ambitions to waste skip we already know the oh Leo Leo nine
misbegotten the fellow man I I was like I was mashing role and I never rolled
you got this whoa how come I didn't roll excuse me excuse me no I'm fine what
though no no really though no no no really though no no really though what
I didn't dodge through that no no like really though huh really though I dodged
right into it like there was no iframe you saw do you literally saw that that
freeze-frame that that has me very concerned because I saw a lot of people
on the reforge saying that their dodge rolls had no iframes the mod you're
using removes iframes no it does not does it I know that you can stand still
and roll and you do this move and that definitely has iframes wait hold on
there's a different dodge I know that dodges but I think I thought dodges still
could dodge the iframes are different in the mod yeah should we try this when you
change difficulties like hard changes the amount of iframes you have what let
me try the new one but that didn't really help but it didn't work good luck
like I just got lucky on that that was too early no how do you play a from
software game without iframes that seems like oh mega difficult we have to parry
everything my game crashed there probably is iframes but it's probably
somebody just said in chat and this is true yeah I don't want to do this I
would like to remove that because we're going to change our muscle memory
completely and it's gonna ruin every single other game you ever play wait
what's gonna ruin your muscle memory changing if there are iframes if there
and we have to learn where they are then we're never gonna be able to play Elden
Ring ever again normally they're supposed to be the same on normal I did
have us choose adept so maybe the iframes are like slightly changed and
we should just switch back to normal mode if that were the case but I did see
a lot of people in the mod comments being like hey my dodge doesn't work hmm
and I was kind of praying like that won't happen to us I'm opening my world
to you and I'm gonna walk you through choosing normal mode okay was it's way
harder it was way harder this way it'll be easier to play the regular game it's
just tighter iframes wouldn't that just make you better at the game no I don't
think so because it then you lose opportunity to dodge with more iframes
and I think would actually make you play worse because the there's only there's
only one way to dodge and getting that perfect iframe then when you play
normally it's like you're gonna get hit because you did it wrong you know what I
mean you get it why is she here once we actually I have to oh I'm
table Melina can you go away no she's fine you're just touching me all right
what incantations do you have okay lame ones for losers lame sling lame
fortification eel I don't want to heal I just want like the frenzied flame
catch flame and flame sling catch flame is godlike okay um we need to exhaust
some dialogue here right so we have we both of the smithing stone change but we
only need one so that's good yeah yeah although I don't really have enough
money sell random items could yeah I guess I'll just upgrade the hell out of
this thing and again the Diablo items only need to be upgraded twice and
that's their max okay but upgrading a mythic or whatever is better than
upgrading a common and they require bigger stones so it's like a life steal
with lightning damage dex weapon and just get rid of it I want it strength
plus two poison moth light Frank holy shit this thing I'm gonna hold on to
this cuz cuz it's kind of crazy so I got a plus two yeah I'm ready to go
yeah I'm ready to although I do want wait I don't want to buy this other
thing be quiet I want to get this catch flame you feel this is good I've never
done any of this before I don't know is it any good a lot of it again with
reforged history is balanced differently sparks flame from hand okay I'll try it
I'm ready to go back to market we have better weapons now I mean you do oh wait
the actual is lit the shop what if there's anything there it's not random
so no it's not random okay um okay and then when you get here we're gonna sit
back down and we're gonna normal mode and hope that it has something to do
with the dodge frames that's what we can hope I feel like I've dodged things I
don't know at what point what happened um event text the top one okay the top
one mm-hmm down to yes okay hitting yes what did you do what did you do what did
you do oh my god what did you do I messed up you fucking idiot god wrong
one I hope we can dodge making making me so angry all right because I don't buy
that there's like oh there's a smaller amount of dodge frames cuz I was it
didn't even look like I was rolling the way I was getting hit like I must have
been hitting them pretty early to not even roll at all go test it I have I
frames again oh yeah I look looks yeah I do as well maybe ish well it's enough
for us to kill him yes enough yes we got it
ooh spell blade gloves talisman talisman carrying sword sorceries Santa
Frutata dude wild strike I forgot is like you can't stop you so is magic damage
fire damage or is it fire damage because I guess I should put this on it's fire
damage all right well now I can level up now the question becomes this I'm not
gonna blow up my character again I'm trying to do frenzied flame so that is
that just only faith I want to be like the the eyes you know burning and
everything like that I believe that would only be faith so I should do faith
and then enough strength index to put whatever item I want and then just
vigor and endurance vigor is a pretty good ability that people like vigor you
should look at extra life like a normal person I don't think you know what we
have activated every item is completely random could be anything magic damage
isn't fire bro I don't think you I don't think you understand what's going on
right now guys I don't think you understand the type of danger that
you're in I don't think you get it I think I'm just gonna go let's just do
bigger and endurance like I gotta get these out of the way your mom so low
walks in the room opens the door behind you and looks at your computer and sees
that oh is that Jerma on the screen and she's blushing and you're like why is
my mom blushing at Jerma oh is that Jerma and she sits down next to you and she's
like I want to watch this and she tells you to get out huh what mom that's my
computer okay cool kill him you got that guy you steal 30% of our ruins when
we're in Syria don't act like you don't know wait do we need him to open up this
gate do we need to does he need to do that does he need to like whistle and
tell them to open it because it would be very helpful if it was open it's not
open and it won't be and won't ever will be okay what did I do wrong I just
steal 30% of your rooms okay so I want to get more arcane I think no no no no
no no no but on Fextral life where do you get your first frenzied ability I
could just look it up I guess but like a normal person it won't be there will it
it will it's not items are not random I just got common frenzied flame seal of
the frenzied fire it just was right here do it you won't you don't have the ball
yeah he wasn't even attacking oh his friend yeah I think it's that this club
is like ancestral quality this ancestral club and it's just feeling
bonkers damage all right I got the frenzied flame strengthens fire monk and
Giants flame incantations that doesn't help me watch out that's not even a
seal that I want to use I want things that add to frenzied flame incantations
eventually I mean oh my god I'm running I've been mad oh boy that's bad that's a
one-hit kill so that's interesting that that hurts that is pretty interesting
isn't it that kid's mom is pouting right now so how close do I have to be for
that it did not hit things from I was very close that that's like closer than
some melee weapons yeah this thing stinks doesn't it it's does good damage
but it you do have to be very close oh my god that is a lot and you can uh you
can like chain cast it multiple times this is dramatically just fall off it's
really good though there is one that's like identical that's like greater flame
that has a little bit more a we get on my way watch out that things I want to
kill hit me three times I'm coming one of us will hit you I promise yeah we
got to go open that door poison we need that oh fuck that's bad I think that I
cannot be stopped honestly okay all right not bad so far in here I'm the
tank I'm I am the frenzied club this thing is pretty good
herb sword talisman what's that do it's normal to be a little curved oh okay
rusty key yep so this specific buff criteria for a frenzied flame I'm in the
mod chat will help me my mom said you suck at this game but stir is amazing
thanks mom you but didn't say that well you're going the wrong way I want to
kill this guy man I love it when you blow little kisses at your enemies isn't
there's an item over here you don't want it I mean it feels like everything's
gonna be hard to compete with Diablo I guess these were Diablo I didn't you
got me there man that rare talisman of emboldening stamina regen 8% um yeah
good thing I picked that up sorry okay let's go pretty good all right I'm just
gonna stack faith now cuz this thing will just kill things oh what a mod chat
is like what are you talking about okay so what is the buff criteria for
frenzied flame stuff somebody put a big paragraph in the chat and I couldn't
read it I don't even know what the phrase buff criteria is like what in
Kent this day this is apparently specific buff criteria to make frenzied
flame do more damage it was spam oh no idea what you're talking about my are
talking about I understand there's there's no buff criteria the seal that
I use is frenzied flame get buffed does it get buffed from you know fire giant
oh that's a weird-looking wall use the frenzy seal and level faith you're gonna
do the German skip yeah the original German skip I made this up patented it
patented edited okay let's go electric flame grant me strength buffs fire damage
and the fire damage is Zeke tear okay frenzied flame seal buffs frenzied flame
incantations think it's fairly obvious well but that's that's not what it says
because this is the Diablo 2 loot version of it does that the base seal
itself is still the same okay so the the stuff that it says on it are additional
modifiers that it has besides the fact that it is the frenzied flame scaling
talisman okay so that was my question it has been answered completely and I am
very satisfied with my new grab of gear okay he jumped don't take any fall
damage in this mod really I don't really I'm just gonna say that because I hope
it's true I didn't I didn't take any either I feel like I should have I am
the frenzied club yeah am I wearing like yeah that I got fire and ice you're like
an anime character I took off the regen gloves stupid of me common acts of
Godfrey what okay cool 45 now I'm not going strength oh yeah common common
acts of Godfrey he goes to the grocery store does a bathroom minus two you make
chicken nuggets or a tuna sandwich I'm gonna go with tuna I would go with you
know you don't think people that like tuna are freaks no and you know I'm
really kind of sick of this weird this weird bullshit where if you like tuna
fish sandwiches you're something's wrong with you but that I've seen are you one
of those people I am one of those people because like fishes this is kind of
gross and then you mush it up you're like a mushed up fish how do you think
they make like a chicken patty you got me there actually and crab cakes are
pretty solid you got you got me what about like a how do you eat hot dogs
yeah I mean I I I take this L and I accept that I've been exposed good good
I think it's freaking me out it's flying weird I don't think my bow works or
maybe like an arrows don't work the way I think they are sleep Kane oh my
goodness there's so many things I think it's a once we get to a bonfire it's a
look at what I have you for gear situation yeah how do we normally you
gotta come in here to open this right stir humbly accepting an L is actually a
W I mean I still think that tuna fish is disgusting but I I see how my specific
line of thought to why it was disgusting is misguided but the thing is I feel
like people that say tuna is disgusting had a gross tuna at one point a great
childhood and a great understanding of like what food really is and they
weren't fed like mush's children because you know this day okay there's
like chunk light tuna is light tuna this solid tuna and there this is a
tier system with tuna fish off in the shelf at the grocery store chunk light
tuna is I do not like it it's it's kind of disgusting I actually don't like it
at all I think to describe it as chunk light has already got me pretty chunk
light tuna is it's not I don't not like it it's way too it's just it's not good
it's pretty bad do a poll and like what's the what's the good one solid
albacore tuna is like just call it solid white albacore tuna like actual fish
not like mush chunk light tuna I don't know what the scale is but it's not it's
a lower quality I don't know the words you're using it's it's just to determine
like the quality and the scale of the ingredients I don't know it's just
chunk light tuna it just means it like really is that a real term or no no
that's a real term that's that is actually on could light yes I don't know
why I don't know why it's called that but that's like isn't this all just
really disgusting sounding no yeah who the fuck is this person in the lobby I
don't think you could describe any food as chunk light and have it sound
appetizing just just protect me for a second chunk light tuna chunk light
tuna typically consists of skipjack but also may include yellowfin or big eye
tuna it features a softer texture and it tends to be darker in color with smaller
pieces and a stronger flavor that's why I don't like it there you go that's what
chunk light tuna is what it means and the kind you like is called solid
albacore well like I'm still like wouldn't just be easier to not eat tuna
but I like solid white albacore tuna I like the way they taste I like it it
tastes good with pretzels but wouldn't it be easier to not like it I don't know
what are some foods that you like that I don't like that green ketchup that green
and purple ketchup that's like fucking weird you like that stop implying that I
like that no one likes that oh you know I do not watch that on my permanent
record you can't do that to someone I'll never work again yeah it's kind of
gross when you know it's over at your very place and open up the fridge you're
like yeah grab a snack I'm like alright and I see you got that purple ketchup in
there and I was like no fucking way does a human have this you you go over like
to someone's house and they're like oh we're having burgers for dinner if you
want to stay in here like oh absolutely I would love that but like they
hand you a burger and like under your bun is purple ketchup you politely gonna
you just gonna politely eat that you're gonna not mention it I'll eat it but do
you mention it no okay then you take a bite and it really tastes like it's I
get it's sickening it's sickening to me yeah yes you want to like gag and like
oh shit I went mad yeah that can happen to people too much
too much her pulled ketchup I feel like you're the kind of guy that would eat
the eat the hamburger with a straight face and a smile and say no I actually
really like this no guys trust me I don't hate this no I actually were like
really actually like this but I say it that many times yes I think that that
was the most accurate thing of what you said of all of the whole thing you just
did the amount of times I say it is what's actually accurate here
what's up actually hurt a lot just burn ancestral stir-w randomly generated I
don't like tuna fish therefore you're gross come on what is this what is this
bullshit there's a lot of enemies out here be fine how did I not lock on well
I just mean like if you go to the store to buy food like you still do that right
and then yeah like there's tuna and then there's chicken next to it then you
willingly chew you're choosing tuna over something is there something wrong with
having options to eat why I don't want to honestly I believe that one day like
people talk about you know the rapture coming and it's soon and that one day
like the government's gonna take over and we're all gonna have to eat the
little pellets that they give us but like I would love to just eat pellets
every day I knew you were gonna say that no like our dog eats the same exact
pellets every single day every day of its life four years and it's good for
it and that's all it needs there's going through his dog food arc I see you just
never on my side we're just gonna they're just not on my side you know what
I I will agree with you on a couple small things here what that there's a
lot of stuff in there holy shit oh my god okay we need to take a look but
there's bonfire up here and we can do like we have 700 items to loot okay your
your issue here with with this is let me let me level up this is the this is the
strategy you hit him with a deranged argument and then you let him look at
his items there's no time to rebuttal I win free faith is pretty good I want the
fire damage one I have a really good helmet for you I see it oh I'm getting
ready to drop okay so what's what's going on again say it again say it again
no I think I'm good no no I wanted I do I had a rebuttal and I want to give it to
you and say your point again I want to eat pebbles okay I understand because
sometimes I think everyone's probably like this sometimes when you're really
busy there's a lot going on there's a lot of things happening it's like eating
food can sometimes kind of be a pain in the ass sometimes always right and unless
you're like I'm out at a restaurant and this this is like really good it was
prepared for me it's like a whole environment but if it's like day to day
if I had the senzu beans I'd just be chomping them I would I think I would use
it only for purposes of hey I know tomorrow is gonna be a really busy day I
don't have to worry about food cuz I'm gonna take the weird pellet that's like
700 calories and it's every nutrient I need I'll be alright I wouldn't want to
do that for every meal I feel like that you're kind of deleting an entire
purpose to be like alive as a human is like to enjoy food right like we enjoying
consuming food is like a huge deal what is the meaning of life eat that food
I'm serious I'm telling you it's probably pretty it's pretty high up
there I think humans getting enjoyment from food is way up there on the list
for you know our existence and if we weren't eating food then we might as
well just fucking die is what you're saying no I'm just saying that like like
think about it food social togetherness conversation around a table at a
restaurant you know what I mean like I don't think we're gonna not gonna go to
a restaurant and we're gonna pick the pill off the menu no fuck that I want I
want to take a bite of my broccolini and go oh there's garlic on here and hey
stir what do you think you want to try by the way how was that ball game last
night right I don't want to lose that my Twitter handle is stir loves food
that's what I'm saying somewhat I I'm aware but like I I wish there was a
pebble I would eat the pebble but I wouldn't want to eat the pebble for
every meal and you are going down a path of the pet like we're eating the weird
like ground up whatever bugs or something pebbles I don't want to eat
that for every meal stir who do you think made the first sauce and I mean
that what what and you expect me to have I don't know hold on let's let him work
through it who made the first sauce is there a clue in that sentence it's just
a question it's just a philosophical question who made the first sauce
philosophically who made the first sauce someone who thought their food was
boring but why but who what do you mean boring food was you need to eat food
for fuel back in like the caveman days what are you talking about why would
you make a sauce I'm gonna make a marinara sauce why you need food
tastes good it's enjoyable but your food is scarce you can't you know you can't
make like you get but you know you're not gonna make a sauce who made the
first sauce hey let me throw a counter argument back at you if all you eat is
pebbles what if you put those pebbles in like milk that'll be disgusting okay
what if you had a lifetime supply of these pebbles all right we can we can
we can walk and talk we can walk and talk okay what if these pebbles were a
little bit fruity or even chocolate who made the first sauce is all I'm saying
and I think like whoever made the first sauce is Jesus Christ no no no no no
follow him no but why I know you cannot doubt it I understand the argument of
and look this whole argument is fucking stupid I'm aware of that it's just I
was I was I was having a fun time I'm I just wished like sometimes I'm sick of
eating you agreed and I also want to say that if you like you're like you would
don't eat very healthy and you're like oh man I like vegetables are so lame
you start eating healthier you get more used to that food and you start to like
dude I dude I could really go from us for some asparagus right now you know
how like you're a child you all you want is chicken nuggets and then you grow up
and you're like you know actually asparagus you know I could go from
asparagus right now yeah so eventually the pebbles would grow on you to the
point they're like dude I could really hit a bowl of pebbles why but these
pebbles have a flavor to them you didn't say that do they taste a certain way
they don't have to also you're gonna want to pick this up you ran past like
the golden seed tree of deliciousness yeah the ancestral beast champion armor
of the succubus I think I think the issue that I'm having as well as
everybody else not just me everyone else in chat is asking the same question
yeah you okay so you're eating multiple yeah a bowl of these so I thought it was
like eat one and it was all of your nutrition for the whole day like a bowl
of pet like you're an adult you have to eat more than one pebble you can't go to
wait and dot and get one dot why would you want this why do you want to eat a
bowl of pebbles you're good it's just like I'm being realistic I don't want to
have to if I could eat one Senzu bean and be done I would love that but
realistically I'm gonna have to eat a bowl full of pebbles cuz I'm like a big
person get it on a whiteboard so I can look at it and I'll give I have one
final argument okay eats bowl of pebbles for nutrients okay I thought that was
part of the mod for a second and I was actually scared that something bad was
going on I don't what does that mean that's my final argument I don't I don't
know what that means that's your problem is that your favorite song or something
I don't get it how does it actually didn't know this eat the geese how am I
the most a zoomer there's no way I don't get it just forget it he doesn't know oh
it's the giga Chad song yeah yeah I only know giga Chad is the face that kind of
appears and leans in on my face has a song I did not know that so I win is
what you're saying I don't want I don't want to eat pebbles I would like the
option to eat one pebble to have all full nutrition but that's it oh you want
another argument actually sure what is our Elden ring character eating lots of
different shit actually runes runes we're not eating the runes make us
stronger all we need are runes we're not eating there's nothing else that we need
we're not eating them we're like absorbing them it's a but they're in the
air it's like a gas we're not eating runes we're eating runes all right can
we fight this boss or are you gonna keep weirding everybody out am I like
chats on my side no they're not no way okay let's beat this boss first try
you're gonna do a poll too late and I couldn't see what it was I think that
actually is a Maleketh what yes Maleketh man wait why are we getting another
mimic here cuz that's the way it be I but why we already pop all it's all
mimicked here now I'm not even casting I'm just cheering you on
well is it another mimic dear there's something wrong no it's not everything's
great yes I got a remembrance and I got a great rune I got a lot oh yeah cuz
it's not it's not randomized we actually I keep forgetting wait play that play
that song again okay you ready mm-hmm go why do you have that ready for that
moment that moment right there you play that when we die to the boss yeah how
do you not know anything about comedy keep it in mind okay go with let's go
25 faith let's go with yeah I also got a remembrance what is it it's uh the
grafted do we care about this or do I just take this and level up some of the
stuff do we care about what the remembrances do they actually work or
would they be yabla it's it's it's all every item that would normally appear in
the game is not randomized and is not a Diablo item the Diablo items are extra
okay so remembrance would just be the default remembrance stuff which would
be really really stupid because why would we want a remembrance item yeah
okay then they're not ancestral weapons so like they're not the cool ones
okay now I don't want to ruin this character because I could oh I have a
faith of bow a frost build-up faith of bow rare if you're interested in that
should I what should I get strength index do if I'm gonna be almost if I'm
gonna be almost a pure caster do I need to even put any points into any of this
if my plane eventually I think that's it right yeah here check this item out
hold on hold on he's holding I'm holding holding holding item I am oh what the
heck all right it's time to look through all of our items I'll see you in
like 30 minutes I'm looking through we got a lot of little gunk I'm gonna keep
this on thorns mind bestial incantations it's got a lot of sickles this thing is
actually amazing I'm gonna use this for now free HP ooh mm-hmm I'll keep the
three HP on or FP that's pretty good this one's better ooh this one's good
too yeah it's one two vigor and two HP every three seconds mmm that sounds
delicious this is frenzy flame though all right don't let me forget I have
this because I want it eventually okay I think I'm all right for now actually
let me hold oh I'm gonna look up the Diablo loot mod and figure out what is
actually the higher tier it goes common uncommon rare treasured ancestral
legendary mythical god-slaying that's a lot of tears there's a lot of tears yeah
frost damage okay so the friend how much the frenzied flame seal is how much base
just for existing how much damage did anybody know because this is ten percent
frenzied flame but this doesn't matter seven that's 20% bro that's Giants flame
incantations is be faith scaling right now this is C but incantation scaling so
this is 152 this one's like better for now I guess 20% normally all right what
about my weapons still better Lee mind I need some more strength to put this on
if I want to put on that lightning spear thing okay do you have any like plus
strength talismans I just got another slot I think I think so if faith one
there's a lot of numbers on the screen right now
great he every 5.8 seconds this is better kind of I guess all right let's
just go I think I know what I'm doing did you go in here did you even sit on
throne I started running through you didn't even do the funny sit on the
throne thing with me in the room oh well you were like looking at your items
fuck dude okay I got on everything I think is worth having on oh so I do have
a big question though what is going on with the that was two mimic tears in a
row why did that happen I don't know I think because we loosened up the the
overall pool of potential things it can be drawing from because we would like
widen to the important areas thing you know I mean there are no oh there are
two in the base game okay are there actually because I was trying to think
like I don't there shouldn't be two mimic tears pops as the regular stuff I
don't need it I don't want it oh it's one in a dungeon and one of the little
mini-dungeons okay that makes sense sounds good to me hot throne items
damage increase I don't all right so and where to now that was cool when I just
go on the left and do the the jail you love evergales just a boss right there
okay all right I mean just boss it's just a boss like it's just the boss bro
let's just get some runes Academy scroll where did you go oh you went down I see
how did you you really went all over here or whatever here we go coming I was
looking at stuff should be a chest in here somewhere I thought there was a
chest in here that's not that's you okay what the hell I'm just I'm making it so
it's easy to see everything all right let's do the average ill let's go to
summer jail yeah it's like not actually that close you got to go like all the
way around oh shit that's I think you're right but there should be it's not it's
not that you know what you're gonna give up when I say something's a little hard
let's stick to our guns here what are you guys doing over here wrong with you
guys I got a sacred tear hold on oh yeah me too definitely use it what's your
coolest item probably the axe that I have right now oh no probably the catch
flame it's the only thing doing damage it is right here yeah but you had to go
down further for that jump all right something very hard nothing can stop me
once I start swinging I've already won the fight I hope is a dragon bulls the
thief of fire nice my god oh my god flame of the fell God yes that thing's
probably pretty good that's not a frenzy spell better than what I have trash
trash hey I don't open up your fridge and say look at all this trash in here
this is my food I would do that if there were tuna in it what's your favorite
food like baby like it like oh my goodness I love it so much it's my
favorite single fucking food item what is it without question my favorite food
is flavorless nutrient pebble no no nobody thinks that's funny besides you
okay so answer question what is your favorite what's your favorite single
food item okay all right sorry my favorite food is a flavorless nutrient
pebble cool that's that that's the answer I was looking for if you were
to pick something else besides flavorless nutrients back it up you you
do come over and you open the fridge and it is like 20 tubs without labels all
filled with the same white paste mm-hmm well but what's in it though there's no
labels on it is a tuna fish it's not no it's it is like oh dude it's tuna this
is not the right one I got the wrong song well I can't hear it so you never
want I don't know I don't really know what's going on right now I typed in
giga Chad song and that was the first one I clicked on I actually I need you
to answer this and I'm gonna ask it until you I'm gonna ask until I get an
answer because you want to make fun of my favorite food no no I'm sure it's
delicious just what is it I honest to goodness let's play yes I was just on a
rant about how I'm sick of eating and I wish I could have flavorless pebbles
like that means you don't have a food you like to eat I like a lot of foods
but I really am at the point where I'm transcending the human form and just
want to be a ball of energy can somebody else answer this question I just want to
bring up a point hey what's your favorite food my favorite foods tuna he
just wrote huh I think that's an item for you that's like oh that is a fire
item nice okay well you obviously I had a thing that was gonna be really cool
and you blew it you like burgers though aren't you like Bert the burger guy you
like like burgers a lot I've been typecast and it was like all you like
it you have like five emotes that are burgers don't you I have a lot of
emails that are burgers but I've been typecast I ate a burger one time and the
Wall Street Journal will not leave me alone about it I think it's all that I
eat okay all right okay chili verde burritos are pretty good I had one
earlier all right thanks Josh so Josh I have a question for you if you opened up
the fridge and there was a chili verde burrito made by a professional chef and
it's like it's arguably the best quality you've ever seen in your entire life but
it is surrounded on all sides by tuna fish sandwiches in the fridge will you
is it are you so rude is it so disgusting to you will you reach in and
will you grab that burrito mom my food touch the ketchup I don't like the ketchup
or my mashed potatoes touch my pee no no they're all the same plate and they're
all wrapped under the same saran wrap like they're on the same plate wrapped
under the same saran wrap gross throw it away they're up there all under this
yeah I throw it away that's disgusting what whatever is under the saran wrap
in like a plate of tuna and you have like a burger in the middle it's gonna
taste like tuna okay I just was I was curious if that was like if it being in
like the same place was disgusting to you well they're gonna taste the same
nothing not I mean you can like burgers and you can like tuna but would you
like a burger that had like the scent and fragrance of like it's been sitting
in a saran wrapped tuna thing I'm just trying to get you to say you would you
would like eat or you I don't know I'm just trying to get you to talk to me I'm
talking to you but I just feel like I'm not saying what you want me to say it
means you didn't wrap it good enough I got some cool stuff and I want to look
at it let's get up to this bonfire up here we can also do this area and then
maybe get some some larval tears up here watch out there's a large doggy and not
the good kind I think it's a lot of help you know you fell off I fell I'm fine
remember why is your only talking point food why am I getting blamed for this
you're the one that brought up the nutrient pellets it's a pretty common
talking point for you haven't you done like it's here lists of like every kind
of food in existence I mean I've done some of that stuff you've done like the
cereal tier list and the fast food tearless Avenue I've done tearless on
things I like yes yeah yes would you be would you do the waifu tier list waifu
war to figure out who your waifu is waifu war yeah it's it's one of those
things where you choose there it gives you two images and you got to pick one
and it goes all the way down to the end round of 256 to figure out who your
waifu is I've just been 200 rounds on this yeah that's the only way to know
for sure oh what did you get I ended up having to pick the hell-taker main
character and Satan all right can I just say Ursula and we can move on Ursula
Ursula wasn't on my list it's a good pick I can't hit on Ursula unless she is
inside a Saran wrap of tuna big laugh by the way shut up wait has even faking
it this whole time I'm gonna I'm gonna push you all right make sure you get
your seal fucking speechless why it's my favorite NPC in the game German if I
ever came to like does it to visit you yeah and you were that old the legs
didn't work you're hiding in a bush pretending to be a pot I'd do the same
to you no no I fell I fake laughed again whatever I don't care coming wait am I
jumping off too I mean what else is up there besides I mean we could do the
little boss up there maybe I mean there is a little boss up there there is a
little boss but I'd have to go all the way around wouldn't okay yeah no it's
too late now yeah yeah we got bigger fish to fry doing it is pretty good on
the stove right watch out dragon I would say I pretty much recommend that there
goes talking about the food again you just killed that in one hit yeah all
right so where's our destination would you like anything in particular you
want to do I I'm feeling very strong I feel like we're following the same path
we did the first time though yeah like this would just take us back to the
glint stone Academy we do like like what's like a different way that we
didn't go last time we didn't really do anything underground last time really we
didn't do like knock wrong we didn't do the we did we also just kind of ran
through Caelan I feel like we could handle Caelan we could probably handle
as early as things are I feel like you know what let's like go back get a
bonfire take the road up to Caelan there's a church along the way I think
there's a reforged boss in that church really like not usually there but it
might be randomized shit out of me okay I was expecting more goofy mods um I
don't think they really exist for Elden Ring there aren't a lot first of all
there aren't a lot I was looking into some goofy mods and then um they're hard
to merge together yeah it's like the effort versus goofy reward and then it's
like one armor piece in the game is like that one's like Batman's armor then
we're randomized and we'll never find it and never even know it was there I mean
that would be kind of funny to be in like a Batman costume I thought it would
be funny you know you go to the roundtable hold and like the main guy
there is Batman like that'd be funny yeah but I already said Donald Duck that'd
be kind of funny um let's let's find closest bonfire oh that's actually
amazing that's one of the things that gets buffed if well we can't really do
it but I think that's one of the schools of magic that's buffed with warlock if
you play the actual reforged for real dragon at the dragon spot unless that's
a distant I remember it being fake is this one fake
seems wiki wheel well seems like it's going to die a lot of health I'm doing a
sneeze build right now yes sneeze on this guy I'm too short
I'm too short oh that I'm alive you are alive that one bigger fuck it's making
really cool looking stuff on the ground though watch out super bomb and here
comes this next attack super bomb oh no look out he's gonna do super bomb super
bomb hit him in his eyes dragons can't see without eyes stop doing that super
bomb watch out I have attacked him in like five minutes I don't I was gonna
say I don't think you have oh shit super bomb that's gonna kill me I'm done you
are dead feel like I feel like I was losing my dignity of running around and
avoiding the super bomb oh that hurts my eyes damn I'm back at the village of
Alba nerd you don't want to die right now I do so look I need to put it I go
getting stuck on his shit are you shitting they're hitting his eyes
quiet did you die no I'm doing I'm going you're back brother I've returned oh
fuck off fuck off I took it so long and I died you gotta be kidding me I can't
dude so bad I'm doing like 80 damage a swing because I do not lose to a super
bomb I will be so pissed at you if you do he's gonna do it stir oh my goodness I
ran around him for so long he just did that don't move and it's okay all right
did you start going back I'm reloading really am the village of the Alba
nerax oh my goodness I mean there is a bonfire next to them hold on no no no
please I need more mana I don't have that thing in my inventory right I might
have two of them two of them yeah cuz I died the first time in the second time
what it might have just cleansed I don't know I'm not gonna die if I jump from
here now but on the regen gloves yeah where are they be right which way come
on I'm getting stuck up here all right I'm gonna sit at this bonfire so don't
lose this again I am going are we aggroing this thing again that was
happening I don't want to fight it it has had it has like multi-screen AOE you
instant dead if you're in it it's boring it's I'm not bad it's boring
gotta believe me you did get hit by a super bomb though it did well let's get
hit by the super bomb or run away on the horse for like 10 minutes yeah that's
true I don't know what hit me all right where's this place right here let me
stop this first here I think you're gonna work to this bonfire though we
gotta fight it again let me just sit down I am I'm telling you to warp to me
now why aren't you right next to me you look right here okay I guess I will warp
to you the axe was doing more damage only than like 40 wasn't it okay I'm like
stuck on the map I could absolutely just run to you yeah cuz I needed to hand it
though it's gonna do less to hand it before you get on the horse does that
actually work hello do you have a stone sword key does work I I do you need two
for this I've got one and you've got one I put it I don't have one you you must
have one I'm gonna drop mine you can't drop them yeah you can I left didn't I
pick one what I swear now I got one so I'm sort of key yeah this needs two I
can't oh you can't okay so yeah you have to have to can't just put one in
dang it I really wanted to do that dungeon with my friend you already killed
the dragon are we yeah okay we can't give up does he only start doing the
screams and like phase two or something cuz he wasn't initially just play it
save look already it already like 10% okay he leans up like that he does the
big super bomb he's not doing anything what do you mean he didn't do anything
he like puts his head up like that we don't have a health bar anymore though
I do I was getting that bug a lot in our last run and then you get to him and
then he flies away yeah he's probably gonna do it he's not he's swinging down
yeah I think it's a phase two thing all right he's doing something weird I went
after you he's gonna bait it out then hmm okay there he goes back here okay
aggroing nice avoidance super bomb super bomb super bomb nice this dragon
opened his mouth I dead though huh-huh fine come over to me super bomb I started
right I was stuck under his wing and I died oh you died oh shit you got this
buddy super bomb who's he talking to super bomb super bomb coming in super
bomb you hit you they hit you dude sneeze on him sneeze sneeze run run run
super bomb I'm already out I'm commentating and going back in with a
couple more sneezes looking good looking good frost you melt in that frost a
little bit watch out for any additional attacks coming in here watch out do the
hitbox on this thing all right we're good don't lose it here
what fight him what do you mean standing here watching you don't want to do this
again I didn't want to rejoin and like discredit your win no it's totally get
by yourself no no the win is us it's us winning it's not me or you winning if I
and just keep surging it you got this you're not gonna even attack it come on
get it all right all right all right you got him can you play the giga Chad
music again for me okay get in there get in there get in there going him but it
flew away again I think just you think your CD is scratched if I die from this
I'm gonna be so bad everything's fine react growing you got this come on a
giga chat would have hit him again a giga Chad would stay alive got him I
actually got the last it you I got him I got last hit I got all the experience my
sword leveled up how can you didn't play at that time oh I missed the moment all
right we got money we got I got a dragon heart we can pick up the thing
right isn't it right here yeah oh yeah lots of stuff okay so now your question
is we should probably we have the key we don't need to come back down here yeah
so we do you want to try to do Caleb said you'd like to go through Caleb we
could do that um yeah up the that road just straight up into Caleb Saints
bridge follow the road I I feel you although can I let me put another spell
on I got a new one just empty the dishwasher dishes washing crazy Friday
quirky yolo lol love that for you hey all right I want a new spell this thing's
dumb this thing is cool enchants right-hand armament with blood flame or
what if I could enchant my right hand with blood flame let's try it I'm just
saying now cuz that looks pretty cool now you look cool man all right let's do
it the Caleb we go it's kind of stuck in your eye now you don't even know that
all night it's catchy it's real catchy this oh this is a boat guy let's get boat
guy little bonfire down here at boat guy millennia keeps talking to me over and
over again you keep saying the same thing that's part of reforge for some
reason there's an option for her to like always appear at the bonfire oh it's
you like her tibia o'neill it's a good name frenzied club I can't stop once it
starts I can't stop a lot of okay wait wait wait no stop stop stop stop stop
actually stop this scarlet rot here that's why I was trying to tell you okay
well I'm scarlet rotted so I'm gonna die dude I swear the hitbox is still
weird with the dodging I'm killing these archers I put on the frenzied flame of
ambition what's up oh they all spawned over there I've spawned on top of me I
have no health I'm scarlet yeah I'm dead too I'm dead too we have rock I should
not have died to that but then they spawned on me okay so he fills the whole
area with scarlet rot it's actually not that bad because we have all the items
that give like HP regeneration are countering a bit of the scarlet rot okay
ready I'm do we need to sit down or no I don't think so staying on the boys I'm
not go fight wait I my head feels what am I am I real what's going on nothing
I'm good I just had a moment yeah I should have just kept hitting him you're
wrong um okay when you hit him he takes damage and when it gets to the zero he
dies only 2400 or what is what that's it who the hell's this who actually is this
it's D is this D's brother D I've never seen him here I'm either I want that
that's what looks awesome I've never seen that weapon I've ever played tibia
no I have not that's not a game I think it's an old game there's an ulcer spirit
over here I'm gonna mess around we do it yeah I want to I want to fuck around and
find out scary must it's not just that that's there kind of scary thing did we
do it something else here okay good dear bird stop that was cool wasn't there
also be a way to go down I think you are correct I think you're right I
remember this one might have been one of the weird ones where there's like all
the way to go on like down like a weird hidden floor yeah is it that way is it
this one that's what I'm asking I don't know we need to find out stir you can
have fun with that dog you need help I think you know what I'm on it you know I
was gonna be I'm here already didn't hear already got it nice okay let's find
a way down um let's ago I think it's higher up on the hill hey dude have you
ever slipped a disc yes right here um there was a while where I thought that
the chest pain brought but I thought that was a disk problem but turns out it
probably isn't oh yeah there you go there you go never did but he thought he
did interesting room not this one not this one they had it coming
ooh that's kind of good turtle talisman I guess maybe not when it comes to the
random shit you can get in the Diablo 2 mod I'm sure that's something we have
on some way better potentially potentially all right we could go do the
bird tree the one that's in Caleb over here we should go to the church the
smoldering church go to the earth tree and then go to the Caleb ruins I think
that's the plan what do you think yeah no okay I'm with you you watch it mister
you watch it buster hey listen listen buster I'm gonna be putting up with this
much longer buster then you understand Jack I'm not your buster pal it's gone
on far enough it's gone on long enough buster anything here we can get oh no
it's first after Miriam no no she's got mad he got this well you know that
actually worked actually worked it freaks me out I didn't I was like what's
going on I was waiting to dodge the projectiles and they just kept
reappearing are you listen here buster that joke was funny the first five times
you made it I don't think it's funny anymore you understand Jack that's funny
from my perspective you didn't see what happened can't level up anymore I think
mmm I think she's gone oh I can't I'm stuck I tried to level up I tried to
level up and millennia kind of just sat down for a second and then left can you
like drag something over here to kill me um is that the play just yeah just
aggro something to kill me I don't I don't know if anything will leash that
far these guys want me to pull a while raid for some of the slowest moving
enemies in the game up here for something Miriam is back and they're
incredibly menacing no let them let them stay let them stay let them stay let's
let let's let this play out you took me out of my weird state I'm dead okay that
fix it what we can't hit each other I can't hit her yeah this is weird like
this is your duel man I won my duel okay she can't hit me I was just spamming one
move I'm trying to do my spells he's spamming yeah hey get nutrition pasted
yeah my one move my one little nutrition pellet it's all I need right it is nice
okay let's level up what what are you stuck yeah
hold on I'll go get something down I didn't even have any I got I guess I got
8,000 souls now hold on I'll get something will a sheep work I don't hold
on you there follow me oh I think they're gonna give up long before they
get to me I don't think they are oh shit got me you got me that fucking hurt
damn it this is kind of tricky okay I'm bringing somebody in to help okay yeah
no no no no no no come on keep going I don't think he wants to come in the
church he is here no don't do this now I think I alt f4 you know hold on I have
one opportunity I gotta get a force okay good luck it doesn't want it he doesn't
want to come whatever let me know when you want me to come back moving as fast
as I can I should upgrade the incantation thing I have because
everything's plus two right yeah just depending if you have the stone that you
need yeah I'm back that's really hoping you would sit down at that bonfire and
not be able to get up I've used I opened my world that bonfire is now off limits
all right I'm gonna 30 a cool uh let's go that way no you already go yeah I
thought I thought it was safe to jump from there yeah yeah a lot of people did
yeah all right um I spawned down here so I think I'm in trouble at the church
down where the ruins are oh what okay I'm coming down I did the statue I
figured it was closer hold on I can wrap around no I can come down please wait
well I need these hold your I have like 5,000 souls are here okay that makes a
lot of sense I hope I wish you the best in the new year thanks okay okay this is
all gonna be normal yep these are supposed to be here oh so we're going
down we're going into that they're a little deluring down there I would like
to what who knows what mysteries could lie beneath the ancient gravel walking
head legendary magic stuff avatar of the battle beast battle mage you gotta use
your stone sword you go first I'll light the way Justin hit a claim demo dark and
darker it's actually really good treasured poison cypher Pata wait a
minute that thing is pretty good isn't it 40 faith poison if that's on a menu do
you order it this is arcane I want I thought the scales with faith why is this
scaling with arcane I believe Diablo Mon does that oh I need 40 faith to use it
but it scales off of arcane it does not scale off of faith that kind of sucks oh
that's sad well cool weapon why are you going faith because I want to do the
frenzied fingers spells like we'll even get that far wait wait wait wait wait
a minute here I'm calling an audible you're calling an audible yeah where's
that frenzy tower like if you go along the right side of Lake of Leone area
there's the frenzied tower we can actually get some frenzy shit wait a
minute you're right is it that it's the highway lookout tower right it's one of
them if you I know that following that long right route is where you get like
spear and some other frenzy stuff where is it right here gosh darn minute that's
this one frenzy flaming tower so we go up this way we've got rapper on the
right side yeah let's get some frenzied flame it's Sunday sparkle on it's
actually supposed to be Wednesday for that but okay any day the one Sundays
any day the week works okay so I was right you corrected me then you
mansplained and then you said I was actually right well the original is
Wednesday okay what is actually here it's like the weird eyeball one where
you go like you out of your eye right what I think that's the one that's up
here the frenzy spell I think they're all along that right route there's the
one tower that gives you the grab one cut them out this is the wrong way we're
on the wrong way dude yeah yeah we have to actually go up this little thing up
here the first somber smithing stone they go fun don yeah we do have the
Academy keys well dong hey also right around here is the the smithing stone
mine I'd be down for that we could go we could go fill up on stones yeah I'm
gonna stone up we haven't done a stone up run ever I want to get stoned in here
let's go there a bonfire this is a bonfire down here isn't there yeah yeah
yeah I think I have that thing on it's real chill man I do yeah that's better
I feel like I'm never going to find something better than this club I kind
of feel you on that but I think this thing that I'm using is really not that
great so I still have room to go crystals that's crack I had a lot of
help now let's just like zoom zoom like in out grab the Duffy keep going got
him got him watch out bear when they group up like that the fire does a lot
now common sacred celebrants rib break okay strength lightning is this this
scales with faith but is this better than what I have right now I don't know
I'm gonna have to sit down and look at all this oh not right now later look at
all these there's so many of these talismans and they all kind of say the
same words yeah we need to like sell them all they're by worth a lot yeah
aren't she's on the mall it's made about a waste to come down here I didn't
realize it was like I love this area is higher level than smithing stone two and
three still not bad to have yes I want to fight the boss button that's all
right uncommon sacred battle hammer of the glint blade I saw how I heard sacred
30 strength come on strengthens glint blade sorceries by fit what a wacky item
it's just like I don't even need to I just that's wacky so that's a faith
weapon that boosts sorceries and is a big heavy blunt weapon interesting common
sacred iron cleaver same deal this one though be scaling I think it's not super
worth looking at anything that is a common rarity really because I think
this is like better than what I have common rarity for a weapon does 0.9
percent damage a mythical weapon does 2.4 times damage so they just
exponentially scale I see unless the mods are on a common or like insane I
guess and care like you know we need that good loot for the guild god did you
give me rot Wow that's a lot good yeah this is all going in guild stash don't
be able to upgrade every single weapon to plus three or four at least was five
plus ten the drama yeah the Diablo weapons go to plus two all of them like
every song oh okay all of you have like a mythical weapon then it requires high
level smithing stones to get to upgrade it but they're all okay I thought it was
and that is a plus two that's why I'm saying it's a little bit of a waste to
be getting these smithing stones because you'd want to upgrade a mythic ideally
and then you aren't really ever gonna use these here let me get them let me get
them let me get this guy okay I heard him once I don't want you to get all the
credit I'm gonna die why did I let you do that why did I let you do that
because I don't have I don't have any healing I had to commit oh come on you
can beat him I still feel like the dodge is off I really do I promise you the
dodge is still wrong I know the dodges is actually slightly different I think
they removed there is a like input delay normally an Elden Ring that they
removed so as such your dodge timings may actually be a little off from
normal Elden Ring this a serious yeah I am I'm not I wouldn't joke with you man
what I joke about that yeah something does still feel strange when I hit the
dodge button now whether that's I'm getting hit in the middle of dodging or
is it happening earlier yeah my brain is having trouble with it
hi bear god dude I can't go I'm stuck all right I'm good okay we're good that
is terrifying me it is very scary oh I know where they other the other frenzy
flame thing is in that small village up in the on the top of that one hill where
all the like frenzied rats are yeah oh yeah is the whole village there's a
whole like frenzied village mm-hmm and they're all insane and their heretics
and we need to kill them all and then continue their traditions I think we're
being chased okay round two wild strikes I'm just gonna keep going what if it
kills you again though we need your expertise you better help because it's
wild strike time okay what the fuck I'm really good no I'm telling you I think
the dodge is fucked I'm telling you it's not I sure I'm sure I'm sure that I
watched that happen did it to myself nearly on purpose and I'm very sad that
I did because it really what I don't want to be dead well we got it I got all
the items anyway I got a legendary something they're getting new I need to
like sit down you know what we need to sell all this crap I'm gonna confuse
myself let's go back to brother kale because in my brain like literally every
single one of these is like the same because I have to hit X to look at what
it actually does yeah yeah but in my brain I'm dead right now I can't do
anything so let's go to kale okay I know it's the gloves but it's just like we're
picking up so many things that I've just random stats on them that everything's
kind of gets lost okay um zero bonfire here somewhere isn't one right there's
one down the elevator and you should be you should be able to teleport without
going down there don't you have to vote for it yeah you're right he's right
again I mean when you have like 30 of these in your inventory it gets kind of
hard to differentiate between which one is what we definitely have to go sell
all these or most of them coming back mmm maybe some no I'll get endurance
sort by time picked up item type order of acquisition god okay we we fail in a
vote I'm just I'm just testing that out to see what it looks like we we failing
okay so who would you say is winning right now neither one of us I think
you're winning you know he's truly winning God and his servants what are
you buying here I'm selling that's what you wanted to sell things what do you
I've heard my weapons that I'm not gonna be using all right I'm gonna dump all
these talismans all right let's 2fp every I mean I don't I don't know if it's
worth holding on to some of these but whatever that's 1.7 fire damage dealt I'm
gonna just get rid of the ones that don't have three things on them right
let's holy damage or 3hp to one lightning damage one 3fp for three years
six is eight if forced it huh or seven's kind of good extra lightning
damage taken I think I'm just gonna get rid of anything that doesn't not
whatever I'm just gonna go for it I'll keep that just selling any basically
anything that's not equipped and I don't want to equip is gone unless it seems
really interesting we're a specific ask but these are only worth a hundred they
are but they're kind of just clogging up the inventory yeah keep that on 1.3.2
I'm not gonna put this on probably this one's kind of good I think all right
oh my god that's a lot of money I don't have enough god damn it it was 86 all
right 15 endurance is fine I'll keep that for now oh hey well then I came
plus to 3hp oh my god those are good holy shit 5fp every three and a half
seconds 3.2 seconds yeah we never even went south and crossed that bridge do
you still want to go back into a lid we should go south to the ailing village to
get you your frenzy fire yeah we kind of we kind of went that way and then we
decided to do something else and now we're I guess we're mm-hmm is that what
we're doing is that the plan yeah so let's go to gate front we got a long
yeah so I'm gonna need you to bring up a very engaging topic for the for the
journey okay dig down into your bag of tricks I am pressing it but it will not
go aw shucks aw shucks I don't think we can go we can cut across here I think
actually I think we can let's just go from here okay yeah you can I just
assume everywhere in Elden Ring is like a gigantic cave that will prevent you
from going anywhere or not cave cliff cliff a big valley yes it does end up
that way a lot of the places though oh I got a rare power bottoms Greaves ooh
let's just check on the map you know making sure we're good where are where
are we going here for the who's fighting who here oh it's a bear a bear
is fighting the dragon who wins 16 damage why could they not even hurting
each other wait what dead no he's not the various a fucking full hell oh wait I
thought it laid down like it was done they're not hurting each other like at
all yeah why not that Deckard Kane well they'll figure it out what what enemies
are even normally hear that fight each other I don't remember he just yelled at
somebody yelled at a crab down there okay why yeah why only doing like 30
damage 10 damage three that's weird the creatures here used to be so peaceful
Jesus he was carrying a box he might have had money on him I had to put him
down was there a summer jail here it might be there is summer jail let's go
all right I'll take I'll flank all right I'll do wild strikes okay I'll do wild
strikes I even I even took damage in the dodge that was I've never seen that
before oh no no no no okay oh no no no he just made that move up no no no using
wild strike wild strikes how's that not hurting you I have a lot of health
virgin per second and I don't know why but my armor has been really high that I
just have been able to like wild strike and take the hits come on I thought I
would I would stagger him out of it because he's a little assassin baby boy
I'm sure I can yeah let's go I need to go over to where you are we buffed
myself too what the what no there's no way he jumps I'm talking about dodging
oh I would have died if that was on me I'm wild striking huh hey you got this
I have no shield with Harry's you're gonna have to kill this thing just be
wild strike Andy no they should just keep standing idiot you had me jump oh
gosh oh my goodness what the fuck is this game talking about I just want to
hit you friend please kill it please kill it sir kill it to end this oh thank
God what a great rare rate winged great horn nice job yeah great job everyone e
faith scaling what do you talk come on every every faith weapon I found is like
oh scales off a fucking dicks I'm finding a lot of end weapons but I would
love to be an eboy where are you I was looking at stuff all right
whoosh careful don't fall oh oh I still love the idea of the crab using that
blue sauna another stone sword keep we need it
oh can we make a short little detour and get the best item in the game which one
the turtle shield if that is your heart's desire let's do it I think it's
up here on the left on like one of those towers either that or we just passed it
it's either up here or we just passed it one of those two it's up here okay it's
up here frenzied flame the village of the fire didn't take this thing we
should take it I don't need it you don't want to miss a bonfire it but it was
replaced yeah oh no yeah it was replaced okay that's real sad oh your special
turtle shield I'm sorry yeah I mean it was like a rare item I don't know if you
wanted to go up there and check it it's like up in here right it's in the tower
you can you can use the air jump to go straight into the tower oh you can't
go do that yeah maybe it'll be rare where I got a where now gonada where
trousers and a warming stone not that great we're gonna go to the frenzied
flame village no I like how Jerma's run really leaves it puts his heart on his
sleeve I think I totally agree dead guy yellow ember it's getting frenzy out
here getting a little bit frenzy beware of danger don't cut yourself is there
anything else you want to get down here or do you want to like go up to the
frenzy other friends in place I'm just trying to get my boy frenzied up that's
really all I'm doing I think it's in here amongst the dogs this is a job for
wild strike I'm fucking dead dude I couldn't even get off my horse before
you frenzy fucking wild strike that thing and I died by electricity uh is
America's statue closer is a bonfire closer uh bye America because it's a
twitch flame of frenzy got it did you get it I got it it's mine can't have it
and a sacred tear and an ancestral furious furious fingerprint helm of the
summoner give me give me give me give me give me give me give me that shit put
it on oh my god you see that no I was looking at items I need a bonfire to
put it on jump but you think you're smarter than me you think you're smarter
than me oh bonfire all right let me look at this do I have enough memory spell
things okay verse of yellow flame of frenzy from eyes yep oh I get it your
name is my eyes you just figured it out now yes it's funny earlier when you said
that that's what like got me to make us go do this you're like oh if we play the
game long enough for me to get the frenzy skills dude they're in the
beginning of the game well one of them is all right I have let me put on this
thing is too good to take off though isn't it ten percent frenzy flame
versus God three HP every second mmm yeah sure all right I'm now a frenzied
flame is it gonna be fun 89 the spear too but the spear needs something else
right I need 20 I need a bunch of decks to put this on or a lot more strength
I'm okay with my spells I'm okay I feel totally fine I feel very strong actually
I swear there's a place you can jump down here um then I also don't swear this
is the part of the game where it started to be like cliff hell this place is
cliff hell every time I'm like oh I have to like go down to that like Western
area down here in the the island place and then I how do you get to that bridge
because you can see it from like 30 different cliffs I mean relax I'm about
to just start spitting you want to go to Caleb instead come here not come here
come here come here listen to me come here listen to me come here where are
you I drop down okay oh you did find out this is the right way oh you just said
Simon Says jump and follow me and I just did it oh you think you're smarter than
me I know you can get down there though and there's a cave okay there they are
all right where are you are you still adamant on my souls at the same spot oh
no I know how you get down here I'm I'm I'm dead again I'm dead build you want
to spawn you I'm gonna be at the bonfire and I'm gonna show you one simple trick
how to travel through Lear and Leah I'm following you here's the one precise
spot that you should go down these cliffs thank God thank God I just did
that I would have you would have heard me scream I would have been like you do
sound like that when you're mad this thing's actually kind of cool
the French heat fire don't fuck with me that's a real epic of you sure you know
what you're doing easy okay cave let's go do you want to go in the cave do you
want to cave yes I think I remember this cave being scaly that one cave we're
like there's there's two of the worst bosses in the game there's like an
invisible necromancer and then something just as bad and also it's very very dark
are we scaly I don't know we didn't buy any lanterns or anything that was
probably pretty pretty bad idea I've got a torch yeah torches on a lathe to
equip it like yeah that's like that's way more like immersive annoying watch out
wizard well you know what I'm gonna be doing the rest of the entire time we
watch out wizard don't worry I have madness you're really just gonna stand
up here and piss on all them oh shit something's wrong with me all right you
can't do that that many on it all right right right oh look out lightning wizard
ooh there's a wizard there I'm fine I keep hearing your guys scream I don't go
too far into the madness you will never return that oh yeah what was that what
a FP every two seconds I mean that's kind of insane that is an ah-ooh if you
ask me that's better than 10% more damage I think yeah I'd take that Wow I
apologize stir in advance this character's gonna be very annoying I like
it I already love it it felt like my character all last run was constantly
screaming every time they got hurt just Arnold okay what do we got I don't know
I'm opening it as fast as I can help help I don't know what it could be we're
gonna die we're dead imagine knowing this enemy's move set you gotta be
shitting me spit me out and I'm in man it's just for real life what are you
saying dude that was pretty frenzy that was pretty how that was pretty frenzy I
got a bunch of items I think yeah it just keeps giving us things like come on
it's frenzy this frenzy stuff lightning holy or fire damage what actual damage
is it I don't know it's all fire okay I have pants that heals others but not the
wearer doesn't say how much you have missing health I'm gonna stand near you
with my pants on I just put on some regen oh like I guess I guess we
wouldn't be able to know where how much I'm healing you doesn't seem like a lot
either way it's not a whole lot but hey it's still something then yeah I'm just
gonna go back to where my power bottoms all right that was an eventful cave
actually pretty it was and then I believe like straight this way is the
the demigod boss who is not a real boss but actually a loser would you say they
were on the scale of cool to dork where would they be demi boss they would not
be at my lunch table if you know what I'm saying unless they want it to I
really wouldn't mind but I don't think that they would initiate that
conversation you know what I'm saying spring and you know the jumpy here I
don't I don't think so there's a weird jumpy there's a weird jumpy over here
where I am the only way you can get in here is with a jumpy I made it you got a
cave down here oh there's usually a good there's like every once in a while the
Diablo loot overrides what would normally be like a cool item that's
funny there's like a it's like a spike punch shield okay and I think it's neat
okay we said sir you're just saying words a lot of them that form a sentence
hold on let me just go ahead and fucking frenzy this well let me friends but let
me I got grab I'm getting grabbed out here let me frenzy this it's hard to
tell what's even happening I think we're good I think we're good because we got
the item cool very nice sorry stir we used to just weird noises around here
I got I got what did you hear that guys I got what he meant by that whoa whoa are
you kidding me don't you fucking idiot asshole why would you what I cannot
fucking believe you just said that I'm sorry
ridiculous you'll get the twit longer once we're done oh no I wish we got
hey man want to adventure into this cave I would love to after this let's go to
Caleb all right that was the goal like hours ago it was unless you want to get
your other frenzied flame stuff which is not oh yes this game he's a fucking
idiot are you coming down here I need to change my flasks dying I need to choose
my flasks my flasks have to be changed oh a chest here
whoa frenzy flame frenzy flame more like friendly fire cuz you shot me what's
wrong with us today I think I don't know I think we're really still raw about the
whole pebbles conversation you think ooh presser trotteries Queens this too many
words there there just is you know and you know what I'm talking about that's
the thing right I do know what you're talking about or you're like streamed a
while and your words become like like I don't know ten out of ten drunk but it's
like we can't say a sentence but it's not just a sentence it's like it's like
ten it's like six to seven words in a string that have no real connection to
each other he fell in oh so you yeah we got to keep going down that's why I like
type racer stuff is harder because you know the words like they don't flow
together like what it what is what is it yeah me gods restorative traveling
maiden gloves it's like it's a lot of random words I'm right there with you
can you frenzy flame this thing yep it's like the text for the items here are
tongue twisters all of them they are they're really long they really don't
make any sense there's no way to speak the English language I've tried I wonder
what attack you're gonna do that one I wonder what I'm gonna do such a boring
playthrough this is just you and I are both gonna do the same one move oh my
god oh damn oh shit what's that oh treasured mad tongues chain leggings of
fury holy damage but you can roll into enemies and hurt them yeah I've seen a
couple items with that pretty sick I'm gonna try it sounds funny I've got my
second moon veil very cool not gonna use it trying to do some strength stuff can
only find this club all right do you want to go to very Lucario do you want
to do a lid what's what um there's the other tower where you can get the
madness grab let's set you up man you want to set me up you you deserve it
you're one of the good ones thank you I guess these hoes ain't loyal all right
where we gone back to the where we were trying to go before frenzy I'm trying
tower to remember frenzied flame village up here I don't know if you see my
markers I know where it is yeah it's like part of this whole tower and and we
have the crystal tunnel there but I think we have to go all the way from
back here you can go up the middle of like from the lake but we haven't got
any good waypoints from we were trying to cross the whole lake earlier here
here here here here we here I know I know we're going it's just a long trek
all right remember my game takes slightly longer than newest to load yeah
I know I wait for you every single time with my overflowing vessel of great
patience of the fourth born can you say that five times fast I don't even
remember what I just said I really am just saying words they all they're right
about me and I'm also gonna stop saying hey there's a thing we can go in right
here I'm just we're just gonna go you know um we can't get to it from this way
we got to go into the lake again trust yeah you have to go through the middle
right yeah cuz then there's one of those uh there's one of those cliffs that you
know just just the world hey you got to go from the middle don't you think the
earth would be better off if it was perfectly flat oh and I'm not saying
like flatter a theory I'm saying like it's a round planet still but it is it
is perfectly flat no mountains no hills no rivers well gravity exists so it
doesn't really matter so I mean like you know wait you mean like every dome you
mean literal flat like the whole thing is flat everything yeah yeah so you just
want like the Great Plains across the entire world yes yes um so you're
talking about you want the roller coaster tycoon default grass yes all
right um I want I want default grass map from the tutorial level of like that
game just no just everything is exactly just green I I feel like this probably
reasons why it would be bad but but here's the trade-off it's like a dwarven
ecosystem underground where these massive caverns and these oars we've
never heard of that can let the elves live forever but we won't let them have
them but they get them the world above is flat but because that's all flat we
can't have rivers so obviously we wouldn't have water to like anything I
feel like I just skipped ten minutes forward in a YouTube video like you're
just something else completely going on all right uh let's do it what was he
cooking the great question
could have just said no the end like a valid answer was just no I don't think
that would be better but no one wants to like speak up conflict-averse how windy
would it get I feel like if it was all just roller coaster tycoon grass wouldn't
it be I don't know question would it we would change the dynamic of all of our
meteor a lot of wind come from like the the melting of the ocean I feel like
you know ocean melts into the clouds and if there was no water on the surface
because it's all flat then the ocean wouldn't be melting so true yeah I've
been a lot of question marks okay so if ice melts into water and then water can
change into gas behind you call that melting why can't water melt into gas
um water blame the flame cleans me in there if you care you probably don't
care oh that hurt well I thought that was you hitting me from behind me all
right stop please I get this guy has been in the same animation the whole time
and he's just wild striking I don't know he's just doing wild strike whatever he
was doing this thing's one hit can you just like fucking go crazy oh thank God
it evaporates like vapor doesn't freeze into water it condenses there you go
there's your answer it condenses and that guy's not like you're not no one's
doing question marks to that guy well that's baked with real science not
nutrient pellet science that you're using when's the last time you open like
a science book don't you think just like feeling from your gut like how the heart
feels is enough do you really even need to know like oh I need to like read a
biology book to understand how my body were you just kind of like you sit on
the toilet shit happens you don't need to know the mechanics of the world to
understand that water can melt well okay water can evaporate okay and then why
why does the word melt it turns into here because melting implies melting
implies okay correct me if I'm wrong melting implies a heat source does it
not well if it gets hot enough out the water melts like melting doesn't that
mean like it needs to melt there is heat involved early melting is from solid to
liquid melting implies liquidification does it imply that or are you like
expecting that it can only mean that I think you're fighting semantics right
now in education guys don't blame any I'm a dropout I dropped out of high
school this is not an ace ball do my brain is melting listening to you oh but
he can say that and I can't say water melts just hurt the turtle I jumped on
him and it turns the turn on him I just tried to stand on him I stir if there's
one person I have ever heard of that would ever hit the turtle it's you I
didn't hit him I tried to be on his back yep like imagine you're a small child
didn't you ever want to like ride a big dog I'm busy yeah stir the type of guy
to r1 r1 r1 the turtle and then be like actually wild strike is just hold l2 for
me it's a lot simpler than r1 r1 r1 I can't handle that many button presses
stir the type of guy to hold l2 on the turtle okay you didn't even talk to the
turtles I I don't need sorceries alright let's go fight something let's
go fight let's go fight like regular karya or you know what we're doing right
now and why we're doing it yes I but I know we're doing the frenzied flame
village do you know how close we are and how far we traveled to get here for you
but you keep pausing and talking about sauce I'm not we've been traveling the
whole time you've been saucing I just need to look at the map and you're
fighting all these guys there's the item here got violet okay any any any map
I would like to look oh that's sad that dog has a collar okay so yeah it's the
tower there's a village we got to go down this hill I don't know who came up
this hill the melting conversation you had is why America isn't top 10 in stem
I haven't been in a classroom in like 15 years wait top 10 in stem there's like
not even there's barely more than 10 countries guys when you get to be over
30 you stop giving a shit about what melting versus condensation you give a
shit about fucking taxes all right got a fucking lawn to take care of shit I
think my game crashed oh true no way dude every time you turn on the news
it's all China this Russia that trying to this Russia that USA you there's like
three countries something something in the fucking water today something in the
sauce today what name another one Canada Mexico I mean come on all right
Finland um Switzerland Sweden and a little like a show-off scholar here you
want to play GeoGuessr again wait I'm not done Germany France England who should
I you want you want more should I go shake it gone unless you want to play
GeoGuessr again Ecuador my world is open to wanderers Egypt what ranking is
Egypt in stem no they were talking about stem cells right where I can like
like how many years before I can have gills sir I gotta tell you I know this
has been like a jokey conversation we were just like pretending that we don't
actually know this stuff but you have to understand that there are chatters that
are going to hear you say that and they're gonna they're gonna think even
less of us oh I'm well aware I am totally and completely aware and I you
know I had an awakening I shouldn't even say more you know what I shouldn't
say more I don't know if I want to hear about the awakening I'm not sure about
that I don't know if I want to hear about the awakening tell us all I'll
say about the awakening is and that some people are the I don't hear about the
awakening I don't want to hear about the awakening I think it's too much eyes
too much I feel like this is the kind of shit you're gonna start talking about
fucking like crystals and gems and you're gonna start talking about like
fucking earth being flat your alarms are going off because you're like
something this motherfucker won't even say I don't want to hear about the
awakening all right fair enough all right how about this you DM me what like
one sentence of what the awakening is it's not that bad if I like leave out
the important parts all right tell me like we could have we can talk about it
later but like to it wouldn't make sense the full context is required of which
you would not have there is awakening I went like down I was concerned about
your awakening so I went down here it's I don't know why we called it an
awakening it's not an awakening I forgot it's hard to even relate to what the
original conversation was because I can't remember what we were talking about
talking about how many countries you can name no like after that um about all
people thinking that we're thinking we're done right like oh they're dumb
they don't know anything about condensation yeah that that was where we
left that and then you said I had an awakening and I don't know if I can
even say it on stream the short version is which is fine is that when I stream
with you huh I never get Twitter DMs but when I stream with you afterwards
sometimes I get a few that are like can you not talk about that ever again wait
for like from people you know or from like no no no no like random people
that I like long messages about like why what I said was actually like there
did you know like I could imagine getting one like it was kind of really
saddening to hear you say there was only ten countries because actually I'm from
one that isn't one of those ten and I really felt like I was personally so so
you're so your concern is you're here on like on like a comedy stream and you're
afraid that you're gonna get DMs where people think that you're actually mean
the thing you say on the comedy stream well it's kind of what you were saying
is that people will think we're that dumb and I don't know why also I don't
know why I called that an awakening yeah that to me you were talking okay you
let's let's go over some very factual information we you first of all you were
like I don't even know if I want to talk about this on stream and that was like
transitioning out of like like yeah wouldn't be better if the earth was flat
you know like you don't have any turbo and I'm just like yeah what do you mean
but and then you know what I had an awakening recently let me tell you all
about it what was it there's a longer there's a longer awakening I just you
know that's but too long didn't read that's all you need to know okay and
first of all I what is why do you have Twitter DMS open open what why don't you
why would you have Twitter DMS open for any Twitter user to just DM your ass
why not stir I I'm telling you right now you just told like tens of thousands of
people that you have open DMS on Twitter like what like what is the worst thing
please do not I fucking go oh my god man like do you just not interact with your
fans no okay I thought there would be more new watch out for the big hand big
hand it's up on that hill up here but I don't think you can actually get up on
that hill unless you come from the other direction because this is where it's
hill hill cliff hell when you look at the map so yeah where were you want to
go to Caleb yes now I don't really use Twitter don't use discord because here's
the thing let's do you want to let's just be real you want to be real for a
second if you have if I have Twitter DMS open and somebody DMS me and I just don't
if I just ignore it because I mean like look let's be realistic it's possible
that and that I was thinking the stand angle thousands of them could come in in
a week or a month period I'm telling you right now I'm not gonna read them I'm
not gonna read them all I'm just not going to and if somebody sends like a
bunch of text to something right you let's say you brought like two or three
paragraphs like a Twitter DM and I just don't even open it because it's just
overwhelming this too much then you spent the time to write to me and I just
didn't even respond there you go okay I don't want to I don't want to interact I
mean how many people just wrote to you in your chat that you didn't respond to
just now while you were saying that that's difference there's a character
limit is there you can write some pretty long I guess remove I guess remove my
nightbot TLDR it can be pretty overwhelming and I I prefer to not do it
TLDR mm-hmm why did you open this I don't know we were just up here and we
can't really get to where we were trying to go to so I think we probably do need
to like leave unless we you are you are with time you are just going on my
screen I oh I'm sitting in place that happens a lot around these altars
actually is where we've had a lot of the desync it does seem to happen here okay
do you want to just pick a place to reset us um yep we are going into the
moldering church do not touch this bonfire let's do you get random DMS
from random strangers I don't to me that's just like oh hey let me open up
my Twitter DMS oh that's a picture of somebody giving a double my finger and
their asshole okay that's cool I don't think people consciously thinking of
stir and being like you know what I'm gonna interact with stir that has never
been a problem and I don't think like maybe they're like oh because I said
like oh I saw them stream like for one day it'll be a problem then it will go
back to like you know I'm just like alone in my basement lights off
boundaries Bob yeah you got I accept them before with you guys come on don't
act like we haven't whoo it's putrid theodoric's not keep going through cave
yeah keep going cuz that didn't even hurt I mean my weapon is still I didn't
never gave it plus levels I think like we starting we were starting to hit
some things that oh my god scale on us yeah we probably should upgrade after
this you don't want to interact with random people no I really don't that
make me a bad person no it makes me somebody that is set hold on counter to
that mm-hmm you used to do like like packs East meetup I can't I can't do a
meetup that's different though or the very opposite ends of the spectrum
there I think that's different though I mean we're all there for that purpose of
like kind of being in the same place bunch of gamers bunch of streamers are
there a bunch of youtubers bunch of people that to me that's different like
I'm going to like a twitchcon or a packs East to go that I can all hang out and
talk to everybody that's like the point you know let these let these flames fly
frenzy these fucks pretty good I'll cover you it's just running by me that's
oh my god this whole hallways full why is there a wild time were you just
surprised at what type of enemy was in this total randomizer where every enemy
is random you said is that a bear like you were shocked I feel like we've seen
a lot of bears we have seen we've seen a few bears is that dead is brought yeah
this is building oh cuz I've rolled I'm an idiot I keep forgetting that do I
even have any of those things no why would we have one of those okay where we
go from here we've can I touch the thing I have rock yeah yeah I don't know where
you go from there they're like one of these walls must be was different
you want well asking what's the difference between randomizers this
randomizer is like kind of doubly weirdly randomized because we have
Diablo 2 loot and it's a lot of it and then we have this is all it's all
different we're more likely to get weirder bosses and in boss rooms and
the items have a lot of bonus extra weird stats coming back I am for you I
touched the thing because I was brought in but I like here oh well you go
underneath this someone shoot me you let this go up come off you go under so it's
not different at all I just we have Diablo 2 random loot what do you mean
like look at all this shit this is all like random shit and we have Elden Ring
reforged but we can't do this the actual classes so that's unfortunate I brought
us here to the scarlet rock cave all good hold on this at this Caleb trip has
been really I fucking did the dodge again we did like six circles to get to
Caleb by now we're in Caleb I'm not the place that I want to be in Caleb now we
got this the lever where do you want to be in Caleb I want to be in the place
where we can get some cool items whereas this one I have no idea uh can you just
go find it okay can you start a conversation sure so what was last time
you had it hmm does your jaw does your jaw click when you open it yes it does
how how far open does your mouth have to be before it clicks like mine's about
30 40 percent pretty much um I don't know I'm doing it now I don't know
happens it like weird spots sometimes it feels like it does it more than others I
remember I had like a long conversation with someone about this at one point
because Ashley sister is a dental surgeon and then I don't know I can't
remember what I learned that conversation started and stopped
instantly you know I know somebody that's a dental surgeon and I don't
remember anything I'm sorry I don't remember the whole thing like I feel
like I should be able to have more input on this conversation but honestly I
don't that just well you know what respect to you for acknowledging that
you don't know and not just kind of making up something you might half know
right I don't do that I could just talk just out here playing the game looking
for the lever for my I said I want to get the rod I had it I was already
built up he went on my website and bought a carry I'm looking like yeah
fine I'll do another carry for you on your Elden ring streams I'm looking I
found it I found it you didn't even find it I found it did you maybe oh and that
giant pile of enemies I ignored them oh god cool you found it cool um you find
it I was just giving you shit but then yeah I came up here and I didn't see it
up here and then that drops back down to where we were and it's like man what was
the point isn't something like in a weird spot I think so I think maybe you
can also go up on that I don't dude I don't know I remember hating this cave
because scarlet rot and they just need to make you hate yourself when you come
in here I thought you were ending your stream I thought you said I I thought
you said I gotta sleep I gotta sleep it's like oh my god I'm gonna be up at
4 a.m. tomorrow off something incredibly important I gotta sleep oh shit all
right then God you yeah take care he's gone he didn't say goodbye he just left
like if you miss this appointment tomorrow at 4 in the morning with three
gotta be up 4 a.m. yeah the doctors off it at 4 a.m. we're we're all booked up
but if you can come in at 4 a.m. still waiting for this door to open dude I
have no idea wait wait wait wait wait wait wait I'm remembering I thought you
played this game haven't you beaten this game before why don't you know this
doesn't come back down so we do we do have to do a loop oh oh oh oh I'm gonna
get scarlet rot you can just go wait at that door I'm just already following you
we got some marinara sauce on our boots some pesh penny pesto I don't know um I
think this is a like the Satanists at from software made this one and I think
there's an like an invisible wall right at the beginning the Satanists yeah like
every single time like a gamer gets aggravated and you like fuck millennia
fucking fucking a millennia like that energy exits your soul goes through the
game through the cords of the internet goes into Miyazaki they're all plugged
into him and he's like in his chamber oh yes oh yeah but it is like they breathe
it out of like a cone or something yeah like it's like that drop under the
elevator people are saying I think that's correct we did that we did do
that oh hey I found it you didn't see this it's right here there's no enemies
here there's no we haven't been here haven't seen that how did you not see
that bro I walked in here and I saw it immediately how did you I don't know
how you didn't see them Satanists well that's how they get you oh you Satan was
an angel himself and then you're in and they got you then we have to drop down
to get back to the door yeah did you drop yeah making sure all right you
ready to kill this boss in ten seconds ready I'm ready to kill this boss with
wild strike while you go should be fun how is this already dead I don't like
that tone that you had nice okay that is a lot legendary graven witches
clean-rod helm of what well I got the same one as you like exactly
intelligence are dying that's a lot of stats it's a lot but I don't really want
it we need it that's what I'm saying like a lot of stuff I'm getting is in
arc mind all this stuff that I don't want like where's the big boy smasher
all right we could keep going to the the thing at the archery was insane we
should probably upgrade our stuff don't you think I don't know what we need to
upgrade you want to run to I would like to run to the blacksmith guy again I
would like to upgrade the frenzy flame thing like it's pretty much the thing
I'm using warpo or we got to get to EG didn't work okay then we got to go fight
this giant salamander that takes no damage I vigor damn yeah you actually
want to fight this well I mean otherwise otherwise I just hear you I'm dead
already nevermind okay this thing has like a million health I don't think that
yeah we're not gonna kill us yeah no way I got you actually I'm gonna level up
yeah fire is bad on it yeah I can't level up because I died I got it sorry
don't we I you want to go get some ice cream let's do um we could just run to
the southern part EG to upgrade you wanted to upgrade I do yeah Ray LaCarr is
the the way to go but we don't have to do that I play five nights at Freddy's
to stir have you ever played five minutes of Freddy's no can we do a
stream where I just watch you I just stream you playing five minutes at
Freddy's we just kind of hang out sure all right cool it's an odd request but I
do it like I just get a bunch of snacks and shit and like and you just play and
we just watch you play I have never watched anyone play I like don't get it
I 100% don't understand five nights at Freddy's or like so I guess it'd be like
the raw the raw deal yeah is there a preference for like what's the good one
is there a VR ones good the VR one actually was pretty fun and what I played
of it but five nights at Freddy's 2 I think is probably the staple that's I
think the the apex of the series for a lot of people raw and then I'll just be
chatting I was laughing you and you get jump what's what's the dumbest game
you've ever gotten like scared while playing like the most scared you've been
but also like you really shouldn't have been scorned there was like there was
like three or four okay so in scorn this weapon container comes out of the ground
and I was not prepared for it and I screamed and it hurt my whole body I did
not expect it to be so recent or yeah now mine is a quake 4 hmm the quake 4
single-player there's a really dark area and I it it took me about an hour to
walk through slowly at the end of this level and if you like know the layout of
what you're doing it's it should take you about 30 seconds I'm kind of a jumpy
person though like I would say so even things that aren't supposed to jump scare
me they kind of do if they're quick I mean when quake 4 came out I was like 13
years old all right can I upgrade this who he sells cool stuff there we go all
right boom boom what did that do 172 scaling now on this thing nice do you
have a smithing stone 5 regular I do not I only have 4 yeah that's what my club
needs well I am gonna level up yeah plus 2 is the max on the mod yep can I turn
him off for a second me I'm gonna can I sit at the grace yeah 10,400 yet yet can
I have a do any crunchies I need 400 I feel like this happens a lot to you
they're constantly taking my crunchies well if you have extra crunchies then
you should be sharing them I need a level so I can equip some stuff all right now
I'm gonna be doing disgusting damage please don't accidentally shoot him you
take just a quick look some of the stuff I think might scale with faith whoa it's
to faith a faith scaling 35 strength but the only thing I have that scales us
eight yeah this is a one-hander though right no is it not anything can be a
one-hander it's true I think that's the only good thing I have for faith I think
the strength that's pretty damn good like I said a one-hander but well okay
well our last playthrough I did a big slow two-hander under that again yeah
but you weren't casting magic yeah but I wanted to be like I want to be a
predominantly spell caster oh follow me this is exciting we split that where
you're going we split that really well I mean we're going to carry a manner no
wait actually exciting I don't know where I'm going and you're gonna leave
the way yep it could be literally anywhere this whole wide open world yeah
can you frenzy this sure can easy that frost dump where are you taking me on a
date where are we going somewhere special I need to look at the map and
they won't let me look at the map I think it's this way hmm it's Applebee's
oh I love the riblets I know this should lead us to the the frenzied village where
you can get your your frenzy on I think I'm wrong no no no no I'm not it's a
long annoying path this is correct though I don't remember the last time I've
eaten an Applebee's like it's been a very very long time it's been a long
time yeah been a long time for me I think we go up here to the right then we
wrap around then we're up on the high ground it's just bears that just bears
everywhere Wow but bear seed Wow another bear are you serious there's more bears
there are a lot what is the staple at Applebee's what is the actual Applebee's
staple oh my fucking god don't please oh my god I got fucking killed by the bear
apparently enough enough bears dude just the stake of America I think it's
probably closer I don't know I don't know probably kind of forgetting I won't
let me look at the map so what's okay Applebee's Chili's Fridays what's
another that that tier of sit-down restaurant what's the best what's the
best what's the best one of those definitively which one is the best
Chili's whichever one's closest true they're all about the same I just remember
I remember being in a Friday's like one time not like I mean Fridays are all
right but I'd rather it be a Saturday the Olive Garden is the Olive Garden on
that tier it is right yeah for sure I would probably say Olive Garden gonna
say like red lobster and all that I don't remember this item actually is in
here this is a place well we'll find it eventually much over the gigantic axe
oh my face I just did a German scream I just I wanted to get this item because
it might be the frenzy fire all right I got the frenzy cookbook this crab I miss
I miss having wild strike already in God why do you have to be here I just want
to get the mask leave me alone why nothing to do with you such carnage okay
there is a giant over his still and I want to find the other frenzy spell I
think it's uh I think there is more up this hill there's like a chest yeah
Olive Garden I feel like Olive Garden is kind of a meme and people shit on it oh
Olive Garden oh yeah of course Olive Garden no don't forget the breadsticks
no but seriously don't they're good that's a that's a great thing to do soup
salad breadsticks actually is fucking pretty legit you're not gonna hear me
talking shit about soup salad breadsticks you're just not there there
balanced based even now the last time I ate at the Olive Garden it's been an
uncountable amount of years I don't I don't remember I am doesn't mean I
wouldn't because it's the closest there's a there's a Chili's near here I
mean I'm on team Chili's just again whatever's the closest what just
happened to me wait you died oh there was there was an invader here I died in
one hit yeah he's definitely is something off with the fucking roll I'm
telling you I'm not crazy yeah that was funny though cuz you went yeah it was
almost a song yeah like like normally in between those you'd be able to roll
that those are not like perfect roll catching doomsday swing I I just yeah
um there's something wrong it's been wrong the whole game I think it lets
you roll a little bit earlier out of hitstun because it buffers it differently
yeah but then actually you rolling earlier is like I do I don't know
something there I would do remember reading the change lock yeah it's not my
fault it's Jerma's fault I yeah yeah that's what your character did and then
you died I we need to work up there I don't know what where you are I'm
standing right on top of it oh I it respawned me somewhere else because I
don't know why oh I need to warp I can everyone's talking about vibes because
they're just all messed up right now you got a problem with the vibes do I do
something it's me isn't it are you where are you I'm traveling down from the
church and we just tell on vibes a funky right now inquisitor whatever that
inquisitor is here we need to kill we have to kill this inquisitor yeah I'm
with you oh we're good vibes are back vibes are good I need to sit down at the
bonfire because I have like I have no HP okay let's continue so what did you get
from the town I didn't finish looting it I got a frenzied cookbook but there's
more stuff down there that I think I want to get I think to our left over
here hold up before we go back down yeah this is the tower this is I know this
something at the top of the tower and it makes you go the top of the tower is the
grab let's get it I think you might have to come yeah do not oh okay I don't know
what I was doing I don't know what I was thinking I just like saw it and I
thought I don't know you've been jumping around all game and I was like oh you
wouldn't probably jump I don't know you've been jumping around all game
then I'm like oh he probably is gonna jump with me I don't know nobody saw
that from Vinny's stream that's fair and valid that I made you do it because I'm
smarter than you welcome everybody from vine sauce what's up playing some Eldon
ring co-op randomizer with Diablo 2 loot and some of reforged it's a little
messy but we are getting through it I mean what's a bowl of spaghetti if it's
not all over your shirt okay we I almost died again you're following me don't we
want to go up to the top of the tower no I mean no you're following me I am
you choose where to go it's off a cliff but thanks to the raid welcome everybody
vibes are back vibes restored okay get on your horsey this is not affecting me
at all it will when you get closer why do I feel like when I played before it
was very very far away it was just line of sight that's okay so that's weird I
remember being much much much I think there's a way worse angle you can come
at it from okay you climb I look at ancestral loot excuse me there's somebody
coming down the ladder what I'm coming somebody coming down the ladder all
right me me I'm ladder you missed the chest I'm killing these things first
god damn it no yeah I forgot it's it's not just an easy enemy it's like this
fucking thing up whatever the hell it's like rats and bugs all right I I thought
it was gonna be like the default shitty enemies but it's like a bunch of rats
and it's a huge flower these vibes are are way off I was like oh yeah these
guys die in one hit they're so easy wait that's right it randomized everything
there's a giant flower up there are you dead no close it's still alive it's got
a lot of hell what's going on up here what's going on up here damn it shoot
him oh god the vibes are a bit off but we have a message saying that they're
explaining something here Elden reforge changes the combat system so attacks
that you can jump over or duck under with the new duck are not I framed by
dodges there should have been a tutorial at the beginning of the game for this
but I don't think it worked because of the randomizer what how do you even how
would you even know what those attacks are I don't know basically any attack
you can duck or jump do not have iframes I don't even wonder which ones are the
did these vibes fucking stay these vibes smell they're rotting to buy a health
bar is I'm like a level two right now good all right all right where is it one
floor down you didn't have to come up here and told you there's a chest nice
yep yep yep yep yep yep vibes vibes vibes vibes vibes vibes I forgot what
that hold castle is over there check it out these a bonfire oh I bet you could
oh this must be a memory slot thing oh you do the thing we don't have it we
don't have the emote oh no emote bunch of losers showed up without the emote
okay so all right I got some cool spells I got some shoot whatever it is let me
see that helmet though what was it did they pick it up oh it's a talisman yeah
never mind there's another spell is it in that they're in the town somewhere
there should be another one I think a giant was just kind of a fit in the ass
I'm just maybe just run around and grab stuff I'll meet you back in the town you
got it where were you jumping to I don't know see the vibes that something's
going on tonight something with that you could I couldn't I frame on the jump I
can just normal Elden ring that's you can do that that's fine no vibe frames
it's true okay I actually have a health bar now did you eat pizza tonight well
that depends did you have pizza last night if the answer is yes is that pizza
leftovers that answer is yes then by all means he'd eat the leftovers make sure
you don't waste any of that you know it's still good if you've eaten to a
pizza yesterday there's no leftovers and you're ordering another pizza today I
would say probably I would say probably not I have a question about that you
could put any toppings you want on a pizza yeah like what a pizza is can
really vary can we kill this I ordered a pizza yesterday but the pizza you're
ordering today is vastly different the fuck that we need to we need to figure
out the dude we got to figure out the dodge thing because I can't dodge any
moves I have not been having that issue you just got hit five times we just
watched it I wasn't dodging though like okay give me he's gonna smack and see
see I uh you got hit he's gonna smack yep you got hit your vibes stink right
now your vibes are your vibes are awful right now all right we need to try
blocking all right doc can you are we gonna figure this out or what how the
dodge works in this game I guess how do we figure that out we have to find a
default enemy and just try to swing like dodge through stuff okay okay this crab
does like a really you'll do like the the slam this thing is awful to test
this on no huh become slam you dodged didn't dodge that you should have dodged
you okay hold on he sucks this guy sucks I'm asleep I've dude I've never seen
that status effect all right let's test it yeah we got to figure this out dude
there's no such thing as a dodge role in this game well does the other can we
do the other dodge where you just like the crouch weird dodge right no you you
should have that come on do this the thing you just did do it another move
all right you try it all right you die you duck under that but I couldn't duck
under it I I think I was just lucky cuz I did it if that's the timing all right
so wait a minute you mean to tell me if a five hours and 30 minutes we have not
been able to have i-frames when we thought we fixed a setting we just
haven't yeah yeah this is undodgeable I thought we fixed it oh I was everything
just felt so wrong everything is felt so off the whole time and it's because we
don't have a touch roll anymore we have to jump it all right we'll try that but
I know that there was something in this mod and it might I hate dude what that
might be it I remember that I think the classes have their own ways of dodging
oh did I get all the items I don't remember we don't have a class there's
one more spell here right isn't there one more spell I know I'm gonna look it
up you run around and vibe I think if you go up and then you go onto those
castle ramparts yeah you like jump on the castle then like bike invades you
and you can get something oh yeah I think it's because we have randomizer we
randomized the person in the tutorial right like we should have gotten
somebody that we also kind of have an issue with a d2 loot was overriding I'm
just all messed up oh yeah there is no bike that was the Giza guy that spell
isn't a dung beetle no it's not them it's not the mods fault it's we have
just a lot of shit turned on and I guess we didn't realize that we were
overriding stuff with other stuff that is really funny though that we've been
operating essentially without a dodge roll this whole time I mean there are a
lot of people saying that in the post that there's no iframes they're not
running any other mods and they don't know what the problem is but also we're
on an older version of the mod and I don't know that's it's alright it's fine
we're having fun oh no our modded sky room why the older version because the
older version stir correct me if I'm wrong but was compatible with d2 yeah
the d2 items have a compatibility patch and it only works with an older version
of reforged like these posts on the forum that are saying there's issues
with the iframes are from like very recently so I don't know I don't know if
we missed something in the the classes or but we kill things in two seconds
anyways it's like yeah it's not been that big of a problem surprisingly to
not have dodge roll I think we just have I expected it's been confusing a big
thing that the mod also does is it changes a lot of hitboxes on attacks so
the hitbox is exactly where the weapon is so it might feel like dodge rolls are
working because your character model is getting smaller and moving out of the
way of it hmm like what when a giant does like giant overhead slam on the
ground it's like a much smaller hitbox and your role is moving you so like
sometimes it's working which is why we probably haven't noticed it where's this
this one more spell somebody said it's outside there's like a pack of rats
not further away honestly if you want to play reforge just play reforge it
doesn't mix well with other mods stuff breaks you should do randomizer plus DSL
only if you want to play reforge do that on its own pretty balanced take on it I
think yeah we were really close to doing one or the other before the stream
started and then someone had some advice to get them to work a bit better and it
seemed to be working pretty well they were just like we'd already spent a lot
of time on it okay let me remember I gotta find this where is this pack you
know what this says with this pack of rats is uphill the hill towards the
chapel but turn left and then find the dung beetle you mean like over here like
up this way up the hill like up here what's the item another frenzy spell
apparently like up here off this way okay well it was a fun attempt I mean
can't get everything to work perfectly every time I really haven't even been
rolling I've just been wild striking okay
wheezing through attacks so where is this other spell up here looking for a
pack of it's not gonna be rats it'll be something else in that little forest I
go over here is this supposed to be them I guess there's a lot of shit here oh my
god will you leave me the fuck alone Miyazaki grows in power where is the
it's like the little dung beetle there was there was one like up the path just
fucking tell if I swear to God it's the worst enemy in the whole game it just
teleports okay we're looking for a dung beetle wait you mean that I wish I
could even look over here I wish I could walk over here and attack but I can't
you need a hand I'm the kind of looking but you're you're having some issues
it's hard people saying look look it's hard to look where there's a million
fucking things shooting and fighting and teleporting on you look at this guy
teleporting this instant transmission it's d-spawn good I don't even care
just dot just I frame dodge it just oh my god are you you're not joking I told
you you can't dodge it and you can't get away from them you can wild strike it
refuse to get off the horse yeah I don't want to get off the horse because there's
no I freight there's no dodging I think what it killed me in two seconds I don't
have wild strikes like he does I think the thing despawned what thing I was
looking for a dung beetle is apparently something over there yeah I think there
were dung beetles and then we startled with them yes the beetle ran away when
you started getting attacked why it's hard to run after it we'll never know
alright so what do you want to do do you want to do you want to keep playing this
or do you want to like fix this and try it again some other time or what do you
what do you what do you want to do I would rather play it correctly I don't
want to have no I don't want to have no dodge roll the whole time we play this
then in that case I mean at that point when we have to make new characters
completely oh shit to like start the game with the proper stuff we were
supposed to have and then I think at that point like we probably have to ditch
I guess we'd just be ditching randomizer and then Diablo 2 loot would stay so we
wouldn't have to restart we would just have to turn off randomizer well how
about this how about we let's restore the vibes let's go kill something fun and
then we will maybe we'll try to get another time okay we have to restore the
vibes though we have to kill have to restore the vibes they have to be
restored where is the most convenient to fight major boss that we have not done
I mean we could just we do but we did Godric could run through the castle of
Lucaria I just sprint through the castle is it easier to sprint oh carry a
manner if we just ran to where Laura it is yeah let's do that let's get the
vibes back we have to get them back I tried to click it didn't work reforged
adds secure style timed blocks it does stirs you know that no here let me read
you a couple of important things we're playing this we're playing this
completely wrong for almost six hours removed the instant input buffer for
roles on most player stagger animations that's why we're like I think it was
more that the rules don't have I frames where I'm looking at the defects are a
powerful time blocks they give more skill and power to blocking holy shit
all right we got to restore these vibes man I'm there hanging by a thread right
now I need him restored didn't read well I didn't hold up hold up hold up I got
it I'm telling you I've read a lot of it I didn't read very specifically dodge
roll the whole mechanic of all souls games we thought like we could do it
better the hubris blocking updated let me find the important bits we're gonna
get these vibes back man we're gonna kill something you recover from block
animations a lot quicker so you can act more quickly out of them deflect
blocking an enemy attack within the first few frames of a weapons block
animation will perform a deflect is this walking in are we just drinking though
the copium or are we just bad like is there actually no I frames or are we
just awful like I don't think we're bad because we I need to haven't we haven't
been I need to know we've been doing fine yeah this page doesn't say anything
about dodge rolls it just says there is a there is a timed block mechanic and
then everything else all right well we're gonna restore the vibes we're
gonna kill a boss we're gonna say nice and then maybe we'll figure it out we'll
come back and try it again with the vibes restored which I don't I mean I
don't know we'll see we'll see okay teleporting to where let's do oh we're
gonna do carry a manner yes we didn't delete the right files for randomizer
compatibility hey sometimes you try to do a bunch of mods and it goes great
sometimes you do a bunch of mods and you can no longer I frame hey that's just
the way it is let me try one thing real quick we want to give me a second I got
to get my like cheat sheet open of what the menus do again I don't know where
they went I sit here at bonfire are we gonna change like a setting yeah top one
event text huh so one was saying this earlier actually this might be what it
was normal mode is supposed to have normal dodge rolls but I crashed earlier
and when I came back there's a possibility that it reverted so we did
the top one down to down to you know no no no wait okay reset Reese I lost my
train of thought go way back to the beginning okay top one top one okay two
down yeah that's such a jump scare so what did that what did that do that set
it to normal Elden ring difficulty which does by default normal difficulty mode
is enabled this difficulty mode well I don't the other difficulties like the
higher and weirder difficulties start changing how many I frames you have on
dodges all right well let's go kill a boss and I might have accidentally turned
one of them on earlier and game crashing might have brought it back okay how you
doing I have one more thing I wanted to get to the bottom this before the stream
ends there do you want to go or do you want it all right exit let's go I'm
sorry sit in the theme I'm sitting down I'm getting the picture picture yeah I'm
getting the picture because we definitely accidentally goofed around
with these and killed ourselves a few times which many did we activate it
something we shouldn't know god damn it you good I'm sorry I'm transcribing top
one bottom one okay for every single one of these yeah open them and then choose
no choose no yeah it's turning all of the special weirdo options off if any of
them were accidentally on because some of these there's like a sure a mode and
it's like hey this decreases I frames by like half and it's hard mode okay so
like some of them might have been on oh shit okay okay let's go
you're all showing up like that for chat because of how many mods are enabled
yeah we might we got too much stuff going on with look we're gonna the vibes
are gonna be fine the vibes are like I can tell that you're about to like like
I'm gonna get a really bad stream rating after this by you I'm gonna DM I'm gonna
be the one DMing you on Twitter oh man stir was supposed to be the mod guy and
stirred didn't do his mod due diligence he's never gonna trust me ever again
like hey you want to play this game I got this cool mod with it no stir said
no no no sit back and relax German I got it I am gonna take care of all the mods
that's exactly what I did I relaxed I didn't you got these cool Diablo items
no it is cool wait I frames do we have them find out oh it's fine like a normal
normie enemy again are the music change crab that's like a Scarlet Rock crab
no all right and if my parents trying to unstuck the car in a road trip you're
you and now you're just spinning the tires you're spinning the tires this guy
this guy this normal ass good dude right here I wanted me for a cup of warm water
behind the tire all right normal ass enemy okay well your role hurt him
cuz whatever item you have that does that you guys swing so slow swing at me
that I didn't even hit the button he swings so this is not a no just kill
that one I'll try it on this one okay I mean they all swing so whatever there's
a torch guy over here let's get towards guy okay torch guy oh it's got with this
guy's aggro yep that's perfect I don't know if it worked but he's got more got
swings dude I get these fucking pants off these pants are ruining everything
I'm bumping him and we can't even tell okay try it again no didn't work nope
there are no iframes yeah let's kill him let's go get these fucking vibes restore
the vibes let's go oh nice like this giant take all your frustration out on
this guy's ankles he'll never play basketball again I don't know I've
legendary look like I did drop a legendary holy shit
vibes back legendary god slayers leather boots of the gravy all right let's go
kill whatever bosses in here vibes gotta get back and I don't we saying that
we're a lot but look we've been dealing with a lot today oh it's just too much
follow me hold on you don't get hit by this bear no oh no another bear don't
get hit by this lobster um dude how are you I was gonna say what are you
thinking you can't get through that I can't did you make it no
let's get these vibes back yeah we have to get all right we'll get we're getting
up there just one frenzy flame you know what I'm saying you know I'm saying one
frenzy flame will be all right well then we'll get the vibes back sit down
sit down everything's gonna be all right everybody relax everybody just calm
down everyone's everyone's happy everyone's freaking out but everything's
fine kill everything that's just a lot of damage fine wild strikes here oh shit
oh shit please don't kill me please don't kill me what's he doing no all
right lobster is dead nice he kills me he fucking kills me he kills me I thought
I don't know why I thought I was gonna kill I I thought I was gonna kill him
with that but he I thought it was whatever these vibes are off let me put
this shit on what does this do I don't want I don't want to be the reason for
the worst stream of the year you respond them all when you rest it yeah well look
who's gonna be able to kill them now hey we're stream of the year is not a
category this year by the way oh I'm removing it oh I forgot I can't dodge
you just try to run I I mean it just good luck good luck okay don't respawn
the enemies again I can't believe we've been playing for six hours without a
fucking iframe no wonder my like ass has been itchy like I've been like my ass
is like it's something's like pissing me off today something's pissing me off and
it was this oh my god I don't know why I like why that it makes me wonder why I
rolled there because I can't roll why is there a roll button hey mod why is there
a roll button it's not the boss ball it's not possible it's your fault it's my
fault all right I made it up I made it up I made it across I made it up now
contrary to popular belief I've actually been having kind of fun that's what I've
actually been having I'm having a good time I by the way I'm gonna sit down at
the bonfire okay do it I am ready to fight the boss I know we're coming up
here to fight this boss to fix the vibes uh-huh I feel like the vibe has got
worse the fire they can be redeemed if you come up here I'm telling you they
can be redeemed I'm here okay you've sat down a wild strike yep here get this
get this tree of Savior mm-hmm I mean that's pretty good I don't know is this
the right way yeah that's the right way okay I'm ready to restore them very good
very good very good very good watch out misbegotten oh whoa oh wait hey I can do
that too doing a bit of that in real life I'll see you oh yeah you don't know
what it is don't look up then I I'd never look at that God the vibes are
dead not quite how about this for vibes that hurt what the fuck oh yeah I can't
dodge it a pretty good challenge run like our string creds going up I don't
know how we dodge these attacks try that thing talk you should deflect I don't
think I have I don't think I even own a shield I'm good I'm gonna die walk with
your axe whoops that's gonna blow up the whole area no come on go we got to
bring the vibes back I've heard I've heard these vibes need to come back oh
I'm dead good luck what am I doing stir only you can restore them oh for the
no he did for hey can you play the giga Chad music just so I feel better no
don't play that oh is it last grace site we're doing it again we're doing it one
more time no we're not all right no dot I'll see you later if you hit me up this
week if you want to do something all right I'll find something to do and I
will ask you to install some no I frame dodge rolls all right I'm up here and
I'm ready to go in for one more dumb attempt dumb attempt what makes this
attempt dumb the fact that we're doing it in the first place again it is pretty
dumb cuz I'm I'm like at the bonfire and you've started oh I thought you were
okay I thought you were serious that you were done I'm gonna try the deflect
thing I didn't do it once but it still ate all my stamina but I didn't take any
health damage I mean it's no I'm glad I may challenge the boss area now your l2
is better than frenzy this thing doesn't do very much damage I mean I my whole
computer just crashed okay my Elden ring crashed but it's still up on my stream
that's fun how there's nothing on my screen Elden ring is crashed right now
and but I can look over at the OBS preview and see you fighting well you
say how do you dodge fire is what they say it's all right there was worth an
attempt worth it was look I had fun I had fun hey when you install a bunch of
random mods and you get in and sometimes sometimes it don't work well together
sometimes they get screwed up sometimes there's no tutorial because we broke it
by deleting the tutorial by having something happen in the randomizer and
then we just you know the vibes get a little fucked up start sometimes
sometimes sometimes I've got this don't even worry about it five and a half
hours went by and you didn't notice oh no we did I just think that we but I
think we both thought it was so used to being gaslit that like I brought it up
at least a dozen times and we were just like no wait maybe I just like stink at
this game yeah I just honestly I had fun it was fun it was worth doing I think
it was worth it yeah we got to the point where I think
once you get past early game you need to start being able to dodge things well
I'm sorry it's all good it was definitely worth doing hey seamless co-op mod
works pretty flawlessly didn't yeah vibes and toilet vibes but you know
whatever it's all right they all you look sometimes you get toilet vibes but
we're good everything's are you good how do you feel you feel I'm good yeah we're
good everything's fine I mean we had just played like it was definitely worth
how many hours of Elden ring though the week prior I just want more Elden ring
well we but like we already did so much you know so we did some new stuff and I
like I had fun because I wanted to play more Elden ring I don't think there's a
problem with that there's no problem with that but it's bedtime it's like
almost 2 a.m. here so it is either way thanks sir thanks for playing good to see you
yep I'm sure I'll see you again soon have a great night thank you for hanging
out take care see you soon dude yeah yeah yeah that was stir and that was Elden
ring and that was mods seamless co-op for Skyrim would be phenomenal maybe hey
we were just checking it out we did have okay we're coming off you're gonna
remember we're coming off like the ultimate high of last week playing and
becoming Elden Lord that's just like you know let's just put some more stuff on
and see what happens the vibes got a little fucked up that we know whatever
that's all good is your PC okay yeah I can change scenes it's just Elden ring
is just not on my monitor just like not here I can change scenes in OBS maybe
try something like randomizer and double bosses or something hmm you're making it
you're making it sound bad no no no no no no I had a good time all that matters
is me and start talking about like fucking bugs and stuff who cares thanks
for sticking around regardless the next time you see me will be on Wednesday and
Wednesday we are going to do hmm wouldn't you like to know we'll see I'll
figure out a game maybe maybe the hitman stuff kind of wanted to do it maybe the
hitman stuff if not that then we'll see that'll be a decision for Tuesday night
oh let me say this too I said that worst dream of the year is not going to be a
category this year I said that specifically because it's kind of to
prevent because I know I told you guys that a lot of the streams this year are
gonna be more chill slowed down a lot and it's kind of a way to prevent people
to come into like a chill stream and go oh this is boring worst dream of the
year 2023 right because I feel like that's definitely possible because if
if I'm gonna be doing more just chill kind of slower streams then I think it
kind of takes takes that out of the equation because otherwise it would be
like looking over here at the pit cross again got a lot of fucking nominations
for that category this year so I don't think I think I'd rather just not have
it be there otherwise it might be a large category yeah thanks for watching
Ellen ring with stir stir is awesome give it up for stir take care of
yourselves have a great night see you Wednesday Wednesday you know the time 6
p.m. Pacific you have an email you if you if anybody needs to wants to contact
me for any it's for business purposes I don't believe yeah it's the evolved one
the evolved email that's on my Twitter is but that's for business stuff though
if you like send a message of this it's probably not gonna get um about my get
filtered or something it's mostly for business stuff but I don't really do
anything else