All right, I'm almost back. I just gotta get my controller, and we can get started. Give me one more sec.
Somebody just said Gremlin's 2 sucks, Jeremo.
Excuse me? You can't say that here. You can't say that here. That's a banned sentence. All right, let's keep going.
So again, thank you Warner Brothers for sponsoring this stream. Season one is underway for multiverses.
Morty is in the game, which we haven't seen yet. Gizmo's in the game. I'm excited! Mod that guy. Why would I mod that guy?
Oh my god. Wait, wait, wait, hold on. You need a live reaction. You need a live reaction.
Come on. You gotta get a live reaction to this. I've been waiting like a hundred years for this.
It's Gizmo from Gremlins and Gremlins 2! No, this is really cool. That's not supposed to be that big.
So how does he play? Is he good? You guys have had access to this for like the last few hours. Is Gizmo good?
All right, hold on. We gotta go to the lab. Yeah, this is part of season one. Yeah, this is Morty.
I haven't even unlocked Morty. So I played this on Xbox. So I have two accounts.
Uh, is the timer going in the chat? Can you guys tell me? You gotta do the voice?
I'm not doing the voice. Should I even unlock Morty? I mean, I kind of, I should, right?
Okay, let's unlock. Let's get everybody unlocked and I want to take these people into the lab. There's cross progression.
I'm so glad you brought that up because you're absolutely right. There's cross progression across the whole platform.
So PC, Xbox, doesn't matter where you are. It's free. Do I even have the battle pass? What do I see there?
Oh, hey, I think I do, don't I? What's this? ToonSquad96 unlock premium. Do I, I don't have the battle pass?
All right, I probably, I could probably just get it. Let's see what you get. So this is the premium battle pass.
You know what my favorite thing about this game is?
This stuff. The ring out stuff. When you knock somebody out and you get to see like the cool animation,
I can't wait till there's a thousand of these. What do you get them for the very, at the very end?
Well, that's app, that's absolutely worth it. Okay. Well, I have to be grinding for that one.
I'm gonna spend some time playing. All right, let's go to the lab. I'm so happy to do this. No, get Taz out of here.
I don't want to play with Taz. Gizmo.
Oh, okay. So he's not tiny. He's not tiny. I got an arrow. Okay. What's, what's, what's the standard combo?
That's seems pretty amazing. Is it just those three? Can I charge any of it? No.
They changed the hitbox apparently in this update.
You can travel really far. All right. So what about the standard? Pretty cool.
Just like from the goddamn movie.
I don't care. I'll spend all day playing to get better.
This is, this is a, this is definitely a moment where I'm going to play as hard as I can.
All right. So let me hold on.
So that's okay. That's that's the air too and it arcs.
Oh, yeah, that's fucking awesome. All right. So that's on cooldown now.
Oh my god, it's just like the movie.
All right, so what about down?
What?
Popcorn?
See, yeah, this is my bat chest moment guys. I'm sorry. It really is.
This is my, this is my bat chest moment. I get to have this. Um, what is it? What do they do? They linger?
That seems amazing.
All right, you can do popcorn.
Okay, cool. So what about the uh, what about specials?
He sings and dances. Okay, that's perfect. What does that do?
I think because he's a support, right?
Let's do all that stuff. That's crazy.
He doesn't have a smash move.
It doesn't look like a power. I guess that could be it, but it's not I don't think it has knockout power.
Find out. All right. So that's singing dance. We can look it up. You go into the box.
Ooh.
All right.
So that turns into that.
Is it defense?
Arrow popcorn.
Okay. Okay. All right. All right. Hold on.
Yeah.
Oh, I feel it.
So you really want to get that out there and just like
Don't die in the lab. That'll be embarrassing.
Okay, that's actually pretty cool.
Now, what about uh,
Up special is sort of just a little jump.
Which that seems kind of dangerous because it's not very far. All right.
Music is really loud.
All right. I'll turn it on. You can drive the little car.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Yeah, you can't swear. What?
No, i'm fine.
Jeremy, you are clamp.
Uh, there is a deep fake
With me as mr. Clamp if you've never seen it before it's actually pretty funny. That's better. Okay
So you really oh the umbrella. What is that?
Okay, you can float around. All right. So down special was that I gotta let's do some reading
Oh, yeah
So I wonder what the what the singing does. All right, let's do some reading. Where is it?
He you can read what can you move? Let's here we go. All right
Some of gizmos attacks apply a music buff affected enemies are silenced if they reach the max stack count
Stopping them from using cooldown abilities effect abilities will create a musical note
Rhythm allows the bard to play magical tunes
When they evade hitting overlapping enemies, okay popcorn it can be ignited
We know that gizmo charges before slamming a keyboard dealing armor break. All right
What's the what does it get in the box one?
This one here gizmo hops on a toy chest which blocks projectiles hold input to stay in the chest
While attached to an ally he will hold out an umbrella for a similar effect on his ally. All right
All right, let's fucking go. I'm ready. Let's give it a try who wants to queue up and get your ass kicked
Here comes the heat
Oh, right. That was lebron. You're a bozo. You should play as morty
I don't I don't know really how to play as morty
This is gizmo only for a little while just for a little while when it's stripe
Yeah, apparently stripes gonna be in the game too. All right, I don't have the skin. Oh, well, that's fine
You have to do the gizmo voice while you play. Okay, hold on. There's a way to do it
It's still kind of like this, right?
I'll get in here. I don't have any perks
All right, let's see if I can do this one v one with gizmos probably bad idea
But whatever i'm gonna get beat up for a little while show them what we got. That's that's stitch
Don't they that they have
That's auto gizmo is supposed to be support. He seems like really actually pretty fun to play
As a solo character too. All right, let's go. I've been waiting 20. Oh, and I gotta tweet. I have to tweet this
I'll tweet it after i'll tweet it
Oh, don't touch those musical notes
You can shoot it up that combo get there. I get the combo get the combo going
just
Run over the car
Whoa, that was a good combo
I gotta charge that more often
Oh
one for blue
That stomp is awesome, too. This one here
Has a lot of priority. It feels like
All right. That's good. Good warm-up. That's good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. I told you we got where's my phone
I gotta tweet. I forgot to tweet
He's fun to play
play again
Yes
Oh this is I forgot. This is what the the tweet I was gonna do was. Oh, that's fine. Yeah, that's fine
Is that a good one? I said I said I was gonna be crying
I can't oh, no, I did that joke. It's fine
All right. I gotta get used to the move set
Wait, no, I just tweeted. Hold on. I mean look at him
Oh
He's so it's he's perfect. He's he's actually perfect. It's one of my actually favorite movies ever
It's just i'm so happy to see him in the game
For the longest time I never thought they were ever doing anything with gremlins ever again
They're making a third movie. I don't know what they're doing. They're doing aren't they doing like an animated thing?
Uh-oh versus a bugs. It's my old best friend
I better be uh, be careful. Why are you so weird? I don't know blame this movie. I wish that was a joke
All right, so it's down the down special is the really only knockout potential that he has
No, no, no, no, no. No. Oh, he doesn't know he doesn't know he doesn't know
I screwed that up. Sorry. Oh I can drive that car
What are you doing? Give me that sandwich
I just looked over and saw that it's not you're fucking with me now
So how did the hitboxes change?
Excuse me
You don't like the camera. Why not? I told you we got this
What's my favorite type of pizza?
standard pepperoni thin crust
And it's gotta be crunchy it's gonna be crispy on the bottom
I wanted to be crispy and crunchy on the bottom and it better be where i'm gonna be
What's happening?
Wait, what's going on? So look there the hitbox is different. So it's now tied to their actual animations
Before it was kind of a little square or oval around them. The hitboxes I think have shrunk a little
Interesting. All right. Is that a better is that a good thing or a bad thing? It seems I can't really notice
Feels pretty good so far
I think it's pretty good
I had a dream that you went to my university graduation
And drank my grandmother's ashes in a milkshake before I was meant to go on stage. It was awkward
Stop fucking eating after midnight. You know what happens? Come on. Show them what we got
What what I was in the stands I was in the audience. Where did I get it? Why would I have that?
Wrong way. I'm used to the way that bugs plays. I gotta get used to uh gizmo. I love it though. He's great
Hmm, that's okay. You got to feel that up way earlier. It's a great move though
All right, come on one for blue does the singing hurt anybody I feel like it doesn't oops
We're good. We're good. We're good
I told you we got this
Why is the gremlin so big? Well
How can we play like you're orchestrating a band because I move around a lot
You look like you you'd like to suck lemons
Wait, who are you? Why what are you doing here? Why are you being so mean to me?
Here comes the heat. Let me go. Let me go read something. Hold on. Should I try morty?
Oh a few more games with gizmo if I play with morty, um
Should I do the voice?
All right. I want to read this because i'm trying to find an opportunity at least in solo to do that. Oh
Can't read it here comes the heat
This camera angle if you were here in the beginning of the stream
Uh, oh, all right, definitely want that and that's good just to have
I'll do some teams to it because I think you can shoot the arrow at a teammate
Show them what we got
Oh, I keep forgetting about the car
Get out of there
Get out of the car. Stop it
stop
Where's my car?
Yeah
Get away from me. You want where you want to go for it?
No, no, no. Hey, hey, hey. Hey, wait, wait, wait, get your car. Oh, you want to go for it?
Hey, I want whatever
No, don't shoot me don't
One for blue
Get out of that car
I'm off to read a 3 000 word essay, but how much I don't like you
Don't
Do you see how happy i've been with this gizmo is in the game, man
Here comes the heat you're doing cvd water. Oh my goodness. I forgot. This was there the whole round
That's so stupid cvd water in your eyes
The point is to get gizmo leveled up as fast as possible to get his ultimate perk
Show him what we got
Wait, that looks wrong
Yeah, the reason why I changed the angle of the camera is because
It used to shake because the monitor that it was sitting on would always move whenever I moved it was really annoying
It looks fucked up
Well, i'll fix it next time
What the hell just happened? That was weird
Good combo good combo
Water in my eyes one for blue. I need my arrows
That's a good. That's a good finisher. That's a good finisher. We got this
That butt slam is amazing if you can get it continue
That was a good game though
Do a different face cam. Oh, I can do this right fine. I'll do the funny thing for everybody
It really does look like someone's coming out of that door piano wire
They're gonna come out of that door with piano wire and i'm gonna get hit manned on stream. That's what that is
Yeah, I wonder what's gonna happen in that door
It's a full monster costume persons coming out of there. Here comes the heat
Something looks so strange about that too. It looks wrong
Monsters ink door. Oh morty. What does morty do? That's a lie. I know what morty does make it bigger
Show them what we got what a png of an iphone around the camera
Why all right first, let me just uh, let me do some are we are we playing or what are you what are you up to?
Wait, what are you what are you up to? All right, we're playing. All right, let's go
All right, let's get a vacuum cleaner he how did you dodge the car? All right, I gotta be quiet
I gotta be shut up
I wasn't in the game. I was too busy thinking about the fucking face cam
I'm sloppy
What is that?
200 almost what the hell?
40 I mean, come on morty
Oh
Oh, what a fucking match oh what a match oh that was close
Oh, I thought I had it on those down. Uh, damn it on the left side
Oh, that's close
Uh, yeah, sure. Okay
All right, i'm back here comes the heat
Morty's got a lot of projectiles, huh?
Okay, that's better. That was so close to I do you see on the left side?
I did the down boom boom. He recovered down boom boom recovered again. I just couldn't follow up. That's a good match though. It's like
His most fun
Who's my favorite gremlin?
Uh, that would be I think the name of the gremlin is actually daffy
Daffy was my favorite gremlin morty is a mage more of a mage than a bruiser
um
No, not daffy duck. All right. Hold on. I gotta be quiet. I gotta be gamer uh gamer time
wrong way
Oh
That's all right. Sorry ready three two one
What the fuck I teleported
No, why do I keep facing the wrong way new controller?
Sounds like a chicken. I thought that was a chicken sound
Went right over his head
Come on that fucking launch power
Close good one. Good one. Good fight. Good fight. Good fight. That was a close one
Continue. I mean we kind of have to do it. There's a best out of three here
We gotta do it again. Hold on. Wait, we have to follow up
No, no, no, like you were shaking my grandmother's ashes in a protein shake
When the dean called out my name and was meant to shake my hand you ran past me and drank the frothy milkshake
What's wrong with you? Wait, did I miss the opportunity? Oh shit. That's all right. Let's stick with the tie
I thought I hit rematch didn't I I guess I didn't here comes the heat
All right. Let's do some
Let's do some team stuff. I want to check the uh, the gizmo team stuff
teams and
free-for-all maybe here comes the heat
Because i'm curious. I think you can shoot the arrow at your teammate. Oh, they didn't rematch. Oh, it's all right
Go to the end of the options and increase the dead zone on your controller
Yeah, how do I do that? Oh wait horizontal dead zone. What what so?
Yeah, I keep not wanting to be facing that direction
What should I put this at?
Higher or lower 40 percent. What vertical should these both be the same?
You should lower it if you feel like you're not getting an input red
It's mainly when I hit left
So I try to turn and then by the time I turn left and want to let go to do the neutral, uh arrow move
He's still facing right
Do you know if we're gonna get the sexy gremlin as a skin? I have no idea
So it should be higher or lower then make it smaller then i'll try 20
See if 20 does it
Use the second stick for reverse moves. Um, not with gizmo because gizmo is standard
Um, just standard attack is the bow so I can't use right stick to aim it
It has to be standard attack two gizmos. This is gonna be interesting. All right, let's go. Let's do it
Show them what we got. How come you're not eating any carrots because i'm not playing as bugs
Hey bugs is old news to me right now second daffy gets put into the game. You know it
All right. Let's see if we can do this with two gizmos
Just get in the car
I think they nerfed jake a lot too, by the way
From what I saw on the patch notes. He got pretty much every move got nerfed
We can drive each other's cars. I think too
Oh
Oh, I thought you're gonna jump oh I could get a double here so cleanly if I could just do it
That does not have priority anymore. Does it that was was that part of the nerve?
Shit, all right, we gotta get this jake out of here
Oh shit
We gotta get rid of this jake
That was huge
Nah, that dead zone. I gotta change it
Stop that's it
Big point for red
Yeah, we just can't launch anybody shake it off. We only getting stuck. We just could not get that uh,
Darn it out of here
play again
Let's go
Your dead zone dead zone should be higher 40 to 60
Yeah, I always have the problem where i'm trying to turn the other way and then do the standard
Attack move and I just am not turning try it. Uh, let me try that is it like 60
That's cool that you can actually do this in the game though
So it needs to be like higher you're saying like that if you're not turning lower the dead zone
Do 60 30 try 60 30
Try it
Oh my god. I want it. Let's get to work
Then you wipe decrease it. Okay
Lebron is bugged really
I want it. Show them what we got. Are you a fan of american edm?
I don't really listen to that much music. So
I mean, I like a lot of stuff, but I don't really listen to a lot
Hey, my sister just ate the last swiss roll. Wait, wait, you you have the stream muted. You can't even hear me
Oh, that was lagging
Getting my ass kicked here
What? Holy shit, I went flying
People weird teleporting around oh my god get down there
You know, my biggest problem with teams is I just it's hard. I don't know who to pay attention
I don't know who paid to pay. You know what i'm saying porky fucking pig will be in the game at some point
This is unacceptable
Big point for red
My ball
Holy shit. Oh shit. Shake it up. We're only getting started
He's on mcdonald's wi-fi. No, mom
Yeah, I did. I want to do more one v ones. Here comes the heat
That's where that's where I i've shined here comes the heat. We demand gizmo. I'll do okay. Let's let's go back to gizmo
The team-based stuff is so is awesome in this game. It's just I I need to know what when to do what that's my problem
Everybody has these awesome
Kind of co-op moves just trying to be like oh do I should do it now?
Comes with game knowledge
I've seen some insane duo stuff though
Skill issue. Oh, yeah, that is what I am admitting to you right now. I look like I made it a nail polish remover. Yeah
Oh
And that dead zone by the way help. Oh a million percent. That's so much better
Thank you advice andy
Okay
All right, i'm getting fucking dunked on in this second around here let's go
Shake it up. We're only getting started
We both went like this
And then I just freaked out and died
Okay
By the way, this stream is sponsored by wonder brothers. Thank you wonder brothers season one of multiverses is here comes the heat underway
gizmo morty
They've both been added cross together over here cross progression, by the way, you see playstation
Can you guess the other one? Oh, no, I hate fighting jakes
Show them what we got. I actually think they're actually gonna add ranked at some point here, too. I would have frame andy. Oh
oh
Steven
Tell me that careful
Who went down, I don't know what the fuck happened what
I traded places with him
That was so good
Oh now i'm gonna get fucking diarrhea on
One for blue
Give me the car
Let's go
Oh, come on shake it up. We're only getting started
I completely forgot that the arrows had cooled down and then I freaked out and then I just stopped playing
See dude, just gotta keep punching till there's no one left to punch. Here comes the heat
That was important this has all been warm up until now this has all been warm up until right now
Can you please read a book on stream? Which one?
You have a favorite book show them what we got
Somebody said will they take the sponsorship away if you keep losing no, that's not how it works
Hey, I am way above 500 right now
I've only lost like three times. I'm not losing this one
You dodged that one that didn't hit all right. All right. All right
I have no idea what happened there. I think lagged out maybe
Wait, you're cheating I didn't do anything. Okay, um the season pass
I should feel like I should have it. I feel like I should just get it
Can you do a sleep stream now? Here comes the heat. Is there any hold on?
Ismo's air down special can bounce off his popcorn and his toy car
To detonate them instantly. Wait, what? So that's the butt drop
So I can butt drop my car and blow them up. That's pretty cool
Okay
So you can be attached to someone
I haven't been using the music at all. I don't even know what it does
I've just been kind of just trying to get people. I want that cool. What about um, is there any gremlins?
Uh, uh, where is it? Yeah, are there any new gremlins ring outs or anything cannonball? Cool
Bossamer cool green lantern. Is there any gremlin stuff? No. All right. No gremlin ring outs
What about banners? I think the only one is the gizmo one, right? Please read that popcorn book
I want the gizmo one. All right, what about announcer? Is there a gizmo announcer?
Do I have enough to buy this?
Oh, I can get it. All right. I got the skin. Nice
I'll do another team fight and we're gonna do team fight. Who got the most changes?
It looks like bugs got changed a lot too. This patch is as of what today yesterday, dude. This guy brought combat gear
Yeah, trying i'm trying a little too hard here. You should read moby dick. I'm studying it
Would you guys actually watch a moby dick stream? I feel like people wouldn't isn't it long though
I don't really want to read that
Oh didn't hit
That's not gizmo talking. That was weird
Oh
Whoops wrong way
Oh, you got me with it. Nice shot
Oh his car had better priority than my car
What do you mean for halloween gizmo
That's a good bench
I I almost got caught like three or four times that could have gone either way
I keep getting cut off. Oh, it's because i'm an idiot you guys want to see anybody
Didn't superman get a bunch of changes too?
Side profile andy. All right. I'm gonna move you from there to here. I gotta find a way to get you over there though
I just did
You're not shaking anymore, which is so much better the announcer. I got a different announcer. It has
Oh
Brat
We're just playing bumper cars at this point. Why is the car still here?
Oh charged good fight good fight
Gizmo is so fun
Not too complicated either. Just really really clean move set. I love it. Oh, I'm most of that. Okay. I want to get to that car
Come on
Character they added austin powers with the would you play with him for a whole stream? Yeah
I'm gonna buy a new announcer. I'll get a new announcer. I don't think I have enough currency left though
You're gonna play 20 minutes till dawn
I actually really do want to return to that that game was a blast. All right, let's go
I've been on a pretty good streak here
Holy shit, we couldn't even hit each other
That was that was kind of wild actually
This is gonna be interesting. Okay
Whoa
That's gonna be close no our cars
That was close good game damn, let's go again, okay, is the announcer the announcer's tabs
Pick character. Yeah, I wonder how many uh, how many
People are not believing. What's the record this dream? It's got to be
It's got to be at least
70 win streak or win rate, right? Although I might hit gamer fatigue at some point here soon. I'm not sure
It could happen at any moment. I just don't know when I can check. Oh, okay. I'll do it after this
start time
New gamer award. All right, let's go bro
Oh nice
Okay. All right
Shit
Oh got tripped up on the left side that was close that was close
That was really really. Oh, that's unfortunate
I was trying to I I don't know if when he looked over and he saw the car
Because I was trying to drop the car on him
Because when he was recovering the car was gonna hit him right in the head and just take him out
Maybe he tried to avoid the car and I don't know
What's up with the land tournament camera angle?
No, that's not accurate it would be right in front of me and down
No, it would be up here and facing down right in front of the monitor in the center. This is podcaster angle. Yeah
The mic in frame is a choice. No, it's not I got nowhere else to put it
If I put it down, you won't be able to hear me. Everyone will call me audio andy. All right, let me read this
So I can down special on the popcorn and the cars to blow them up. That's pretty like pretty cool
Mike shouldn't be that far from your mouth. Wait, what?
Here's the thing if it's here
Then I I can't see the screen this sucks
All right, i'll try one match like this
And you can't see my face
No, I can't see the screen. What the hell is that?
What's that? That was crazy. I don't know what he's doing
What is he doing? I I can do that. Can I do that move?
Oh, we both did it
All right, let's go let's go come on
All right. Oh, I got saved
Sorry. All right. Let's make it happen. Let's make it happen. Geez. I almost came back
Winner winner winner
nice fight
You're playing like a fighter pilot
I move man. I gotta I have to move around. I think this chair is electricity is surging through this chair
Come on pick character
All right, how about hmm should I change character and just get absolutely decimated like that's a bad idea
I feel like I got the rhythm with gizmo right now
It'll do gizmo for another one mattress. Oh, and then i'll play some morty. I gotta see what the hell he does
interesting
Iron giant versus gizmo
I feel like i'm gonna get pretty destroyed here
start time
Your title would be lying. I don't know if it'd be lying
I
Alright, let's see what I can do. Are we in is this the scooby-doo level? Oh, this is gonna be bad. I lose
I don't think it's possible. I can win this
Although he's kind of huge though
Oh jesus
What the heck?
Oh my god, I can't bounce him
Oh
Oh, i'm in trouble
I knew this was gonna be a major problem
What the fuck to die?
I'm too small to get rid of them
Okay
I gotta go for I gotta go for something weird here. All right, i'm gonna go with something weird see if I can do it
He's too big
All right, if you stick with iron giant then i'm gonna have to go superman
Come on
I don't have superman
What didn't I have didn't I unlock superman? He's level seven. Oh, he was free rotation
All right, I gotta remember how to play with superman
Change the announcer
I don't have any other announcers
I have lebron taz and then the default right? I don't think I have anybody else
Change it back to lebron
All right, let's make this happen
I threw him up
Let's go i'm done with this
Steel
Are you kidding me what what the fuck
You just can't watch him so he just says you suck
I'm, no i'm not naked your mic cuts. It's because I scream too much and my audio sucks. I keep forgetting to do the um announcer
professional andy about professional andy I
We're gonna we're gonna see just how good and it does feel weird looking all though
You have no idea how far away you are. It's strange. All right, let's go. Let's go. What the hell I pressed buttons and it didn't happen
Hey, dude, did you see that stun?
Oh nice
Ooh
You look like you eat pizza with a fork who cares eat food the way you like to eat food
Why do you have to judge people for the way they eat their pizza?
Eat it cross-side first
Like here, all right, that was I think that's a good gizmo one to go out on let's uh, let's try morty i'll try morty
Oh now sir. Oh my god. I keep forgetting. I'm sorry. I have no idea what morty does. So let's just kind of get beat here
This is kind of free points
I'm very honest
Do the voice just wait till I fall off the screen accidentally. You'll hear it
These moves do but they're cool. It's it really does sound like a chicken or a turkey
Oh look at me
I like that line, too
He's kind of cracked if i'm honest this he's kind of ridiculous what the heck
All right, i'm not gonna get lost come on
Oh, I didn't know what the moves were
He's kind of cracked. I just don't know what he does
Oh jeez was this match more than you bargained for rematch, okay
You just do another you laugh you lose
We can set it up
Uh, let's go back to the trident true
See if I still got it
I could have had that if I uh, if I tried to really pull that together. I probably could have had it start time
They nerfed bugs. They well they did
He was really good though bugs was amazing
So makes sense
Really almost had it. Oh, yeah. All right
Check this out
Where is it? Where is it?
There it is
Damn, damn
Jesus
So
I'm gonna try to finish that up. I was too scared
Gamer fatigue sets in
Oh, I could feel the fatigue fit, uh, just fitting onto me I didn't land
I think I only needed one of the bat move. They really did nerf that, huh?
That was a good match though
So the bat move has less, uh hit frames right stop drinking ethanol
I don't I don't do that
Spreading rumors. All right. I will change the announcer. I promise
Okay, i've got default announcer lebron has
I don't have enough coins a character choose a character who are you gonna send in who you're gonna play as
You must select your combatant
Oh, man, who are you gonna choose choose your fighter
Take your fighter pal. What are you gonna put in the ring?
Zoinks a lot of fighters to choose from man. That's definitely the best one
Choose your character
All right time to select your character. I was not ready for the laugh at the end of that
A lot of fighters to choose from man. Ah, it's jaggy. I don't have any coins
Do I get do I get whoa, hold on a second 250 gold. Hold on a second. Excuse me
All right, 70 win rate. That's pretty good
I'll take 70 percent. I have a premium token. Oh dude. I have one. I have one
Oh shit. All right. That means I get all the stuff. Oh I get okay. So I got a rain dog taunt
I got a taz skin. I already had tokens. Okay, cool. Happy fin hover taunt for superman. All right, let's do some teams
I'm just gonna mess around with teams. We'll close it out with teams. Yeah, so they're gonna be adding um
Black adam and stripe will be coming at some point soon during I think this season
I'm curious with how stripe stripe stripe is gonna be a bruiser. I'd imagine. All right, let's do some teams
Do I stick with gizmo or do I play with somebody else I feel like well, let's try the new skin. I mean, come on
Is taz any good anymore? I haven't really played with taz at all. You don't it's still taz
Well, yeah, because I don't have any currency. I don't have any uh in-game money
That's not gizmo. It's close enough. This is chad gizmo
Have any of you guys actually been really putting time into the game?
Who do you think is the best character in the game right now? Jake?
Is it gizmo gizmo feels really good. Oh, I caught them both
In aria. Oh, yeah, wait, you can do his sandwich more than a few times, right?
Oh
Oh got it not good enough though, where am I what's my character I died
What was that voice by the way?
That was like a uh, please put this in the youtube video voice
I just I just pulled this back
Oh, we did it rain dog. Nice job. I don't know. I kind of don't know what happened but whatever
He's not in the reddit room anymore, oh, that's right it looks different doesn't it
Let's all fight fair and this should be fun
How's auto auto's doing great. He's he's a little he's a little chunky, but we're working on it
Let's do that. We'll do a few more. We should see him again. All right on the next stream. I'll show auto
Um, i'll let you see the dog. He's doing good. He's happy. I think he's just hanging out
He's sleeping in the other room start. I ran out of water
I was too busy putting it in my eyes. Remember to blink when you're in those, uh, deep gaming hours guys
It's got stuck on the lip
Jesus behind me
That's how you get it done. Excuse me
What happened doesn't it just does harley quit have a tv show by a new tv show what doesn't jump off
Is it any good?
It's not new and it's three seasons old. Oh, is it any good though? It's okay
I love chat the only place where I can look over here and see yeah, it's pretty decent and then right underneath that
It's fucking awful, dude
I can't I feel like i'm doing i'm neglecting lebron. I really like lebron. Let's get it
Asking thousands of people their opinion on something. Yeah, it's just funny though. Just looking over and seeing it in real time
Batman's fun
I feel like I need to go through and play all the characters again
Just in the lab because I really did just pick bugs bunny because I love the looney tunes. What the hell is this?
start time
It's not so fun. No, I don't I don't think elmo is owned by one of brothers. Sorry guys
I don't know if that's possible. I'm not sure big bird can be in this game
Whoa
What's happening?
Oh my god, that movie's crazy
Heads up. No, don't throw the basket. Oh
Oh that hurt
All right, we got it
All right, we're going gizmo again, okay, all right one more one more one more one more one more gizmo one more
Come on pick character
They want to do gizmo then well, I can do that
Like that. Yeah, give me money
The mic ruined it
This mic stinks. This mic stinks. I'm done with it. It eats every weird noise
It eats every funny noise you make. I don't know why okay. Can if I don't know can you know
Did that come through or did that get uh blocked out? So wait, it's only high noises. That's weird
There must be some pitch that this mic does not like. All right, this is it last one. Let's go
Let's do it. Let's make it happen
Oh
It didn't get hit by that. That's kind of weird
All right, we gotta can we launch somebody out of here, please?
What are we doing?
All right. I'm just like pressing buttons. I gotta like actually play the game
What the hell did I what happened? I what I pressed jump. Why didn't I now jump?
All right, dude, you're too
Huh?
Get out of here
Oh my
goodness
And you let's pull it together here
Isn't that priority?
What what happened? Why couldn't I move what?
Excuse me
What I just sink to the ground
What you heard me smashing buttons? What the fuck just happened?
Continue
I just I'm spread like this. I'm just sunk to the ground. What did I lose connection?
Come on pick character
That one doesn't count that one doesn't count
I literally just turned into a pencil and went straight down and I was pressing buttons
It counted for us sag. I'm sorry. I'll do better david jake though
That's my kryptonite a lot of my points are on the line
A lot of you are voting for is that for me or against me? Because that's a lot. That's a big difference
Oh, okay
So you do believe let me try to reward you. Ah
Oh, it's all right, sorry
Oh, that was a good block from jake
What's going on? I guess I freak out
Let's go. Okay. All right. We're ahead
We won you guys got your points
Look at that damage. All right. Um
One more and then i'm out of here and then I will be back and we'll do some more art
Maybe some more 20 minutes till dawn i'll be back on sunday sunday the 11th here
Either something maybe saturday. We'll see maybe sorcery
Would be uh any of those things?
I want to do one more 1v1. Uh last 1v1
And I want to play a character that I want because i'm about to keep doing i'm gonna do taz 1v1. I'm very curious
Also, yeah, thanks one brothers again for sponsoring the stream I genuinely love playing this game so
It's just that's really awesome that I can just get sponsored to do it game's really fun if you haven't checked it out
Season one is underway right now. I think that we're gonna see some more characters and probably ranked and some other stuff
Don't do sorcery on sunday. We'll figure it out. I don't know if I would bet on this one
It's a 1v1 with a character. I haven't been playing
Yeah, I I love taking sponsors like this because I I actually like this game
I really really do
So it's perfect
All right, let's see if I can do it
What the fuck is going on?
What the hell is happening?
So confused
I get a turkey it's all over. I don't know. Did you vote for me? Because I did not think I was gonna win that
All right, that's it
One of others. Thanks a lot for the sponsor. Seriously game's awesome
Season one is underway gizmos in the game
Morty's in the game
And we'll see you again
This one doesn't count. It's just an extra bonus one. I mean I have to do the rematch. I can't just say no
That's not how it works. If somebody says rematch you say all right, let's go for it unless there's internet problems. Come on unwritten rule
Please juggle germa on stream and teken
Okay, come get me in multiverses, man
Hi
All right. That's it. I'll see you guys later. That was fun
Multi versus thanks again. Warner brothers game is good
It's always a pleasure. Thanks a lot everybody. We'll see you soon. See you on sunday
There's a link in the description if you want to check it out if you want to go use that link
You don't you know if you can if you want to i'm gonna just put this in my mouth such chat was awesome, too
I've been having a lot of fun playing games lately. Have you noticed that the last uh,
Five or six games like it's time for gamer streams. I've been having a lot of fun
Kind of feel like i'm getting back into it
Yeah, i'll see you guys on sunday. Thanks a lot. Take care of yourselves
Have a great night
And we'll see you soon
Binding of isaac. Um, i'd probably rather play cult of the lamb before binding of isaac again
If i'm completely honest you go do your homework if you haven't done it. Come on somebody said i'm not doing my homework
I've been watching make sure you you know
Do as do as much as you can do as much as you can right dude his teacher is watching right now
You can't make me dad eight. I thought this was an 18 plus stream. Oh, yeah, never mind. Well that
College, excuse me. Oh, i'm so sorry. I just moved this thing and I bumped you
Yeah, have an awesome night guys. See you soon. See you sunday. Uh, probably around
Four o'clock pacific. It's a good place to start. I think good night everybody. Should you call your mother? See you soon?